It's what? It's a what? It's been like six minutes. It's only been six minutes.
Eight minutes. No, I pressed it at six. Hey, don't worry. We're gonna we're gonna hang out
for like 10 minutes anyways while I drink my iced coffee. That's how this works.
It's good. I'm out of here too. I don't want I'm gonna bump into this shit in the middle of the
stream. It's gonna be bad. I already smashed my finger today. I don't I don't even know how.
I mean, I do know how, but it's weird. I don't know why. It's weird. I'll explain.
Another game reward? No, no. I was touching I was hold on. Give me one sec. So I was
getting making a coffee and I was just kind of talking to myself like I usually do
and I was picking up random items on the counter and I was going what's this what's this what's
this violence what is it is this violence is this violence and I was doing the thing that
um that he does in that interview uh Ed Harris he's he if he watches an Ed Harris interview
where he like is looking at stuff in an interview like a panel for like Comic-Con
and they ask him hey what do you think about like the the history of violence and he goes
what is it what is it what's violence and he like grabs a coffee cup on the counter like smashes
it and like throws it behind him I was just doing that without a coffee cup and I smashed my hand
on the fucking counter I was I got like too into the character and I like hit my finger and it
started bleeding I put a band-aid on it's a little bit tiny bit of blood it's a game reward
it's an excuse oh that's real you want to know what the worst the best and worst reality show
ever would be if they was just if you just like filmed the living room in my house I just have
to be I'll be walking around talking to stuff people would think I was possessed talk about
Halloween just like grandma no I have I have an actor scar okay no one is here for you we're
here for the game are you a huge fan of the exorcist deluxe edition I don't know you were
such a big fan and I don't know what deluxe edition means I have no idea what any of this means
by the way my mic probably sounds crazy because the compressor is way up I'm gonna be standing
way back here look let's put it on whatever yep oh I saw a comment somebody said that my style
looked like I had been a rang a tang stomach and I was like come on Star Wars shirt is half my
wardrobe man credit boys how's the hair hmm could be better it's a little fucked up over here I need
a haircut to be honest all right this is what we're gonna hang out for a minute I'm gonna just jump
right into this I've got an iced coffee to drink I saw or stopped streaming I saw yesterday and
everybody hated it I by the way I need to apologize to everybody in the chat right now
I was laughing my ass off about this earlier and before I went to sleep if you didn't watch the
stream last night uh I had some work done on my body I had some body work like massage and like
and it made me really tight I have a whole medical problem you'll you can figure it out just go look
at the reddit uh so I took a little bit of extra uh THC yesterday because I've been taking it for
pain and I couldn't read an analog clock on stream last night I couldn't I couldn't do it I thought
826 was 855 it's like this I had to have been doing that for a joke I just need to apologize
because a human that's over the age of 30 should be able to read a clock which is I couldn't do it
I couldn't I couldn't do a lot of things last night apparently but it's all good
read one right now I don't have an analog clock in my room he's drug addicted no I'm not get an
image draw a clock right now no I've got like an entire VR room set up I'm not I'm not going to
like draw pictures for you right now that's what an addict would say I I'm not doing it today
I'll puke in there if I do it today oh I can't scream this close sorry hey princess hotcakes
thanks for the 10 immunity subs thanks for 10 subs thank you princess hotcakes yeah what's
with the golden kappa I don't get it golden kappa is it were they doing like an arg or something
nobody knows yet yeah wake me when wake me when viewers can convert that to money from me I don't
care all right would you say somebody said something that was in the sea of emotes this
is my friend stream of yours this is my first stream of yours I've seen I'm glad I even know
I'm glad to even see you don't use YouTube but you still do stuff here I'm pretty fun
welcome to the stream and you know what happens when we get a new viewer you know what happens
they're lying on the ground apparently I was gonna sing you the new viewer song but uh who
is the new guy do not sing it sing the new viewer song no no I can't no I'm not gonna chat I'm
not gonna do it I'm not gonna I'm not gonna I'm not gonna I'm not gonna do it okay and then I've
seen I've seen them I've seen all the memes you guys are spamming me well now from now on I ain't
gonna do it if I say I'm not gonna do it if I say I'm not gonna fucking press the button I ain't
pressing the button ever again just warming up before I get in the fucking zone man dropping
viewers no I'm not you can't even tell it's too early all right we're gonna play exorcist oh
there by the way there's my actor scar so I'm going what's this was this violence was it I hit
the table too hard 5k Andy that looks really little that didn't look like strong that's like
a little boy did that come on look at my big muscles oh oh my goodness they're huge yeah yeah
hey I'm just trying to finish my coffee guys hey I can't drink this when I get in there oh
fuck that these can't turn off hey oh just I got you don't worry guys I got the new viewer
hey you are here okay you're all right let's go ah nothing like a Nickelodeon slurp sound to get
you ready for VR all right let's go I'm not gonna stall anymore I promise coffee joke we have to
have a joke in front of it and I just drink a coffee weirdly why it's not a joke I'm just a
weird guy I don't know hey he's ah it's on the top of the head we're t-minus 10 minutes
away from the stream starting okay I'm kidding wait I don't have my hair sucks okay gotta get
the right thing set in here we can get started with the exorcist in Boston oh shit okay one's
right and left left okay this one's left and this one's right hey uh this is getting terrible I know
I say that often but this game probably sucks right exorcist hey there you are you're good it's
good all right all right let me just take care of because it's annoying wires okay put the hand
straps in realizing right now I have like an item right here that I need to look at all the time
don't I well well and in the famous words of Michelangelo Luigi here we go all right this is
how you move okay teleport you can teleport you can free move okay teleport um I can only
teleport like oh whoa that's weird you teleport based on your head movement that's a little weird
I don't know about that okay and then when this icon appears press the menu button and they just
keep getting bigger and they just keep getting bigger right here comes a funny joke where I'm
gonna talk about how big the iphone is now you're gonna get this thing in your pocket you know
what I'm saying I remember the iphone 4s okay oh there we go I'm a police officer I did button
aim locomotion oh locomotion loco type move speed fast yeah fast come on rotation mode
ouch crouch on now I can crouch in real life that's good right I just freaked out for a second I
don't know why I thought this was like my real phone hold on wait I know the problem that's
better okay that's better reset reset progress all right point at button pull trigger all right
let's go unknown I saw you you see hi dad I'm heading back for
Donnie ringside seats okay what do I fucking do get out of here press the menu to go back
oh this is just teaching me to play press the navigate inventory yeah yeah yeah press the menu
to go back yeah yeah yeah uh game restart exit locomotion interactions hint okay cool
oh why am I just stuck in this room how do I play the game I guess this is really scary
leave the office I get the fuck out of here let me out let me out of here what the fuck
what do I do what do I want to game restart level what are you talking about why would I be able
to do I what I can't why I don't walk to the precinct I use my telephone and call the precinct
and call the precinct and then end up there and don't walk out the door to go to the precinct
all right I'm already not happy that's just already already not happy hey yes me uh hello
uh answering machine at the fucking precinct and I just like end up right here oh sick like wait
I mean I want to get a coffee grab the coffee yeah all right I got it for the day in the evidence
room who drank my coffee what gremlin just ran by and drank it like what looney toots cartoon
when I'm like oh what happened there did it go it must have been daffy duck all right detective
I'm gonna get that motherfucker we're gonna sit him right here we're gonna interrogate his ass
I tried I tried okay hey all right why would I move the chair before I sat down
is this my desk oh a radio okay okay this is uh Roger that I don't know why we're living in like
1980 what's this what story what what town what day does this take place oh this doesn't take
place in like the 80s doesn't it okay you know you're in the next room you can just literally
walk over here I most wanted okay chapter one Roger that uh over and out I'm ready to do my first
case yeah oh shit that's me where'd it go where'd it go uh where's what I do with that yes yes
god damn it Judy I'm in the bathroom let me wipe my ass before I get in touch with you Jesus
no sound no sound there's no sound there's no sound okay we're good we're good we're ready for
VR I'm so glad I looked oh you missed so many funny jokes too they were talking to me and I
was being so rude oh you have rude is funny lol the lady was like yelling at me on the thing
okay it's been a murder okay we're in fun okay the cross is missing there's no cross in here
all right now what okay no cross got got blood okay blood got a piano oh my god this is a puzzle
I hope not a lot going over there there's two person on the screen oh my god I'm telling you
need three people to play VR I need somebody I need a walkie talkie telling me hey there's
cursor on screen oh you can't see it but uh you gotta take care of it send him into the spine
let's talk to them first what did you do sir sir you can't be in here okay something gross in there
I just spoiled myself oh who would do this gonna go like I know what I told you he was gonna do it
what is this what oh I got I got mom's perfume what do I do with it oh it's a lighter I don't
want to what the fuck man can I put this somewhere besides having to hold the grip button permanently
uh all right so that we got a lighter keep going through here right here literally like running
into somebody turn turn okay why can't that be the trigger you know what I mean why is that the
grips I have to squeeze my hand like this okay four what we got what this delicate glass case
holds holy water thrown it smasters on impact I'm trying to get powers from God what do I do
tape recorder tape recorder what happened to that holy water check this out what is that
cocoon all right this is cocoon notes on exorcism father bell oh dear oh boy this is the mother
load in here oh that was the guy that was in there wait it's an emergency button the gun's
gonna come up where's my lighter why are things just disappearing what happened to my lighter
oh shit more tapes what's this one I'm just waiting for one of these to be
back what people used to do back in the 80s and 70s and hear a song on the radio
and they would hold the tape recorder up and just record the song off the radio on a tape
and it sounded like shit have an inventory of titles
opens the way and wishes the giver into the presence of the great
um please return to father bill church all right stop talking
that's just monologuing oh shit oh it's the book all right subtitles I don't think I can turn them
on uh English I'm not sure I can turn them on guys I'm sorry facing a certain way those how do I close
the phone okay um what is this sand oh I found the cross don't touch that I guess don't touch
stay back why is it playing the tape is it coming through the cross
it's a walkie-talkie cross oh god sorry fault spray all right let's I'm gonna put this back
should I do it oh what all right I'm gonna bring the zebra thing I got everything I need right
read the clock good night look I'm not high today I was a maybe a little a little problem yesterday
but I'm fine where is that okay I need give me the book I need that wait it's got the god has a
thing on his head oh god there's somebody in here what that was the warning what what do you mean I
just got warned for being I'm not gonna talk shit about it anymore god god get away from me
wait where's my book of spells wait get out here headshot okay close this book oh god I already
hate this I fucking hate this already I fucking hate this I hate this I'm gonna spray somebody in
the face with this open this back up open this I did it with my book where's the where's the father
gonna be right fucking behind me all right I'd like to go home now
fun I'd like to go now I'd like to go home now I'd like to go home
don't you there's a lion behind me I can't see fucking anything what can I go up there what's that
uh
my name is
mama I want to leave the party
you leave my headshot get up get up throw it out so disorienting exorcist he out cold and that
thing in the shadows here's the cross how the hell do I write this up
I'm just standing here going like this did I lose no uh that's it you died package
I knew it was from the ocean oh no don't put it on I put it on who's delivering this shit to me
okay chapter two idle hands chapter two laceration bruising break lesion burns swelling
almost as many uh hearthstone hard types can't wait to see those minus two that that was funny
you know it saint dimna community hospital is star war what can I find about
lucy moss what has been taken of her what has taken hold of her that was really pretty that
was scary it was really disorienting and terrible calling hello mike I'm gonna cut you off here
mike mike stop calling me from the shower okay thanks you're talking full blast in the shower
man oh what's what's going on up there oh all right somebody clean that up all right what we got
patient f4 d2 right my book of spells they're moving around is every time I go to press this
button I move forward and open it it's so too many buttons dude come on the precision and
swing that into precision open the book they blame it on cuts last in first out they say
or work they even called me to cancel when I was on my way and what the hell
why is this like laminated issue one of venom or something I don't understand oh it's evidence
right okay f4 d2 what do these do I just heard something f4 d2 a6 c1 a6 c1 uh d3 bingo
ha ha ha a6 theater but it actually does say that what approach was caution all right approach
with caution I have to play chess versus myself and checkmate you move right a give me these
f okay need a6 c1 a6 c1 f4 d2 e2
a rare a rare sap found in tropical climb it's burns at a much lower rate than traditional oils
upgrade added to kip found a rare item today he's binding of isaac it really is binding of isaac
I found a rare item today added upgraded items to the source of power there must be more locked
away oh my goodness okay cool where is it must be more locked away not in there I tried leaving
oh can I leave oh the person's in that room upgraded your flashlight I need to change
the locomotion it's so awful and open that can I do anything with this over here I can't like
change any of this altism and demonology weird thing to read at the security office okay well
now what I have to eat the donuts oh shit should I call in this guy again well what is this
one day tuesday wednesday thursday friday
walked in here dude frozen in a block of ice dizzy in y2 was adorable today saw the boys
poking at a live frog out on the litter pick and instead of screaming like the other girls
she moved the boys aside and carefully picked up the poor thing she was awesome we walked down
to the lakeside and let him go so cool uh thank you dave 10442456 for the 200 bits I appreciate it
what the fuck do I do here wait oh milk in here is something in this uh
wait all right so we just have to sit here I feel like like look at this it is 829 got you
so what the fuck am I do something all right and what what is that what do I
I can't like interact with this anybody have any ideas point the cross at the lady
okay oops open the door excuse me can you open the door this way all the wire and the wire
right there which goes into there high voltage sure okay that goes there there behind the tv
stop crying hit the alarm what I'm gonna do is just hang the guy in the shower
I think I probably haven't touched yet I'd like I'm missing something here
nothing else hidden here right they're gonna be behind this shit right there ain't nothing
else in here I have like keys like come on no way I want the other stuff hang on here that's better
all right failed virgin that's not what that says the hint looking for something
you'll find me the button what I'm not even scared anymore I had to touch the every
that's what is that phone down put the phone down put the phone down that would have been scary but
I wouldn't have to grab the book that's over there I've already touched every book in the room like
I've done I've picked up every donut oh fuck where's the cross hey kind of a bad time yeah
I'm invincible with this this is like a shield in front of me right when I can actually open this
door oh no no no no no no no no no no wait wait wait wait wait put this down for a second I got
to prepare I got my sea salt spray I've got my okay put this down oh give me that oh stop
disappearing I didn't mean to do that spray her right in the face and spray and get it in her eyes
imagine somebody walking in the room like this okay just stay right there don't move or I'll
spray you with this with this windex uh where's give me a gun but where's like what's like my
fucking like size or something like this is like what am I gonna do with this hey I gotta oh
oh I'm coming in there I swear back against the wall oh what the fuck am I what's going on
where am I it's red in there why is it red in here what did I got to go in here
hold on stay right there for a minute don't move don't move stay there for a second I gotta get a
soap come here oh dude you can pet frog
what I'm not a fucking afraid to use this the rare pez dispenser I'm telling you
I can't put that out what holy water oh shit this delicate glass case holds holy water throw it
ashes wait more it's broken my hand what right I don't know what the item to use
there you're not gonna like this one this is a rare fluid quickly get another one quickly
oh shit oh shit
it right here I mean hey pretty scary game you got here right here up down okay I changed my mind
all right I don't did I look man I'm just a security guard I usually just fucking play my
switch and eat like ramen and donuts and stuff while I'm watching
about oh you think I you think I am where are we I'm gonna put this in my left hand
hold on I need to prepare my gear before we go don't even think about it what the fuck wait
wait a minute shit come back you fucking vile demon I got way more of these
oh my finger why is it breaking my hand what the fuck is happening dude
power of christ oh there's a word there that I like power of christ oh power stay in there
stay back okay now spray her with them you must obey you must obey obey you must relinquish the
demon and obey and john and that would be a good time to fire the laser um hold on I can
let's go I can't let go of this let's grab the demon out of her head hold on switch hands
what do I do take a picture what do I do about this the power of christ compels you
just die already you vile fucking demon what do I do I can't I can't even move
I'm stuck I can't move here stay there I'm gonna call somebody what is this
hello wait wait wait wait wait wait wait hold on hold on hold on okay all right the taken of the
old souls his work is to harvest the weak decrepit and those who wear death it is said that he
tortures his prey first through mind games dimensions and stress then the seal pain begins
with physical abuse delivered from hellish flame uh historic weakness uh this is not the bible
this is like my this is my like trapper keeper from math homework what do I do I can't put this
down this was stay back I can't I lost both headphones oh my fucking god get me this sucks
just keep them in
we spray them in the base with the salt canister and we will be victorious
you okay it was used by ronova to take souls that's fucking horrifying oh
we see was free of evil at what cost everything I did it okay everybody's
everybody's ears gets too slippery when they play vr oh this this doesn't work
I'm saying I need something better than this these things are covered in oil right now and
they're just like if I turn my head across I turn my head this way this is not long enough
were they afraid you're gonna trip over this hey guys doing good
it's number two field uh oh it's weird to see the light it's weird because it's just like I
was like in a cave hold on red eyes I gotta wipe this down that one was terrifying I get it now
it's just like it's five just scary cool chapters to get over the control schemes a little
pretty good the nose nose piece fell out uh I'm telling you this shit is greasy in here
to go oh hold on I think I just put it back in I see in 10 years when this is ready to use
I'd see you guys in 15 years when this is ready to use what the hell the nose come out I gotta
play noseless now I think I think I actually have to play noseless I mean it's kind of in there
with smellovision I mean it's I actually kind of like it more like this you guys have fucked up
my head so much I thought that said pretending like I'm like no I'm not fuck you chat all right
let's go let's call it skin deep the hospital again skin deep everyone has a psychotic breakdown
in vr strange voice on the cd the same voice heard back in 1974 and that guy I don't know
lied all the fucking time shit my face is so itchy okay skin deep all that needs to be
added to this is save the date tyler and carol are getting married can you believe it
I'm sorry that was rude a baby it's a baby demon oh fuck this one's gonna
suck someone has this one's a baby demon or sir gone I can't I seriously can't see
on okay these stairs are fucking crazy this minecraft level of steep I they're like crawl up
these oh god damn it dude okay let's get this started get out the fucking spray
in there I'm opening this already something's gonna be in here by the way this is a ridiculous
baby room it's huge if you have a walk-in closet in your baby room you're in like the 37% tax
bracket you start your puzzle yeah baby suits and a bunch of suits babies goes out maybe
that was something in here that was in here um don't you uh more suits you have no idea
you suits on top of suits you got clothes full suits suits everywhere holy shit baby hey there
see what you got whoa gucci is way too expensive and overpriced oh these are diapers here oh nice
hold on would you like to come sit down here I've got some tea for you are you gonna be demon or
what I don't want to spray a baby in the face with like whatever chemical this is but I will if I
have to okay well it's a normal baby this is a normal baby see hey baby it's a just a normal
baby okay baby both your doctor in the early stages provides about you and your baby your
body is undergoing big changes so it's natural to feel unwell okay uh oh come here I've got a
binky for you just don't scream in my face hey baby baby hey look take this it's your favorite
toy it's it's it's tommy the teddy and I've got your favorite book got your favorite baby powder
hey hey cool you can keep that one and look we've got tall tales for small children you can read
that one too organic baby formula put that in there with you you can just hang on to that
oh and I almost forgot you can cross to keep away the demons oh you're protected
wait put it over there wait okay if I get this within three tries I get a thousand community subs
you understand I get a thousand subs if I can get this first try with three tries
booty we got a problem here you keep this put that right there and I'm gonna go listen on the
other end hey good boy or girl I don't know this wait this is the rooms in the house all right I
want everybody to be in the kitchen everybody be in the kitchen get out of my way you don't
drop something okay and I'm gonna take this because of it it's just so cute it's mine anyway
I have a cross all right now let's listen to the monitor I'm gonna be like burning hell holding you
son of a bitch right it's just tuned to Alex Jones
X burning hell I'm telling you junior don't touch that why what's going on fight it wait
that was the wrong one I think it just broke a monitor I think it does punch the hole in the
monitor all right you have to feed the baby why do I feed the baby I don't think I'm supposed to
do that okay well if you wanted it's there I can't have so much stuff on this baby I gotta back up
I'm gonna hit something organized okay so what do I do oh blocks oh wait is there an s
I want to spell up let's go whatever who cares I fucked with this in the space noise so let's do
there are people talking in here okay I gotta move turn turn all right this is good good I just
start picking this shit up and throwing it around wait a minute if I drop this in here we'll drop
in the room all right I'm gonna take these two out I think these are like the parents
where we put them or right here if this is the bathroom I ain't fucking around I'm ready
in like indeed pregnancy test why is it like a phantom pregnancy test why is it like a ghost
I did yeah what is it you don't seem to be doing anything all right then I got the pregnancy test
clue okay what about in the toilet no here it is pregnant oh pregnant what's it doing that
in the toilet watch the toilet whoa whoa whoa whoa whoa whoa what's going on in here why is
it like all spooky I'll just take it out all right what if I put you in here instead
you all just fell off all right now what is it maybe doing anything uh we do give me this read
the book read book read the book on ground book on ground okay I see you peekaboo I see you I see
your secrets I see your soul see your soul didn't I already do that maybe okay it's a worm I need to
put a worm on here what does that one what do you do you see that what is that firm up uh I'll try
this a little bit of holy water uh that didn't really do what I wanted it to no nothing back
downstairs go back downstairs glow this globe I didn't touch uh okay all right find out is it
it's calling somebody
for the camera oh I'm not even in the frame it's probably info somewhere that I didn't get
out somewhere but I guess should I do just mercury in his gatorade what I think that would be
correct though the line that's done off right yeah that's it I did it
client stated that the lights in the loft are persistently bursting upon inspection is unclear
what the cause is the fuse box and electrical circuit are working correctly 25 dollars for an
electrician uh at a zero that's usually what it is this that's okay so uh I kind of I don't
can I move that I want to like move this because this is wrong three levels on the globe yeah how
do I how do I move this part oh what the fuck I didn't know you could do this
a crystal this is drugs I think this is drugs a holy mineral found throughout ancient civilization
to draw out evil spirits where is it where's my shit here holy water holy water where's the uh
what's your shit upgraded salt spray okay so I got it let's upgrade it salt spray
all right let's go I'm scared I'm gonna go spray the baby
I'm spraying the baby I'm spraying the baby I don't want to do this but I'll just mist it over him
I'm not gonna spray him in the face I'm just gonna like just mist it it's like essential oils
let me stop fucking back here what the fuck is that what is that what's that
there's something in this wall there's something in this wall let's hear that all right on there is
eight eight and a hair cut eight and a hair this tune will be found soon enough how do we get in
here I'm sorry the fuck is going on in this room I can hear kind of noises and shit
I think that's a broken those are broken all right time for a hint time for a hint I'm going
for it let's see yeah I've already been over there man you need to stand in front of this mirror
in front of the mirror get over there okay where's the other one kitchen um a knife
is it all right you pick up a knife in the back tea kettle what else is in here all right hold on
give me my thing what is even in here what can't take these pills what the fuck okay that was
fucking high that that was that was one of the scariest things I've ever seen in my life
that's one of the scariest things I've ever seen in my whole life I didn't that was
powerful that's horrible that's terrifying that was the worst thing I've seen in my life
my whole life that's like a monster in this one oh no that's not good god damn it give me the
put this out going full blown fucking firepower but I need the salt spray give me that instead
okay uh maybe your mother is uh not you're not here oh my fucking god don't even tell me where
are you you're the rocket chair wait a minute no I don't want to listen to bugleberry tell me
any more stories teleport thing for oh yeah yeah where are you you're fucking weirdo
quickly quickly quickly quickly shit I hate this one I don't like this one oh no it doesn't open
distractions it's like a flashbang no I don't want to go in there just let me put this over
here for a second wait wait wait wait don't give me that back hurry hurry hurry come on respawn
you motherfucker you're gonna be in this closet I'm gonna I'm gonna smash into something I don't
know what it is on the ceiling oh whoa I heard somebody over there all right can I just like
stack I'm just gonna tape like a hundred of these to myself I'm gonna make a cross-suit of
armor shit fuck touch the chair move the chair I can't go in here I can't leave I can't fucking
leave give me monitor oh give me this please why can I not use this okay okay I'm gonna maybe
monitor okay right there and oh my god oh my god oh my god oh my god oh my god I fucking hate
this door in where was this a door in here door oh shit what's up it's a door right there it's
not the door globe door I can peel that I'm gonna peel this oh my fucking god in heaven
um okay just wait I'm gonna stay right fucking here I need all my tools I need my tools
whatever will whatever you believe you will always be beautiful to me okay and flowers don't okay fuck
oh we've been here
no but I don't want to put this down but I have to oh no this is not a this is not a cross
but it'll do this man are you talking you can really jam this into somebody's fucking eye if
you need it to oh my god oh my god oh my god oh my god give me the thing oh my god
respawn this mother now and you can't take him away from me
I'm gonna make that easy are you that moving it's moving I'm ready to spray
I'm ready to spray this fucking baby he took my spray he took my spray I don't like the fact that
it took my spray did I leave this I can't move this take the baby go to baby throw yourself
it's definitely something I can do can I I can't walk through the mirror can I go through the
mirror wait I'll throw holy water at the baby okay it's just a fucking thing that's terrifying
there's got to be something I can do about this right
can I just leave no way I'm just gonna leave all right that was fun I'll see you later bye
bye bye wait the light on right who's the light there ain't no baby in here with the magic light
oh I don't think I can do anything that's it light on the dollhouse that's the crib
nothing in here man oh that's it drop something here how did I do this come on out of there
I need that I need that I need that detective you shouldn't play around with such things
I've got a fucking spray got a spray I'm gonna spray him all right when when I walk forward like
that and my teeth start to hurt oh quickly quickly quickly quickly quickly give me the spray quickly
quickly quickly quickly quickly quickly quickly quickly quickly quickly quickly oh no
oh it's not gonna work I need the spray it sprays more deadly raise the one that you need to use
as I mean I got laughed at fuck oh son of a bitch oh don't I'm fucking ready for you
to shoot this stay on a wall so you know where you are
where is it oh that's not a baby in there fake baby the cross is still down here though what
the cross is a light holy shit
don't come near me don't come near me don't come near me dog shit this one it's this one
it's just one sprite this one it's this one it's that one it's a snake it's that one it's that one
where else somebody else it's you if you show yourself Satan show yourself Satan where are
you come on out Satan come on out Satan oh why I'm gonna exercise these demons
don't you worry about that jr. up right there come on come on come on come on
come on spray spray spray spray spray spray spray spray spray spray spray
spray spray
alright
get out of here snake
get up
get back get back you little shit
bye baby
bye
it's okay honey
you just had a little bit of baby diarrhea
nothing to be afraid of
dad's got it under control
closing the door in the bathroom
that was
no idea man
stretched out
up next we have samaritan
passports
this parcel was flagged by the post room
it came illegally from an inmate in the new hampshire
corrections facility
find anything dangerous detective
watch the ceiling baby clip
baby
ceiling baby
you mean ceiling baby
what I didn't see this
hold on let me see
I was too I was too busy trying to be
funny
I missed it
I was just terrified you know
it's a coping mechanism you know what I'm saying
you know it's been two hours holy shit
it's been like ten minutes
I'm gonna do one more and then I'm gonna go pee
this is gonna gross everybody out but I don't care
this is gonna gross everybody out
this coffee was in here and I finished it
it was ice in here the ice has melted
into water
I do that what's wrong with that it's the same liquid
I got a base station error
actually you know what yeah
let's go I want some more
that was too little of a taste I want a full water
give me one minute I'll be right back
OP we'll take our first break
see you guys in a minute
okay I've returned
oh I just like chugged two
full glasses of water
oh great
we got two more chapters
these have been pretty good I was a little annoyed at first
a little annoyed
once you get used to the controls
this is really really fucking scary
what are you guys doing
how long have I you've outdated
how long have we waited
nerds hated
the default iPhone emote
alright let's go
let me get this back
I'm just doing some stretches too while we're at it
has the base game too big
I feel like it's huge
is that too big
alright let's go
back in I look forward to finishing the two
final chapters
let's look at the results when we're done
there's straps Samaritan
and the tomb
alright let's move
I have hands to put up
everybody's a slug
okay let's go
Samaritan
unknown epidemic has ravaged a Haitian community
causing unrest
an international team of doctors
was sent to investigate
since
Harry
run by looters the Sainte-Sainte
health center now strikes fear into
the residents
he's mother nature at work or something more
unnatural
there's a knife here
clean this place
I can't
I can't clean this place
do I hear a dog
in real life
what is it
yes can I help you
can I help you
can you do something
hey
you kinda can't be in here right now
he's so weird
he came in the room
I heard him barking at the door
and I opened the door and he was sitting there wagging his tail
I'm like yeah what do you want
and he's like I'm just coming in
and I close the door and he just lies in the corner
all the way right next to the door
he knows I'm doing VR in here
he's like I'm just gonna get the fuck out of the way
I'm just gonna watch you be a weirdo
go him
he just sits right here
he just sits in the corner
like I'm not ever gonna go over there
he knows he's like yeah I'm just gonna sit
right in front of the door
is that in the right spot
he's just like I'm just gonna hang out
I just don't want to step on him
you know what I mean
don't worry
back to what we were doing
such a good boy
he is a very very good dog
let's keep fucking going
we got a knife
a little beacon
this is the weirdest thing
this is an intercom
GPS
traffic cone
I don't know what that says
stop the spread
networking cleanse
it's a
network cleanse
that's like some fucking internet
online bullshit snake oil
it's a program
it's called the network cleanse
you just run it, it'll scan, it'll go through your network
and it'll clean out the pipes man
only $64.99
how do I type all the images?
that's pretty nice
bags
these are people
this room ends
I don't, I don't know what that is
because it's in this room
and looks like when you get
a zombie thing or whatever
thank you
danger, contagious dead inside
we're protected
there's somebody in here?
why is there somebody in there?
yes, okay
break glass
it's like the big guy in the movie goes
come on, okay, little twerk
give me that fucking thing
and he does it too
he's like, I can't, what's wrong with this thing man
I can't break it either, it's some fucking bullshit
and he starts panicking
and fucking screaming
and everyone's like, calm down dude
he's like, oh no, we're gonna get the fuck out of here
in that movie a hundred times
I can't pull it
somebody in there
I can open that with a key
what is this?
back here
cigarettes
why did I just blink?
what about the virus?
alright, what's
it's got pictures in this room
of where?
cleanse
alright, why was this picture taken?
this is grown
cleanse their souls
cleanse this place
can I take any more pictures with this?
no knives, oh
hammer
I have weapons
ready, back in here
yeah, and help
hey, in there
can I break it with this?
what the fuck, what the fuck
what the fuck, what is that sound?
is that the board?
I have too much weight, there's too much weight
this went down the stairs
oh shit, earth is going on
that crow had a human voice
sample 13
oops, oh no
I just let it loose, I just let it loose
whatever it is, I'm sorry
oh no
oops a daisy
alright, the water don't work down here
give me the cross or something
give me like the spray or the
how do they break in my face?
no
oh shit
what is this?
chat is dead
this is audio from this stream
alright Jerva
battery low, please dock to charge
Siri
please dock, please dock where?
where do I dock it?
nitrochloric acid and hydrogen
hydrogen oxides
I feel like I need to hold on to this
but this is a puzzle?
wait, wait, that power
that's the power, motherfucker just stood up
dude
I don't care, I don't want to read that
I'm gonna read some essay right now
where there's a monster
literally, literally
standing up
how do you think I feel right now?
charge it, charge it, charge it, charge it
charging station
charging station, I thought that was a charging station
don't get up
what is this? charging station
gun, gun, gun
is there a gun? somebody said gun
you said the word gun, gun
oh, where's the gun? you told me gun?
I don't see a gun
is there a gun?
or, there's a knife
where do you see a gun?
where's this, where? on the body
under the body? what?
oh, dude, I
don't, you just stay there
mister, I'll kill ya
I know how to use this thing, I've had
two seconds of training
I should fire the gun
now get out of town
I can't, what am I gonna do with this?
what monster is gonna be scared by this?
bang, bang, bang, bang
it shoot a ghost, yeah, so who cares
I'm not going anywhere, actually
can I get up? can I get up there?
too short, is that actually what I need to do?
okay, mister Anderson
fresh food is here
uh, wait, what's that?
uh, can I look at him?
whoa!
scalpel, do I do surgery?
I don't think I do surgery
oh, you don't do surgery
I don't know what to do, over here?
research notes, UV
exposure, okay
it's killed by UV
samples, infected
blood, okay
that's great
access credentials, alright
mister Moser
print that, access code
I have a
I have a scan code now
J Finch
uh, I think it's Finch, right?
yeah, it's Finch, isn't it?
you're gonna run out of cyan
okay
thank you, mister Finch
exception, hey
okay, go now
he is not the first
to try
not the first to fail
Gollum
the ring's not worth it
come back with me in Gandalf
easy now, easy Gollum
trust me, someone that's bared the ring
I know what it's like
heretic is here
he'll be my vessel
this is not fun, this part
ehh
I think we need to turn around
oh
what the fuck
wait, use the lightsaber
no, no jokes, I do
that's passing through
nobody get up
nobody, I said don't get up
it's too dark, where's my light?
there we go, that's a
chicken? what the heck?
what the heck?
chicken feet, used for protection
against spirits
they must be fixed by a
chicken foot
this is a chicken feet
thanks for the chicken feet
this is chicken feet
this is made of the chicken feet
we don't have no soul
and that's yours
that chicken foot, I could use it
right now, please
what's that
um, hi
uh, give me that back
no, obviously that didn't work
I need mine, mine's made, look, I got
that's a wooden cross that this guy
had to fucking make, that guy made
that, I
I bought mine on the fucking
free to play store, okay
this thing was like
1999, this one's gonna be
way more effective
chicken feet, I don't know
do I need to do something else with you?
hi, oh this is
Jay Finch's key card
I'll take this
I'll use it, better than you will
hey, alright, I'm going back
I have his key card
my free to play store version
um, what is
going on
ah, chickens
something with the chickens
this valve, grab this
knife, use the knife
use the knife, cut the chicken
alright, I'm gonna get a chicken
it doesn't work, it doesn't work
wait a minute, wait a minute
shit, eat UV light
oh
eat, eat, eat like
spray, have some holy water
bro, they break in my
fucking hand, they break
in my fingers
why am I doing this so tightly
spray, use the other cross
this is the chicken feet cross
what does this say?
they must be fixed by a
hanger, or mambo
um, use the spray
on the guy
I'll try that, this clearly is something right in the middle
of the room, holy fuck
it worked, oh my god, oh my god
oh my god
there it is, there it is, there's the thing
there's the guy
time, the answer is time
sit back down
where the fuck are you going
where are you going
okay
god's gonna save me
god'll protect me in this
scenario, I can guarantee
I need a chicken
I need a chicken spray in the face
fuck, you didn't like that
you didn't like that, you didn't like that
you didn't like that, you didn't like that, how about this one
how about another one, right up your nose
mother fucker
don't, don't do it
me, I need that
evil heretic
there it is, he said this one
ahhh, what should I do, should I put the cross on
take the cross out
oh my god, it's time for the
class, I think here
I will not be cleansed
now, you're gonna get cleansed
I think, I think you're gonna get
I'm gonna spray him in the mouth
you, oh my god
go for the wolf, mambo
come to me
you
it's a chicken, where is it
I feel it, I can feel you somewhere
oh, he hit me in the face
where is it, it's a chicken
chicken
it's a chicken, what's happening
I can't do the spray, I can't
put my hand down
he's throwing another chair at me, man
is it a body, it's the inner body, I think it's
one of the bodies
why is it not working
I'm gonna cross him
hey
you don't like that
do you
oh my god, that's gonna put you all over the internet
you're gonna be all over the internet
in a very embarrassing manner
okay, I didn't
below ground, the Haitian army found me a day
later among the corpses of Dr. Hopkins
I made it to the airport without too many questions
these demonic encounters have left me
with a strange sensation
as if I am being led towards an inevitable
confrontation
Azuzu's presence
auto check
hang it up
oh, this is a tape
Hampshire
ooh
one of our inmates attacked and almost killed a police officer
Detective Jameson
how in critical condition
lacerations to the throat and neck
inmate widely known as
the Gemini copycat killer
on life three days after the attack
back on
Detective Jameson
final chapter
why don't we take a look and see how well we did so far
75% that's a C
I didn't do the artifact
I didn't understand that
I was learning the game and I got my ass kicked
100%
I did pretty good on this one
100% on the baby one
and 25%
why was that so bad
research the disease, don't get hit by flying objects
final chapter
exorcist deluxe edition
cut off its head
and the body will follow
that's what they say
I have traveled too far on this path to turn back
at least that's what I told myself
Iraq-Syria border
upper Mesopotamia
oh that's really immersion breaking
chapter five, the tomb
I gotta hold it like every
movie actor and every cartoon actor
you don't go like this, you go like this
wouldn't like your hair catch fire
holy shit, this is huge
why not just hold it like here
or like here, why go like this
I gotta go that way
stick
that's haunted
not bad, not bad, rock
ah, alright, that's good
ah, alright, corridor
ooh, bonfire
oh wait a minute
that's annoying
at least I know what that is now
defense center
danger, do not enter
it's gonna be, why did he open that
gonna be a monster in here
shit, hell
going back that way
wait, do I have my book of spells
what the hell
that was fucking horrible
light the candles up in this room
no way
no way out
I gotta pull this, watch out for that
pull this, alright
what are you doing to me
why are you doing this
bug, bug
I can't do anything with that
I thought that was a turtle
why am I walking towards the scary voice
somebody above me
oh shit, happy Halloween everybody
I went in a circle
that wraps around the circle, remember that
somebody keep that in mind
I'm gonna need that in like 10 minutes
what do you want me to repent, I'll do it
tell me, what am I repenting
oops
why did I do that, what was the point of that
why did I do that
I feel like I needed that, did I need that
softlocked
this way right, yeah, follow the voice
bottom, I guess I'm gonna go with Diablo 2
I feel like I'm in the maggot lair
hey, it's risen
I feel like Christ
I just went in a circle
and this sucks, I just went in a goddamn circle
alright, this way
wrath 2
I went all the way back
oh
do I need to grab that rope and pull it along with me
we're gonna go right
he is risen, wrath
now what
wrath is that way
go this way
this is a new room
what's it doing, what is that
should I spray it or something
should I spray the paintings
I don't know, what the fuck
I don't know
I don't know if there's something wrong
something going on, I don't know what's going on
I was just trying to light the candles, I'm not trying to do anything mean
I think it might be a hint time
what do you think
it's time for a hint
oh, it's gonna jump
IRL
walk forward, teleport
that doesn't work, look
I'm not sure you can teleport in this whole level
I can't teleport
how am I gonna be able to jump this, are you guys crazy
in 30 feet
throw the torch down, why would I listen to that guy
thank you developers
I really appreciate it
that would be really
stupid to do that in real life
face devs
go back to the rope, go back to the rope
go back to the rope
back to the rope
sorry, now
I have to
take this rope
walk it through the whole level
what do we do
burn the rope
I tried that already, they're not working
saw two waiting to grab it at the bottom
it's part of the scary movie thing
that's supposed to be happening
ah, ah
put it back, put it back, put it back
put it back, put it back
put it back, you know where it is
burn the rope
that doesn't work
it's okay
it's knocking my shit everywhere
I kind of
have ideas
Abraham, how'd you get here sir
down here
it's for me
get the fuck away from me
damn it, that was a good idea
these pictures
go in here
invisible further inside
back for you
okay, crap
we pulled the rope off
this way
right, left, this is the way
this
dumb boy
I don't see anything highlighted
only highlights it for ten seconds
oh, come on
it's risen
fast
spray the giant chasm
is softlock
what is this?
are you into the candy?
oh, it's broken, fine
restart
um
can I just reset progress
because that was really weird how that played out
did you see that? that was odd
reset progress
alright, we're good
boom, yes, alright, here we go
boom, let's go, walk, walk, walk, walk, walk
there is no teleporting
anymore, careful
scary, scary, scary, scary stuff
come on, keep going, move, move, move
cool, really cool
this might hurt you, I'm sorry
whoa
that shit feels really good
on my chest and back
I need to take a bath after this one
I am
okay, here we go, remember I lit this
ow
that was one of those
moments where if that was a little kid
it didn't hurt that much but it hurt just enough
for me to cry and start screaming
like hit my hand and then
here's a screaming
okay, it says, come on
get me
hi, hi, hi
alright, rope
if Jesus
have hit
so now, let me just touch the rope
this doesn't do anything
now we walk
please now
open the book, Jeremy
open this book
now reached
now reached what looks to be a cliff edge
now place your tomb
torch in the tomb holder
now equip your bee oil
I can't read
what you're saying
say it again, I can't read it
place your, pick back up your
tomb torch and
put on the right while you equip
your bee oil torch
what the fuck is bee oil
hey, okay, here we go
be to repent
pray at night
we
okay, a secret bridge
will reveal itself
when I use my bee oil
your lamp oil
the light not the salt, idiot
why would anybody do that without a cheat code
like that, what
this way, give me this, I want this back
I'm holding it by the
oh, it looks like a bee, alright, let's go
alright, everything's gonna be fine
you guys remember the
you guys remember the undertaker
remember the undertaker's theme song
it always start like this
you just go
underneath
you
oh
Owen, where are you going
hey, bitch
it's me, the comedy guy
hey, look at that bitch, excuse me, where are you going
hey, don't hold up for me
it's me, the comedy
horror guy, I just make
fucking jokes, well I'm scared, it's me
the comedy guy, I'm
ruining your fucking enjoyment of my playthrough
oh, it's open now
oh shit, oh my feet
it's hot, ow
oh it is, it's me, the comedy guy
hey, what
that's not fair
give me this back
I need that
how do I get this back, fucking god
forever, I need it
I need it, I need it, I need it
I need that
oh fuck, I need that
is there another one, devs
help, shit it's in the wall
it sucked it up
oh my
goodness, why did I have to do that
oh my god, damn it
I need a torch
torch
torch, torch respawn
point, torch respawn
point please, I'll take it
I'll take a torch respawn
point
fucking, fucking circles
I have to go back and get the torch
oh my god
oh shit
let him out, let him out
ow, that didn't hurt
I just pretended it did
let him die
it was too hot to open
the light from this
ok, ok
not ok, not ok
not ok
where is it
oh
who likes children dead
wait, wait, wait, wait
I can put the fire up
it's breaking my fingers every time
hold on, hold on a minute
fucking swear to god
I don't need to fuck
anymore of these
I saved ya
don't you do it to me
hey, hey
what the fuck, I'm not prepared
I don't want to hit anything
you stupid game
I'm ready for the final encounter
yes
yes, yes
it's me, the comedy guy
it's fun playing horror games
got my confidence back and I'm ready to try
and guess what, it's time to fry
this is open now
hey
walking, skull
oh, blood, left or right
let's go left, maybe
what does that say, no way
out, no way out, no way out
no way out, you could have just wrote it one time
and then you could have used other
seven times to find a way out
didn't do that, did you
alright you guys, here you are
I hear a clock
clock, oh, who's
that leans in and goes
that's gonna get up, soft spray
ooh, I'm gonna soft spray this dude
hang on, give it a go, won't I
hey
illegal, illegal
illegal spray
what, should I do that too, should I do that too
look, I'm one of you, I'm gonna do it too
you don't have to come kill me
look, it's upside down
fuck, hey
don't do, I'm getting the fuck out
of here
it's me, the comedy guy
I made up that scream to make you cry
you thought I was scared
why don't you die
not you, that guy
why
that was fucking horrible
that's the worst
Dr. Seuss book
that was the worst scare
of the whole game, comedy guy is the worst
character, here's the best part
about that, I can't see what you guys
are writing in real time, so I don't know if you
hate it or not, I'm just
you know what
oh why
we love comedy guy, oh yes
I'm so happy
I actually lost like two years
of my life from that one
it just sprinted right into my face
oh my god
I feel terrible
right now, I feel like somebody just punched me in the face
like five times
alright, get me out of here
I need a torch
alright, I can't see shit in there
bones here
god save me
I'll do it myself
oh look, that's what the rope
is there for, rope reveal
fog
no, no
that's arguably more important
I want that cross
let's get on this boat
on down, I move the boat
the fake bridge
I swear to god, Jeremy
oh
we're good
so fake bridge here
oh, you just row
are we going?
oh, this is the bad part
this is father Phineas battle
of sanctism to Paul
if you listen to this
I expect that Pazuzu has already
stayed in my mind
I will not let him
do the same to you
you must finish
my work
however lucid his savage visions
however piercing his violent threats
he must be
stopped
his flame must be extinguished
and his presence expelled from the tomb
it is the only way
and he's gonna be like
right?
I see something up there
put the torch down
there's light, too much light
what the fuck is that?
oh shit, that's Pazuzu
that's the Pazuzu statue from the first chapter
it's gonna be a tongue
it's gonna be a giant frog
this is a tongue
that's a tongue
thank god it's not a fucking guy's tongue
we gotta go up to Lord Pazuzu's
temple
come on, man, let's go
this way
oh, I climbed this
we gotta lose the torch
alright, bye
okay, here we go, holy water
holy water, and then bring the demon out
here we go
undo it
through the
floorboards
you think humanity
deserves to thrive
in its own
rotting decay
that's the wolf from the never ending story
that I should not indulge
in humanity's madness
let you
such an holy slime
carry on the gods
back! stay back!
I will use
how I knew that you have never seen
before of the thousands of years
you don't scare me
vile demon
if you think I'm going to be
terrified by something as vile
as you, you have been mistaken
now come down here and face me
and face the light
face the light
once that cracks into twelve o'clock
noon
you will be vanquished from this earth
once and for all
get a little scared
but it's okay
stay right there
it's time I accept
that you are of any
species
no, no I will not accept
it
right, no I don't need to spread
come on
wait what, why did I
you all believe that man
I'm trying to dodge him
kill one another
I think I just threw my shoulder up
is he going, what's happening
earn him
come on, what do you got
you got nothing, you're really
looking a little green there
aren't ya
how
go back from whence
you came
go
back from whence
you came
sorry for turning the world
green there folks
back, alright
ready to go
oh shit, I'm mean now, I'm him
lucid and suffering
am I suffering as well
look at it, stare at it, stare at it
Jesus he'll help you
you helplessly follow as others
come
do it
however their victims
this is a new beginning
detective
you will be there
and you will watch as I disembowel
the remnants of your so called
humanity
join us
oh
the light
will always prevail
ever sometimes when it doesn't
flash of brilliant light it was
over, told you
everything that led me here crumbled to dust
around me, wait I can't read it
we can't hear you
you're talking to like the wrong direction
alright, hold on
back you vile demon
I'll kill you in VR
get out of here
whoa yes so epic fight
sequence here
get him
oh it's not that exciting for you
it's exciting for me
right between, that's sick
doozoo's
running flush that lingered around me for months
let's talk about the real
that have been watching this stream
talk about the people that have been watching this stream
that didn't really know they were watching this stream
potentially my neighbors
think that there is some weird
really wild shit going on in this stream
performing exorcisms talking about like
slay the demon, go back to hell where you
belong, go back to where you came
eat holy water, like what am I doing in here
this is concerning
let's do this
alright that ending sequence
was pretty crazy, it was really good
75% I'll take it
what time is that by the way, that is
well would you look at that, it is
would be 11.10
11.10
alright let's uh
what are we doing, 11.05, 11.10
sorry I just punched you
is that
a zuzu in there
is this the chief
disgusting vile human
same like actor
oh this is cool, this is all the stuff
why wouldn't we want to get rid of this or something
I don't think we want to keep that
all my stuff, oh cool
this is all my things
that was fun, actually pretty good
I'm coming out
coming out, coming out
that was good, that was actually really fun
how's your hair, how's my face
don't worry about that
I'm more worried about like the 5
FPS camera that I have
next game, yeah we will
we're going to move on to the
actually hold on, I have the
walking dead, walking dead is coming up
next, either the walking dead or
what's a short one
I'm probably not going to go for more than probably another hour
what's a short one, I don't want
to do Five Nights at Freddy's, no, I played that game
I played that game in like 2012, I played them all
how about a chair
in a room, excuse me
you didn't do it in VR
you really don't
the VR one is better, the VR one is different
alright, how about this
we'll save that for Halloween night
but I'm going to play a chair in a room
it's probably not going to be very good, but it might be
let's have our expectations in the right place, don't you think
and then we'll do the walking dead as well
I'm going to play a bunch of scary random shit on Halloween night too
let me go just get some water
I'll be right back, see you in a minute
go back from which you came