Hey, what is going on, everybody? Jerma here with Nightmare House 1. It's the actual prologue to Nightmare House 2, and I did it sort of in reverse.
I did Nightmare House 2 before I did Nightmare House 1, and that's my mistake, but I did promise I was going to do this. I did promise I was going to do the prologue.
So let's wrap up Nightmare House 2, the playthrough, totally, I guess, with Nightmare House 1. Prologue, here we go.
I heard this is very, very scary. I heard there's a lot of moments in the prologue or in Nightmare House 1 where you crap your pants.
So let's see if I crap my pants. Currently at the loading screen.
Uh oh. Nightmare House 2 will start after finishing the prologue. Okay. This is going to be real scary.
All right. The prologue. Oh man. Oh boy. Birds. This is very dark. I might turn up the brightness just a little bit because I can't see anything. Brightness.
Right there should be better. Hey, it's still pretty dark, but a little bit better. Let's just go here. In the woods.
Over the hills and through the woods to grandmother's house we go. Look at that house. It's a nightmare house.
Okay. Blood at the door. Anything around here? Bottle. Get out of here. Table. You know what? Let's wreck this guy's whole picnic table.
Oh, that's all I can do. Get out of the way. Can I open this up? No. Uh, door will not open. That's okay.
Whoever lives here, you are a freak. What's that? A bulkhead? Can I open the bulkhead? No, it's locked. I can't do anything with this house. This nightmare house.
Let's, uh, can I go around? Hmm. Maybe there's a way to break it. Can I like break that for the shovel or something?
Break it. Open the doors and smash the window. Oh, smash the window. Smash the window. Give me something to smash the window with.
Oh, that's not gonna work. I can see inside, but I cannot get in. Come with me. What about the shed? Let's go check out the shanty.
Anything? Hey, the shed opens. There's an axe. A bike. I'm gonna ride my bike out of here. Give me the axe.
Why can't I take the table saw? I'd rather have the table saw. I could probably just break the door down now.
Actually, you know what? I'm gonna go for the lock. Lock seems like the sure thing. And... Yay! Door! Hello? Hey!
Do I have a flashlight? Okay, good to know that you have a flashlight in this one as well as the second one. Good to know.
Let's move along here. Electric. I'm assuming I'm gonna get hurt if I touch that. Go! Nope. Oh, it's all water.
I'm gonna electrocute if I stand on that. Jump! Alright, let's go tub. Let's go move the tub.
Hey, dude. Are you okay? Are you okay, sir? You don't look okay. Got a gun. Break some of these crates. Let's get the hell out of here.
Door opens. Now this just comes back out to the electricity room. Can I jump this? I thought the guy was gone.
Move this thing. Get out of the way. Oh, I think I know what to do. I gotta make like a quasi bridge. That didn't work.
Come here. You go right here, and you get over here. And you go right here. Is that gonna do it? Is that gonna work?
Ah! Physics! I don't know how you work! I die! Come here. Get over here. Oh my god, maybe this is not what you're supposed to do.
I can't see any other way though, so I'm gonna say yes it is. Hey, look at that! No, don't fall over. Yes, it worked! I made it!
Door won't open. Of course the door won't open. Why would the door open?
No, that's not the way. Secret room. Secret room. Where am I supposed to go? Maybe out to the back here? To the door, maybe?
I'm gonna try my block building routine again, because I think I saw something up there. Is that gonna work?
And support my weight! Yay! Oh, hooray! This is what I just looked at. What is this? Oh, hello! Guy sitting on the toilet is now not a guy on the toilet.
It's two guys. Kinda looks like an egg. Got my flashlight still, right? Anything in here I need to know? Turn on the water, clean my hands.
No, I knew it! I knew it! I knew you were gonna do that! Why am I kneeling? I was just kneeling, like just swinging at him. Now it'll open, right?
There's another one right here, no? I thought his legs were gonna get up instead of attacking me. Anything in here? Bullets.
Oh, this one is so scary because it's just confined rooms. It's like hallways. Storage. Can I move this? Don't think I can. Can I open this door?
This door looks like it's already kind of ajar. No, I don't know. Open. Can I break? Maybe I can just break this. No, I can't. That's good to know. Good to know.
You got anything in your cabinets, lady? Hey! Hey! Whoa! Oh, I thought someone broke in the door. Okay, the lights out. Lights out. It's curfew.
Blood. Recharge flashlight. Lots of blood. Lots of blood. Lots of blood.
Get the hell away from me, you son of a sneaky snake! Get away from me!
Oh, TV. What's on the TV? Anything interesting? Come on. That eye just looked at me.
Gah! I want to watch like Spongebob Squarepants. Do you got that on your TV? Do you have cable?
Alright, we're gonna go, I'm gonna go in here to pick, there's probably stuff in here. There is a, what the hell is this thing?
Is this like an incubator? Are you making like chickens? Are you gonna hatch like little chickens? Bullets. Good to have bullets. It's always good to have bullets.
This is the only way to go. He's in here. Let's go. Come on now! Come on! Don't do this to me!
Charge the light. Hey! Where am I? Where the hell am I? What is going on? Hey, weird house you got here, dude.
Your house is like a bunch of bricks. I fell down. Alright, well let's just do it again.
We're right here. That's cool. Land on... I'm stuck. I'm stuck! Why am I stuck? You, get out of my face!
Thank you for getting out of my face. I appreciate that. Now why could I not land on that? Did I mess something up? Let's see, hold on.
Got a board over there. And can I just jump from here? Hey, I can! Excuse me, miss. Um, there seems to be a problem here.
It looks like this guy is dead on your wall and you're just sitting there watching TV. Oh, I don't want to walk over near her.
Slow down, sequence. What you got for me, huh? You gonna run? You gonna run? That guy's gonna chase me.
Garen? Oh, she wasn't even watching TV. Who can I... Oh! My dog is barking at me right now. Did you guys hear that?
He was like, Ruff! Get me in! Get me out of... Why are you doing this, lady? Why are you scaring me so much?
Through the next door. It's locked. Gag! Come on! She's just always standing in front of you.
Come on! That's a two-piece! Something in my eye. Something in my nose. Something all over me. Can I break this?
Give me that shotgun. Oh! Shotgun, baby! Overconfidence! I just got... Good! What is that?
Alright, I'm keeping the shotgun out. I don't care how many bullets I waste. No one is coming near me.
Charge the light. Let's go. God! God! He's... Double shoot! Double barrel! This is just a jump-mania game.
Everybody just jumps in your face. Got this girl jumping in my face. These guys with the broken necks jumping in my face.
Guys on the ground. Holy hell in a hand basket. Is he dead? He's dead. Come on! Hide somebody around every corner.
Keys? Any keys? Hey, a key! Give it to me. I want that key. Give me that key. Hey, can I pick it up?
Hey, I can pick it up. Hooray! Get... These guys are so creepy. Just these grotesque freak shows.
Let's go, key man. There we go. Open the door. Get me out of... Let me guess. The stairs are going to fall down. Hooray!
No, they didn't. Oh, it opened. Where's my shotgun? I'm only comfortable when I have the shotgun out.
Charge the light. Another door. Open. Get me out of here. God, this is gross. Oh, you're moving. You're rocking. That's not terrifying.
Hey! Get me out of that room. Get me out of that room. Get me out of here. I just keep hearing noises. Get me out.
Get away from me, you crawling... What's in there? Nothing? Nothing. Got to go in here. I'm okay with that.
Break down the walls. Break them down. It's going to be a jump. I will make this jump. Here we go. Jump, master!
Bullets. And... A ladder. I can't move. Can I break that stuff? Oh! I thought that was a person. I thought that chair...
Oh, it actually was a person. Never mind. Really? Shoot him! Shoot him! Get me up off of here. Will you get off me?
Why can't I get out of here? I'm stuck on this ladder. I fell down. Oh, well, that was dumb. I was glitched out on the ladder. I couldn't get off.
Alright, this time I'm going to be ready for this guy that was side swiping me when I climbed up the ladder. Yeah, you're dead, bro. Let's go.
Get off me. Hey, my whole job is to sit up here and... I almost just got scared again from that. Get out of here! Okay, go.
Okay, we're good. We're good. We're good. We're good. Load up that shotgun. Open the door. Something's going to break through the walls. Something's going to break through the walls.
Just run everywhere. Too many. Too many. No more shotgun bolts. Should I go down? What was in the room across the hall? Might as well look.
Let's bar it up. Can't get in there. Only one option. Looks like we're going to have to take it. Down. Going down, down, down.
Oh, that one hurt. That one hurt my brain. That and that one. Damn it!
I thought I got better at these scare games. I got worse. Hey, Komodo, come over here like Quasimodo. Eat that. Eat that.
I only have two shots in this. Not anymore. 20 now. We're good. Charge it. You have to do that. She has to just appear randomly. Did I like escape the house? I think I did.
Get me out of here. Take me down like the King's Road. Game of Thrones reference. That was a Game of Thrones reference.
Who's going to combat me and get shot in the face with the shotgun? A lot of people here. What's going on? Maybe I should just be running.
Oh, I have a sprint. I forgot about that. Oh my God. Look, it's a light. Hey, it's a truck. Ah! You can't escape from Nightmare House. Oh my God.
Well, that's it, I guess, for Nightmare House 1. Now, if you were watching this right now and you didn't see any of the Nightmare House 2 stuff, I'm going to put a link in the description to start off at Chapter 1 for Nightmare House 2.
I suggest you watch through that playthrough. It was very, very fun, very, very interesting. And yeah, that's going to wrap it up, guys. I will see you guys all soon. And take care, everybody.