Hey everybody, it's Jerma here with a Pax East compilation video.
First of all, Pax East was amazing, and a special shout out to everybody I met there.
All the people I hung out with, all the cool dudes that really came out to say hello.
It was amazing, a lot of fun, a lot of friends.
And I just want to say that a lot of this footage is a little bit on the low quality side.
I wasn't going there as really press, but I wanted to get a couple iPhone interviews.
I wanted to do some Sony Handicam stuff, so keep that in mind.
The audio isn't really the best you'll ever hear in your life.
And I have about maybe enough footage for one more video.
I'm not really sure about that, but we shall see.
But enjoy this video, guys, and I'll see you all soon.
So take care, everybody.
We're on our way to the PC free play right now.
PC free play is where it's at.
Am I right? PC free play is where it's at, right?
Come on, we've got to get a chant going.
Get to the group, it's way back there.
Hey, you know, we're going to go play PC free play right now.
What do you think you're doing?
Sorry.
This is PC free play. You know what we're going to play at PC free play?
I'll tell you what we're going to play.
We're going to play Team Fortress 2.
Team Fortress 2. Team Fortress 2. Team Fortress 2. Team Fortress 2. Team Fortress 2. Team Fortress 2.
Oh, everyone fucking hates me.
How do we even get downstairs?
Right there, that's where we're going, boys and girls.
We're going to the PC free play room.
Wait, hold on a second. Hold on.
Hey, is that...
This down here is, I think that's like the tabletop stuff.
It's fun. It's a fun time.
It's going this way, going this way.
Oh, it's PCs. I wonder how much energy this is using.
Like, how much electricity is powering all these computers? Oh my god.
We're over here with Dan from StealthMachines.com.
This is a crazy PC building company.
Basically, our company started with $200.
It was eight years ago, and all we did was use the word machines.
We started to market. We're getting our name out there.
Besides, it's just for your gamers.
We have a 10-year warranty and almost a perfect record.
10-year warranty.
PC builders, they have like a three-year warranty,
but you have to pay for a 10-year warranty.
That's insane.
This is the first time I just walked over here and had this stuff,
and it was like, oh shit.
No matter where you are, they'll get you.
You can hand deliver it.
Take a look at this beast.
This is the fastest AMD graphics card on the planet right now.
It's the AMD Radeon 7970.
Over three gigs of RAM.
Oh my god, there it is.
Look at that alien spaceship.
Guys, I'm here with D, who is the creative head,
and the guy responsible, I guess you could say, for Dust and Elysium table.
It's an Xbox Live arcade release.
Coming out, no release date yet, but he's still working on it.
He's done everything for this game.
So I want you to introduce yourself in the audience
and tell them what you're doing here.
It's amazing.
All right, so I come at this as an artist.
You know, my background is in animation.
And I wanted to work on a program.
So I decided, you know, I'll pick up XNA and C Sharp.
And before I knew it, I started making a game.
And Microsoft showed interest in it.
And now here I am, almost four years later, showing up.
In fact, it's great.
Four years of work.
So let me get this.
You are doing all the artwork, programming.
What have you not done on the XNA?
I'm not handling the audio.
I've got people coming and using.
But I'm doing all the design.
I'm doing all this work.
It's crazy.
But it's a dream come true.
Anything you can give us about when it potentially might be coming out?
Well, the game will definitely be finished this year.
You know, it's up to the publisher as well when to release it.
But it'll be done this year.
And it's close.
It's close.
Unbelievable work you're doing here.
I can't wait to see what you've got in store.
Thanks a lot.
Thank you, guys.
Well, we found it.
The Team Fortress 2 store.
Look at all that stuff.
I'm about to instantly transform my outfit into one of these.
Absolutely.
Axis, bitch!
Burger Boy.
Axis.
Yeah!
So Burger Boy, I was talking to you the other day.
That was a spy.
Spy!