Yo, yo, yo, what's up everybody? Jerma here with another Team Fortress 2 gameplay commentary.
Like you know it everybody.
Today I'm gonna be playing as the Tomislav Heavy.
Something I haven't done in a long time. I haven't played Heavy in a very long time.
But Tomislav Heavy is very fun, very interesting.
They didn't nerf it. It was supposed to get nerfed.
Minus 50 health, I think it was, if you equip this item.
If you guys are in the beta, if somebody's in the beta, let me know if they're still testing this.
Because that's a pretty huge deal. So if they're still testing it like that, I would like to know.
For my secondary, I'm using the Sandvich, which is pretty standard among most Heavies.
And for my melee, I'm using the Killing Gloves of Boxing.
Not the Gloves of Running Urgently, because guys, everybody uses the Gru.
Everybody and their grandmother uses the damn thing.
And here is a good reason why you should switch sometimes.
Oh, a Shabow got the crits now on the Tomislav.
Coming out here and just wreck house on a bunch of people.
Which is a great tip if you're going to use the Killing Gloves of Boxing.
Make sure you use the Tomislav.
Because guys, if you equip the Shotgun or the Tomislav, it's a much quicker slap down time.
You don't have to wait for a spin up.
You can just switch over and absolutely mow people down in seconds.
Playing on King of the Hill Viaduct right now.
And Viaduct is an awesome Heavy map.
I came to the realization about this like a week ago.
When I played Heavy on here for like the first time.
I never play Heavy like I said first of all.
And I play Heavy on here once in a blue moon.
But take a look at this little choke point they come out of.
When they turn this corner, it's too late.
If you're already here with your gun spun down, it's too late.
They're just going to get killed.
And especially if there's a Medic healing you too.
It just makes it that much better.
So I guess you learn something every day.
Get killed by that Pyro right there.
And that Uber charge, they had to pop it early.
Which is actually a good thing.
I will accept that death.
Because that Uber charge had to come all the way up the stairs.
All the way around the corner.
Their Uber was gone by the time they even got up here.
So I'm okay with that.
Even though they capped the point, it's okay.
At least we tried, right?
That's the name of the game.
So here comes Jerma embarrassing moment number 7,955.
Just embarrassing.
I'm sorry about this.
I really do apologize.
So I come up here, there's a Heavy.
We're going to do a one-on-one Heavy fight, you'd think, right?
I'm afraid he has full health.
So I run around the corner and just go,
well, I'm just going to switch to my sandwich and I'll be fine.
No, I missed it.
Dead.
And the real kicker of this is look at the health.
He had like 20 health.
Oh, if I had just stayed up there and shot him for like two seconds,
that would not have happened.
But it did.
Have to move on, have to deal with it.
Here is a tip for you guys right now.
Kill the Medic first before you kill the Heavy.
If you're in a Heavy-Medic fight, chances are if you're close enough,
you can kill the Medic first.
Definitely do that.
Don't just shoot the Heavy if you're that close,
especially because I'm using the Tomislav.
As we all know, the Tomislav is the weakest next to Natasha.
It's the weakest minigun in the game.
So if you're going up against a regular minigun Heavy or a Brass Beast Heavy,
you are not going to kill them one-on-one.
You're going to take health off of him,
but you're guaranteed not going to kill him,
unless of course he has lower health.
But seeing that he had a Medic with him and that he was using the regular minigun,
I had to make the decision to go for the Medic.
That's really important because if I didn't do that,
we would have both died, me and my Medic.
So for the next minute or so,
I want to talk about something that has nothing to do with Team Fortress 2.
I want to talk about Grandpa's upload to Machinima Respawn.
So if you're watching this in the future, I apologize,
but if you're watching this in the present, like a lot of you are,
Grandpa's first video is going to be on Machinima Respawn tomorrow.
I'm not sure if it's going to be tomorrow afternoon, tomorrow night,
but a lot of you wanted me to tell you when it was going to be up there,
and now I found out it's going to be every Friday.
It's going to be the same video.
It's going to be edited a little bit to make sense on Respawn,
but it's going to stay similar to the one you've already seen.
If you guys could please go support that video,
if you liked the original one,
I would totally, totally appreciate that.
And so would Grandpa.
Yes, I would.
Yeah, he would.
So let's get back to the gameplay here.
I just wanted to let you guys know about that.
With less than 20 seconds to go now, we look like we have this in the bag.
Unfortunately, though, they get on the point and they cap it.
So it looks like a big, big deal, but it's not.
Do not worry.
I am back here and I kill about five or six people in a row.
So what that means naturally is they cannot even get out to the point.
So once I get a couple of friends on my team to get onto that point,
we're going to cap it and we are going to win.
Come up on this left side.
They don't even know I'm here.
This medic and soldier pair don't even know I'm here.
I end up getting the soldier.
Medic goes down as well on his own, Will.
Don't even know how that happened.
Spy gets on the point, but it's not a big deal.
We cap it.
Five seconds left.
One Pyro gets on the point and almost gets it to overtime again,
but he doesn't succeed.
This is the end of the gameplay, guys.
Thank you so much for watching.
I really do appreciate it.
Shoot me a like if you enjoyed this video and make sure you be on the
lookout tomorrow for Grandpa on Respawn.
Hell yeah.
See you guys next time.
Take care, everybody.