Hey, where do we make the cheeseburgers?
I love how we each have a different name.
Alright, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, stealth. No, no, no, no, no. Do not just start...
This is... What are you doing?
That's not me.
Oh, shit.
Why are you Star's girlfriend?
No, no.
I thought we were doing it at the date.
Oh, yeah?
Alright, so...
I can't control his mouth sensitivity.
You have to turn your, like, DPI down.
I can't fight my mouth sensitivity.
This is so high.
Alright, you are seriously, you are seriously messing this whole thing up, you guys.
We were supposed to build burgers.
You guys are just taking all the ingredients and throwing them all over the place.
We got people coming around.
They're just putting them on the floor.
We have customers.
I'm going to say hi.
Look, you need to look at, like, the note board to see what we have to do.
I'm just watching Star, like, literally just hold his hands out and just hold left to right as he goes down the road.
What are you doing?
Trying to fix this shit.
You have just, like, single-handedly destroyed what we were doing.
Can we actually make a burger or are you guys just going to be dipshits this whole time?
Look, come out here.
You sprint.
You can sprint.
I figured I'd just change the field of view.
There are people out here looking for cheeseburgers.
This guy wants a bacon burger.
Alright, we got to set this up.
This guy wants...
There's so many people in here.
There's, like, sick people in here.
This guy wants a...
There is a burger patty.
She's not happy.
Alright, who wanted the lettuce?
No, nobody.
Alright, seriously.
Meeting.
Team meeting.
Uh-oh, the manager is displeased.
I am not happy.
You guys...
One of you guys is getting fired.
Hey, look at all this stuff on the grill.
Yeah, it's all burnt.
Go to the front desk.
Go to the front.
I got a burger.
Wait, what do you mean?
What are you talking about?
No!
He took the patty.
Catch it.
Someone catch it.
I caught it.
And she's still in the restaurant.
Oh, there goes the rat.
Oh, he snagged it.
Oh, no.
Look at this trail of rats.
Look at the live rats.
They're all...
It's like a rat fight.
They're all going after this one piece of meat.
This one guy.
Don't let them get away.
We are chasing this rat all the way down the street.
Come here, you son of a bitch.
I got it.
I got the rat.
Look at all these people just watching.
We caught the wrong one.
Can we actually play this game?
We're not.
Hold on.
Everyone get in the back.
These rats are burned.
They are crisp.
They're not even...
They're dead.
They're black.
Okay, we can finish the rat burger.
I found the patty that they ran away from.
All right, get the rat and put it on the bun.
I'm crying right now.
This is so stupid.
Okay, can we please restart this?
I don't have any fucking rats everywhere.
How do I get the rat?
I don't even know how you draw.
How do you even control this?
I think it screws up in multiplayer.
It looks like a two-year-old drawing.
You're holding two?
All right.
All right, follow me, though.
There is a prisoner back here.
There's a person back here.
Oh, my God.
You fucking idiot.
What are you doing?
We just remade this game.
Why?
You're fired.
There's a person.
What?
There's a guy in here.
I know.
That's what I was saying.
What's wrong with this guy?
Can we punch him?
He is the rat mama.
Can I pick him up?
What if you could pick him up and make a person sandwich?
No.
Oh, no.
We all conspired against you.
Yeah, it's just like all at once.
No one said anything.
I'm very happy with our teamwork.
I am completely lost.
There's no way I'm getting out of this.
We did that very silently.
We all knew.
You dicks.
It's just me and this weird hermit guy back here now.
He's fighting through the shrubbery.
I'm fighting through.
He's bringing the rats.
We're doing it.
Also, we're wearing bandanas and look like pirates.
Okay, Star, you're not allowed to look.
Not allowed to look?
No, because you're the burger judge.
There's people coming in.
There's customers.
I'll talk the people down.
You got to show them to their seats.
I'll lower their expectations.
Lower their expectations because they're going to probably throw up after eating one of our burgers.
I'm going to go.
You look mad.
Oh, I picked something up.
Yeah, still.
We have to make burgers.
We have to make our own delicious cheeseburgers.
By second rule.
Start with a bun.
Everyone get away from each other because we're just going to knock into stuff.
I'll take my stuff into the bathroom.
So here's my burger station is going to be right next to the sink.
In the bathroom.
Yeah, I'll be in the bathroom with my...
Oh, well, the cheese is completely...
My cheese, seriously, is just like a black tile.
You don't put the cheese on the grill.
I wanted to like melt it.
Okay, well, get out of my station.
You dick.
You son of a bitch.
He just dropped my burger in the fucking sink.
Hey, hey, you don't got to...
You got to play to win.
Oh my...
Where are you from?
Never...
Star, just pretend like you didn't hear that.
What are you doing back here?
How are you like multiplying these bacons, Star?
Come back here.
What?
What's going on?
I know how to break everything.
Where are you?
It's like duping poop.
I'm in the back room.
What the hell?
How did you get all this bacon?
I'm the Baconator.
Who's under the ground?
Jeremy, you're under the ground.
What the fuck?
Oh no.
What the fuck did you do?
No.
I'm gone.
I was so hard on that.
Oh, Phil.
Where am I?
I don't know.
I'm...
Somebody else fell.
Who just fell?
You went wizened by my screen.