Hey, what's going on everybody? Welcome to episode 3 of The Binding of Isaac, German Let's Play.
Not really a Let's Play in parentheses. So, I took a lot of you guys' advice, and I'm not using the mouse anymore, as you can probably tell.
I'm using the keys, and it is actually a little easier to move around, so thank you for that.
And I'm also not going to miss any secret rooms, or I'm going to try not to miss any secret rooms.
So, I died, as you just saw in the last episode. So, let's start it, huh?
Alright, that's fine. Coins, I can't get you. Maybe later. Bug bitches.
So yeah, a lot of you guys were like, oh my god, you're missing so many secrets. And I am sorry.
I did kind of just jump into this game without really thinking about it a whole lot. So I'll try to keep that to a minimum now.
Can't get those right now. Let's go up. Okay. Oh, there it is. See, there's the blue tinted rock.
A lot of you guys said, look for the blue tinted rock, so there's one right there. I'll remember this room.
Let's go to the right. I've never seen these enemies before. Like jumping jack freak shows.
Oh my, it is so much easier to aim with the arrow keys. Oh, and you also said to hit the chocolate syrup, because there could be items in there.
So I will. Item boss? Really? This is it? That's not very many rooms.
First item. Mr. Boom. Mr. Boom. So that's not a bomb. That's... it is.
Should I blow up the thing to get the thing? I don't know. I'm gonna do it. Whatever.
Small rock has appeared in the basement. Ooh, damage up. There you go. Oh, that's morbid.
Oh my god. There's a rock sticking out of my head. So that's awesome. That's awesome.
So when you blow up the tinted rocks, items can go up. I'm cool with that.
So that's it. There's nothing else. Wow. Okay. Isaac versus Monstro.
I've already beat this guy. I know what he does. Let's go. Yeah, go ahead. Come on. Come on. What you got?
You ain't got nothing, you friggin' goofy-toothed bastard. Keep puking.
Keep puking. All right. The damage up is... I can tell it's doing more damage. Oh god, I'm getting hit.
Wow. So definitely they'll spirit... Oh, I hit a spirit heart. That's cool.
What do you got, Mastro? Oh, it is. This is so much better.
Using the mouse was just so counterintuitive. I got you. Nothing.
I am gonna beat this stupid level. Not level, I mean this series of levels.
And you are dead. What do I get? What do I get? What do I get?
Underwear. Mom's underwear. Oh my god. I look ridiculous.
Oh, let's keep going. The basement. Level two.
Let me take a sip of my delicious soda pop.
All right, I'm ready to go. Up or down? All right, I'll go up. I heard you.
I heard you through the computer screen. You said to go up.
You guys, what do you got? Were these... Okay, somebody in the comments want to let me know.
These characters, these guys that look like the fluffy cauliflowers.
Were they in another game? Or in another series or something?
I feel like, cause Edward McMillan, or McMullin, is the guy that is the artistic brains behind all this.
And, oh my god. Should I go in?
I'm going to the item room. I have a key. I'm going in here. Hell yeah.
Bobby bomb. Homing bombs? What the hell does that mean?
I'm gonna do it. I'm gonna knock this out of the park.
I can't even... I need a key. Damn it.
It's all right. But yeah, Edward McMullin is the guy responsible for this game.
So I figured a lot of these guys must be from a lot of his other works.
And I just opened up the floodgates right there. I don't know if that was a good idea.
I got it. Come on. Oh, the green one.
Somebody told me the green ones are like worth more. Ooh.
They were. They totally were. Doing good so far. So far so good.
Oh, damn it. Die already.
Geez Louise with a piece of cheese. Nice.
Nothing in the chocolate syrup. I'm going to go open that chest.
I am absolutely going to go open that chest right now and probably get my ass kicked.
What is it? A bunch of... Oh, that was...
I don't know if I like that. I also read somebody said to not use the bombs
just to kill random enemies. You need them later or something somebody mentioned.
So I will heed by that advice and I will not do it.
Look at these crying babies. Oh, no. Did I really get hit by that?
Bilarki. Oh, man.
I'm going to cook you on an open fire, baby. And another chest.
And I don't need any of it. I'm going to go down.
I'm not going to go right. I'm going to go down.
I'm not sure if that was a great idea or not. Not sure.
But yeah, I swear to God, I've seen these guys from something else.
So in the comments, let me know what I'm talking about.
If I'm crazy, I'm crazy. If not, then I've seen them somewhere.
I think I'm going to go down. Oh, well, you get over here.
You rat bastard. Get over here.
Good to go. Getting stuck on these rocks.
These things remind me of fleas. Oh, a chest. Cool.
Coins, coins, coins.
See, okay, this is crazy.
The last level that I did was like less than like five rooms.
Ooh, pills. All right.
Somebody also said don't take the pills because it could be bad.
What? What? What is going on?
This is a boss? This is not a boss room.
What is going on here?
Oh, my God.
This game is just trolling me right now.
It is a troll. It's a troll face.
I'm going to die. Oh, boy.
So what? This is like a mini boss room?
Get the hell out of here. No.
Damn it. I'm going to die. No, God.
Geez. Oh, Q the fool.
Which one of these should I take?
I need heart. I have no idea what this does.
Somebody's probably screaming at the video right now.
Pick the pills back up.
I'm not going to. I'm keeping this thing.
I need life. Oh, if I die right now, I'm going to I'm going to throw up blood.
Blood is going to puke out of my mouth.
I'm going to hit Q. I'm doing it.
What? What just happened?