Hello. Big Brain Academy is installed. We're not gonna play it yet. Not yet. That was fast. It was.
Jump scared you? I'm sorry. I'm just ready to get back into- I'm gonna play one more
Picross level and then we're gonna open Big Brain Academy, okay? One final Picross level.
Agrabas. Oh shit. I cli- all right, never mind. We're playing Big Brain Academy now, apparently.
I- I clicked that button. I did the- I closed it. All right.
Big Brain Academy. Brain versus brain. Here we go. Let's go. Big Brain Academy is not brain age.
What? What are you talking about? This is not brain age? Wait, how many brain games are there?
What do you mean wrong game? I bought the wrong game. Big Brain? Big Brain! What? What are you
talking about? There's another one? Brain age is not available on the Switch in North America.
This is the one we're playing. Yeah, me. Me. Johnny 500. Okay.
Do you feel as if your brain has been a bit more stiff than usual? Well, here at the academy we
offer a variety of activities to help you stretch and flex that brain of yours. This game is good,
don't worry. Okay. So without further ado, let's get started stretching your brain. To begin,
we'll enroll you in the academy. So if you would, tell us about yourself. How old are you?
Did I have to fucking ask that question? No, I'm not that old. I'm- I'm like fucking 32,
man. I'm like 34. I'm too old. Yeah, I was- I was going on January 1st, 1988. 1987. 1986. 1985.
Who cares? Tell us your style. Your occupation. Choose something close to your real occupation.
Um, okay. Preschooler, grade schooler, middle schooler, high schooler, college student,
student of life. I'm a- I'm a business owner. Self-employed, free agent. I'm a business owner.
I'm a business owner, free agent, self-employed office worker. Just combine them. Self-employed.
Next up, your catchphrase. You can change this later, so just pick anything that strikes you.
Uh, buried in homework. Send help. But you forgot like the crying emoji. Can't say no to candy.
I have only one speed and it's easy, does it? That's kind of accurate. Gotta finish strong.
I'll do it to- or that. I only have one speed and it's easy, does it? I'll do it tomorrow.
How do grown-ups get to have all the fun? It's- it's funny how the ages- the different age groups.
This is like for a kid to say this. Is it a lounge day? Why do grown-ups get out of fun?
Like a grown-up's not supposed to pick that. Comfort is key. Can't be too careful.
It's simple. Be sincere. I like to be liked. Why- we- why make only one mistake? I'm a big-
I'm a fan of being a fan. My grandkids are the cutest. Horses are better than people.
I like the appearance you prefer while attending our academy. You can change this later as well,
so don't fret. Okay. Okay. Gotta- hold on. That's pretty close. Close.
That's not bad either. Which one? It's this one. It has to be. Okay, facial hair. No, I don't have
facial hair. German, I hate 5 green. All right, I'm done. Also, allow me to introduce our online
features. You can compete with others in Ghost Clash. I don't want to do that. Are you comfortable
with photographs of bugs? This option prevents photographs of some creepy critters from appearing.
But they were- what do you mean bugs? Okay, practice. Let's go. Let's begin by stretching
and flexing your brain in practice. Tada! Welcome to practice. It's our specialty here at the academy.
If I may, I suggest you start by trying an activity in the identify category. Why not
give whack match a try? You can play with either button or touch. I'm gonna play with buttons.
Whack the mole with the matching picture. That's kind of depressing. Okay, just click the things.
All right. It's easy. All right. I need a face cam for this, don't I? Yeah. No, no, no. I got it.
I got- I need- I distracted myself. Fuck. All right. All right. All right. All right. Right.
I need a face cam. I gotta put clothes on. Hold on. You guys need to be able to see my face for this.
One sec. I just need a shirt. Okay. I'm back. Let me just make sure this looks- all right.
Should. How's it look? Do I look all right? Too dark. Why is it so dark? Oh, shit. Hold on.
I gotta change the setting here. Hold on. I wasn't planning on this. Put the light on? I do have a
light on. Every webcam that's been created is- has some of the worst light controls ever. That's
better. All right. Let's go. You ready? This is gonna stay on for Elden Ring anyways. It's a delay.
Oh, shit. That's right. Hold on. I gotta fix that. I didn't even check to make sure that that was
actually working, by the way. There we go. All right. We actually have to test this to make sure
that everything's synced up correctly. Because when you pull a console through a capture card,
it just delays it. That's good, right? One, two, three. I did pretty good. All right. One gold
lobe medal. All right. This is actually kind of- this is gonna be fun. No. Try to collect all the
gold lobe medals. All right. So that was just one- all right. That was a cool thing. Your journey
towards impressive big brain bronze scores just began. All right. I'll just keep doing it.
Memorize, analyze, compute. Oh, wait. We need to test this. One, two, three, four, five, six,
seven, eight, nine, ten. Is it in sync? One, two, three, four, five. No? Videos later? Is it close
enough? Game is late. I'm going- all right. Let me try this. One, two, three. One, two, three.
Better? All right. Flash memory. Let's try this one. Use the buttons. What were the numbers and
symbols? Five, six, six. They're just showing it to me. Six. Oh, okay. I get it. What the fuck? I
didn't- what? What? I didn't want to go forward that other way. Dude, I didn't want to go- the
button- I pressed the button accidentally one more time. All right. That was fun. Focus up. I'm
focusing. I just pressed the- I- by the way, would you like to see the perfect controller?
This is perfect in every way. And placement, analog placement, the face buttons. I thought
you just got mad at it. Yeah, but I got mad at me because I pressed the button accidentally
one more time. I actually think this is- the one thing I would change on this is the triggers
I think should have a little bit more give. But placement wise and hand placement, I like it the
most. The pro controller. The PS5 controller is the best one, right? I mean, that's simple.
All right. Which one is heavier? I don't know. There's too many things, too many colors.
There's too many colors. Literally. I can't do this. It's too many different things are on the
screen. I saw a Mega Mart shirt. Oh, you noticed. That was really cool. I got three medals. Wow.
There's more? Choose two cards that add up to the number shown at the top.
So it's just addition. It doesn't matter what animal it is. Oh, that was a nine?
Um, ah! I can't. Too many colors. Oh my god, he's stupid. No, I'm a visual learner.
Okay, you- I'm gonna destroy- here's the thing. People are gonna talk all this shit.
I am going to destroy one of these. And you people are gonna think there's something wrong with me.
You're gonna think I'm cheating. There's, like, one learning category that I'm gonna do really
good in and I'm gonna get, like, ultra advanced. Ultra advanced. The rest of these are gonna be,
like, at a fourth grade level. This is not one of them. This is not one of them. I know this.
I've had- I've taken this test before. Wait, oh. What? Little one. But that was every single piece.
Being a visual learner was proven to be bullshit. Only, uh, people made it up.
Only intermediate. I'm not good at this kind of stuff. Just wait till they get to the fucking
numbers and I'm gonna destroy it and I'm gonna make you all look foolish.
How would it look if you looked at it from the direction of the arrow?
The fuck are you talking about? That one hurts my head. Slow down? Uh, isn't there a timer?
The timer. Isn't it, like, tick. Tick. Tick. I hear, like, a clock ticking.
There is a timer. Yeah, there is. Add the missing tracks. All right, let's fucking look-
let's look like an idiot. What do you mean, add the track? Oh. Oh, I didn't want to press that one.
I- seriously, it's really sensitive. Um, sometimes I- it's like, I go- it goes, like,
double or it doesn't go at all. Like, I was trying to move and sometimes it would go, like,
tick, tick, and tick twice. This D-pad sucks. This controller sucks. It's just got good placement,
that's all. Oh my god, it's perfect. Uh, yeah, I'll put on sunglasses. Cool. All right, nice.
So that was memorized. This is analyze. I'm gonna look really bad to a lot of people.
People are gonna think, like, I'm on drugs or something. Speed sorting. Which picture
fits the description? Plant. Living. Plant. Fish. Doesn't swim with fins? Wait, what does that mean?
I don't get it. I don't- what does it mean? Doesn't swim with fins. What does that mean?
No, I wanted to do the car. What the fuck? The fucking ladybug is not- I could start using the
analog. That's worse somehow. What was that? Was that a mall screw? It was an eggplant.
I thought it was a muscle. I want to do that one again. I want to do this one again.
Ah, okay. I thought that was like a celestial body. What was it? Fins. No! I didn't want to press that.
For some reason, I didn't think pig was a mammal. I thought it was a trick question for some reason.
I was like, what is it then? What's- um, I don't know. What else is cold-blooded? A bug's cold-blooded?
I can't even relax. A bug's cold-blooded? I'm serious. I don't- I don't know. You only hear
that for like lizards and shit. I don't fucking know. The bugs don't even have blood. They have
like fucking- they have like cerebral fluid and that's it. Bugs don't have blood? They have like
a little bit of like juice in their head. Shark is not a fish, I thought. I thought that was a big
debate. These eat things? No! I thought it said move with legs. What do you mean? A tricycle is-
What do you mean slower than a bug? Fourth slowest? No! The fucking d-pad sucks!
I want to go like this way and I go like up left, up left, up left, up left. It's like up left,
up left, up left. I'm just trying to go right, man. One more try, that's it. Okay, I don't know,
the octopus laid eggs. Oh, I got it. All right, that was super elite. All right, cool, cool, cool,
cool, cool. Let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go. All right, match blast.
This is fun, damn. Break blocks to copy the top shape. I get it. All right, that was too hard.
That was too hard. That was too- that was way too much. Oh yeah, I fucking guarantee if he tried
to hit me with a sword I could dodge- I could dodge it. I fucking guarantee it. If you had a
fucking battle axe and you were gonna try to get me with it, you're not gonna get me with it.
You won't- I'm too fast for you. Way too fast. I would- I would- I would- no way.
Okay, I am fast as fuck and I have- I have lightning-like reflexes in real life.
I don't care what some little fucking grasshopper says about how stupid I am.
You got- you got swing of the axe? I'm fucking gone. Not happening.
Why- I've been playing too many video games. Like, why is that the first thing I go to? I've been
playing too much Elden Ring, I really have. I've been playing too many video games. All right,
how many cubes are there? Three. What the 16 of those? I can't concentrate.
18, 19, 20, 21, 22, 23, 24. I can't concentrate. I can't concentrate. I don't like this one.
I actually can't concentrate. I'm fine. I'm okay. I just can't concentrate. I'm-
I have huge concentration problems ever since I was a little child.
I'm telling you, you got me with an axe! And I'm fucking gonna dodge it.
Compute. There's more on to memorize. Memo random. Memorize the picture on the car before it flips.
Which one was it? I should be- I'm gonna do- I'm gonna get super little on this one. Wait, oh,
it's the one it flips over. Okay, I didn't understand the rules. Oh, fucking come on. I didn't-
I didn't even fucking look at what it was. Slow down. All right, and I understand- I didn't
understand the rules at the first few rounds for this. All right, reverse retention. Remember
the order and answer in reverse. Shit! Did you see the face you're making? I don't care.
This game is fun and everything, but what would happen if somebody came at this guy with an axe?
I'll tell you what would happen. They wouldn't hit me. I would be on the other side of the room.
It would be like Dark Souls in real life. They'd be like, oh, I'm coming this way. And I'd fucking
dodge it with perfect frame rate. Perfect frame invulnerability. Covered cages. Where are the
birds? Make the cages go faster if you're up for it. I get it, okay. Already gone. I didn't get to
super elite? Ooh, he was happy about that one. Legit based elite brain. Thank you. All right,
okay. All right, so what do I do now? Oh, okay. Practice. Test. Wait, I haven't seen all these.
All right, here we go. Species. Which animal is there more of? Look around with the spotlight.
I don't need them. They're the same. Not even super elite. I wonder if this guy could definitely
dodge battle axe. I could. Which piece belongs in the box? Pay attention. Oh, I didn't want to pick
that one. I'm getting frustrated. It gives me a fucking headache. I like know it too. I can see
it, but my brain just can't do it. I can see it. It's just like, it's like mushing it all together.
I can't. I just can't do it, man. It's just like, it just mushes in my brain.
It's like I start looking at all of them at the same time. My brain sees all of them and yo,
I'm dodging that. He's peeking. I'm fine. Fast focus. What is the picture of? How fast can you
figure it out? It's a rabbit. It's a hippo. Owl. Snail. What? What is it? Is it a dog? It's a dog.
House. I don't know. A butterfly? What the fuck is that? What is that? Snake. I'll try it again.
I like that one. That one's fun. Again, I like that one. It's the concrete that fucked me up.
No, I didn't want to press it. I wanted to press panda. I guess it's a cat. It could have been a
snail. How the fuck are you supposed to do that? One more. This whole game could be contained in
a 10 megabyte flash website from 2008. I mean, that's kind of funny what you just said, but
oh, it's probably seal or fish. Probably seal. Seal. Cow. Giraffe. Ostrich? I don't know what this is.
I don't think you can blur it any harder. What is that? Fucking panda. I wasn't pretending. I was
looking at the middle because the panda was facing the other way. It was like the back. It was like
the back of a panda. I haven't seen a panda very much in my life either. No. All right. That was
cool. So now we do. There's a couple we didn't do in visualize. I'm going to do this one. Shadow
shift. Find the pictures that match the shadows. No, I didn't want to click it. The round head.
Well, it's in there. You got something on the top right of your screen. What is it? Tell me what it
is so I can be aware of what it is. Okay. I have, I have to read it analog clock. Mallet math. What
is that? Oh, mallet math. Whack the blocks. You don't need to leave behind the correct total.
I need four. I'm going to be ugly. Three, six, nine, 12, five, 10, 14, 21.
Oh, seven, 14, 21, six, six, seven, eight, five, six, seven, five, eight, nine, 10, nine, 10.
No, I didn't want to do that. Why did it fucking move? I wanted to get rid of the other one.
21, 21, 21. No, I didn't. I seriously, sometimes it just like goes. I don't not try to press the
button. You dodged into it. Rotate the clock hands to match the time. Bring forward an hour.
Fall back 15 minutes. Uh oh. Fall back 30 minutes. Fall back 240 minutes.
Go forward 120 minutes. Where did I start? Bring forward 245 minutes. Five, 10, 15, 20.
It's weird on the controller. Look, let me show you what happens. Let me show you what happens
when I use the, it's weird on the controller. You're supposed to fucking touch that. Like,
it's weird. Like, I can't. It's really weird on the controller. I swear to God.
Hop from lowest to highest. Fuck you. Fuck! Negative 80. What? Dude, I fucking hate this
controls. I'm trying to fucking. I can't start over. Start over. Start over. Start over. Start
over. This, this D-pad sucks asshole. It's fucking the worst D-pad I've had in any controller.
Use the analog stick. Analog stick is awful here. Negative 71. Fuck you. I give up. I don't care.
I, who gives a shit? Who fucking, what does this even matter? Brain. Oh, brain training.
Who gives a shit? What does this matter? Why does this even matter? Like, this whole thing is,
doesn't make, who cares? What specific case does it matter if I can pop balloons in a certain order
if they, like, are tricked to make you look bigger and smaller? You know what is practical?
I'll tell you what's practical. A guy running at you with an axe and you got nowhere to go.
That's what I call practical fucking things to know. I'm telling you, dodging, dashing,
and shit. Like that, oh no. Here comes the fucking battle axe. Open up. One, two, three, four,
no, you're gone. Sorry buddy. I know practical shit. I don't care about impractical shit like
counting balloons in a room of various shapes and colors. Let's take the test. Let's measure
your big brain brawn by having you compete activities in five categories. I'm going double
headphones. Memorize the numbers and symbols. Repeat them before you forget. All right, identify.
No. Which piece belongs in the box? Pay attention to the movement. I'm going to,
shut up. I'm losing points. Number of cubes. The number of cubes. I think I did pretty good.
All right, let's go with the train one. I was good at this one too. Oops. Oops. I'm fucking,
I'm flopping here. I had it. I got to move with it. That's how I do everything. All right,
computing time. All right, that's going to be bad. Put it, sorry. No, I didn't want to go up again.
Fucking controller. What are you doing? Well done. How'd I do? How was your first test?
Your test results are reflected in your big brain score. All right, my big brain score is 3,300.
An average person who hasn't spent time in practice will score about 1,500. So I practiced. So I
should be somewhere around two or three thousand. 2886. This is a very good score. I'm going to
give your brain a grade. A plus plus dude. You're getting started. Let's aim for even higher.
I can't get higher than A plus plus. I told you I was a visual learner. I'm very, my analytics are
terrible, but I can visualize, compute and identify and attack. I'm going to lay into this.
I don't need to memorize anything. I don't need to analyze anything. Visualize. It is important
to accurately perceive that what you see with your eyes. Furthermore, there's room for improvement
in analyze. I recommend flexing and stretching there. What is analyze? If you can answer a little
faster, you'll be better. Tell me, have you been collecting gold low metals? I have no doubt you're
capable of buying more. Well then, it's time to announce your big brain type. This is your brain
type. Visualizing and computing. See it, compute it, and I can attack it. Visualization and
computation. Battleaxe brain Andy. That's fun. So I can do more? What is this? I wonder what that
button does. Try to earn gold medals in every practice activity. Do a ghost clash. I don't think
I pay for the switch online. I don't think I have it. I'm pretty sure I don't have like, I think I
stopped it. So wait, this is apparently what I'm bad at. That makes sense. Is it though? I crushed
this. You had it from Mario Tennis. Didn't I crush this in the actual exam? This was bad. So was this.
I nailed it. I got to like, super elite. When are you going to play Elden Ring? Well, I'll tell you.
In literally like, five minutes, ten minutes, I'm going to take a break. It's going to be a long
break. It's going to be somewhere over 15 to 20 minutes. I'm going to eat. I'm going to chill.
And come back in about 15 plus 20, just probably about 20 minutes. And we're going to come back
and play Elden Ring for the rest of the night. So there's going to be an intermission for food.
Because I started at like one and I want to be able to go till like, you know, 11, 12, 1 a.m.
I have like a 10 to 12 hour stream, but I want to eat in the middle and go, you know, if I need to
do things I can. So I'll be playing it in like 25 minutes, 30 minutes. It's going to be a long one.
Well, the reason, the reason why I did a long stream today specifically, specifically so
is because I'm not going to be around for the next like week.
Uh, and I really want to play Elden Ring. So the idea was to break it up a little bit and
play something else that's not Elden Ring, but I still wanted to play Elden Ring because I'm
obsessed with it. And I don't want to not play Elden Ring for like the next five straight days.
You know what I mean? Like I was like, I could have just played this and then like done the
streamer award stuff because that's this weekend. So that's why I'm not going to be around. So I
will be, and when we come back, a good question of what I'm going to do after that. I'll be on
the streamer awards on Saturday. So I'll be hosting it. You'll probably be able to
pick me out in the crowd. I'm sure you'll see me there at some point walking around.
I'm also presenting. So I think I'm not hosting it. No, no, but I am. I'm going to be one of the
presenters. What about baseball stream? Yeah. I got to get, I got to get a good suit and everything.
Yeah. It's going to take, I need to spend the next day or two getting really ready for this.
All right. Let me try this again. But yeah, in about 15, 20 minutes, I'm going to take a break.
It'll be a long one and we'll come back with Elden Ring. No, 16. Why is the controller so bad?
I just, I, who cares about how many blocks you can count? Who cares? I'm going to do that test.
I want, I want to do a different one. I don't want to do the block one again. You idiot.
Got it. Oh, it's too much things. I don't care. No, I want to do the monkey. Yeah.
Oh, my analytical brain. Oh no. Okay. I can't analyze things. You can't get all,
you can't have all the infinity stones. Sorry. No, this game. I just, okay. I can't play this
anymore. Can you guys hear? It's coming out of my speakers. It's literally coming out of like my
monitor. I, I think I fucked up the whole sound thing. My sound is fucked up permanently. I have
to play like this until I do, I take the break. I'm going to turn this off because like you can
hear it here. Do you hear? So whatever. I don't care. I fucked everything up. Almost had it.
Almost had it. It's too awkward. It's coming through my speakers and I can't fix it.
I'll turn it up. Can you hear it now? You guys should be able to hear it now.
At the train to the exit. I think my noise gate is making it so you can't hear it.
No, wrong controls. Whoa. I thought I was starting on the other side. All right. Let's see if I,
my brain age went down because obviously, obviously I got fucked up and I was
under extenuating circumstances with this unplugged. I got a higher score than last time.
How? A S minus. I got to S. I don't care. I win. Let's take a closer look at the test results.
I can't stand this, but it has to stay that way. Oh my God. It's a whole chunk of my brain missing.
What the fuck? I'm not going to improve in analytics. It's not going to happen.
That sounds so weird coming through here. All right. We're about to take our break
in just a moment. In just a moment. That's fun. I can't get the weight thing down. L ratio brain.
Whatever. I have such trouble with this. I always have. You want to talk about,
okay, wow, dude, your spatial awareness. This is exactly what you should be talking about.
I have trouble with like, like orientation of stuff. Okay. I'm being analytical about this.
I'm not, I'm just trying to, I'm not going fast. Okay. Okay. That's better than last time.
I don't know, dude. I don't fucking know. I don't know. It sounds like you're making
pop. When is this bit going to end? I'm, I can't plug this back in. This, this took like five
minutes to get in the right spot behind the monitor so I could hear it. It's not going back
in. I can't do it. Sounds like somebody's breaking tiles in another room. I'm not going to be able
to get gold on any of these. Hold on. Let me try to plug it back in. It's such a weird spot.
I don't think I, do you want to help me plug it in? All right. Here. Go back and play. I just can't
see. Oh yeah. She got it first try. This is so loud. I got to turn this down. She's like sneaking
back here. I'll see it a bit. She's like sneaking around. I'll be really honest. I got to be really
honest. Holy shit. I don't even know how she just did that. I don't think you guys understand.
There's like, there's like six inches of space behind the desk and she just was like, boom,
bam, in, gone. That was unfucking believable. It took me like, it took me 15 minutes to get
this plugged in. She's just fucking there. Isn't she great? That was cute. I love that. All right.
Just without even being seen either, she's just like gone. Sneak queen. All right. Two, four,
six, seven. I'm about to throw it into the ground. Oh, she knows how to analyze shit.
I just can't, I'm sitting there like, I'm sitting there with a plug just going like,
I don't understand how this goes in there. I just, I can't analyze how it plugs in. I see it's small
enough to fit in that hole, but where's that hole? It comes in here with an axe. I'm dodging it.
All right. Start over again. Game's muted. It has to be worth a gold medal. That's a gold medal.
It has to be, right? Yes. Much better. Yeah. Okay. How about identify? I'll get, okay.
All gold medals give you something, right? Fuck you. That's gotta be gold, right? That has to be a
gold medal. That's better than what I had before. Come on. Gold. Are you doing the stream? Yeah,
I'll be at the stream rewards. Seven, planning on it. Compute. This one's just add up the numbers
and that's it. Don't do anything else. I fucking can't do this one. I can't. No, I need gold. Do
it again. Come on. I need 300. Bingo. That's going to be huge. That's the, that's a triple gold
medal. All right. Come on. This one's weird with the analog. This would be way easier with a finger
or a stylus. It's time to 12. It's weird. 180 minutes, six, 12. So it's backwards. 80 minutes,
six. Okay. Backwards, forward, six, 12, 18. So that's three hours ahead. One, two, three, five,
six, 12. So one, two, 35 minutes, five, 10, 15, 20, 20, 30. All back. Six, 12, one, two, right there.
Do it. I don't think that's gold. I don't think it's gold. I need to be, I need to do a little
bit better than that. Come on, man. No, controller. I fucking hate this thing. It's such a shit.
There's a weird reverb on the mic. It's probably the fan. The fan's blowing into the mic. Is that
the fan on? All right. That's all golds. I could definitely get gold on this one. I only did it
once. Yeah. All right. Only two more and I'm good. Okay. I got to focus on this one. Don't be an
idiot. Fuck you. Do it again. I'm never going to get it. No. Huh? Dude, I don't think I'll ever get
that one past silver. I need 400. I got to do, I almost had it. I just got to get it quick. Shit.
No, you kidding me? You got to be fucking kidding me. The fuck, dude? How are you supposed to do
that? How is it, how is that possible for you to get that in? I don't get it. 100? Oh, wait,
then the four. This shit is just, I can't do it. My brain just can't process it. I don't think I'm
ever going to get 400. Dude, it's like the, it's the segmentation that my brain just goes,
you can't fucking do it. It's the segmented pieces down here that it's like, look, it's done up there,
mom. It's like, no, I can't, my brain just can't do it. Oh, bro. I don't, I can't, I can't, dude.
I can't. This is the one thing that I will never be able to do, ever. The segmented pieces become
one piece in my brain and it's physically not possible for me to do it. Come on, dude. Try
playing it drunk. That would actually probably help. They're all one piece. They're all one piece.
My brain is mushing them all together. It's like, I think they're all connected because they're all
connected. Okay. You know what I wish they would do? I don't want to see the top one. The top one
is fucking with my head. It's, it's making them connected down here too. Like I'm just going to
not, I'm going to literally block the top of the screen up. Fuck. It's happening again. Fuck. Did
I get 400? Let go, let go of me, let go, let go of me, let go of me, let go of me. Okay. Fuck.
I got how far did I get? Oh my God. I thought I was up really low on that scale. Minus 300. I got it.
Okay. I got gold on everything. Super practice. In this harder practice, every activity starts
in the advanced class. This is not happening. No, fuck. Jesus. Bet you can't do that. I'm fucking
at it. I will see you guys in exactly, exactly, um, like 20 minutes. We're going to take a long
break. I'm going to come back with Elden Ring. That was fun. This is the end of the first segment
of this stream. I'm going to eat. I'm going to pee again. I'm going to refill my drink, get a water,
and I'll be back for Elden Ring. I'm going to play Elden Ring until I'm done.
So see you in about 20 minutes. I'm going to put text on the screen too, just because
I want to make sure people know that I'm not coming right back. So let's solve that now.
That's where it needs to be. Okay. I'm going to add some text on the screen. This is the intermission.
There you go. I'll see you guys in about 15, 20 minutes. It might even be shorter than that.
Include where you left. Oh, that's a good part. That's a good idea. I don't know. Yeah. I'll write
this 15, 20 minute break. I'll say back at six 40 specific. There you go. That makes more sense.
Let's see how this plays out. So I'll be right back. I'm not going to have any music because
I don't think it'll, it'll just be looping for like 20 minutes. Let's make this really easy to see.
All right. I'll be right back. I'll see you guys at six 40 ish. See how this plays out.
I'm really curious how this works. No, no music. Do random music. Um, I feel like it's going to loop
the same thing. Yeah, this is, this is, this is all right. All right. I'll be right back. 20 minutes tops, probably less.