The heart of Atlantis is power beyond belief, forged by the greatest civilization ever to walk the earth.
Whoa, dude, you need to chill out.
It has to be.
You gotta calm down and take your sand raider with you.
From fucking Star Wars in the background.
You!
Let's go.
What?
It's an evil pharaoh.
What the hell is he doing?
He's like, oh god, I can't see.
Oh, fuck you, dude.
Come on, dude.
Put that thing down.
I'm just an evil pharaoh guy.
I just wanna swing a sword.
God damn it.
Would you just stop it, man?
Where is he?
Where are you?
I know I'm gonna find you.
When I find you, you're gonna die.
I swear to god, dude.
There you are.
You thought you could get away from me?
You thought you could escape the mummy?
Oh, dude.
Oh, come on, man.
Oh, what the fuck?
I can't see.
Oh, what the hell?
Tell him to put the light down.
We're just playing.
This is the dumbest thing ever.
I feel bad for this guy.
You burn him with the light?
Is he dead?
Dude, life sucks for this guy right now.
This guy is just having a...
Yeah, you'll be fine.
You're obviously not slipping.
I got you.
Don't worry about it.
Whoa.
What?
Oh, we're sliding down this right now?
It's like a big schneid.
Look, you can see my little elf shoes.
Why do I have like little elf cowboy boots on?
Oh, no.
Are these guys enemies?
Is everybody an enemy?
Are you serious right now?
What just killed him?
Who shot him?
Did he get just friendly fired?
I think he did.
Watch it.
Mummy's to your right.
Don't worry.
I got this.
I'll flashlight him.
I'm gonna do the flashlight and you guys take care of him with the...
What are you doing?
Don't get that close.
This guy's a fucking idiot.
Why are you getting that close?
You guys...
Who would ever get that close to a mummy?
Who would ever do that?
Well, that's a pretty large machine gun.
No.
No, we're not doing it like this.
We're not doing it like this.
We're gonna see if I can use the light on people too.
Can I be the annoying flashlight guy on people?
You really can.
You seriously can be the annoying flashlight guy on...
Oh, fuck.
He's aiming it down here at my face.
What?
This guy apparently made his way to Hoff, which is interesting.
Where's the AT-ATs?
Where's the serial AT-ATs?
What is that?
What?
Did I walk over another one of those mines?
Or the tripwire things?
No, there wasn't anything on the ground.
What?
I need to be sure about this.
Another one of those tripmines killed me when I was looking at the freak baby things sitting on the table.
Why is this place booby-trapped?
What have they got to hide?
Like, seriously?
Okay, that hurt.
No, there is not one of those in here.
Oh, it's...
Who did that?
Who does that and who's stupid enough to walk into it?
Apparently me.
I guess I'm dumb enough to find, like, Buddha.
Whatever this is.
You see him?
I can't really see him.
He's down here somewhere, though.
Well, just keep firing down there.
You've got to be able to find him.
We need to get this kill.
I can't even tell where I'm shooting.
Can you help me here?
I can't...
He's right next to you!
What?
What are you...
Are we just not realizing what he just did?
He's just like Incredible Hulk through a steel door.
And they're having just a general conversation.
You heard the man.
Name is the era of Waffle Router.
You don't know how to speak that language, idiot.
Put down your waffles.
Oh, that was such a funny joke.
Afraid of heights?
Not until I saw that rope.
No offense, Doc.
But we have no time for a detour.
I'll go first and prove it safe.
Oh, someone's shining a light in my face.
See?
How do you like it?
How do you like having your eyes blinded by something?
It sucks, doesn't it?
So I have found Han Solo from Star Wars when he's in like the steel glue shit.
He has Luke Skywalker's lightsaber.
This is not canon.
This didn't happen in Star Wars.
That's a...
Look at this replica of a lightsaber.
We'll see.
We'll try to get him out of there and see what he has to say.
Han Solo, it's time to let you out of your chamber.
Give us the secrets of the Millennium Falcon.
Oh, God.
What's with the light, dude?
What the...
Oh!
Oh, what's going on?
Don't shoot me!
I'm just gonna have to fucking go!
Oh, please!
I'm just gonna let you...
Where's Leia?
Ah!