Hey there, hi. How's it going? People watching the Vaught have no idea about what. I wasn't late,
I was there exactly at 3.59 p.m. Yeah, I was just talking to Mr. Italics. He expressed interest
in hopping in a little later. He's like, yeah, I kind of want to play. So I was like, yeah,
whatever. So we might see him in an hour or two. Maybe sooner, we'll see. Tell him you don't
want it. That's like so rude. Why would I do that? Hey man, yeah, like it's a game that has
multiplayer and stuff. Like, yeah, I'll play with you. No, I don't want you. That's like, why?
It's like a co-op game, isn't it? What are you fucking talking about? Anywho,
hi guys. Yeah, here's the plan. We're gonna do Mordhau. I hope I'm saying that right.
Probably not, but you know, one guy said that. You must be new here.
5,000 of you could write the same sentence and I wouldn't see it. They would be one person
in between that 5,000 sentences of the same sentence and I would read that one out loud.
It's like my brain finds patterns and then the ghost for the thing that's not the pattern.
I'm always connecting patterns with words and language. So, but yeah, we're gonna do Mordhau
tonight. I don't know how long we'll do this for. Who knows? I might get addicted to this game and
it might be the only thing I play. You know, I think I'm gonna get so good at this game. I'm
gonna play it so much. I'm gonna make a movie. I'm gonna make a game. I'm gonna make a horror
game in Mordhau too. I'm gonna spend all night playing Mordhau and like that's all
I'm gonna do. And then tomorrow you'll see some more Mordhau of me of what I've been
able to come up with. But no, it's that Dreams is a lot deeper of a game. I want to spend more time
with it. So what we're gonna do with Dreams is we're gonna spend... That's a new lie.
No, it's not a new lie. It was never a lie in the first place. Did you look at the tutorials
for Dreams? Yes. I did look at them. I looked at them. There's quite a few of them. I looked
at them. I mean, I didn't do any of them. I looked at them though and I looked at them.
Now we got a tutorial. Speaking of tutorials, we've got one to do here. So we might as well
hurry this up. So let's go ahead and get that off. I don't have the camera on right now.
Hey, look at that. This is Mordhau. It is a first person medieval multiplayer action
attack each other game. Looks like fun. A lot of people were requesting this yesterday,
so I figured I'd give it a try. And let me make sure the audio is okay. Make sure
it's not too loud. It is probably way too loud. You're gonna have to tell me. You're
gonna have to yell at me. It's probably a little bit better. That's okay. So I have no
idea how this works. We get 2,500 bucks when we complete it. So let's play it.
Go. Takes approximately 15 minutes. Now that's the kind of tutorial I like. Only 15 minutes.
Hold on. I gotta fucking stall for a second so I can tweet it. I do this thing where I
make a tweet before and then I accidentally just cancel the tweet and then have to redo it.
What I'm saying is, I'm just fucking not intelligent. It's all been a lie. I had two
IQ tests. Yes, I did. It was very bad. And I just tell everybody on the internet that I'm
smart so people think that I'm smart. Don't you understand? Oh, okay. Mordhau. Landlord?
No, lardlord. I should just change it to landlord. Why is it lardlord?
Twitch.tv. Why is this pre-recorded? I don't understand. How can you guys
determine that? What makes something pre-recorded? What is it? What does it take?
Is this the way I'm talking? Like, okay, so let me type this in.
Is it? Press end for a new beginning.
I'm fucking huge.
Go on. Look around. This is the place where I'll teach you how to fight without stopping
yourself in the process. P is first person. Okay, hold on. This is sensitivity. It's way
too high. All right. That's quite enough sightseeing for now. Eyes on me, you two.
Mouse x-axis? Oh, should I hate when they do this?
I can never get this right. I always accidentally make it like two points higher.
It's gotta be lower than that. All the pros told me.
Point fifty point fifty. Right? That's better.
Might need maybe a little bit higher. Okay, go back. Go back to first person.
This is a real battlefield, but don't be alarmed. We're perfectly safe at the moment.
That seems to happen quite frequently.
Where's your sword, recruit?
Where's your sword? Sword!
Get down to it. Hit dummy three times.
Dummy. That's not the dummy. The dummy's behind me.
Left mouse button to perform an attack. Here's the... oh, look at that. That's the direction
that you go. So you come from each angle.
Press the left mouse button to perform an attack. While that attack is halfway through,
press the left mouse button again to execute another follow-up attack.
Easy enough.
All right, he's fine.
Holy shit. I fucking slit his throat like five times.
Oh, what a classic Jerva joke!
Again, one more. I played enough Sekiro to know how to do this.
Good. If you quickly toime your attacks after a parry, you will perform a repost.
A quick follow-up attack that will catch your opponents by surprise.
Toimen is crucial. Toimen.
You must perform the attack slightly before or exactly at the time of the block.
Parry my attack. Right before. Okay.
Here we go. Excellent repost.
Jesus. One more thing about parrying it.
It only lasts a short while. The way you turn your hips can make your weapon hit sooner or later.
This can be used to create an effect and throw off your opponent's toimen.
Try to block three of my strikes as I turn in and out of them.
Okay. Good.
One more. You're only coming from one direction.
Make sure you have the stamina to perform a parry.
Otherwise, you might end up losing your weapon.
Oh, stamina.
Parry my next attack.
Ha! Like stealing candy from a baby.
He just took my...
I'm not your butler.
Oh, we're getting a classic fucking Jerva YouTube joke.
So that's E. If you have no...
Pick it up. If you have no inventory space, press G to drop what you're carrying.
Let's see if you can do more than just mindlessly quail around with that weapon.
We will start with a simple horizontal strike.
I see.
Chop that stick up with three horizontal slashes.
Okay.
Move your mouse slightly to the left or right and press left mouse button to execute a horizontal attack.
Yeah.
Good.
So you kind of just...
Like that.
I see.
One more.
Does it matter if I take the thing off?
Is there a way I can make that slower?
I feel like it's really erratic.
It's like holding a compass and spinning around in a circle.
Move your mouse slightly upwards and...
Upwards.
See what I mean?
It's like...
Yeah!
I feel like someone's holding a magnet up to my fucking compass.
All right.
So anyway, where's the pumpkin again?
Good job.
Next we have the stab, which is an attack that allows you for precise hits.
Stab that cabbage over there.
See what I mean?
It's kind of...
Stab.
Mouse wheel up.
Interesting.
Nice farming, recruit.
Almost missed the pumpkin.
Most weapons have an alternate mode of use.
What's that show where they cut shit?
They make the sword and then they have to cut a bunch of stuff and run around and
get winded hitting like meat and chickens and stuff?
No, not Fruit Ninja.
It's an actual show on TV.
Okay, so R to switch weapon mode.
Why the hell would I hold it like this?
Hit the dummy on the helmet.
Why?
You're not supposed to hold a sword like this.
Kicks cannot be blocked by a parry.
Kicks can't be blocked, right?
That makes sense.
Forged in fire.
That's the one.
You can defend yourself against kicks by performing a kick yourself.
So you can block a kick with a kick.
Kicks by kicking right before I hit you.
Good block.
Another.
I want to rebind that.
All right, all right.
Okay.
I don't want that as F.
Sometimes it's a good idea to cancel an attack before it is fully committed.
This can trick your opponents into firing early.
I can't pause it.
Can only cancel an attack before it is fully committed.
So don't wait too long.
Get around my defense three times by tricking me into parrying it.
Left mouse button to start and then just after press Q to faint.
All right, okay.
Press 9 to skip this tutorial stage.
All right, I get a follow up but it's okay.
Well played.
Snakey.
Well done.
This kind of reminds me of if For Honor was cool.
Form an attack morph.
Or cooler.
Only morph from strike to stab or vice versa.
To perform a morph, start an attack and then start another attack shortly after.
Morph an attack.
This will morph the original attack into the new one and throw off your opponent's sense of toying.
Get around my defense three times by tricking me with a morph.
Okay, you can morph from strike to stab.
So stab just press left mouse button before strike and then quickly mouse wheel up.
Well played.
Okay.
So you can do the same thing in reverse.
Snakey.
Yeah.
That's enough.
Cool.
You can go back and forth.
I'll show you an advanced maneuver called chambering next.
Instead of parrying, you can mirror my attacks with your own attack.
If you do this just before the attack hits you,
it'll act as both as a block and a counter attack.
All right, we'll do it in the same direction.
You must learn to successfully chamber.
I will perform a left horizontal slash,
which you must counter by performing a right horizontal slash just before I hit you.
Get ready.
Okay, right horizontal right.
Well, I didn't do it right.
Got to be quick.
Wait, what?
Wait, hold on.
Wait, wait, wait.
Perform a right slash right before the weapon reaches you.
Oh, okay.
I get it.
I thought I was going to like Darth Vader.
I thought it was going to be going to do the lightsaber connect thing.
It's right when you get hit.
It's literally right before it touches you.
All right, let's see.
Now apply all that you have learned and land five strikes on me.
For this time, I won't hold back.
Come here.
Good, again.
God damn, this is fucking crazy.
So there's only, you can only parry for a second.
Uh-oh, died to the instructor.
One more, not much worth it for the fight.
Hey squirts, thanks for the five community subs.
It's time to play with some new toys.
Hold G to guard.
Oh, isn't that funny?
You ain't going to get me on that one.
I'm sorry.
You know, I could, I might be dense, but I'm not thick.
I have a really heavy brain, not a thick brain.
All right, so pick up a bow.
You kind of have to get out of the way.
You asshole.
Supposed to be the instructor.
Get out of my way.
All right, let's get the bow.
And there it is.
There's my bread and butter.
Oh, bread and butter.
He said bread and butter.
He says that all the time.
What's the drop like?
Outer circle.
It's not bad.
Let's see, how high?
Outer circle.
No, is there, is there any drop?
Oh well, you're not blind after all.
I want some real shots now.
Hit that medium range target three times.
First of all, left mouse button, start drawing the bow,
and release when ready to fire.
If you run out of ammo, you can restock from the ammo box to your left.
Cool.
Far outer circle.
Far outer circle, okay.
No, so it is a little higher than that.
Let's see.
Like up here?
Inner circle.
There it is, yeah.
It's not, it's really not that much.
Want to prove me wrong?
Three hits on the far target.
Oh, fuck.
Ah, too bad.
Far outer circle.
Ah, no, it's a little bit lower.
It drops right at the end.
Far outer circle.
No, give me an inner circle.
No, fuck you.
Okay, okay, I'll admit, you're a natural.
However, what separates a true marksman from a talented amateur is the Hanz test.
What separates a true amateur, as you've been able to tell,
I have a really dense brain.
No arrow, what?
I have to shoot this guy?
Is this the guy screaming running around a field?
This guy's harder than an actual video game.
He's like the ducks.
I'll get him right here.
This is actually really hard to hit somebody.
Splendid shot.
Don't worry.
He's at wars.
Follow me.
I have a surprise for you.
A surprise?
Hopefully, you're not afraid of horses.
Pick up that lance.
How much is there to do in this game?
The lance is useless on foot, but it is devastating on horseback.
Now hop onto the horse.
Jesus.
Press F while riding fast to start.
All right, we got to get F out of here.
Yeah, we got to get F the hell out of here.
Hold on.
I got to change that to a mouse button.
Key bindings.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
What's F?
Kick?
I want this to be this button.
Yeah, whatever.
Upper right strike, lower right strike.
I think, do I need to know?
Do we need to have this shit?
All right, press thumb mouse button while riding fast to start a crouched attack.
Okay.
Hit the dummies.
Oh, I have to hit the dummies.
So do I have to hold it or just press it?
Probably have to hold it.
Uh, what?
Just get me off the horse.
I'll never be on it.
I'm never going to use the horse.
Uh, so you just have to be...
How fast do you have to be going?
I have to hold it.
I'm holding it.
Okay, I'm holding it now.
You know, okay, it'll only last for a certain amount of time.
Now you actually have to pull the...
Your hand out like this.
You don't just have to aim down.
You have to like pull...
Or don't fall off the horse.
This isn't red dead.
I got to turn around.
I wish I had a more open field for this.
They're kind of like sticky in the middle of here.
It's hard to control this too.
What?
Why?
How is that missing?
What?
Oh, get me off this thing.
Quit horsing around.
That was funny.
Come on.
Give him that one.
Just don't do that in the game.
I'm not gonna because I'm not going to be a horseback person.
I'm going to be a assassin.
That's my character.
And I'm going to roleplay on Mike the whole time.
I mean, what I meant to say is I'm going to be axe guy.
Axe guy doesn't go on a horse.
He runs.
That guy doesn't get on the back of the horse.
Hey!
What the fuck is that for?
All right, I'm going to be meat tenderizer guy.
So I have to repair both doors?
Well, that seems fairly...
This probably costs money.
Longsword.
Oh, a trebuchet.
How are you...
Mouse wheel down, mouse wheel up to increase the disc...
Okay, to increase and decrease the power of the shot.
This is just golf all over again.
I'm not going to play this either.
I'm not going to touch this because this is golf.
And you see how bad I was at golf.
I got it.
Okay.
Take out the middle one.
Increase the middle one.
That one there.
That's way too far.
Damn it.
Do you want to point blank him in the face with this, can I?
No, you can't.
What if I just...
Okay, what if I just go closer?
Hold on.
Can I just seriously disintegrate his head?
No, that's not going to work.
Just fuck that.
I'm just going to go down here.
Oh, god damn it.
I just ruined everything.
I'm stuck and he's actually in the way.
Just back it up.
I can't move this now.
There we go.
Okay, all right, all right.
Easy, easy, easy.
All right, turn.
Right there is fine.
How are you supposed to hit this shit?
I was going to say, if that wasn't it.
Oh, god damn it.
First try, get it.
Yeah!
Wait, let's throw one more rocket.
All right, so everyone that was asking, well, what the hell happened to Sam and Max
and what happened to Dreams?
Dreams is not something I can...
Okay, here we go.
Quote, start now.
Dreams is not something that I can make something worth doing
and worth streaming in one day.
I need to go through all the tutorials
and really get the knowledge of the program
and make something more than one thing
over the course of the next four or five days.
Now, what does that mean for you?
I'm going to hold a community event, maybe a week from now,
where we can...
Whoever has Dreams can make something with the hashtag Jerma
or Jerma in the title and we will watch it all
and play through them all in a week.
That's what's going to happen with Dreams
and I will be contributing as well.
That's what happened to Dreams.
That's why it's not here right now.
A week isn't enough time.
Well, then two weeks, I don't know.
We'll figure it out.
Why does this take so long?
So there's a Battle Royale mode, from my understanding.
Isn't enough people willing to learn Dreams.
It's hard.
Wait, didn't I just do this?
Where's my money?
Hey, what?
Why do I have zero dollars?
Okay, Battle Royale.
What should I do?
Battle VR?
Europe?
Oh, it's West.
Horde mode, frontline Battle Royale.
This is the first time...
Okay, let me tell you something.
This is the first time I have ever played a Battle Royale game.
On this stream, besides PUBG, like once.
Okay, let's go for it.
Do you drop?
Do we fly in a giant taxi cab and have it drop us?
How do we land?
I don't understand.
Do we have to pick up items?
I'm so confused at how this is going to work.
Yes, a medieval plane drops you off.
Yeah, I mean, this is a long time ago.
It's probably one of those little sea planes.
That dragon?
Now that would be cool.
30 damage.
Oh, right in the face.
That did extra damage.
Got him.
See you later.
I feel like I'm going to like this Battle Royale because it's not...
You can't camp with, like, a sniper rifle on the roof.
You have to go beat the shit out of each other.
Oh, that would hurt so bad.
We're just punching a haymaker into stone.
What is going on?
They got DC?
Did I DC?
What the fuck?
This is going to be fun.
Come on.
Get me in there.
It's the server?
Should I join, like, a different server?
Should I join, like, US East or something?
Come on, get me in there.
I feel like I'd be very good at this.
You know what I'm saying?
I'll try this one more time.
I could burger boy technique at least half the people that play this game.
This used to be a variety stream.
Now you play Battle Royale like everybody else.
The matchmaking is all fucked up right now.
Okay, well, hold on.
The boomer technique?
Yeah, VR normie boomer streamer.
It's like, look, look.
The boomer technique is real.
You have to press the buttons as many of them as you can at the same time.
So you'll go to, you'll fight somebody in the arcade.
And you'll make them cry because you...
Well, I mean, like Mortal Kombat, like arcade cabinet.
What I used to do when I was a kid is they would be these dudes that were older.
They were like 10 years older than me, right?
And this is back when arcade machines had the good console games
because console games weren't good enough back then, right?
So Mortal Kombat 3 was in the arcade.
And what I would do is I would go there.
I was probably like 15 or no, I was like 12.
What am I talking about?
I was playing Mortal Kombat when I was like 12 in the arcade.
They didn't like, nobody cared if you did that.
So anyways, playing Mortal Kombat when I was 12 versus like a 19-year-old.
You know what I mean?
And you had the face buttons.
You had like six of them and you had the joystick.
And it was a thing back then where people would line up behind
whoever was playing and it would be like,
okay, when you lose, yeah, now it's my turn to try and take on the champion.
Because if you won, you didn't have to put my money in.
You got to stay.
So what would happen is I would get up there and go up again.
I would pick smoke every time in Mortal Kombat 3.
Cyborg Smoke was the best character ever.
And then this guy would crack his knuckles like,
yeah, this little kid's got nothing on me.
I've been practicing.
I got my own kit.
He'd get up and he would be doing his little button combos and shit.
And I would be going like this.
Just pressing every single button I could, mashing as hard as I could.
And I beat them all.
The guy would get fucking flawless half the time.
Am I supposed to be playing?
Next in line, please.
How does this work?
So there's 17 people left.
You want to fight the fucking 12-year-old?
That's a real fancy fucking kit you got there.
Too bad you didn't think you were going up against smoke.
He's trying to pick up items.
Oh shit, he's got, what does he got, a leg?
He doesn't even know.
Well, this guy's good.
Uh-oh, it's Kabal.
I'm standing in the fucking fire.
Why can I, why are we all so dumb?
Oh, I got to write the teeth.
Oh, you didn't think I was going to come at you like that, did you?
Oh, give me that.
What's that?
Give me his helmet, too.
Oh shit.
I'm going to get the presents.
Hold on.
Wait, wait, wait, wait.
There's a lot of stuff on the ground.
How do I go in my inventory?
I don't know how to go in my inventory.
Long sword, rusty shovel.
No, I don't want to use the rusty shovel.
Maybe I do.
What else do I have?
Okay, here's the poleaxe.
This is too nerve wracking.
How big is the area?
There's the guy right there.
I'm going to shovel the fuck out of this guy.
I just broke all my legs.
Is there a heal?
Am I healing over time?
I don't understand.
Oh my god, I'm going to shovel this guy.
What's that?
Just kidding.
Oh, where's it going?
Someone's going to come from behind me.
I know it.
Eat berries?
Is that what you do?
Oh shit, I almost had it.
I don't know what to do.
How do I heal?
Give me the poleaxe.
What's this?
What the, what the, whoa, whoa, whoa.
What, what, what, what, what?
What is that?
What did I die instantly for?
What?
Was that out of bounds?
That's the circle?
Oh, there's a circle.
I thought it ticked damage on you.
Guys, I don't play Battle Royales.
I've played a Battle Royale like twice.
Oh, I can't believe he's not one of these streamers
that plays Battle Royale every day.
What?
I can't believe you didn't know that that was the circle.
I mean, this guy streams Battle Royales 5,000 hours.
I can't believe you didn't know.
I didn't know.
It was just gray.
I thought it was like going to battlefield me
and turn me around.
You know what it goes like?
Please get back to the playing field in five seconds.
Hey, it's Alex.
I did really well.
I was killing people.
I just fucking walked out of the circle
and died instantly.
I'm calling him.
He needs to know.
I'm calling him right now.
Hey, the Battle Royale circle thing instantly killed me.
I was doing well.
I was in the last six.
Did you get like chased and you got caught in the circle?
I cowered it out and I ran away.
But then like I stepped out of the circle for a second.
It was just like somebody hit me in the head with a rock
and I instantly died.
I don't play Battle Royales.
Hold on.
So you like you strolled casually into the fog?
Is that what happened?
And instantly died?
I was doing so good too.
All right.
How do I add you?
We're going to do that.
Can you queue as two for Battle Royale?
There's a party system.
Let's see.
Oops.
Party.
Home.
Am I logged in?
Probably not.
Maybe I can see you.
Are you like in the game?
Oh, there we go.
I think I can just add you.
What's your name?
Stixon.
All right.
There you go.
Did you get it?
You should have got it, right?
Yes.
But I don't see you in the party list here.
Yeah, it just it said I got an invite
but there's not actually like an accept invitation button.
Can you join off me?
It doesn't even say that you're playing Mordhau.
What?
Can I join you?
When's this game coming out to the Epic Game Store?
Just wondering.
What?
Oh, hold on.
Can I leave party now?
I don't think I can.
Yeah, I'm online.
I'm appearing online.
Should be.
Invites do not work.
Oh.
Well.
Invites don't work.
So like if I invite you, what does it say?
It says you invited me to play a hit play game
and I can't join you.
I just probably pressed it.
So, so we can't play together.
Is that what you guys are saying?
We have to find a server browser and join the same server.
Oh, that's that.
That's minus a full etiquette.
I think we're on the bad.
Okay, but that means that people can like come get us.
Isn't it?
Because they'll know what server we're in.
Isn't that like, isn't that the streamer thing?
We put on like a three minute delay and put a fake name on.
Hold on.
Server browser.
Rent a server is down here.
All right.
Server browser.
Are you getting anything in the server browser?
I'm not getting anything in the server browser.
The rent a server button works.
One availed by a server.
Okay.
How do we not full has players and no password?
They're official servers yet?
Game mode.
We should probably just do death match, right?
Yeah.
I hit refresh.
Let's see.
There you guys can see.
See, I'm kind of just sitting here.
Oh, there we go.
All right.
Real questions.
Is this game early access?
Uh, I don't, I don't know.
Is it, uh, there's his official death match.
Los Angeles with only one slot though.
Uh, all right.
So these, these mean that they're official servers.
All right.
I'm going to, okay.
I'm going to, I'm going to mute everything.
And I'm going to tell you the server.
Server browser works now.
Yeah, I can see it now.
Well, it don't, it don't even matter.
It doesn't matter what server people know we're going.
Cause there's only 16 people allowed anyways.
There's only like five that we're going to be able to choose from in the first place.
All right.
So we're going to whatever.
I don't matter.
We're going to sort by name.
We're going to.
Yeah.
So if I ping, I can't click any of the sort buttons.
No.
Uh, well let's just, well, it was fun playing with you.
That was really good coffee experience.
Glad you like asked me to play the Charlie.
Let's go.
Uh, there's, did you see this one?
Do you see the official U S West number eight?
I mean, there's nobody in there though.
There will be.
There's okay.
Official Dallas.
I'm going to find it before I can.
Do you see Dallas?
Official death match, Dallas.
There should be spots in there.
We don't have the greatest ping, but you know.
Well, what's the, what's the ping?
It's like a hundred.
Official team death match, Dallas or official death match.
Dallas is going to be full.
No, nobody's playing right now.
All right.
I'm going to give this like 30 more seconds
and then I'm just going to join a random server.
Yeah, that was, that was open.
Is it official death match?
Dallas.
Does Spina for it's like the high row can quick up.
I'm not going to be able to find it.
Uh, so all right.
There's no way to.
All right.
Wait, wait.
Okay.
We're, we're on the same internet.
So we have the same thing.
Tell me an exact ping for something.
And I joined.
Do you see the one with, uh, 65 ping Los Angeles.
Official death math.
Watch inches Phoebe five.
Okay.
Uh, 65 Phoebe.
See which, which one Los Angeles Phoebe.
I see Los Angeles, the mirror, Los Angeles, the Lhasa.
All right.
Well, I'm just going to, I'm going to play.
Yeah, I don't blame you.
It's not, uh, anyone's fault except the game
that the matchmaking doesn't work.
How do we not see the same one?
It's what's with this video game, the Lhasa.
Did you see Dallas Lhasa?
Go click it quick.
No, it's full.
It had like a few spots.
All right.
We'll just, um, I'm going to mute everything
and we're just going to talk.
Ready?
Oh, let me view you here.
All right.
Well, we're going to get this figured out.
I know.
Like, uh, I couldn't get like the surfer browser to come back.
So we're kind of just, we're just going to queue up the server browser.
Like wouldn't come back.
Let's try it again.
So Talix is no longer with us.
We will try again later because like this seems to work.
We can't see the same servers.
And when we try to join them, when I last tried to do that, it, I got errors.
It was like error.
Could not join.
And I was just trying to refresh the list.
I would sit there for like 20 seconds.
It wouldn't do anything.
Should have set this up before the stream.
I did.
I mean, I don't know.
The server is going to have problems right now.
Right this second.
How am I supposed to know that?
What's the date?
What's the default FOV?
Let's find out.
I have it at 90.
Should be more.
This is not going to count for points, right?
Should do a hundred.
A hundred might make me puke.
No, 95 is fine.
Yeah, this is too, this is, this is already, if I go more than this, I'll have a problem.
Yeah, when, when FOV is too high, it actually kind of sucks.
Because every time you turn, it's almost like you're looking through a telescope.
Sub 180.
How many players are here?
High ping and packet loss.
Uh-oh.
We may have hit the wall of playing a new game on the internet.
How new is this?
Didn't this come out like a week or two ago?
When did it come out?
Yesterday?
Oh, I forgot.
God damn it.
I forgot.
Any video game that releases for the first three days doesn't work.
God damn it.
My mistake is you got to wait for the first like week and a half to go by
from the, to patch the game three times.
And then you can play the game.
All right, I think we're starting.
You know what a game company should really do?
And maybe they do this, but who knows?
Do people do this?
Let me, let me ask you a question.
So if you had a video game that was releasing,
why wouldn't you just rent like an absolute shitload of servers?
Like too many, like a joke amount for like five days.
And then just turn them all off.
Just rent like an absolute dumb amount of servers for a month
and then just turn them off.
And then reduce it down to like the amount that you want.
All right, here we go.
That cost money though.
Yeah, I know.
Let's like, I'm not talking, this is not just like an independent studio thing.
This happens with like, does that, this happened with like Anthem too, didn't it?
I might be making that up.
Even AAA studios have the same problem.
All right, I'm gonna, this guy's fucking dead.
No, I'm just saying a triple, all right.
I'm gonna kill this guy with my bare hands.
No, I'm not, I'm gonna run away.
I'm gonna, I'm just gonna break my legs.
Shit, no, I don't have to, I don't have to read the queue now.
God damn it.
No, I was like, ah, I'm so fucking mad.
I just want to play.
All right, I'm gonna pick the other game mode then.
Use the server browser.
I just tried and I got errors trying to use the browser.
This is a pretty good menu stream so far.
Breathe Arnold.
So I guess just don't queue for BR.
My god, you gotta talk to Chad about Sam and Max.
Yeah, I'm gonna finish it, don't worry.
I, this is a fun game though.
Fuck.
Okay, come on, show me something.
God, okay, I don't even care what it is.
Just let me play, right?
Okay, don't give me an error.
They gave me an error last time.
Oh my god, it's not full.
Oh my, I can't believe it.
Let's go.
Huntsman.
Now don't die immediately.
I got a cleaver too.
This is actually, this is exactly what I'd want as a weapon
if I was in a medieval time.
All right, is the way they're coming in through here?
Is that a magician?
I, I hit that guy right in the head.
No, I can't, give me my cleaver.
So are we defending a point or is it just team death match?
Is it friendly fire?
Ooh, see ya.
Oops.
No, there's no friendly fire.
Oh wait, doesn't look like they can have archers on the other team.
I'm going up.
Help this guy out.
Oops.
Do they have any archers up?
Right there.
Oh, shit.
This guy's just wildly swinging.
I don't have any more, my bow is gone.
Did he knock the bow out of my hands?
Somebody said that guy is the headless ape swinging.
Oh shit.
I can do better than that.
Crazy man with cleaver charges into battle.
Guy's almost dead.
We're getting overrun.
I hit my teammate right in the head.
I'm going in.
No, get up here.
Oh, almost.
I helped that dude out.
Guy crossed the way here right there, right in the head.
Bang.
God damn it, he moved.
The archer's so much fun.
Okay, I'm going to try something else.
How about knight?
This is just standard battle.
Stream sniped.
See, I told you.
Why'd you hit me?
Are you stream sniping me?
That guy just stream sniped me and he's on my own team.
See, look, this guy's stream sniping.
I'm going to fucking kill the stream sniper, watch this.
Oh, look at you.
Oh, you got the stream open?
No, it's not a stream sniper.
Another stream sniper.
Welcome to VR.
Well, this isn't VR as it's just sticking around.
Here we go, one on one.
Don't hit me from...
Oh look, I'm not a stream sniper, huh?
You can't just run in there swinging and hitting walls, man.
Oh my god.
Shit, I got too many people there.
Dude, imagine that's how you die.
You'd probably still be alive for a second, right?
No, I don't think you would.
New class?
No, no, no, hold on.
Not yet, not quite.
Watch out.
Shit, where'd he go?
Is there a way to heal?
Oh fuck, he just ducked under it.
This is fucking fun.
You passively regen when you don't use stamina, okay.
This is like a combination of chivalry and for honor.
This is fucking fun.
This is actually a lot of fun.
I'm glad I get to play it.
I'm gonna do some more techniques here, man.
Like for instance, this stream sniper over here.
Which one of these stream snipers should I go after?
This guy right here.
It's not that long.
God damn it.
It's actually kind of hard to hit somebody in the back if they're running.
Because you have to take this time to swing.
That guy had a smaller weapon.
But where did I just go?
If he was doing it to me?
Yeah, because he had like a little knife.
All right, I'm gonna make up for it right now.
I'm taking this guy's head off.
Oh, that wasn't a parry.
Somebody's behind me too.
Fuck.
Not good.
All right, let's try a raider.
This guy's got a huge axe.
I'm not gonna run in this time.
I'm gonna stay back.
It's too fun just to try to go and take somebody's head off though.
That guy just threw an axe at me.
This guy's throwing weapons.
That guy's throwing maces and shit.
All right, I'll take care of this.
Nice.
Good job.
This guy ain't not paying attention.
Not paying attention.
Free head.
Damn it.
Wasn't enough damage.
Fuck.
No.
I have throwing axes, do I?
Oh shit, I do.
Okay.
What just hit me?
What?
I just fall back.
I just fell down.
I just tripped.
Are you coming down here?
All right, fine.
I'll come up there to you.
You're gonna be dishonorable?
You're gonna let me up?
Fine, I'll put the axe away.
Let's go.
Is it?
Oh, no, no.
There's another guy.
Get him.
I'm distracting him.
Hey, who did that?
I just got sniped.
Like there's an actual sniper rifle up there in the kill feed.
I love this.
This is so...
Oh man.
All right, first time ever getting to really play.
That was awesome.
Reminds me of Fistful of Frags.
It does.
It really does.
It's like Fistful of Frags.
For honor and chivalry.
It does have that Fistful of Frags feel.
You're right.
Uh, let's stay on the same team.
Why not?
What about protector?
So I'm like the shield.
I have to stay out in front of everybody, right?
Smoke bomb?
This is Dark Souls.
The Dark Souls guy, yeah.
Let's go.
I will be your shield.
And my bow.
And my axe.
Why is there not voice chat?
I want to have people scream memes in my face.
Um, speaking of people screaming memes in my face.
What is that sound?
Oops, no longer the shield.
Sorry.
Okay, this guy's just like Saitama.
Why is he winning?
It shouldn't be happening right now.
Damn it.
Got him.
All right, all right, all right.
Oh, all right.
Who is it?
Eat shit.
Um, did I just kill somebody?
I think I just killed somebody with the firework.
That was a bad idea.
Oh, no.
Was that a bad guy?
I couldn't tell in the smoke.
I just, I just Stephen, I just Stephen King to that guy.
They made a movie about what I just did.
Hitting somebody right in the face.
Let's do it again.
No, I don't have any more.
No way.
Somebody killed this fucking guy.
It's a frying pan.
Stop playing the guitar.
All right, that's the only death I've had the whole time.
Let's go.
Oh, it's you doing that.
I don't feel bad about that.
Am I going to get banned for what I'm doing?
Look, he's clearly being a nuisance.
Okay.
Clearly being a nuisance.
I don't get points taken down for that.
That guy was a nuisance.
Let me go in front.
Let me get in front.
Damn it.
I don't know.
Okay.
I look like such an idiot right now.
Come here.
Damn it.
All right, I'm going to change class.
Uh, what is, uh, Brigand?
Uh, Footman?
Scoundrel?
Engineer?
I'm going with veteran.
He's taunting?
All right.
Yeah, I was gonna say that's not a good idea for you to taunt right there.
See ya.
I'm going for an overhead smash right in this guy's head.
Damn it.
Too many.
Oh, here we go.
What does he get?
So he's got Evening Star.
This thing is huge.
Wow, that does a lot.
It's brutal.
Oops, sorry.
Oh, shit.
Fuck.
Oh, he fucking just baited me so hard.
I thought he turned around and ran.
I thought he was, I looked like he was turning around to run.
Look at the big chunk missing.
Watch out.
Naked guy.
Naked guy with the pan.
Oh, this is bad.
This is really bad.
Oh, fuck.
Nope.
Dude, I always have to get like, it's always like a 4v4v.
Aw, team stack.
Scramble the teams.
Yo, you idiot.
Get up.
Oh, God.
I'm team killing.
So is he.
He's arguably killing more teammates than I am.
What do you mean no?
He's like standing in the way and, oh, my fucking God.
I'm gonna go to, let's go Huntsman again.
Damn it.
You're not gonna T-back me in my own stream?
Fuck, he did.
The loot gives health.
Oh, I thought he was just like doing a taunt like command.
A little chip damage, not a big deal.
Uh-oh, here they all come again.
Watch out.
Pick up your sword.
Okay, good.
Oh, I didn't get him in the head.
Get out of here.
I get it.
Right here, right in the head.
Damn it.
Almost.
Oh, boy.
Gotta make the shots count.
The shots gotta count.
Didn't count.
Get.
What is he doing?
Oh, he's just stream sniping.
That's what he's doing.
Did he block that?
He's blocking the arrows.
Damn it.
Did it not hit him?
Sounded like it hit him.
Damn it.
I thought the guy was still next to me.
Oh, I wanna go, I don't know.
I haven't done this yet.
You definitely wanna do a lot of stabs with this.
Don't get baited out.
They're trying to bait us.
All right, this guy too.
Oh, that's a lot of reach.
This thing is nice.
Shit.
Watch out for this guy.
Oh, come on.
Spears are the best weapons.
Oh, medic bag.
Do I have to touch people with this
or do they just get healed if I near them?
How'd you get to the side?
Just drop it over here.
I only get one.
All right, so it's just behind here.
Well, I thought they were gonna be fighting here.
This way, doctor.
Kind of.
You can buy weapons and customize a character.
Really?
That's actually really awesome.
Nice.
That was a good backswing.
Good job.
Why is the guy with the pants so good?
Oh, fuck.
There's somebody here.
So it's currently bugged right now?
That's okay.
I see.
Parry.
Oh, damn it.
What?
How did I not?
I don't like it.
Who have I not?
What item have I not used?
Try this.
Oh, a zweander.
What?
All right, watch out.
What do I have for a...
Oh, I have this too.
I have a shortser.
That's good.
That'll come in handy.
The Nintendo's zweander?
I'm gonna die in one hit.
It was one of those medical sandbags.
I need one.
There we go.
Oh, we win.
64-person server.
Should I try to get the 60?
That'll be absolute chaos.
All right, I'll go for it.
What do I...
Server browser.
All right, that's not quit game.
That's a...
That's not quit...
That's quit game.
Does that take me to the menu?
Or does that quit out?
Okay.
Some of these games just boot you out to the...
They take you out of the whole game.
I'll try like a huge one.
You're gonna regret that, probably.
But it's all good.
Customized gear.
I don't think I can, right?
It's a bit messed up.
Isn't it broken?
I don't have any money.
I'm not even getting currency.
New mercenary.
Zweander.
Head.
I'm gonna...
I'll put peasant hair on.
That sounds good.
Torso.
No, that's too easy.
This one.
Peasant, sure.
I'm just gonna be a peasant.
I'm just...
I'll be really unassuming.
Okay.
Legs.
Workers.
Shorts.
Pants.
That's fine.
All right.
Gear.
Equipment.
Oh.
Cost of point.
Yeah, I don't...
I can't do any of this.
I'm not getting any currency.
Yeah, customization does not work right now.
Okay.
Well, that's all right.
That's all good.
I had 15?
I thought that I couldn't do it.
Everyone just said it was down.
For instance, okay, like dagger, right?
Yeah, progression doesn't work.
Oh, god damn it.
Did I just spend those or can I...
Okay, wait, okay, okay, okay.
Peasant.
Okay.
Why would that be a perk?
What does that do?
Crouch movement speed.
Cat.
Friendly.
I like that one.
Ranger.
Scavenger.
Dodge.
That's actually really good.
Brawler.
Might as well just...
Wreck structures, repair.
And bows, crossbows, and throwables deal more damage
against enemies carrying the quiver.
Stimina on kill increased by...
That's good.
And we'll do fists.
Why not?
Peasant does not do anything.
Well, why would it be eight points?
Gain full health on a melee kill.
Yeah, why would I not just select this?
And then, like, fury.
And instantly start sprinting upon killing an enemy.
Gain three extra stamina on hit.
That's good.
Friendly fire reduction.
Fine, I'll do rat.
It's because I have to.
And then, fatal melee and projectile damage
except a headshot does not kill you immediately.
Sure, why not?
And then, that's it.
Okay, so that's it.
But he doesn't have any items.
What does he have?
He doesn't have anything.
He has no equipment.
I can't unlock this.
None of these can be used.
He's just gonna be fists.
Well, then I have to...
Well, then I have to take that off and go like that.
All right, that's fine.
I'm ready to go.
So we're looking for a high.
I get 64, 48.
Okay, let's do 48 first.
You know what I'm saying?
You know, I'm not gonna do 64.
Right off the bat.
All right, this one.
There's a lot of people here.
I have to choose my spawn point.
Oh dear.
Capture the enemy flags.
What?
That probably looked so funny on their screen.
That's why he's called this way, Ender.
For this exact purpose.
What does he got?
No, I'll keep this.
Whoa, fire bomb.
Fuck, what was I thinking?
Get this health over there.
No!
From where?
From behind?
I'm gonna do a couple more times with this useless character.
And I'm gonna go from there.
Get a horse.
Enemy is capturing the rafters.
Well, stop them.
This guy's just laying out everybody.
Give me that thing.
I'm gonna use my rat skills by crouching.
I got 20% more crouch power.
Jesus Christ.
What?
By what?
Did I get my head cut off?
All right, I wanna do...
Let's go with like an actual character here.
All right, we took the rafters back.
Good.
Try engineer?
Oh yeah, that's right.
Okay.
I will.
All right, let's stay together.
What's that thing?
Stay together or die alone?
Some video game had that for a tagline.
It was a great tagline.
Was it Vermintide?
Was it?
Oh, that guy's on their team.
What?
He took my arm off.
Oh god damn it.
What?
I'm covered in plate armor.
He took my arm off?
What?
Holy shit.
Oh, that's my perk.
Okay.
I get it.
That's funny.
He's trying to run away.
I love this shit, man.
People just whacking at the walls.
What is this guy doing?
All right, only a couple more.
Don't let up.
How do we lose?
We're standing here.
Surprise me.
Okay.
What if we weren't standing in the capture point?
Oh, reinforcement's okay.
I'm never gonna rank up.
I'll always be level one.
Let's go here.
I wonder if I get better.
I gotta like practice and get better.
I want to do the other game modes too.
All right.
I've played with everybody except the engineer.
So what does the engineer do?
Toolbox, loot, blacksmith, hammer.
So I can do this now.
Loot.
The hammer fixes the walls.
What does this do?
I put down walls for people to hide behind?
I guess.
Oh, I can put down spikes too.
All right.
Well, here we go.
Put the spikes down right here.
Um, I really don't.
I don't know.
Come on.
Hurry up.
All right.
See, we got like a strategic location here now.
Come here.
Come here with that horse.
Oh, I could have had a chance there with the hammer.
Get back here.
This is healing people, right?
Oh, look at this.
The internet is having problems.
Oh, I thought I could really take him off.
I'm gonna get him right here.
He doesn't even know I'm right.
He doesn't know I'm chasing after him.
I mean, it doesn't really matter.
It doesn't matter.
I'll get him right here.
Oh, what does this do?
Repairing?
I don't even know what I repaired.
What is the loot?
The mandolin?
It's, uh, I don't know.
I think it heals.
Build a stables.
Do I have to do that?
Oh, fuck.
Hold on.
This is a bad guy, right?
It is an enemy.
Kill him with the horse.
Get him.
Kill him.
He's can't.
You can't let him get away.
God damn it.
I'm not even paying attention.
I hit him off the horse.
Oh, what the fuck?
I don't want to be this guy anymore.
I feel like I don't know enough about the game to be useful.
We'll go back to Raider with the...
Look, I'm going to help a little bit here.
The horn!
The horn has been blown!
Whatever.
Just give me...
I want to be the Raider.
He's helping.
Not really.
Now I'm going to help.
Watch this.
If I don't get at least three kills here
and clean not assists me get the kill,
then bye bye Twitch channel.
That was mine.
And wait for it.
Wait for him.
I'll get him on the run and back.
I'll get him on the run around here.
He's going to come around here.
Watch this shit.
Here he comes around the corner.
He's going to wrap around.
Three, two, one.
No, never mind.
Oh, by the way, if the game lags out, it doesn't count.
One, two, three.
Oops, three.
That's mine.
He had the last stand thing.
I killed him.
This is mine.
Mine.
How is this guy still alive?
I told you to leave me alone.
Okay.
Does that negate the other one?
I think that negates it.
Oh shit.
Okay, run, run, run, run, run.
That doesn't negate it.
It doesn't negate it.
I win.
I got more than three.
I got four.
Oh my god.
This game is fucking bonkers.
That's four with a team kill.
So it was minus one, which means it's three.
He seriously just walked into it though.
How many people do you think back in medieval times
like fucking killed each other accidentally?
Think about this.
If there was a giant battle like this shit,
you're going to swing in a circle and you're going to hit five people.
Don't ever charge in with anybody.
Archer was where it was at.
You couldn't accidentally take off a friend's head with an axe.
Oh, that was pretty clean.
That one hit right there.
Oh shit.
Come on.
Oh, what's that?
How did that feel?
How did that one feel?
Dude, there goes your head.
All right.
I'm starting to get the hang of this shit.
Oh, that was a little delay.
This is pretty high.
All right.
Let's just let's get let's get back here.
That wouldn't be the guy's shield.
Oops.
Oh, this thrusting swords.
Is that me screaming?
What's the emotes?
Oh, the scoundrel loadout.
Okay.
I actually I should do that.
Let's try it.
Although I'm getting used to axe guy.
A lot of people coming up.
Oh, man.
That guy got killed by something.
I think that guy got trapped on here.
He's playing like G mod death run.
The guy like turned on the spikes.
Oops.
Sorry.
Oh, yeah.
That was team damage, but I killed somebody.
It's okay.
Oh, damn it.
Went in for a big hit there.
Where do you think you're going?
What was that guy doing?
There was no plan for that guy.
Oh, I walked into it.
Shit.
Saying sorry won't grow that guy's arms back.
That's true.
What the fuck?
What?
I must have got headshot by something.
Why are these guys?
What are you guys doing?
Guys, guys, guys.
All right.
We're going to have to quarantine this guy.
Excuse me.
Can we get a little help here?
This guy went rogue.
Oh, no.
He's been taken by the madness.
I kind of want to get in a horse
and just ride around like an asshole like that.
I thought there was a guy hiding.
Oh, damn it.
That guy would have been dead.
What?
Just what is killing me from behind?
All right.
I want to do.
Whoops.
Let's try scoundrel.
It's me.
Okay.
So what do you have?
I got fireball.
This is the guy that's like the magician.
Okay.
So what's the swings like?
A lot of thrusts, I would say, with this dude.
There it is.
All right.
Behind.
Oh, shit.
This guy ain't going to make it out alive.
No.
Right into my sword.
Come here.
Right into it.
Really?
What?
He don't go.
God, I don't care.
That was bullshit.
You've got to be kidding me.
He can't...
I...
I don't even need to say anything.
You guys already know.
You already know.
Swing.
What the hell?
What the...
Lag.
I tried to swing again.
Input.
Wasn't.
Done.
No input.
Oh, fuck.
I have an arrow in my arm.
What?
I was doing all right.
He's a stab spammer.
They're having server issues due to way more people playing it than expect...
I thought that guy was aiming from my head.
I need to use the fire bombs too.
Is that a...
Who's up there?
Is that a guy in red or blue?
I can't tell.
I think he's blue.
All right.
I'm going to put this down in a strategic location after I do this.
Oops.
Did I just step in my own trap?
I was too busy paying attention to what this guy was doing.
Oh my god.
Okay.
No more scoundrel.
I'm going back to Raider.
That guy distracted me too much.
That guy distracted me into another class.
What a god.
I'm going.
You know what?
I'll show you what I'm going to do.
You want to see how we do this?
How I would do this in a real war.
I'll show you real war Elbertson right here.
Oh, fuck.
There's two of them.
I'm just kidding.
This is not what I would do.
Is this the guy laughing at me?
There's too many.
That guy didn't come over and start distracting me into another class.
All right.
We're getting kind of destroyed here.
Press V.
That's pretty good.
All right.
I should be able to get this guy from behind here.
Play it smart.
This guy's distracted.
Oh, caught him.
What?
What happened to my sword?
My axe?
My...
Okay.
I think it's because maybe the packet loss removed it.
Ah!
Oh no, I'm stuck.
God.
Get it!
You little weasel.
Nobody can catch him.
He's taking down our defenses.
All right.
Pickle.
Just like in baseball.
You gotta be fucking kidding me.
You little rabbit.
We were just chasing that guy in a circle and nobody could catch him.
We were gonna pickle him and it didn't work.
All right.
I'm gonna start playing the game again because I was top five and I'm like in the bottom.
Okay.
They're in our fort now.
This is bad.
I got it.
Relax.
Everybody relax.
They're gonna drop down here.
Watch this.
He's gonna drop down, isn't he?
Drop down.
All right.
Well, I made the board shake so he fell.
What is going on?
What?
Ow.
Oh, there's a lot.
Never mind.
I somehow ended up back here and he ended up behind me.
I swung at that guy and then I teleported back and the guy was behind me and killed me.
What the heck?
No swear is here.
Only H-E-C-K.
They're gonna take it right now.
I'm trying to get this dude that's running behind.
Damn it.
Oh my god.
I helped him.
Wait.
That guy turned to dust.
How does that make it?
He said.
Oh, no, no, no.
He threw it.
Okay.
All right.
Get up on the battlements.
They're killing each other.
No, too many.
You're dead, man.
You can't be over there.
I gotta help them.
I'm going this way.
They're coming up here.
Scoundrel.
I'm taking his head off now.
You're not gonna get away with this shit.
Not this time.
Wrap around back.
Oh, this is bad.
They know.
Oh, kill the archer.
Kill the archer.
Oh, I had too many people behind me.
15.
Die to the archer?
No, I died to archer.
I finally got money.
You're talking about died to the eight people that were behind me.
Oh, I think that we cannot.
Is it gonna be good?
I like this game mode, though.
It's fun.
Progression seems to be working.
That's good.
Chase that paper.
I want to see what other weapons they have.
All right.
Who do I like?
I don't know.
They're all kind of fun to play.
We try archer again.
Unarmed or bust?
No, I'm not very good with unarmed.
Can we both get on?
There's many more weapons for you to customize.
That's awesome.
So we got our first.
Oh, that was a guy in VR chat.
I'm gonna go this way.
I think they're wrapping around over here.
Yeah.
Watch out.
Get off the horse.
Yeah.
Oh, fuck.
Help, help, help, help, help, help, help, help, help.
Oh, I'm dead.
I just ran in with the horse.
You've been hunted.
I'm gonna get a good perch.
Looks like we're right in the middle.
What's with all the swords there?
This guy's taking out everybody.
Really?
Come on.
He just took out three people.
This guy is killing everyone.
Oh my god.
I've done 50 something damage to him so far.
Did I kill him?
Jesus.
That guy was unstoppable.
Got him.
Damn.
I'm actually glad that the arrows are hard to use
because they're not.
Oh my god.
There's somebody up here.
It's hard to use the bow.
You got to be really, really precise.
But it kind of has to be like that
because otherwise it'd be really, really powerful.
It was really, really easy to use.
There's crossbows.
Are there?
That's interesting.
All right.
I got him.
I got to kill him right away.
Oh, fuck.
He threw a fly.
I'm just being a dickhead now.
All right.
Back to Raider.
I'm trying to do too many things.
Stay with one thing and do it well.
I'm jumping around too much.
Okay.
Let's go.
Bring out the knives.
Oh, I got him right in the head.
Shit.
All right.
This is bad.
I don't want to be on the bridge.
Bridge bad because I can do that.
Yeah.
Okay.
Well, is that...
Does somebody...
I didn't get team killed, right?
No, I did.
No, I didn't.
Can you cut the bridge?
You might be able to.
Maybe.
This guy is...
Needs to die.
I'm going to go straight on.
That hurts.
Is he alive?
He's alive.
Fuck.
I thought he was dead.
He went on the ground.
I was hoping I was going to catch somebody.
One of those.
Just right like in the face.
All right.
Not good.
I'm going to go.
Watch out for the fire.
When the fire goes, I'm going.
They're climbing up and in.
They're going inside.
They're up here.
They're already in.
Oh, shit.
That guy looked blue.
Look at how blue that guy looks.
I'm so sorry.
He looked blue in the shadow.
He did.
He really did.
Are they clear out of here?
Yeah.
We're good.
Nice.
He's almost dead.
Cleaved.
Oh, shit.
Bad.
I had a chance there.
Can you still do the overhead swing?
You can do this.
And then that's a little stab there.
The poke with the axe seems pretty bad.
Yeah, I would assume it would be.
Just try to change it up so they don't think
you're going to do the same swing every time.
I hit that guy right in the lip.
I busted that guy's lip.
I just gave a fat lip.
That's all I did.
Goodbye.
How that guy blocked so many hits.
What a fucking pro.
I ain't going to let you do that shit.
Sorry, dude.
No, somebody had to deal with you.
It might as well have been me.
Goodbye.
Huge cleave.
I love it.
Oops.
Hold on.
I'll help you here.
Oh, damn it.
I was trying to help.
We're going to kill each other in here.
All right.
With just too many of us in here.
This is bad.
That motherfucker is still alive.
Remarkably.
Okay, I'm going up this way.
We're going to push out of here.
Oh, dear.
They got a horse.
Where's he going?
He's all the way around.
He's going to wrap inside of here.
Where the hell did he go?
He keeps fucking team killing.
You fucking idiots.
That's not my team.
You can't blame that one on me, guys.
Not my team.
Oh, shit from behind.
Damn it.
I was going to look behind me, too.
Who knew this would get so heated in chat?
This dude's fucking team killing.
You fucking idiots.
Is there a way to shit from the front?
Oh, I see what you're doing here.
Damn it.
Fire sucks.
Did I get his leg off?
Holy shit.
I went backwards.
Was he hopping on one leg?
It looked like it.
Yeah.
All right.
Another string of legs.
Three, four in a row here.
I got to climb back up to like top five.
Come on.
I can't just be this bad.
I have to be good.
This is the first little area.
This is where it's contested.
You know what?
Is it...
Do I die if I go in the water?
I don't know if water's an instant kill.
All right.
Here's the conflict.
Watch from behind.
Who keeps team killing?
You fucking idiot.
Let's check in behind.
There's a person behind.
Is he still there?
Oh, you think you can escape me?
Oops.
Oh shit.
No.
I didn't...
I was locked in tunnel vision again.
Trying to hit that guy with an axe on the bridge.
Jeremy, you just team killed, you fucking idiots.
What?
Well, I don't want to hit them.
It's going to be the same shit to you, man.
Too many, too many, too many.
They're all...
Too many.
I got to get like...
Look at this ping.
Everyone's ping jumps up to like 400.
How many tickets do we need?
What are we playing until?
I'm sort of confused.
Is it like 1,800?
I really want to just dig in there.
Thank you.
That's what I wanted to do.
Just dig the fuck in.
No, fuck.
Oh, I'm so tunneled in.
I'm so tunneled in.
I just get...
All I think of is hit guy and face with axe.
I just...
Me swing axe.
Me do damage to face.
What about limbs?
No.
What about throw the axe?
Only damage in face.
Only.
You're an idiot.
Okay.
Me only damage in face.
Me run.
Is that guy red?
Why is he blue?
He's got blue tint all over him.
Me hit.
Me don't care if team or not.
Me hit face.
Me miss.
Me not very good at game.
Me not understand how ping work
seemed like should have landed.
Me dead.
Ah.
No, stay...
What do I play?
Footman?
I don't know.
I just...
I'm so excited.
Hey, can you stop hitting teammates?
No.
Why?
It's not that hard.
We have different...
Everyone's a different...
We're the same color.
Red.
Yes.
Okay.
Me hit red.
No.
I don't want you to hit red.
Me go for blue.
I try.
Well, try harder, stupid.
Okay.
Hey, don't do that.
What?
I'm fucking confused.
Good thing he...
Don't do the joke play.
I had an opportunity there.
I had an opportunity to kill two, three people in a row.
I got a medic bag.
All right, let's give some poke.
Poke, poke, poke.
Find the opportunity.
Don't get involved in a situation
where you're going to get yourself killed.
Take it easy.
That's...
Okay.
I just stepped into the bonfire.
What was that guy?
That guy was holding his weapon the other way?
Oh, right.
Okay, that was confusing the fuck out of me.
Can I do that?
What does that do?
Does every weapon have, like, a different way to hold it?
I don't think so.
Most of them do.
Okay.
So now it makes it...
Stab.
Really?
How did that not land?
I'm trying to kick him off the fucking edge.
Did I?
What happened?
I think he fell off.
I did.
I did what I wanted to do.
Yeah, he's dead.
He's dead.
Get the horse?
I feel like there's only one horse, and it only spawns...
We have one horse.
Oh, he had the five second life perk.
I did kill him, though.
That guy's coming in so much blood.
All right.
Let's pick...
Oh, come on.
Really?
Why the fuck am I so focused?
These huge, huge player battles...
My brain.
It's just...
I get locked into one thing for more than one second, and I'm dead.
Let's go knight.
When there's 50 people on the battlefield, I'm just like,
wait, what about this guy up there?
Oh, he's dancing.
Oh, that's fun.
And then I'm dead.
Hit ah?
Do ah?
All right.
I will.
I'm trying to just do not...
It's so easy to hit somebody in the head you don't want to hit.
All right.
I helped.
Ooh, got them both.
Ooh.
All right.
Give me that.
Whoa.
All right.
We're clearing them out.
Hey, don't do that.
Right into my trap that I didn't lay.
Archer.
Oh, that was delayed.
What?
I'm...
Okay.
That was odd.
Of course I...
Okay, of course I get hit.
I'm the one that takes the one hit in the head and dies.
I'm actually pulling it back.
It always happens to me.
It never happens to anybody else.
It only happens to me.
It's not fair.
Like, this guy doesn't have to deal with high ping.
Only me.
Okay.
This is a bad idea.
You're running into me.
Oh, god damn it.
I'm just like in the worst place at the worst time, apparently.
Oh, now I'm trapped in here.
This is not a place I want to be.
Too many bodies.
Anybody know what killed me?
That wasn't an arrow.
It was a mace.
Like a mace.
That's a team damage.
What are you doing here?
No, no, no, no, no.
Oh, god damn it.
It's just such a mess.
Oh, sorry.
Sorry.
It was just medieval times.
It just happens.
I'm getting up there.
Somebody hit that guy.
I'm gonna fucking throw an axe at this guy.
Oh, he just moved at the fucking worst time.
He died.
He fell.
It's okay.
I've done it before, too.
Fuck, too many.
How are we still ahead?
I think the axe is my favorite weapon.
The bow is my favorite weapon, but I can't use it because I'm not good enough.
And I've accepted that.
Jesus Christ.
Jesus, man.
What, do I have a target on my back?
There's like four people.
It was like four of us standing there.
Upset because angry.
Mad because bad.
Bad because bad.
He blocked him.
He's blocking me.
We're just throwing rocks at this guy.
What?
All right.
This guy's gotta go.
Where is he?
Does that person...
That person had...
Wow, how did you do that?
How did you do that?
You have to have like eight arms with like three different mice to do what he just did.
He has like four keyboards.
Watch out for the archer.
Okay, good.
Charge.
I need health.
Okay.
All right.
I just got sacked.
I'm the fucking quarterback and the guy just sacked me.
What?
A meltdown stream.
No, I just hiked the ball.
It was 10 defensive linemen there.
Offensive linemen.
And he got through them and he sacked me.
All right, I want to do a different game mode.
Oh, I'm sorry.
Yeah, I want to make a class.
Room temperature IQ rants about game mechanics.
That was a 500 ping server.
I'm not going to let that hurt me because no fucking way.
I can't believe it.
You have it like people jumping in front of you and killing you.
You jump up to 650 ping.
Now, you just got a room temperature IQ.
Out of here with that.
I can hear that.
Whatever.
I don't care.
One point.
Okay, it's 16 points.
IQ test stream.
No, I'm just fucking around.
I'm not mad.
I'm just fucking around.
I can't unlock this?
Why?
Two points.
Don't I have 16 points?
I don't have it unlocked.
Oh, okay.
So I don't have anything unlocked.
So I can't make a custom class unless I do nothing.
Fists.
Restart the game.
Okay, try that.
Mortal.
Let's try it again.
I'm sorry.
That was a lot.
It was too easy.
What are you talking about?
I already did that too.
That's unfortunate.
All right, can I?
No, can I?
There we go.
Okay.
500 gold to buy.
How much money do I have?
1120.
300 for a dagger.
Wooden mallet cleaver.
Primary.
Training sword.
Really?
You can use a wooden sword?
Quarter staff.
Arming sword.
Damage, speed, and reach.
I think I want this thing.
A little one-handed little...
I'm getting it.
Arming sword.
Secondary.
I want...
Oh, there's actually a lot of stuff here.
Wow.
Long sword?
No.
I had something small.
I need like a little secondary.
One two-handed.
One-handed shield.
Shield.
Maybe I should get a little shield.
A little targe.
I think I'm gonna get this.
And then a tertiary.
Bandage.
Quarter staff.
Training sword.
Fire bomb.
Maybe I should get the fire bombs.
Get the loot.
Rock.
I don't need to see anything else.
Okay.
Body.
Fat.
Okay.
Armor.
I don't have any more money.
I could make myself look like a total dickhead.
That's what I'm going for here.
I can't get anything else.
All right.
Shoulders?
No.
I have not enough money.
All right.
So then body, face, and voice.
Perfect.
This is just Geralt.
Whatever.
Facial hair.
All right.
So this is...
What?
You can...
I can actually do this?
Holy shit.
Wait a minute.
Guess it's not that big of a deal.
It's not that huge.
Five hours in.
We're at the character creator.
Okay.
That's fine.
So we have you.
I need to edit you.
We need to do skills, right?
Where's the skills?
And they're like perks there up here.
All right.
So a friendly fire reduction.
Absolutely.
Extra stamina on hit.
Full health on melee kills.
And reduces fire damage by 80%
because I walk in it all the time.
I think they're ready.
There's better armor for free.
Oh.
There is.
But it costs one point.
I think it's all right for now.
There's more free armor.
Chainmail.
Oh.
What level am I?
Two.
I can do chainmail, but it's two points.
So that means I have to remove...
These are very important
because I'm fucking terrible.
You're wearing a hospital gown.
All right.
I'll get it.
Metal tint?
Oh, that's cool.
Hospital gown.
Okay.
Let me see.
That's all I can do.
Chainmail.
Legs.
I don't need them.
I'm ready to fight.
Fight.
Should I do battle royale again?
Try BR again?
Horde mode.
Let's try.
I'm gonna try BR again.
I know.
I don't want to watch you do battle royale.
You fucking wanker.
Relax.
What is horde mode?
Oh.
It's probably just survival.
I think you're the one that needs to relax.
No, I'm fine.
You relax.
How about we all collectively relax at the same time?
See?
Don't you feel better?
You fucking relax.
And no, you relax.
Yeah, you relax.
Check my emails while we hang out here.
I'm just gonna read you the first email that I have in my inbox.
It's from JetBlue.
It's talking about how there's sale right now for airfare, I guess.
Interestingly enough, this is just my first email.
Okay.
I'm not kidding around.
First email, almost.
You still use email, but you don't have an email?
How do you not have an email?
How do you get a bunch of stuff you don't want to open, a bunch of trash?
How do you go to a retail store and give them your email so they leave you alone?
You want to sign up for rewards?
Sure.
Who cares?
Guys, I have like, I'm pretty sure I have like 44,000 unread emails.
And I would say probably 80 to 90% of them are like coupons from Whole Foods.
Overhead swing.
Ooh, a little jab.
I didn't think I was gonna do that.
Who's next?
That was mine.
Did you sign up for the stupid rewards programs?
Yeah, but jokes on them.
I don't even open the email account.
You know, jokes on them.
They probably go to their email and they see that I haven't opened it.
This guy won't open anything.
What the fuck?
Because don't open it because then they'll know.
Their little read receipts will be on.
What am I doing?
Um, can I, can I run?
Is he dead?
No, stop rubber banding me around.
That's a loud and scary noise.
Well, I got on a horse and punched somebody and then I ran in place for five seconds.
That was a rage quit?
No, it wasn't.
I got kicked out.
All right, try this one more time.
VR sucks.
Yeah, but that's, come on.
That's going to get me the views.
I would turn my webcam on and show you.
I was going to get me the fucking views, but dude, I have no clothes on.
All right, here we go.
I'm going to actually give it an attempt this time.
No face cam, no views.
Do I have arrows?
Oh shit, he has the same thing.
Got plenty of arrows.
Someone's going to drop down around behind me or something.
I hear somebody.
All right, I gotta move.
Got a crossbow as well.
I've never even used the crossbow.
Is it good?
Huh?
That's such a scary fucking noise.
They need to turn that down.
I think that's an arrow hitting right next to my head.
Okay, I gotta go back to the bow.
No, what the fuck?
Battle Royale.
You watch another streamer do it.
They won't be hard to find.
Trust me.
Did I just have somebody coming back?
Hey, dude.
I knew you said I could go find another Battle Royale stream.
I couldn't find one.
I searched.
I was down on the browse and the category list.
I didn't find anyone playing Battle Royale.
Are you sure?
Maybe that you were just speaking out of tone there.
That's what I would do if I was like a troll in chat right now.
I'd be like, hey, dude, I couldn't find anybody playing VR.
Could you play it again?
What's Battle Royale?
Just the word Royale makes me sad.
It shouldn't.
I don't think anyone's playing this mode.
Well, all right, let's try the actual browser.
Oh my god, what happened?
I think it started.
Check your emails in the meantime.
All right.
Arming sword at 60.
Oh, I see.
This is cool.
Bandage.
Maybe she got a bandage.
Wave one.
How easy is it to kill things?
How did you get a knife?
Where do they pour?
Is it just default enemies that you have to kill?
No, we're just playing Cod Zombies now.
Kind of.
I see them.
Don't go too far.
Is that an enemy?
Are we just?
All right.
Where are the enemies?
Do we have to go looking for them?
Are they just scattered around?
They don't like come in the same place, it seems.
The rock killed stinky rat.
Oh, they got in.
They got in.
The farmers got in.
This is great.
God.
Can I get his weapon?
All right, we did it.
How much money we got?
34.
All right, give me a weapon.
This side is 90.
Damn it.
Light legs, bandage, light helmet.
No, I need a sword.
God damn it.
Where's their weapon?
Over here.
Ammo, toolbox, chest.
This one's 50.
What about inside here?
Bear trap?
No.
I'm not picking up any of that.
Buy a sword?
Yeah, I mean, I bought a rock.
Rusty fork.
I really don't have enough.
Rock OP.
Yeah, I'm just going to hit people in the face of the rock.
Do I have to throw it?
Does it throw?
Yeah, it does.
Got him.
We got two more.
Fuck.
Oh, that somehow got me.
I got a rock.
I'm dead.
I'm dead, I'm dead, I'm dead, I'm dead.
What, he got me with the backswing?
He went all the way back?
Buy a sword?
I don't know.
I don't even know where they are.
Where are the weapons?
They're just randomly kind of scattered out.
There's like a dagger over here in this tent.
There's a bear trap in there.
Nothing in there as chests over here.
Rock at the fire.
All right, I'm going to go in here and get the dagger.
It's near the spawn.
So like back here.
Ye olde no sword.
Well, here they are.
I can't afford them.
There's those two.
Where's that dagger?
I can get a chest.
Is it worth getting a chest?
I'm going to try it.
Oh, nice.
I got something to peel fucking apples with.
Anybody need a potato peel?
Well, that's what I can do with this.
Just throw it into the darkness.
This thing is so tiny.
How am I going to kill anybody with this?
What?
Oh, get away from me, please.
Oh my goodness.
Well, I didn't do the worst.
Uh, I want to play the actual game.
I want to play the actual video game against other players.
It's BR.
No, it's not.
All right, I'm going for it.
Out of 64.
There we go.
What is this?
Game mode?
Is this protector?
Do I have to wait till another game starts?
How much is the game?
It's like 26, 27 right now, right?
Oh, it's only one life per round.
Damn.
All right.
How did that guy?
That guy fell off and grabbed the ledge and didn't fall.
That was incredible.
It's like red has the upper hand.
Not really though.
Turn around.
Everybody has tunnel vision.
It's so easy to get tunnel vision in this game.
It seriously is.
No, you're dead.
All right, here we go.
Let's see how long I can last.
Watch out to your side.
Protector, get behind me.
Behind.
Nuh-uh.
Oh, that's what we call a double kill.
It's when you kill two people at the same time.
And I don't know if you've ever heard it before.
I have a little bit.
Oh, fuck.
Oh, I was the only one left.
I would say it was 1 v 10.
That was ridiculous.
I thought tunnel vision, 2.0.
I didn't even know I was the last person left.
Oh, I thought I could catch him.
Let's fuck the whole thing up.
Watch this.
No.
Yeah, not a fall joke.
It was actually fall.
Fucking god damn it.
No.
Why?
It's called disorienting.
Okay, blue team is so much better.
I don't think anybody on blue team died.
That's not fair.
You can't put the NFL team against the Pee Wee team.
What are you proving here?
What if you're gonna get two yards?
That's another football reference if you're counting.
It's been at least two.
Fuck, I'm dead.
I'm just getting fucking rolled.
Stay alive.
You can do it.
How many are left?
Come on.
There's only this.
I know you can do it.
My pregnant.
My girlfriend pregnant.
You can do it.
Get him.
Come out of AFT.
That's too bad.
There was an opportunity there.
We're getting so badly beat.
All right.
I gotta step it up here.
Come on.
Step it up.
Red team blows.
Hey, don't say that.
Good.
Push him back.
Just fucking killed it.
It's too much.
When we're getting beat this bad.
There's bound to be some cows.
I gotta change class.
I'm gonna go, I'm gonna go Raider.
He pushed him into me and I hit him right in the face with a swing.
But when we're losing this badly, there's only, look.
Oh, I thought that was the girlfriend guy.
Are we gonna win?
Holy shit.
How did they?
Were they just sitting in the back?
How did you guys pull this off?
I can't believe we just won.
Wasn't there just a bunch of blue and not a bunch of red?
Is the strategy to be AFK?
Holy shit.
We actually did it.
Nice job, guys.
I think somebody's stuck inside of me.
Yeah, don't please.
Just don't shoot me.
Don't shoot me, dude.
Just he's trying to shoot me.
How did this even happen?
Somebody just killed one of us.
Just turn around and kill us, please.
Okay.
I don't know.
That guy wasn't even connected to us.
Got you.
Oh, that was an uppercut.
I had a chance.
Fuck.
Changing maps.
This is kind of fun.
This is fun.
I think the game is more addicting than chivalry.
Chivalry was a lot of fun.
All right, skirmish, team deathmatch.
Hold on, are we gonna do...
Does this mean it's 64 people or free-for-all?
No, okay.
Next day, Raider.
This game is a mess in comparison.
It's kind of fun that way, though.
That would have been a clip
that somebody would have saved if any of those had landed.
Hitmarker sound, yeah.
Oh, watch out.
Hello.
Who is it?
I think I just got shot in the back by the guy with the...
I'm in trouble.
There's so many here.
Oh, fuck.
Oh, my God.
Was it bear trap?
Oh, I thought I got shot from behind in the back of the head.
Am I a drumstick or am I a wingman?
Drumstick.
Oh, my fucking God.
You're putting this here to death.
It was there as a prank.
I got pranked by my own team.
That's what that was.
I've walked in...
Why is it in our spawn?
That's the question you should be asking.
Not did he walk in it, but why was it there?
You ever stub your toe on something?
You don't go, wow, he's literally blind.
Oh, my God.
So if a friend of yours stubbed their toe on a sofa
that's been in the same room for five years,
how many times have you done that?
What, you didn't know there was a sofa there?
Were you blind?
No, sometimes you just stub your toe on shit.
I do say that.
Well, you're mean.
Don't be so mean.
What the fuck?
Oh, my God.
What?
How did none of those hit anyone?
Statistically speaking, one of those had to have hit.
It's impossible to miss that.
No, it's not.
Never mind.
I was trying to parry it.
Easy.
I had to be right there.
Let's go up over the mountain.
Let's do a mountain run, first of all.
Second of all, it's really like playing the lottery
when you do that.
If you hit, it's fucking huge.
It's like a million dollars.
Okay, don't get stuck on the stairs here.
Damn it.
Oh, this is bad.
How many Mordhau montages are we going to get?
Depends on how good people are.
You got to get play by play.
I can't get play by play
because then I'll lose over and over again.
He came all the way back to the spawn.
Where?
He's still here.
I'm getting on the fucking horse.
Oh, my God.
That guy was reading the map.
Oh, my goodness.
That was a very quick match.
All right, I'm going to be my guy.
Stop team killing, you idiots.
I think I'll be all right with this.
I got rocks.
Okay, this is going to be the run.
This will be the round where I'm at least in the top five.
I'm going to try as hard as I can.
I'm seriously going to put everything into this.
Here we go.
That's a cool hammer.
This is the enemy spawn.
You can't go down in the enemy spawn.
Why?
It just kills you.
I love it.
He's dead.
I have an axe in me.
I just took the axe out of my body.
Oh, he killed me.
I got a little too close to the teammate there.
He just kind of elbowed me in the mouth.
It wasn't my fault.
People are going to say it was, but it was not.
The head.
Right in the window.
Coming up.
I'm going to kick him right in the face.
Whoever comes up here.
Easy.
Wait, wait, wait.
Don't, don't, don't, don't, don't, don't.
Don't go up there.
Wait for them to come up and we can helms deep them.
Then you see helms deep.
Then you see them when we lord of the rings.
Turn around.
You're going to get sniped.
He's coming up there right now.
Look.
We're going to helms deep this guy.
I told you.
Did you see the movie?
You got to watch out for that shit.
They ain't fucking around.
They really want to get up this ladder.
Can I throw this sword back at them?
Who's that?
Oh, they're coming in the other side.
I told you.
Apparently I told you.
Watch the back.
Watch it.
They're going to climb up the ladder.
Helms deep.
I told you guys.
You act like you've never seen any of these movies.
I'm going to start spamming voice chat as close to the mic as I can get.
Well, that didn't do anything.
I still don't have the drop down on how hard those rocks get thrown.
Watch out.
Don't backswing me.
I just back.
Okay.
Well, I did what he...
It's too chaotic.
There's too many people on this server.
He's dead?
He's not dead.
He's still alive.
Oh wait.
We both died.
Where am I on the chart?
I'm not even on the chart.
That's how you know it's not going well.
I got to kill some more people here.
Oh fuck.
Kick.
What?
Okay.
Why couldn't I kick?
I can kick now.
I was literally spamming this button.
Did I have no stamina?
Lord.
I spent all the stamina throwing rocks.
Well, I did hit that guy right in the face.
So it's worth it.
You can't kick with a ranged weapon out.
Oh, really?
I didn't even know that.
Good to know.
Every team I'm a part of loses.
Well, you could say that about all the other people on the team.
What?
They win sometimes.
There's almost 64 people in this server.
You're going to put it all on the one guy that's throwing rocks?
I need a better weapon than that.
I think it sucks.
I made him drop his lunch.
Oh, come on.
We were having a duel.
We're having a duel.
You can't.
Come on.
That's dishonorable.
Oh, this actually is just free-for-all, isn't it?
You goddamn opportunists.
You can't even.
You guys want to swing in a circle.
Who the fuck is this?
Is that Colonel Sanders?
Get Colonel Sanders out of here.
I thought I just had a shotgun.
That was my kill.
Oh, ow, ow.
You're going to club somebody?
No, I'm not.
Fucking 60 goddamn people here.
Watch this.
Want to see a real dickhead move?
I'm waiting for the spawn.
Where did you?
Just look at how far down I am.
I'm not even up there at all.
Oh, it didn't kill him?
How is that possible?
Get away.
I just turned into it.
AFK, AFK, AFK, AFK, AFK, AFK.
Come here.
There it goes.
See you later.
Oh, there's people just in every direction.
How did I end up like this?
Holy shit.
Uh-oh, uh-oh.
Come on.
I got to get at least...
This guy has 29 kills.
My goodness.
It's really just swing horizontally
until you take off somebody's head.
It's just a horizontal swing
until somebody's fucking head comes off.
We're just trimming each other's hedges.
That was fun.
This game's a lot of fun.
All right.
A couple more and then I want to make a new character.
I want to actually buy something.
Let's go red.
And this time...
Oh, I'm going to go scoundrel.
I like the little stab.
I like the little thrusties like this.
You just dash forward
and I'll test it on this guy's mouth.
Here we go.
Four, three, two, one.
Go!
Oh, nice block.
Sorry, guys, but you're all going to burn.
It's all about the dance.
Oops.
Oh, you've closed yourself in.
All right.
Who's left?
Guys, okay.
Well, if you're going to do that...
See you.
Just a little.
All it takes is just a little bit.
Who's left?
Up top?
Who's this one person left?
Oh, we won.
Nice job.
If somebody throws...
Look at those Fortnite gamers in the middle.
Yeah, you guys are in the wrong game.
I thought it was right there.
Easy.
Too many, too many, too many, too many.
Back it up.
I'm not that I could do about that.
I didn't put the trap down, damn it.
There they go.
Yeah, that's too bad.
It's just good to...
It's a people-watching game.
It really is.
Because this guy has no idea.
And now there goes his leg.
And there's his buddy, Archer2,
desperately trying to fight off.
That guy didn't even know that
there were five people around him.
He found out that this many people were here.
Not even one second ago.
Oh, getting some points there.
Easy.
Caught him right around the corner.
You did exactly what I thought you were gonna do.
Poking away.
Just a little bit at a time.
He has his...
That's 138 damage.
This guy, how much health does he have?
All right, just the Archer over here.
I'm gonna get accidentally hit by this.
Nice swing.
Just these guys over here and that should be it.
I thought it was gonna spin it around.
Help! Help!
Guys!
I don't want unnecessary death.
I need a weapon.
Who has a weapon on the ground?
Did we win?
What's going on here?
I'm not a coward.
I'm just trying to play my battles correctly.
Where is this person?
Hey!
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
Oh, there he is.
All right, not doing too bad this time.
Right in the corner here.
Right there, right when they turn around.
They're not even gonna see it.
I want to get a good fire bomb
right inside of there.
Right up back there.
I think I got hit by it.
I think I got hit in the head by an arrow.
Oh, a throwing axe?
From where?
I was inside the corridor.
Look at this bullshit.
This is such dog shit.
Dude, go run around the other side.
Run to the right.
There's another opening.
He wants to go in through here.
See, there he goes.
He's like, yeah, that's a good idea.
You're right.
See?
There you go.
You got an opportunity to maybe
hit the guy right in the back of the head.
All right.
Let's do...
I don't know.
Ah, shit.
Didn't do it fast enough.
Give me some ticks.
Come on.
No ticks?
Come on, bait him.
Come on.
Oh, you dick.
That was bad.
Shit.
I'm backed all the way up here.
I think somebody's a loot.
All right.
Well, let me see if I can sneak up behind one of these.
No.
No way.
Isn't a real safe way to go, huh?
I guess whoever decides to make the first mistake.
Like that.
Oh, fuck.
Get him.
What's this?
How does this guy in here?
What the fuck?
He just climbed in here.
I can't believe he got up there.
He climbed all the way up.
Free guard has won.
Well, that's just stupid.
Here we go.
I'm sorry.
It's not intentional.
Did he seriously come all the way back to kill me?
What the hell?
He just walked in a straight line and killed me in one hit.
No, I don't want to be that.
I'm going back to Raider.
Hey, I know I was shooting him, but where was all my friends?
All right, let's get a good cinematic view of this.
We're following the archer.
They're not your friends.
We're fighting for the same thing.
Our leader wants the crown.
We're all on the same team.
We all go to the same ale house together.
We're not friends, though.
How?
There's like 1,500 of us in the whole fucking city.
You don't think you know everybody here?
They talk about you behind your back.
There's a difference between a co-worker and a friend.
We all probably work on the same farm.
It's probably the same damn family.
All these guys came from the same like five people.
You want to know the history of the universe?
30 people all had sex with each other.
And then that's how we got to 10 to 11 billion people.
It just kept going.
All right, give me my...
No, I don't...
What the hell?
I picked Raider, didn't I?
I don't want to do archer again.
I'm not very good at it.
Jeremy, I don't know what sex is.
Someone will tell you eventually.
Huntsman hallway.
Can I take out my cleaver?
Honestly, why?
I'm starting him mashing the number two and it will not take it out.
I'm just going two, two, two.
Don't.
No, I'm not taking it out.
No, no, no, no, no.
Nothing.
No.
I don't understand how sex caused 30 people to go to 7 billion.
Well, 30 people created 80 people.
80 people created 160.
160 created 380.
380 created 5,000.
5,000...
Those people were having a lot of sex.
5,000 created 8,000.
8,000 created 50,000.
50,000 created 200,000.
The plague happened.
Minus 100,000.
Those 100,000 then had to make up for it.
So they made a million.
Those millions spread across the entire earth and they had a bunch of sex and got it to like a billion.
And that was about like 80 years ago, 100 years ago.
That's just how it worked.
There was only a million people up until like 19, but like 18 fucking 60.
There was less than like 425,000 people in the world.
I'm not...
Okay, I'm going to pay attention because what number of person am I?
Probably like...
That's...
You know what?
That's what an interesting question.
That is such an interesting question.
I'm serious.
What person are you out of the, you know, 7, 8, 9, but 8 billion, right?
Like 6 billion, 254 million.
That's an interesting question.
Oh God.
Got you.
Got you right around the corner.
Gonna help you.
Coming in.
Oh my God.
There was two.
No.
Fuck.
Oh God.
I knew they were behind me.
Oh, they're everywhere.
Nothing.
Haven't done anything.
See, German, you know, you're on the losing team every time.
It's not, it has nothing to do with the guy holding his sword in his hand in the back
or the guy hitting him with the giant spoon.
But it's, it's my fault.
It's my fault.
That's the enemy team.
That's the other team.
Oh, well, I was on that team before.
I'm just getting the fuck in there.
No, I'm not.
It's so fun.
Just a whip shit.
We've got less people over here.
Oh shit.
Too many.
Oh, there's fire.
Look at all the fire everywhere.
Aye, aye, aye.
That's too many.
It's that they, how do we, how do they get so many back here so quickly?
It's like, seriously, there's two of them.
And then they have sex, and then there's fucking eight,
and then all of a sudden there's fucking 15,
and then there's 50 just standing around you.
See, this is, we need you on the front lines.
You're not going to make it.
They're not going to make it.
I can't believe you're making it.
This should never work.
The guy with the pole arm has killed I think six people so far.
Switch teams.
This game is really fun.
All you need to win a war is a stick with a pointy end.
We need a lot of those.
You need at least two to three hundred thousand of those.
If we were to talk about a scenario back in the medieval times,
it was, guys, you remember war back five hundred thousand years ago?
It was like, it was like maybe 80 people.
It was like 60 people versus 150 people.
Maybe there was like, it was like a thousand versus a thousand total.
There weren't very many people on earth.
Somebody said, I can't listen to this anymore.
Bye.
What's the truth?
Even people in the Roman age were 50k.
I know, I'm just fucking around.
Oh, you guys really don't think I thought that like 200 people fought a war
back in like the medieval times, right?
If you do, then I must be a pretty good actor then.
And I am, so I already know that.
Damn good fucking actor.
If you could redo your life again with cheat codes, what would you put on?
I could like snap my fingers and get a meatball sub.
That's pretty handy.
I don't want to fly or any of that bullshit.
Oh, let's go.
Let's go back to the, try this guy again.
Well, I stumbled.
Oh, who's dead?
Both.
And you really, you know, I'm just going to leave you alone
because you're like, you really want to, you really want to get that done.
I'm protecting them right now.
No, I'm getting out of here.
Watch that over swing.
Oh, I thought I was going to get killed by the guy behind him.
I had a streak going there.
That wasn't bad.
What?
From behind?
Hmm.
I think someone came behind me.
Oh, he came out of nowhere again.
Is blocking directional automatic?
It is not.
It's right click.
Really, I just blew it.
Faked him out.
Ooh, he's got a little streak going, doesn't he?
Come on, where am I at?
14?
The highest is 24.
That's not going to happen, I don't think.
From behind again.
I got to go back against the wall.
I just got back to German make this in dreams.
Yeah.
I've been behind me, right?
I tried to fake him out.
Didn't work.
Watch out.
Always took back against wall.
Fuck, everyone just keeps coming in.
It's like the WWF.
I'm in the ring and the keep interference just keeps happening.
All right, I'll take top five.
That's the first time it's happened.
Only 280 gold.
I feel like I deserve more than that.
I kind of just want to keep playing.
This is, I'm just having a good time.
I'm going to get to level three.
Actually fun game in 2019.
Yeah, it's just kind of fun to play.
I didn't think I was going to be this entertained by it, but I am.
Let me try this guy again.
So this dude is a big heavy evening star.
So you really want to just try to club people in the head with this.
What about does it changing?
I can't change the...
Okay, I can change it into a...
I hold it closer.
So this is, I guess, short range or...
Let's see what it does.
Oh, there's so many coming.
What else do I got?
Nothing.
That's too many.
All right.
Shit, I thought he was going to...
Damn, I'm trying to fake him out.
I'm starting to do that more often.
That's actually a really good tactic.
You do the stab and then people try to block it, but then you come over with an overhead.
It's very, very effective.
I got to do that more often.
I'm getting a little better.
I'm starting to understand mechanics and opportunity and stuff like that.
And stuff like that.
All right.
Well, not when there's this many.
Come on, give it back, back, back, back.
I got an assist somehow.
All right.
I want to go down here.
I'm more useful when I can get in like a one-on-one or a one-on-two scenario.
Like this.
That.
Yeah.
All right.
Come on, bring it on.
He blocked all of that somehow.
This magic shield.
Look at this guy.
Wow.
Damn it.
I was doing so well.
Come on.
I'm still doing all right.
That was me.
No, it was me.
All right, good.
This guy's trapped in here.
All right, move up.
Nice team damage.
I know.
I'm trying.
I'll take a medic bag though.
Get out of here.
He's just laughing with all of his...
Are they even attacking me?
How do they all get back here?
Oh, fuck.
You got...
You'd be kidding me.
That dude seriously went around in a full circle.
I really...
No.
He was behind me.
That's not our horse, right?
That is enemy horse.
Dead ahead.
How did that not hit him?
Geez.
We missed.
Did you really just duck that?
We've got ourselves a gamer here.
I didn't do anything.
I was watching him die.
Can you please stop blizzing?
My son is watching.
Son's not old enough to watch this game.
I'm sorry.
He just doesn't...
Is the game still in development?
I don't think so.
I think they're gonna keep adding stuff, right?
But is it...
I don't think it's early access.
Is it?
My son is 35.
Well, then that changes everything.
Onward we go.
A little chip damage.
It's all good.
Don't hurt each other.
I know it's easier said than done, but...
Open the door.
Open this door right now.
Can we get an axe guy to break the door open, please?
Axe.
Kick door open.
Somebody open this door.
Open the door.
I'll reach in there.
All right.
Okay.
God damn it.
This was planned.
This was a planned thing.
I hope you guys are having fun.
The old door-stuck guy wraps around trick.
Stop opening the door.
My son is in there.
So we share this castle.
And his son's like 40.
In fact, what's he doing here?
This is my castle.
Yeah, that's like...
That's the stables down there.
He's hanging out in the stables.
You're not supposed to be down there.
After four o'clock.
You know that already.
We've got some really great shit in the chat room there.
Somebody said, I actually eat poo-poo pee-pee.
I'm talking about like top of the line chat box stuff going on in there.
So, you know, that's great.
I'm not getting door baited again.
That's not gonna happen.
I'm going down here.
Are you serious?
Like, what the fuck are you doing?
Oh, I bled out.
Jeremy, I think you're projecting.
There's one person.
The guy with the pregnant girlfriend
is the only person on the team that's doing anything.
Look at the rest of us.
I guess we're four people.
I want to see what's going on in here.
I'm actually, I'm curious.
Am I banned from going in here?
Even as a ghost, I can't go in here.
Yeah, I almost walked into it.
All right.
I need to get at least one or two kills.
I have to.
I can't just sit at zero.
Watch the back.
They like to come around there.
I can do that too.
Thank you.
Didn't get it off first.
Thought I did.
Close the door.
This is bad.
There's gonna be a reason why we're not supposed to be going up here.
And there's the reason right there.
All right.
Okay, I got him once.
Easy, easy.
Don't get piled up here.
This is gonna be a disaster.
Watch out behind, behind, behind, behind, behind, behind.
Oh, God.
We're surrounded.
You can go.
Whoa.
No, no, no, no.
Oh, that guy.
Oh, my God.
Oh, there's too many.
I couldn't see what was behind me.
Coward.
How would you?
I was trying to be tactical.
Watch out.
He's gonna get around us.
He's dead.
Didn't hit anybody.
How?
Kick him off.
A bunch of...
Oh, God, please.
I just got sniped.
Not by a stream, but by an arrow.
Just watching the guy go down.
I didn't have any health left.
Of course, I'm gonna die from that.
Firebat.
Yeah, it was behind me.
I had like 15 health left.
I'm gonna play that.
Remember when he was getting better?
Well, look at...
Okay, look at the team.
I'm technically in fourth place on the team.
Technically, that's...
I'm just giving you facts here.
Without making it political, pee or poo.
Both at the same time.
Does that make you happy?
What?
Somebody pushed me into the fucking thing.
I got wedged in.
Why?
No.
Give me a break.
Why is that even there?
There's fucking 40 fucking people in the spawn.
And somebody...
Oh, yeah.
It was just like, sorry to eat, kid.
Excuse me.
Get out of my way.
We were out there.
I was standing right here and it was like...
What the fuck?
Clip it.
I wanna see it.
Somebody watch it.
I think you need to adjust the difficulty.
Well, now I'm not in fucking fourth place anymore
because I don't even get to play this one.
Did the Sonic movie trailer haunt your day?
Yeah, I mean, I don't know why they even make that movie.
Super Mario Brothers even knows to stay the fuck away from film.
There is a Mario movie.
Yeah, and it's widely seen as one of the worst movies ever made.
That shouldn't be a barometer there.
All right, make sure you don't get pushed.
Watch this.
Go ahead, open the door.
Come on, somebody walk out there.
Dude, the one time...
I'm going this way.
He's dead, right?
He's dead?
He better be.
He's not dead.
There's so many people right there.
Are we really doing this again?
Watch this right side.
They're retreating.
That means they don't have much health.
Again.
Nice.
Good work.
See you.
Okay, good.
Who's left?
That is not a good battle cry.
See, look, I've climbed all the way back up.
17 kills.
Don't fall down.
See?
He almost just did.
He did.
Look.
He fell all the way down.
He did.
I don't want to do that.
How am I hitting a teammate there?
Well, now you got to get down.
Fuck.
No!
What the hell was I doing?
Why did I do that?
I got a kill for it, but I lit like two of my teammates on fire.
Fuck.
The person that made the Minions movie is making a Mario movie.
It's hard to do a Mario movie though,
because just by its very nature, Mario doesn't talk.
I know he did.
I know there was the Mario Super Show and all that shit,
but if it's a cartoon, like 3D animation,
Mario doesn't really talk.
Is it just going to be Mario is no dialogue?
Yeah, a Mario movie is way harder than a Sonic movie,
because Sonic never shuts the fuck up.
Half of Sonic the Hedgehog's appeal is he talks really loudly,
and all the time.
So Mario doesn't really do that.
I mean, maybe Luigi, but Luigi,
they've made the characters over the years
very, very simple language,
really easy to understand.
You know, like, oh, oh, bingo, right?
How do you make a whole movie of that?
Their dialogue is all in Mario Kart.
I'm dead.
Now I want to play with here.
I need to get some more items and armor and shit.
They did Minions.
Yeah, but are the Minions?
I mean, I never seen the movie or anything,
but do the, I don't think I've even played once with Knight.
Aren't there other people that are in those movies
that talk for the Minions essentially?
They're the ones that are there
to kind of experience the world with you in a way?
Or do the Minions just,
it's just absolutely can't understand anything?
Peach can talk.
Yeah, I mean, but you need a character
that is going to have most of the dialogue,
unless they're really going to make Mario
fully voice acted dialogue.
I mean, Taro's Martinet, right?
He's still doing it.
Is he still doing it?
I wonder if he would just do it.
You see, he was doing it for a very, very long time.
Fully voice acted Wario in the last WarioWare game.
I'm all for it.
I'm all for the attempt, right?
But having a protagonist that doesn't really speak.
That was beautiful.
Hit him in the face with a hammer.
He's going to get away with that.
Just one blacksmith versus an army.
He has a voice actor.
Yeah, but he doesn't really,
Mario doesn't have a fully scripted dialogue.
He has phrases.
I'm going to put a bear trap down right here,
right at the top of the stairs.
Die!
Did he not die?
I'm surprised by that.
He did die.
He fell for a very, very, very long time.
Did he not die?
No, he did.
You used the loot?
I'm so useless with this character.
In a little bit.
Not right now.
Oh, somebody went in the bear trap.
Okay, that makes more sense, doesn't it?
Let me show the action, Jeremy.
Come on.
You the last one standing?
I think there are two red archers left.
Scary.
Almost.
Very close.
Is he dropping them from above?
Bear trap.
Not cool.
Oh, well.
We tried.
All right.
I'm a knight.
I've never played as the knight.
Let me string together two and three.
I just want two.
Two per round is good.
If it's even possible, it is.
But I don't like this map with this many people.
I blocked it.
Right in the head.
Keep that.
A guy needs one hit and he's dead.
We got more than them.
We got more.
Go in.
Go, go, go, go in.
Let's go.
No, no, no, no.
I'm in the fighting area.
What are you talking about?
Oh, fuck.
No.
What?
That was...
This is bad.
I'm in trouble.
Oh, well.
They're gonna vote kick me?
Well, then they don't get to play anymore.
Because I'll go to a different server.
It's that simple.
The vote kick is real.
They can play without you.
You don't think they're gonna do that, do you?
Do you really believe that?
Do you really think
the guy that taunts every time
and runs through everybody to come find me
is gonna play a different server?
Hey, don't fall.
Do you really think that?
Oh, this is a bad place to be.
I don't want to be here.
Uh-oh.
Too many.
Oh, fuck.
No.
Are they playing door pong?
Let's see how this ends.
How is this gonna end?
It ends with the squire killing both of them.
Watch.
Oops.
I don't even know what that was.
This game is fucking ridiculous.
That was, uh...
Oh, Sir Davos.
I'm not much of a fighter.
Apologize for what you're about to see.
You know, the Red Woman.
Get him, Davos.
Does Jerma only read your messages out loud if you insult him?
Yes.
Look at all that.
That team had like 40 combined stream sniper kills on me.
They were only killing me.
I was the only person to die.
Notice everybody on my team had zero deaths
and I had 48 deaths.
That's unfair.
It shouldn't be like that.
I need to level up.
Why am I not getting any...
Did XP turn off again?
Jerma, you are a badass.
Hey, thanks.
That wasn't a mean comment.
I read it all up.
Try getting more kills than deaths.
I have like 12 kills and 48 deaths.
This is so much fun, though.
It really is.
I'm just gonna pretend that I'm Ned Stark and it's just ice.
Oops.
I thought I was still on the...
Okay.
Well, Ned Stark did...
I made him...
I thought my last game was...
Died immediately.
Damn it.
I thought I was gonna faster.
Yeah, he wouldn't have been in the show for very long.
Somebody kill him.
God damn it.
Is somebody behind?
Oh, can you guess who that was?
I wonder how many of my deaths have been to that guy.
It's got to be at least like 30.
I'm going over here.
Kill!
Give me that.
An archer.
Can I pull the arrow out?
I can.
Uh-oh.
Guy on a horse.
Whoa!
No, I'm reconnected.
I think I'm back.
What's my favorite movie?
That's a tough one.
Ghostbusters or Gremlins 2.
That's a toss-up, though.
It's hard.
Nice.
Good.
Keep it going.
Holy shit!
Whoa!
Too many people.
Oh.
It's Back to the Future.
That's a good one, too.
There's a lot of good movies.
There really are.
Fuck.
Everyone's fighting this like pen over here.
Horizontal strike.
Right in the...
Never mind.
Aw.
Kill the archers.
That's a good...
You know, I'm going to run around.
I'll try to wrap it up and kill all archers.
I'll be on archer duty.
There's an archer!
We lost?
That's sad.
I'll kill the people that can't fight back.
What do you mean?
They've been fighting the whole time, shooting arrows at me.
Experience.
Come on, more.
No.
Why does it have to be shut off?
All right.
I'm going to take a look at what I got.
Because I have money.
Let me go see what I have here.
I should be like eight or something by now.
Let's go down here.
How much money do I have?
Why am I not making any money?
I have not gotten any experience points and no money.
But did they turn it on and then turn it off again?
Because it was working for about 15 minutes.
Damn it.
Oh well.
All right.
Let's go somewhere else.
Play the tutorial for cash.
I tried that last time, but I'm assuming it's not going to work again.
Because the servers are not keeping up with what you're doing.
It probably won't work.
So no, it's all good.
We'll just join another one.
All right.
Something a little more low scale.
Like this.
Never mind.
This is called very horrible place.
I don't think I want to do that.
Team deathmatch.
Here we go.
Let's go try the night again.
Real gamers don't care about cosmetics or currency.
Well, you have to when it involves buying new weapons
that you can use in the game.
What are you going to do?
Punch me?
You're going to TK me?
All right.
Let's go.
I don't even know how the fuck I wrapped around you like this.
Kill.
Is it bleeding?
Uh, okay.
Delete OBS.
All right.
I'll show up behind you.
That was what I would consider a bop.
What?
What happened?
Did I jump directly into them?
That's the...
Okay.
I've been playing this game for almost four and a half hours.
And I've touched those spikes before and it didn't instantly kill me.
Uh-oh.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no.
I jumped face-first into them.
I thought they were just kind of there to be an annoyance.
I didn't know that you died if you touched them instantly.
It's the first time I've seen them work.
You killed them.
All right.
I'm going.
The bridge is just death.
They're all piled up on the bridge.
Was there anybody even around?
What the fuck?
I guess I've been behind me.
You're going down.
Through the hole.
Come on.
Right in the head.
I can't get that.
Get his loot.
Stab.
There it is.
All right.
Keep it up.
Rock.
Didn't think I was going to turn, did you?
Nice.
That guy dead?
Not yet.
Oh, great.
Well, oh well.
That was good spicy team attacks.
They were pretty good.
That guy looks like the ref.
I wonder if they...
Imagine if they had refs back then.
All right.
Don't touch those.
They're bad.
They did have a ref back then.
No, they didn't.
All right.
I got thrown the shit at me.
It's got to go.
I'm going to drop down.
I know it.
What do I have left?
One, two, three.
Well, that was dumb.
I didn't even click.
I swear.
I promise you.
I didn't click.
The guy with the fucking frying pan.
It's only so many times I can block the fucking attacks.
I got looted.
I did.
Oh, that guy got in the way.
This guy is fucking relentless.
Somebody behind me, right?
Goodbye.
He didn't see me in his peripheral.
But I did.
Oh, good.
Very good.
MVP.
Took his legs out.
Good work.
This is working like a team.
This is what it should look like.
No.
I'm going to bed now.
Can I get a good night beer?
I was going to do it right into the microphone,
but it's getting later.
I don't want to do that.
The referee got too close to the combat.
Watch it.
He's going.
I knew you were going to do that.
Is this going to be my first battle?
No.
Friend.
An annoying friend.
I'm dead.
Friendly friend.
Did I tap the button?
I think in my repost, isn't that what I'm doing?
It's like right after you swing, right?
After you block.
Like that.
I think I've been doing that.
He even tried turning the...
Yeah, but it's kind of...
My brain just wants to kill things.
No, I thought he wasn't going to pay attention to that.
Come on in.
Oh, he's got the bow, doesn't he?
See ya.
Damn it.
Get the ref.
I missed.
Wow.
What did I hit him with?
I didn't hit him in the back of the head?
That was interesting.
Eventually we're going to have a fight.
No!
Oh, die!
I can't have 13, that's unlucky.
Seven minutes left.
In the fire.
I didn't get him.
Watch out behind.
The combo.
Nice cross.
Holy shit.
Oh, I think I...
Damn it.
Come on, I can't have 13 kills.
14 at least, or 15.
Is this game out?
No, oh yeah.
You can buy it right now.
Should be on the front page.
Hey, we did it!
I'm not on the losing team this time.
Yeah, as of right now the game is released, but it's kind of broken.
Progression is turned off.
The currency is turned off.
The game works.
Some of the servers have issues.
Damn it.
Re-turn it back on.
Turn it off, turn it on.
Will that work?
The game itself is a blast.
Oh yeah, no, it's awesome.
I wouldn't be playing it for this long if I didn't think it was great.
I've been playing for like five hours.
I think it's fantastic.
Who do I want to be?
I don't know.
All right, let's go.
The protector of the realm.
Is it behind me hitting me?
Fuck!
Too many.
There's a lot.
No, no way.
Too many.
Oh, this is not...
Okay, this is just spawning and I keep going.
It's right ahead.
Damn, they're like all the way back at our spawn.
Let's try the spear.
Actually try to use it this time.
Fuckin' hell.
Oh, this is bad.
I got a long weapon, man.
I could stay up here for a while.
God damn it.
Let's not do this.
Oh, we're getting so badly smoked right now.
Where'd you come from?
All right, I gotta be somebody else.
We just can't even leave our spawn.
Come here.
Damn it.
Leave me alone.
Nobody on my team has more than three kills.
Kicking is good,
but when there's three or four people around you,
you can't really do it.
No.
Damn it.
I made you two.
There's no fighting them.
Finally, one like ant came out too far out of the nest.
We got him.
Our like shitty ant colony finally killed one ant.
Laugh at that.
You son of a bitch.
I got him.
Oops, I'm sorry.
I didn't mean to do that.
I was trying to click.
I'm sorry.
I didn't mean to.
I'm trying to do it again.
I'm trying to kick that fucking guy up again.
Do you ever press X then two?
Why is that a thing?
What?
I accidentally hit my own buddy in the face.
Oh my god.
No, no, no, no, no.
Kill.
Oh, hello, sir.
Zero health.
Almost.
I'm just getting fucking destroyed.
I want to kick more people off the edge.
No.
I got it.
Plus one.
One damage.
It took like five people.
What the fuck?
Oh my god, my...
Oh my god.
Oh my god, what do I do?
All right.
I want to try...
I want to try the actual VR again.
I want to see if I can actually do it.
Is it...
Can we do it?
This is where it begins.
I gotta pee too.
I haven't peed once today, have I?
No, I haven't.
That's a first.
I don't think I've done that in a long time.
It's been a while since I've not had to pee for like five hours.
I did pee right before the stream started though.
Should I go pee right now?
Okay, I'm gonna go pee...
I'm gonna go as fast as I can.
I'm gonna get some water.
I'll be right back.
Hopefully by the time I get back in here, we'll see.
All right, I'll be right back.
Okay, bye.
Did I get in?
No, I'm still looking.
Oh, really?
This would be fun.
Quick drawing does not work.
Oh.
Well, that's unfortunate.
Sometimes it takes up to 10 minutes to find a match.
Is it just because they're all full?
And a ton of people are trying to join at the same time?
This has been okay recently.
You can't select Battle Royale.
I see.
Well, shit.
All right, let's go...
Server.
Five out of six.
That's a little one.
Maybe we should do a little one.
It's Horde.
Horde would be fun with an actual five or six people you know.
Here's Battle Royale right here.
Can I just join this?
I guess so.
Interesting.
I think so.
Hide the server browser.
Yeah, but there's really nothing you can do about it.
Because, I mean, it's not that hard in an attempt of me to hide the server.
I mean, how many VR games are currently running right now, you know?
It wouldn't be that difficult to find it.
Hi-yah!
This might even be the only Battle Royale server that's on, like, U.S. West.
That has players accepting it.
So it's like, hey, I'm in VR!
No, unless you had...
Unless matchmaking works, that's not gonna happen.
Life is bald.
Old guy versus young guy.
Who do you think?
I think young guy's gonna pull through.
Old guy has the upper hand now, but I think young guy's gonna throw a few punches here
and knock him out with one hit.
I'm commentating.
You don't come attack the guy broadcasting the game.
I'm broadcasting the fight.
Why would you punch me in the face?
You punched the ref.
No, not even the ref.
I'm the guy with the microphone in the ring that wants an interview.
Can you die by that?
Quick, quick, quick.
Three, two, one!
Ah, all right, I need something.
Come on, anything.
Can I pick the horse up?
Can I hear horse, weapon, chest?
All right, I got a maul and a branch and a mace.
That's a lot.
No, don't use the branch.
Use the maul.
My game environment is being compromised!
My game environment is being toyed with!
All right, this isn't gonna last for more than 15 seconds.
I hope you know that.
Someone else's gamer gunk is in my gamer zone!
All right, here we go.
Nobody can know who I am now.
Is this free for all?
I think so.
Damn it!
What?
Packet loss, packet loss.
Oh, that's far.
That one's gonna come behind me, aren't they?
Damn it, I was so paranoid about somebody being behind me.
I don't know if it's Raider anymore.
I think I was having more...
Gamer fatigue also is probably settling in here.
Right in the head.
There's a naked guy.
Come on.
Come on, give me one of these.
Gamer fucking fatigue, man.
I just had the one zone I was going.
Good, I wanted to do that
because now I can play the class I want to play with.
Turned all the way around.
Let's watch the stamina.
Two!
Stamina, 100%.
Don't tell him I'm behind him.
Speaking of which...
Damn it.
That's not gonna kill me, right?
Jump!
Somebody behind you, somebody behind you!
That was not honorable.
Although I do it all the time.
Wow, that hurt.
Fuck!
He outplayed me there.
I was gonna debate...
I was gonna debate him.
You got...
No, you do your thing, do your thing.
I won't get involved.
Are we playing a game or are we having a picnic, fellas?
He blocked it.
Oh, he's stuck.
Okay.
Well, let's help him.
Did I die by the...
Oh, by Dothmal killed me?
Didn't think I was gonna do that.
Do you like that move?
I call that one the 1v1 lock-on technique.
Ready?
Thanks for the...
Thanks for the Band-Aid.
Oh, that was fucking ridiculous.
Oh, fuck!
I forgot you had those.
I can't...
I can't block with a Band-Aid?
What the hell am I thinking?
I'm trying to block with Band-Aids in my hands.
It's made out of cloth.
I'm not sure you're aware of that, Jeremy.
Oh, he's back.
Oh, good fake!
No!
The new D group keep looks really good.
The game is really fun.
Ha ha ha.
And I just got...
I aggroed both of them by doing that.
1v1 server...
Wait, am I...
It just says deathmatch.
Wait, am I ruining everything?
Other people are doing that to me, though.
Wait, wait.
Everybody is doing that to each other.
Wait, hold on.
I've been attacked from behind like five times.
It's because I started it?
That's not what happened, right?
I'm not the bad guy here, am I?
See?
Look.
Look at...
Say that with 1v1 server.
Yeah, okay.
I didn't...
If that's...
No way.
They didn't learn it from me.
They have the servers been running for like four days.
Look, I'm observing right now.
They're all just fighting each other.
They're just wildly swinging at each other.
That guy's got double frying pan.
I'm not listening to you guys about that.
Uh-uh.
It's just a fight each other server.
It's not about 1v1ing.
Oh, that was a big hit.
This is an RP server.
I'm doing it wrong.
Ooh, all right.
Oh, I bled to death.
Fuck.
He beat me.
Ah.
Oh.
That didn't just spawn right there, did it?
It's okay.
I made it.
I made it to the fray.
Where is he?
What the hell was that?
He like tripped over a few things.
Nice.
Ooh, here he is.
He doesn't have a sword.
What?
Nice.
Ooh.
Wait, no, I'm alive.
I got a Coke ad?
Oh, I'm sorry.
Unless you don't...
Unless you like Coke.
I don't know, whatever.
Can I get a...
I took it back.
Oh, that's...
This game is fucking so funny.
Oh, he didn't even know.
I'm just gonna wait for it to happen.
I don't even care if I didn't get the kill.
Ooh, watch out.
Ooh, that was a double bait.
Holy shit.
Did you actually hit that?
Fuck, too early.
I'm taking him down with me.
He's got three pans.
All right, you and me, let's do it.
Honorable.
We'll do it honorably.
Oh, he's like spinning.
He's doing like a weird thing where he's...
Oh god, I'm dead.
No, don't fuck this up.
Ah.
He was like turning his back all the way.
He was going like this.
It was weird.
It's like throwing you off.
He goes like...
And then wraps around.
He like spins his back this way and then turns.
That's a pretty good tactic.
Rematch.
What?
Good job.
The spin doesn't do anything.
It's just a little...
Awfully.
I wish I could make some money.
The worst part about this is
not being able to unlock more weapons.
But I'll do...
I'll do like another two or three matches.
And then tomorrow we'll do...
Re-launch the game.
I did that before and it only worked for like...
Five minutes.
So we'll probably...
What we'll do tomorrow...
We'll finish Sam and Max season one tomorrow.
That's probably what will happen.
Because it was...
That it's about like five or six hours, right?
Same thing.
How do I 1v1 with a...
Head?
He dropped a bandage for you.
Is that what happened in my...
No, stop this.
Why am I doing this?
Gun game would actually be pretty cool here.
If they started you off with like the little potato knife.
Be the guy with the frying pan.
I can't.
I don't have a frying pan.
Now, are you ready?
Do we have to do this honorably?
Are we doing this?
Who's doing this?
Wait, wait, wait.
You both can't just come in at the same time.
Oh no!
Hey!
That's me from an hour ago.
I honorably would have...
You want a 1v1?
Is that what you want?
Is that what you want so bad?
I don't want to fight.
You're like so good at the game.
What do you want me to do?
How many hours do you have in this game?
How many days have you been playing all day?
Aim for the legs.
Dragging is the reason I didn't get into chivalry yet.
This feels slower than chivalry though.
This feels...
A chivalry was a little quicker, I think.
From what I remember.
I don't know.
I don't know when to go in.
I think I'm going in now.
Got panned.
Yeah, I gotta take a break too.
I've been playing for too long.
It's kind of blending together like it usually does.
I guess I'll do pan guy version two.
I didn't expect to kill that guy instantly.
Top of each other.
I didn't think that was gonna happen.
All right, another guy with a pan?
Are we doing pan three?
Okay, pan three.
No, this is not pan three.
How long is this map?
Oh, it's short, so we'll try it.
I thought for some reason that guy was gonna come in behind.
Who?
Who's coming in?
You?
Let's go.
You fight with disorder!
All right.
I think I gotta take a break from this game.
I need a mental break from five and a half hours straight of swinging swords at people.
We'll probably just hang out.
We'll hang out for like a half an hour.
Just chill.
And then tomorrow I'm gonna bring you...
Sam and Max.
Episode three.
We were in the middle of it, so we're gonna finish it.
Will I stream Mordhau again?
Once it works.
Completely.
I'd probably jump in here with some friends and do the horde mode.
Because there really is only so much of no progression that...
And like buggy servers not being able to do matchmaking.
You know.
So I am going to say goodbye for now.
For those of you that wanted to watch this game.
But for those of you sticking around, I'm just gonna chill.
We'll just hang out.
Probably do the bits too.
Just hanging out talking about stuff.
And I'll see you tomorrow if you're leaving for Sam and Max episode three.
And probably episode four and episode five.
Would you recommend this game?
Oh yeah, definitely.
Once all the bugs and everything are ironed out, this is gonna be a great game.
I mean it already is a great game, so yes.
Definitely.
Uh, I'm gonna get one more water though.
I'm like sweating in here.
Give me one second while I get a water.
And we'll come back and just chill.
See you very soon.
Okay.
What can I just put on the screen while we hang out and do bits?
I don't know.
Oh no, no GeoGuessr.
No GeoGuessr tonight.
Maybe we will just do the bits and call it.
That'll be just probably at about six hours.
Which is, that's fine.
That's good.
And we'll start tomorrow.
I really do want to set up that personality test.
That's probably what, I'm gonna try to get that done.
There's like two or three things that I really want to get done here.
But I'll see you tomorrow.
Don't worry.
Drink more water.
I actually, I drink a lot of water now since moving to Vegas.
Yeah LaboVR is on the table too.
There's a lot of random stuff to do.
Yeah, maybe we'll just do the bits and hang out.
This will take us to about six hours.
I'm gonna grab some food and we'll go tomorrow.
Poor Far Cry.
Oh no, Far Cry.
I forgot about Far Cry.
Instead of Jerma lied about certain things,
you should just do Jerma forgot about certain things.
That actually is way more accurate.
Jerma forgot about Far Cry.
Jerma forgot about Sam and Max.
Jerma forgot about Minecraft.
Jerma forgot about Dragon's Dogma.
There you go, you got it.
Jerma lied is more clickbaity.
Yeah, it kind of is, isn't it?
But I'll see you guys tomorrow.
We'll go back to about six hours ago.
To Louis with six bucks.
Six hours ago, six dollars from Louis.
They just say hi.
Thank you, Louis, for the six bucks.
We had 10, 15 community subs from Squirds that I missed.
I was very focused in the first couple hours of the stream.
And I think we'll be in italics of trying to
get in a lobby and stuff and it just wasn't working.
But thank you so much for the 15 community subs.
It's a lot.
Thank you.
When's the next big stream event?
Hopefully soon, because I started working on
something very in particular that I've talked about recently.
It should be a blast.
The pieces all have to come together though.
I don't think that'll be more than another month.
It'll be within the next 30 days.
No, not green screen, too.
Something a little more weird.
Hopefully it works.
But PeacefulHaley, thanks for the 250.
Hey Jerma, how was your vacation?
It was good.
Hope all is well.
I auditioned for something recently and I felt really confident.
I had it in my head that I was going to get it,
but I found out today that I didn't get casted.
Hurts my feelings a lot,
but I guess this is just what I have to go through till I get casted.
I guess it just sucks because I really felt confident.
I don't usually feel that way.
Maybe I didn't do as well as I thought.
Well, I think you're approaching it the wrong way.
I'll tell you exactly why.
Because every single role that you audition for
is not a role that you kind of have to look at it like
audition for a bunch of stuff.
And if you get one of them, great.
But if you get attached to a role
before you even have a part in it,
you'll be like,
oh shit, I really wanted that fucking part.
I really wanted to do that.
I wanted to do that.
It should be me, right?
You get kind of stuck in there.
But the way to combat that is to just keep auditioning for things
and then by the time you audition for another three, four, five things,
the thing you auditioned for earlier,
you don't even care about it anymore.
Also, it can take a while for anything like that to even happen.
You know, casting and acting and it's a tough business
because there's a lot of people also doing it too.
So if you like a regular job process,
yeah, I mean, that's what it is.
When you go, when you send an audition tape in
or if you put in an application to a job,
they're kind of the same thing.
Maybe they didn't think that you were right for it.
That happens all the time.
You talk like you used to be an actor.
Well, I mean, I've been in a few things
and I had like demo tapes and reels and stuff.
I've done all kinds of stuff like that before.
Not even professionally either.
Like this is all stuff from years ago.
I used to do that instead of doing YouTube videos.
It was what I did.
I just did it online.
Send a tape?
Yeah, the best advice that I can give with that is
you do not go into auditions
thinking you're going to get the part.
You should go into auditions
thinking that you have an opportunity to and a chance to
and you're in that with everybody else.
So you should try to rise above everybody else
because you know that it's not certain.
So try to do a better job than everybody else, right?
But I wish you luck.
Punch away at a few more auditions, see what happens.
You're never going to know what happens unless you try it.
But thank you.
With the 250.
Appreciate it.
My name is Peef.
Gave $10.
Thanks for the 10 bucks.
They say P-P-P-Pass the Ale.
Thank you.
I don't know what that's from but
maybe I do.
Maybe I've heard it before.
But I appreciate the $10.
Thank you.
My name is Peef.
What do you mean?
What are you talking about?
Passes off his dreams.
Jeremy's a lazy boy.
Oh, dreams.
Oh, his actual...
Okay, I see.
I see where you're going here.
Chunky baloney.
Thanks for the 10 bucks.
Don't listen to them, Jerma.
I love your boomer techniques.
I was doing all right.
Okay.
I was doing okay.
And not about how good I'm playing.
It's about how much fun I'm having.
Don't you understand?
I hope you guys understand that.
Fun, Jerma, disgust.
No fun allowed.
Does this streamer have a dog?
Yes, this streamer does.
It's a Dachshund mix.
His name is Otto.
He's a very good dog.
Great dog, actually.
Thank you, Ixian Games, for the 550.
One of my rats is sick
and since you're the Jerma Rat Guy,
I figured I'd throw positive vibes
into the universe in your direction.
Thanks for the laughs.
Hopefully your rat is okay.
I'm sorry to hear that.
Thank you for hanging out.
Otto, all right.
Otto is in bed right now with Kim.
That's all.
But I wish your rat a swift recovery.
Hopefully they're okay.
Otto, waiting room.
Waiting room.
You've seen him before.
Hey, thank you to Zorro Carlos.
And it's an ASCII art.
I don't know what this is.
It looks like the first half
or first third of an ASCII art.
I don't know what it is.
The only ASCII arts that I know of,
I only know of two.
And one of them is Mario shitting and the gnome.
I don't know any other ASCIIs.
I don't think there are any.
I've never, I just go,
oh, there it is.
There's like that fucking, there it is.
Cool.
There's like Mario like shitting
or whatever he's doing.
I'm like, all right.
No other ASCII art exists.
I thought he was pissing.
I don't, it gets deleted so fast
I don't even know what it is.
It's on there for a tenth of a second
and it's just gone.
And look, I'm not going to go to Google
and be like, what's that ASCII art
where like Mario's naked and pooing?
Why would I ever do that?
That's not something that I want to
go look up for any reason.
If only you had a Chrome extension
that could let you see deleted messages.
I don't want to see deleted messages.
They're deleted for a reason.
Curiosity killed the cat, man.
I don't want to open up like a virus website.
But thank you Zorro Carlos for the top half
of I'm not sure what it is, but thank you.
Snoozing Copter, I have VTTV.
Snoozing Copter, thanks for the 250.
Hey, I just want to say thank you
for showing me that Dreams exists.
I was a huge little big planet fan.
I never knew this game was in development
until you first mentioned it some time ago.
Can't wait for the insane shit people make.
You could have played the tutorials on stream, by the way.
They're much more fun and interactive
than the first introductory tutorial.
Would have been nice learning along with you.
Whatever, looking forward to it regardless.
No, I thought about it, but
there's two sides to that coin, right?
The first side is just play the game
and do all the tutorials
and sit there for three, four, five hours
and just do the tutorials
and just enjoy the game.
But for a stream and a broadcast sense,
a live video sense,
I don't know if I want that stream
just because that other side of the coin.
The first side is great.
We do it all the time,
just hanging out and playing the game.
But still, remember,
I only stream three or four days a week.
Sometimes maybe, it depends on the week, right?
Maybe four times, maybe five maybe
if something's going on.
So I want all the streams that happen
to have something,
at least something significant to happen.
Not every stream has to be crazy,
but if I'm given the opportunity
to play Dreams and stream the tutorial
for one of my streams during the week
or check out more of the content
that's available to watch,
I'll do that one first, right?
That's not to say that I don't
just hang out and play a game sometimes.
I did that tonight.
But playing this game
and throwing axes at people
and these giant battles,
I think is more engaging
than simply just doing tutorials
for five hours.
That's kind of the deal.
Nothing will compare to German
crying and farting noises.
I don't think I'll ever be able to see
some or do something like that again.
That was just that stupid and ridiculous.
You did a seven-hour stream
on that dumb newspaper game.
Newspaper game.
But also, I mean, I don't have
a certain thing that I do every time.
Picross? Picross is great.
I decide what I'm going to stream.
Usually, if it's not something
that's a big elaborate plan,
usually that week I decide,
hey, what's coming up?
What's out now?
What do I want to try?
That looks like fun.
No, no, I don't want to do that.
So if during the week,
hey, I'm going to play Sam and Max tomorrow.
That's just what I'm going to do.
I'm going to play Picross tomorrow, right?
That is what it is.
But I do appreciate that.
Thank you so much, snoozingcopter.
I can't wait to see
what people come up with in dreams.
I'm going to try to make at least a few things
that are worth showing.
Maybe we'll find out.
Freudian weapon, thanks to the 250.
No message.
They just say bleed purple bonus.
Is there like a bit bonus going on or something?
But thank you.
Sawdust bunnies, thanks to the 360.
Bonus 36.
Thank you.
So there is a bit bonus going on.
Cool. Thank you, guys.
We got Tingy for 250.
Thank you, Tingy.
Hey, dude, I went to go look for another battle royale.
I couldn't find one.
I searched.
I was going on the browsing category list.
I didn't find anyone playing battle royale.
Are you sure?
Maybe you were speaking out of tone there.
Oh, fuck.
Okay.
Yeah, I didn't.
I forgot what I said three hours ago.
God damn it.
Thank you, Tingy, for the 250.
Deep fried Gundam, thanks to the six bucks.
Six dollars from deep fried Gundam.
Well, I can't believe it's been two years
since I subbed to you, Jermbo.
Anyway, just wanted to let you know
how much you've helped me these past couple years.
Dealing with some crazy anxiety pretty much all my life
and your streams and videos have helped me
totally forget about it.
Even if it's just for a couple minutes.
So from the absolute bottom of my heart,
thank you so much.
It's my pleasure.
Thank you, deep fried Gundam.
I'm really happy that you enjoy the streams.
I'm really happy you enjoy the videos.
And thank you for being subscribed for two years.
That means a lot.
Thank you.
That's a fucking long time.
I wish you the best.
Thank you so much, dude.
You've got a great name, too.
Thank you for peeing?
What?
All right.
What is the pee poo obsession?
The pee pee poo poo thing?
Why is there?
What is that?
But is, okay.
But is that from something in particular
or is it just so stupid that it's funny?
I mean, I can get it.
I said that.
Did I say that before?
No, I didn't make that up.
Somebody just typed it one day on the internet
and then people started typing it again.
And you keep encouraging it.
Whatever.
I hope you have fun.
As long as you have fun.
I hope you're having fun.
Remember the guys that were building
the Fortnite Minecraft base in the game?
I hope you're having fun.
Sound like you.
Oh, it's instead of being,
it sounded like you said peeing.
I see.
Hey, Meef Playable, thanks for the $2.69.
BRB, designing a game where you have to have sex
with your teammates to respond dead players.
That would be pretty wild.
Imagine a game where you had to, you had to like,
no, it wouldn't even have to be,
you'd just be like procreation,
like cells or something.
This should be like a cell first person shooter
where you have to like spread out
and make it injured.
Does it exist?
No, not like Spore.
I guess this, this is a Garrio.
That game does already exist.
Nevermind.
Hey, Dr. Pepper, thanks for the $20.
20 bucks from Dr. Pepper.
German movie when?
I have some ideas.
We'll see if they end up coming to fruition or not.
I have a few things that should happen.
Before the summer is over,
there should be at least two or three
elaborate streams that happen before summer's end.
They, I don't know why they wouldn't happen,
but thank you, Dr. Pepper, for the $22.
Appreciate it.
Hawkeye of mine, thanks for the $15.
Would this convince you to use the loot
for a couple of rounds?
I beg you.
I beg of you as a bard.
I used it for a couple of rounds.
I just don't, didn't like the building.
With coordination that would work very well with the team,
but I just want to slash at people
and laugh at rocks being thrown.
When's the next Labo stream?
That Labo stream is going to be, are you ready?
The Nintendo Labo stream is going to be on Saturday.
Saturday, the 4th of May.
Maybe I'll have a few glasses of wine?
Maybe I'll break something in my room?
Probably not.
And I'm going to be dressed as Darth Vader
because it's Star Wars day.
Why do they say that?
No, I have to do that.
Don't do that.
Get a sound effects lightsaber.
What would that have anything to do with the Labo?
And have the Darth Vader voice on the whole stream?
Uh, no, I, nobody will, everyone will hate it.
Everybody hated Bugleberry
because he couldn't understand a word he was saying.
You think that'll happen on the Labo?
We'll see.
He wanted to do it, but he's blaming us.
No, I'm saying that's stupid enough
for where I think it's funny that I wouldn't want to.
Maybe.
I'll at least wear a Star Wars t-shirt.
Is that enough?
Fucking Bugleberry.
Bugleberry should do haunted house reviews.
I want it gets to be that time of year.
Yeah, that sounds like fun.
Do IRL haunted house reviews.
And the camera goes through with him
and he's criticizing things
and talking about how scary things are.
Bugleberry should be put in a retirement home.
He's not that old.
He's like 41.
Why do you think he's that old?
He's like six or seven years older than I am.
But thank you to Ert.
Ert110 for the five dollars.
Were you serious about community dream stuff?
If so, can we have a submission date?
I would say let's...
To make it for real, right?
Because somebody was saying
five or six days might not be long enough.
Let's say...
Well, remember, it's not a submission deadline, right?
Because I'm not compiling them.
What would happen is we would...
Let me look this up
because I want to make sure this is possible.
Have a tag or a searchable title tag or something
where we can get a playlist or something like that.
So it'd be easy for me to just type in the word germa
and have that just...
I can find them from there or from a hashtag.
Let me see if that's even possible
because this currently is the dream's early access program.
So all these features might not exist yet.
Let me figure that out.
But it would be at least a week from now.
But yes, I am serious about that
because I want to make stuff in it too.
At least movies or a short video
or a little game or something or a painting.
I want to do...
I want to at least make something.
I've been waiting for that game for a long time.
Hey, Mr. Comcast, thanks to the $5.
Hey, Germa.
John Comcast here.
Just letting you know that we here at Comcast
have forgotten about you.
Have not forgotten about you.
I personally caress a picture of your face
every night before bed.
But anyway, yeah, just calling to let you know
what we're about.
We're still around.
You know, if that cock stuff doesn't work out for you,
also ignore that guy
that comes to your house every morning
trying to break one of your windows with a brick.
My aim is pretty bad
so you shouldn't have to worry about it much.
Well, but why...
John Comcast, why do you say you're calling me?
Just calling to let you know we're still around.
This is a text.
Just calling to let you know.
A weird creepy ex-Comcast.
Well, Comcast, I'm sorry, but I have moved on.
You should too.
And let's get the credits rolling here.
Thank you, everybody that played.
If you jumped in.
If you jumped in and stream sniped me
and killed me over and over again.
Thank you for playing.
No, I'm kidding.
Thanks for playing.
That game's a lot of fun.
I'll probably...
You see it again.
Made Jerma mad.
Oh, fucking stream sniping.
Hey, long as you're having fun, right?
I need to have a permanent defender with a shield
that just gets in the fucking way
when somebody runs across the map to try to kill me.
I need someone just to always be looking for that.
I need to have my own personal shield butler.
A spy's statue.
Like a bodyguard?
Yeah, a shield butler.
A bodyguard.
You get it.
I'm going to have a bodyguard next time.
I'm going to make sure it's something
that's real fucking good at the game too.
You know, I might even hire that guy.
I might hire the guy.
Okay, you know how like sometimes people like...
You like hack something.
The hacker gets in and fucks up a bunch of stuff
and like the employees get a hold of him
and they're like, oh, hold on a second there.
We want to hire you to fix our infrastructure.
And they're like, what?
Fucking okay.
Maybe that'll be the defender.
And then I kick him off the cliff and exit the server.
I make him defend me for like 30 minutes
and then I'm like, all right, man, high five.
And I go...
And just off the fucking edge.
And I point down and I go,
that's what you get for crossing me.
That's what you get for crossing me.
And by this point, I have a full fucking hood up
and my skin is starting to turn like blue.
No, not green, blue.
Anyways, let's get the credits rolling.
I'll see you guys tomorrow for Sam and Max.
And then this weekend we'll do the labo
and then probably in like a couple of weeks maybe
a little bit more we'll fucking try to dunk me in a tank
and see if anybody can do it.
You didn't hear about that stream.
That's the next...
Somebody asked what's the next big project.
It's that.
That's going to happen.
I'm going to do whatever it takes to make that happen.
Twitch controls robot to try to dunk Jerma
that makes fun of you.
There's the next project.
People need to know that it's going to potentially happen
because the stream just can't turn on with controls.
Jerma is going to get hypothermia.
It's going to be like 115 degrees in Las Vegas
during that stream.
Hypothermia.
It's going to be...
You guys aren't even going to be able to do it.
I don't think that you guys are going to be able to do it.
I'll be sitting there taunting you.
Why does the sus say next week?
Does it?
Next Wednesday.
Uh well that's definitely tomorrow.
See you next week.
I'm taking another week off guys.
Yeah my mother decided she was going to come back.
See you in a week.
No uh hold on I got it.
I got it.
Ready?
Let's run those credits.
Thank you for all the resubs and all the new subs.
All the everybody that decides to support this channel for $5 every single month.
You guys keep the wheels turning forever.
Anybody that contributes a cent to this channel.
You're the battery that powers the vehicle to drive on the road.
So thank you.
And let me edit that command.
Commands.
It's Wednesday right?
Wednesday.
Weird way to say that.
That should be good.
Hey.
We also had uh one more bit come in from Jack.
Jack.
Jet Island.
Sorry he froze me.
Thanks for the 250.
Yeah VR.
There's two games I need to complete in VR.
I need to do Gorn.
I'm gonna be honest with you though man.
That shit killed me.
I don't know what it is.
Something about the last week of doing VR.
I did like three or four days in a row or something of VR.
And it fucking killed me.
More so than ever before.
So I had to take a break.
I had to box it up for a little while.
Gork VR?
What do you mean it killed you?
It just drained me so much that I couldn't do anything.
I could barely get up the next day.
I got up and I was just I was decrepit.
VR hangover.
I think that's a real thing.
That's my life.
Yeah I know.
VR hangovers every day.
Imagine what VR will be like in five years.
I don't think there'll be a headset.
Remember when the 3DS came out and everyone was like that's not possible.
How does it work?
I'm not wearing stereoscopic 3D glasses right now.
How can I see 3D without having 3D glasses?
That type of technology was just out of this world.
It was impossible.
There'll be a technology that comes around over the next decade
where you don't have to have that headset on.
You're not even gonna have to have a TV.
You'll have a little dome that just projects onto a wall or into your living room or something.
Everyone will just put on glasses and sit back in the chair wherever they're sitting
and there'll be no television.
We'll all be watching the same thing but through glasses
or through a new type of media that is made up.
That shit's not gonna happen by the way.
I don't think it is.
I think we've plateaued in the electronic department.
And I know I'm gonna be one of those people that's quoted here 100 years in the future.
Remember when all the people like 150 years ago, 200 years ago,
they were saying that planes will never exist.
You'll never fly.
Birds only do that.
You're not a bird.
Idiots, imbeciles.
I'm probably gonna be one of those people that just says I don't think in 50.
I don't even know if in like 30, 40 years it might not be possible.
I think we've plateaued electronically.
Things will get faster but until quantum computing
deletes our universe, we'll see.
It's gonna be wild.
Guys, just watch.
They're gonna turn on the quantum computer
and a little red line is gonna shoot out just instantly.
They're gonna be like oh we programmed it to do Simon Says.
Things gonna turn on.
Quantum computer is gonna point a fucking laser beam at the wall
and just it's gonna be just deleting.
And they're gonna be like trying to turn the fucking thing off
and it won't turn off and just delete, delete, delete, delete.
It's gonna go in a line and start deleting the earth.
Just one line by line, just back and forth.
They'll drop a nuclear bomb on this thing and it won't work.
They'll just delete the nuke before it lands.
It'll just point up like a sentry and just
just paint it over it like an eraser.
So I have no mouth and I must scream.
They were on, come on.
Every major scientist, every brilliant scientist,
you know what they all say, the biggest threat to humanity
is AI, is quantum computing, that's the biggest threat.
That's what they've said.
I think I trust the greatest minds to ever live
to give us an accurate representation
of what we should potentially be afraid of.
That's what Stephen Hawking said.
You don't trust Stephen Hawking?
He's right about black holes.
Yeah, he said aliens.
He said aliens.
But he has to say, oh, did he?
It wasn't aliens.
By 2014, Stephen Hawking and business magnate Elon Musk
had publicly voiced the opinion
that superhuman artificial intelligence
could provide incalculable benefits
but also can end the human race if deployed incautiously.
There you go, it would end the human race.
I remember he said that.
He said that artificial intelligence
is potentially one of the biggest threat facing humanity.
Anyway, thanks for sticking around.
I'll see you guys tomorrow.
Look up aliens.
Now, I'll see you guys tomorrow.
Take care, have a good rest of your night.
See you really soon for Sam and Max episode three, part two.
Good night.