Hey, it's me, Jeffrey. Liar. What do you mean, liar? That scared me. Don't be scared. Hey,
Jeffrey. Jeffrey's the name of your cat. It's also the name of the Toys R Us giraffe.
Is the Toys R Us giraffe still in the commercials? Does Toys R Us still have commercials?
Or did they blow their entire advertising budget in like 96 and then just hope that
the 500 million dollars they spend every day on TV, people just remember who they are.
They're bankrupt. Well, looks like somebody had to grow up eventually. I don't want to grow up. I'm a
Toys R Us kid. Until the fucking tax man comes and the 400 franchises you have go under.
Gonna have to grow up. What's with all like the sad faces? You haven't even shopped there.
What was the last time you've been to Toys R Us? You haven't even probably seen the
inside of it. You probably never even google image searched Toys R Us. Makes me sad to
remember. Toy grocery store. I don't like this meme, Jeff. Bring back Jerma. All right.
All right, I'll be right back. Hey, guys. It's me, Jerma. I'm the friendly one.
That's a good coffee. Do a co-op stream with Jeffrey. Nah. We're gonna go back to Sekiro.
It took a couple days to get better. I was feeling, as you know from the last stream,
a little fucked up. A little under the weather. And I'm feeling a little better. So without further
ado, we're gonna pick up exactly where we left off. I haven't even opened the game,
which has been hard because I've really wanted to play. Kick the plebs out. What? Why? Oh,
you're talking about sub only. Do it. Wait. Easy. Hold on. Like we could wait a few minutes.
Doesn't have to be immediate sub only. He's gonna play terrible because it's been two
days. No, that's not true. I should do fairly well because I see it in real life. I picked up
a broom and I told Talix and Kim to both like throw shit at me and to both like come at me
with like all kinds of weapons and stuff. And I like was blocking them and parrying them.
So I've been in real life. I've been practicing. Yeah. Kim, like just pick up
that fucking phone and just throw it at me. I don't want it to just do it. I'm ready.
And then hit me right in the fucking mouth. Broke all my teeth. But you get good, right? I went
to the hospital. Got good. You know, got a $2,500 hospital bill. Got it. You know, let's go.
Sub only now. Not yet. Where even are we? So those of you that don't know, this is secure
row shadow stacked wise. Uh, we were going down through the sunken temple.
Let me just like remember the buttons. Hold on. Right trigger. Right trigger. Right trigger.
Oh yeah. Okay. Now I remember. I remember. So this is the sniper roost. Does this game have a
multiplayer? I don't know. It does not. There is no multiplayer in this game. No invasions. No.
Well, that's a lot of stuff over there. That's probably a trap though. Uh, let's just go get
it. Is it a trap? Oh, I can see that. Can I jump up there? No, no, no, no. Okay. Well,
now it's something we learned. We've, we've remembered that this forward momentum,
uh, this forward momentum in secure. All right. If I, if you jump, you kind of just jump forward.
That's not a death. Doesn't count. People are counting those. I want to make it very clear.
That's not a death. It takes away like 30%, 40% of your health bar. Not a death.
All right, let's just go. I hear something. I think I hear a goofball over here. Oh my God.
What the fuck is that? Okay. Well, it begins. That's like Wolverine. That's like they dug
up Wolverine a hundred years after he died. And this is probably a boss. Yep. Long arm centipede
giraffe. Okay. Nice to meet you. What is this name? What kind of name is this? Oh shit. It's
Jeffrey from Toys R Us. All right. So he's got one, two, three, four, two, three, four,
five, six. Is that all he does? Well, he's fucking relentless. That's for sure. All right.
So it's one, two, three, four. That face. Okay. I got it. That's a slash. I don't know.
So I got it. You just got to carry the fuck out of this guy. So we got a slash
and then we're just going to make it come in. One, two, three. See you later. One down.
No, I didn't get it. Okay. This one. What am I facing? What the fuck was that?
Why was I facing backwards? Oh my God. That was stupid. That was stupid. Why was my back turned?
I can get it right here. That was actually stupid. Again. Again. Dad, you're dead.
Okay. That was fucking dumb. I had my back to him. Like he was just hitting me right in the
ass. Anyways, he's dead. Yellow gunpowder. Sick. I gotta get that mouse off the screen.
Oh, he beat Jeffrey first try. Yeah. Back to the bankruptcy board with you, Jeffrey. That's,
I'm not saying that. That's like not nice. So this is a prosthetic tool upgrades. Prayer beads.
Nice. Oh, that was fun. He was fairly easy. Not, well, the easy is the wrong term. Fairly
predictably. Just the same kind of chain. Some scrap. Nice. A large fan. A large fan
made of dyed red Japanese Aralia leaves can be fit into the prosthetic tool. Fanning it creates
a large vortex of wind. Spiriting away those it catches. Okay. So it was like a little knockback
or something. That's probably a knockback. Can I look in here? Gun for shrine key. All right.
So that's just like a little mini boss in front of them. There was a place to go down
here. I don't want to start a new area until, there we go. Yellow gunpowder. More
upgrade materials. I still have a little bit of a cough, so you're going to hear it a few times.
All right. Well, there's no reason why I wouldn't just refill my shit, right?
He's not going to respawn. Okay. I got my recoveries back. Oh yeah. Oh yeah. All right.
Sunken Valley passage. We have nothing over here. Now everybody, now don't get too excited.
Don't get too excited, everybody. Because I saw the trailer for the game.
And unfortunately, if you see a trailer for a video game, you're spoiled at the fact that
the giant snake is going to come up here and attack me right now. I did see the trailer.
I told you. I saw the trailer. I saw the trailer in the game. Why did I watch the trailer?
How do I get out of here? I'm assuming this way. It was part of like the E3 presentation.
And like I, I knew what was going to happen. Fight this now? Boat kick for spoilers.
Is it a spoiler? If two years ago they showed that. Oh Jesus. He's right here.
All right. I'm sorry. Let me apologize because I'm realizing something right now.
Like I saw the movie. You got, some of you guys may not have seen the movie.
So we were both watching infinity war right there. And right before like the big climax,
I told you what happened. Hey, did I, I've seen this movie before? Have you seen this movie?
No, I haven't. Oh, well dude, uh, watch what happens when, uh, when he gets killed right here.
Oh, okay. Yeah, it was cool. Huh? Did you like it? Yeah, I guess I did.
Vote kick. You can't vote kick me on my own damn. All right. But there's something
going on here. What do I, can I like slash him through here? Can I kill this thing?
Uh, what's wrong with him? Can I jump up on his body?
I mean, that's very clearly making a bridge. All right. I gotta get to his
plant. Oh shit. He's staring at me. Is there anywhere I can grapple to over here?
Looking for a grapple point so I can at least make my way up on him
because I can't grab him. I wonder if he's going to attack me from here.
Okay. So he's just set up for me to walk on it. Well, I made it. Oh, hey, by the way,
I watched a walkthrough up here. Just wait till I split his whole body in half. I do
this thing where I jump and it's a really farm software really over did themselves here.
You jump and you hold the sword out through his mouth and you zipline down his whole body
to be able to traverse the gap there and you cut the whole body in half while you
zipline down through his whole body. I think we just go up, right? Item.
Adamantiaite scrap. You're a jerk. This is, this is the cool part right here.
What I remember for the trailer. Oh, oh, almost. Uh, any more like monkeys that jump
down. I guess I have to jump for, wait, somebody can see me. He doesn't, he can't get up here,
right? I highly doubt he can. Can he? I don't think it matters. He has a gun. Okay. Well,
that's great to know. Not going to happen. All right. So from here, I need to drop down
there. Do a monkey voice. I don't have any monkey voices. There's an item over there.
I'm going to get that. Do it. I, no, I can't. You literally can. You happy? There's an item
down here, right? Where was that item? I saw it from far away. Uh-huh. Oh, YouTuber reactions.
Whoa. Whoa. Oh shoot, guys. Shoot. Well, I got more snap seeds. Probably going to need them.
Can you not swear? No, I'm a swearer. Sorry, guys. I say like poop.
Shit. No, I think he's starting to run out of content. Just the fuck up one. All right. Down
or up? Ooh, I don't, let's go down. There's actually a, can I get back up if I go down
here? Let's see. Oh shit. There's like three in here. I think. Yep. Oh boy. Oh, you do a
lot of damage too. Jesus. Oh Jesus. Get me out. Okay. Here comes one that actually,
this is a really bad place to fight anyone. God damn it. I have like firecrackers. What the
fuck am I doing? I just forget. Wow. That's the easiest way to get rid of them. Damn. All
right. What the fuck? Okay. This is the surprise level. Contact medicine, weak poison
status have been inflicted. Okay. Yeah. Where? Okay. Back it up. All right. Where are they? I
don't even know where they're all coming from. There is an item here though. I think.
Think. No, I think it was just the spirit emblems. I might be missing things.
Nope. It's right there. There's actually two. One down here. Sugar. I hear movement. That
better not be what I think it is. I see green. I got a story for you guys. By the way,
this is a true story. This happened last night. Do you want to hear something fucking insane?
So me and Kim have been sick, right? And the reason why I'm looking at down is because
it reminds me of ecto cooler. And if that, but let me just finish my last statement.
If that's a poison swamp, this is the worst game ever made. So let's just be clear on
that. Uh, but anyways, so last night, Kim and I were in bed and we're doing our usual
ritual where we just sit there and look on our iPads, iPhones, just watching random videos.
We kind of just like at a certain point, stop talking and just read and look at stuff,
right? Like good night. Good night. Okay. Yeah. So I was watching a video of this guy
because I don't know. I sometimes I get on a kick where I just want to see like things
from the eighties and old sixties commercials and well, ecto cooler. Let me read about
that. That sounds cool. And I got on a kick on the ecto cooler from high sea, which is the
ghost busters tie in, right? I just was looking at stuff about it. So there's a guy on YouTube
that had one from 30 years ago and he was going to drink it. He's like, Oh, I got a
found one. It was original packaging. It's been expired for 30 years. And he opens it up and
he starts talking about it. And the whole time I'm just paying attention to it. And Kim's
watching whatever she's watching, look, you know, looking the other way. So he eventually
gets it into a glass and he drinks it. And instantly, not even five seconds goes by,
he fucking pukes projectile throw up coming out of his mouth. And I was like, Oh, that's
fucked up. Kim looks over, sees the prop, the puke coming out of his mouth. First time
she's paid attention to anything I've been doing in probably two hours. She has an
immediate reflex. If Kim sees another person like throw up, she has an immediate throw up
reflex. So she fucking sprints to the bathroom, all puking like, and I'm laughing
my ass off. I can't fucking believe it. Like that, that's, that's the shit that she caught
me watching like an ecto cooler video. So I'm laughing. Remember, I have a cough. I
start coughing uncontrollably. I'm in pain, laughing hysterically while I hear her fucking
like puking in the toilet. I can't help it anymore. I am in a full coughing fit.
I get the fuck out of bed. I go over to the sink and I start fucking puking in the
sink. I'm not kidding. This is a real fucking story. And I was still laughing.
So it was like, this is a real story. This is 100% true. I thought italics was good. I think he
was still streaming at the time. This was at like two, three, four, like the clock in the
morning. He was still live. So he didn't hear us. I thought we were going to wake him up
and he was going to think we were fucking dying in here. I, that is fucking real.
I didn't puke that much though. It wasn't like a full puke. It was like
funny. It was the fucking funniest thing all year. I think Star made this comment before
and I adhere to it completely. He said, he said in the past, I wish if I could go back and have
like HD cameras record something in my life, I would want it to be X, right? If there was
like two or three cameras in the bathroom and like in the bedroom and stuff, I would love to
see that footage. The whole thing play up. That's so many. Oh my God.
You're not supposed to fight those. You're not supposed to fight those monkeys over here.
Nope. That's a joke how many there are. How am I supposed to get over there?
I have to climb. I have to go across this way. There's no way you're going to make that.
Oh Jesus. What the hell you were doing? Just firecracker them.
Oh, this is going to be a death here. God damn it. I'll try. I'll try. All right. I'm going in.
Not yet. Wait, wait, wait. Let me just get like the item that's over here.
There's like shit. Okay. This shit like over. No, there's not. I'm already good to go.
Three, two, one. I'm going to get so many points for this. I can't, I can't call you
right now. This is not even hard. This is not even fun. I don't even want to do this
anymore. All right. They're getting me close. Hey, in Sekiro. This is a from software game.
You either die or you don't die. I'm sorry. How much money was that? Wow. Nothing actually.
They get monkey booze. I got monkey booze. Okay. A bunch of community subs came in and
I missed them. My phone was ringing. Community subs came in and I had to fight like 15 monkeys.
More than that. How many community subs just came in? I didn't see.
It was like at least five to ten, right? Five, five. All right. Awesome.
This Jerma lied about Minecraft VR. Thank you so much, dude.
More community subs from Jerma lied about Minecraft VR. I kind of like this area.
Until I look, until that's a poison swamp. And if it is, then you know,
that's two fold letter grades down. If this game is at an A right now,
that makes it a C minus. Oh shit. Okay. There's an idol there,
but points can be added back up. You know what I mean? I'm going to get this first in case I
can't get back up. Well, that looks like a big, that's a mini boss probably.
I crashed your computer by killing the monkeys. No, I didn't. I'm still waiting for one more
to get this because that's a pretty big deal. I don't have enough of that. All right. Let me
go look and see what's down here. There's an item down this way. Balloon of soul. Yeah,
that's, that's a, that's a green swamp. All right. Let's try to fight this. See,
thankfully this run back is pretty easy. It's just right here. Let me just get that
little health back. All right. Here we go. Just checking. Just checking. He's huge. Well,
I'm already seeing that there's a lot of things to grab onto here. How did you even
see me? Jesus. You have to fly around here. He's trying to see what it does. What about this?
It's affected a lot by that. Sweep. It is. I'm assuming it's a lot of sweeps. Whoa, that hurts.
Get me out. Get me out. Get me out. Get me out. Here's a run in. Oh shit. Oh, that's
a blow. That's an instant kill. All right. Whoa. I don't even know. I don't think you
can dodge it. Do I have to deflect that shit? Maybe. Oh, he's shitting in his hand. All right.
That's what that is. It's hard to get that. It's all right. This thing where he spins around
and like whizzes around and shit. You can't go in, but he does that. Okay.
Can't follow that up. Oh, he comes out of that quick. I don't have any heal. Oh boy. Oh
boy. Where was he going? He's going to shit at me. Okay. You can, you can block it.
One down here. Oh, that's not it. That was a grab. Whoa. All right. He did like four sweeps
in a row and it went for a grab. Sounds about right. Let's go again. I'm going to get in there
quick. Try to get a couple hits on him now. Never mind. What does that wiggle look like?
Fuck. I didn't block it. Fuck. No, not already. I don't think I should be parrying him. He
does a ton of posture damage. Like almost unrelenting. Give me help. Oh fuck. It's okay.
I got to use these more wisely. That's like, that's the key here. Oh fuck. He's like
stunned. Damn. I got to block that poison thing. He's around. He comes again.
Comes to shit. I'm like waiting for it. That's what I wanted to do. All right. All
right. Easy. Easy. That's the grab. Oh, that sucks. It's so hard to determine. No.
Again. No, that was a sweep. Shitting. Oh, there it is again. My God. That's what that's
good for. He does like a little shimmy. Damn. Oh, that like symbol and into the moves. It's
like the hardest thing to get on in this game because your brain sees the symbol and then you
kind of just panic for a second and go, which one is it? Which one is it? I'll get him this time.
What? What the hell? I just wasted two somehow. I got to be closer to that.
I think I'm just going to jump every time. Wiggle. Wiggle. Wiggle. To cool down. Fuck.
Oh, that hurts. Oh God. What's he doing? Easy. Here comes the poop. Here comes the poop.
Fucking camera. Please don't do this to me, camera. This time. He hasn't done shit at all.
Eat it. Easy. Back it up. Don't get greedy. Damn it. Not close enough.
What am I? Oh, he shit on me. Oh no. This is bad. Hold on. What the fuck? What? What's
going on here? Use. I can't use this? That was weird. All right. Come on. Back it up. Back
it up. Too much. Back it up. What do you got? Oh, don't get greedy. Fuck. Here comes the shit.
Fuck. All right. Come on. Come on. Come on. I got two resurrects here. I got it.
Oh my God. I thought that was going to stun him or something. Oh fuck. Oh my God. Oh,
why did I do that? I had, I've like, I thought it was going to like get hit.
Damn it. Damn it. Damn it. Damn it. For some reason, I thought when you latch onto them,
you have like immunity or something. No, I don't have any pellets either. I gotta get this on the
bar. Fuck man. That was close. Yeah, I have no pellets. Get that on the bar. Damn it. That
was close. Anything else I need? Maybe it might be worth putting one of these on here.
I want posture. Posture. Fuck. So this is the poison one. Man, I'm so like riled up right
now too. Damn it. That was so close. I need to take like a sip. I'm like a lightning rod right
now. Damn it. I thought that was the one too. It's all right. Let's go. I'll tell you,
the first two firecrackers, remember how they didn't land for some reason?
I feel like that's a victory right there. That was, you know, but whatever. I can't be mad
about that. I really wish I could attach. Let's see. No, god damn it. That's bad. This is a bad
start. Really bad start. Yeah, this is an awful start. Kill me. I'm gonna do it. That was just
a bad start. Hey Magellan, thanks for the five community subs. Magellan, 36. Five subs. Thank
you. I gotta land all of them. I don't need to, I can just get a couple in here. I don't need
to do anything. Save the shit when I need it. Get away from that poison. Take the shit.
Okay, when he throws the shit, I got at least two hits there. I can do it. Here comes. Get away
from him. Oh baby. Oh baby. Come on. That's a grab. Uh oh. Bad. Bad. Bad. Very bad.
Oh that's what? That's a grab too? I thought that was a sweep. Oh no. Oh no.
That's, that sucks man. Like seriously. It's all right. That just wasted like three. That sucks.
It's so hard to tell what the fuck he's gonna do. Yeah, this is a really good start too.
That's unfortunate. I still can do it. Wiggle, wiggle, wiggle. Let's just get it. Let's get a
short thing. Wiggle, wiggle, wiggle, wiggle, wiggle, wiggle. All right. Let's go. Don't do it. Don't
do it. I got, I got, I got it. This is it. This is it. It's done. Goodbye. Right in the heart.
All right. Damn. That was fun though. Oh no. Of course not. Yeah. Welcome to From Software.
Oh great. I got to learn a whole new fucking move set now. Well this is fucking fun.
I don't even know what that is. I can't even scare him. What? Is that a jump? Um.
Well this is interesting. I mean you spend the whole time trying to figure out. Now I
got to fight another boss. Oh this is great. Oh no. Someone's rotting. Well this um. Hey is
this a From Software game that was made after 2016? Every boss has two or three phases.
I should be aware of that now. Fuck. Okay. I wonder what the tactic is after he's dead.
You really can't take that much damage here then. What? Where are you going? Back up.
Oh god. Not the camera. Not the camera. Not the camera. Just use one of these now.
Damn it. No. That's bad. Not that bad though. The wiggle. Asshole. Come on. He's gonna throw.
You gotta be fucking kidding me. That was absolute dog shit. Like give me a break.
Are you serious? Really? Dodge grabs. Except when you can't. I did that. I timed that so
perfectly. I did. Give me a break. Now he's doing this every single time. His fucking move
set changed since the last time I fought him. I'm not locked on anymore for some reason. Why?
I'm gonna get the fuck away. You know what I mean? Like there's no reason to do that.
Fucking Jesus. How are you supposed to beat this second phase? Why? Can you do it? Why is
that not hitting him? What the fuck? Give me a break. What? I feel like I'm gonna be here
for a while. I'm trying to figure out if his ass is more horrible or his head.
I've been hitting his ass. He can stagger a little bit in the head. It seems his head is
staggered. Not so much his ass. Dodge frames. I can't. No. God damn it. I might stop drinking.
I'm still alive. This is insane. The fact that you gotta do this twice with a move
set I've only seen one time. I'll be here for the next three straight days.
What the hell happened there? You gotta get the free tap there. You have to on his head. You can
get it. That's what I'm doing. I'm trying to jump fast enough. No. I think it was just so
debilitating seeing that I had to fight. I like drained a bunch of energy and now I gotta
fight this. Oh fuck me. This is gonna be horrible. Whatever. I'll do it. Let me put
it on. Let me go into my inventory because I feel like this shit is worthless. So maybe like
fire the axe maybe? I wonder. When he goes down try to get a hit on his ass or his face maybe.
I could try to poison him too. We'll see. We'll try the fire.
Wait for the first wiggle and see what happens. The worst part about that is I can't do the
follow-up. He's apparently too big. Burning? How long is he on fire for? That's actually not too
bad. It really isn't. Just gotta hit it like a couple times after he just wiggle wiggle.
Like here. Ready? Then get it. There it is. Now that's it. It's actually very effective.
I gotta get out of the corner man. The camera's gonna possibly... I gotta stop
dodging that. It's impossible to dodge it. I have to walk into the jump. Come on. Let me
see it again. Like even me. Like really? Why is this still a problem?
Why does it have to still be an issue? Like after 15 years? Still. He's gonna throw shit.
Alright guys. We get to see the second phase again. Are you ready? I'm excited.
Can I still hurt him? Come on let me do like damage to him now.
I don't... Oh fuck. How do I get rid of terror? I'm gonna use that but hold on. What's the terror
one? This one right? Oh man. I don't know what the fuck he's doing. It was a sweep.
I don't fucking get it. I don't... I'm gonna try again. Man it's so awkward. Jesus.
What am I doing? What? That takes so long. That takes forever. That takes forever.
Why would you ever have that? That... oh I'm gonna do a little stance now and pray.
I don't have any healing. This is fucking insane. Holy shit. It's just... it's fighting just
two bosses back to back that are not completely different from each other.
You gotta fight the the ape and then you gotta fight the headless horseman with a sword.
My goodness this is fucking crazy. They're not fucking around. It took until like the Dark Souls
3 DLC before you got a boss like this. All right let's see. Oil, fire. I feel like I should...
I'm gonna like waste these here. This dude is a full-on wall. Uh well I need... I'm just gonna
go in the inventory and take these because the game pauses and having too much shit on my
bar always fucks me up. Let me see how this goes. Let me see how oil works on them.
There are hooks all around for the scream. Yeah but it happens so quickly that it's almost difficult
to kind of rip the camera and like find a tree. He knocks the trees down too doesn't he?
Just kind of have to turn and just do it. Man. All right here we go.
Fight over his head. Covered. Wiggle. I'm just gonna see if he's done anything.
Okay he's only gonna do it once. He's covered in oil. One thing I don't know about oil,
does oil have to be applied every time? Or is it just on him? That's unreliable.
Nah that's very unreliable. You gotta get like the perfect opportunity. Don't do it.
Oh that was enough. No don't do it. Is it enough? In the corner. Wiggle wiggle.
Burn him. Oh right let me do it twice. Shit. Not good. Not good. Not good. Not good.
All right here comes the shit. Missed. All right five heals. Let's go. Come on.
Bring this fucking giant Donkey Kong asshole into the grave. All right here we go. Wait wait wait
wait wait wait wait wait. Let's make this quick. Let's let's get some shit like okay done.
Pacifying agent. And I think I'm gonna take like a cookie here. I don't know.
I think I'm just gonna. How long do these last? Attack power. Vitality damage.
What do these fucking things do? They last for like 15 seconds. It's not long enough.
I'll wait till he gets up and I'm gonna do. Ah fuck. Shit.
I gotta get a plan here. I'm gonna use a. Okay I don't know. I'm gonna use the.
I'm just going in hard. You ready? No. Vitality damage. No. No take it off. Take.
I'm already panicking. Okay I'm gonna take this one. This one. Attack sugar. Let's go.
Here we go. Go. Mistake. Mistake. Mistakes. What the fuck is that move?
What do I do? What do I do? Oh my god. I can't see the water is fucking me up.
No. Wrong. Wrong. Wrong. All right. What happened? What the fuck is going on? I don't.
Ah fuck. Jesus. No. No. There's no. That fucking camera man. You see what I'm talking about?
Give me a break. That's so hard to do that. It's so difficult to find a little spot.
It really is. It's fucking ridiculous. See? Like where the fuck can I even grab from here?
I don't even want to get close to him. One more of those and I'm fucking dead.
I'm gonna stay near like a tree. Get out. Get out. Get out. Get out.
Fuck. Nah fuck. That was a different combo. Okay come on. I got this shit. Let's go. Oh no.
Out. Out. Out. Out. Out. Out. Out. Out. Out. Out. Out. Out. Out. Out. Out. Out.
Out. Out. Out. Out. Out. Out. Out. Oh shit. I don't know where to go.
I have to take it. Damn it. This is insane. Oh no. This is so. I had it too. It's just so awkward.
And I got no more pacifying agents. Oh my god. He's incredibly fucking difficult.
God damn it. Oh I have no more. God damn it. You can hold run. I know it's just it's so.
I just. It's it's real easy to say. Oh you can just do this. You can just do that.
When you're in the fucking driver's seat. When you're in the. When you're piling the airplane.
It's a lot harder. A lot easier said than done. Do this shit again. I feel like I was
fighting him in that other phase for like fucking 45 minutes. Bad run already. Nah kill me. This
is bad already. Just kill me. I had it too. So close. You just gotta. You gotta parry that
string when he's in that second phase. Those weird awkward thrusting. And then he does the
big one overhead. And then you get the free hits. But fuck man. You gotta do that so many times.
I feel like I'm not even doing any damage to him. Out of pacifying agent. I'm gonna have to buy some.
I really think I might have to start drinking. It'll like loosen me up a little I think.
Because right now I'm like. I'm like fucking tilted right now. I'm not even angry. Just
like fuck man. Everything's gonna be so perfect. Nah yeah. I don't know guys.
I might have to take a second here. I've been here for like 45 straight minutes.
I feel like I have to beat him here though. Man oh man. Man oh man. Man okay. I gotta just be
clean. Alright if I die again I'm going. I'm popping the bottle of wine. And if I beat him
I'm popping the bottle of wine anyway. For victory. Alright just be easy. Play it smart.
I know all his moves at this point. And shake. You can hit him so many times with fire.
What apparently. Every single one of them. Like somewhere underneath.
Now hit him right like a sack. If I get there with at least like three or four.
And I got like the dodge frame. Why even have a dodge? Why even tell me to dodge grabs when
there's eye frames for dodging grabs is like there's none. Why even have that tutorial?
We'll be here for the next six hours. I feel weak. I feel like I should be doing more damage
to him or something. The second phase I was hitting so many times. I feel so fucking weak
right now. Should take a minute. Should. I didn't. Fuck you. That like 180 degree
insta turn into grab. I thought that leaf was a person. And I was like how did somebody get
down here? I got one healing potion left. This is gonna be bad. I just gotta parry everything
and then run away. No healing potions. No pacifying agents. Just parry everything and run.
I'm gonna try. Sugar. Sugar doesn't seem to last long enough to. Alright here we go. Oh no
I forgot. It's okay. I don't know why I didn't get hit by that. He stopped mid swinging. Did
you see that? That was really weird. He was doing his like animation here and just decided
to do something else. That's without the good view of that. It's hard dude. I gotta get out
of here. What the hell was that? Here comes a big sweep. I'm so afraid of this terror thing
at this point. I tried to hit. I tried to grapple it and you see how it happened.
Thing in the top right. I was gonna do it. Just act out of frame. You can hear me pressing
the buttons here. Trees down too. Oh I'm too scared to fucking do anything man.
I'll do it. I don't care if it takes me 30 minutes. What? I don't know. Oh shit.
Calm down. What the fuck. Okay that's it. It's all sweeps. If you missed the first one
that's such a weird little place to go. He does a little turn and if he missed the first
one you're fucked. You gotta be close before you get him. This just takes forever.
You can do four. You can do four. That's a bad. That's a mistake. Don't do it like that.
Coming up. Oh shit. Oh fuck. Whoa he stopped mid animation you asshole.
What a dick. Fucker that was so ridiculous. Sometimes he changes that combo in the middle.
I am gonna have to tell you guys something here right now okay.
I'm ready to take this. I'm ready to take this. In fact I'm ready to take this. Bring it up.
That's positioning. Oh fuck. Oh fuck. Oh fuck. Oh fuck. Oh fuck. Oh fuck. Oh fuck. Oh fuck.
Oh my god I fucked it up over here. It's time. It's time to take it. He doesn't.
Kill him. Kill him please. Take the worm out.
Don't get up again. He better not get up again. If he gets up again I'm quitting the game.
I heard the scream. Oh my god that was fucking ridiculous.
When they throw the second phase shit at you. You just. You gotta redo the whole. You gotta
relearn the whole fight twice. Hey I told you. Win or lose. How many attempts was that? That
was a lot of attempts. Slender finger. Empty the cupboards. It's time for a glass of wine.
So the slender finger of a young woman can be fitted to the prosthetic to create a prosthetic
tool. Found in the belly of the guardian ape it is partially digested. There's a shinobi
technique called the finger whistle that can drive beasts wild. The one he used it before
clearly used it for this purpose as evidenced by the finger's open hole. And let's read the.
Okay now I can do what I wanted to do. Oh man that shit is fucking. That's fucking crazy.
I want to read the uh thing that I just got. Where is it? There it is. The battle memory of
an extraordinary foe lingering in the mind of the wolf. Commune to the sculptors and confront
memories of battle to permanently increase attack power. The guardian ape was defeated
though its roar can still be heard. It is said that an infested body marks the undying.
Oh boy. Enhance attack power. Let's go. But such a long life would surely be quite
lonesome for even an ape. Perhaps the echoing roar of the guardian ape was in fact
a solicitation of sorts. Sweat check? I'm not wearing any clothes. I'll put a t-shirt on and
I'll get the bottle of wine though. I don't even. Do I have a blind opener? I don't think
I even do. I've not had a blind opener since moving to this place. All right there it is
finally. Recovers vitality upon performing a successful death blow. Uh yeah now we're in
business. I still do want this and I got these two. I think I want these as well.
Your face can't be on the entire time. All right hold on. I'll be right back.
Let me let me go see how hard this is going to be to do. Honest to god
I will never understand why I am the way that I am. You know I sometimes just think
about that. There are like four bottles of wine in this house. There's no way to open them.
I just keep adding to my collection. Oh that sounds good. They've corked. I can't open them.
I never get a wine opener. I just keep adding to my pantry of wines. I can't you can't use a
knife. I'll be able to fuck it up. But it's all right. We'll do the next best thing.
That's a cider. So here we go. Cheers everybody. Turn on the camera like 30 seconds.
But cameras aren't plugged. Who did this? I didn't do this.
Somebody came in here and did this. I didn't do it. Is this it?
What where did this magically disappear? Where's the USB plug for this? What the what?
It's just gone. I don't ever have a computer. Ever. Only read newspapers,
do crosswords, and use your phone. All right here we go. Hi guys. Cheers everybody.
This is cider. Ew. That was fucking insane. This game's crazy. Drinking at four o'clock
in the afternoon. It's five o'clock in the afternoon. Therefore it's legal. It's legal
now. I can do it now. I need a minute after that. I need to go on like a light jog
after that one. What's wrong with your sideburns? They're always fucked up. I have
like a misshapen face. So they're never gonna be correct. Sorry. It's pretty good. No wine
though. I can't have I can't have wine. I look lovely. Thank you. What's going on here?
What's going on here? Okay I thought hair just fell out but it was actually on the screen.
Why don't you do face cam? Always have face cam on. Dude you'll get like more viewers.
That's why we turned it off. All right back to the game. So who's my favorite boss so
far? Uh for those of you that have gotten this far and played this far probably uh
Genichiro. That one felt the most uh I felt that that one was the most involved for me.
A giant gorilla throwing shit at you and I mean this was cool. All right I'm thinking
ready. Typical typical Saul's camera right guys? Oh look at that. Sorry. Complain,
complain, complain. All right can I ask you guys how many of you guys have watched
other streamers play uh this game? Maybe a bunch of you? What what's percentage wise? Okay let's say
well not percentage but where do I fit in like the streamer complains about the video game
and is like angry at the video game? Where do I sit there? You know let's say one is
streamer didn't do it at all and ten is streamer is so obnoxious with how much they're
talking about how the game's not good and how it's the game is hard and it's too hard
and I hate this game it's stupid the mechanics are dumb. Like where do I sit there?
The four? About a four? All right I'm all right with the four.
Keep me honest though if I get over a five if we get to like six territory you guys got to
let me know. I don't want I don't want to get to six territory. Get it off the screen!
All right a white lotus flower found blooming in the depths of the sunken valley where
the fountain had waters pooled deeply. The flower's aroma attracts female apes.
Thus the guardian ape carefully tended it to it so as to offer it to his bride.
One of the incense ingredients sought by the divine air for immortal separates. That's kind
of sad. Well I have the lotus. I can now go talk to the kid and we can continue to progress.
Nothing up there right? How could you? Well I needed his soul. I needed increased attack power.
Look he is he was like suffering down here for like 4 000 years.
But wait don't ever just leave an area without checking.
You know there could be something over here. Nothing? Really?
What's wrong with some of you guys? Um let's just go back. Jerma lied about Minecraft VR.
Thank you for the five community subs. Again thank you. Coming in with the five subs.
All right so I got the flower now. I have to go put the flower.
Talk to the kid. He's in the library right? Is he still in here? I got the flower!
I procured the flower for the was it truly blooming in the sunken valley yeah deep within the
valley so that is where the fountain had waters pulled deeply he's done well to acquire this
wolf oh and actually i found something i discovered there's another scent we need another one what
is it the blood of the divine air of the dragon's heritage in other words my blood
what i gotta kill him
whoa i just like fucking went down in my seat however
in the world can you walk this thing i found a curious journal belonging to lord tecaru's page
and it appears there is a way for me to bleed for now i'd like to ask you to keep this for me
here we go page's diary an old diary entry written by tecaru's page lord tecaro held his
arm over the incense burner and attempted to cut it with a sword but incredibly his wound healed
instantly and not a drop of blood was shed lady tomo said without it your blood cannot be spilled
what could she be referring to i wonder now then we just need to figure out how to make
me bleed perhaps we should ask lady emma let me ask you this she should have much knowledge
do you bleed let me ask you this do you believe let me ask you this superman do you believe i gotta
get it right let me ask you something superman do you believe perfect emma emma emma there is
i'm reaching a six at last like what the sakura tree behind the castle
it is a sakura tree that lord tecaru brought from his homeland so it's a sakura tree from
the divine realm yes it's quite a mysterious one is that it was constantly in bloom even
outside of spring poison swamp town oh i can't wait why there was a person who cut off branch
and took flowers from he stole it without the everblossom there oh i have the monkey drink
right there was a dragon rod epidemic in ashina what every single person i see it was the title
of the stream i don't remember what it was i can't see it from here has alleviated this regret
oh right right right i mean that's kind of true all right so we're going to poison swamp
can't wait anything else i can do what do i have for uh lady emma about the sakura tree what
she said the tree is called an everblossom lord tecaru brought it here from the divine realm
but it has withered away i wonder if i should give the prosthetic guy the monkey booze however
it is said that someone plucked a branch from the everblossom and stole off with it who would
do such a thing some fucking loser what's lost is lost finding a stolen tree branch
we have no information to go on let us gather what we can for the aroma first as you wish
nice whatever you fucking lose oh why doesn't the souls team make like a boston guy for like
never mind i gotta dial the weird back a little bit uh okay well let's go back to where
we were so this is let's just go back to the watering hole and go up from there drunk off
of one cider i've had a sip and a half of cider logically speaking and scientifically speaking
what you are describing is not possible okay it's not physically possible can i get back
up it's this way right can't get up there we'll just go to the isn't there an idol
right here weighing less than i weigh like 152 so give it a rest is it this one yes so
here we go can i go is it can i jump to anything kind of we're just gonna keep going down um
yeah it's a poison swamp they i don't know why they keep making these at this point it's
it's an inside joke right it's a joke this is them just making a joke there's no way that
they do this again this is specifically to make people like me angry why really we've done this
like six times the sludge you can't go that fast poison like they okay hold on it you then
they've done fire level lava level they've done ice level poison level too much why don't
you do like a celestial level or something get us like onto the rainbow road and go to outer
space or something it's their signature at this point well this signature is a fucking mess i
can't even read it it's just like scribble whatever who cares just give me my what'd you
what'd you tip off six percent what a dick what my hamburger was a little undercooked
you're a dick all right is this guy gonna do something oh that's a lot of swings back it up
oh fuck break them six percent is a lot a six percent tip is not a big tip
six percent six percent is like the server didn't refill your water one time she came over and said
that your shirt looks ugly and was visibly drunk at work all right so let's go here
all right i will tell okay i'll give you one i'm gonna dial back my um poison swamp stupid
thing because at least i can jump from tree to tree here it's not totally awful yeah okay
this is not that bad all right we got two you're gonna sneak up behind here i think
that's not gonna happen never mind and there's another one there's the other one
another gun there's one i gotta get the person with the gun you will fuck this whole thing up
all right now one on one nope there's a guy with a gun down there get out of the poison
out of the poison out out out don't want to stay in here for that long please out all right thank
god all right up here you and me one on one let's go you're the hard one
oh that didn't like that did you oh he's gonna break my posture fuck this guy's a rough
he just parried me there it is come on whoa he's gonna kill me damn what happens
community subs i just missed i was focusing sorry it was intense what uh who gave the community
subs 10 community subs damn germa lied about minecraft vr you are just coming in hot with
subs ever since i played minecraft vr on stream uh thank you i need to start using these i just
i have so much trouble i can't help it i did the same thing in resident evil 2 you can
saw me play through that any item that looks even remotely useful i can't use it because
it's so useful that i don't want it to use i don't want to use it it's too useful okay so
where do i go from here this way i guess we're gonna wrap around here it's not useful when you
don't do anything when it does nothing i know it's bad i agree with you completely
it looks like we're going that way give me up okay oh something over here npc maybe or
mini boss probably somebody in the hut and somebody in here hello
pellets are very useful i should probably get as many of those i can afford
uh yellow gunpowder that i got green mossy gourd refills upon rest
it doesn't heal poison status it reduces poison build-up and increases poison resistance
another gourd huh how much money do i have i have one dollar
that sucks um i have a thousand i have 1100 god damn it well i don't have enough money
and go this way so this is that way i'm gonna go down see what's down here i don't
like this already uh huh apparently there's a there's something here i have to react
immediately uh ghosts in the walls or rock people okay even further down oh jesus christ okay
it's that was scary is there something i need to do here i think i'm i don't know it's just
should i sneak oh fuck you come on do it again no you're just annoying jesus
oh god i'm trying to i'm trying to catch it just go ash i feel like i'm wandering
into something i shouldn't be here wait i just heard him does he know i'm here he know oh that
was a very bad move i don't understand okay hold on sneak under here it's all poison in
there what the fuck i didn't see him i'm fucking poisoned god all right get me the how many
geckos are in here what what it's i don't i'm getting indicators in every direction
there's a lot of them in here off i don't want to accidentally hit the snake
you little punks stop it is there anything even in here uh now what i'm stuck am i i don't
am i gonna do the thing the thing that i made the joke about that wasn't even real
oh shit look at all that i'm gonna get across who's over there can i jump on him
i don't know where i ended up where am i i don't know where i am where the fuck am i
i'm gonna die this is i'm i'm wasting so many of these uh where you know i wish that instead
of just teleporting you to a random spot it's so easy to get lost i wish it would just do the
mario kart thing if you fall off and look he too comes over and pulls you up you know
what i mean like i don't even know what the hell it even put me it went to a black screen
and i teleported to a random place on the map at the very beginning well that sucks i'm just
gonna run get through here watch out this guy right in the corner right over here watch out
all right don't ask me how you still like now can i get up this way because that's
where the items are what come on really how is that how am i not grabbing onto this shit
ah is it something i can do from here
ah watch out it's gonna be like dun no scrap yeah i guess it's a snake boss isn't it
no not another one of these scenarios where i have to hide no well i mean i can go there
but can i make that jump but what do i make the jump where do i go from there um
is there anything to grab
okay but that's not possible what about i can't grab anything there's nothing to grab there
i didn't know this was here i didn't know this was here um oh shit it's a guy with a frying pan
isn't it no oh he was hiding from a snake too i'm sorry i'm sorry i didn't i didn't mean to
what i did all right um up and then sneak that's it i have to do this uh okay well
that's unfortunate where the fuck am i supposed to go then not down there there was another
place i could go i was trying to grab onto something oh well it's okay fuck that hurt
here we go yeah fuck the fighting just get me to where i was before because there is that way
but there's also this way i can go over here oh this no no no no no around the corner
that's down into the pit again up here i think what do you mean i can't grab it
what do you mean barks has bite what do you mean barks has bite what do you mean barks
has bite johnny what do you mean barks has bite um do i i might have to go down no this way
am i just going the direction i just came from yeah because this just wraps around unless
i can go over here which doesn't look like it huh i guess i have to go to snake i thought
maybe there'd be a way to go down here i don't think there's any other way to go
no snake it is apparently or did i open i don't think i opened up in the area after the gorilla
um hold on oh no no no i don't want to fight this guy
so the snake but snake instantly kills me and then i'll reach this i'm just gonna bond
the hell out of here all right let me look at the let me look at the bonfires
so wait i have a new prosthetic hello what's that you have there where did you get that finger
the guardian ape of the sunken valley i found it in his belly i see you think it was in the belly
of an ape let me see it i'll fix it to you okay so this is the finger whistle divine abduction
can i finger whistle the snake its sound will grab an enemy's attention and draw them to the
whistle's location by locking onto a target only the targeted enemy will hear the whistle
i can't be like enrages beasts making them unable to discern between friend and foe
well there it is okay this is i need to do this first if i want to do better uh
firecrackers try figuring the monkey that's hiding behind the snake
will that scare the monkey this guy's dying you've caught it too
oh shit how many of those things do i have do you have any more stuff to buy you know
you have a lot of pellets okay let me see all right we have antechamber the dojo the
lookout point the old grave the giant serpent shrine the reservoir i think from the reservoir
can i go up or is it maybe the dojo i feel like there was a way to go out here
go check on the training guy nothing in there you may use me uh he's got no new training or
anything if you have tech all right i'm gonna go this is tricky because i think i have to go
either here or here what about this place oh wait a minute what about the there's like a
guy here right isn't there a boss here this stuff this shit down here too this is new
it's fake uh say hello every time you sign is it me you're calling hi if it isn't the
shinobi following the sound brought me here this whole is he talking about the magician down here
i see the gals matters the melody i don't i don't know is that so then please i'd like to listen
there's a melody there's a song down here there's a melody down here
oh wait a minute this part ah right okay i remember this now bye you're not gonna throw me
off here ah that was death i would have died right there thank god i got the intuition of a
goddamn leopard now what now what do i do down i guess over here oh oh okay excuse me
easy enough you just hollows ash i got so much of this another hole uh do i check up here first
i feel like there's another way i can look you just killed a homeless guy in a cave
um no i didn't well yes i did okay that zombie did not have a home he was walking around
aimlessly so yes that zombie was probably homeless probably i'm just going whatever terror
well wait don't okay i found a new one this was his home ashina depths back to the poison
wonderful lots of items scattered everywhere like over there let's just get that one first
let's wrap i gotta use this shit can i make this i think i can kill this guy
well i thought i thought okay he could still hit me from here snake eyes this uh okay fine
i don't even know who is attacking me apparently there's a mini boss down here
uh somewhere is it the guy that was right here is that guy right there
i have to kill this dude like from the ledge it's very obvious
okay that's that's snake eyes on the right there he shoots the gun
who else is over here i gotta take a look before i commit to anything okay lots of gunpowder and
lots of stuff around all right what else we got a guy up there no i'm doing that poison in the
water here whoa it's just the item run oh what wow no fucking way that was unbelievable
okay i think i got all the items jesus no i can't oh you can't dodge in the water
you can't dodge in the water great oh i fucked this lady before it's just one of these
but not with a guy raining mortars everywhere there's like three people doing that here
oh my lord i'm gonna have to go around and kill all of them one by one jesus this is
stupid i was i was about to say stupid i was about to don't say it yet don't say
it i'm i'm at like a three or four right now don't do it well i did i got the items so let's
try this again give me this one at least just give me all the item and okay just i guess
we're gonna do this and get me i have to put that back on all right i could try i could go
this way though let's see what's over here no all right so what's up here is there a guy over here
i need to like pull one of these guys but they can just shoot from far away and if i go over
here the lady will just see me maybe it's just back stabbed a lady and just fight her over
here without being seen that's impossible right who's seeing me now okay got back up top
there now i gotta deal with that guy first get out of the stealth please what this guy's
got to die oil is this one oh he didn't see me hmm there's two one there one there i wonder
if it's worth trying to backstab and then try this does this actually work can't really lock
on come on can't come on you can see me but i can't see you come on i'm just gonna see
if it does come on come on come investigate what all right well um if i go over there she's
gonna see me if i go over there to fight that i'm just gonna fight i'm just gonna backstab this
person and just fight i'm just gonna go for it hopefully i can do a position where i can
backstab her and then run back this way without aggring everybody she had this
kind of sight right here here we go right all right then you see me i think get out of
stealth why am i walking onto that person all right here we go back up this way all right
how are we doing good i'll fight you right over here let's go come on come on come on come on come
on no no no no where'd you go come on come on get over here good good good all right i'm
getting poison damage though all right back it up right here let's go all right one on one
come on in i wonder if she's taking poison damage right now yeah she's poisoned whoa oh
it's because i'm in the fucking swamp oh that sucks very bad very fucking bad i can't dodge
this is actually this is a terrible idea damn it that move sucks
almost almost almost almost get out of here all right miniboss done
turned out it was a great idea i just said 85 dollars somebody's gave 85 bucks hold on
uh thank you tate teidolf swiftler thank you for the 85 dollars that's a lot of
fucking money thank you so much and you say wait a minute hold on am i paused okay yeah uh they say
hey germa boot camp sucked since nobody got my germa impressions uh but now that i have some
money in my account i figured i'd show my appreciation with the bits thanks for all the
genuine heartfelt content you keep putting out and i look forward to tuning in to future
streams it may it may not mean much coming from me but i think you're the best streamer
on twitch since you make an honest effort to reach out to your audience stay great thank
you so much uh tato uh it means a lot that means a lot don't ever think that that doesn't mean
anything you say you may not mean much uh it means an absolute fucked hunt thank you so
goddamn much i wish you the best thank you for being here if you give if you give me 85
dollars and you don't think that means anything you get it that's that's an incredible amount
of money to give somebody and with a message like that attached to it it means a lot
even if you give a dollar a 10 cents it doesn't matter you allow me to do this every day for you
know four days five days whatever once a week but for real i i say it a lot but it's true
i gave you a dollar once and thank you for it because you don't have to do that it's all
optional which is it's just i can't believe it i don't want anyone to ever feel like they're
required to pay money to me you know i say i say a lot but seriously that's a big posture break
oh give me give me give me give me give me okay well i might as well kill you so i can
just take a little look around here i was just predicting i was gonna go up here can i get
them are you gonna forget i'm here because then i can go over there okay this should be
it right no i don't even need it i don't even need it excellent all right that's level that's
three so here we go item run i want the thing is i think i like the firecracker is the best
out of all the items seems the most useful for me so i'm going down firecracker tree
i have to make a decision uh fuck that guy i already got everything up there this where was
that little mini bus standing right here how do i get up there from here that way
you got a hand i can grab onto maybe i can do from up there across the way
wait too long whoa i don't think he's gonna do that bad he's gonna do it okay goodbye
from here i can go on top of head on top of head to hand really huh well shit anything
up there i can grab holy shit 90 dollars 90 bucks from comedy chat man that's a great name
thank you for the 90 dollars military gang coming in courtesy of my local casino losing
for once love you thank you comedy chat man gambling money glad you made it out glad you
made it out of the casino with some cash but thank you for the fucking extreme generosity
that means a lot thank you well i don't endorse this gambling i i've already we've talked about
gambling already if you if you're just gonna enjoy yourself and have some fun at the casino
and you're of age then yeah like you can have some fun but don't just don't go overboard don't
you just have fun don't do anything crazy find a small minimum table play minimum bets
enjoy the atmosphere and know what to do know when to get out vegas corrupted him
i did i'm fine but i am absolutely i'm grateful to take your casino winnings thank you so fucking
much for the 90 bucks i i'll tell you i'm kind of stuck here i feel like there's something i'm
missing because i can't go from here to there there was a wall behind the mini boss yeah but
it looked like it was a little too high for me to get over there am i crazy i guess not okay
i thought there was a wall to try to jump up okay well uh this definitely leads to
around the corner holy shit comedy chat man i gave another 50 dollars what if i said i won
this with max bet uh look so that hey that's on you to decide i'm not gonna tell you not
to max bet nonetheless that's still that's another 50 dollars oh jesus is that another
that's another rape no no no no that's not another rape do i have to do this again
does this one have a headless horseman thing no way do you have to do this again
i refuse to believe that no way uh-uh uh-uh that's not true you know i don't have to do
this they're not going to play that same card twice why would they do that that it
makes no sense i just need to prove to myself this is like a scripted moment i'm not gonna
jump down here and like the snake's gonna eat them or something or they're gonna get a fight
it's gonna be like the t-rex versus velociraptors where's my idol from here nice what did it what
i don't they both look exactly the same i don't know which way is the right way
of course god damn it why okay so this is i let me just see what's this is that's not
the way to go guy with one of the guns did this to you um really both there's no escape
i'm getting telltale aped right now okay well um knowing that that's over here
i'm gonna go heal at the where's the nearest one probably this one's the best one to do
because you can just jump and run straight right i would assume this is probably the better one to
do because it is just just jump off because this is holy shit more money another 50 bucks
50 more dollars from pro sef pro star military money let's go except i'm only rotc got the
military represent coming in here thanks a lot guys thank you pro sef for the fucking 50
bucks you guys are too kind thank you now i have to fight the monkey um that's what do you think
i'm doing i'm just getting full health so i can go in there with at least an attempt yeah this
is the best route because you can just all right um i'm ready to watch the but what can i like
sneak on hold on why would you be able to go from this way does this do anything for you
can i like do something sneaky here or is it no you just kill this guy again all right i don't
believe they're gonna do this again but let's go let's see what happens is it the same guy
it's the same same ape okay well hopefully my muscle memory is still here seems to be pretty
good easy i got this again so what is phase three of ape he has two bars what the hell
could this be well yeah i could have had it missed it though oh don't get too close
oh shit bait oh what's with the double bait here get in back it up what's phase three
does he put the head back on and fucking start singing i don't understand like what's he gonna
do damn it i tried here we go all right here we go what is this what's the next phase
okay are we just gonna stay here we're gonna just keep he's running away he's gonna put the
head back on head is back on i knew it he it's a tag team okay that's just fucking fantastic
what the hell do you do sir who i don't have to fight him anymore i just have to avoid him
are you serious he doesn't have a health bar anymore um well fuck off i don't know where i
am back it up there it is come on no don't do it don't do it don't don't easy easy
i got him right where i want him shit come on he's so close look at that health got you
motherfucker all right get out of my way let's go you ain't gonna do that shit to me i ain't
going down here not gonna happen come on get the combo going really fuck you man
oh no you call the tag team fight in there oh what's that doesn't even fucking matter
easy now easy not gonna fucking fool me here man but after all this bullshit pull it in oh
you are so close i'm topping myself off see you later hey call your mother for me
you're gonna get up again unbelievable i can't believe that they did that memory headless a
the battle memory of an extraordinary foe lingering in the mind of the wolf commune with a sculptor's
idol and confront memories of battle to permanently increase tack power good colossal beast plague
with the power of undying you're gonna stand up i know it that's two of course you're gonna
stand the fuck up why wouldn't you of course you are he's dead he's gonna come back
uh i got him okay he's dead is he dead is he gonna stand up he by hope not dude if i come back
here and have to do that shit again oh come on uh well let me put my points in there we go
physical attributes vitality and posture have increased and here it is headless ape at one
time the guardian ape shared its den with a mate but he alone became infested with while
the other passed away even the flowers offered in tribute to her passing have withered to dust
so this thing is going to be like mr rex well at least i got points for it uh we had huge bits
come in from comedy chapman during that fight thank you so much for the hundred dollars
comedy chapman and my bank just texted me asking if this was fraudulent uh you probably
you probably should so not would you not charge that many times but be careful
i appreciate the fucking hundreds of dollars holy shit thank you my god all right well i have a
feeling you'll be back why don't just just just cut this thing in half whatever it's undying
i got it i got the ape let me see was there a way i could go from here can i go up that
cliff no i can't reach that yeah i can't wait i can from here oh okay well i didn't see the
indicator all right now what the hell am i supposed to do oh hi still walking around huh
she's gone but she was here just moments ago shinobi listen i finally saw her the shamisen
player was a woman i only saw her from afar i tell fleeting presence oh i should have asked
if she was calling to me before i knew it disappeared this guy's kind of going crazy huh
now that i think it over my father told me stories about a hidden town shrouded deeply don't
ever go there he said but now misty forest if only i could figure out how to get through it
and find that shamisen player it's coming from deep in the fog i don't know shit apparently
that melody is calling me apparently i just don't know shit if only i okay uh nice knowing you
well here's the fog oh i got five all right what do you say
i feel like i need to get some more of these run slide or i don't feel like i don't use this
that often though it does it twice this is the night jaw slash i mean i am so far down this
tree that i might as well just do it let's do it so this is a double and this is the cross
it covers posture upon executing a successful death blow that's really good
that'll be helpful in some boss fights maybe not um probably this then or i'll hold on to
it all right what about my skills here is it already equipped double let's see here
adds a follow-up attack so wait hold on so oh wow so i can just do it twice
your posture that way all right cool what's this uh is breadcrumbs for me to find my way around
probably who knows oh well it's the return of the chickens any more chickens no just one
hiding over here oh by the way i first tried that double ape thing
just in case somebody wouldn't pay attention i told you i was gonna do it once what does
that mean i am just gonna do this are we talking oh come on i'm still like
how much does the mist protect me this guy's a ghost wait can i kill this yeah i can kill
that's it right you did you know what i'm gonna use one of these
i like what is this sure like just do it oh uh not yet whoa not yet hold on who
uh this game is relentless i just did double ape and there's already a guy standing there
that guy also doesn't have a head is that a small ape what's with small ape without head
just wait there's other shit up here i'm not going to run into a wall for the next 40
minutes right now let me just get some stuff and just take a look around this item right
the apes they're it's all apes it's all apes hey you one of whom i speak
hides in an abandoned temple up ahead he sealed away the village in a shadowy fog
but he can fool the villagers an abandoned temple yes it's an old building
the door may be closed hole in the second floor should be a hole in the second floor
thanks for the help old man anything else you have for me
hole in the second floor go up to the hole in the second floor i will try no guarantees
let's get this item while we're here pellets i thankfully getting a lot of those
what is it turkey oh you get over here okay hmm coin purse haven't found one of those in a
while that leaves me how many how much money do i have i gotta go buy some coin sacks you know
i'm saying i'm getting into the thick of it here well i thought i was only gonna have to
hit you once okay there is the guy with no head down that way somewhere in the beginning
okay well there's the second floor
who's next more ow it's a ghost dog
oh fuck where is he oh i can't you hard to see them through the fog okay not not yet not yet
not yet not yet i need to explore oil well let's just look down here i see some items
mr was three sacks down there that's gotta be a trap right who who is it what the fuck
oh fuck i'm broken i think i've heard that holy shit i knew it was kind of just get them get them
oh fuck holy shit oh boy this is bad very bad i'm dead there's like 50 people down here
get me out get me out get me out out out where the fuck did i just fall what the hell
see you uh-oh can everybody see me because i got kind of you motherfucker of course right sure
you seriously seriously where what what the fuck it why
hey he's all the way across there unbelievable i can't do this that guy has to die where's this
asshole my fucking god is so many oh my god they just are in brand okay not gonna happen sorry
no you fuck off go to hell there he is yuck finally can i get a second here now can i get
the actual items please scrap somebody else is up here laser lightning vision doesn't matter
where you are i'll have tracking and line of sight on you forever did you jump fuck it i
still got you are you between are you across the map through mist 2 000 feet away i still
got you in the head okay i think that freed it up now i should be able to get that item
over there i think we'll see because that guy was standing right here and now i can shimmy
across right it better be if you're good at something to never do it this guy likes to
complain huh across the map the mist i could complain about that what huh what was the mini
boss thing there i just got like an indicator that's weird why did i just get a mini boss
thing oh i'm back here i'm back here the headless guy right oh okay well let's try
to go inside the uh tower everybody's dead so
except for you you're still alive take a look around don't just wait look around back
uh-huh see see this is what where'd he go i'm gonna kick well dishonorable dishonor
okay this guy's gonna fucking kill me the dirt-throwing asshole
oh no he had air pods in he can't see or smell or whatever knock this off now i'm only doing one
at a time look you can't they're invisible and how did i not block you oh the complaints
are starting to pile up he's starting to get to like a four it's going to a five what were
you looking at just a ceramic shot the worst i don't let him get to you i think i've collected
everything is that the music that the guy was talking about the melody i can hear it now does
that mean i'm going crazy anything up here don't think so maybe yeah there's some stuff over there
can't grab anything from there are we supposed to hear music yeah it's supposed to be playing a
little tune right now um what's the correct path to get up there we go this way um nothing
above me either i don't think i can grab anything over there i'm here can i grab that well this is
the only one i can grab right here apparently a dog i'm not i can't grab these ones who's this
dog right there where are you where the fuck are you it's two of you
yeah no the door is locked i can't go in the front door i have to go up top
somebody said go inside it's not that easy you would think that i would be able to jump from
the one over there to somewhere whoa you just scared the shit out of me okay let me go around
this way i think these guys just respawn here what the fuck i'm just lost here
and this is they just keep respawning in this misty bullshit zone i went all the way back
here well this there's a guy here now who the fuck is this why oh it's all about the monkeys
welcome to skiro do you like apes my god it's a drunk guy fuck me really um
i gotta remember how to fight this guy maybe not what if i just get the hell out of here
uh i don't have any healing i don't know if i'll be able to beat this guy with just one
no health back it up i'm surprised i have to fight this guy again to grab right
weird oh i'm fucked bad idea bad idea get me the fuck out of here where he kills he's gonna
kill me right now i can't jump off the wall oh game i hate you you put like two defensive
linemen in every place that i want to go there's a guy downstairs the guy upstairs
the hell is in here nothing oh fuck he's chasing me oh fuck that he can't get over
here right oh thank god it's just barely out of reach everybody calling me a coward right now
uh yeah i'm sorry i'm not gonna fight this guy with no health potions a dude i haven't seen in
like 22 hours of gameplay i'm not gonna fight him right now i need health uh am i going i
think that this is probably the is this the right way i'm gonna take a pellet because one
yeah i will accidentally get touched by somebody and die lump of fat wax can be used for
intermediate and higher occultic upgrades for prosthetic tools nice oh all right so you have
to go that way now how the fuck would you figure that out i mean i did but how the hell
would you figure that out i thought the guide do i get another stone where's my stone okay
this is a this is like a zoidberg i don't get a i don't get a thing for zoidberg uh well time
to die might as well give it at least an attempt dude i still got it i just got sucked
lump of grave wax wow that guy i just destroyed that guy this is a giant shrimp
no i didn't get a bead for that the mist is gone that's a plus okay now the enemy is just
alive now they need to be regular dogs i have no idea what did i go so they would illusion
people was that dude feels weird oh wait i can see there's a thing right there but if i go
down there where's the guy i need to complete my quest thankfully there's an idol right down
here what's that i don't know well i'm gonna get the idol because by the hell wouldn't i
okay i have a checkpoint here is this this dude's back where you find the departed
you'll find the memorial
buy an offering okay what you got sugar you got scrap dragon spring sake you got these
no i haven't seen a gourd in a long time what do i have for money
3017 maybe i'll just buy a ship one of these 1800 for this reduces terror and increases
terror resistance where you find well i don't know apparently i didn't have that on
what do i have to sell a whole lot of nothing i have 31 of these what does this do restores a
node of resurrected power
i gotta pee this is a bad guy yeah i guess i almost have four points me boo village whoa
they're back we'll never die are they just coming out of the ground i can't tell
that was the scream that i make did you almost just get
grabbed by the monkey boss okay what in the name of god is going on here
all right i gotta pee there's an item and i need to i don't know what i i i'm i'm i'm
getting off my head here there's a couple of mini bosses back there who the hell are you
who the fuck is this you're you're uh not nice move nice move no don't i gotta stop
doing that shit man this guy's hard scrap what was he guarding he's guarding something
treasure carp what's that noise can i sneak under here i guess not okay i need to pee
i'm gonna pee i'm gonna drink a little bit of water and i'm gonna grab another cider
i'll be right back we get this okay uh what about that guy living down here
kinda there's a little entry way to go how many dogs gotta go i just gotta go and swing
him there's a bunch of dogs swinging everybody sometimes you gotta spam dogs what's the music
still playing for this item i think that's the only thing that's over here well that's
wonderful all that for just a coin purse no what oh what you dick i don't even know
the fuck i am a really bad place to fight this dude
fuck no god damn it he's kicking my ass break him get out of here
okay that's that was the wait was that the guy that i did what give me that item even
item this is the item writer that i was looking for fat wax any more items no this is shit i gotta
be careful there's stealth there's a bunch of people here fuck oh i'm okay i'm okay
are you a person yes thank goodness you are an honorable person
you want to ask look sorry but if you have questions i'll have to answer with this basket
on my head um okay ask ask about the village what's wrong with the village sure like to
know that too before i knew it everyone had gone insane for a while i too was in a daze
i snapped out of it after i
i was thirsty so i drink a lot of sake i'm sure that's what made me throw up the head priest
sometimes treats us to sake but you know when you drink sake you get thirsty the sake cask
runs dry in no time so everyone has no choice but to drink the water in the ponds and rivers
but drink it the thirstier you get what the fuck is going on here
thirstier thirstier can't ever drink enough uh what about the villagers wrong with the villagers
no idea all i know is they all fear fire for a while
now
fire it's a real nuisance you know he goes the village outcast he likes eating wild
animal meat in the sword that's why the head priest doesn't give him any sake
where is inohico's house oh what the fuck was that okay what is that noise
be about the priest someone just broke a bunch of shit important person in the entire village
you can find him in the shrine although we have the riverside near the water source
he told us let us become citizens of the palace if you drink enough sake you shall
i'm safe in here right i hope so i don't i hear something getting louder
okay you've been i'll be here you've been a big help thank you um i'm gonna go in the boat
wealth balloon uh okay he said the house over here hold on i'm gonna get this stuff in the
boat pellet all right safe more houses can i go into any of these
i wonder if there's a place to drop in um e items give me this bowl of ash
scrap pine resin ember a piece of resin that contains a continuously smoldering flame
can be used to upgrade the flame vent the resin was found in a black pine within the
forest of meble village the ever smoldering flames act as a landmark to find ways to the
village in time the villagers came to load the flames and the black pines were lost those
who defended the flame were equally low god of last uh uh i'm so i'm so confused and scared at
the same time i don't like this place i'm just gonna go to the hut over here down there i can
go across this oh can i go down here i wonder if i can make it from this way probably can
where oh you can swim yeah but i don't i want to check the outskirts it could be items and
scrap and shit all right hi i'm paul forgot about that i'm doing anything over there
um what i'm kind of uh all right it's time just to see what the hell you got going on over here
i get off me really what is this resident evil one yes gourd seed oh i'm just picking
up items oh oh somebody's got me get off me too many too many duns too many duns
we got a guy with the bell make it make it make it make it come on grab you yes okay i'm
almost there um fine confetti i have yellow gunpowder oh fuck and then i'm gonna climb up
here there's a wheel give me this thing oh all right rest here so i have a statue on this side
and the statue on the other side didn't say there was a guy in this house whatever that
item is i want i need it um fuck there's a way to go over here too oh god can i get him
twice all right we got another big guy i think i can wrap around here uh is is this a starter
zone that looks like the thing in the beginning contact medicine good i gotta get this guy first
what are they what are they doing like stardew valley out here okay is there any what's over
here i said this is hard to explore because it's kind of all over the place but i kind of want
to see what the hell is this is what is this no i already got the seed item right here pellets
so i got i got i got both side there i got one they're got incoming plane something in there
something in here there's a lot of items fuck i want to get up there fuck there's too many
items in this zone i have to get them i could go down there too oh okay what's this yes
i'm starting to feel so fulfilled but i almost have every item in this whole zone
all right let's go i'm gonna level up my gourd thing fuck let's take a look five midair deflection
i can get this i can get the ashina cross i can get the final thing in this tree
from a sheath stance draw the blade at high speed sheathed how do you how do i do go to
into sheath and l rt to enter sheath stance release left trigger cancel sheath stance leave
sheath battle stance release right trigger ashina cross fuck it let's get it all right so
sheathed that gets you out if you let go of left trigger but if you let go of right trigger
okay there he is did you make it hey sorry i slaughtered the person that you thought was cool
i guess did okay that's it anything else um i feel like this is not going to be useful here
uh i don't know hey there welcome to my little comfy mode i forgot hold on all right uh gourd seed
i would like to level it up please first of all here didn't i get something no i didn't where is
it hey okay didn't i get something special all right it's time to start spending points i can't
just be a piece of crap right like i have to use these i hold on to them what if i need them
i gotta pick a tree just go i did get the flame thing right i'm going for it let's go flame
vent then we can go through to loaded umbrella magnet when spread open it will protect against
attacks from all directions hold it out while moving to protect from light attacks as a
tempered magnetic shaft that makes it nearly unbreakable enemy attack can be deflected by
spinning the open umbrella all right well here's the fucking super one if it's a short range flame
blast continuous fire damage will inflict the burn status it is able to maintain a continuous
stream of flames due to the smoldering resonance side of the tube mechanism so i
just need money and then a few more well let's see yeah i need money and then a few more
those so i got a better flame vent i just need money that seems stupid how much money do i have
i got money i've got some money how much is it 500 okay it's 600 so that brings this
is the better umbrella that we got the flame vent which goes to golden vortex
jesus what do you mean na math it's 600 i'm talking about so i need three more black gun powder
and then look at this shit golden vortex a large and with a golden fan gather illustrious
golden wind and release it to force enemies caught in the vortex to face the other way
can be performed twice in a row enemies that have been turned around drop items or money
considered to be donations and this is the new umbrella when spread open it will protect
against attacks from all directions the blessing of the vermilion bird prevents damage from fire
and also prevents burn sounds kind of good all right so i need some more black gun powder
i got you want some monkey booze i got it here i brought something for you monkey booze is it
it burns the throat same as ever this really brings back memories did you drink this often
i trained in the techniques of the shinobi in the valley where the monkeys dwelled by yourself
no there were two of us we were rogue shinobi there was no proper master for the likes of us
that's why we went to the valley to run to jump to clash swords where one slip would mean
your doom that was how we trained we came to move exactly as monkeys did after a time
i drink this monkey booze whenever i tire
dude i can't wait for the youtube channels that come out with
the diy monkey booze from sakiro it was from his unique ring one part simple syrup
two parts grenadine a splash of sprite and triple sec i'll take seven million views please
thank you guys all right i think that's all i can do that's shitting it like a monkey does
monkeys don't shit in their food they shit in their hands and throw it at people
all right umbrella spring loaded firecracker and okay well what the heck and spring load flame
vent i've got all what the fuck am i doing spring load spring load there we go thank you
now i need to give the seed to the lady i can charge it right
oh that's actually really cool it shouldn't cost a money here let's be real where's the lady
oh wait didn't she why are we owning we're just owning this is a stream where you come
and you see me own in a game i spent like 16 hours fighting the double monkey headless
thing now i own here there is something yes in the divine air be made to put you seek to do so
the blood of the divine air is required obtain the dragon tears from the divine realm
and achieve immortal severance oh i see it is true that the divine air's blood cannot be
shed by normal need however the means to do so can be found in sample temple the mortal
yes mortal blade immortal severance scrap part of the book of immortal severance left behind
by takaru with mortal blade in hand my blood may be shed with my blood the aroma will be
complete the divine realm will be in reach immortal severance will be at hand i must ask
tomo to assist with the beheading this was written by lord takaru it was with the
mortal blade you may wound the divine and his blood get the mortal blade i see this brings
us one step closer to the yet and how about that right of course but i got a seed can i
have some extra gourd because i told the mortal blade yes i should of course here oh this is
this is monkey what you don't like it well let me try it i kind of want monkey booze
oh monkey booze is the moonshine of sekiro right yes seem to have a strong connection with monkeys
you do yes i was rescued by a monkey after all this is some jungle book shit here do you
was young raised by wolves i could do nothing neither cry nor even get angry complete shock
you i want to be like you maybe an ape walk like you talk like you
didn't they add that character didn't that care to not exist
he gave me the rice ball it tasted so good what a kind monkey
king louis does not exist in that story disney added that character
sorry to ruin your childhood goodbye did you speak with lady emma i did i did and what did she say
that it could be possible with the mortal blade i see so the mortal blade will allow my blood
to flow as you wish i've heard the mortal blade is in senpo temple will you obtain it for me
as you wish i mean as long as you don't get too prideful in full metal alchemist
i went i went i went i went i went
keep up the good work wolf the ever blossom has withered that is correct it is said that
someone plucked a branch from the ever blossom you can go off with it what's love finding a
stolen tree branch let us gather what as you wish listen if you that's right that door marked
with the outline of a person once called it a shinobi shortcut i haven't a clue how it works
but seeing as he mentioned shinobi shinobi shortcut okay um just because you reference an
animated show like well you're not allowed to you're not allowed to ever watch a single
anime ever never you never i'm not you're never allowed to watch a single animated
television show that's not spongebob or family guy i've watched one anime per year
and they're all right they're fine okay so let me go back to where i was which where the hell
was that depth right what am i watching for 2019 um i don't know i don't know all right let's
see where the hell happens over here we're gonna there's the banjo lady let's see open
okay it's not a boss you're right
is it the guy that's following her around i don't know
she's gonna go like i told you i knew it that's a slash okay that that is not a slash
easy here that's okay it's a sweep it's a sweep oh boy oh boy i just took a fucking big
hit that was a crab i don't have any fucking clue oh my lord it's like one two three four five
she has like illusions yikes okay well lady just relax for a second so i can
that's a crush she's a sweep and a grab you know like fire what about about this
okay fireworks work every time damn she's really really good at this game damn i didn't
get it starting to figure it out a little bit all right so when she does that big
swooping slash she goes right into easy don't break the posture here this one
hurry up here we go all right but you can turn to like a fucking demon let's see what she does
comes like the broom
come to me instead shit i don't want to do that oh fuck bad bad that's okay
back it up all right so she does that like the little spin around thing i gotta be it's
a little weird the time is a little strange oh ow ow owie ow back up posture watch that
posture fuck man i'm in trouble here yeah i'm dead all right well i'm starting to figure it out
her moveset is really really interesting though what the hell didn't get it yeah i did all right
all right it's all about that posture speaking of posture and watch out for yours
fuck she's gonna recover it faster than i am all right come in aggressive don't let her get
a move in oh my god i wasn't even paying attention to my health whoa i wasn't even
looking at it i wouldn't pay any attention to it at all i was zoned the fuck in holy shit
that was fucking what a mistake you wanna know what's funny my beer is directly in the way
of the health bar to a point where i can't see it i'm gonna throw this thing i'm gonna
spike this into the wall behind me i'm gonna fucking baseball throw this beer out of the way
i'm so tilted right now these stupid fucking beer in my way i'm about to baseball throw this
into the wall it was right in the spot where like i couldn't see the health bar get out of
my fucking way jesus the streamer can't move head to see health bar you have to pay
complete attention to everything that they're doing fuck you lady all right one down one
down don't make me baseball throw shit come on really really give get give me a fucking
two seconds lady i didn't block it fuck my posture
come here don't let her just get it just get right up in there what do you got you got
nothing you bitch see get slice hi why are you still talking and he's right i don't
need beads okay thank you hers vitality upon performing it didn't already get this
uh what about this guy is he still here is that you yes if you my thanks listen player to me
just a moment ago he caressed me playing her sweet melody okay it was a different song
than before so this guy gonna go home
war spoke to me she played thank you for coming she said it turns out she was calling
to me this whole time too bad for you she was right around the corner what do i get
quest complete restore a note of resurrected power please take this cloth and use it to
bundle his little ones that he may live on in peace he's dead does it get dead uh quest complete
thanks hit him no what if he comes back thanks for the baby i'm gonna heal germa doesn't give
a shit if we backseat um i mean to an extent i do right like i don't want to see major
game spoilers in here and if you do goodbye you know mean like pop out but stuff something
like hey you know that if you consume that then you get another resurrected power i mean that's
fine but don't tell me the fucking next boss or you know like more wax cool i need that
all right um i see a potential cutscene over here wait oh you should see my face right now
that was the most puckered like face i've ever done how do i get that
i gotta drop down from here i don't think i can do it from there oh fuck this guy's alive
i gotta stop doing that i just do it my brain just does it okay we got something going on
over here i was loud got it what's in it what's in it okay divine grass it's very useful as you
saw in that ape fight it's a pad it's meant to be used now how the hell am i gonna get back up
here now this way this is something down here too i like it uh now this is the other way to go
okay so now i guess we're just gonna go across the bridge and see what's on the other side
i got a checkpoint right there okay nothing over there how do i rate the game so far on a
scale of one to ten hmm that's tricky hmm uh it might be like a seven maybe like a six point four
no i'll be honest with you i'll be completely honest i'm not gonna pretend to be like nine
eight i think this is like an eight four right now i think it's an eight four at the moment
the swamp brought it down to a 70 because it was like a 90 i told you if there's if
there was a swamp in the game i was gonna give it a minus two letter grades and i did
none of these people are even worth my time so sneak over this way uh it is since from it from
the two letter grades come up to about an 84 we'll see how the game continues oh shit can i
get in here oh i'm just looking for like a i'm just looking for a way to get that item
okay and i'm just an item sicko that's i'm sorry guys i can't get up that yes i can
come on you've got like a double jump on a wall and i can't grab that well fine okay no i didn't
want to do that i gotta go all the way around or they can i it's gotta be way to grab something
over here i want that item oh fuck it whatever you know i'm gonna have to get everything in
the game i could probably wrap around there anyways this is there's something here there
okay um hi your illusion cannot what about those hold on wait just a minute wait wait wait wait
that's a sweep hold on what about these oops he looks like a loot he looks like an illusion
let me just see what happens here oh okay that's not a terrible thing to do
not a terrible loot set so far he's doing a lot how do you fireworks how you doing
how do you fireworks fireworks is as effective as the snappy things oops i didn't block that
that's a thrust different fucking different moves okay what's this what's the hand mean
i blocked it now that was a sweep oh shit fuck you don't have very much time at all damn it
that's hard to read not terrible though i got a feeling this is going to be phase one
shit that was a sweep that was shit okay i gotta i gotta get that down
fuck you that's just you got too many movesets man what a fantastic camera you have in this
video game it's like the best it's it's the best camera i've ever seen but the best i've
ever used better than mario 64 i'll tell you comparing them all too how many pellets i think i
do damn what's phase two let's see it i can bait it here okay corrupted monk watched over the cave
entrance breathing technique allows one to dive underwater as well as breathe underwater indefinitely
oh man i can dive underwater good night oh best camera i've ever seen in my life that's true
though come on give me a break it just went like right into his pelvis for five straight
seconds so that means every pool of water can now be oh man don't do this to me now i gotta
go check every pool of water camera's not that bad no it's not but in a game like this that
requires such pinpoint focus something like that can ruin an attempt like the camera going
like like zooming straight into the front of your face and you can't see the animations
they're doing you could that could ruin an entire attempt and then i would just complain
about it and i blame the camera good thing i didn't have to do that how would you have the
camera behind you in a corner spin around and show it from bird's eye serious have it come up
and have it be a bird's eye like isometric camera for like two seconds and spin in circles
i'm fucking kidding it's hard to do that it's you have a game engine right that's not easy
to do i don't know it isn't that doesn't mean i'm not going to complain about it
sometimes make the obstacles transparent has been a staple for years yeah i mean i guess you
could do a thing where like for instance like this if when the camera the camera could essentially
just i don't know how you would do it but because this sucks right it's too close and
if the guy's in front of me he's taking up the whole screen and it's like oh shit
so i'm gonna figure it out in like 100 years anyways that's fun that was a really
fun fight it was just you just that was all about this timing the parries and the sweeps
they had a couple that was a couple of fun fights in a row all right we've gone for it's
like an 86 now it's the flower in here what's it like being a las vegan i don't know what that
means is this another boss there it is a stone found in an altar deep within the village
of the water dwellers stones will sometimes appear in the bodies of those who have long
drank from the waters step into the marital stone and offer the fragment as versus stone
one of the incense ingredients stopped by the divine air for immortal severance so i have the
other ingredient what happened in here i like this area i'm supposed to i could have fought
that guy in here just checking just checking ape incoming yeah wouldn't that be something
if i had to fight the headless ape again all right i can just go back
because this is part of storyline quest item shit i think that's all i can do here something that
this game does that all the other ones that they've ever made don't do is a lot of the
mini boss mini boss boss they don't really give you any time at all all right what do you
think you got a second nope there's another fight i actually i like it though all right uh
this looks wrong wake him oh it's just you wolf i'm sorry i was asleep i got the other ingredient
look i found something that may help us it's a stone a stone i found that stone look at this
a fragrant stone enshrined in a village within the depths of the chino one must throw oneself
forward to be found with this the found head fragrance is complete let us depart now to
the divine realm what is that strangely shaped rock you got it right now the fragrant
stone of the fountain head my lord this stone appeared to have been enshrined yes it is just
as the book described yes there was also an inscription a sweetly scented bridal offering
written on the altar bridal what sort of place was this it was in a cave
fucking dump that's all i remember in that case where was the wedding procession headed
no way to know i guess sweetly scented lord kuro that place might be the gateway to the
divine realm this is a nice length of game too because how long have i been streaming so
far i see you've gathered some of the ingredients needed to create the aroma of the fountain head
just about five hours so what it was eight hours the first time well nine hours the first
time eight hours 17 like 189 20 we're like 22 hours in and i'm still it's still a game here
it's cool so that's it but it is yeah i already heard this what's lost finding
all right so that door marked with the door marked with the outline of a person i haven't
but see do i have anything else fuck okay i'm glad you've come don't have any seeds
it looks as if your brow is less furrowed than before if only a little
please see that lord kuros wish to sever immortality is met goodbye um okay ancient text i
i don't really know what you want me to do i i i got it though uh palace key waters
in a deep pool uh i gotta start diving around probably um i see you gather keep up the good
thank you oh that door lord what door are you talking about the door with the outline
i don't even know what the hell are you talking about what do we got outskirts castle
that's dungeon i could go back and try to kill yeah hold on a minute here
watering hole let me go fight some of these there's a couple of mini bosses that i want
to take down let me go back here let me go fight the headless ape thing let's go down
he was down here right somewhere down here is this guy there you are okay what do you got
you i'm looking at you lab first of all what am i thinking here because i'm gonna just jump
down on top of you if i can now we don't need crutches let's fucking go i was gonna
see you're done but that's terrible i can't dodge here no dodging allowed against this guy
oh my health i wasn't looking at my health again the most important thing in the game and
i'm just like yeah i guess he does damage even if you bury that's why i'm not paying attention
to it um i might have to use an item here that chip damage is insane um yeah i'll do this
again i have that item that stops all illusions right holy fuck that was a one that was a one hit
kill let's see that's oh my god now someone's i gotta i might have to use another one of my
things um let's see here wait for driving away apparitions well that dude looks like an
apparition if i was an apparition that would that's be that's who i would be let's give it
a try uh where the fuck was he over here divine confetti snap seed yeah that's all i just that's
all i got i wonder what about did snap seed work i'm scared to use this i feel like this is an
item i can't get okay so i got pacifying divine confetti i'm just gonna let's see what happens
um i just kind of scratched my ass for a second
all right let me reach in my pocket and let nope sorry i'll eat my fucking ass
hold on you want to use this item let me get it and use the fuck i don't even know what this
is supposed to be doing what i get it okay i thought i for a second i thought it was
gonna get rid of like the illusions i thought it was gonna get rid of this shit i didn't oh my god
give me a fucking break i didn't know what coated my sword i thought it was like a thing where
they got rid of the mist or something really this doesn't say that it's it doesn't say it
coats your weapon it just said it drives away apparitions fucking god damn it so i'm gonna do
this before i even go in here and then he's gonna teleport behind me how long does it last
my god this terror builder is fucking killing me dude that happens so fast give me a break
you don't even get a tenth of a second through that holy shit this guy sucks you don't even
get like a quarter of a second to react to that what the fuck i'm gonna use all these
items this is gonna be fucking miserable i'm dead fucking jesus christ oh my god this is
just i hate this dude that terror buildup if he touches you fucking once he's gonna fucking be
behind me i hate this guy oh my god oh my god i this is the worst boss in the whole game
i hate this so much i have to beat this though holy fuck this is bring me to like a six or
seven right now this motherfucker is gonna bring me to like an eight this is the lag is my
last attempt on him fucking terror dude i'm almost dead again he's gonna stab him
no no fuck this game fuck this boss this is stupid
like this eats shit it still builds terror even when you fucking walk i'm dead here man i'm
fucking dead i got no more i got one more oh my fucking jesus christ
fuck that guy i'm never fighting that guy again i'd rather just piss down on his head right now
what a waste of fucking items oh fuck that enemy that just brought it down to a seven two
that's a seven two now it is all right where do i have to go pool doesn't want to learn
how to beat no i know how to beat him it's just the terror buildup the fact that you can't
dodge you can't dodge and the terror buildup even when you block i know you have to parry
but his moves are fucking hard to parry because he's such a slow motherfucker right
that's a hard fucking encounter fuck that encounter you can you locked in place you need
a special item to fight him oh poop in that guy's fucking mouth seriously uh there's i need to
why would i want to go into poison water that's not a pause maybe the castle i really just
don't know maybe here this is a body of water i don't know where if i can do anything here
now it's not deep enough can i go what does this bring me i think this is back out now this is
what i got the flower um okay dive something under here dive down precious bait ring the bell
drop the bait what the hell does that mean all right well i got bait uh let's keep looking
in other bodies of water wouldn't have water around here somewhere the very beginning of the
game there's a ton of water right okay into the water this is water right that's not the water
i thought that was water it's not all right okay here we go is there any water to dive in here
no but that uh okay didn't get that before apparently uh nothing's deep enough here
that guy um i really have no idea i'm just gonna keep looking for bodies of water
i guess i don't know where the hell to go uh i could have sworn there was water like over here
is there something over here making sure i'm not missing something like on the inside or
uh i think i have to kill people this one all right water let's see water let's check it
can you drown what down here treasure carp scale uh i think i'm going the right way
i don't know i this is still going where am i now uh i don't i think um
well i've been here before let's see what's over here water down here now this is the
what the key to a samurai gatehouse located in the reservoir not far from the will the wolf
is kept in here you'll be the demon's broken horn is guarded by ashina samurai the broken
horn is a spear blade what uh why did i just i i killed these guys before i killed these guys
like like 16 hours ago in game time and i didn't get that key um okay is there a better way for
me to take this on i don't think so he missed whoa he's gonna try to catch me oh my god how
many times is he doing this what the fuck oh my god you psycho
does the bar have to be so tiny like look at that it's hard to tell if it's falling
it takes up like fucking not even a quarter of a percent of the real estate on the screen
god that little tiny baby like fingernail posture bar can i make that even five percent
bigger well this is a new zone i guess he seems heated i am i can't get that fucking stupid
headless dumb fuck face enemy out of my mind i hate that thing i wish i could go into the
game's code and delete it okay to purchase an offering everyone's always hiding in these
little sheets where you find the departed you'll find the memorial we the impure cannot turn a
blind eye to anyone go ahead buy an offering oh shit oh didn't somebody have the other half of
this what is this what do you get for doing this how many do i have two i don't even have
remotely enough money to do it where you find whatever what do i have for money five
ten fifteen twenty i got two thousand there to purchase enough i'm not sure anything maybe
this is worth buying just to have another one i'm gonna buy this why not so i got 150 let's go
i need one more and i'll buy two of these thank you for your business down we go let's go
down what was the indicator that i just had abandoned dungeon i don't want you to touch me
okay and he touched me he got on top of me he's you want to see my face you don't want
to see my face trust me you're doing of all places are you perhaps shinobi oh do i answer
or what do i say to this i wonder if this guy's that's right i thought might you be willing to
take on favor i am doju i've been tasked with the preparation of a medical treatment
using the rejuvenating water i'll get to the point my dear shinobi this is a letter i received
the master the particulars are contained within okay one tough man preferably a strong samurai or
a young large soldier such as a member of the tarot troop must be delivered unharmed
one tough man okay i don't get it my dear the details are in the considering the nature of
the information i think you'd agree that the less we know about each other the better one tough
man is this a tough man i can't go behind him i can go down and give me that item oil
oil hey hey stop it leave me the heck alone what's up here terror agent sure red lump
consumed to gain red eyes and reduce flinching from enemy attacks but you can't resurrect
shit okay hello just these idiots oh that was under the assumption i have a chance i've been
hitting them allegedly not don't like this no one ah there's no way to dodge these guys come
back to life it looks like yeah well i'll take this now is there a reason why i can't uh water
we can dive under here maybe i shouldn't have done that anything down here yes there is
three items we got coin purse 300 gold i'll take it it's very mcshard
i'm not gonna go under there just yet where we at what the hell are you throwing was that a
piece of dust no he's a gun right i didn't really just had a gun feet cam why would i do
a feet cam no i'm not gonna fucking do a feet cam uh ghost guy ghost samurai
you that was a lot of experience for this guy operate mechanism turn on the wheel
going up can i help you bucket headed three that sounded like the kid i think i'm going
fucking crazy please is anything else you got for me proceed with care i'm not gonna stop you
all right well i have an idol right here okay you're gonna pray for my safety okay
senpu temple mount congo um who do i go for the guy on the bridge or guy sitting down
can i talk to this person
are you crying everyone's gone who's everyone it's a baby look at that bat looks like a couch
cushion
all right scrap iron i need like two more gunpowder right and i could have
go back and upgrade my flame thing again do the bridge this is an enemy is should i just kill
him i'm just gonna kill this guy it's a beautiful zone wait let me take a look what's
over here oh it's a kite fly kite uh let go what the fuck is going on let go i can't
why can't i let go of this is this is this a part of the game well uh thanks to somebody
in chat i had to press e on the keyboard all right well i don't know what that does
that would have been so lame if i just got stuck there forever helpful one guy yeah you
guys are saying that these guys were peaceful that's that's not true these guys are clearly
fucking trying to kill me oops wrong button jesus man they were peaceful until you trespassed
let's sneak up on this guy oh boy okay this is not a place i want to be oh fuck watch out
for the shit oh not good oh boy how the hell was i supposed to know there's three dudes over here
okay shit load of them are up there i probably shouldn't go head on let's go this way there's
the front of the temple big marsh five community subs thank you big marsh big subs from big marsh
no thank you for real no power and no power who are you ghost version of the
this is so not good god is there another one here is it three this is not three right
no there's people around so goodness holy fuck that guy did like 80 percent of my health in one
hit what the fuck all right all right settle down settle down where are we at top i don't
think i can fight all these guys at the same time and go up there but can i even go in the
front door i don't think i can open this door um can i get why does it look like i could go
up there can i not make it to the roof from here yeah look it's i can get up let me get
up here
might as well all right i'm in the house i've made it oh god this is a whole like prayer
it's like five people in here doing prayers oh you guys got a fucking roach problem you get
some like get the orchid man in here for crying out loud jesus oh come on oh oh
there's a huge guy there too um who are i got a gourd seed is right is right now done that
um all right gourd seed and pick up the fucking item this is not good this is very bad
yeah window right here out the window somebody to talk to you guys can't get out here right
no i'm safe good to go can i cheese this i better believe i can
maybe not maybe not well let's just see what you have to say motherfucker
oh fuck off no what am i gonna do about this burn
well i maybe i just you gotta do what you gotta do how are you still alive how is that person
still living what the hell of course is a cockroach okay can i lose them fuck there are
two kinds one is fresh the other is dry it's over there the fresh one's over there over the cliff
through the hole that's where you find it fresh what are you talking about something troubling
you for rice for me that's the way rice i say if something is troubling you in your mind
bless me with rice anytime okay all right all right i have any rice right from the divine
child why am i panicking because i have to read that fast or someone will throw a rock at me
oh okay so this i feel like there's a lot going on in this zone what about what's up here
can i do anything from i mean look it up across the way but i don't think i can get over there
from here should i go for it i mean i don't know what the i put the kite out but i had to pull
it back no that's not gonna do anything i can go up there i need it a bonfire is something
this is bad i'm almost dead i guess i'm gonna go over here i guess no i tried to jump across
and it just didn't oh now i'm fucked i'm gonna try this way i don't know i have no idea is that
a mini boss no it's not can you see me whoa you can burn everything here who hello what the
hell is that thrust jesus oh no okay yeah good luck no thanks this is another one this too
oh you motherfucker why oh this is far away i am at the very beginning oh shit all right that's fun
it's fun having the indicator there and when i jump it just disappears it's not there anymore
that's great i love it it's my favorite thing about the game which way i don't even remember
which way it was it was like around the corner right i don't even know yep it was up here
here through here through the woods forget about the cockroaches just get through here
all right skip this guy jump across and then i don't know we're gonna fight the alien that's
in the temple i'm not even entirely sure i can get across from here i'm gonna this way all
right i guess maybe let's try this well found it oh let me check down here first somebody
oh almost got dropped on you come this way sugar i go this way oh watch that health okay
around the corner no i'm almost at the top of this damn mountain what's up here
oh what an idiot that's the first enemy in the entire game to do that no other enemy has
done that he's the first one and he didn't even mean to that wasn't even cool i seem to have made
it kind of i mean really kind of let's see red and white pinwheel everyone's right here pinwheel
that's i don't i don't know what this is for but there's hope i don't die to that thing
yeah i mean
yeah fuck this yeah okay yeah really i wonder if i'm gonna be safe for the sake of my god damn
it he hurts hurts what's happening i don't know what that he's doing something weird
check out that fucking posture easy oh it hurts no no no no no no i timed it too and
he's gonna get it didn't get it didn't get it didn't get it didn't get it fuck i had it too
fuck you i had it get out of here what okay well that's i'm not entirely
i gotta knock them off the cliff that's very clear right knock them off the cliff
goodbye yeah did somebody just say i've read chat how the hell would i do that during that
fight let me just peer over here just take a look what you got what no he's like breaking
the sides like how would i read fucking chapter in that they very clearly these things would
be exploding around us well i knew that was not going to be so easy and that might be
the spot to call it for tonight because that's probably puts us no maybe not yet
not yet i'm currently i'm right here um me okay let me put enhance my attributes
but go for a little longer okay so that puts me here i probably have to get up that way but
let me just see if there's anything else over this way there is somebody down here dog
more than one dog another dog dog three come on dog three what do you got dog four
can i open this front door no i can't dog three for rumble yep you got it
of course it's just a monkey another monkey i think i was in the middle of an animation
dog what's the animals the animals are everywhere i just healed back almost everything that was
gone oh that's not good fuck off permit permission ready to eat for a time allows one
to cover posture even when attacking or taking damage okay that sounds like a good item
i'll take it is this wait this the flower guy i have a flower for him
that's a ton of posture damage fucking monkey give me a break oh my god they don't they
let up at all like kids guys
oh my god fuck you ethos i love the use of the monkeys in this game they are kind of just
everywhere they're just everywhere here's the other side of the bridge oh well isn't that nice
okay that's what what am i what do you what do i do now
oh that's the dead end do i have to go back up i'm not going to fight those guys you're
kidding me this is up here just hang out for a second because now what is that
they have homing fireworks all right i can't i gotta move dude uh this place is kind of hell
i picked up an item and they spawned like four ghosts and now i this is hell this is actual
hell uh the game wants me to go at this point up there i'm going up here and then we're going
up there i think i think uh okay so let me up that can i go up here shit
oh my god oh no no no yes sekiro skip all enemies i'm not dealing with you guys not now
no escape there's no escape is there something else i can get here
oh at this point i kind of just got you got to just go i gotta go i just have to i have to
get out of here there's too many people here there are too many of you here uh there's a
but that's this guy's gonna see me maybe not the door
touch it oh what is this oh no what did i just do i activated something i teleported somewhere
monkeys panels is empty it's dunston a five-pronged bell made of h bronze can be used repeatedly
when rung monkeys and wolves alike are returned to their initial states however a monkey caught
on the folding screen will not escape whether the bell is rung or not folding screen monkeys
folding screen monkeys uh where where what is it did do i just have it and i just have to
ring the bell near things or something elusive hall bell okay so then let me put it down here
monkeys and wolves are like a return to their initial states however a monkey caught in
the folding screen will not escape okay i yet another i believe you are on a mission
you wish to leave this place yes then you must defeat the monkeys depicted on the panels at
the whole entrance once you have done so the divine child's voice
the monkey purple kimono is the seeing monkey he has excellent eyesight can see great distances
and is very attentive if he spots you he will rock this exceedingly purple one
this runs and can see from a great distance over the orange one
while he does not have particularly good eyesight or hearing he makes a big fuss when
he sees a threat causing all the other monkeys to run oh perhaps he merely enjoys toying with
so kill orange one first
he has excellent hearing can hear across great distance hearing
he will generally run away
making it hard he is exceedingly
i do not wish to be it is usually quiet here which means it is near to nirvana in its own way
at least that is how it feels to me oh yes there was once someone who like you
a mission i believe he chased the monkeys for a while but everything here i pray that you
succeed uh okay okay okay there's the orange one orange and green do i do have to kill them
or do i need to just ring the bell near them uh well i'm gonna is he above me well there's
a bell here this is read this bell is deafening ringing it recklessly will also make your ears
ring which is the one that had bad hearing what green what i need to like can i talk to him again
green was purple is seeing okay orange is speaking bad eyesight and hearing
so orange is seeing green is hearing so the green one you can fuck up with the audio
can hear a few ways all right so green audio wants someone i believe what does this mean
no one can hear anything else in here so i'm gonna lure somebody in here lure the green one
in here i don't know how anything else to read so there's the waterfall room there's the bell
and then there's whatever this is bear flame in the wind when it goes out the place becomes
dark uh so the seeing monkey has to be killed in here let's see so it's dark in here now orange
is what the hell does this say the bottom cannot be seen above his darkness nothing can be seen
so the seeing monkey can get like pushed in here well there's the green one where does it
go where's the bell i can hear the monkey chase like running around but it's still i
have to like ring the fucking bell turn the place dark just talk to the monkeys uh are you come here
i know i have both earbuds in now i just i don't i don't understand what they want me to do here
i have to i'm gonna ring the bell and then try to chase the green one what's the orange
the arm is the orange one is the orange the orange the hearing one or the orange the seeing
one come here get over here fuck you piece of shit fold that where are you come on
okay can i go down and around no no i i just heard him behind me where the fuck are you
man come on in the well he's like under here surprise dickhead god damn it
okay he's not right here they keep getting closer look at he's right here where's that room
there's purple there's purple you're a dumb ass okay where's the last one is there some
the monkey in the green he has excellent view here okay i know there was once maybe i
i'm gonna bell where did he go where is that guy what huh huh who what the fuck
what's going on i'm on terror terror terror terror terror terror what the who is this
why oh there's a bunch of them now what the hell why are they all here where's the green one
oh god wrong one wrong one where's this last uh where's the green monkey you asshole why
where is he he was here before i don't know where this other monkey is huh oh shit man oh
there's too many of them i don't know i don't know i'm making a new monkey uh found a green
motherfucker right there green come here you son of a bit i no no get over here come here
oh he's already gone wait a minute what if i do this what the fuck was that that's not where
i was aiming oh god damn oh god damn it can i go back to sword fighting remember the game
about fighting with your sword not like chasing monkeys where the hell did he go
oh you piece of shit
ring the bell oh my fucking god i don't know can i throw a fucking knife at him
die why can i just fall from here no bell bell bell bell bell bell bell do it
no where do where where what i heard him go eat shit that was fun
skiro has a gamer neck
but what are you talking about he doesn't have a gamer neck i accidentally killed the invisible
monkey what they guarded the halls of illusions and befriended the divine child puppeteer this
technique temporarily forces one who should have fled this realm to remain a puppet moves
on behalf of its master interesting okay what is that go to the halls of illusion
i don't think i want to do that again okay you're getting more and more weird as we go
why do you seek this place i seek the mortal blade do you know of the blade that cannot be
yes it is so called for not one who has drawn it has ever survived yet you still wish to attempt
this this in this way this is not the same person never mind i do i see very well
you're gonna give me the sword if you are prepared you may gaze upon the blade
i got this at an auction six hundred and forty five dollars
why is it i wonder are they not i looked at the sword and they killed me how are you
can't kill me your eye you have a sans eye you carry i accept its power
oh new sword capable of slaying the undying its crimson blade will take the life of any
who dares draw it without the power of resurrection one could not hope to wield this weapon
which allows one to defeat even infested beings long concealed within the i'm going
i'm going back and i'm gonna kill the fuck i'm gonna go kill that fucking ape
hopefully he's still there lying in the ground see you serve the divine
heir of the dragon's heritage yes why do you seek the mortal blade
i wish to obtain the dragon tears from the divine realm to sever the ties of immortality
i see i have read about this i have read there is a way to sever the dragon's heritage
which means the divine heir begrudges the power of the dragon's heritage that's right
go kill tutorial guy that's so mean i am one of the children of the rejuvenating waters
created by those who would stop at nothing to achieve immortality my false dragon's blood
was created by man children so there are many of you i am the only one who survived the process
the others are laid to i know of another one here i see i do not know if it is right to
sever the ties of immortality but the dragon's heritage undeniably corrupts the lives of men
and i share the air's feelings about that truth shinobi of the divine air i have decided
to assist you please hold out your hand what bless us with bountiful harvest
what do you got rice rice that spilled from the palms of the child of rejuvenation gradually
recovers vitality for a time didn't that lady want rice this is rice there you are
rice is a precious thing it tastes better the more you eat it and restores one's figure
thanks shinobi of the divine and you are welcome here
have some more apologize the rice is not yet ready i shall give you more okay well i can get
more rice only one piece of rice thanks for the one grain of rice hope we didn't need any of that
stuff all right i got everything i need what about over here i told you it was gonna be
there okay i think it's time to go up here this is open it does
uh how you're weird because you sit still and your centipede fights for you all right
i can kill you permanently now all right i gotta go kill the monkey easy oh you're hard to
parry you don't have a weapon so you're just weird you slither around like a weirdo
oh that was fun i'll be back all right where's the monkey is he still lying down in that spot
down here no not this one it's another one which one is it wedding cave wedding cave right here
right because isn't this the monkey cave no it says guardian eight that's what i just went to
isn't it oh that's up whatever all right here we go time for you to permanently die
what do i get for doing this the wolf discovered this technique from behind the
foe the mortal blade extending its reach okay so that's just cool let me see seven emblems to do
it coats your blood blade with the blood of your target interesting and what about the toriel
guy i wonder what he's gonna say on your back what is it no blade it's real you don't suppose
you could use it to end this curse of mine i could i will thank you man with your skill
could grant a merciful death and you leave it to me splendid i must give my thanks to
sekicho i will prepare for the beyond the next time you see me i'll be ready all right
cool so is it time to do it should i just do it now prepare for the he's not ready yet
he needs to prepare he needs to use the toilet take a shower let's go to this
screen monkeys departed souls of the divine children drift and sway taking shelter in the
monkeys of the temple such as the way such as why the divine child of rejuvenation speaks of
them as friends ap up now let's go talk to the sculptor's idol is unavailable until it's
communed with again let me commune with it again let me go over here first do i have enough
to do my upgrade i might well okay they're in here now i see you're here too i'm busy carving
my buddha didn't i get something new i need two more gunpowder master wolf i've always enjoyed
the sound of a buddha being carved so i stopped by this place every now and then cool goodbye
uh so that means if i do i have to go back i can't even go back to the that's how did i even get
here what do i have to like go back through here i have to commune with them again go to
this one i didn't die to the screen monkeys what are you talking about where are you getting
that info from it took me a while it's a pain in the ass wait no i didn't even see you
i can still get it let's open this up can i not open that door interesting why so you tell me
i gotta go all the way back up here well this is a new enemy level three cool um oh you all
right moat i guess we're going down to the moat are they actually in the mode swimming
around that's not that's a goldfish that's not a shinobi okay then back through here i guess
wait till they're fighting each other and then go in is this one
why do they turn them off that's weird what's the point of them turning them off
there's a stab right oh my god i didn't see you damn it man where the where did it even come
from what uh this is a fight angle three cool no thanks what the hell is this
who is there somebody behind this door oh god is it doesn't open from this side
i'm so confused why this whole area different uh okay let's hope this whole thing's different
weird god damn it i'm soaking god give me a break i didn't even know what direction that
guy was facing oh i'm so annoyed like a hyper focus it's hard to have any of your senses work
when you play this game what happened to gonzo uh that's a good question
are they i feel like this i thought it was um i have no words to describe what the hell
i'm trying to say
jesus christ that's just the thing that batman does before bain fucking breaks his back it
doesn't do anything oh oh i just fucking dove into it gamer fatigue it's time for a break i'll
see you tomorrow
god play pick ross no i'm going to bed playing securo for six hours or seven hours is like
running 200 marathons there's so many of these people out here
why would i even fight them oh no this is i remember what is back up here again this is
what didn't we do this already i heard stories of your death yet here you are what are you
flogging al flotting isn't that dead i must ask that you accompany me i wasn't the assumption
that he was dead protect the divine heir from so the dragon's heritage has seduced you too
and there is nothing to discuss take your leave i'm so stunned uh
hmm okay this is a boss i ain't doing this tonight i can tell you some i can tell you right now
father to think you were still alive that was my but the same could be said for you
i was certain you died the power of the divine heir brought me back that's it what the divine
heir the dragon's blood father now you see it remember the first rule of the code
as your father i order you to forsake your master from this moment he is your master no
more forsake the divine heir listen to me wolf obey your father's command and forsake the
divine heir uh obey the iron code for say kuro break the iron code stay loyal to kuro
isn't the iron code to protect kuro i thought that was the whole point so either dad or weird
son uh i don't know does this matter i did say in the very beginning i did say i was
gonna stay loyal not do as you ask a shinobi showing the likes of passion i said it that was
the point of the first options i got i said i was gonna be loyal miserable display why why
can't be determined by the individual this is what i've decided i'm so glad we got to come
up here and fight in the boss zone dad why would you do this
and i can't wait for us to see this tomorrow this is gonna be the fight of a lifetime tomorrow
afternoon i've got news for you enough talk see you tomorrow just kidding first try
what's that grenade smoke grenade how about this dad this seems like a really cool fight
my posture is terrible i can't wait to put like a real tempted tomorrow
at between three and four p.m pacific time he's not even trying i i i'm just tired so you really
just got to run the fuck up there one more try one one try one try with actual uh healing
potions and shit let's go is there come on actually there's got to be a quick way for me
to get up here there's got to be a fast way for me to do this where is there like an idle
oh
where is it it's right there in their window i fucking miss it i have what oh god whoops
there's beautiful so now can i get there from here oh god damn it no i just get out there
and run i can go bingo is there a faster way to jump up all right let's give it a try
i'll try it once why why let's go in a while since we did this in a while since we did this
spongebob that does way too much posture damage you don't want to i'm gonna have to dodge that
that's actually a good opportunity probably to come in for an attack broken damn i don't
really have an opportunity to attack him i'm trying to think about the best place
he's just super aggressive even when you parry like three or four times in a row damn fuck man
all right whatever
gotta be an opening somewhere
i think it's just dancing around until he does that move and then getting the actual health
damage on him that's what i that's what i would say if i were a video gamer
there we go as long as that he wins the race just like the turtle
the same idea what's wrong with me i have a status effect problem what is this effect
come on dad that was a mistake
oh fuck back it up no something else besides that
all right just one what's phase two dad what
all right that was cute it was cute did you really just do the rick flair poison
watch out get that out of here fuck that stay away from the right side
while i have a second i gotta put this shit on the bar i'm gonna put on the antidote just in case
and just in case of an emergency don't let him get fucking behind you he's gonna do something
wacky this is what i put it on the bar for that's what i put it on the bar for but i'm
all right that hurts no you don't you can't get nothing on me dad i don't know what the
fuck that was you know it's posture hill dickhead i got you i got you getting close
get in here
good i don't fuck i'll kill you i'll take you down to zero health oh whoa missed dodge missed
dodge fuck no bye dad bye dad
ha ha ha i'm the real shinobi unless you have a phase three which i hope you don't
battle memory of an extraordinary foe lingering in the mind of the wolf
dad uh aromatic branch the ever blossom is a sag oh this is the blossom okay that was a
i like that fight a lot why is it both of all the fights that took place on this platform
on my favorite i don't know why this is the gamer platform apparently no that was a cool
fight let's use it the great shinobi owl's unbridled ambition was to obtain the power of
the dragon's heritage now is the time to let one's true name ring out across all of japan
it was all for the sake of this ambition and that's gonna call it tonight thank you for
joining me on secure i'll see you tomorrow we're gonna pick up right here i bet you'll
get real salty tomorrow too oh you will probably i probably should like at least take a look in
here now we're gonna i'm just gonna this is this saves right here right yeah yeah it does
kill tutorial guy no we'll start with that tomorrow we'll kill tutorial guy tomorrow
first thing promise gonna have to redo them oh that would be bad it won't hurt you one look
all right i'll see you guys tomorrow thanks for coming up and i started to hit the
gamer fatigue like a half an hour 40 minutes ago but you have to pull up your pants
sometime i'd love and hate this game at the same time i love this game more than i hate it
you know that what all right the one bar the guy down with the magic shit that you can't dodge
and the terror and he teleports behind oh boy oh boy i know you love it and you hate it what
would you rate it 8.7 mad because bad i was so fucking mad i was furious that was reaching
mario tennis that guy just because i hated those mechanics that was almost mario tennis
that was like a seven and i it wasn't even i didn't even die that many times i died like
three or four times i don't know something about that encounter is mario mario tennising
me but we'll pick up here tomorrow what encounter i'm talking about the the headless
the headless magician guy that just stands in this weird tiny little area that you can't
dodge and you have to coat your sword in magic and he's really slow and he can teleport behind
you that was close to about a seven in anger for me anyways uh let's get to the bits thanks
everybody for sticking around it was a shit load of money earlier too you guys are fucking
spoiling me but this game's really really fun it's essentially you're you're at a hundred
the whole game let's go back to about seven hours ago let's get this on the screen that
i can actually see what was a ten on the anger scale i don't think i've ever been a ten on
the anger scale on stream i think like seven six to seven is the highest i think i've ever been
actually on camera i don't think i've never been like a nine or a ten on stream i feel
like a nine or a ten on stream would be like me turning the stream off being so angry at
something that i've gotten bleeding that's probably what a ten is tennis that's probably
what a ten is
oh my goodness anyways let's uh go through these i know it's getting a little late so
thank you sad vega for the 250 i had something really witty to say here about
skiro and your progress but i forgot what it was hope you hit the temple up today
because that temple is crazy i did hit the temple it was glorious uh fitty thanks for
the 25 dollars earlier fitty i'm not sure if you're still here but thank you
do you ever really miss the old sakiro streams can you cough just once more for my nostalgia
i can only cough on stream for you thank you for the 25 dollars cats or quats thanks for
the 25 bucks right after that two 25 dollars right in a row thanks for being such a cool
dude love your content twitch was having a sale on bits so i figured it'd be great time
to give back keep being you hope you start feeling better soon i'm feeling pretty good
i still it's lingering a little bit it's not as bad as it was a couple days ago no way
i really oh that was bad that was old man that was terrible thank you for the 25 bucks though
for real uh timmy tim tan thanks for the 250 i come to you today with sad news after seeing
the latest second germa video of the quiet man's dreams i want to check out my favorite
channel on youtube daily english tv i was met with only sadness as the channel has deleted
all of their videos no longer may we talk about a lazy boy or wait why why would they
delete every one of their videos that's strange what they had like hundreds of thousands of videos
didn't they that's insane thank you dork cube for the 250 this really is the only good use
of poison swamp in a from game it's not just fat roll till you die a slow death because
they give you all the movement mechanics to avoid it yeah once i realized that it was just
sort of small the dark souls 3 swamp area is so huge it's just gigantic you can actually
jump out of the poison i don't think i even got poisoned once in there so really not a big deal
it was in article 13 didn't wait no article third didn't article 13 just get through like
the first part of the like the house or something it's it has to get voted on again second time
it had passed but it's not going into why yet doesn't have to go through one more
what channel we're talking about daily english tv yeah it's not implemented yet
i think it has to go through another vote hopefully they fucking shut it down
kazi thanks for the 25 dollars kazi pretend i said something nice well thank you you did you gave
me 25 dollars that's an incredibly nice thing so thank you honey chain thanks for the 250 germa
can you pretend i wrote something funny in this message thanks what uh sure that was fucking
funny but thank you for the 25 bucks oh no sorry the 250 25 was kazi 250 was honey chain
you both had a similar message that's why i kind of mixed you up but thank you to amish robot
for five dollars ass either tastes like soap or ass that's a disgusting image that i can't get out
of my head now that i'm gonna have in there forever what what a revolting thing to think
about right now i'm gonna go brush my teeth three times that's disgusting oh that's not
even that's not even something i want to hear might have to run 200 marathons thank you
though amish robot for the five dollars frodean weapon thanks for five dollars frodean
watching these streams is spoiling the game for me but i don't care this game looks so
entertaining and difficult i'll play it five times over plus i enjoy your unique commentary
thank you sometimes when you get in a boss fight that requires total focus i don't really
say very much but i do love the game we'll see what letter grade it drops and then raises
tomorrow thank you frodean proceph pro star 25 dollars thank you so much they say army
uh beat navy i don't know what you mean by that but thank you for the 25 dollars proceph
you gave 50 dollars earlier military money let's go rotc don't doesn't the army and the navy do
with like a football game every year or two they do like a thing every year the unique
commentary is me struggling to find a monkey it never really just throws you off though
your timing hits and parrying and jumping around and fighting people and all of a sudden
it's like well what about that like orange monkey go catch him it's like the rabbit from
mario 64 but four of them and it's a boss hey pugatron thanks for the 10 bucks let's get him
thank you pugatron was that really four hours ago damn thank you d jack for the five dollars
i take a professional accounting course and today the lecturer booted up his powerpoint
and the title was sale at undervalue and i burst out laughing in a room full of business
type people because i thought it said sans undertale i'm blaming you so thanks nice first
try on the double monkey by the way why is that my fault sans undertale thank you d jack
thank you void thank you void oh one for the three bucks hey germa just wanted to ask
your permission to make a tf2 item for the scout based on your likeness asking especially
because there's potential to earn royalties from it and i can add you on the submission if
you'd like you'd hit me up on twitter or here if needed keep doing you the streams are great
while working um it really depends on what you're talking about i mean i don't really know
exactly what you mean but if you uh send me a tweet maybe with what you took with like the
maybe the design or something or what it is because i mean that's it's cool a decal on
the scouts ass what a cosmetic based on germa so a furry rat skin they came pretty close during
halloween that year the alien morph suit thing the whatever it was could have been or it's a
you could it could be an animal but thank you for the three dollars and before anything
else is said good luck on the submission or good luck on the work on it anyways thank you
void uh peaceful hailey thanks for the 250 hi germa just want to say that i'm doing better
than i was last time you streamed also i'm taking a voice acting class with chuck huber
known as android 17 from dbz etc that's pretty fucking cool i'm pretty happy about that i just
want to overcome and get out of my comfort zone of being embarrassed by my voice but
99 percent of people are too so i have to keep that in mind i always hope you are doing
well have a good night germa and chat you've already got a lot of knowledge from that so
definitely good luck you should pull something great from that uh from that class so thank you
so much peaceful hailey good luck to you keep us updated thank you shadows one discipline for
the i lost it here what was it for the anger link here what is this i don't get it what is
it is that from office what is that did i say something like this like a few hours ago
hey pugatron thanks for the 10 bucks don't be angry germa i tried to eat it i really did but
i wasted items that i was just so upset by it i was so angry just seething at that guy with
no head it's a good thing i got out of there when i did it's a good thing that i have to
use items to fight that guy because if i had to stay there and fight that guy for like
another two hours what was the part when i said i was gonna throw my beer bottle behind
me as hard as i could was that the was it that guy wait no that happened before didn't
what fight was that oh that was the ape
so i did get kind of irritated today but it's just the nature of the game
i really hope i don't come off as like an asshole or like an obnoxious dick because
like i i hate thinking that that's happening because there's like angry there's like upset
and then you like start to crawl into like annoying where you're mad about something and
you keep talking about how mad you are about something you keep talking shit and then you
kind of trek into annoying so i hope i didn't trek that far but this game is really it'll
do it to you it will it just has that effect apologize to green monkey
hey dr pepper thanks for the 10 dollars there's more where that came from if you do a feed
cam i will never do a feed cam that's not gonna happen thank you for the 10 bucks though
that's not ever gonna happen uh internet Jorge thanks for the 15 bucks i've been stressed but
laughing with your laughing with you kills all the stress they say show love thank you internet
Jorge thanks for the 15 dollars it depends if you're actually critical of the game design
trust no one's got a new video i'm gonna queue this up i'll queue that up we'll watch
it right at the very end um yeah i don't like to be too critical of game design and
because i know that is it's you just get it rubs people's just the wrong way but in that little
zone with the no dodging i don't know if it's critical or if it's uh if it's just disappointment
that i couldn't move i don't know anger is a funny thing frustration is a frustration is a
funny thing because no matter what happens you are always going to try to find a way to
a way to relieve your frustration and sometimes that's just like talking shit just out loud
it's just salt yeah salt just it just happens and like i said there's a way to hopefully not
cross that threshold of salt into all right dude relax you're fucking irritating i really
hope i don't ever get there and if i do sorry that i did it is that kind of game
extra salt uh we also had it's time for slime thanks to three bucks not sure we solved this
but vinnie uh watched the clip of you playing mad dog mccree oh god this is the best game
ever made i think this actually might be the best game i've ever played
okay now someone needs to clip me doing this
someone needs to clip me laughing over that and send it to another streamer
hey he sent it to me i'm that streamer all right now somebody's gonna clip that
and then send that to my grandmother no that's fucking funny let's let's link it so you guys can
watch it if you want yeah but thank you it's time for slime for the three bucks and the clip
pro step pro star thanks for the 15 dollars i got the horses in the back what does that mean
thanks for the 15 dollars though drosophilia 25 dollars thank you so much it's been a lot
of 10 20 20 10 15 15 15 50 50 50 80 80 50 10 10 10 10 10 you guys are coming in with tons
and tons of big donations so thank you uh drosophilia says what a god of a gamer
25 dollars thanks a lot guys uh yes is online thanks for five dollars without spoiling anything
there's a boss fight on this i don't want to know anything about boss fights i'm gonna stop
at boss fight i'm gonna i just i stopped at boss fight but thank you for the five dollars
there's a boss fight i know there's a boss fight now somewhere but thank you yes is online
appreciate it i just try to stay away from pretty much as much as i can unless i specifically
ask for but thank you uh thank you tay thank you uh tayone oh my god for the 250
i like your title today it's cute have a good night remember not to watch any puking videos
fucking hilarious peek a banana thanks for the five dollars great stream germa hart always
love watching can't wait to watch the moment you beat sekiro i'm gonna try i'm gonna try
i'm gonna come tomorrow i'm gonna be i'm gonna eat a bunch of i'm gonna eat a huge breakfast
tomorrow and i'm fucking gonna lock in i can't wait i cannot wait if i had energy i would
keep playing right now but this game is pretty draining so after about seven to eight hours
it's time to call it but do you want to keep playing let's do it tomorrow and then something
order thanks for the 250 nice job killing your dad i always knew you were hard thank you
something good rudder and before we run the credits let's go ahead and put this video on
screen this is from trust no one let's see the latest in the saga audio today we play
some fun vr games all right are you are you going in what is it wait seven to it's ten to be 50 okay
god damn it
okay this sounds like this is what you would hear this is the audio that would be pulled
from a haunted house these are all the noises that happen and you know like that they funneled
people into the haunted house like 50 people could be in a line going through and you can't
clip all the audio from that haunted house
oh my god it's probably a gnome at the end of this video
uh i'm staying here for the end for the recommended okay police try playing grab it without what
oh that was fucking fantastic thank you oh my god you guys that's fucking hilarious
that was great thank you so much trust no one again until next time all right let's run the
credits see you tomorrow guys for more sakiro i wanted to wait until the stream was winding
down but i'm working on a big unmonetized secret project about some of your old content
and if i get your blessing before going through with it how can i propose it to you
um that's that's fine if anyone wants to make stuff like that you know i mean that we have
the stream highlight channel is already there for you know stuff new content right but i'm
not i'm not gonna like flag your videos if you make a little highlight fun thing or something
you know that's not that's not something i'm gonna do so you don't have to worry about that
i made a movie inspired by rap movie is that okay yeah that's that's fine don't worry about
that i mean unless you like okay if if you like i've got an idea for a new series on nbc
it's called germa 985 stream clips and they green light you and you just put germa 985
stream clips up on like nbc at like eight o'clock prime time or something then it would kind of be
like all right um that's me any chance of you going back to hollow knight no probably not
probably not i keep hearing the idea in my brain to go play it again but i just don't think
it's gonna happen i'm sorry my scatter brain ruins playthroughs it does oh sakiro sakiro
after you beat sakiro what's the next stream gonna be going back to vr uh monster rancher four
okay here you go monster rancher four and maybe monster rancher two i'm getting the itch to play
those games again also i do have mr mosquito that'll probably be another stream at least for
like an hour or two on top of that i have like another one or two playstation 2 games
it might be fun mr mosquito is going to be that's like an old one rare but after monster
rancher four to mr mosquito i'm going to go back to vr again this is so much stuff to do
but i feel like we should have a return to monster rancher and with that i will see you
all tomorrow get some sleep take care guys see you real soon