Here we go. If this doesn't work, then I am gonna quit streaming.
So it has to work. You know what I'm saying?
Here we go. Please work, please work, please work, please work, please work, please work!
Capture the whole thing. Why is- oh my god, I'm gonna fucking pee my pants on camera, I swear to god.
Oh my fucking god, I hate computers. You gotta be shitting me.
I can't play it in that fucking shitty little window, guys.
And I can't even fix it, because I have to-
Nice resolution. I'm just installing another one.
I can't believe that people are still here watching this mess.
Nancy Drew's Secrets Can Kill.
Install it.
Hi. If this doesn't work, I'm just gonna go to DOS.
You look like a ghoul?
I was about to just do a fucking ghoul scream into the camera. Like, right into the camera.
Alright, Nancy Drew's Secrets Can Kill. Sure, yes. Just steam client, strap in, whatever it's called.
Alright, is this one gonna get captured?
It's- this is the same thing as the last one.
Why is Secrets of the Old Clock captureable now?
The game fucking crashed.
Hi, I'm Nancy Drew. This is my center of operations, my desk.
Go ahead and poke around.
If you want to know the particulars of how I do what I do, take a look at the-
What? It's there, it's there, it's there, it's there!
... how to be a detective.
It's real helpful, especially if you're new to the mystery-solving-
Shut up.
Excuse-
What?
Excuse me, giant hu-
Excuse-
Excuse me, giant human person, but you seem to-
... business.
And be sure to check out my scrapbook.
I put memorabilia from all my past cases in there.
Killing-
Killing the old clock?
And at times, really scary.
But don't say anything about that to my dad, okay?
Nancy Drew's Secrets Can Kill.
And whatever you do, read what's in the file called Case File.
That'll tell you all about the mystery I'm about to try to solve.
If you think you're ready to dive into that mystery,
just click on the plane ticket and you'll be on your way.
Alright, Case File, let's see.
Curse, I gotta change this to be what the actual thing's actually called.
Secrets Can Kill?
Alright, it's alright if I'm having you sit there for like 15 straight minutes
of like a black screen.
Let me just change the stream info to Secrets Can Kill.
A student named Jake Rogers was killed at a high school last week.
What?
An undercover detective by the name of Beach asked Aunt Eloise-
Eloise if I could go undercover to investigate the murder.
I'm posing as a new student to see what the other kids may know about Jake
and his untimely aunt.
I'm posing as a new student?
Wait, how old am I?
Check out How to Be a Detective.
How do I close the book?
What the fuck, man?
Shut up!
Okay, give me the plane ticket.
Put down the book.
Put the book down.
Put the book down, Nancy.
How do I put down the book?
Oh my god.
The police detective wants me to pose as a student
to search for any leads at the school.
So, it's undercover I go.
I'm calling this case, Secrets Can Kill.
Love, Nancy.
Alright.
Nancy, I had to close the school library early today
but if you need to do any research for your case
the key to the library is in the safe.
Remember not to enter in a wrong combination.
Why is that underlined?
Is it going to like explode?
Why would you write that?
Six zero KS.
Raseo del Mar universe in the...
Is this my diploma?
Why would I have my diploma folded up into a drawer?
Don't you put that shit on the back of your wall.
Oh, what was it?
Six O-K-S, right?
That's not correct?
Six O-K-S.
Ooh, a key.
I got it.
What is going on here?
That's incorrect.
It's got to be...
This has got to come down.
Is this all the way to the little...
This is the top right corner.
Alright, so this is...
I'm getting there.
This is her face, right?
Hold on. Is it going to come down?
Now, I hate these types of puzzles.
Yeah, they're...
I'm keeping it together.
Alright, alright.
Now, I've got to get this.
I'm going to have an aneurysm by this.
You're fine. That goes up here.
I'm so close, but so far away at the same time.
Where is... This goes to the left.
Motherfucker, it's right there.
Alright.
Come on.
So close.
I can fix this shit later.
You have to be done.
Okay, hold on. Wait, wait, wait.
He's not a senior detective.
I'm fine. I have to get this shit over here.
What?
I'm almost there, guys.
I have it. I'm almost done.
I...
One guy that said, I hate these things.
They are the worst.
They really are the fucking worst.
I hate them.
It's so close. It's almost here.
It's ready, but they need to be moved.
I just had it, and I fucked it up.
I know it's easy, but
I'm fucking so done.
I'm trying
to solve it.
I'm about to just hold the power button on my computer.
I'm about to hold the power button on the computer.
I'll see you tomorrow.
I'm about to hold the power button.
This needs to be up here.
I know.
Look, it's like the streamer
curse, okay?
If I was lying in bed doing this, I could probably do this in
five seconds.
I was seconds away from holding down
the power button, I promise.
Okay, login name. Alois Drew, password
Owise Elder, school computer.
Okay, got it.
Pain in the ass that was.
Alright, let's go.
This is kind of freaking me out.
So I'm pretending to be
a high schooler
and this guy's pretending to be my uncle.
Students, too.
The high school.
Is he pretending to be a student, too?
We're all pretending to be students?
We're all just detectives?
Wait, what?
That's me, right?
And I'm pretending?
I can't. I don't know you have contacts.
That's something I didn't have.
That's not part of my job.
What?
I can't play Barnacle Blast? Are you serious?
That's a shame.
That makes a cool sound.
Alright, let's find our uncle
who's hanging out somewhere in the diner.
Oh, hey Jimmy!
He's a pulling dynamite character.
Of course. I'm just a bit...
Well, my undercover assignments
are usually not so...
suburban.
I understand.
The victim was a senior named Jake Rogers.
As usual, none of the family, teachers or students
know about any enemies he may have had.
Nothing came up from searching
his home, computer, cell phone or locker.
His bank records tell a different story.
Bank records?
He had a fairly large savings account and a lot of cash deposits.
We suspect he was involved in
something shady.
Drugs, gambling or blackmail.
That's where you fit in.
Talk to the students and see what you can find out.
We think he might have kept information about
his activities in a notebook or journal.
So keep a lookout for anything like that.
Anything else?
Bye Uncle Steve.
Goodbye Nancy.
Okay. Any food on the table?
Anything I can grab? Any slide puzzles
for me to almost turn my computer off?
I ripped the plug out of the wall.
I'm looking for another slide puzzle.
What about here?
This is my house.
Okay. Homecoming.
I thought this was a golf club.
Surf club is cool. That's cool.
Is this the locker?
Alright. I don't know this information yet.
Alright. Is this the gym?
Homecoming.
A note.
Message. KRL.
Sneeze and vid.
Unroy.
Alright. What is that for?
Okay. For a second I thought that their mascot
was a sock.
With boxing gloves.
What a dumb mascot.
Extra pop. Grape. Orange.
Soda. Cool.
Or spot cola.
I would love to have a sip of cool cola.
Soda pop?
This is probably a puzzle.
Spot cola. Cool soda.
Orange soda.
Grape soda.
Grape. Orange. Cool. Soda.
No.
I need money.
Out of order?
Why do you think it costs money?
Holy shit. You just kind of stand.
The Hulk?
And then the pros.
Showtime.
Who are the manatees?
Paseo Del Mar's mascot is a manatee.
Don't tell me you're afraid of a little sea cow.
Of course not. I know what to do if I come across
a manatee. Why would you immediately
talk about how you would fight and punch one
and hurt one?
Of course not. I know what to do if I come across
a manatee.
Yeah. Just sneeze and it'll swim away.
Seriously. The manatees are a great team
at a great school.
This school is cool. Except for a few punks like
Jake Rogers.
Jake Rogers?
I knew Jake, but I didn't hang out with him.
Is it the guy that died?
Sorry. Can't talk now. I gotta go to practice.
Later.
You name dropped the only person
who died.
Yeah. This school is pretty cool. Except Jake
Robert. Jake Robert sucks. I hate him.
Oh. Okay. You know, he's dead.
Oh. Yeah.
Welcome to the school.
How could I get into Jake's locker?
I could tear the door off with my teeth.
But it just might be easier to ask
Hal Tanaka. His locker was right next to
Jake's. Okay.
What can you tell me about Daryl Gray?
He seems like a cool guy.
His family used to sponsor the annual football
awards dinner until last year.
You know, he's the one who found Jake's body.
Wait. What?
Hold on. I'm so
lost right now.
He knows, he knows that he's
that this
this guy's dead.
He talked about how much he's like
he sucks. And now he's like, oh
yeah. That's where the body was.
I'll talk to you later.
That's a psycho. Financing. Yeah. This is a psychopath.
You like checked every
box of are you a psychopath
or not? Alright. We gotta find, where's this
in the trash?
Eye test. E-V-I'll do
it. I'll do the eye test. Let's see
how good I do. E-V-I
F-O-R
E-Z-E-E
R-H-T
E-G
A-P-K
O-O-B-Y
R-T
C-Z-M
N-M-C-Z-M
N-J
K-O
O-L-K-M
O-T-E-M
I don't know.
B-F-F-A
L-E-E
U-L-K-Y
K-A-A
P-I
Go to the doctor. No, I
can't do this. You know, okay,
when you go, okay, Jeremy, please
cover one eye and do it. And you cover one eye and you do it
and then it's like, oh, do the other eye. And it's like
I can't. It's all blurry.
You can only do this once. You actually
can only do that test one time. You can't do the other eye.
Because my eye, the other eye is like all
fucked up and blurry and shit.
You got about half of that wrong.
Well, maybe down by the bottom. Don't
press it. No, it's the
it's the light coming back into your eye.
It's like all blurry and smushed.
Go to a doctor. What are you talking
about? Go to a doctor.
What are you talking about? I'm fine.
Alright. Please go to a doctor
that shouldn't happen. What are you, what?
When I cover one eye
and then I do, I cover one eye for long
enough and I take my hand off that eye and I cover
it. It's like this eye that was covered
is all fucked up.
Bro, don't you have a hernia? Yeah.
It sucks. Okay, I found a coin.
Let's go get a drink. The drink is not
in the women's bathroom. How do I get
the hell out of here? Alright, drink.
Uh, I want a
what should I get? Cool soda?
Or should I get extra pop? I think, yeah,
cool soda. Definitely.
That is wasted quarter.
Alright, we're gonna go talk to this
whoever was the locker?
Where would I find this person?
Learning is the only thing the mind never
exhausts, never fears, and never regrets.
Da Vinci.
Thank you, Da Vinci. Very nice.
Yes. Thank you, Da Vinci.
Danger. Admit to authorize
personnel only. What do you mean danger?
This is like a high voltage room back here?
Alright, hold on. This is a puzzle?
Oh, I don't know the code.
Alright, I remember that's here.
Okay. Hi, I'm Connie.
You're not from around here, are you?
Usually, Paseo Del Mar High is
really quiet and boring. Connie, where'd you get that?
Lately, it's been totally out of control.
I want one of those.
Where do I get this? They don't have that here.
They don't sell that here. You brought that in from home.
No outside food or drink
allowed. I'm reporting you to the hall monitor.
Out of control?
One of the students was
killed last week. Who
was killed? Oh, just this
wannabe stud named Jake Rogers.
Why are people shit talking?
Jake Rogers was a total creep.
Nobody liked him. I gotta go
now. Later. Oh my
God. Didn't he just
get thrown down a flight of stairs
and died?
Hey Nancy, need something?
What do you know about Hulk
Sanchez? He's a big jock on
campus. Never dated him or anything.
Why do we need that info? Why do you
have to say that? I don't
need that info.
Hey, who is this person? Oh, you know, he's a jock.
I never dated him though.
Alright.
Okay. I just asked
you who he was. How well do you
know Daryl Gray?
They both did it.
He's the only guy I'd ever consider dating.
He's student council president,
holds a cool job at a diner called Max scenes,
and drives a CBAC X8.
You're really hammering down the like, who I'm going to date.
Drives a sports car and works at a diner?
That doesn't compute.
Yeah, I don't get it either. Daryl's family
was rich and used to throw major parties all the time.
But not anymore.
What is that? I'll talk to you
later. Bye Nancy.
What is that on her neck? Is it like a medal?
Is it like a gold medal? What is that?
Hey Nancy, need something?
See you later.
Bye Nancy. It's an Olympic medal.
Is it? Magazine
puzzle? Connie the Olympian.
Paseo students of the month.
Why is this like
this? Somebody did
this wrong.
September, October, November, December, January,
February, March. Why wouldn't this be in a row?
It's weird
in a row. It's a school year.
Look at the chat. Look at the chat. Look at the chat.
Look at the chat. Is this a puzzle?
What do you want? Alright, that's
What do you even get that image from?
Alright, so maybe I need to remember
this. Alright, well we know that now.
Let's go in here.
I'm going in. I'm old enough
to go in here. I'm like 37.
You're not supposed to go in there.
Sorry, blew my cover.
That was a shiny thing.
Oh, a quarter. Am I going to softlock
myself? She did it.
I didn't do it. She did.
She did it. Oh, a quarter.
That's some.
Can I nominate
that? Oh,
another quarter. No, I might
need this. Alright, I have to find this
student. Debate
team, math team.
Hi, my name's Nancy
Drew. What's your name?
Hal Tanaka. Actually, my first
name is much longer than that.
But I want to fit in here in America.
So I chose Hal as my nickname.
I'm a Japanese exchange
student. Why do you think it's
easier to have an American name?
I want to be part of the culture and
succeed in this country.
Do you plan on staying in America after
you finish high school? My family
is counting on me to succeed here.
I must make them proud of me.
What's your favorite soda?
So what's been going on at school lately?
A murder was committed here.
Everyone is very stressed out.
Alright, so we have a little
bit of
actual human being here.
I heard about that.
Some kid named Jake?
Oh, yeah. Jake Rogers
was a dark soul.
He created a lot of trouble.
What do you mean a dark soul?
What do you mean by dark soul?
Jake wasn't a happy
person and made others around him
very unhappy, too.
How did Jake make people around him unhappy?
This is weird written dialogue.
In English,
you would say a bully.
He wasn't very popular.
I'm behind in my studies and I must get back to the library.
He was the dark soul of
high school students.
Oh,
can I
What's the combination?
Do you know the combination to Jake Rogers' locker?
I'm sorry, Nancy.
I can't help you with that.
How do you not know the combination?
Hoke said your locker is right next to Jake's.
Are you sure you don't know the combination?
Hmm.
I remember one day Jake was mad because
he couldn't open his locker.
He told me he wished he had a phone handy.
Would that help?
Phone handy?
He told me he wished he had a phone
to do math?
Have you heard of Hoke Sanchez?
Heard of him?
Hoke holds the conference record for quarterback sex.
He's been the state's number one player
since he was a freshman.
He's also a candidate for a big university
even with his injury.
Injury?
Hoke got hurt a few weeks ago. Ever since that game
he hasn't played the same.
I worry that his chances of playing for
top school are not as good
as before his injury.
Hmm, interesting.
Do you know Connie Watson?
Yes, we've been in a few classes together.
I think she was dating Jake Rogers.
Yeah, where is this looking out to?
They need to mow the grass.
That shit is getting wild.
What can you tell me about Daryl Gray?
He's very popular
and a good politician too.
Just like his father.
Like his father?
I hear he was a great politician
but not a very good businessman.
I think his company went bankrupt
a few years ago.
See ya.
See you later, Nancy.
Here's my phone.
Holy shit, Nancy.
You don't have very many people
in your phone.
That's it. Just Ned.
Only Ned.
Is this Martha Windeglassen?
Who is please calling me?
Um, no.
I'm trying to reach Ned Nickerson.
Nancy, it's Ned.
I thought with you being undercover and everything
I had to take on a different persona.
Ned, I'm the one who's undercover, not you.
Okay, okay.
I guess I'll just go undercover vicariously through you.
Which for some odd reason feels very
deja vu.
Would it probably be a good idea if you didn't
mention my assignment to anyone?
You never know who may be related
to this case, even up at Emerson.
Your secret's safe with me,
along with your heart.
You're such a sweetie.
Enough lovey-dovey talk. It'll make me miss you even more.
So have you found any homicidal secrets yet?
Have we even seen each other in real life?
I feel like we haven't.
Ciao.
Because I'm playing as a senior detective, I don't need a task list.
What?
Did that.
Are you kidding me?
Another coin? Cool.
Another coin in the trash?
There's a lot of coins now.
Alright, let's go back to the locker and see what the hell's going on here.
Alright, he needed a phone.
Why would he need a phone?
He needed a phone.
Why would he need a phone for this?
Maybe the code is...
Yeah, maybe it's like...
Why would you put a picture of your...
Maybe take the phone out here?
Zoom?
I don't know, is there anything over here?
Get Hulk to rip the door off.
Maybe it's his phone number.
The last four digits?
I don't think I have that info though.
Who am I calling?
She hangs up. Who hung up?
It's Jake.
Oh shit, it was Jake.
A treatise on etiquette.
There's a ripped up piece of paper in here.
What else have we got?
T120.
There's a tape. The tape is gone though.
Judo today.
New judo trends. Tournament winners.
Holds and throws with style.
Masked Marauder flattens foes.
I don't know anything about judo.
Who's winning here?
Is this guy doing a huge flip
over the other guy and ripping him forward?
Or is the other guy throwing him over the shoulder?
I don't know who's winning.
Breaking at local pharmacy.
Paseo County Police responded to a breaking
at the drug station pharmacy on 80th Street
in the early morning hours yesterday.
Whoever it was knew exactly what they were looking for.
They broke in the building
through the back window, took the drugs
and were out for minutes.
According to the report, several vials of
hectanol were taken.
We were just lucky that
no of the damage was done to the store.
What is hectanol?
Why was there a coin in the A?
Alright, so we've got
breaking at the pharmacy.
Let's go talk to the pharmacy.
Alright, let's go talk to the pharmacy.
Wait! Let's go.
This is pretty sick, actually.
You know what they haven't made in a long time?
An updated cool
version of this game.
They keep making the same iPad version.
No, not Peggle.
Breakout.
Cool Breakout? Yeah.
I remember the best part about
Breakout is when you beat a level
and the ball stayed up top and you just
let it just auto play.
And have it just take out. It just got stuck
on the top row.
And almost the whole level would get completed.
Let's see if we can do it.
Do it. Oh, come on.
How many levels are there?
Get stuck up there.
Oh wow, this made it real easy.
This is an amateur detective, not a
master detective anymore.
Forty hour minigame. Do I get anything
for doing this? I lost. Yeah, it's okay.
You lost our respect.
Don't worry, I'll get it back.
I'll get it back when I bag the
killer for who threw Jake
down the stairs.
Probably not tonight though, because this is probably like
a 16 hour game.
And we're doing, hopefully, no more heroes
tomorrow.
Oh, nice. Alright, I gotta make this work.
Get in there. Come on, get in.
In, in, in. No, in, in.
Ah, it's over. I wrote it.
It's alright. Is this 700,000
games?
It's probably better than
what's on that disc.
Is this available on Steam? Yeah, it is.
I think all of them are.
At least most of them. This is nice.
I actually am really, I'm just kind of
relaxing now.
Yeah, that was pretty good sync.
I'm gonna say there's probably five levels.
And I'm never doing this again, so I might as well try to beat it.
And get the achievement at the end of the game.
We needed
to unwind after that slide puzzle.
Yeah, we needed a good unwind.
Which in itself should be an
unwind, but it wasn't.
I can't believe I almost turned the power button
off on my computer.
I was gonna do it too, and I'm gonna be like, fuck it, I'll see you
tomorrow.
Almost makes you forget that someone was
murdered. Yeah,
as a detective I shouldn't be doing this.
Shouldn't I have dusted this thing for fingerprints?
God, how many levels are there?
I wanna get it up there.
Come on, do it.
Get up there.
Do I have ten lives?
This is never gonna end.
If I could turn my camera on right now, I would.
I don't do this very often,
but I'm doing it right now.
I'm leaning forward on my desk with my
left hand. My left elbow
is on the desk, and my
left hand is on my chin.
In a fist, just kinda hanging up.
Why didn't I look?
I wasn't even looking, I looked away.
Now I know why no one's
made another version of this game, because after five
levels you're like, alright, this is, I'm done.
There's a reason why no one has
revolutionized the breakout
game. Battle Royale
Breakout? Alright, there can't
be more than ten levels.
You're killing me. You're killing me.
Come on. Alright.
Level six.
What does that say?
Eighty...
Eighty what?
I gotta sit up.
Alright, sit up, sit up, sit up, sit up. I'm starting to not care.
I have to care.
Does Bond?
I wonder if that's a code or something. Maybe that is a code for something.
I want a pizza so bad.
I don't, what is it with
streaming? It's something about
streaming. On a day-to-day basis,
I don't want to eat pizza.
But during a stream,
I sit here, and I just
think, you know, I just want a full pizza.
It's only when I'm streaming.
Me too? Do you guys
get that too? Maybe it's a Twitch
thing. Yeah, yeah, yeah.
S...
SCK.
Suck?
Sucks.
I want to hit those three
whirlpools. I want to make it harder.
It's definitely ten.
Why would it be more than ten?
I guess it's not that hard to make these games
because once you have the template for them,
you can make ten thousand of them.
Maybe they just never end.
Comes in a break. What if it's just randomly generated?
That would be bad.
It's the eyes.
When you get it going sideways, it's good
shit. It's going sideways.
Come on, do them all.
Yeah.
Wii Sports Party Game?
Well, let me do No More Heroes first. I gotta get my
Wii mode to function.
Only two more levels and I, regardless,
I'm done. This is nice, though.
Yeah.
This is the taking a bath
of video games. Level nine.
Speed it up.
That was fast, holy shit.
Another sorting
algorithm.
I almost hit five hundred thousand points.
What kind of bath is like this?
Well, I mean, just the way that my brain is
acting right now. I'm just relaxing.
I feel good.
Get all the beaks. You're coming down
from the drugs.
God damn it.
This better
be it. This better be it.
Is it Y2K?
Yes. Is it raining?
No. Maybe in the game.
All right. I gotta get back to detective work.
This is putting me to sleep.
And I am not going to sleep without a full pizza.
So like that's not going to happen.
Get to one million points.
Damn it. All right.
This looks like a final level. Look at this.
This is like original Donkey Kong.
Yes.
That's what I wanted.
That's all I wanted.
What about the...
What about the guy that was murdered?
Yeah.
I'll get to it. I promise.
Who?
What do you mean? Oh. Who?
I think his name... I don't even remember his name.
Jake?
All right. Fine.
You guys want me to test for it? I will.
Never mind. I am just too late.
I was going to blow into my Wii mode again.
Oh no.
I have to like brush my teeth.
Oh boy. Oh my god.
Oh my god. Oh my god. Oh my god.
This is a used Wii mode and I didn't clean it.
And I put it in my mouth like four times.
Ah!
Oh no. No. No.
And there's like stuff on it.
Oh fuck. What happened?
Oh my god.
Oh my fucking god.
I have to brush my fucking teeth right now.
You see this?
Darn it!
I'll be right back.
God damn it.
I hate that.
I hate it.
Oh my god.
Oh.
It's like in a room with like
a shitload of cigarettes in it.
It's yellow.
Like it was probably
somebody probably smoked in their house.
Look.
Somebody probably was just like a smoker
and that's like all the smoke filth.
That fucking, that shit
was in my mouth and I didn't even clean it.
Oh my god.
How far did I put it in my mouth?
It's Cheetos.
That's somehow worse.
What you just said is worse. I'm just thinking of some
some like fucking kid
with like Cheeto covered hands
always and never washing his hands.
No. That's definitely
a cigarette. Oh! That's a cigarette
stain. That's somebody's fucking
cigarette fingers.
Fuck.
Damn it.
Old plastic turns yellow.
I know but you don't, I put it in my mouth.
I just like
I just put somebody's
cigarette fingers in my mouth.
What level is this?
It wasn't on camera. Oh I'm talking about from like
two hours ago. Like three hours ago.
That was a delayed reaction.
We did get, we got the cool Drupi
picture though.
Yeah but is that
is that worth getting like
is that worth getting like cigarette
hepatitis? Yes.
This is garage band music.
Alright if
I can't stop at 13 because like that's unlucky.
So if it's
there's more than 13 probably. I'm
gonna turn my computer off. Five.
Four. Just kidding.
Finish the
barnacle game.
I fucking
fucking can again.
Alright this one. This is it. This is it. I don't care. This is it.
I'm gonna stop at 14. I don't care. I'm done.
Mouth. Isn't there a murder solve?
Yes. Eventually. Maybe I
will eventually.
Once this girl in my eighth grade class
licked a pig heart we were dissecting.
Oh wow.
Yeah but don't
don't they
like dunk those things in acid to
clean them? This wee moat was not
dunked in like dissecting fluid.
Somebody scratched their ass, smoked
five packs of cigarettes and put it into a box.
Bite into a raw egg
to kill the bacteria.
What would that do?
I licked the floor
of a school bus once.
Why can I see? You know
like images you can
hear. Why can I hear
that story? Like a bunch of kids
saying, you want to lick the bottom of the school bus?
Yeah I will. No you won't.
Loser.
Yeah.
He did it. Whoa.
I can hear that image.
The bus driver's like shut the fuck
up back there.
The bus driver's just like hey
you little bastards.
Don't touch anything.
How dare you
lick my bus.
You little shits.
Okay I gotta pay attention.
I need to say something.
Okay. Can we
give it up
a little bit here and give
the respect that's deserved
to our school bus drivers?
The amount of shit
that they have to listen to
and the amount of nonsense
that they have to potentially put up with.
And they've got to pay attention.
They've got to make sure they get these
kids around safely.
That's a pretty
that requires a little bit of
applause.
Because I am
I cannot imagine me ever
in any scenario
where I would be able to pay attention and drive
with this going on.
Think about it. What the fuck is this?
What a weird gif.
Okay. Alright so
imagine driving a car and needing to pay attention
to this going on. This is why we need to give our respect
to those people.
Okay I have to get
off at the next exit.
Stop!
Shut up back there.
This is a long video.
This is fucking loud.
No it's just like an airplane.
That's like an airplane
sound. Why would that come up as
a car driving?
Okay I don't know why I saw
car sounds sleeping.
Car sounds white noise
for sleep. Why would a sleep
what are you talking about?
No I can't add all that fucking
bullshit. Alright
give me a second.
No these are cars driving by on the highway.
That's not going to work.
Nope. I ain't going there.
I ain't going there.
Let's try.
No
there's a stage where that goes
too far and I don't want to take it
there.
Just go!
Just go! Go! Go! Just go! Do the detective
case!
Get me out!
Get out! Get out! Get out! Get out! Get out!
Out! Out! Out! Out!
Hi Nancy. How can I get
into the teacher's lounge? Why is this so loud?
Look Nancy maybe this assignment
isn't for you. I can't be holding your
hand all the time. Your job is to come
to me with solutions not
problems. When the police looked through Jake's
locker did they take a videotape? When the police
looked through Jake's locker did they take
a videotape? No
we didn't.
That was a very unconvincing note.
Okay so I need to find the videotape.
I would appreciate the
if we got rid of the Mario Kart
intro music.
Is there anything else in the house?
What the hell am I supposed to do?
Besides drink soda.
What the hell do high school kids do?
Besides walk around and drink soda.
Hey Nancy. Need something?
Do you know why Jake had an empty
videocassette case in his locker?
No. Why are you so interested
in Jake anyway?
I gotta go now. Later. Nancy
I'm starting to wonder about you.
Didn't I hear you were dating Jake?
Hey a girl can make a
mistake can't she?
Do you know how Tanaka?
Not very well. He's an exchange student
from Japan and a total workaholic.
He told me he's trying to get
more scholarships for college.
Lately he's been looking really burnt out.
I think the pressure's getting to him.
What pressure?
I guess it's a big deal for his family
that he'd get into a good school on a free ride.
I'll let you go.
Bye Nancy.
Okay. What's
to play here? What do I have a key?
What's this key for? You got it? Wait. Okay.
What's the key for?
Have I found a key yet?
Have I found a place for this to go?
Is it the maintenance closet?
No. This might be a puzzle.
What would it want me to do?
Go to the library? What the hell is the
library? I mean that's the exit.
Other way?
Down here? Library.
Library. Library?
This library sucks.
Do you know why Jake had an
empty video cassette case in his
Yeah I see it. I see it. I see it
and it's beautiful. It's very nice.
It's very very nice. I didn't know Jake was
interested in video. I avoided him
whenever I could.
Jesus Christ.
I avoided him whenever I could.
I hated him. He was an asshole. He was a piece of shit.
Nobody liked him. I don't like him.
He sucked.
My God.
Are you in the library?
You're in the library.
That's where you are.
Oh no. Here's a library.
Who locks a school
library?
Is there forbidden knowledge in here? I don't understand.
Monday through Thursday, 8 to 4. I can't go in there.
Yeah I can. Give me that key.
Fiction. Secret
books? No.
What is a relic?
What's a relic? I don't know.
A perfect alibi.
Doesn't seem to be very interesting.
What even is a relic?
It's weird. I know exactly what a relic is.
But it's hard for me to describe to you what a relic is.
It's an old
piece of an
old medallion or an old
crafted thing
that is
old and from an old
culture, an old
religion.
It's an object
that holds significant potential
cultural value.
Where's my
book?
Didn't I read somebody's password?
Catalog search. What am I looking for?
What was the name?
What was the relic?
Check shelf.
Star Wars. It's not going to be a Star Wars book.
This book is something I'm specifically looking for.
I don't know what it is though.
What were some of the other names of those?
I don't think there was a book.
There was something written down.
Somebody has a book somewhere.
Why did the music just change?
What the fuck is going on?
Do I have to look these up?
There's got to be something about...
What's this one called? The Meltdown?
Digital Meltdown.
A novel by Jeremy
Albertson. What's this one called?
The Crystal
Skulls? Jake was here.
Things to remember.
The answer to my fate lies
in the box.
A matchbook behind Maxine's
schedule holds the first step.
My messages hold the remaining
18 steps.
The elements tell the
order. The letter and
digit tell the direction.
J.R.
God, man. U2.
Where is U2?
What element is U2?
No, we've got to go...
Underneath the schedule.
It's an incomplete table.
Matchbook behind Maxine's schedule.
Well, let's go
Let's go look at that.
Take a screenshot of this.
Yeah, good idea.
Good call. I hate when it goes to
this music. It always goes back to this.
Alright, who's
gonna find Maxine?
I always thought they were
gonna make me do another one of those.
Oh no, they might.
Thank god.
Behind the schedule.
Who the hell is that?
See you later. Goodbye, Nancy.
Okay, see you later.
Wait, this is a Kevin McLeod zone?
Really? Let's go talk to Mr. Jim.
How's it going?
Who's Maxine?
Tell me about the robbery at the drug station
pharmacy.
Why would I know about a robbery?
All I know about is football.
I'm really sorry you got injured.
Does that affect your chances
of playing college ball?
I had a little sprain, no big deal.
Within a week, I was better than before
and impressing the football scouts.
I'm as strong as ever.
Anyone that says I'm as strong as ever
usually is about at 40%.
What can you tell me about Connie Watson?
She hangs out at the gym a lot. I heard she's been having
a real tough time.
Why do you think she hangs out at the gym so much?
I don't know.
She's a pretty good athlete, but never joined any of
Paseo Del Mar's teams.
Why not?
Not exactly sure.
You said she was having a tough time?
I heard she's been having some money problems.
Did you take the videocassette from Jake's locker?
Do you know why Jake had an empty videocassette case
in his locker?
I didn't pay much attention to Jake.
I'm tired of talking about that loser.
I'll kill you with my bare teeth.
Do you know Hal Tanaka?
That dude is always studying.
He's a huge fan of mine. Real smart guy.
But I never understood why a
brain like Tanaka would hang out with slime
like Jake.
Hal was a friend of Jake's?
Why?
Let's just say I saw them talking together a lot.
Jake's locker was right next to Hal's.
But they weren't really friends.
Is that what you're saying?
Jake didn't really have friends.
And Hal, he may seem pretty chill,
but I've seen him crack a couple of times.
He's seriously uptight.
Crack a couple of times?
He's got a temper, a bad one.
He lets the pressure build and build until
he's wound so tight the slightest thing sets him off.
Like last week, I strike him out
and he goes ballistic and charges the mount.
He's got some serious issues.
Now that I think of it,
last time I saw them together,
Hal seemed pretty upset.
Goodbye.
Well, we have new info to
bring to...
I'm not into pushy girls.
Do me a favor and bother someone else.
I'll talk to you later.
I'm going to drink a Mountain Dew
just because of that
dick.
Oh, just regular soda water.
Gross.
Who would ever buy that?
Cat puke.
Let's go talk and say,
hey, so you attacked people.
See ya.
Goodbye, Nancy.
I need a schedule.
Nancy, I'm starting to wonder about you.
Have you seen any of those weird messages
on the bulletin boards?
White Claw?
Yes, and if I catch the guy who's doing it,
I bet it's the same person who keeps on setting off
the soda machine alarm.
There's a soda machine alarm?
I guess that comes with a territory
of being a school monitor.
Normally it's not this hectic.
When I figure out who's been pulling all these pranks.
Hulk told me
money's been tight for you these days.
What a dork!
Hulk Sanch has doesn't know the first thing about my life.
He needs to get a life and stop talking
about mine.
I need to sit before these people in this room
and sit in each one of these chairs and go fucking hash it out
and walk away. Seriously.
See you later. Adios.
Bushcan?
The soda can't just be for fun.
Can it?
Looking for the schedule.
Somebody had a schedule we needed to look behind.
Maybe on a bulletin board?
Wait a minute. What's that?
Meet in the parking lot at 9 in the morning.
Pippen will take place to survey the Dresden Reservoir.
Brass set for later.
L-A-U-2.
Uh, okay.
Well, there's the U-2.
Yeah, why are there only three people in this school?
It's gonna be real easy to narrow down
who killed Jake, considering there's only
four people in the game.
It's a 25% chance to get it right.
Announcements.
Student bulletin board.
Attention. Wait.
The Roaring Girl.
A Jacobean comedy.
Talk to Deception. A poetic drama written by
the senior essay winners of
The student files under lock and key
will show the lies of the doctor to be
H-F-L-1.
I feel like this shit is important somehow.
Something about the elements?
I have no idea.
Why would I need to be, why could I look at this?
Take a picture of it?
Is there anything else I can go in town?
I feel like I'm just trapped here.
What can I do for you?
Do you know why Jake had an empty
video cassette case in his locker?
Why were you in Jake's locker?
It was
open and I just looked through it.
Oh.
I have no idea.
What else can I do for you?
Didn't I hear that you
found Jake's body?
Yeah, I did.
The student council president gets keys
to the school. We had an early morning
council meeting and
I found him lying there. It was the worst
thing I ever experienced in my life.
And I really don't want to
think about it right now.
Do you know Connie Watson?
Not that well. She keeps to herself
a lot. I've always thought
there's something mysterious about
her. Kind of the same way
I feel about you.
$1.30 for a ham sandwich?
That's pretty cool.
How well do you know Hulk Sanchez?
Big guy, big muscles,
big dreams. A lot of
football scouts have been coming over to watch and play.
He must be under a lot of pressure
to perform. What can you tell me about
Hal Tanaka?
Hal's an exchange student who's all scholarships
and study. He's very
intense about becoming a doctor.
How much ketchup can you drink in 10 seconds?
Talk to you later.
Impress me. See ya.
Can I go in the back? I didn't even
know I could go back here. That's just
very realistic. That's a pretty
realistic looking knife.
Cooking minigame, I hope so.
Payday, payday, payday, payday.
Hmm, looks like something
was removed here.
Didn't I find it in his locker? Wasn't it in the corner?
First aid? No.
He's on the schedule, yeah.
Hold on, let me see that again.
Behind, right, behind the
schedule, right?
Didn't say the clue was behind Maxine's
schedule? T-E-L-
three, where is it?
T-E-L-three.
C-ki
ichi.
What is that? What does that mean, though?
He's not looking at those edits? I'll look at
one. Pretty good.
Pretty good. What am I supposed to do with this?
Boop boop boop.
Boop boop boop. So I have it, now what?
Yeah, that's good. No, fuck off, says
German 985. When did I do
that? What does this mean?
Is that numbers?
Typed like C-E-E?
Or...
I don't know. I don't get it.
That's braille, right? But
what do I need that for?
What about the periodic table?
See ya. Farewell, Nancy.
It's Eric from High School. Remember me?
Me and the guys used to give you a hard time in English
class. Sorry, you're just an easy target.
I cannot see much to change.
Remember Jenny, the girl you had a crush on when we were
married? I now make over $200,000
a year.
And I drive a really expensive car. I guess something
never changed. Holland Loser, that's catching up. LOL
Pathetic. I made more money than you.
In the last, like,
14 days.
So, um...
Cool, good luck.
That's not even true.
I can't perpetuate that one.
That means
I make like fucking $70,000,000
a year. I need to go
to the pier- Alright, I'm about to turn it off.
I need to get- I'm gonna go- I'm- I'm-
My pizza levels are at a dangerous
level. What's that?
Wait, how do I flip it? I can't
flip it? Flip your head.
This isn't-
Nowhere to turn to, nowhere to hide.
Let the books in the
library be your answer guide.
Okay.
It- This is-
This is mirrored.
That- Hold on, it's mirrored.
Okay, got a picture.
Now, can you flip horizontally in
iPhone? You can't.
Just mirror OBS.
Oh, right, I use mirror OBS.
Uh, nowhere to turn to,
nowhere to hide. No- Wait, what?
Transform.
Flip horizontal.
That- What is going on?
That someone-
That someone must-
Why is this wrong?
The letters- It's the placement
of the letters.
That someone must
hide
reflects big
secret.
Worn with
great pride.
A symbol of
jank.
kanji.
Wait, the thing around her neck?
That medallion, right?
Now, what's this last one?
Took it
to bib.
I have to go eat a pizza.
Took it- Took it to
bib.
I had to- It's upside down though.
Flip it upside down.
Yeah, it's time to get a pizza.
Let me look at it here. He did what it took to make
the grade, even if it meant cheating to keep up
his charade.
Talking about me?
Alright, so we gotta talk- We gotta talk to, um,
that-
the lady in here. I'm gonna sneeze.
I can do about it.
Alright, let's go talk about the necklace.
It's almost time for me to get a pizza.
Close.
Where was she sitting again? I don't even remember.
Okay, hey, what's with the medallion?
What is this?
What does it say?
Okay, it looks like
I need to get- I wanna see.
No, I'm trying to get a picture of the medallion!
Oh my god.
What does this mean, too?
Probably get rid of you so I can go in here.
You're eating pizza right now?
I've never been more jealous in my whole life.
What kind of pizza is it, though?
Talk to me.
Best pizza on Earth
is very, very thin,
crispy, thin crust.
And I'm talking paper thin.
Pepperoni pizza.
That's it. Don't put any of the junk on it.
Just a super thin,
crispy pepperoni pizza.
I don't want anything else on it.
Don't load it up with hamburger meat
and onions and garlic and bacon
and salami.
Because then it's not a pizza anymore.
You're eating
spaghetti and meatballs
at that point.
You might as well just put it all in a bowl and eat it out of a bowl.
Because the thing just falls apart.
If you get a meatlovers pizza, don't eat
meatlovers pizza, seriously.
They're just making a joke.
Because you pick it up and you lift it up
and it goes- here, I'll give you an example.
So you pick up a piece of pizza that's
meatlovers, right? I just picked it up.
This is the top. This is the crust.
So I pick it up and it goes like this.
And everything just falls off into the plate.
And then you go, oh shit, oh well.
Looks like I'm eating a piece of wet paper
with spaghetti sauce on it.
What's that down there?
The shit that I paid for? I'll eat it with a fork later.
You have to fold it.
Oh, sure. Let me go ahead and
let me fold the pizza now.
Let's fold it in half. And then when I bite into it,
like this,
all the toppings mush out
into my face and go all over me
and burn the fuck out of me.
Like, ow! And it falls down
on the plate and there it goes again.
If you- no, don't say we.
That's why I didn't do it, because I had touched it.
If you fold a pizza that has a ton of toppings on it,
all the toppings just mush out out of the top.
He's never eaten- do I have to
order a meatlovers pizza and eat it?
To show you that-
where are you getting your meatlovers pizzas?
They're loaded with toppings!
You're a crackhead. You don't eat tacos.
Tacos are messy too, but they're good.
No, I'm not doing it on stream right now.
Alright, fine. How about this? I promise.
Listen, time stamp this.
I will eat
a big meatlovers pizza.
Not the whole thing, but just enough for me to prove
that they're a fucking mess.
Not tomorrow. We're doing Normal Heroes tomorrow.
It'll be its own stream.
The stream will just be titled
Dickhead Eats a Pizza
to prove a non-existent point.
Alright, see you tomorrow. I'm out.
I'm going to get a pizza.
I'm going to get a pizza. Now we talked about it. Now I want one.
Boo, boo, boo.
Five hour stream because
Hungry Boomer. No.
Five hour stream because I couldn't get
no more heroes to work.
I still have- I thought this was a good one.
I had a lot of fun playing Nancy Drew.
Maybe not this one, but the last one. Eh, this one too.
At least first- I liked it.
But we keep talking.
You guys messed it up. You talked about pizza too many times.
The second you bring up pizza, I'm going to leave. You know that, right?
If you guys want
more than, you know, six, seven hour streams,
don't say the word pizza in the chat.
How many times have I looked over here
when someone's like, oh man, I really want a pizza tonight.
And I go, oh cool, me too.
And the stream ends in like 40 minutes.
That's happened at least three or four times in the last six months.
It's our fault.
What topping should I get? I told you.
Pepperoni.
Cheese with the nice
tangy sauce. Crispy.
It's gotta be crispy.
None of this folded.
No, no, no. I want it when I bite into it to sound like
a fucking goddamn potato chip
cartoon commercial.
I want to bite into that crust
and have it be like
this. I don't like doughy
ass pizza. I want it to be like
this. Maybe, okay, maybe not-
that's not like someone chewing on sand. Maybe not
that crunchy. Dude, people-
Here's another thing that's weird.
It is 50-50 split
whether or not people
want to instantly throw up when they-
like somebody crunching
on something is instant-
instantaneous.
Just vile
reaction. And then there are other people that go,
oh, do that again.
I remember I was eating chocolate one time
on stream. This is like three- I don't know why I remember this.
This is like three years ago. And I was eating
Reese's chocolate or something.
And there was like
at least a bunch of people- there was a bunch of people that were saying
dude, you're fucking disgusting.
Like stop- I don't want to hear that.
And I had to mute a bunch of times.
Was that a dream? No, it wasn't.
Chew with- I was.
I swear to god.
Mute your mic while you eat.
Nah, nah, nah, nah.
I'm gonna put the can on this one tonight. We're gonna start
No More Heroes tomorrow.
The viewers are dying. Well, I did-
I did just say the stream was over.
No More Heroes starts tomorrow. We're going- we're going four days in a row, by the way.
I didn't- did I mention that?
I don't think I did.
The reason why I didn't stream the last three, four days in a row
is because I was getting the New Year's Eve stuff ready.
And that stuff is almost all ready.
So we can just go four days in a row.
You'll have No More Heroes tomorrow,
maybe No More Heroes again, depending on if I
do that on Monday. And then New Year's Eve
stream on 31st.
More Nancy. I don't think
there'll be time for it tomorrow or the next day.
Maybe I'll get a pizza on New Year's.
That's not a bad idea. What a good idea.
Alright, fine. I'll get- I'll get a pizza
and I'm gonna eat it on stream.
I'm gonna get burnt. I already know it. Alright, I gotta be careful
on that one. Alright guys, I'll see you
tomorrow. Thanks for sticking around.
Now we're gonna go over the
subs and bits and everything, so don't worry.
And stick around if you want.
Sort of an impromptu Nancy Drew stream because
last second I couldn't get my Wiimote
to work, but it's kinda
what I plan on doing tomorrow.
Is making sure I can get it to function.
If I can't, then we're just gonna have
to boot up the old Wii.
I'll see you guys tomorrow. Have a great
night. Those of you sticking around,
let's talk about bits.
Shall we? Uh,
Melatonin Dream Boy, thanks for the 500 bits.
Uh, no message, just
500 bits, thank you. Uh, thank you
Heavymen for the 300 bits. No More Heroes is
one of my favorite franchises.
And I'd be sure happy to see you play it.
I'd recommend playing the Wii versions
on the original hardware since they can be both
up for like 10 bucks.
Uh, never experienced emulating it though.
Also, difficulty is really not that bad on normal mode
and the controls are easier to control on the Wii mode than you think.
You can also use the Wii Classic controller
if you don't want to deal with the motion controls.
Uh, I've, I played No More Heroes 1
and 2 a long time ago.
Uh, I love these games.
They're a little janky and a little wonky.
But, um,
I wanted to
do them both,
but I didn't want to split it
up to do PS3 because it's a better version
and runs better and then go to Wii
and it runs like crap. And I'd rather
them just both be
um, streamed
through the PC. Because I can make the resolution
better, I can make it look a lot better
because the Wii version, I know we were
we were memeing
on, um,
the original version. But it
really does run like crap
in a lot of places from what I remember.
If you hit somebody with your, uh,
blade and their blood blows up
out of their head, I remember it specifically
chugging down to like 10 frames a second
half the time. So
I'd like to run it in his best
way to present it to people.
The PS3 runs
worse like crap, really. Well then they
both do. So then even better reason
to not stream it on original hardware.
Because I did walk around
in it very, very briefly.
And it seems to run pretty well
on the settings I have now on PC.
Through emulation.
Riding the bike through town will be rough. Yeah,
it always is though. Uh, but
yeah, it's, um,
it should be a great experience. It's a really fun game. It's a really
interesting game. I'm looking
forward to it. To return to it again.
Uh, Heavymin.
That was you. Thank you
again for 300 bits. I don't know why it does
this sometimes. Like I lose, there it is.
Thank you. Hate
sucks. Hate
sucks. No, it was me. It was
not you. Uh, thanks for the thousand
bits, hate. They say DruCru. That's
right. It was the last minute DruCru.
Thank you so much for the
ten dollars thousand bits from hate.
Dark Souls, thanks for the 250
bits. Do you think one day we'll get a lifting
stream where you do a workout set?
Uh, like getting slimed for
doing something chat predicts. Assuming the doctors
can put your Humpty Dumpty streamer back together
well enough.
Uh, probably not for a while. I, I have
to get 20, okay,
2020 is the year for me.
Is what I'm gonna be doing
physical therapy. I have to
figure out what's going on with my body.
2020 is the
get healthy year. It's not like
I've been living an unhealthy lifestyle or anything.
It's just for some reason a lot of things have compounded
on top of each other.
The last year. So I
am gonna do everything necessary to get
100% healthy again.
And whatever that means, whatever procedures
or treatments or therapy that I
have to do for
my rib cage or whatever
the fuck is wrong with me and my hernia.
I might just have surgery. I might just
go do it.
A hiatal hernia doesn't go away.
It gets
worse until you get surgery.
So I might just go do
it, just get it over with. The surgery
is a simple procedure. It's
fine in like four days
or something. Cause I feel like there's a bunch
of issues that are kind of stacking on top
of each other. But we'll find out.
I have a couple of appointments coming up.
And then we'll talk about maybe doing
some more of that stuff. We'll see.
But appreciate the 250.
Fitty. Thanks for the 500 bits, Fitty.
Hey, Jerma, this site shows your
net worth. Can you give me some investment
advice? You seem
to be quite successful. Worth of the
web. What the fuck is this?
How much is
youtube.com slash user slash
Jerma985 worth? You can
find the estimated website value for
Jerma985 in US dollars.
What is it? Oh.
102 billion dollars.
102 billion
650 million dollars.
Wow. That's pretty good.
How much is amazon.com
worth? Amazon
dot com. Okay.
Amazon.com is worth
4.8 billion dollars.
That's cool with me.
I'm okay being worth
like 50 Amazons.
Buy Amazon now.
Dude, that guy from English class.
Yeah, that guy from English class. Ain't got nothing
on me. Did you see that website?
Yeah, man. I got 200k.
I got this awesome
life. What about you?
Hey, I'm worth 102 billion dollars.
Mr. English class.
That's wild though. I don't even know
how is it even calculating that?
Little Wolfie. Thanks for the 850. Cheating
bits. 850 bits from Little Wolfie.
Is that bits because
I cheated or bits for me to not cheat?
I wonder. Jerma.org is only
worth 150 dollars.
It was a bit bounty.
Thank you.
Thank you Lula. Lula
Moore for the thousand bits. Ten bucks.
Hey, Jerma. I've been a long time sub and
fan. I was watching YouTube with my son
the other day and without being prompted
he asked to watch some of your videos.
He said, Jerma is amazing.
He's so hilarious. I wish I could be that funny
someday. I just thought it was cute
and a testament to your content that me, a 34
year old mom boomer
and my kid both
think you're hilarious. P.S.
He peed his pants from laughing.
It was gross. Love the stream
and content. Happy New Year.
Happy New Year to you as well. He's
so hilarious. I gotta
stop swearing. I gotta stop swearing.
Think of the children. You know what I mean?
And I gotta stop pretending to
stand up over my desk and pee into a cup.
You know, I just have to figure that
out too. I gotta clean my act up
a little bit. That will literally never
happen. If you think I'm smart enough to be able to put a
filter on some of the things that I say,
you're sadly mistaken.
I tried it. I tried it
for like a year or two. Didn't work.
Dude, he's got no filter.
I say what I want.
No filter. That's when
like every single person in the audience, their eyes
just rolled in the back of their head all the way to the
back. But no, thank you, Lula.
I appreciate it. I'm also
a 34-year-old boomer, so
he's unhinged.
Thank you. DarkSoul, thanks for the 250.
Checking in from Gap Gaming again.
Really great job with our testing.
With testing our anti-ad gimmick
last time. You really got your chat going.
Any Gappers?
That said, it is concerning to
us that you can't seem to beat a game made
for three-year-olds. We'll have to dock some points
for that in your upcoming review.
Hope you get better, you dumb
idiot streamer.
Thank you, Gapp.
Appreciate it. No, that's
DarkSoul. That's DarkSoul9669.
Your name's not Gapp.
Max, a disaster
thanks for the 500 bits.
Alright, Jermit, just want to thank you for streaming today. My mother was
just diagnosed with multiple
myeloma.
Myeloma? It's a blood
plasma cancer that affects bones.
So I'm glad I have your
LUL moments to take my mind off things.
Here's five bucks to show my appreciation
for your Twitch funny man endeavors.
Thanks.
I'm really, really sorry to hear that.
I don't know, I'm not sure what
stage or what
how far along that is.
But hopefully
it's very treatable. You do what you
can, right? Thank you so much.
I wish the absolute best
for your mother. Glad to have
you. Cancer sucks.
If I could seriously just go like this
and get rid of it. Oh, I would do it a hundred times.
Everybody would.
Just one of those stupid fucking illnesses that
we still can't
seem to figure out, you know?
But a lot of it is treatable. All the best
to you and your mother.
Thank you for the five dollars.
Shitty viewbot thanks for the 500 bits.
Not like this, not like this, not like this.
Drugs are bad. Was that when I was pretending
that I was on drugs?
Oh, I mean, we can talk about this very
briefly now if you want.
I think I haven't talked about it
really that much at all.
But one of the reasons why
the rumble has not been done
yet is because
the next
rumble is going to be
a charity event.
And all the money that that stream takes
in, whether it's bits or
subs, whatever money that that stream takes in
that day,
is going to go and sponsor
a good friend of mine's
Boston Marathon run.
And all that money is going to
go to a, I believe, a pediatric
cancer ward in Boston.
So we're trying to figure
out maybe some fun things to do.
But that's part of the plan.
Have him run in
blue man attire. We've been
talking about ideas of
essentially we're going to have
him be a character in the rumble.
And whatever he has in clothes,
we're going to have him run in those clothes
and I'm going to have him take some video.
This should be fun.
He's going to be a new original
character. He's just like, yeah,
I'll do, that'll be fun. I just want to make
sure I can actually run in whatever it
is. And it's like, don't worry, I'll take care of you.
And the way that it's set up, it's actually
should be pretty easy because
there's specific, there's
going to be a specific website that is linked
directly to the charity.
So the money,
I can, from everything that comes in in that stream,
I can just put it directly in
to that website.
So it's not like, oh, I'm going to
just make all this money on Twitch and then
then I'll figure it out later.
No, it'll be, there'll be plenty of avenues
to get that figured out.
It'll be live action, it will not.
But that's the plan.
Because the marathon is in April.
So I want to do it a little bit
before that, obviously, to make sure
because it's to essentially sponsor
is run. Or at least to contribute
what I, in this
community, can, right?
We'll see.
But thank you to Jim, Jim
Poe for the 300 bits.
Somewhere in January.
When it's
ready. It will be
absolutely before March.
Let's just put it that way.
Before March.
But thank you Jim, thanks for the 300 bits.
No message. Tar Alephren
thanks for the 253.
Jim's use of a guide in the stream invalidates
all prior alleged accomplishments
on stream. How can we be sure
this guy didn't use a guide in all three
Dark Souls and Sekiro?
Um, here's
your rebuttal here. I played
Dark Souls 3 and Sekiro
when they launched.
I played Sekiro the day it came out.
There's no guide. What guide existed on
day zero? I played it when it
came out.
One day had gone by and nobody even had
beaten the game. You don't have
any witnesses. Guides
came out pre-release. You think I was flipping
through
the shit that they sell at GameStop?
That's as big as an encyclopedia with the pictures?
All prior
accomplishments.
Sorry I wanted to, uh,
keep
the Nancy Drew stream
on track.
All prior
accomplishments are null.
Oh, he's stuttering. He's stuttering.
He's stuttering. Hey, little kitty,
thanks for the 500 bits. They say good job.
Thank you. Hey, you did a good job
too, in whatever you did today.
Thank you. Influx meme,
thanks for the 300 bits.
Uh, this is a two-part message.
This is the second part of my message.
Oh, I see what you're saying here. Okay.
Uh, just want to say your huge
influence you've had in my life as I
approach my twenties. Your videos and
streams have always brought me comfort whenever times
have been tough, and your unique brand of comedy has influenced
the stuff I like so much you have no idea.
I know you've probably heard this stuff
before, but you really have a huge impact on your viewers.
And I get to germ a heart
with this absolute chad of a man.
Uh,
I really appreciate that. That's
there's a lot of nice things to say
about somebody. And then you say
one of your early TF2 Q&A
videos you were initially going to delete your
channel, but a friend stopped you
and told you to just see where
it took you. Do you sometimes think about
that? What would have been had you not taken
that chance? You still
talk to that person who was at Burger Boy.
I'm not sure of my path in life, so
you don't have any advice. I'm not sure of my path in life.
Do you have any advice for me? Thank you.
Mod that friend.
Well, here's the thing.
Anytime you start something new,
right, it doesn't matter what it is,
after you do it for the first
time, and you
go through with it, you have
that first initial bump
of, this is dumb,
this is, I probably shouldn't
have done this. This is like kind of dumb, right?
Like, I can
probably use my time somewhere else.
Uh, nah, yeah, I'll do something else.
That happened to me all the time.
I'm in Vegas right now, I'm over
21 this time. And if memory serves
me correctly, it was a
long time ago. I don't
remember if it was Burger Boy or not.
Maybe, I think it was somebody
that I went to college with.
Maybe it was, no, who was it?
This is gonna fucking eat me up now.
Who said to like just, I
said that I made a YouTube channel.
Like you went to college.
I did. I showed
my diploma on stream. Did you see it?
From Blockbuster. I don't remember
who it was. That'll probably
come to me, like later tonight or
something. I don't think it was Burger Boy.
But they watched, they watched the two or three
videos that were there. Which by the way, I deleted
and re-uploaded, I think, twice.
For some reason.
Cause once like three or four
five views came in, I was like,
what, uh, these videos suck, I have to redo
them. Somebody watched them, I have to make it better.
I'm pretty sure I deleted and re-uploaded
the same three videos like twice.
But, I was told,
who cares? Just
let them ride, it doesn't matter.
I'm gonna have to fucking go searching for like
who fucking said that? Who was that?
Maybe it was Burger Boy. Cause we were going to the gym
all the time. We, me and
Burger Boy, believe it or not,
were in the gym three, four
plus days a week. Back then.
And I think I just offhandedly maybe told
them, yeah, I don't know. Just two
chads going to the gym.
But what would I have done if that was,
I mean, I don't know. I don't know, I can't
rewind the clock and
do another life.
What probably would have happened is I would have gone into something,
I would have just continued doing the stuff that I
liked already.
I was really into
stuff with animals.
You know, like volunteering. I was
probably going to maybe go to like vet tech school.
I still ended up volunteering
for a while. But yeah,
that's sometimes I think about what would I,
what would happen if I had not made
half of those videos that I made in the
first two months that I started
this channel. But what would
have happened if my first
TF2, the Uber
update video, didn't get on
the TF2 Reddit?
Like what would have happened?
Would I even be sitting
here right now doing this?
Probably not. Probably not.
You would go be an English teacher in Japan.
I can barely speak English.
You think I can teach somebody how?
But any advice, don't
get in your own way. Because what
you are describing is me
almost getting in my way
to a point where I didn't do any of this stuff.
Don't get in your own way.
Got it. Now I'm worth over
a billion dollars.
I wish you luck though, Influx.
Thanks for sticking around. Really
interesting thought, though. I haven't thought about
that in a long time. Tar Alecran
thanks for the 250. Jerm, have you played Heaven's Vault
on stream? It's made
by the same crew that made Sorcerate. It's
an amazing adventure game in its own right. God
dammit, I'm going to like burp. Hold on.
Alright, we're good. I have not played Heaven's Vault?
I'll have to look into that
but ankle? I'll check it out.
For any weapon, thanks for the 250
forodian. Hey Jerma, just wanted to toss
some coin to my streamer,
Jerma Bald.
Hope you had a Merry Christmas. Hopefully I'll be able to catch you
live on New Year's Eve.
That stream will be starting probably around 6
o'clock Pacific.
9 p.m. Eastern.
We'll catch the Eastern ball drop.
And if there's
enough time, maybe we'll catch the Pacific one as well.
Maybe.
I was not with
Kim last
year on New Year's.
So I think I might want to
kind of end it after the Eastern
ball drop. Because
last year I didn't spend New Year's with Kim.
And
there's an opportunity too this year.
It'll be a solid
probably. We'll at least
get one or two of them.
Jerma loves his Eastern time zone viewers.
I mean I spent
my entire life on the Eastern time zone.
And everybody bases
pretty much everything on the Eastern time zone.
EST is
so much
media is
dictated by what time it is Eastern.
That being said, I do love
PST though, because I gain 3 hours.
I get 3 hours on
all of you. Right now it's 10 o'clock.
It used to be 1 a.m.
when I would turn the stream off back in
Massachusetts. It's 10 o'clock.
I can still get a pizza. But thank you
Frodeon.
We'll see.
Don't forget to vote for stuff yet.
Subscribe for more, plus like if you did.
Thank you, level 6.
Hey Reaper, thanks for the 250.
Hey Jerma, I was doing the survey for voting and went down
memory road for this year.
It's been a great year. When I got to the end
I wished that I could choose more than one
for best joke of the decade.
Keep up the good work and let's make
this decade as great as the last one.
Cheers to you and Happy New Year.
Happy New Year to you as well.
Yeah, just stay tuned for that show
on New Year's Eve.
It was the hardest choice on the list.
There were a lot of nominations.
It was actually hard to remove
some because there was just so many
in every category.
At least 10 of those categories were
full with 25
plus nominations. It was just
so many.
I'm glad there wasn't enough time
this year for people to at least have
that week to kind of think about something
that was fun rather than two days.
Yeah, it's been a great year.
A lot of stuff has changed for me
this year. You know, moved across the
country. Started to do the stuff
that I wanted to do many, many years
ago. Get into some more
high production, high
octave streams.
And I plan on just kind of keeping that
going for as long as I can, right?
Cheers to you. Thank you Reaper.
Dr. Cad,
thank you for the 500 bits.
I need you to watch a video just a little
bit. It's a music video, but I think you'll enjoy it.
Music video. What do you mean?
This video is 28 minutes long.
What the hell is this?
What?
What is going on?
No, this is like scary.
minutes long. I'm gonna get
gnomed. I might. I feel like
I'm gonna skip.
It's a pretty good video.
It's 30
minutes of that. I don't want to watch that.
That's a long time to sit there and
watch that. Yeah, there's the link.
It's right there. It's just a little
bit. It's a music video.
Hey Flustered Flamingo, thanks
for the 300 bits. Hey German, thanks for the laughs this decade.
Quick question. If you owned the internet
for one day, what would you change?
I would delete Twitter, Facebook,
Instagram, Snapchat,
TikTok.
I would delete all social media.
But not Twitch though, because that's cool. It's fun.
No, even Twitch. Even Twitch.
And YouTube. Delete it all. Get rid of it.
There would be instant replacements.
No, and I would have broadcasted on every
airway. Do I have control of the
airways? No, I don't. But even
just,
they'd instantly get replaced.
But even just for one
day, if
everybody didn't have to use
it, even for one day,
even for three days,
announce it on Twitter.
Hot boomer take.
That's a villain thing
to do. Is that a villain thing
to do though, really? Think about that.
We will rebuild it.
Facebook and TikTok? No. The
rest, yes. You're a Sunday morning
cartoon villain.
And then when Scooby-Doo
and crew stop
texting each other, and
they go play tetherball, and
then they go, whoa!
Maniacal Martin sure was actually
right, wasn't he?
We enjoyed some time outside.
Should we go get him out of jail?
Nah, nah, let him rot.
Oh, okay.
Boomer, hot boomer take.
No, if I had control of the internet,
no, okay, I wouldn't delete all social
media. I would take it all over.
And I would make one tweet and one
post on Facebook, on Twitter,
on Instagram, on TikTok. It would
just be, I'm only
writing this so people still don't think I'm
at TwitchCon-Germa.
Right, going live
tonight. Here's the
link. And try to
break Ninja's record
for like concurrent people on
a stream.
Everybody
come to this link and just be there.
So I can get like 700,000
concurrent viewers for 10 seconds.
By the way, do any musicians want to play
a video game? He'd still be
late. No, if I control the internet,
I don't know what the fuck I would do.
I'd get scared. No, but way
better. Yeah, I would take over all
social media. And what I would
simply do, this is the perfect
take on this whole scenario.
All I would do, I wouldn't
delete them. I wouldn't get rid of them.
I wouldn't take over and tweet something myself.
All social media platforms,
all text
would just be what happens when an
orc tries to talk to a human in Warcraft.
Done. Good luck.
You could be the only source of porn
on the planet. What are you
talking about?
Why would that be the thing I go to?
Anyways.
Thank you Flustered Flamingo for the 300
bits. Appreciate it. Gnarly
thanks for 250. I know I said that I couldn't donate
for a while, but I will gladly go into debt
to tell you, don't go into debt.
Don't go into debt to give me money. Don't do
that. Number one. Number two.
Let's see what you said.
Do not listen to the garbage that the Drew crew
spews.
She's not even a real detective. Nancy Drew, more like
Nancy fuck you.
Damn. That's harsh.
That's really harsh.
That's a pretty hot take, yeah?
Don't go into debt for giving me money.
Ever. For any reason. Keep that.
Bank it. But thank you for the
250 though. Drew Hater
is out. Hey Shmoo,
thanks for the 500 bits. Thank you Shmoo.
I've been a viewer since your first Surgeon
Simulator 2013 video. They're coming out
with a new one too. You helped me recently
get through an isolating period in my life.
I have to think about your advice on
persistence when things don't happen immediately.
Also the fact that you've never shit in a public
bathroom. You've got a lot of dedication
and that's inspiring as hell.
Yes, that is true.
That is still true. I
have never taken
a shit in a public bathroom.
It has never happened in my entire
life. Not once.
Never. That's not false.
I wish I could prove that somehow.
I've never taken a shit in a public bathroom.
That's fine. You don't have to believe me. I just
know it's true. I know it's true.
Someday you won't have a choice.
That day has not happened yet.
Now, I
don't count
private
bathrooms. So
yes, I have taken a shit in a private
bathroom. One where it's one person
you go and you can lock the door.
Right? Like what
do you classify as like a public bathroom?
Changing the definition. That
counts as a public bathroom. A
public space. Public private bathroom.
A private bathroom is
one not in your house.
More than one stall is a public bathroom.
Well, I guess a single
toilet with a locked door is technically
a bathroom for the public.
But it is a private
bathroom. It's a private bathroom
in public. Yeah.
No, it's not. It's a private bathroom
in... No, that's perfect.
If it's not in someone's house, it's a public bathroom.
Yeah. Okay. So I've taken a shit in a public
bathroom in a private setting.
Maybe once or twice. But I've
never taken a shit in a
multi-stall bathroom.
If literally anybody can walk in, it's public.
But I can lock the door. If I
go into a bathroom that's one
toilet, I can lock the door and
just exist and be alright.
So is that a public bathroom?
If you can't walk in
there, it's now my
temporary private bathroom.
A real public bathroom has a toilet with
encircling theater seats.
Holy shit. Why did I read that?
I never thought this much about the walls
I shit surrounded by.
Do you remember a public bathroom? It's public.
If you lock yourself in a
school gym, it's not a private space.
Yeah, but I'm not taking a shit.
The school gym is not
supposed to be a private setting.
Pulling my pants down and going to the bathroom
is a private setting.
It's a private place.
I'm not going to go to the bathroom in the gym.
It's open to the public, so it is
public. Yes. It's a public bathroom, but
it's a private section of the public
All right. Listen.
I've taken a shit in a public bathroom,
but never a multi-stall public bathroom.
There you go. Done. What's going on?
All bathrooms are private.
We can't sit here and argue
semantics. I've been trying
to for the last, like, five minutes.
Then you shit in a public bathroom.
Your semantics are bad.
What about that person that said all bathrooms
are private? A bathroom
is a private place.
This is the best
comment of the night. Who the fuck
cares? Yeah.
That's true.
That's right. Like, who the fuck cares?
Who cares if I've never taken a shit in a
multi-stall public bathroom?
You do. I do.
Hey, ButtSquire, thanks for the 250.
Seeing you react that way to germs on a
Wiimote reminded me of something.
What does it remind you of?
This is a full video. I'm going to watch this
full video. Have you peed your
pants? Yes.
Probably at least a dozen times.
I've peed my pants.
Yes.
I have peed my pants. Not in my
adult life. Maybe when I was like
nine, ten years old or something.
Hey,
very nice. Thanks for the 750.
Germa, listen to this. Three months ago I visited a museum
dedicated to Native American artifacts and memorabilia.
I eventually came upon a dark and
foreboding mask with crimson
feathers adorning it.
When I stared into its hollow eyes, it had something like
a spirit trip or a vision.
I saw everyone I knew and loved become great
bears, soaring eagles, and
trampling buffalo.
Then I woke up on a bench in the museum
and said, Bobby, have you ever had anything like that happen to you?
Don't do drugs before you go to a museum.
That's probably the moral of that
story. Say no, don't do drugs.
That was very well-written.
It was. You're right.
Can we get back to the game?
Oh.
New Basaurus,
the stream is over.
If you might be new,
then that's fine. I don't think you are though.
I think I've seen your name before.
At the end of the stream we do all
the donations that came in that
have reached a certain threshold.
We talk about stuff, we just chill out for
like 30, 40 minutes.
Sometimes less, sometimes more.
Just play the game. The stream is over.
This is the post stream wrap-up
hangout session.
It's been on this screen for six hours.
That would be bad.
Hey, Matty Eyes,
thanks for the 510
bits. Watching through the
old clips while I was voting for New Year's Eve stream was so
fun. Looking forward to plenty more fun times.
Wishing everyone a fun and safe New Year's.
Much love and may the New Year bring
great things. Let's hope so.
I hope so.
Thank you.
Snipers, thanks for the thousand bits.
Here are some bits for that pizza.
We'll be getting a nice thin crust
pepperoni pizza. Gonna just
slowly enjoy it
while I watch
surprise eggs videos.
Oh, can't wait.
Thank you for the thousand bits.
Very nice again. Thanks for the
250 bits you made. Me buy 250
more bits because you made so much sense
when you talked about the necessity of simplicity
in pizza. I was right there with
you. I felt you. I've been telling people that for about
five years now, but no one listens to me.
Maybe they'll listen to the greatest internet entertainer
alive. German985.
Hey, if you like
whatever pizza you like, you like it.
That's you donating to yourself.
The rock.
Wrong pizza opinion.
Pepperoni is greasy as fuck.
I like pepperoni on pizza.
It adds like a nice delicious smoky
flavor. Especially when
the pepperonis are
really crispy. When you bite into
pepperoni, you get that pepperoni crunch
that's almost like candy pepperoni.
It's the best.
It's the best. And then when you get
sometimes when pepperoni,
not all pizza places do this, but
some of them do. When you have
pizza in the oven, right?
And there's pepperoni on it.
After a little while, the
little pepperoni discs
turn into these almost these little
bowls, right?
And inside the little cooked
pepperoni bowls
is a few droplets
of this delicious
magical
liquid.
And then when you bite into it and you get
the crunch of the little pepperoni bowl and
the sauce and the little oil,
it's called liquid fat.
Yeah. And that's good.
Just don't eat it every day.
That's fucking heinous.
No, it's not. What?
Do I like bacon crispy or soggy?
Crispy, crunchy, crispity,
crunchity. Don't give me any soggy
bacon. Gross.
Who likes soggy bacon?
Yeah, I don't. I don't see
why would soggy bacon
I wouldn't want to eat soggy bacon.
Crunchy pepperoni bowls are the best food in the world
don't change my mind. I'm not trying to. I'm agreeing
with you. Turkey bacon is also
awesome. That's true.
Hey, gray blob thanks for the thousand bits. The only pizza
topping is worth a damn are bacon and green pepper.
Bacon's alright in
small doses. I don't like it all over
the pizza, but if it's kind of
put out there, crushed up
gently. I don't like
green pepper on pizza. I like a simple
pizza. I like just cheese, pepperoni
like margarita style
pizzas. I like
just simple. Simple, simple, simple.
Gray blob thanks for the thousand bits.
Sucko,
sucko, me must
thanks for the 250. Hey, German, here's the protection
money. I know it's not the agreed amount, but please don't
kill me.
That's 250
bits. That's not
protection money. That's not protection
money. What are you talking about? I'm not
doing anything.
That's not enough.
I'm just saying
250 is not like
that's not protection money.
That's alright.
It's not.
If you walked up to me and said, hey, here's
$2.50, man, it's my protection
money. I'd be like, just fucking
go buy yourself like a pack of gum.
He's saying that. No, I'm
not saying that. Here's 250.
Don't kill me. No,
I'm not going to kill you over 250, dude.
That's not
what I'm saying. I'm not going to
$2.50, man.
I'm not going to die over
250.
Guys, there's no
crime movies that are ever made.
There's no mafia
movies that are ever made where the guy opens up a briefcase
and there's $2.50
in it for the big switch.
That would be a really shitty movie.
Do you take Bitcoin? I used to until nobody
did it. I used to have an Ethereum
address down in the description.
And over the course of seven
months, I think like
$4 of Ethereum came in.
I closed it. I'd never
told me, but I was like, I'm out
of here. No one's using this.
How much is that $4
worth now?
Probably less.
Probably a lot less.
Why are people spamming this video?
No, I'm not. I'm getting enough
pizza for God's sake.
Post your ETH address and I'll give you $100.
I don't even know what it is.
I don't even remember. Just
fuck my shit up.
That video is old news?
Yeah, that video is circulated like
a year and a half ago.
For the life of me, I can't find the no emotion stream.
I don't even know what it was. You know the
address? Well, don't send $100
to that address because I'm not even sure I can get into
that account. It was HotLavaNGU.
That's right.
That's true. Do you have an OnlyFans?
I don't know what that is.
Anyways, we're almost at the
end.
Gnarly thanks to the 250.
Oh yeah, I had a dream on Christmas Eve where I woke up at 6am
on Christmas morning to you streaming.
You were being recorded by a camera behind you.
You were playing League of Legends on a
tiny laptop. Hope your Christmas
went better than dream
Jerma's.
Alright, here comes the credits.
Here comes all the subs.
Thanks a lot guys.
See you tomorrow for No More Heroes. I'm going to get it to work somehow.
I will. I will figure it out.
Even if we have to play it on original hardware, I will.
We'll figure it out.
You didn't say it was better? Jerma had a bad...
No, my Christmas was fine. My Christmas is good.
I had a relaxing Christmas.
It was nice.
But, that's a weird dream.
Why would it be on a tiny laptop? You can't play games on a tiny laptop
unless it's
Candy Crush.
Why would you play Candy Crush in the first place?
There are only two places where you
play Candy Crush.
And one is
in the airplane
because it's on one of those
weird devices that has weird games on it.
Or sitting at the one...
Like sitting at Chili's.
Because it's on that little kiosk thing that's on the tables.
Otherwise there's no reason to play that game.
Should I do it? No.
Yeah, I'll do a Candy Crush stream.
No, I won't. Lie. Yes, I will.
What are my thoughts on acne videos?
I don't... What do you mean acne videos?
Videos about people's acne or videos about people
popping pimples?
Which, both of those, I'm going to say
I don't think I want to watch them.
Hey, Lula!
Lula, thanks for another 500 bits here.
My son is 10, but he's aware of
entertainment versus reality, so swears
aren't a big deal in our house.
He knows I'd kick his ass if he talked like you.
Oh my god!
But he's allowed to enjoy the show.
Believe it or not, your content is pretty wholesome, really.
If you think so.
As much as we fuck around,
I do try to just have...
I try to stay... I try to have fun.
I don't ever want it to be
like a downer stream.
I know sometimes I can
fly off the handle, and then I can have
little episodes.
But for the most part, I like to just
have fun. And I don't want to
have fun in
mean, bad
ways, I guess.
Unless it's, you know, we're joking around with
channel stuff.
Let's put it this way, I never want anyone to feel
bad when they watch this stream.
Like, truly be like,
oh, I feel like shit watching this stream.
I don't like this. I don't...
I feel awful.
I don't want you to feel bad.
That's completely against why I
wanted to have fun.
You killed God, though.
Yeah, and like, that was a lot of fun.
You're a psycho.
I'm not... Look. Fine.
You can have your...
You can have your little... You can have your fun.
I'm not gonna clip that. That's fucked up.
What, are you guys trying to protect me now?
Should I be paying you protection money?
Alright, we're almost done. We're at the end.
We have...
But seriously, thanks for the subs, everybody.
There's a ton of you now.
Thanks for letting me continue to do this.
All of you. But thank you, Lula,
for the 500 bits. Thank you, Space Marine,
for the 1500 bits.
I just got out of my most difficult semester
that I've ever had in schooling.
I'm a chemical engineer junior
at a private university, so we've got a fucking
real smart one here.
We bring this up, but seriously,
chemical engineers in chat,
doctors,
lawyers, dentists.
This past semester has crushed me
academically, socially,
mentally.
You're one of the few people that can always make me smile and laugh
even when I have been beaten down.
I wanted to give back even a small amount
for the great things you've done for my happiness.
Thank you for being you. Turbo Heart.
Thanks a lot.
Hopefully your...
The hardest part of your schooling
is over.
And you can relax a little bit and it won't be as
bad the next time or when you graduate,
obviously, when you're getting close.
Thank you so much for the 1500 bits.
I wish you luck on your journey
of becoming a chemical engineer.
Thanks for watching. Thanks for sticking around.
Don't push yourself too hard.
Try...
Trump...Chump...
T...Trump...
Chump TTV.
Here we go.
Thanks for the 400 bits.
I work as a movie theater usher and have to clean up the movie theaters.
Every time you end the stream,
it reminds me of my job. So dirty.
Love the streams, big guy.
Thank you, Chump.
And maybe if some of you guys would pick up after yourselves
at throwing shit, dumping drinks on the ground.
Come on.
The Jerem Plexus Theater has been open
since 1981.
Okay?
I know that when you're walking it makes
that horrible sound.
But
that's because people are just throwing shit on the ground
and they're being disgusting.
When I go to the movies, I buy two drinks
and just dump one on the floor.
That's kind of what it feels like sometimes
in some of these theaters.
That people are just buying extra popcorn
so they can just dump it on the ground.
It's like somebody goes into the movie theater
and they buy a bunch of those...
They buy like
two boxes of dots
and a lighter
and they just slowly melt down
all the dots in the
container.
They just slide out and smear the dot
candy sludge shit all over
the ground.
And all over the seats.
How does a floor even get like that?
What am I talking about? I'm talking about every movie theater.
That's not even true.
Movie theaters nowadays, a lot of them are
really nice.
Reclining chairs.
Room service.
Have you heard about this?
You can get room service to your chair
in some theaters now. You press a button
and a flight attendant comes down and is like,
Oh, what do you want? I'll take the
ham and cheese and...
That's crazy.
That's $15 a ticket.
Here's the thing. I don't think I'd want to do that.
Imagine ordering a
full dinner at a movie. You're like
watching the movie. Your ticket bites out of like
an avocado BLT
melt turkey sandwich and like it's
getting all over you and you like wipe it with fucking napkins
and what happened on the screen?
Like you're eating like a full spaghetti
and you're like, Oh, hold on. I'm like eating
a full dinner and it's dark.
It's pitch black in there.
They have little tables. Yeah, but I don't want to eat in the dark.
There are some things you can eat in the dark.
Popcorn, pretzel bites,
corn chips,
and those little hot dog bites.
Get a whole lobster.
Alright, let's get out of here.
Al Store, H2O, thanks for the 250.
Speaking of you in college, you've been approached by your college
to come speak to students.
No.
No, not even close.
Hey guys, welcome to the graduating
class of
2024.
And the man given the speech today to
congratulate you all is one of our
alma mater. You might have
absolutely no fucking idea who this guy is.
He got popular by playing
Team Fortress 2 and saying the word
Shpee over and over again.
And by getting his ass kicked
by one of his close friends
who would get him to a point where he'd get
so angry that he would start screaming the F word
and he was recorded
without his knowledge and uploaded to
YouTube. Here he is, ladies and gentlemen, that's where he got his
star, German985. And like three
people in the audience would be like
and I'd have a wicked red face.
Hey, everybody.
Oh, I don't feel so good.
I'm nervous. Hey, everybody.
Keep asking.
It's cool. Keep at it, everybody.
We're going to get out of here.
Congratulations, everybody.
Fuchs? No. No, to answer your
question, nobody knows who the fuck I am.
Outside of, you know,
this space. I don't think there's
very many people there. You also mentioned
granted my own college hasn't asked Logan
Paul to come speak, but I can see colleges
thinking it's something students would be interested in.
Would they?
No, you want somebody at your college
speech to be somebody that can
tell you, you need like a
president or something.
Like a senator.
I can't make that speech.
I came back to the stream to hear that.
I'm sorry. How bad
was that? Was that bad?
It wasn't that bad, was it?
Sorry. What do you mean sorry?
It was pretty bad?
Thank you to
Cheezance for the
400 bits. 2019 was a bad year
for me, but your laugh brings me life. Thanks.
Gotta go. My goddamn
cat just puked. I'm sorry
to hear that. Hopefully your cat's alright.
What size shoe are you? 14.
I'll see you guys tomorrow. Have a fantastic
rest of your night. Thanks for sticking around
for the end of the Nancy Drew
the Sea of Mystery.
Make sure you vote.
You only have three days to do so.
You have until
you have until 12pm
Pacific time
on the 31st.
That's when the poll is no longer going to be accepting
any votes.
I'll be talking about this for the next three days straight.
I will make a...what are you voting
for? The worst stuff this
channel's done in the whole year and some of the best
stuff the channel's done over the year.
There are a lot of categories.
I actually...we got best
auto appearances on there too.
And yes, if you were curious, I
think it was just every time auto
appeared on the stream in
2019.
Have a wonderful rest of your night. See you guys tomorrow.
Take care guys.