Hey, what is going on everybody? Jerma here with a Team Fortress 2 gameplay commentary, and tonight, gonna be playing as the Demoman.
Two different setups, I have two gameplays back to back. Well, not really gameplays, but kind of clips of using the lock and load, and then of course using the default as you're seeing on the screen right now.
The default grenade launcher, that is.
And while that plays out in the background, I want to talk about 200 uploads to YouTube.
I can't believe I'm actually saying that, guys. It's crazy. And I kind of want to get Burger Boy's opinion on this.
So yeah, it's very exciting, as you can tell. I never thought I would ever do something like this, guys. Never thought I would upload over 200 times.
Because I do have some unlisted videos that were kind of pointless that I took down, but for the most part, this is my 200th actual video.
So I figured for the 200th upload, I wanted to tell a story. And I want to tell a very, very important story, and it kind of ties into the motivation and the goal setting video I made a while back.
And it has to do with doing something, and actually doing it, and actually going hard on something. And I get this in PMs a lot, and half the time, it doesn't even have to do with YouTube.
Half the time, it has to do with life situations, or you're trying to get a job that you really want.
And I am so flattered, guys, that you come to me for this type of advice. It is so humbling, and it is so mind-boggling, and it's something I've been taking in the last few months.
But I want to give you guys a story about me, and how I kind of got to this position where I am.
So let's first start off by saying that I am the biggest procrastinator in the world, my entire life.
I have never done a job pretty much to its potential. Every time I've had something to do, it doesn't matter what it was.
If you told me to mow the lawn when I was younger, or you told me to do well on my schoolwork, or anything, I always just did something.
Just, okay, yeah, I did it. Like, I'm doing it. Here, I did it. I mowed the lawn. See, I did my homework. It might have sucked.
I might have done a terrible job on it, but I at least did it, and that's my entire life.
And the crazy thing is even stuff that I wanted to do. I wanted to be a filmmaker, guys. I think I've talked about this in previous videos.
I wanted to be a film director. I wanted to make the biggest Hollywood movies in the world. I wanted George Clooney in my movies.
You know, it was going to be so awesome. But I never did anything. I never ever tried. You know, I pretended to try.
I said, oh, I'll work as a PA on a movie set, or I'll go do this, or I'll go talk to some actor that I know.
I never actually really tried to do it. The effort was never really there. And I think that's a problem that a lot of people have.
And if I could give you any advice as to doing something, it's just you have to put a ton of effort into something.
If you know you can do it, and you know truly in your heart, I can be a doctor, or I can be a singer, or I can be a writer, or even YouTube.
You have to really try. You have to put every ounce of your being into it. And you can't lie to yourself. You can't pretend to yourself.
And that's what I was doing for so damn long. I was just lying to myself about what I was doing.
And that transitions to this whole YouTube thing, and the 200 uploads, and to why I'm so shocked, and why I'm so happy, and why I'm so appreciative of all you guys.
It's because I've uploaded 200 times. I can't even imagine doing that. Like three years ago, the me from three years ago, or two years ago.
I wouldn't have even uploaded 10 times. I had an old YouTube channel. I had a YouTube channel with like 14 videos on it.
Nothing to do with gaming, and that channel is now closed, so you can't really go find it.
But I had an old YouTube channel, and I never really used it for anything.
And now that I really started to really put all this effort into this channel, and uploading 200 times in the last year.
It's not even been a full year. I sit back and I go, did I really have this in me the whole time?
And the answer is yes. Everybody does. Everybody has it in them. You have it in you. You can actually do it.
You just have to tell yourself it's possible, and you have to act on those possibilities.
Do not do what I did until I was 26 years old. And that is procrastinate, and talk about it, but never actually really put true effort into it.
I did this for years, guys. I did this for five, six, seven years. And now finally I'm starting to do something, and really enjoy it, and put effort into it.
And I can tell you right now, guys, I'd say exactly one or two years ago, I was probably at as rock bottom as you can get.
I was very, very depressed. I had a lot of problems. Not really problems, but I just didn't see what I was doing with myself.
I was like, what the hell am I doing? What am I doing? Where am I going? What am I going to do? I'm 25. I need to do something.
And finally I started to actually do it, and my life has improved immensely, and my outlook on life has improved immensely as well.
And it really is all because of effort. And I think that's the quintessential thing that you have to remember, is effort and progress go in the same sentence.
So that's going to wrap up this video, guys. Thank you all so much for watching. I really do appreciate it.
And let's shoot for 200 more, 300 more, 500 more, a thousand more. I'm going to keep doing this for as long as I possibly can.
And hopefully a lot of you guys are still here in the end. So I will catch you guys all soon, and take care, everybody.