Yes, so take some wine please. Someone's buzzing my apartment. I might go see who it is.
That's a good berry wine. Who is it? Hey! Hey! It's my good friend MLC Sterls. Come on in.
I've got some fresh wine for you. See it's right here. It's a Cabernet from the year 1444.
This is your Christopher Columbus sail to sea. Do you know that? I love Cabernet. Yes, yes it's good.
Take some please. Please have some. Please have some please. Ah yes. Now you. Let's have some more
wine. Let's have some more wine. Oh yes. Oh yes. Yes. Oh yes. What's this? Is it wine? I haven't had
this in so long. It's been at least five seconds since my last glass. My screen is shaking.
There is a dude behind us. We better get going. He's behind us. Maybe there's a dude behind us.
He's coming. There's a guy behind us. Maybe he's just gonna get in the car. He's gonna get in the
car. Is he just gonna get in? There's not enough space in the car. He's gonna shoot us. It's a two
door. We better leave. No, it's a two door. He's kicking the door. Hey, cut it out. He has a knife.
Put the knife down. There's no reason for this. Look, let me get out and I'll like just listen.
I know I have your insurance. My insurance. We'll work things out. We'll exchange papers.
I'll send it to you tomorrow. Take us up to the top of this fucking mountain. This looks really
stupid. Why? I'm in first person just behind you and it looks like it looks like one of those old
80s movies where you're in front of like a green screen and you're like apparently driving right
now. Oh wow, look out. This looks really great on my fucking green screen. This looks so stupid.
I'm just like eating. Oh my god, that is 90 degrees. That was 90 degrees. Yeah,
I don't think I'll be able to get down the whole mountain. You're gonna try to get down the whole
mountain like that. Sure. Oh no. Speaking of going down the whole mountain. Oh no.
This is a terrible place to do this. I don't know why I keep trying to do that.
It's not gonna happen. Okay, see ya. See ya. Oh I'm alive.
And here's the mountain. Push me. All my lights, bro. Push me. Push me. I need a push.
Push me, mummy. Push me, mummy. Thank you for the boost. Oh no, you're fine. You fucking idiot.
My bike. You need to land this plane and the nose has to be directly in front of me just like that
movie Supergun with Thomas Cruise. I'm going really fast. You are going like kind of fast,
but it's okay. You'll get it. Yeah, you did it. Can you take a selfie? No, I just have it like
zoomed in on your face. Oh no. Oh no. That's great. That's good. That's great.
Your guy's face is as if nothing is happening.
He is like, I've got a big deal. I'm just driving. Well, oh well. Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait,
hold on, hold on, hold on, hold on a second. Don't move. Do not move. I can't move.
Hold on. Don't, don't, don't, don't. I want to get like a first person look at you.
I want to like take a picture of you. I'm rocking out to the music. What are you doing? Yeah,
you're rocking out to the music. What a sick fuck. It's scary on my wayward son. Your character is
a psycho. How beautiful of a sight is this? Hey, I just love sitting here parked looking outside
of the wonderful islands and all the other great stuff in this wonderful world. Oh my gosh. This
game is so fun just to drive over mountains, the fly. All right. Caps coming. All right. Well,
I got us a cab. Do we both get in the cab? Um, I don't know. Well, don't get in it yet.
Okay. Um, hi. That's not a cab. That's not a cab at all. That's a, uh,
what kind of cab company sends a fucking chopper and shoots you.
This bottle is from Thomas Jefferson, circa 17 BC. Let's get, oh yeah, that's got some aroma to it.
Oh yes, that's got a very nice little flavor to it. Kind of reminds me of poison.