I'm gonna find Poseidon and kill him, apparently, and I've taken my boat over to this area. We'll see what's over here.
Who sets foot upon the sacred isle of horses?
Lord Poseidon preserves his favorite creations from the ruination of the world.
To trespass here is to call down the fury of the master of steeds on both land and sea.
Okay, uh,
This guy sounds kind of like a wuss if you don't mind. Whoa, shit. He's attacking me.
I didn't think it was gonna happen that quickly. Get him!
Yeah, you wuss.
Whoa, he's running away. He's running away.
Pulling out my bow.
I'm gonna shoot this motherfucker. Get me on this, get me on this goat.
Come here, you fucking master of steeds.
I'll kill you.
So I do want to pop in here for like two seconds and explain sort of what's going on here post commentary.
I'll cut back to the live session here in a second, and it's gonna be a very quick video.
I just wanted to show that yes, that is me. I am the horse lord in apotheon.
It was a ton of fun to do the voice for this guy, even though it's not very big.
It's just a boss battle. It's just a little thing that you run into when you go towards Poseidon's area.
If you have the game, maybe you already knew this. Maybe you were like, wait, is that fucking, is that actually him?
And yes, the answer is yes.
And if you're interested in more voice stuff that I've been doing recently, if you're curious at all,
the link in the description is gonna go to an animation that I was in this last couple months.
And it's not like a Cartoon Network or like Nickelodeon or something like that.
It's just a flash animation that I was happened to be a part of and it's in the description if you want to check it out.
It's there. Ow, my finger. I just bumped it. Ouchies. And that's gonna end this awkward post commentary that I've cut into a live video.
I don't know why I decided to do this, but I wanted to give some context and that's pretty much it. Enjoy the live
parts and bits of this video guys, and I'll see you all next time. Take care everybody.
And let's see who wins the battle of Poseidon's horse lord versus the Parthian guy. I forgot his...
I have to kill him on foot now? That's not good.
I'm just gonna throw fire at him.
Great acting. Good acting job you did there, sir. Whoever you are.
I'm gonna die. I really think I'm gonna die here. Uh, do I have any? What is this? I don't even know what this is.
I'm gonna drink it.
God, I'm gonna die. Maybe not. Can I craft anything?
I can't even craft any fucking healing shit.
Dammit.
Dodge, dodge, dodge. I can't get killed by me.
As me. That doesn't work that way. He only has like 30 percent, 20 percent. I should be able to get him.
Throw some axes at him. Blast arrows. We'll go with these. Oh, another, another steed.
Give me the steed. I don't even care about this guy.
Let's move.
All right.
Ooh, they explode. These arrows explode. Isn't that just nice?
I don't want to waste these. I have 22 of them actually. That's not terrible.
Whoa. Whoa.
Shoot him. Please hit him.
Oh my goodness.
Now my horse is dead again.
I'm just gonna spam these arrows over here. I don't even know if they're gonna hit him or not.
Controlling shit in this game can be difficult.
There's some regenting my health.
Get back to the spear.
The farmer's pick. Whatever the hell this is.
Fuck. No.
Don't kill me.
The hell. He's getting so close.
I still haven't picked up any nectar or anything. Is there any in my boat?
There might be like one on my boat and I still I didn't. Oh, I, I nice. I, I can, I can craft one.
Eat it.
Get these pieces of crap out of here.
My beef is not with you.
It's with the lord of horses.
There he is.
A couple more hits. A couple more hits.
Ah.
No.
Shoot it.
Fuck.
I'm gonna come for you. You don't have very much health left.
One more little tap.
I've done this like four times now. I gotta kill me.
I got you, me.
Fuck you.
Fuck me.
Fuck us both.