I'm changing the title. All right, let's play Dusk. I got it right here. Go back to sniper. Get out of here.
It was an interesting idea
I would just would have liked to go to other games the other levels instead of just playing on the same one for like
One to two straight hours
All right dusk ain't coming
There it is loading tunes. This may take a while
Headphones recommended. I got them in
All right. Why is this taking a while?
Music in the game is amazing. Okay
Campaign endless save load. Let's go to settings. Oh, that's loud. Look feel
Look nice to have a 1080 full screen v-sync off weapon size drop that a little bit
I don't like having huge ass weapons on the screen. I'm actually that's really cool about that 120 is my frame rate
Field of view 110. That's a little too much. That's puke inducing. Let's stay at like about 100
color palette
Default, what are the other ones vivid? Hold on
not sepia
vivid
Strelok
hold
fury dragon
No, just default
customize crosshair
style
Now this is loud. I need to go back
sound
Okay. Look we'll go to crosshair. I want style. Let's see. What's the best crosshair for me?
It's got to be a little one little circle
small circle
No, not that small except actually maybe no the little like one of this one right here
Scale a little small little grit there red tint
green tint
opacity bright
Okay, that looks good to me
uh
Advanced display settings. Uh, well everything's off for some reason lens flare off gross
pixelization
Oh
off
Off. I want to be able to see the hell i'm doing
low spec mode retro palette
bloom off
By when you're filtering turn it on I guess a little chunky
All right, i'll do a little chunky. I want it to I want it to be a little brighter, too
i'm doing vivid
vivid or
What's clown vomit? Oh, I think I like vivid
sound feel
Difficulty accessible go easy. I can take it
uh
Sarah mio dough or duskmare. How about how I can tell I can take it weapons sway off
Camera animations, I on I guess vertical flipping. I don't know what the fuck that means water control style know what that means
input settings toggle crouch on always run
On look sensitivity drop that by a lot
Auto aim amount just turn it off. Enable controller off auto switch weapons on
I don't know what this means
customized bindings
Crossbow alpha six what the hell is
Forward back left right jump space crouch left control walk a shift fire mouse one zoom mouse one. Okay flashlight f flip
use
Okay
holsters h
quick melee mouse two toggle stats
Center view record time quick save is at six quick load at nine. Got it. Okay, let's just go
All right, let's go campaign i'm ready
new episode
the foothills
I can take it. What is intruder mode?
I've taken turn off the filtering
Is that bad? Should I not have it on?
Let's see. I'll give it a minute
kill the intruder
Do I have a gun this was moving really fast kind of hurts my head
Press f for flashlight f
e interact lift box
Oops boy, is it gone? No
What's that?
Pistol bullets. How do I I only have sickle
Turn off somebody's to turn this off
When I can customize this way way way way way way way go back to normal. Okay, hold on
Turn off the filtering
Oh that actually does look kind of like bad
All right. Uh, wait a minute
brightness
up
Saturation down a little contrast down
brightness up
hue
That's okay. Maybe a little bit more brightness like right here
Drop the saturation and drop the contrast. I think that's okay for me
No, all right. I wish whatever health 174. All right, let's go
How do I get weapons?
What the fuck how do you get weapon
I can block those
What's this? Ooh pistol, okay, how do I aim?
Oh, all right. Nice
Oh
How much I get 56 bullets is it does it reload or does it just you have 56 shots?
Something below is calling us
Is it headshots in this game?
No flick. Oh shit. I'm surprised. I found that so quickly. All right. Hold on. What's up here?
Sacrifice
Oh shotgun
Oh shit
This is loud as it's very loud hold on toilet flush toilet secret
Lip barrel
Oh, they explode
I have a lot of shotgun shots. This is miss secret. Get the secret room
Get the secret you want me to the first time i've ever even played this video game go get secret
I I can't even go back guys
In the game where you sprint a hundred miles per hour and enemies are all over the place
Why didn't you get the secret room?
There you can all calm down now. Everybody can hold you here. Everybody can relax
Which way
I should probably hold this. Yeah, i'm gonna hold on to that more double shotgun. Okay, that's cool
Cool
What did I just do?
Did I open another door or something? I don't know. Let's go this way. I could go up flick both switches. No
Let's just go back up
Something up here
Double pistol now
Should I break every barrel?
All right, i'm good cool, I got the secret
Let's move, uh, wait, that is the right way, isn't it? Yeah press e on beer
How about I sneeze first?
Uh
Do I have to go back in this house?
Is there a door
Uh
Did I miss something back here? I guess I did crouch while moving to slide
cool
Oh
Total kills 24 secrets one out of six only one out of six
I can't believe this
Imbasile can't even get two secrets
Prepare thyself presented into the horror
Down on the farm. Let's move
What do I have a super move
All right, cool, what do we got I almost almost out of bullets bad guy that's an enemy, right
Shit got hurt. That's the first time i've been hitting the whole game
gas can
You're wasting bullets posting no trespassing
Use more sickle, but
Only in bullets and they get this gun i'm fine
Gas can oh another shotgun. Oh fuck
Just jump the whole thing
All right. I got I got money
Don't go up there
Manga s don't go up there
Don't do it. Don't do it. All right, i'm gonna here's the plan. I'm gonna throw this right into the window up here
Well, I missed
Can I go in what is that up there a carrot i gotta get that
Whoa, it's a baseball bat drink. Whoa
All right, this helps everywhere though
That just went to bed
Fuck I thought there was probably something in there. Whatever. I'm scared to go in here
Is poisonous a gold coin more what does morale do
It's an armor. Oh, okay cool
Did I get everything in here? I think it did I want to go out the window though and jump
All right, cool, I guess i'm just gonna keep going I want to get out that window though
Try to get up there. I don't think I can I knock it up there. Well, this thing doesn't hurt you
I thought that thing hurt you
Diamond there we go diamond now i'm gonna get from here over there
Okay, cool. Now let's go
Sinner wait nothing else. Let's move. This is make sure i'm loaded
Oh, I didn't know you were there
I knew it. I knew it. I knew it. I knew it was gonna happen. Fuck. That was actually kind of scary
I need the red key to open this
Well, that sucks. Oh the music's getting higher
That's a lot of people over there
That's a lot of people
Nice strafing. Thanks, dude
What's that? You found the hallowed health 166
I'm a strafe master. God damn it
Holy shit
Does distance matter?
If I it doesn't matter for how far away I am
Because well, I do more damage if i'm closer or
hammer
Yes, okay. I just want to make sure some some video games like this don't doesn't matter. What's this do?
secret door opened
Where somewhere else? Okay. Well, I got the key
Is this like experience or something?
Magic notes. I know it's a health increase. I see
I'm gonna get spawned on or something. Aren't I?
What about the secret door?
All right. Let me go back here. Is there a secret door?
Not really
In the house
I don't see a door here
Can I not pick what? Okay. What are those? Why can I pick that up?
Oh already what's the secret? Oh, you can't have over 100 morale. Okay, cool
Um, what about back here?
I guess it wouldn't be a secret if it just you knew where it was. Can I get on the building?
secret secret
secret
Shoot this
Wait, that looked that does look like a door
Secret that's not that's not the right secret. That's not a door
This is pretty cool though
I'm just gonna go I could find it another time
Wait, let's hold on if I jump and I see where i'm going
Hold on what about over here?
There's like a shed over there. No, i've already been there. All right. We'll forget it. Wait
I missed
I'm so paranoid about losing secrets
Oh, whatever. Let's go
Do it. I know you're gonna do it do it. What else we got?
One enemy left one out of six. Yeah
Yeah
old time religion
This way i'm gonna save the shot. I have tons i'm using too many shotguns. It's too easy to use the shotgun
secret
He found the yellow key secret key
There's gonna be a way down in one of these
What's that minecraft?
102 I thought I couldn't go over one. Oh
Buried with his favorite video game
Weird look at this is a secret. I'm gonna be okay. Remember that building
Do you get more points for killing him with a melee blue I need the yellow key
I hear something. All right, this chainsaw guy's over here. All right. Well, they get they've lulled me up with shotguns. So let's go
Book and uh, bring it somewhere. I don't know
It's probably a secret with that
I'm gonna put this back on like a little podium or something, right?
This is kind of a long fall
Throw the bible
There's no loot lift baits
All right, what do we got behind this door?
That's a new weapon machine gun pretty good it's not bad I hear people walking
Oh my god the shotguns
Nothing over here no secrets. Fuck
I took a lot of hits there that I didn't want to take red key loot just health. I already have plenty of health
so
All right red key blue key
Jump while sprinting. Uh, i'm not i'm not smart enough to bunny hop. It's been proven time and time again
Does that
Plus when I bunny hop it I go too fast and my brain is like a full second behind
So I can't play as good
Hurry up
What was that?
Yeah, if I bunny hop if I go like insanely fast I can't even process the images on the screen
All right, I got yellow
That's the yellow key is for the no that I have the red. Do I have the red key now?
What the fuck is going on?
All right, that was kind of fucked up. All right, let's go. Where is he? Where is he? Where is he?
Which way let's go this one not like it matters
Oh
Give me back down. Put me back down. Put me back down
No, put me back down. I
Okay, oh
That was that hurt my head
Anything in here that I need?
Now I have blue
Yellow blue and red which there's another door over here. Wasn't there?
Move health good if we just go down again
That morale
Didn't I do this already?
Wait, I already did this
You got the key. Oh
That's true
We tried god for we traded god for demons
The scourges of olden times
I think under the bridge. Yep
Take them up
Uh-oh, where is he? Oh god key
We
Hallowed health and a super morale
Blessed rng what do you mean? Bless rng? I only have two shots left in the shotgun. Not good. And um, i'm gonna use the pistols for a little
bit
That's a boss
What did that do press the button?
What am I doing cool this boss is in this game
quaff
Uh-oh, you can actually you get drunk. What does intoxicated do?
Besides hurt my head
All right. I'm good
All right, that's good
I don't think I got any secrets
Bump up the difficulty
I think it's in a good spot
I'm on I can take it
Can you though? I mean we'll find out
Fuck
I just took so much damage for no reason you're destroying on this difficulty so far
Uh, what do you think I should bump it up?
To one more am I doing am I doing too well?
You haven't died yet
so
You're talking like that's some kind of bad thing
Um, I don't can I even change the difficulty here? I can't
No
Sorry guys. I'm on like just the standard
Why is the soap so good
Just save ammo
Oh, is that a rifle? I like the look at that thing
You got a super shotgun, oh double barrel nice
That's pretty cool. All right, got the yellow key here
Doing too well, am I doing too well?
I don't think I got
You need one more difficulty and it'll be perfect
Really?
You think so?
We want you to rage
Is that what you want? You want me you want me to put it on the?
What's that? I don't know but give me this
Put it on the i'm not gonna do the hardest difficulty that's just
This is the first time i'm gonna be playing. I need to like just see where i'm at
Oh, that's like a oh damn
Oh one shot if you get real close cool. All right, i'll make it harder. Fine. Now the next
Is that acid?
Are they burning me?
Oh down there shit
You're gonna suffer if you do that
Oh, well, i'm willing to give it a try
The portal's work he is pleased
He is pleased
You won't you're doing as well. Okay
I think you guys all thought I was gonna just do this
What the fuck?
How the what's I don't fucking understand this is it's to I have to move that
This is fucking stupid. That's what you thought was gonna happen, isn't it?
And now you're upset that this guy is just holy shit look at his movement
Look at his skill. Look at how he's fucking moving around. I've never seen him like this before
I've never seen anything like this before
And I watch some of the top players in the world
Oh, I don't even
You guys forget there's one thing that I do well
and that's
Just fucking beat sakira. You know what I mean?
If you give me a game where it just don't just shoot things hit things and don't get hit
I might I might do pretty well. You forget this
I mean I and speaking of forgetting I forget I have a yellow key now
And by the way, this is not on the easiest difficulty
I've seen like this is on the third difficulty
Oh fuck
sourceful, too
Turn difficulty difficulty. No. No. All right. I all right. I'll put I'll put it up one more
fine
I got a raid lazy purple. Thanks for the raid dude. Welcome everybody from lazy purple scream
Thanks a lot, dude
Okay. So if I can I go back to the menu?
So this is sawdust, right?
Can I leave?
What happens if I quit this?
Can I come back to where I am right now?
Save the game
Okay, the game is saved
So quick game
Yeah, I can't look difficulties in the settings, but I can't change it. I don't think
Oh, I can okay
All right, so this I can take it. Uh, we're gonna go to zero meado
All right. Here you go
Here you go
Everybody can chill now. He's he's playing on a hard the hard one
All right. So I I I think it's they just move way faster
I've been playing this game for like 40 minutes
With them moving in a different way, so it's gonna take a minute to get used to
Let's go that way. He's too fast. He's too fast
All right, i'm gonna run out of bullets
Somebody in the chat earlier said stop stop shooting man. Don't shoot those
Oh, I feel what you're saying
You're reloading okay, what what color was the key that I just got purple
Okay, let's keep going over here
Okay, i'm trying to be
trying to be
I was trying to just like make everybody go like oh wow. You know what I mean?
I was just being I was being a dick. I'm not gonna lie. It was being a dick
All right, give me ammo
Okay, yeah this way this way this way
It's difficulties back. What are you talking about?
Can't get one by you
How do I get on the train?
Do I have to put the boxes up to get on the train?
Wait, hold on. There's a quicksave right f6
Good. All right. I just need to ammo
I need okay yellow key. It's back here. Good to know wait. What about down here?
Something else. Yep
coins
Hold on to these bullets
They call them hit him with every shot
albertson
I need a yellow key
What was that? What was that behind me?
Someone's shooting from up top
Yep, it's you
bastard
What we got health?
Not good actually
But not bad
Red door over here
Okay. Shit. Where's that key again?
Oh fuck I didn't realize it was already selected
Get there. Okay. I should have listened to that guy
I was too confident and that guy was like dude, you shouldn't be doing don't use your shotgun
I'm like, what do you know? What do you do? I really don't know anything. I know everything
There's ammo over here and there's the yellow key
Don't tell them
I mean don't tell them
I can't even I cannot pay attention to what you guys are doing. Oh up here press right to zoom
zoom
Holy shit
What the fuck?
It said zoom in I gave me a zoom in. Oh, did I last time I saved is up here. God damn it
No
No, I say I gotta okay. I gotta rebind that
I'm rebinding that to middle mouse button. Okay. Hold on. Where's my uh, customized bindings?
See, where's okay quick save
middle mouse
Good all right. I'm ready the dev tweeted out the stream. Oh, that's awesome. Thanks a lot
This game is fun
Whoa, I don't want to get it. Did it save the uh, it did
Okay, i'm ready
Can't believe I died there. That was too fun
All right. I gotta be ready
there's uh
big all right
All right. Stop
Holy shit just dodged. All right. We're good. Uh, oh, I think I pressed. Yeah. Did I press the button?
I did I pressed my
Bpi button
All right. Let me take out the there's still a couple more of those guys left
Why do I do that red key do I have the red key wait read the tweet?
What is the tweet?
What does it say?
Don't read it. Don't read it. Don't read it. You can't oh, all right. All right. I'm I won't read it
Should I know don't read it?
I don't know what the tweet says
The tweet could say like this guy sucks
The tweet could actually read I hate this streamer. He's the worst don't support him ever. I don't know
Oh fuck don't die here, okay, I forgot about that dude
I gotta get up there
Red key got it
No, I won't read the tweet. Okay. All right. This is the part save it
This is the part where I fucked it up last time. Okay sniper rifle, but why use the sniper rifle here? Should I use it?
Are they gonna come up here do they come up here?
All right, we're good
Chat you baited you wait, this is not real. No, so none of that was real. Well, whatever that's okay
All right. I got red key. Let's go to red door
Eat that hash
Can I make this jump?
No, all right red door. Let's go
Where was it? I don't remember
Why?
It's a waste I should have done that save that for the boss
Shit, that's a lot of people. That's a lot
Read it don't read it. I'm not gonna read it. Should I not read it?
Should I?
Read it
Don't read it. What are those globs?
These are super gems
Crystal of madness
Should I breathe this in as deep as I can?
All right, I got the yellow key
Read it eat the raspberries. Don't eat the raspberries
Should I bring this with me?
Just read it. Holy shit. The mod said read it
Did the mod say read it?
Oh, okay. I've read it
Don't tell him about okay. I saw it
Well now I know why did you guys tell me to do that?
Now I know what's a boss in the game. How I can't believe you did this to me
All right, need a yellow door. Where was it somewhere over here? I think it was down here. Wait
There's a letter
Let's go read the other tweet the other mod tweeted and what what?
What's with all?
All right
I'm going
Read all tweets
What is this a tweet reading stream or is this me playing dusk and playing like at an 88 out of 100?
All right, here we go
They weren't human no, they were not
All right, retweet retweet retweet check out the tweet I got a couple of tweets for you
I hate durama 95. He's the worst don't support him ever
Oh, well, we we all have opinions we can have them that's all right. All right, we're in the mine kill him
What just happened?
Do I not have any? Oh, I don't have any bullets in it. Okay. I have pistols only
I can't I guess
Okay
Okay, can can I talk uh, can I
No talking these things gotta get close
Diamond the track door opens
so did you the the devs that are watching I know could you guys do you think you could have ever put in a like a
minus 50 speed on everything mode
What is that as a ghost here?
What does the ghost do is this like bubble bobble if I'm taking too long
Yellow key, what is that?
Two three shots with this point blank double barrel shotgun
Damn, could you guys just give me a separate like client?
That was
You know, maybe like two times less difficult and but just don't I I have it on the hardest difficulty
But you guys have coded a special copy for me so I can pretend to be fucking awesome at this game
Totally he already is we don't even need it. Dohly dohly this is intense, but it doesn't feel
And it doesn't never feels unfair even on the second hardest difficulty in the game
I feel like i'm in control
Does that make any sense?
Sad
Oh my fucking i'm dead i'm not almost if I didn't miss that first shot I would have been dead. All right. Hold on
What does that mean?
What does that mean? Oh god, damn it man. Holy shit
Oh
Is this the load is this the save?
Is the one that I just saved I think so, right?
Yes, it is
My god don't get stuck i'm stuck
i'm stuck
It don't matter. I can't get out. Oh my god. I can't get out. Oh my god
How did I live how did I live?
There's no way. Thanks a lot dev. I appreciate it for that like fucking extra copy of the game that you coded
When I get with this five enemies surrounding me, i'm always gonna get out
Okay
If I get touched i'm dead. I hear a fucking chainsaw guy
Those are the worst because now the difficulty went up. So they're 10 times faster. Which way is he?
There's a red key. Oh my god, just stay. Oh my god. He's right there
This is a preparation
Ah
Where you at where you at slow down i'm almost out of ammo what did that do? Well, I think
I killed all the enemies
Very cool. Let me make sure I save it dead of the night
And we're gonna do this. We're gonna go to sound we're gonna drop the master volume put the music up a little bit more
What are the subtitles for?
Red door gold coin bonus. That's a lot
That's a lot of people
Oh, it's already happening, okay, uh strategy pistols for a little while
I just walked into it
Like is that guy extra fast or something?
Damn, I got it
Okay
Let me continue
No time to stop I gotta move
Should I go down?
I found a secret
Yes. All right. What is it gonna give me?
uh
Where am I?
priceless diamond I get 50
Damn it
I just lost all that fucking all right. Hold on
Let me go back in there. There's another secret in there another way to go
How did I get there?
I don't remember how I got there
I'm serious another secret
That's two
All right blues back there
All right, 72 health save it right here
I I don't remember I forget
I'm sorry everybody
I can't get the other part of that secret. I have no idea what that was. I'm moving so fast
I don't know
Ah tiny little quarters
What's that breathing?
Holy shit. I thought I didn't die
There's too many rooms
All right one room at a time slow
That's the way to get out
Bookshed this bookcase is weird, right? This is a weird place for a book weird
Jesus, okay
All right, we're good crap I get that soap good call what's that I hear something
Oh my god
Oh
All right slow down
I got the blue key
That's so
Dude, the soap takes too much time
It does it's a great weapon, but damn it takes a long time to use
fireplace
eat
Eat glass eat glass
Oh who cares? I don't need it
What hold on easy?
You have to use a rifle what's the light in there from was it a crossbow?
Oh fucking god, they just no don't jesus
Was he throwing all those
No, all right. I give me that
Okay, give me the crossbow crossbow bolts will pass through enemies and walls
Really a lot of items
Oh my fucking jesus, what just happened?
Where did I just save it?
Right here. Thank god
Give me the crossbow
Fuck it. Let's go
Didn't spawn. Oh, yeah, they did
Oh and a guy with a shotgun it's all right
All right blue door
Power
What do we got health mana yeah, i'll get on these rubes bounce on the other side
Good. I need to get all the rubes
All right. Now, where's that secret?
It was one of the silos, right?
But then on the there is
All right. I went that way. Let's go up here
nice good
All right
I think i'm ready to move on i've got the blue key
Wait, nice
Okay, i'm in a good spot
shave it
Let's get out
And open up that blue door
Why am I talking funny?
bald
very funny
Got one whatever
Red key now
All right time to take out the big gun
I feel like i'm gonna get stomped on out here
I should have used the rifle. What am I thinking?
The rifle is instantaneous
Now we get in close with the super shotgun
Good red door guys watch out, but I knew you were gonna be in here
And your friend
There's another one
Oh, there's one of you
Did I miss
No, just throw it throw the gas
Throw the gas. I can't even pick it up
Ow rub lotion on skin
Well, I don't know there could be something down here
No hose for me
Trinkets nice trinkets left to right. Uh, let's go up
Oh, man, there's a lot of those guys. Oh shoot through them
Oh
You're not making this easy. Are you?
How did you miss that?
All right, let me open the actual stuff here for a minute
Oh my god
I'm trying to conserve i'm trying to conserve
Sanctum of the worthy not there yet. Not going in there
Nothing else for me to grab
I already got all the max. All right
Maximum that we're good. Okay
There we go sanctum of the worthy get out my shotgun. That's my favorite weapon
This is absolutely a boss fight. Why would they be this much stuff?
Ooh
What do these do?
Oh
All right, I know what I gotta do shoot through them that's double damage
Wait the other one didn't come out yet
What's going on?
Let's do
I thought maybe this would be one of those scenarios where I could just I could just press the three buttons and then they all die
All right. I'm ready. Can I knock these away?
All right, don't fuck around
Oh my god, okay, I got I got a I new plan
What okay
Unworthy let's try it again
Do these have to hit a surface how far these go let me see these go forever until they hit something
Don't spread them out. Don't spread out. Don't spread out guys got double tapped bad
Fuck I still still uh dead. Not dead. Not dead dead
Okay, one two three
safe
There's gonna be something right behind this door
How do you open the door?
What? Oh, okay. I didn't know what this is. All right. I did it. Nice. Let's go damn it. That's all right through the gate
Ooh, I stood still you can't stand still in this game
I knew I installed it. They said dude. I heard you installed the game. I'm like, yeah, it sounds like fun
It's like you can't stand still though like really important I want to make sure you like a good stream
I was like, holy shit. I appreciate that dude
And he was like I and you suck so bad at games like please don't make our game look bad
Like i'm trying to help you so you don't do like
I don't I don't I don't think the game's good not watch your shitty gameplay and then like not buy it
And I was like, dude, it's the game's good
I
Dave would actually say that I don't know who that is but
Secret he's just like yeah, dude. I I mean the carnival was like really fucking cool
That was a really awesome stream. You did a cool stream. Um, but I mean, but you like this is a hard game with like a lot
Of twitch reactions and shit
I think please try
This one's for me
That's a little spot
I hear birds bird enemy
Oh my goodness don't hide I have to
What's this bird I hear a bird and it's freaking me out man, how do I get up there?
Hold on. Stop. Stop. Stop
Whoa, my whole body hurts
What was there?
Oh my goodness
I said, hold on. It's got what's
I've got dm from uh, I got dm from the devs
I said, hey, dude, just hold on. I'm trying to read this
Hey, dude, just want to just let you know that we've refunded the game for you
Please don't play again
What the fuck is it? This is the worst gameplay I've ever seen. What the fuck?
This is really fun. Why didn't I play this like a year ago?
Why didn't you guys tell me to play this? I'm actually like 10 of you did like a hundred times
Where are we going? I need the yellow key
Ooh
Look at that
Played in vr. I don't think I could ever do this in vr
Vr. No way
Is this vr exists for this?
I just got destroyed
Is that it? No, I can still hear them. What was up there?
Weapon in there. How do I get in there? Teleporter?
Well, i'll be damned. Look at that. Can this thing break? Or do I just have this forever? No
Oh
Cool. All right. So how do I actually?
Progress I need to go through the teleporter
All right, let's progress
progression
This way. Well, that's a really good thing to do. I guess I could jump on top no key though
That's where the yellow key is
Over there
Over no, where?
here
All right, i'll try the sword. I get the red key. Oh, I didn't get the red key. You're right
Let me try the sword out though
Seems like a fun thing to use
What was the red door?
I hear something
All right. I'm
I don't think I can excalibur these guys. I'll try it
He just headshot me
Holy shit, this is pretty good
It's because of this guy in here
Give me the soap
Where'd it go? Where is it? Is it breaking? Pog. Let's go
Dude pog, let's go pog. Let's go
Whoa, I shit that guy went so fast
Oh my god, what do I do? What do I do? What do I do? What do I do?
What do I do?
They can't get in if I have the box in front these guys move so quick. Damn it
Okay
Uh, that scared the shit out of me
You're playing this like a horror game
It is oh it is
You don't think you're not gonna you you didn't scream at that part
When you turned that corner you didn't scream
I bet you did
I bet you anything that when that happened you put your hand in the air and you went like
Like I did
Can't get up there
This guy's gonna get up. I know it he's gonna do it
Grenade wait ready here he goes one two three what just happened. Did you shoot that out of my hands?
God he's gonna do it. He's I know he is
Blue key here he comes one two
Son of a bitch son of a god. Damn it. He head shot me. They're too good
This military
This they have all right
I did it back around the corner
All right, let's just go with the sword
Oh
That was a huge mistake
It was awful. It was a really bad idea, but i'm still alive and i'm mad about it
Because I wish I just died so I could start with a bit more health
All right. There's a ghost busters 2 slime gun
It's a grenade launcher. He has to use two
Pepe left
Whatever, whatever
What did that do gate control?
Where's the gate?
gate
Did I miss the gate?
Uh
Was it was I down here? No, not here. Where is it back where the blue key was?
They're fighting each other. Let them fight
Holy shit. This is chaos in here. Um
Watch out for the scarecrow with the shotgun. Let them kill each other with its crates. Oh grenades. I see
ow
Not smart
Hey
Whatever. Oops random money
Fold that fold that save it here good. I'm so happy right now posted no trespassing
This place is doomed not done in the little yet, all right fine and the level when is it gonna play sniper contracts?
um
I already did
and
It was not a fan favorite
it was a uh
Not a fan favorite
Oh right off the bat secret you want me to do sniping? All right, I can do that
Where is he where's this dude? Who the fuck is he?
I tried to jump. I'm idiot blue door back here
Okay, can I get in there
Oh load up
What the fuck was that?
I got in where the hell
We're gonna be a chainsaw guy right here
No, but all right, cool
I get in there
The ladder damn it. I don't think I can get in here
Well, let's go
Use props. I mean props use props
You can pick up boxes and you use props to go up there
Wait, uh
Can I crouch joan? Oh, well, I think I destroyed all the boxes
We don't need everything
We just need most of it
That's a secret I just walked behind cars
Use a barrel and then you called me a dumbass
so um
like
Should I listen to that person?
Very rude
All right, just want to get that
Got it. All right blue doors back here. I will not remember actually books and beer. I'll know that
I will remember that one. Let's move
Another secret in here. What is that? Why is that blocked off like that?
Damn it. Really?
No, I wanted to save that. Ah
Can I get up there? I'm just making sure
Secret located
I don't think I can do this
Whatever I can jump on top though. Can I?
Just please
How does that not kill you? I don't know. I should probably use the sword on these guys
Instead of freaking out I just swing once
They made that but I can't panic which is that's hard
That's asking a lot
Don't use the mortars here. I would keep the shotgun out. That's the bread and butter
I feel safe with
Need a yellow key. Shit yellow key is down here
Into like the weird great sewer thing
All right, so i'm just gonna keep going over this way
I could jump
What's it gonna jump to?
Oh, can I jump to there?
Let's see
Oh, yes, I can
I can do it
Give me that first
Shit, how do I get over there? I know I can get this
Should I get a crouch jump into this?
Because I hit oh here we are
Yellow key down into the basement
Oh, I can go that way. Wait, wait
fuck
I hear chainsaws. I hear them
I hear them
They're in here somewhere and down here. I know I can hear them
Oh you prick, which way are you going?
In a chest what's in it? Not a whole lot actually
Not a whole lot. Okay. Well, I have plenty of shotgun shells
back down to where I was
into the
basement thing
Which was over here. Was it? Yes, it was yellow key open yellow door save game
Let's go
That's too stressful should I go down I guess I'm gonna go i'm going under here secret here
kind of
Maybe a little what's this do flick the switch?
I don't know
Now we go up
I know i'm hiding. Yes, I know
Okay, so now I can travel
What am I looking for here? Probably the blue key
Go up here and this goes around and then down
and then
It's a sludge here red key
I don't remember there being a red door
Give me the thing i'm looking for
Give me that blue key got it you spawned something on me buddy
Where they at?
All right, see you
Collect everything don't leave it up full everything doesn't matter
I'm gonna let you ruin my day
All right full everything
full health full weapons
full ammo full armor
Blue key coming up
Oh, oh that sucked
I'm gonna die up here
All right, i'm gonna get the health that was down here. Can I teleport back? I can't
Oh, well, what about any help that I missed?
I can't be opened
What's that?
Oh wait
I got a good view
Nope, it's just blue door time
You take a lot of hits nice health good i'm ready i'm happy
I like it
There were 10 secrets in that level. Are you serious?
That's a lot
We are now at creations
Pardon me, what's next?
It depends
What do I have to do?
I got the
the hallowed health
Yeah, how do you respond to that question?
Yes
Scientists in here. This is a cut scene. Should I not fight? This is probably a cut scene
Oh
All right, that was pretty good cut scene now, what's what's the boss that this obviously is
Let's go with uh
My let's go grain launchers
Open the door
Uh, just stand here and wait open door
Uh quarantine release do not touch
Let's go what's next more buttons another code to crack I think I can handle it
What are we doing for 100 health for and anything else I can grab while i'm up here
Here's while I have a minute. All right, here we go. Save it here
What um, wait, hold on
Second experiment how many experiments are there? We got a lot of experiments in here
Okay, well, uh, let's go
All right, is there more experiments should I not have done that
Wait, this is only the beginning
All right, that was called creations
That's cool
I just I did it. I'd be level one
The meat hook wounds in your back still throb as you make your way down the cold black and bloody hallways
Uh that once held these monstrous creatures you leave the ruined town of dusk behind littered with the corpses of possessed
hoping never to return
This is standing imposing syllabus of what appeared to be military facility, but why a dark voice pushes forward
Do you truly seek answers or is it simply too late to turn back continue the dusk experience in episode two?
the facilities
When's that come up new episode
Oh, it's already here
It's already here
It came out today. Look at that. It came out today
All right. Let me show you guys something
This difficulty is not intended for a first playthrough
This is my first playthrough. That's what i've been doing
Do dusk mirror for one level. All right, i'll turn it on for one level
How fast are the chainsaw guys?
All right, because it's a new level. I don't like this. I want to have all my stuff
I don't it's not about how fast you can go guys. It's about how cool you look
I think I look kind of cool in some of these fights. That's they're too far away. That's not fair
guns give me
Any more guns? Yeah, of course. There is much if I didn't look back here
I'm smart enough to know that now
Maldi why am I malding?
What the hell did I do?
We got a raid
Another raid. This is like raid two tonight. Damn tomato. What's up tomato?
How the fuck are you dude?
Hope your stream was good
Welcome everybody that was in tomato stream. Thanks for the raid
I wonder what you're doing. I don't know why I just did that this
This is what happens when my brain has to focus on two things at the same time
I just I just threw a box in there and tried to shoot it
I don't know what I was doing. But thank you. Welcome everybody. We're playing dusk
And I think I got everything I need to get the blue key card
Red door is back here
All right, i'm fucking ready. Let's rock and roll. You guys ready to see some action? Check this shit out
Now I typically I if you guys are new to the channel typically I play the sims. I play the sims 3
Uh four days a week
But i'm known to play a little bit of ps gaming from you know, sometimes
Oh
But yeah, if you're looking for some sims 3 gameplay
Uh so far we have about we have to wait 10 years going strong. I have an entire family tree
it's been uh
10 generations now
15 people in the family. It's been going on for about 10 like 8 to 10 years on youtube and on twitch
All right, let me get behind here
Actually do that though
What was the point of this?
And i'll get up here do I have to do this?
Oh, here we go
Here we go up here and then around though. Is there anything on the other side on this one?
I feel like there'd be something back here
But there's not
I have the blue fucking key. Oh god. Damn. What an imbecile. I didn't I didn't even know I picked it up
I'm a sims player. Okay, sorry
What is that
That's a big fat guy
Is he explode too? All right, they explode be aware of that
Oh
Dude, I kind of like going fast. Where's the big guy? I just heard him. Is it a flame thrower?
Wow
Okay, uh i'm on the other side rat
Zoomer versus boomer. Who am I in this scenario?
Oh, yeah
Just the right amount just the right amount of shots. Sometimes you need to call in a friend
And sometimes you need a friend. I will sit here and farm this. I don't care
I ain't gonna let that happen. I'm not gonna go on the roof and get stomped by this guy
Bad, but you bad bad bad, but you bad bad bad, but you bad bad bad
Shots, right? Yep. Yep
Uh, wait, give me the diamond
Uh red cartridge cool
Remember when jeremy plays a game that he has to focus 100% on
You just get the names of things that he's looking at
For all of his dialogue yellow key
Okay, jump up
npc commentary
See imagine if I had not done this
You guys would have been like don't tell him
He doesn't know
All right, good shotgun bullets. Wait a minute
I thought that was a person. What's that super sickle?
Ooh, should I get it? Yeah
I think so i'm gonna try
Let's do a little bit of balancing. Oops
You know, there's no fault damage, right? Okay, good try it again
I saw i'm a i'm a i'm a squirrel. I swear to god
I'm just trying to get that thing. I'm just trying to get the little death star
All right
That way just this way. Can I jump from here to there somewhere?
Uh, no, I can't how do I get up there?
How do I do I can get up there? Hold on
Now
Yeah, come on. I'm trying to jump into that window
Okay, I gotta slow down. Wait
What's the play here I can't jump up what am I supposed to do though? How do I get up there?
I did it. I did the thing I wanted to do but I didn't get what I want
This guy wouldn't last two minutes. What did I just step on? I can get up there. Hold on. I'm gonna try to get back in there
so
um
Other tower or something. Let me see
How do I get that?
Can I climb up that thing?
Wait, oh, there's a fucking gun right there double shotgun. Just get it
All right double shotgun
Okay, so
I want to get this stuff
But I don't I don't know how to do it
Okay, then
Help me
No, what do you mean? No, I'm asking for your help
It's more fun when you don't know
Obviously, I mean I have to go from here to there. I'm probably do I have to jump from there to there?
That's what I was thinking of trying to do
That's the only way to get over there
Okay, I i'm not i'm not quite
Correct though. Uh, what over here? Can I do anything with these?
Do I have to come back with a barrel though, it's probably something so simple that i'm not seeing
Let me try that again wait, it's f9 right there you go
Death from above what does that mean?
What I heard something
I'm hearing things
Should I get the magic sickle?
Hold walk to climb anything
Oh, oh
Hold walk what?
Hold walk to climb anything. What are you gonna?
Walk is shit
I thought it meant like just hold walk up
Oh
Now what do I oh no, okay. I think I blew it
No, I didn't no this shit just opened
Yeah, this is open now. Good yellow key somewhere
Crusties now what these are open
Oh
Red key card got it
New viewer here. Whoa, this guy's good
Oh, I know. All right. Where's the red door red key card red doors all the way back, isn't it?
red door
blue door
Just talking
That just swung around me new viewer here. I remember that happened to me too. It was not fun
Oh, thanks. Appreciate it. Welcome to the screen
What a wait, but what about the door? There was a yellow door
What was that yellow door?
New viewer here. Can you just gotta do a flip? Yeah. Oh, yeah
I've done it on stream
How do I open this? I know that means I could break it. I need to use the rivet gun
Lie
Oh, that's the rivet gun
Right. Thank you for that
Just extra ammo. Oh, there was extra ammo in that secret area
Oh
You know how I know people hate that
because yawning is
Seen as one of the most obnoxious things to hear
easy
What's this mess?
Oh red door. I need the red key
It's electrified
Am I gonna get killed electrocution?
artifact storage
Don't go in the ruins
Oh, well, I will
Don't worry. I will
Is that a person? I don't know
Let's go. Oh, there's nothing here. Wait. I got steered for no reason. What about that?
This looks suspicious
Where am I going? It's just a cool secret
Look at that
Oh, all right
Nice. It's very
I don't like how claustrophobic it is down here
You're gonna bust out of the jail cells
Is there I know it's gonna happen this happens in every video game with the someone at the end of the hall
Don't trust your eyes. Okay, i'm not gonna trust my eyes. I'm gonna run this way. I'm gonna go i'm gonna leave
I'm gonna go home. I'm gonna leave home
I think I killed something
Did I just kill one?
How many do I have to kill?
Oh, at least they have a lot of health
Don't trust your eyes
That means I could walk through this
Oh really? I thought that was gonna be like this is fake and you walk through the wall and this is the next part
How do I open this
Is there a switch to open this stuff?
Oh don't even need a switch
Got the mortar
He's talking about the invisible enemies
I don't know. I don't think so. I think he's talking about a visible wall
But like we have different opinions on it. So that's all right
That's what I think it is though
Very clearly that's what it is
All right got the turn the visuals off and do audio alone
I don't think that sounds like a fun game to me
Okay
Did my speed increase?
We're going faster
Where's the red door up here? There it is
Turn the stream up tweet your actions
Going down this hall now guys going down this hall i'm going down here
If I did that I would tweet more than I've tweeted probably in the last five years total
All right, it's invisible. It's invisible. Whatever it is. It's the invisible thing
Oh my fuck
Oh, that sucks
And they make the burger boy pterodactyl noise
that like
I can't even do it
You know the one knowing that those things are here. Oh, I hate it
invisible enemies really
invisible enemies
I was gonna give you a game of 9.4
Now it's in 9.3
All right, we good am I safe I think so I gotta open this though
Let's go there. How do I get back up?
How do I get back up?
Okay, excuse me the streamer asked you a question. How do I get back up?
Oh, no, it's the five. It's the 5g tower noise
All right, would you guys put your head?
Let's say this is the 5g tower
Would you connect your forehead?
To the 5g towers tip top like this and stick it on there for 10 seconds. Would you do it?
No, you wouldn't
But it's what if but it's so safe why wouldn't why won't you
You would get powers would you get powers?
All right, but when you do it
So you have to hold it there for 10 seconds, but when you do you own that cell tower
It's now yours and any phone calls and anybody's plans that go through that you get a month
That's what you get for like you get money a month like for anybody that uses that tower
Can I like get under here?
It's tempting
I probably should have opened that right now. I probably shouldn't have done that. I shouldn't have done that
Oh my lord. Holy shit. There's a million people. There's no way I was getting out of that one
with my
Not your head, but like the tip of your
Wait, would you just get electrocuted?
If you just went like
Yeah, and just placed it on there for one second
I have not slid at all this whole time i've played this game
Okay, so i'm seeing a lot of like yeah, sure. Sure. Yeah, sure
All right. Well the closer you get with your tongue the louder they're like
Gets
And you can feel like static electricity like pulling your tongue forward still doing it
All right, I gotta get in a good spot
and I gotta get my
Mortar gun i'm ready
Activated how much money we talking? I'll tell you in a second
I'll tell you so how much money we're talking about all the data that goes through the cell phone tower
Is you get it as you know, people have their cell phone plans. So you get a portion of whatever their cell phone plan is
Like you do whatever data comes through that tower. How do I get this?
Are you serious?
Well, I gotta I can still use it
Get the health. All right. Well fine. So here's the scenario you get you get five hundred thousand dollars instantly
but
by doing that
What you've just done is you have given yourself a reverse superpower
Which twice a year it will not this you don't know when two times a year you just violently shit your pants
Yeah, you get a curse
You don't know when two times a year. It's random on 365 rolled days
Could be any time
It could be one two twice in row
You get five hundred thousand dollars
You missed the first part of the scenario. Well, don't worry because none of it matters
It was a double red meat bread exit
What the fuck
Fair it's gonna laugh at me, right? Oh my goodness. We're still back here. I didn't know
Century going up
Oh century going up
Rifle who's still firing at me you
You
Stop using the rifle for the small fries. It's my it's one of my favorite weapons and pinpoint accurate
Boring boring. That's one guy left
Grenade down here behind me. Someone's behind me
What's that? All right, get me over there
Excuse me
Somebody's gonna laugh my ass. Why did you write laugh my ass up? What'd you do that for? Tell me why?
Did I say I didn't say anything funny? Did I say something funny? When did I say something funny? When?
I didn't say anything funny. You got the last hit off. Okay yellow. Uh, i'm in trouble
This is the last person
Funny health
Shit, I almost died
Should I save it? Yeah, just be good
Oh, man, I didn't think this was gonna happen
Jesus
Oh, man
Good
Now i'm gonna go pick up all the stuff that I didn't pick up
Not yet, I was about to scream
But I didn't everyone would have been it's too late for that we're chilling down now I see you
I just fucking freaked out. What did you hit me?
No riot riot riot riot do it a riot
No rioting
Settle down everybody calm down everybody settle down
Settle down
Settle down or i'm gonna call your parents
I'm gonna call your parents if you don't stop i'm calling your parents right now
They're gonna hear about this
Fuck it riot
We're good open. I just feel powerful when they play this game
I do
You've never played it go get it
Go, why did you not? Why do you not have this game? Go get it?
That dude was invisible. Where'd it go?
lost lost progress
You threw it over the building you threw it over the building
God damn it. I keep losing progress
I built my shotgun. Yeah, I've got like 16 bolts though
It's where is it where are you I heard it I heard it where is it
What the fuck is it? What's happening? Where is it? I don't know where it is
It's underneath me. It's underneath me
My goodness, where are we? Where are we? Where are we? Where are we? Where are we? Where are we?
Where are you? Where are you? Where are we? Where are we at? Where are we?
Where is it? Where are we? It's not gonna be behind me, right? Whatever. I have blue
Jeremy don't do that again
Don't do that you idiot
Clutching your TV
Why did you do that you idiot?
All right. Where is it?
Where is it? Where I can hear it
Absolutely riveting gameplay. I'm like very vocal right now. What the fuck's wrong with me?
I'm melting. No, I'm not. I'm just I'm just enjoying
I want to grab
Yeah, I knew there was something back here
Hold that underneath
Well, I don't care. It's a secret, but I don't need it. I don't think I don't oh my god
What did I just miss something up there? Well, not go back
Good it was worth it. All right, save
Like way over here
Okay. All right. What?
What how's that fair?
I can't I can't shoot you but you can shoot me
Oh, you're a turret just go fast. Oh my god. They're shooting
No, i'm dead
All right. I gotta use the uh rifle here
One shot with the rifle find him
Wait easy. It's right there. I got you
Hey, I just got here. How mad is he?
I don't fucking want to talk about it
the game's fucking good, but like
Fucking god, man. I really don't get this fucking mad on stream really
But if you just joined us like i'm fucking see what i'm talking about. Like what the fuck is that?
See what I mean? I don't want to hate getting fucking mad like this on stream fucking furious right now
Whoops, what where am I?
I hear I hear the dogs running
Okay, one just bumped over a basket. Okay, i'm gonna stay up here. They're everywhere
I see baskets being bumped
See him talk about oh, I didn't save it
Okay, I got a stuff being such a fucking weirdo
Is it seven eight? Where's the hunting rifle?
Which number is it on? That's how we get rid of this guy
I can't believe it's the first time I've missed the whole game. I think although they're all done
Looks like it
They're in front of me. They're in front of me. They're in front of me. They're
Did they jump up too? I think they jumped
They're not up here, right? Okay. All right. Now we mortar. Oh my god. I fell off
Oh, they almost made it
Oh, yeah, now we got all kinds of help
That was everybody's sunday, by the way. I know today's not sunday, but i'm talking about like last sunday. Did you have a good one?
Those are sunday all hail the great thresher
So I have all the keys
Good save
Thanks. All right. I need to get in that door
So this do I actually get to leave them?
Am I getting baited again?
Okay
Can I go down from here?
exit
what uh
What am I missing?
Red is there another red door over here?
Press zero
What is this?
You just smoke a cigar
Why is my health not going down?
I'm gonna go back in the other room. All right. So what am I missing here?
Is there another door that's red? Oh, here we go
Smoking is bad
Okay, I thought it was one of those okay, i'm fine. I thought it was one of those um
Handlers i'm just gonna call them the maintenance access is open
Turn
Maintenance is now open
Whatever that means
Uh, i'm turning this to the beginning of the level
Do a flip. All right. I'll do flip
Right
one two three
Oh my mouth
I hit my mouth with a fucking desk
Oh
Oh, and fuck I gotta go
No, i'm not like let me wipe that blood off. I'm fine
Oh free stuff. Okay. Where do I go? They might i've lost my mind
Wait, what's this?
Get in there
What is what is that? I have to go did I get it? I think I
I almost didn't get it
I fell down and just
You can actually flip in this game. That's pretty cool
The infernal machine that hurt
The fall broke your flashlight. Uh, oh
That's not good
That's not good. I hate that
I'm not happy about this
Play the game like daredevil save, okay
I was I was in the middle. I was in the middle
Save
Is that noise man
I don't know from here red card
I can see again. All right, good in that shocker. They want me to use the shock in here
So i'm gonna use the shock and i'm gonna keep the shock in a clip
No, you don't i'm gonna two pistols
Let's actually let's actually use this the way they're supposed to use it
Be good at the games. They don't waste any i'm not good at the game though claustrophobic in here to be good
New flashlight good
Holy god my fucking hand my hold on I have to restart but there was no reason why there'd be a door open behind me
And my brain hurts
Okay, where did you come from?
Where did that guy come from?
Shoot him. I will terrible tracking jeremy
Oh approached a little long slide
Yellow key damn it
Looks like we're going down save the game again. Don't get killed by the blades
Forward
Now I gotta walk back
Oh, he's a slide I didn't slide that's the problem I didn't went without even looking last time
Yeah
Right in the blades almost jesus that was
Was germa good at tft? Yeah
I played uh engineer
And soldier and scout
It was pretty good
You know back in my heyday
I would be number two with three or one on the top rag list
Did I miss the yellow key?
Did I not get him it looks like it opens this door opens elsewhere
All right, let's go i'm gonna try it good I can climb this
Climb if I walk don't don't shoot the buttons
Not bad aim it has to be something like over here is there is there a spot I could go in
Is there an opening that i'm just not seeing because it's blending in or something
I thought it said don't shoot
Oh, it's a joke
Didn't I shoot it i'm confused I thought I shot the damn thing
Give me a bad aim. I shot it like 15 times
I get it
Go get back here
And you missed no, I did not miss I was just not I apparently wasn't close enough. I shot it straight on
Go look at the clip. I don't even do whatever I do bend myself
I don't look at the clip
That's un-fucking-believable just restarted. Oh my god
I just slipped off
the fucking edge
ready
Tell me again what I did wrong
What did I do wrong? I shot it a thousand times
Okay, I do not go back down
And this time you hit it
What the hell is this okay blue
No, wasn't that gonna be that easy now, was it turn it back on turn it back on turn it back on
When was the last time I saved it did I not save yes I did turn it back on
What is it homing missiles in my face?
Damn, okay
These guys suck to use
Jesus I gotta just run down. I think my goodness. All right, this is the
Hard fucking hole. Uh, i'm gonna use this i'm gonna stay back here
Shit reflect them i'll try it wasn't very good at this last time
What
That's the way to do it just hold the attack button that's not gonna work watch this
I'm dead that one guy. I banned that one guy
No, we're doing it my way. You can't just ban people to solve your problems. Yes, I can
Whoa
Don't softlock
Why are you still alive?
This guy made out of fucking titanium. I don't understand
I can ban away all my problems
Somebody says hey streamer, you're an idiot ban them
Somebody says hey streamer. I think you look ugly today ban that person. Hey streamer ban that person. I don't even want to hear
Can I get in there? I do I love how they have the combine voice that like
Like that was just delete that whole clip. It was not even worth watching
I could have done it better, but um, it's it's been um, it's it's getting late
Does it fall damage?
Rivet gun the hell is down here. You found a secret. Hey, you stream live for once
Welcome, what's up? Hope you having a good day
First thought what's your first thought coming in here? What's the first thing that you're thinking of right now? What's the first thing?
You go maniac
All right. Yeah, I was supposed to go in the door
The door over here because there was
Not bad. Oh shit. I'm gonna start using mortars. I have so many of them. What's the river to ammo look like?
Best weapon my favorite weapon in the game got it
This door opens elsewhere, of course
Oh, I know where it opens
Get out of here
Fuck out of here anymore
Goats have gone mad
I figure there's gonna be one right there. This one's I can hear them
Does that mean i'm gonna get the crossbow?
I would hope so
Oh crossbow
Okay back up to it
I've got the other key now
Let's get the hell out of here
Soap up there. It's all good
All right. Now if I remember this one is down this one down or up
I don't remember this is the yellow one, right? No, it's not. Yeah, I know
You're not gonna tell me. I know already
I gotta get i'm gonna get back here
Cross there up
Not worth using that
All right, here we go just open a bolt just in case I did it wrong
Good thing I did that this guy would have collapsed on me. He sneaked. I was sneaking up behind me
The hatch is open so what?
So what?
Where's this hatch i'm looking at?
The hatch is open is this the hatch that's down here? That looks like a hatch
It depends on what you mean by that
Holy shit
Save it. Oh, we got a boss now. I think I I I have a boss feeling right now. What do you guys think?
Just the end of the world
That's the coca you did
Guy is dead completely dead so dead no reason to use that switch to the uh stickles
Jesus what I didn't know this was a new room. Was it?
Press e on the computer
Don't have time to play with myself
You got me
Yep, you got me. You got me there guys
And say whatever
I need the yellow key does this door open? No, the other door does I know what that one is
At least I don't have the sword anymore. Do I damn it? Oh, well
I thought that was an enemy
We'll do mortar it wants me to so bad
Why it wants me to have seen that coming from a mile away
Soap i'll try it
Take it
Taste the power
Bad ending if I
Maybe I should do a mortise in here. I wonder if I uh
Turns out yeah, soaps an insta kill. Yeah, I know it's just hard to move around with let me go over here first
Take it
Time only moves it
Was that kind of moving
It's freaking me out. Let's offer
All right, give me just give me the big one
Shouldn't be wasting that on these guys. I don't need to do that
Holy fuck that was a turn
Every time you kill one of the guys sounds like you grunting I guess so Jesus let's get the fuck out of me
I didn't mean to do that
So can't open that
Something isn't right
Yeah, what's not right?
Does this we have life give me something good give me something I can use give me something good
Uh, I get i'm gonna go
Up speed running this game would be so stressful
Holy shit
No, not really on the hardest difficulty though, I feel like it would be
I that's why i'm just not cut out for that shit
Just not at all
I got the yellow key
Hardest difficulty is one hit one kill for everybody
That's kind of scary
Wow, I gotta try that
I didn't get a chance to look how cool that was
slow down, uh
Anything up here?
Oh shit, there's somebody over there. Wait
Oh
I could just
That sucked
That hurt red key
You overthought that I know if I'm not going up there and there's a
don't
Uh, I didn't
All right. Let's keep moving
You save yourself save the game
What a reference somebody just said wild woody
Wild woody
That's unfucking believable. What a reference the tank opens. Oh my god. There was something in there
It's mama
This is uh, i'm gonna probably be here for a little while
Considering you can't fall off
That's all I do is fall off stuff was made to be a wall for me
all right, i'm gonna go with the
Riveter first
Fuck oh this is gonna be forever get it later wrong way. I keep predicting the wrong side
Oh, I fucking swear god
Barricade the door
No, i'm not using cheat strats
God damn it
I bet 10 bucks. He falls off again. I'd like to see your ten dollar bill
Wait, wait. Whoa, what?
That's to make sure you don't have to send any bits. All right, let's go i'm help i'm helping this person out
wacky scientists
I hear another wacky scientist
Let one of them stab you no my you oh hint I didn't get any secrets
the arabist reactor
That's they're just waiting for me to come up. They haven't started their ai yet. What's this bulls on parade?
Is that what this is on this
God damn it everything I can fuck if I fall down I get a ah every time
5g I can feel it already. I can feel the waves of my brain
Oh my fucking god
I can take a break i'm peed. Yeah, I had to pee. That's the problem
uh
So also something important to know
I gotta leave in about 20 minutes
I gotta leave in 20 minutes stuff for lydia gave 10 community subs. Thank you for lydia
I gotta leave in 20 minutes. I gotta get uh auto food
And I want to get it before they close
But we'll pick this up tomorrow. We're not done yet though. We got like another 15 20 minutes
It gives you um, this is awesome. I'm having a lot of fun. This is great
This is fucking fun. It's really fun
What I just do?
Quick save, right? What's going on?
What happened?
Why is this the I I haven't saved it since back here
That doesn't make any sense. It's impossible
How would I have started the
I'm so confused right now
Wait, why is
Going on
Oh, okay. So this this is the very beginning of the level, right? Okay
All right. No fucking around here. We go
That's a waste but sometimes you gotta do it
Where the fuck are you and how you got a sight on me you guys with your aim is better than anybody's i've ever seen in
My life
What the fuck am I doing?
Push
I swear, okay. I'm gonna I might have to take a break. I'm thinking about it. I might have to I might have to take a break
I'm i'm alive. I'm alive. I'm alive. I'm like quiet down
How do I get out from here?
Climb I could climb that shit
What?
Why there's a mama back here. There's a mama
There's a super soldier
Jesus they're raining hell over here. Where's the mama? All right, i'm running I need uh ammo
Let's go
Don't step in the reactor jeremy. What are you stupid?
I'm panicked for no reason. I just freaked out
I saw you. Okay guys sometimes when you start losing track you start losing track of everything
You start making mistakes
I saw I shot that around
Holy shit. What a name. What an arm
Okay, I gotta save right there. Holy shit. There's a lot of people over there. Why do I have to fight? I'm
Mama is here. I have to find a mama
I think that's it though
Two onions. All right. I got two two onions
Three onions. No
Waste I know it was a waste. Don't remind me. It's a key card. Let's not
What the fuck was that?
I'm sorry
Yellow
Oh fuck guys coming in right here. All right, so now I got some time. I'm gonna go pick up some shit. I need blue
More rifle ammo. That's my favorite weapon
I'm gonna save and I i'm gonna go down and collect stuff
I think blue I think the blue thing might actually be down here. I wouldn't be surprised
Damn, look at this
Perfect. Okay. What else is in here?
All right, destroy the reactors
Found it finally
I love this thing
All right blue with the blue one blue blue blue blue
There we go. I gotta open this door
There it is all right good. Oh shit didn't know you were in here
Sorry, didn't know someone was in here
onions ammo
I'm ready
Fuck oops
He was glowing that means he's stronger did it but wait
Here we go ready, where am I what?
Okay, I i'll take that sure whatever. Okay
red
All right red door done
You're using a macro. I I don't know how to I have no idea what that even means
All right with the bread
And it was safe right there. What the fuck am I doing?
Jesus
And there's one of these
I've wasted them
Don't be softlocked. Don't be softlocked
shit, uh
They still stop coming out
Oh
I need to get that help in there
Oh shit, what the fuck?
God give me a fucking break
Both dead. Oh, you gotta be fucking kidding me. No
All right
This ain't no super mario needed to hit that one
I needed to hit it
Holy shit, she's got the aim of an of an angel
Where is she? I don't know what she is. I don't know where they are
Save it right here. Don't move. I will heal now save it
Whatever give me that whatever that is
I pressed this I pressed the razor never buy a razor product, uh button on my mouse and my dpi went up. Sorry
Where is she?
This is freaking me out, man
ever save
I'm just gonna leave. All right. Bye
The music's still playing though like just blasting music did she die did she run into a wall?
Okay, we just
This door opened somewhere else
This is a huge area
secret onions
Good, okay. What about auto i'm good as long as I get out of here in the next
15 minutes
Okay
I'm here kill me
Come on kill me
That's so stupid, okay, whatever
Come here kill me come and kill me stop and kill me kill me
That's it. He says that you're probably gonna say it over and over again
Actually, I need to save this
Okay, then we're gonna go
Riveter and then bang
Where am I going did I just pass him?
What hold on
He is coming after me he's right here, holy shit, okay i've got an idea
What the fuck did he just shoot me back up he's coming he's coming he's coming he's coming
He's going too fast
All right. Well here it comes
Oh, he's still up there where is he there is all right one last thing I want to try
I'm waiting for him to bounce
Is he not gonna bounce?
There he is. He's aiming down. Let's go dodge the bullets. I'm gonna go by him again
I'm gonna shock him right in the fucking face
Jesus
Where is he?
His bitch shit. All right, kill him
Oh shit, you gotta move. Oh man. I just got like triple tapped
Oh fuck
Holy shit too close
You gotta unload it immediately I gotta go far away
All right. Now I gotta take out the I don't even know the hunting rifle
Oh
Wow, I just can't fuck it. I can't I can't circle him. Jesus that's a grenade i'm dead
My chest I killed him. All right
Do I guys leave?
I think so
Yeah, I do he's dead
That was fucking wild
All right. I uh, i'm gonna call it here. We're gonna continue with this tomorrow
This will be what we uh start with
I believe we're probably
Uh, we're probably what like halfway through the game?
Just about okay cool
Just a bit more than half cool
Yeah, I gotta go, uh get food for Otto
I don't want him to close because uh, he needs it. So i'm gonna take care about him
But uh, we'll see you tomorrow same time
We'll finish dusk
Which i'm so glad
I'm so glad that
I switched off of that sniper game
To play this
But yeah, we'll see you tomorrow. Uh, i'm gonna do the bits and the subs. Uh, hopefully very quickly
I'm leaving myself a good 10 to 15 minutes here to get to the store
But no, this is fantastic. Uh, let's save just give a regular save right here
Uh, that's fine. Yeah, okay, whatever it doesn't
It's the same damn thing
All right
I'll see you guys tomorrow
Thanks for watching. See you soon
Those of you that's sticking around
Let's go through the bits
Let's go back
Back back back back back to five six and a half hours ago
Og thank you og m here for the 300 bits
Hey, german just started watching both you and star. Well, not just started. Hey, I started watching you guys back in 2011
That's around the same time. I picked up tf2
From your casual gameplay commentaries to the very list of wacky shenanigans you got up to
Always kept me glued to the screen and even in stitches from time to time. That's a long fucking time
You've been a fantastic source of entertainment for many years and kept me smiling through many during hard times
Thank you for being you and never forget about the sheer joy and laughter you spread around the globe
Thank you for the incredibly nice message
That's a decade ago
I can't imagine somebody thinking the stuff that I say
Is still interesting
10 years later
Thanks
That's all I can say and I hope in another few years you think the same thing
Thank you
Don't feed his ego like this. We need to know we got to bring him down
Seriously, thank you og
Ben folds 20 community subs huge amount of subs. Thank you ben. That was earlier. The chairman gave five community subs
For real though. Thanks for the 250. All right jerma since you turned down my suggestion for stelares
Money suggests free space to open
It's a really cool space combat game that has a lot of mods for it and adds a new content
Uh, it's the first i've ever heard of it
free space to open
Look it up. See if it's something I want to play
Thanks for the suggestion free space not new space free space, too
Thank you. I'll take a look
Hey, uh genie. Thank you genie for the 500 bits almost there chat. I'm not sure what that means, but
Uh, you're you were almost somewhere
Thank you
Lost fables gave 2,500
Bits 25 bucks earlier
Thank you lost fables if you're still around
Jerma i've been watching your content for the last five years and you're without a doubt the most creative and hilarious person i've ever watched
Wanted to give something back since i'm not a sub
Also, not sure if you take game suggestions, but titanic
Adventure out of time seems perfect for you
Much love and continued success titanic
You play is that get you play on the titanic?
All right, we're gonna write these a couple of these down
Also, if you have game suggestions, make sure you throw them not just on here
But make sure you put them in the actual recommended discord channel
I check that all the time. I'm always scrolling through there. So
If you're not part of the discord draw the discord too. It's open to the public
There's a sub room, but it's pretty much just completely open
I came in wanting to see dusk. I got you baited. Well, you're gonna be real happy
Because i'm playing it tomorrow, too
Hopefully get to the end of the whole thing
That clip is really yeah careful listening to that clip. This is one of the loudest things i've ever done on stream
But thank you lost fables
Don't worry if you're not a sub
Thanks for watching regardless
Uh, mr mcgee guy. I don't even know why I don't I added mister
To your name. That's not your name. Your name is mcgee guy. It's not mr mcgee. I don't know why I said mister
Mr one guy
Thanks for the 1500 bits. There's no message here, but just 1500. Thank you
Dark soul, thanks for the 250 bits finally done with my 70 hour work week
But by all means take half of it. You worked 70 hours and made five dollars. That's not good
That's really not good
Is that was that like
76 cents an hour
That's not good
The children can eat their beds made from amazon boxes. That's okay. But actually thank you for streaming
Also, you're really cute. Please play metroid prime. I have like three days before I consume the game cube
Uh, we had a couple of raids we had uh
Tomato came in with a raid. Thanks tomato. Thank you. If you're still watching from tomatoes
Stream, thanks a lot guys
Hope you enjoyed it. We'll be doing it tomorrow, too
and we also had a raid from
Uh lazy purple
As well, so thanks both of you appreciate it
Let's put the subs on the screen
and go to this
Hopefully the camera's not on I just start wearing shirts to turn it if I need to
Thanks everybody for your subs
All of you, you're all fucking incredibly special to me
There are a lot of you. Thanks. Look seriously. Thank you
Nice boy. Haha. What is he called a special the dev sub to you?
That's that's fun
Who actually who made the game who actually what was it? What studio was it?
It's really good
Who made this who made this game?
I okay. This is how stupid I am. I went into steam and I typed into the search bar studio
Dusk, okay. Oh, it's just me
Just made by one guy
Really? It's just me. It's one guy just well not probably not but just david
developer
David so that's the david you guys talking about. Oh, that's cool
Well, the game's awesome. So
Look forward to what you do in the future
But uh, let's keep going because I gotta get out of here
Thank you everybody for your subs. Seriously
and dark soul, uh
I'm glad you don't use 70 hour work week. Take a nice needed rest take a couple days off
You deserve it for lydie 10 community subs. Thank you for lydie earlier about 30 minutes ago
I think I caught it but just want to say thank you again. It's a lot of money
Malto, thanks for the 500 bits. I have to say my favorite movie quote of all time is i'll be
Biac from the 1985 the germinator
It's not a bad one
Sorry
And then xion's w a s d. Thanks for the 500 bits. I'm gonna start a riot
Halo is not better or equal to tf2 xbox
Back me up against the pc oppressors
halo
What is this?
Halo is greater than and not equal to tf2's xbox
Well, all the console team fortresses were terrible
They never received an update
That's not fair
There were still glitches in the game where you could insta kill people with a melee attack in xbox
tf2
You could store a crit and just insta kill somebody and it was a incredibly simple to do
Uh, i'll be playing halo though. We'll see if it's any good on pc
All right, guys, see you tomorrow. Thanks for watching. I gotta get out here. I gotta eat at the store
Gotta get out of some food
Dusk is awesome. We'll keep playing tomorrow and see if we can beat it
Good night. Take care
See you tomorrow