Hey, what is happening guys? It's Jerma here again with another gameplay commentary for Team Fortress 2.
This time I'm playing as the Huntsman Sniper on King of the Hill Nucleus.
This is not the gameplay. This is kind of the beginning. I jumped in a little late.
I'm gonna show you the gameplay after this. This is kind of just a few headshots and stuff like that, kind of,
because I didn't want a two minute gameplay, so after this is when the actual gameplay starts.
But I go on a pretty good run here, get a few headshots, get some good nice long shots. You know the deal.
Huntsman is fun. This is the Huntsman, the Vintage Jurati, and the Shahenshah.
And this spy, I knew he was a spy, come around the corner, I just smash him.
Don't know why he just was standing there, but you know, probably just caught off guard coming around the corner.
If you're looking for Huntsman tips and strategies and stuff like that, this is not gonna be the video for it.
I have a video up on my channel using the Huntsman, showing you real strategies how to use it, how to get better with it.
So I suggest you go, I think it was a month or so back, just go search in my channel page.
I believe it's called Huntsman tips and tricks. So if you're looking for that video, that's what it's called.
Now very, very briefly, I want to talk about my livestream schedule.
I know that a lot of you guys are going back to school or are already in school right now.
So I gotta change my livestream schedule so I don't have to be like,
oh, I gotta stay up till four in the morning to watch Jerma, then I have to wake up in two hours to go to school.
I don't want that to happen, so I'm gonna change my livestreaming to Saturdays only.
I'm not gonna do it two times a week anymore, guys.
Only Saturday nights, Saturday evenings at around six o'clock Eastern Standard Time.
I'm sorry if that screws up your schedule that you had when you originally were watching me,
but that's gonna be the way it is because I know a lot of you guys are in school,
so you're not gonna be able to do it on the weekdays anyways.
So that means that today is Saturday, so there will be a livestream tonight.
Check your local listings because I'm not gonna be able to tell you what time it is in Germany
when it ends up being six or seven o'clock Eastern Time in the United States.
So that's gonna happen tonight.
Stay alert on my Steam group because that's the only place I'm gonna ever tell you.
Maybe on my YouTube, but that's about it.
So let's start talking about the gameplay now.
Fresh start, three minutes, three minutes, King of the Hill Nucleus,
using the Huntsman, the Girardi, and the Shahansha, like I said.
Standing still, Demoman gets shot right in his face,
and looks like we're gonna cap the point. I think we get it, actually. We do.
This part is actually kind of funny.
Scout comes after me with the candy cane, and I think I'm gonna get him.
Oh, what's this? Another Scout coming after me and a Spy.
This is fantastic. Nothing bad's gonna happen here.
Get the kill on the Scout, but I get shot in the face by the other Scout.
Got our death out of the way right there.
That's the only time I die during this particular gameplay.
Let's keep going here. Roll out of the spawn.
I was thinking about spamming the point, but it looks like our team has it pretty well secured.
Heavy Engineer on the point.
I don't think I have to stick around here and get myself killed.
That's a Spy. I know it.
You can always tell if a Scout is a Spy, because he's running slower than a Scout.
And watch this! God, he just, like, breaks his neck on the wall right there.
I thought that was ridiculous.
We only have an Engineer sitting on the point right now,
so I figured I have to get over here at some point.
This Scout tracking a Scout is the most difficult thing in the world.
I end up getting him, though, with a nice little track shot.
You'll see I turn around, he's coming up the stairs,
and I just barely get the shot correct.
And there we go. Me and this Engineer got this point pretty much on lockdown.
Minute and 47 seconds now.
They still have three minutes left.
They haven't capped the point one time, which is huge,
because we're more than halfway there now.
Probably securing a victory, unless they can pull off something really, really crazy.
Coming around here just to check the perimeter, and I see a flaming Heavy.
Guys, your teammates really appreciate it,
and you get points for putting them out with a compression or a Girardi,
so if you don't already do this, please start doing it.
People really appreciate it.
This Spy right here comes up behind this Heavy.
I'm going to slow it down for you. Watch what happens.
He backstabs the Heavy and gets headshot at the exact same time,
and both of their reactions, I thought, were so funny.
I was dying laughing at that one.
So I come down here, shooting near their spawn area,
I get a couple of kills.
This is a great thing to do on Nucleus,
because so many people are just pouring out of this doorway.
It's such a small little corridor that you're pretty much guaranteed
to kill at least one person coming out of here.
Throw the Girardi.
Don't get anybody covered with it, but it's all right.
I end up making this Pyro free Willy off the edge here.
He falls way down to the depths.
So I get on the point, turn around, I see a Sniper,
and I know for a fact he's going to go to the little spot right there,
and I end up timing it right, get the kill.
That's what's going to happen.
There's a Sniper on this map.
They're either right in that corner,
or they're going to be at the top right on one of the balconies.
That's pretty much every single Sniper spot.
Get another kill for a Soldier that was coming for the point,
and I get another kill on a Pyro coming for the point.
So now there's less than 30 seconds.
Everybody's here.
The whole family is here on the point just hanging out.
Dead Ringer Spy activates his cloak,
but he's not going to be able to do a whole lot,
because there's so many people squashed on the point.
He's going to have to bury his way into people,
and he probably will end up just falling off the edge,
so I'm not concerned about that.
So slowly we are all creeping up to their spawn door
with less than 10 seconds now,
less than 5 seconds.
The game is over with a flawless victory.
Thanks everybody so much for watching.
I really appreciate it.
Hopefully you show up tonight to the livestream.
If you don't, that's cool too.
I'm glad you watch the videos on YouTube wherever you watch them.
Thank you so much.
Take care everybody. I'll see you all next time.