Hey, what is going on, everybody? Jerma here with some more Hitman Absolu-
Whoa! Hitman Absolution. And this is episode two. This is the King of Chinatown.
And what are you cooking here, dude? There's nothing in this pot. You're not cooking anything.
You know what? I just like hammer punched him in the face. All right, I gotta restart.
All right. Time to, uh, to actually play the mission. Get the hell out of my way.
Get out of my face. This place is so crowded. How am I supposed to ever assassinate somebody here?
This is going to be like impossible. Where is the guy? Oh, he's over there.
Yeah, let's kill a guy that's like standing in the middle of the area. King of Chinatown. There he is.
Get out of the way! Get the- Get out of my face! These people are just blocking my path.
Uh, hello there, officer. Can I like come look at that guy? Nope. What? I was just
kidding. Spotted. It was just a joke. Cool down, man. Wow. What is that? Oh,
it makes some points of interest. I see. There's a lot of different ways to potentially do this,
probably. I can't believe I just lost 1,500 points just for going up there and like smiling.
Should I get a tattoo? A lot of people over here. This person. What's this person selling?
You got fish? Watch out. Let me like look at it. Oh, it looks good. Fresh fish. Now,
get the hell away from me. Where should I even go? Oh, oh, oh, oh, there's like a- Well,
that's that guy's trail. Okay. Can I walk by this guy? Is he going to freak out? I don't think I
can walk by this guy. What's this? Sabotage? Hell yeah, sabotage. Oh, I can't believe that
guy didn't see me. How did this guy not see me just do that? Dude, you're an idiot. You say nice
shirt? What a prick. Look at the nice shirt to you. What is it, like 1984? This isn't like the 80s,
bro. Sneak up behind that guy. Trespassing, but he can't see me. He doesn't even know. Yes. Okay,
get that bottle. What the hell do I do? Are the lights off up here? Is anybody else up here? I
swear to God, I'm going to get myself murdered. No, there's nobody here. Keep out. An apartment
overlooking the square. FitzBirdy's description. Okay. A lot of places to hide. I'm kind of
afraid of this area. I guess I can go. Can I even open this door? Ooh. Oh, this is the guy's
apartment. It's... Oh, yes. I'm going to snipe the hell out of this guy. Where is he? Can I even go
in this window? I'm scared to go in it. There he is. Hold on. I need an escape route here, guys,
because if I shoot this guy, I don't want to get in the window. Someone's going to see me in this
window. It's going to be over. There's the guy right there. Can I shoot him from right here?
No, I got to be standing. Oh, man. I don't want to take the shot. Oh, I can't pull the trigger. I
can't do it. Oh, I can't do it. I can't do it. Oh, I got to do it. I got to do it like right now.
I got him. Didn't anybody see that? There's a guy coming. There's a guy coming. There's a guy
coming. He didn't see me. Oh, my God. There's a guy at the top of the stairs right there.
Look at... Look in the radar. Look in the radar. There's two people that are coming up here right
now. I am actually shaking. I'm like, oh, my God. Oh, my God. Oh, my God. Oh, my God. There he is.
Please don't open this. Please don't open this. Oh, should I get out? Oh, God. This is the most
terrifying thing ever. He's looking at me. Oh, get out of here. Get out of here. I'm freaking out
right now, guys. That was so terrifying. Am I in the clear? Cautious. Okay, I need to get out of
this closet. When this guy comes back in there, I'm killing him. I'm jumping out. Push him out the
damn window. Choke him out. Choke him out. Oh, that's the guy that talked a bunch of crap. I'm
breaking his neck. Remember this guy? This is the guy that said, oh, what do you like? What do you...
Nice shirt. Yeah, disguise. Can I bury this guy somewhere? There's two dudes right here. Come on,
get in here. Get in here. This guy looks like an idiot. Oh, that's pretty morbid. Hey, I had to
break this guy's neck. He was an absolute prick. Oh, don't mind me. Just carry on. I gotta throw
that down. All right. Now, I'm this guy. I'm gonna walk out as this guy. All right. What's up? It's
just me. Oh, hi. Yeah, remember me? I just need backup. I need backup. Oh, my God. I'm actually
gonna get away with this, I think. Anybody else? They're looking for me out here. Hello, officers.
Good to see you. Nice to meet you. Wow, everyone's freaking out. I should get a pretty good score
for this, shouldn't I? Well, I did break that guy's neck. How do I get out of here? Oh, it's over
here. I want to just like sprint. That was terrifying, guys. That was ridiculous. When those
guys were like looking for me and they almost spotted me. Oh, I'm home free. This is like an exit,
I think. Yes. I did it. Oh, nice. And there it is. 36,000 points. Target kill, one. Non-target
casualty, one. Minus three. Ah, that's the guy. But that guy was a jerk, so he deserved it.
Three objectives complete or times three. Body hidden and headshot. Hell yeah. Nice.
But that's gonna wrap it up here, guys. If you missed episode one again, it'll be in the
description and probably an annotation on the screen in the beginning and end of this video.
So yeah, thank you so much for watching. Really do appreciate it. I'll see you all soon.
Take care, everybody. Stay tuned for episode three.