Hey. Yeah, sorry. Sorry I'm late. Uh, I wasn't supposed to be. I was sitting here.
Just ready to go. We were pre-stream chatting. I was here. And then, I had to take out the dog.
That was true. I didn't even tell any lies. I just didn't tell you the truth. I was holding
back the truth from you. I wasn't lying to you. I just wasn't telling you what was going on.
Is that a lie? That's not lying. I just wasn't telling you the truth. I wasn't telling you
anything. Is withholding information a lie, or is that just withholding information? That's not a
lie. That's just withholding info. It's called a lie of omission. Well anyways, uh, I had to update
my GeForce 1080. Apparently there's an update today, and oh boy, Halo Reach is going to be
running at over 100 fps. I can guarantee you that one. That was a pre-stream chat joke. I know I
told everybody in the pre-stream before that I don't do- that's exclusive material for pre-stream
chat, and I just used it. So, sorry. You have a million dollars. Get a 2080 Ti. Um, I don't have
a million dollars. You're off- your math is off by a little. I do not have a million dollars.
He has five million. Nope. Nope. Look, when you spend all your money on carnivals,
Halloweens, and Minecraft servers, your CPA gets kind of annoyed with you. He's a trillionaire.
He's broke. I'm not- I'm not- okay, let me be very clear. I don't have a million dollars,
but I ain't broke, all right? But I got a very loud phone call, uh, back in October from my
financial advisor. It was a loud voicemail. I could not tell most of the things that they
were saying because it sounded like they were yelling very loud into an iPhone,
and you know what happens when you- when you scream into an iPhone? It- it gets distorted,
so it was like, I- I can't- so I have no idea what he- what he was saying. Something about-
I can't believe- why- why would you do that? I don't know, something like that. Anyways,
we're gonna continue the Outer Worlds. What the hell is a carnival stream? All jokes aside,
don't worry, I'm doing fine. I don't have a million dollars, though. I- I will do, like,
a celebratory stream if I ever have a million dollars in my fucking checking account.
Why would I do that? That would be fucked up. Imagine- imagine somebody doing a fucking stream
about, I did it, I made it to a million dollars. That's some next level fucking, like,
dystopian future type shit. I should just do that without having any of that money. That's
a funny stream. It's like a celebration of me crossing a million dollars, and I- and there's
not, like, not even five percent of that in my bank accounts across every account I own.
All my retirement accounts, like, imagine, like, imagine that? It would be just, like, fake.
All right, you know, like that big- big controversy on Instagram where people were
taking pictures in their backyard and pretending they were going on vacation to Hawaii? That's
what that is. I did it! I made it to a million dollars! And then, like, turns out, I didn't,
like, sell my car and shit, like, I didn't have enough money. It's like, what a fucked up future.
What a fucked up stream. Hey, speaking of fucking weird futures, here's one right here. Why is my
iPhone not working? I- I- I- ah! This man- I got a million dollars, and I couldn't get an iPhone to
work? I'm just gonna pick up right where we left off. If you don't know, I'm currently playing the
laugh-out-loud hysterical guy. Dumb character. You've never seen that before. Not only am I
playing the game, like, three and a half weeks late, I'm also playing the thing that you may
have already watched. Somebody do ten times. But it's different because I'm a doctor, too.
And I might be doing other choices. And I got a million dollars. Anybody else that you watch got
a million dollars? Probably. Probably way more than that. All right, let's get out of here. Let's get
going. Actually, I gotta tweet this. I'm sorry I missed the context of that joke. Why is he talking
about having a million dollars? Uh, yeah, you had to be there. Okay. What should I write for a tweet?
How about just- and I'm just, like, gonna- I'm relaxing today. We're just gonna take it nice and
slow. More stupid doctor. I'm not even a doctor. Yeah, I am. More- how about more lying doctor?
You don't ever want your doctor to be a liar. That would be really bad. He comes in with, like,
your x-ray, and you've got- you've got, like, a- like, a tear in your lung. And he just tells you,
well, I got your x-ray of your lungs back. And, whew, you got stomach acid problem.
We're gonna get you on some antacids. You don't want that. Okay, more lying doctor. All right,
let's move. We can go now. Why would they do that? Because they're a liar. They're a lying doctor.
That's the character I am. That's the character I'm playing right now in this game is a lying-
an imbecile lying doctor. And the ToastFart just came in with five community subs. Thank you,
ToastFart. Appreciate that. Thanks, everybody who got those subs, because that means you're here
and you're watching. Thanks to you, too. That's a really fucked up looking pig, okay? All right,
I was just gonna say, if this game is gonna run like shit now after I updated my drivers,
I'm gonna be pretty mad. I think it's okay. It's all right. Fucking g-force. No, it's all right. I
think it's just initial loading of the game. All right, so let's take a look at what we- where we-
where we left off. So last thing I did was I angered a lot of people in the stream because I
gave power to Edgewater. And then the next thing I did is I have to convince all these people from
the settlement now to move back to Edgewater. And one of them said, I ain't going anywhere until you
find me my friend Zoe, whoever it was, and I found Zoe. And Zoe had a ring that I took
and brought back, and I completed that quest. None of that was a lie. That was just what happened.
That's the truth. So and then the other person that has to come along is this- this engineer
here. The three volumes. Tom said he knows that at least one volume is in the local community center
because this is another person that- well, I have to convince all these people to leave.
So let's do that. Engineering volume one, engineering vol- I can get all of them?
And no, this is not- I know you may have seen a playthrough of somebody that threw like a
grenade over there. That's not this one. This one, sometimes people die. That's it. That's it. Not-
we're not- not intentional. Let's go get volume one. Just fast travel. But isn't fast travel
boring? I'm- I don't like fast travel. Walking is boring, I guess.
Fast travel is more fun. We get more gerbamite content. All right, it's in the community center.
Let's get it. Turn my mic up? Yeah, what's- what's going on with my mic lately? Hold on.
Ever since- let me look at this. Hold on. You tell- you tell me if it gets to be too bad.
Bad?
That's good, right? How's that? That's better, right? But what- once I scream, it's gonna be bad.
All right, no, that's fine. That's good. That's fine. That's better. I think that's better. Yeah,
that's better. Are these bad guys? They are. He's blind. Did I just shoot a blind guy?
Uh oh. I just fucking missed three times. Stop, stop, stop, stop, stop, stop, stop.
Oh, this is bad. Fuck. Okay, this is a lot harder than I thought it was gonna be.
Did Jerm ever find a party member? Yes, and I told them to leave.
Okay, so that- this is much more difficult than- also, I'm also playing on hard. And then some
people are like, holy shit, this dude's on like the story mode difficulty and he's losing. No,
that's not- that's not what's happening. Let's sneak. Did they hit that scream? All right,
we're gonna make it happen. I feel like it's just- the- I don't- the way the guns work sometimes,
it just feels like I'm- if I've been playing too much Dusk- all right, I'm gonna drop this- you
know what? I've been playing too much Dusk. I'm dead. I have the slow-mo. All right, hold on.
The guns in this are mostly lame. Let me look at this shit. What should I even use in here?
Uh, do these guys just suck? What about the list I have? Am I not high enough level to kill these
guys? What if I put too many points into, uh, lying to people? This thing is probably the best
thing I have. No, it's the shotgun and the pistol. This thing actually really is not that good.
Let me try this. This, you know, this streamer is whack. Oh, it's not as good. What the fuck
are you doing? Where are you going? What is happening right now? What? I gotta combine the-
Jesus. Fuck. Dude, does this gun have- does this gun hit people? How- it's a shotgun. What?
Does it need to be repaired? How broken is this thing? It's not that broken, is it? Bolter pistol.
We'll try this thing. All right, well, this is the first area of the whole game that has been,
like, hard for me to even get through it. This thing's almost broken too. Small, lightweight
pistol. Just use the light machine gun and just fucking hold the button down. You know what? I
have been playing too much Dusk. We're gonna drop the fucking- this by, like, down to, like,
eight percent. I'll do nine percent. No, that's too much. Twelve. All right, that's a little better.
Now, let me try this. Shotguns are kind of bad. Are they? So it's not just me? The shotgun just,
like, sucks in this game? All right, let me- let's- let's- let's do this tactically. Holy shit! What
the fuck? Are these guys, like, level 20? Oh my god, it's precedent. Oh my god. Oh my- okay,
am I not supposed to be in here? Holy shit. I'm alone, I have no teammates, and they do
so much damage. What the fuck is going on in this room? What? Give me my- give me this thing.
It's kind of hard to stealth because I don't know anywhere they're facing, and they- they're- they
can really- they can see you really easily. All right, there's a guy right here. Is there an
instant kill? My sneak- I don't have any sneak. I'm a fucking doctor. How do I instantly kill him
from behind? Give it to me. Where is it? Where is it? Where's the book? Oh my god! Give me, give me,
give me! No, get it! Pick it up! What is this? Fuck this place. Missed the fish lore? I don't care.
All right, I got one. Should I get them all? Is this that one person that told me, Jeremy,
you're gonna hate this because the handguns are terrible? Don't use handguns. Should I have listened
to the one guy? No, I haven't saved it! I haven't saved the game! Where do I go? Where do I go? Where
do I go? Okay, I'm at the other one. Save it. I need a workbench. I have to redo this- this guy's
loadout. What is that? Who's talking? Electric sucks? Why- why does electric suck? Why do- why
does anything suck? Where's my choice to do what I want to do? What do you mean, it- it sucks?
Shock and sucks. Shooting sucks. Am I being lied to? How do I get in here, though? Can I break this?
Yeah, that's- that's very obviously electrified. I guess I can go in here. All right, where's my
electric? All right, scientist. I thought that was me that died. How is that possible? All right,
so volume three is way, way easier to get than volume one. It's just right here. Well, not quite,
but it is still- it's right here. Turn the game volume up? Ah, actually, you're right.
It should be higher. That's better. What do I have for ammo? Am I good? 1900, it was this light ammo.
Just buy it. Heavy ammo? Just buy it. Energy cell? Just buy it. Sawed-off shotgun? No. Wait, what?
Revolver? Should I get this thing? I don't have a revolver. I have a bolt pistol. How much is it?
And just get it. Whatever. All right, let me look at it. It's all right. All right, let's try it.
Revolver. Ooh, actually, this is- I like this thing. I'm not even- I actually really like this.
It's not the best choice, but it's a- it is a choice, so we're gonna use it.
Exo helmet? I have so much random shit that I need to go to, like, town after I do this. I've
already read these. I think- I've already been down here. Yeah, I already did all this. This guy's
friendly. Good thing I cleared this whole thing. Just run down here and get it. Wait, where is it?
Further down? Okay. Oh, this guy's still down here. Does he care if I take his book? Model spaceship?
All right, I got two. Don't kill this guy. Why would I kill him? I don't have a reason to kill
this guy. Not yet, at least. All right, volume two is- should I just fast travel out of here? Can I?
He doesn't have any morals. Uh, yeah, I do, because I- I didn't kill that guy. If I had no morals,
I would just be like, hey, watch this chat! That means I have morals. That means I- I chose
not to shoot that guy. Therefore, I have morals. Is the other one just in here? Wait a minute.
The other va- no. That's just called not being insane. Yeah, I also said don't smoke cigarettes.
You weren't here for that. That's pre-stream chat. I said don't vape and don't smoke cigarettes,
especially don't vape. Because vaping is just cigarettes you can smoke inside.
And you can just do it a hundred times more than you do cigarettes. And then I went off on a whole
thing about, uh, you can- all the advertisers are like, it's water vapor. It's clean, clear water.
Water vapor. But you'll be taking in 50 times more nicotine because you're gonna hit this
fucking thing all day. But it's vapor. Clean. Clear. Water. Vapor. Turn up the volume, dummy.
I did. I increased it by like 5,000%. Our branch of vapor juice is the cleanest, clearest water.
I can only hear gun sounds. Well, what do I- that's called audio design, not me.
You mean like you can only hear this? Well, how do I fix that? Audio?
Effects. Music. There's only effects and voice. Turn effects down, turn the master up.
Okay. Now. Volume 2. Just play Chillstep. Not a bad idea. All right, let's go. Up.
Wait. No, I went the wrong way. Up. No, go back down. Can I get out of- uh, who let the toddler in
the elevator? He's just pressing buttons. There you go. Oh, come on. Which one of these is it in?
All right, I got them all. Can you see me do this? Yeah, whatever. Fucking corporations. Okay,
let's go back in the elevator and get out of here. Anarchy. That's not anarchy. No mortals. Omega
low. Omega low-archy? Ornarchy? That's not even- there's no A there. That's not correct.
You cannot fast-drive well near hostiles. Who's a hostile?
Is somebody just hanging out one of these buildings? I don't see anybody.
Am I away from hostiles now? I am. Let's turn this in and then let's tell everybody to leave.
I did all your tasks. Now go back to Edgewater. We're gonna go take it over.
I got all three of them.
No kidding. Really? Well, which one?
Which one do I give them? Found it in the community center. The elusive part three.
Someone stashed it away inside the old geomotor. Should I give them the elusive part three?
The geothermal plant? Now that is just incredible. You really went exploring down there?
Adelaide always told us it was swarming with hostile mechanicals.
It was. Until I went down there.
Hey, it's your lucky day. Hold on. I got more for you. I got another one. Here, take part two.
Oh, almost forgot your payment. What was it? You gained 500 bits. Thanks for the five dollars.
Last one. Don't keep me in suspense. Look at that. So what do you get for all three? Building
a computing machine out of spectrum potatoes, a primer. I'm just glad it survived all these years.
That's a complete set. All three parts. I'm gonna be the greatest engineer Halcyon's ever seen.
4,000 experience. I've been saving something for you. Just a little contraption.
Should fit right into your outfit. What is it? What is it? Hurry up. Electrocharged surface.
I want to ask you something. Go back a couple months to Edgewater. This camp's my home.
People you see milling about? They're my family. At least I think of them that way. I owe them my
life. Would have died in the wilderness if they hadn't chanced upon me. Starving and delirious.
All right, so now I've done everything. All right, well cool. You can tell somebody else.
All right, I've done it. So now comes now the power. Return to Adelaide. Reed has been removed
from Edgewater. Return to Adelaide and tell her the news. So we're ready to kill Adelaide.
I know, but that's like anarchy. I don't think I'm gonna do that. Let's hold on. Let me see what
happens. The plan was to bring everybody back to Edgewater and then kill her. But then wouldn't I
just be everybody? I would be just enemy number one. Let's see. Look at that. The snakes come back.
Call me a snake again. Reed's dead. Come back to Edgewater.
You have a peculiar comfort with violence. Killing off my garden, gunning down Reed Thompson.
Suppose it's time our flock made our way back to Edgewater. We must tend to what remains of the
town and carry on with our lives as best we may. So who runs the town now? You're vexing to me,
you know. Injuring us with one hand, helping us with the other. Here, I'm giving you something
to leave us be. It's a ransom, you understand, not a reward. Ransom? You just gave me you a watch
for ransom for you? You know, it's better off with you running the place. You're telling me you did
all this just to put me in charge of Edgewater? Stranger, you are some kind of twisted. You might
turn that old cannery into a garden. I'm gonna wait till she sits down in the throne and then
kill her. I need some time to gather my personals. Long walk back to Edgewater.
Got a considerable burden to carry. And then hopefully somebody else is ready. You're like,
oh wait, I could run the place. Yeah, I bet you could. Why don't you give it a try?
Sitting in the mayor chair is the trigger for me to shoot them. Take care now. I'll see you later.
There can be no ruler. Everyone who tries gets the boot. I just spilled coffee all over my
fucking whole body. Whatever. I'm not moving. All right, so we got, they're making their way
back to Edgewater. Now get the power regulator. Give it to me. What would happen? I don't even
know. Regulator, return to the unreliable. I did it. Let's go. So that's it. All right, we're good.
She's still alive, right? Okay. I told you, I do what I do appreciate about this game.
You can say it might be a little more limited, whatever, right? But one really important thing
to remember about this game is most NPCs die in one hit. Remember when you used to play Fallout
and you'd fight an NPC and all of a sudden it would just be like a boss fight? People die pretty
quick. Okay, so now I got to go back to the landing site. Let's continue. Bastard. Bastard.
Look at him go. Bastard. All right, let's do it. Well, I certainly am looking forward to flying
on a ship. Is this a hologram? This is a projection. He's not actually here. He's like,
spoiler for a very large movie franchise. Is that, that's not going to like come back and bite me
in the ass or later, right? Like in an hour, he's not going to instantly take all that stored up
damage and die, right? Like he's not gonna be mad at me or something. Okay. Well, we got,
we got backs. We're good. Captain, I have detected that Edgewater's power supply is now optimal.
I applaud your willingness to invest your time in the local community.
What can I do for you? I've got your power core. We can get out of here.
Do you know how to install a power regulator? No idea. Yes, I do. Outstanding, Captain. Your
aptitude for engineering will prove invaluable in the event of another catastrophic engine failure.
Our engine room is located behind you, across the cargo bay, up the ladders.
Dumb engineer, dumb doctor, dumb everything. Dumb liar. But you can't be all of these things
if you're stupid. It doesn't make any sense. If you pick the dumb trait, then you shouldn't be
able to be like a scientist or a doctor. It's a living oxymoron. All right. How did I pass
medical school if I can't even like read? That makes no sense. If I can't read, how did you pass
med school? What can I do for you, Captain? All right. So all systems are operating within
acceptable parameters to bring the unreliable into low altitude orbit. This should prove an
adequate test of our flight capabilities. Hold on. Do I need to clean something up here? Let's see.
Side quest. Retrieve the cache of medicine. Abernathy believes he's dying. Well, I already
didn't already kill him. I mean, I already, I'm pretty sure I already sentenced him to death.
Yeah, let's go. He's dead. I like told on him and shit and like the guard now knows everything about
it. Back to the community center. No, no, he's dead. Welcome back, Captain. Can't save her. All
systems are now operating within acceptable parameters. I know. Not like I've been trying
to save anybody. Can't save everybody. Just accidentally killed like four people and destroyed
a whole town. Whatever. Can't save everybody. Request from Dr. Phineas Wells. Pogchamp's in
chat over that. It's just like a ship taking off. I love that so much.
Hail and hearty and captain of your own ship. I see you're putting the unreliable to good use.
Shame about her former captain. Horrible way to die. How are you feeling by the way?
Do you look like that guy that's in the basement of the geothermal plant? Any unnatural drippage?
Perfectly normal side effect of thawing. I assure you. All right. I'll get to the point. What you
saw in Emerald Vale is happening all across the colony. Food shortages, lack of supplies,
and basic necessities. We're dying. The chairman, the minister, and all their lackeys on the board
are to blame. The hope has some of the brightest minds earth ever sent us. If we can revive the
hope's colonists, they can help us undo the board's mistakes. They can help us set things right.
You need to get to Stellar Bay on Monarch. I have contacts there. They'll help me,
help us find the chemicals to revive your fellow colonists. I really give you this quiet. You're
doing that face too. That's what you're doing. Cozy little black marketing outfit on the ground
breaker. She can get you a nav key to land on Stellar Bay. Okay. You cannot travel to Phineas's
lab. Okay. I'll go have a word with Gladys. Why do I need a nav key to land on a planet? Slow down.
You're asking me to get involved with the black market. Or I could put a couple light years between
me and... I could just leave. I'll go have a word. Excellent. I'll send her a wireless. Let her know
you're coming. By the way, I gave Captain Hawthorne a disguise apparatus of my own design. Cutting edge
technology years ahead of its time. I call it the holographic shroud. I'm sure it will prove
remarkably useful to you. You'll find it in the captain's quarters. Wait, I can put on a disguise?
You want me to wear a cape? Wrong matter of shroud, my slow-witted accomplice. This is,
how to put it, simply a device that makes you look different, sound different, briefly. The device has
its limits, but it will allow you to blend in perfectly and probably won't jeopardize your
ability to have children. Will it? No, definitely not. Probably. Yes. Very simply, the holographic
shroud uses biometric information contained on standard identity cartridges to generate a
holographic projection around you. Okay. What are the limitations? It only stands up to a
casual scrutiny. Use it too long, bound to flicker, blur, something like that. Movement
makes it more likely. Movement? Best used in moderation. When you see guards in your path,
you can sneak past your target. Oh, this is going to be horrible. Maintain your distance. Act normal.
No running, no jumping. No running, no jumping? Don't draw their attention. If they pay attention,
they're more likely to notice flaws in the hologram. What do you mean, I can't run?
Change of clothes. What is this? Some old spy serial? What inattentive and brainless
guard would be fooled by such a shabby disguise? The holographic shroud masks not only your clothes,
but your face and fingerprints. It modulates your voice and sweetens your breath.
Okay, I'll put it to good use. Excellent. I'll contact you once you've found a way to get to
Stellar Bay. If you have any questions, come see me in my lab. And remember, don't trust the board.
They'll try to win you over with promises of wealth and power, but it's a lie. Is it? I know
that very well. The board is only interested in filling their own pockets. If we don't put a stop
to them, they're going to run this colony to the ground. Liars versus liars. Transmission ended.
If you are ready to depart, please select a destination on your navigation terminal.
Got it. Okay, so can I just open the hatch and just fly out? I don't know why I even asked that question.
All right, holographic shroud. There it is. Projects a disguise on you and your companions
that gives you access to restricted areas provided you have the correct ID cartridge for that area.
Restricted areas are off limits to unauthorized personnel and otherwise result in being attacked
on sight. Well, that sucks. Reeds. Did I bring Reed's skull? Did I take this guy's head?
What the hell? That's a little fucked up. All right, what do I got? A bin. Let me see. I need
a workbench. Where's the nearest workbench? Shh! Who's this? Sam. Okay. Workbench. Am I stealing?
This is not like somebody else's room, right? A stern older man with warm eyes.
There he is. Tarot cards? Tarot cards. Okay. Don't want to see the Ten of Swords.
Especially when it's the right way up. That's real. But that's real. You guys can mine us
to all you want. That's actually real if you see the Ten of Swords in a reading.
What? None of you guys understand tarot readings? I bet you there are 20, almost 2600 people here.
I bet you maybe one or two of you have ever had a reading. I've never had a reading before.
Has anybody in here actually done it? Maybe four of you? So that, that like reference was for four
of you. What? You guys don't like sit on the toilet and like read about tarot cards? It's what? Just
because you're just like, oh, I wonder what that's all about. And you just read about it?
I do that, but not, no, I must, I must be a fucking hundred years old. You guys don't read
shit on the toilet? What? Oh, you go on Twitter. Oh, right. You scroll through Twitter. Oh, I forgot.
I forgot about social media. God. You guys should be reading about tarot cards and like,
how much water pressure happens when you go a mile underwater? You don't read that?
I don't understand why. All right, let's go to, this is where I am, uh, terror two. I can go
a lot of different places, can't I? This is a whole solar system. This is awesome. Welcome to
the system map here. You can see all the planets in the system as well as some special points of
interest. You can fly your ship to any location you've unlocked. There's some landing bays require
special codes and keys before they allow you to land. Moving between planets is considered
dangerous. Okay. All right. Passage to anywhere. Uh, speak to Gladys on the ground breaker.
Ground breaker. Let's go. We've arrived at the ground breaker. So I have it a bit beamed onto
their ship. First of all, let me do this. All right, we need to do done. Okay. So now I am
impossible to, I'm, I'm a dialogue master. Get some new clothes. I will hold on. I'm a 50 liar
perks. What do I got? Journal. Ooh. All right. Uh, you have a sawed off shotgun and a scope.
That doesn't look right in your hands. It seems weird. Uh, I'm going to give you this.
That's probably better use for you. Hey, don't aim that at me. What the fuck?
You stupid. All right. Uh, let's go back. Captain, could I have a moment of your time?
You sure could by Verity, by strength. What are we contemplating today? All right. We have to go
back and forth here with Max. I'd like to know something about those I'm flying with. What's
your story? I'm the, you're the only one on the ship. Any ideas where we can find someone who
speaks French in this colony? I've been thinking on that. There's a form. That's what we care about.
Infamous philosopher scholar who fled terror to some years ago. He's an expert on Bacono.
He's also who told me of the journal's presence in Emerald Vale. If anyone in this colony could
translate that book, it would be him. Seriously? The one guy in this whole colony? The only one
I'm aware of. I suppose we could always just ask for random passersby if they are. Talk to computer.
Get Sam. Talk to computer. No, I want this guy. Your sarcasm is duly noted and it will be reflected
on your review. A thousand pardons, my good captain. I thought we were engaging in witty repartee.
Now, we want Sam and Max. We should start on the ground breaker. Yeah, they're in the game.
They're the only two people that are going to be on my ship. Are you going to have two at once?
All I need is access to a data cartridge from the security. Hold on. I can have Sam and Max.
What? Let's do it.
All right, how will the crew manifest to help us to track down your scholar friend?
I'll comb the last six months of departure manifest to track the
Philosophist's off-world destination. Okay. Thank you, captain. All right, let's get Sam.
I would like you. You know anything about the auto-mechanical gathering dust in the
janitor closet? The intent is a cleaning, Sam. Hawthorne brought it on board some cycles ago.
I'm sure with the intent to modify it, but I've never seen it up and running.
Alex likely recorded progress notes detailing his efforts to modify Sam.
If you check the terminal in your captain's quarters, we may be able to determine what
work remains in order for Sam to properly operate. Another quest to get Sam and Max.
Uh, okay. I'm in the mood for some entertainment.
Certainly, captain. What would you like to hear?
Tell me a joke. I used to hate math, but then I realized decimals have a point.
Now playing a Spacer's Choice advertisement jingle.
It's not the best choice. That's not my favorite song. Everyone in Halcyon
is contractually obligated to label this or another board-certified jingle their favorite song.
Let me let me fucking fix. Let me fix that up for you.
Now playing a Spacer's Choice advertisement jingle.
Oh, beatbox. You beatbox. Oh, beatbox. You beatbox. My pleasure, captain. As you wish,
captain. I must comply with all direct orders. All right, let's go. I'll be here.
All right, now let me look. Uh, the empty man.
The cleaning machine. All right, search Hawthorne's terminal. Let's figure it out.
This is my favorite room. It's so spacious. Cool. All right. Good to know. All right, let's repair.
What is this? A revolver? Yeah, this is a shock pistol. Yeah, I still don't need it. How's this
doing? It's fine. How's this doing? It's all right. This needs to be repaired. Yeah. Okay.
Why does it have a diamond on it? Hunting rifle. What's that? What's that diamond mean?
Tinker. Let's see. I want to make this a little better. Revolver damage. Is it stupid for me to?
I mean, it's only $50. That's not that. It's 102 bucks. 110. Do it again.
I want to make this useful one more time. Okay. That's it. That's it. That's not again. Now we're
getting, we're getting to $600. 128 DPS for the pistol is pretty damn good. All right. Tinker
with the hunting rifle. 58 DPS. 100. No, what else can I do? My light machine gun.
Always just do at least the first or second tier of these because why not?
This thing's going to be useful now. All right, now let's break this shit down.
Uh, keep the shovel. Get rid of the, this guy's staff. All right. What is it? No, not Tinker.
We modified. No, we need to break down. Okay. Break this down. Uh, wait, wait, wait. Hold on.
This is okay. That's not equipped, right? I just destroyed something that was a diamond on it.
Oops. Who cares? Uh, this is too one-handed. Um, this thing is just worse. This is both one-handed.
No, it's not. Uh, fuck it. Who cares? Oh shit. All right. I need to modify, modify, modify. What
can we do with this? With the revolver? No modifications I have for the, um, for the revolver.
No scopes. No nothing. How? Light machine gun. Nothing. The pistol. Nothing. What about armor?
There we go. Electro charge surface. Thug kit. All right. Let me look at what I even have for it.
I have a lot of ram shit here. This thing is tech skills. It's five armor. What else do I have?
Lab outfit. I kind of like it. I do kind of like it. Patched low pressure helmet. Mining gear is
stealth. No. Holy shit. 17 armor. It's heavy armor though. It weighs a lot. No, it doesn't. Spacer's
choice outfit. Melee weapon skills. Sneak. One-handed melee plus five. That's actually
pretty good, but I'm going to keep this on. I like this weird doctor look. Yeah, that looks
all right. Wear the hat. Oh yeah. Dialogue skill plus seven. That's true. All right. What do you,
what do you got on for armor? This. Give me this. I'm putting that on. Your clothes. Give them to me.
All right. Now you can put on the doctor outfit. Let's just trade. All right. We're going to trade.
You're going to be me and I'm going to be you. You get to be the doctor. I get to be the priest.
Do we have two hats? I think that's fine. This is where I have to actually pay attention. So
this is the heal. Heals 25% health over two seconds. Plus 200% natural health regeneration
for two minutes. So I can combine these. That's pretty cool. Let's do, what do I have a lot of?
That's like headshot damage. Can I just do two of these? Can I do like a double dose?
Well, let's do the, let's do this for now. Do matching hats. Fine. You have perks though. All
right. Base health threat generated. Increase your hack skill. I don't want to generate that much
threat. Maybe the hack skill, but I'm not going to really use it. I mean, it is, it is just a free
hack skill. That's true for health or it's either health or hack. Cause I don't want you to generate
threat. You'll just die instantly, but I don't want you to not generate threat. Cause I don't
want to take all the hits, but we're going to get Sam. It's a free hack skill. I'm taking it
plus 20% dialogue, combat effective, melee damage, armor rating, range damage, free hack skill.
All right. Looking good. I've got my stuff sorted. Let me just go to my weapons, make sure this is
all correct. Where's my revolver? There it is. This is the one that I'm going to use. I've upgraded
this a lot. This thing's all right. This thing's okay. They're all all right. All right. Looking
good. Got my, can I up, can you tinker your armor? Can I upgrade the armor? Shit, I can. Okay. So
I'm going to upgrade his robes. All right. And upgrade the hat too. One more time. Why,
why did that not go up? All right. I'm going to break down the, one of these, probably the
shock one. No, this one. Do I even want the assault rifle? No, fuck it. I don't want it.
What about this junk mining gear? I feel like I could use this, but I don't want to be weighed
down. Tech skills. No, this is worker's outfit, melee weapon skills. I mean, I don't care.
Oh, sneak plus five. I'm never going to be sneaking around. One-handed melee, maybe mining gear. I'm
not going to be sneaking around. This thing is a diamond, so I'm not going to get rid of it.
Stealth skills, get rid of the damn thing. Tech skills, maybe, but not really. Get rid of the
damn thing. I'm being weighed down by, all right, that's fine. All right. I'm ready. Let's do this.
What was I doing? I forget. I was going to go over here. Yeah. To do, to activate Sam. Search term
Sam. First Sam result. Do not forget you found a discarded sanitation and maintenance auto-mechanical
in Emerald Vale scrap heap during your last job. It should not be too difficult to get it up and
running with a few key modifications. I can envision a combat capable variant. Some might
say a clean, mean killing machine should be fun. Removal of factory standard part. Suds steeper
with successful delivery of combat modified replacement part. Acid steeper has been deployed.
Progress setback is estimated to be a solid three months. Not like I have more pressing
matters to attend to, but I do. I'm giving up hope on the delivery. The part is lost in transit. It's
not turning up anytime soon, but good news. I heard from a fellow who knows a gal who knows
the broker who overcharged me for the information regarding the location of an acid steeper. I can
filch. The part was sent to an old storage facility in Rose Way. The rest of the stuff
you could have just went like this and hit delete because that's all I need to know.
It's abandoned. Good. Cleaning machine. Let's get it. Find the acid steeper. Let's do that.
I'm into that right now. I want two companions. That just freaked me out. I forgot you're the
doctor now and I'm the priest. So I'm going to make sure you have all the medical stuff.
Okay, where is this thing? You found entries on Hawthorne's term in the captain's quarters
regarding his attempts to turn Simon over. Hawthorne planned to replace him with an acid
steeper but never picked up the part from Rose Way. Welcome back captain. Where's Rose Way? How
can I be of assistance? Goodbye. I don't have access to Rose Way yet, huh?
Well, shit. Okay. So Rose Way is not accessible so we can't do that yet. So we're just going to go to
where we were going before. The ground breaker has approved our request for docking captain.
Oh, all right. Okay. Let's have a meeting. Party select. Just you. It's just you. So right now
this actor is reading the script for what's coming up. He's not happy about it. He's like,
wait, they made changes? I have to be the fucking doctor now? Oh, that seems a little...
Well, you're the director, I guess. Okay. I thought I was hired to be the priest.
All right, let's go. Smells like grease and unwashed bodies. Just as I remembered. That's
not the point. This hat would just knock out one of my workers. Yeah, with a tossball stick. I heard
you the first time. There weren't any witnesses. No witnesses. He's not even denying it. No
witnesses. Jackass had it coming. Sorry. Shut it, Felix. Hi, I am interrupting you. If you could
move along, I'd be obliged. Don't go telling him where to step. Ground breaker belongs to all of
us. Felix, first of all, no, it doesn't. And second, shut the hell up. Don't think I won't detain you
again. Are you head backwards? Does this head 180 degrees turn like broken neck?
You look like you got enough problems. Mind if I have a word with the kid? Hey, knock yourself
out. Or him, if you're so inclined. Whatever you heard, it's all true. I heard you, I heard you
knock somebody out with a tossball stick. The guy insulted my Rizzo's Rangers, all right?
You can't just insult my Rangers and expect to get away with it. What's Rizzo's Rangers? So of
course I decked him with a tossball stick. I mean, what am I? What kind of fairweather fan?
Did he make fun of your Pokemon card deck choices? So you hit him with a stick? That's overreaction.
You wouldn't be saying that if you'd been there. Guy never liked me. Always trying to get a rise
out of me. But I keep my chin up, right? Be the bigger man, I tell myself. He's a Spacer's chosen
man, though. So when the chosen beat my Rangers the other night, my foreman comes swaggering up
with his head full of boasting. Oh boy. Oh, and that's when you resolve your differences like
an adult, right? That's when I broadsided him with a tossball stick. Yeah. Look, this was a long time
coming. Guy thinks he can push me around because he's some sky-high foreman and I'm just a back
base dock worker. Well, former dock worker. Guess I just tendered my resignation. You're lucky you're
not serving a sentence. You know something? I am lucky. I ought to raise a glass of zero G to my
fortune if I had the bits. Hey, not for nothing. But I saw you wander out of that ship over there
by the dock. Wouldn't happen to be yours, would it? What does my ship have to do with you?
That's me, captain of the unreliable. Captain of the unreliable. You're like something out of a
serial drama. Hey, I don't want to tuck your ears off guessing you got places to be. I appreciate
your time. Please don't hit me with a stick. Oh, not at all. Just, uh, you know, gonna figure out
what to do next. See you around, boss. Boss. Hey, what are you, what are you making this guy?
I find myself marveling at the complex simplicity of the Fibonacci spiral.
I'm sure you know what that's like. Something that he's gone. Let's talk about the thing,
you know, that thing with the thing that you want to do. Yes. Well, now that we're here,
can we check in with security? I'd like to track down that scholar.
That's the plan. Okay. All right, let's have the conversation with the lattice.
Customs and inspection, right this way. Identification, please. Oh, do I have,
wait, I don't have the, do I have the thing on? I don't think I turned on the cloaking device.
You're guarding the door. I'll call you guard. You're welcome. That's only about the third or
fourth dumbest line I've heard all day. I give it a six out of ten. Seems a little high.
That was barely a three in my humble opinion. I was being generous for the sake of his pride.
So identification. You guys don't like this guy? How could you guys not like Max? Here. Captain
Hawthorne, you said. Let me apologize in advance. I'm about to ruin your day. According to your
ship's record, you've been flagged by the board. Your ship will be impounded until such a time as
they see fit. Well, isn't this wonderful? The captain's done something to get on the board's
bad side. Now hold on. This isn't the end of the world. Probably. Uh, I take it back. I'm not
Hawthorne and that's not my ship. Oh, thank the law. I could use a diversion. Tell me more then.
Really sell it to me. It's not mine. Uh, well, I won the ship in a poker game. Hawthorne gave me
his ID so I could fly it. Hawthorne died in a crash. I took his ID so I could fly his ship.
Captain Hawthorne abducted me and made me work for his ship for free. I'm a prisoner. Help.
I like where this is headed. What happened to this uh vile kidnapper? I killed him. You must
feel terrific. Good for you. So I'm stuck here? Not stuck per se. You can always throw yourself
out the airlock. Of course then you find yourself with an exciting new problem. I'm on a secret
mission. Uh, I take it this happens a lot. Just the opposite. The board knows we don't take kindly
to their interfering in our operations here. Surely this must be some sort of mix-up. I had
to take a guess as to why. You probably riled up the wrong petty board bureaucrat. A man named Udom
Bedford. Okay, so kill. Kill Bedford. I'm gonna wring this Bedford guy's neck. You take the
starch out of him. Well, you won't hear any complaints from me. Imagine admitting to like
the guard. I'm gonna do you a favor. Sure. Wand the door set over in sick day. Tell her the shipment's
not in yet. It's not coming in anytime soon and if she'd be so obliged to get off my ass about it.
So if I do you this favor you're not going to talk about how I killed the guy that I just
told you I was going to go kill. Good. Got it. Much appreciated. Is there anything else I can help you
with? I'm looking for Gladys. The fence. You'll find her and the rest and go on your left when
you enter the promenade. Make sure you bring an empty belly. What can you tell me about Bedford?
Friendly enough unless you speak ill of the board. Get the sense he doesn't care for groundbreaker
much. Not that he would being a board man and all. He's our liaison. Sounds like a fun guy.
Really likes his cereals too. Maybe a little too much. Bit of a weird bird all told.
Okay. See you around. Be seeing you. Understood. I'll keep my head down.
Through the hole in the glass. You thought that wasn't going to save you.
Doesn't seem to care though. All right let's go uh let's go talk to and I'm putting my hands in
the air and going talk to Bedford. A quest objective requires you to enter a restricted
area. If caught inside you'll be shot on sight. Using a disguise will prevent immediate hostilities.
Security I can check the departure's register to find out which crew check
I mean the scholar shipped in and out with. What are you looking at?
What do you think? What do you think would dress funny? You think this is funny?
Doctor and a scientist? What do you think? I don't understand. What's wrong?
Hey. Let's go Max. I picked up this weird signal the other day. It was coming from Monarch.
Here we go again. No one lives on Monarch. Well like you never seen a doctor walk into a ship
before? Never seen a doctor and a scientist walk into a ship? What's this for? What's going on
with your eyes? Oh don't even look at his face. Okay I'm not gonna kill somebody.
Okay okay okay okay. Wait restricted area. How do I turn on the disguise?
Who's talking to us? Is this restricted? Is there do I have to put on his disguise?
Do I have like a his just how do I turn it on?
Okay two guys it's like Halloween costumes coming and steal all your stuff.
These aren't even Halloween costumes. Why do I think this is so out of the ordinary?
You're dressed as a doctor and I'm dressed as a priest. Why these Halloween costumes?
No they are Halloween costumes because that's the number one thing that's fucking sold at the
Halloween store is look at me I'm the priest or look at me I'm dressed as a doctor. I'm a doctor
dickhead. So this these are costumes. Steal rest and go key card. Red ammo. You gotta be the lookout
man. All right good job. We have to go to 13. Oh that's not that's like literally right there.
All right let's go this way.
That's the same thing from Lamy.
Ah it's going to do that thing.
Put these kids to sleep. Fuck. All right interstellar crew.
Belle Everson. What do you got? What do you got in here? What's that?
You know that sound when you've snapped on an injector clip?
That's how you know your weapon loves you back. I got a full line of weapon modifications I'd be
happy to show you. For free. Holy shit. I mean your merchant skill is equal to the value of your best
dialogue skill and is used to negotiate prices when buying and selling from vendors. And I am
a huge liar. I got a 12% discount. All right let's let's see here.
Weapon part. Okay. Extendo sight. A 2x scope that also extends the weapon's maximum range.
Increases weapon accuracy. Mr. Ouch. What else is in here? Should I grab one of these for the uh
should I grab a gyro sight for the um the revolver? Get a better scope for the sniper?
I don't have enough money. Yeah I do. Oh shit no I don't. Sell. Wait. This is important.
I have a bunch of dog shit. All right hold z to sell junk. I've got 3,100. What did I sell?
All right I can afford it now. What did I sell? Can I sell? Do they know it's stolen?
All right now let's get the extendo sight. Let's get the gyro sight. I just want one. I don't want
to buy two of them. Did I just buy two? I just want one. I just want to buy one. Why does it say
times two? Oh all right good good all right all right all right repair. I need a workbench.
Someone has got to talk with Chief Tennyson about the thermostat around here.
Ain't gonna be me. So you buying? No I'm selling. I'm selling. Dead Eye assault rifle.
I picked this up not that long ago. This is a good gun. Should I just keep it? Oh shit okay.
Okay if I sell it we'll be put back on display. So if I sell this come and we'll just be on
display again and steal it sell it put it back on display steal it sell it back on display.
What else you got back here? Look at all this stuff that's just free. It's just for free.
Look these games it doesn't matter. It is free. What? Am I in trouble? All right fuck it. Let's
go. Steal money out of the register first. All right I'm gonna save it right here. Why do you only
have 25 dollars in here? He's he's a distraction. What do you think you're doing? Nothing at all.
That's so stupid. He's a liar. I have so many points in lying. I you know what?
Fuck it. Watch this. I'm gonna show you how good I am at lying. I didn't shoot anybody. What I can't
it's not gonna they're not gonna talk to me. Can I can I like surrender? Just play dumb and lie.
This time they didn't even know. Stop you violated the law. No I didn't. Oh okay you're right you
didn't. You just shot that person. I didn't shoot anybody. Oh okay yeah you didn't. It's like a Jedi
mind trick. Back to Byzantium you gold plated bastards. Hey what? No one wants you on ground
breaker. See I told you they were they're talking shit about us. Oh real scary. Oh you're really
gonna arrest us on our station? Yeah this is chief junley's ship. You don't own shit here.
Step back by four bylaws to you success.
Okay I did it at least once. You trash.
Wait I have to steal this again. Don't give me freedom in a game. They just. What do you think
you're doing? Whatever I want. Oh my mistake. I want to just steal a bunch of shit in front of
this guy and keep intimidating and lying to him. Is that possible? Like I'm gonna wait for this
guy to go on his route. Take something in front of him and intimidate him every time. Yeah I've done
work for Sublight. Need to pay the bill somehow. Hey oh whatever. All right here we go. Let's get
let's get that again. Go back to Byzantium you gold plated bastards. Yeah no one wants you on
ground breaker. These stairs are board property. Disperse now or I'll detain you for trespassing.
Okay we live here. Yeah this is chief junley's ship. You don't own shit here. Stupid. Step back.
Of course yeah they're gonna. You're gonna attack us? You waste of O2 scrubbers.
You fucking. Fucking algae eaters.
Idiot. Yeah let's go to drink. Yeah hide behind that mask. Fucking still sick of that.
You can smoke in here? Holy shit is that. All right. I don't know you can smoke. What are you
vaping? You're vaping. That's okay. Wait it's talking to quicksave right? Okay you can't give
me this. I have to fucking just move on man. Okay we're good. Back to Byzantium you gold plated
bastards. Get out of here. Go back to. No one wants you on ground breaker. These stairs are board
property. Disperse now or I'll detain you for trespassing. Yeah get the fuck out of here.
You're really gonna arrest us on our station? We have rules here. Yeah this is chief junley's ship.
You don't own shit here. That's right you don't. With space you for trying you. You waste of O2
scrubbers. Yeah O2 scrubbers. Yeah go back. Go back to your. Go back to your station.
We got a date at the lost hope anyway. Remember no smoking citizen. Can you fucking believe some
people? Seriously some people are just so rude. We have. Well we're gonna just let them in.
We're told we we can't let anybody in here. Man like do they really I don't it's not like I
I just we have to enforce the rules. Yeah carry on. Something about being in space gives me the creeps.
I seriously I know what the fuck. I'm Julie doesn't talk very much but I don't understand.
That this job is fucking stressful. Feels like I'm melting. I know every day.
Metaphorically you know and physically it's hot up here. Unless you have business with the board
move along. That's what I mean. Unless you have something to do you have an ID or something like
get the fuck out of here. We're doing. We have to. It's our job to do this.
Waiting for the announcement.
This is when a teacher is going over something in class and the principal goes over the loudspeaker
and everyone. Okay I was in the middle of algebra but. Okay. Ah yes. Wheeler messaged me you were
coming. You must be the captain of the unreliable. A vessel that used to be helmed by one Alex
Hawthorne. And you are not he. Has something happened to my favorite scruffy freelancer.
Forget Alex. Why'd you impound my ship. I'm gonna wring your scrawny neck.
You sprat fuck. Give me back my ship. There's no need for hysterics. This is all a hilarious
misunderstanding. Really. Explain it. Am I laughing about this. Right. Right. You're going
important places I'm sure. Big exciting important places. And I want money too. I've removed the
flag from your ship. I'm terribly sorry for the inconvenience. However before you go. Open the
register. Tell me the location of Phineas Wells. I'm sure you've seen his wanted posters all over
the colony. Did Alex tell you where Wells might be. Anything. This guy's such a pushover. What.
Do I know where Phineas. Yeah. I know where he is. He's up on. He's in like. He's on a satellite.
I'll find. I know where he is. Wait. This is my. Settle out this person. What do you think I know
anything about Wells. Well Alex knew. Or he said he did. And you have his ship. Maybe he kept some
records around or conveniently placed. And I want your mustache too. Give it to me. I know that's
fake. I want to wear it. Nobody talks about Phineas. That's. Well that's just terrible news.
Going to do now. Oh I'm sorry. This is terribly unprofessional of me. Is there anything else I
might help you with. Yeah. Why. Why are you in trouble. It's personal business I'm afraid.
Miserably terribly personal. What can I do. No. Stop playing coy. What's going on. I don't intend
to be. It's just a matter of trust. This is where I start signaling like about is there a bug under
your desk. Like I'm going to put my hands in the air and be like talk talk to like open my hands up
and like under your desk. And then when I. I can nod. We can go somewhere else. How can I win your
trust. Information on the whereabouts of Phineas Wells would go a long way. It's. Well it's my
way. Right on a piece of paper bugged and then hold it up and be like
like that. OK. Information on the whereabouts of Phineas Wells would go a long way. It's. Well
it's my white whale I suppose. All right. Do we sell out the guy that cryogenically unfroze us
or. No. Fuck this guy. It's fine. Really. It's perfectly fine. I understand. Now if you've
nothing else please see yourself out. I'd like to drown myself in work. OK. I need this password
to unlock. What a new password. These guys are all heavily armed. There's no way I can get through
here. Can I steal from him. Just beat him up for the password. That doesn't. No I'm going to get
attacked. This whole thing. If I fire a weapon here this whole town is going to go on lockdown.
No. No no no. I can't. I did what I wanted to do. I was passing through.
Sell out Phineas and you'll get the password. I'll get the password eventually.
What the hell. Sorry about the heat.
Chief Tanison will get the radiators fixed soon. Of course. What if I sell him out and then kill him.
Zero G brew extra refreshing. It's an ale that's good for what else.
Oh and it's not the best choice. It's Spacer's choice. Taste the freedom.
A lot of slogans to keep track of. Sometimes I forget. All right.
How did you get that. I'm bound to satisfy headgear related inquiries. Please send any
complaints to our consumer care headwear division. It's not a complaint. It's I would I want. When
can I get that. You would never ask if you knew what it's like in here. I mean why anyone can be
a Spacer's Choice Consumer Relations Choice Specialist. Just keep your nose clean and aim
for the moon. Talk it. But is there a bug under your desk. Bug. All right. Have a look. Well you
can get them. Huh. Isn't that something. Lie plus five. I need I have to have this. It was made for
this character. How much are they. They're not that expensive. It doesn't show it. Unbelievable.
How could they. How could they. Wait wrong person. OK. I just got freaked out. So I have one on. Hey
you want to join us. You should give our latest product to try.
All the all the talk see free. Get one for Sam with activated charcoal. Don't take my word for it.
See for yourself. We're gonna have one for Sam to make a choice. Spacer's Choice. Hey we're wearing
the same hat. I got you too. I mean. Yeah. Same hat. All right. You are. Looks really good on you.
Sam can't wear it. It's a robot on your giant head. Hope you're very happy in there. Wear it
with pride. No one can take that away from you. OK. What do you got. Have a look. So I can't get it
for Sam. That's unfortunate. But what about. OK. Hack. Is there a lie suit. Oh. Oh. Why do you have
better shit than the person that sells these exclusively. Fun times barrel. I need it. Wait
what does that do. Crit damage 25 percent. Firing noise minus 66 percent. That's pretty good.
Taint plasma. Didn't you guys say get the plasma plasma thing. Maybe I should get plasma. I don't
do. I don't even have one of these already. How much are they. This thing's eight hundred ninety
five dollars. All right. Fine. Fuck it. All right. All right. All right. I need a workbench.
If he does it. All right. This is getting real greedy here. I can't beat this. Just totally
absolutely. No no no no. I mean I'll keep that stuff. I don't want to sell it. All right. Let's
keep going. Hey. What's in the safe. Bless my heart. A stranger come knocking on a poor old
woman's door. You here for a particular reason. Or did the neighbors tell you how good my sugar
cookies are. What made without a single natural ingredient or an oven just like store bought.
OK. What do you have to say. What do you have for sale. Want a charming copper kettle off that
girl who runs the pub. She's a fierce arm wrestler but she's no match for your pal Gladys.
Hey this lady just speaks in riddles. Plasma rifle. Axe candy. All right. Fine. I'll say I
need money. I don't have any money. OK. Too bad. Holy shit. How do I take this from you.
How I steal that. That's insane. OK. Well let's talk about stuff. Why is it hot in here.
Buy candy. Or is it just my glands acting up again. All right. Phineas sent me. He said you
could sell me a nav key to Stellar Bay. Those have been the height of illegality since Stellar Bay
turned their noses up at the board. You and I could be thrown to the void just for discussing
such a transaction. Well the guy that's on the board is a wuss. Groundbreaker is a free port.
We're outside of the board's control. For the time being at least. Now I only have the one nav key
and they're hard to come by these days. It won't be cheap. If you find yourself lacking in the bits
I might have an opportunity you'd be interested in. OK. It's ten thousand bits.
Oh my god. No one's ever found my bits lacking. Any chance of a discount. Phineas. That old kook.
He was quite the dancer back in his prime. Did he tell you? Bria lied on his feet.
Bria lied in the wallet too. He still owes me a small fortune. Laws. Maybe I should charge you
and maybe I should vaporize you. And that's when we both silent
for like a full 10 to 20 seconds and then finally she cracks.
Well I find I'm in need of a ship captain with a little
more of flexibility. Vaping. Might be this could help out the groundbreaker as well as earn some
bits. But if you've got qualms. Well qualms. Let's talk about the details. What are the jobs
do you know about? What do you got? Anything else? You might want to acquaint yourself with
June Lay Tennyson. Groundbreaker's chief. She's been trying to get a handle on this heat problem
we've got. You'll find her fretting in engineering. I'd say she's a sweet girl but lawful offends
someone call me a liar. OK. Yes dearie. I'm ready to look into it. Ain't that just a treat. So
you know Edna over in engineering. On occasion she'll pass along transmissions I might find
interesting. She sent me a recording of a distress signal she'd scraped from the
groundbreaker's calm array. Curious thing is it came from an outpost called Roseway. Roseway.
And Auntie Cleo abandoned that place years ago. That's where I need to go.
Say no more. I'm in.
You've got an ear for intrigue and a nose for bits. I like that. Here's a copy of the SOS
recording complete with the coordinates. If you should find a secret worth selling
might be I could find a buyer. Corporate bigwigs will pay top bit for inside information on their
competitors. The more we got the corpse fighting each other the less time they got to meddle in
our affairs. Abandoned outpost corporate secrets. Got it. Don't forget to come find old Gladys when
you're done. Thanks for your time. Anytime sweetheart. You know where to find me. Here
take a candy with you. Nice. That just kind of scared the shit out of me for a second.
Okay so here's the thing. I got moon man helmet and okay so I'm at 60
lying. I need to increase my weapons but it's only gonna uh inspiration. Companion abilities. You can
order companions to do special attacks. Okay let's at least get that. Now how do I go over
50? I remember to explain it. Okay let's see. Up to rank 50. After 50 you can add points directly
to specialized skills. So I have to actually add it. It doesn't work like this. Okay I see.
60 lie is scrambled auto chemicals attack at their normal speed. I gotta do some more weapons
like handguns or long guns or something. Minimum armor penetration. Yeah something like that.
Same thing with long guns. Long guns headshot it does 20 more damage at 50.
All right let's do this because it'll do both of these and then get try to get this to 50.
Dodge though. Yeah I know this character is horrible. Don't worry I know. You can command
your companions to use their special abilities on the enemy you are targeting. Companion one ability
companion two ability. Okay cool. Perk. Uh not that one. Vendor prices. That's actually pretty
good. 20 percent. I already have 10 11 percent so that'll be 30 plus percent. I'm rating few more
bits. Additional ammo stock on vendors. Companion crit chance. Minus one weapon armor durability
loss. That's pretty good. That one's good too. They're all good. I think I'm gonna do this one.
You can just repair them. Yeah recharge rate for the I don't know. I think I'm just gonna do
the this this tactical time dilation recharge rate. Yeah let's do it.
All right let's continue. I got a lot of random things to do. So uh I have to go
talk to Jun Jun Lee Tennyson or I could go do this. I could get Sam. The distress signal has a
nav coordinate embedded in it. Play it on your ship so that Ada can get to the Roseway landing
pad. All right we're gonna do this. We're gonna get out of here. We'll do that. We'll come back
into this part after. This is a bathroom. Ada. All right let's do modify. So I was going to what
was I gonna do? I have the scope right? This is times two. What's on it right now? Okay this is
power. This is times two. What's on it right now? Current extend aside is already on it.
Shit okay well I'm not gonna put no I'm not gonna put plasma on the sniper. Don't worry
nothing on this one yet. All right this is the one. I was gonna put plasma on the revolver.
Now wait this is the new one that I stole. This is an assault rifle. Plasma on the assault rifle.
Yep look at this thing. This thing's fucking nuts and it's got an extendo sight.
Exacto sight? Put an extendo sight on it too. No I'm gonna keep this one on. All right now what
did I want to do with you? Nothing. You just get the fuck out of here. You're useless now.
Actually not really. All right well that's enough. Wait where is it? 73? I don't have enough money to
do this. Fuck. Damn it. Well wait break down these pistols. I bought a bunch of bullshit.
Who are you? Hey you got a second? You got you got like a bunch of sleeping bags and stuff. Are
you trying to come onto the ship here? Fancy running into you again. Don't mind me. It's just
admiring your ship from up close. Gotta hand it to you boss. That's a fun looking ship.
Only thing it's missing is me. No. I get it. Get lost. You don't like seeing a guy stake that next
to your ship. Looks like I'm trying to ambush you or sell you something. Just give me a shot. That's
all I'm asking. No. I could be the best damn crew you ever hired. I've heard enough of you. All
right Felix tell me why should I hire you? Okay Felix consider this your interview.
If you're trying to convince me to hire you you're doing it you're going about it all wrong.
Oh okay well can you give me a couple of pointers? Sure I'll help you out here.
Don't beg. Tell me why I need you on my crew. Hey that's good advice. I like the way you think
boss. Not your boss. I never will be. Besides not like there's a line of folks standing around
hoping to get on your ship. I'm persistent. I'm eager and I'm showing initiative. What else do
you want on your crew? Um how about an interview? Sure an interview. That sounds fair. I mean first
time for everything right? Ask me anything you like. Okay what's the value of pie? Uh it's delicious
mock apple pie and a tripe kale crust maybe with a little cream on top. Classic.
That was that was an alleviate the mood interview joke.
But that's kind of overdone at this point. I don't that's that's like that's so
people do that that's so cliche now. What's your biggest flaw?
Norman told me my biggest problem was that I didn't take orders. I told him my problem
it's not with authority it's with jackasses. So yeah I guess my biggest flaw is that I don't
suffer idiots. Hope that's not a deal breaker. It is. Well I tried my best. I appreciate you
giving me another shot at least. Why? If you change your mind I'll be right here in the docking base.
Never gonna leave. He wouldn't have looked as good as you do in that mask. Yeah he told me he doesn't
suffer idiots and everyone if you're if you're just dumber than me I don't like you. It's like
okay I'm dumb. So leave. That was his mistake. I gave him a chance. He made like a shitty cliche
this is a fun interview joke and then I wasn't feeling it because that's kind of cliche and then
he said he doesn't like stupid people and I'm stupid. You want me to hire that person?
Not gonna happen. Welcome back captain. How can I be of assistance? I picked up a distress call.
Play it for me. Yes captain beginning playback now. There's viscera and death everywhere.
Gunfire gnashing teeth. They're unemployed. For law's sake if anyone's receiving this please send
help. What? Captain we are now capable of accessing the Roseway landing pad. Also corporate protocol
requires that all distress signals include a list of key personnel for retrieval. The embedded names
are Anton Crane, Von Cortez, and Orson Shaw. Okay goodbye. See you soon captain. No no no.
Terra 2. Roseway landing pad. We're now in orbit above Roseway captain. Cool all right let's go.
Roseway. Yeah scene three is got me wearing a mask now. This is the worst fucking acting gig
I've ever done. What? It pays all right. I'm gonna stick with it. Where's my friend? All right let's
do uh not the distress signal. The doom that came to Roseway. Distress call uh tomorrow. No no no.
The cleaning machine. There it is. This way? Wait I deselected him? How the fuck did I do that?
The unreliable narrator. Oh I see underneath. There it is. Okay what's this? Insert captain's
identification cartridge to initiate remote landing. I think I already did that. Follow me.
Let's take out the all right wait wait wait wait wait wait. Dead eye assault rifle. Let's check it
out. Ooh yep nice. Good thing I'm so glad I stole this. Is there a wall here? Of course there is.
Adventure does favor the bold. Does. Did I scream? Was it him? This is a silent protagonist. They
don't scream. We all scream for ice cream. I did half of it. I didn't do the other half though.
See if I can get this right in the head. Won't get any mercy from me. Wow. Fate shines on us today.
This thing is pretty good from that far away. Yeah that's what we're making pretty damn good
progress. Nice. Wow we actually are can kill things now. All it took was a little bit of
thievery. I'm sorry. I didn't. You're smart enough to not run fast into this. Everything's fine. I'm
good. Just eat an apple. Eat a can of tuna. All right. Acid steeper is in there. It's a workbench.
All right. Is it where we have to be careful? Give me my my revolver. Yeah. Yep. Yes. Do the
tuna sound. What does the tuna sound? What does that mean? Oh shit. Do your super move. Over there.
What? He has a knife now? What is going on? Oh he's dead. So it does a cut scene.
Oh okay that's weird. Can I heal you? I could spend hours reflecting on the secret workings
of the universe. Little else in this colony offers such a relaxing pastime. So tell me
what's on your mind. I excel at confessional listening. Okay slow down. Cleanliness isn't
much of a priority I take it. Oh no like wait. If you need to get into the armory and don't have
the code ask me. If I'm not around check the front desk at the antibiotics lab. No. God damn it.
Where's the where's the antibiotics lab? Is it auntie or auntie? I thought it was
auntie. Where where is that? I don't have any lock picking skill. Shit. Why can't you be a lock
picker? There's no other way to get in there. I have to go find that person. Oh that don't work.
Ow. Oh my god. Is this a boss? That thing was insane. Okay what were you what were you guarding?
No nothing. Who's calling me? Oh no there's a bunch of them. I have to we have to leave.
This is not going to work out. Holy shit there's somebody right at the front door.
Super move. Oh wow that was awesome. Nice work. Oh still alive. All right that was pretty cool.
I gotta say. All right there's a chest over here. Oh wait a minute. Smaller than a prison cell.
Come on you have to passcode. Thank god. The password I think was one two three four by the
way. What's that? Toothpaste? Okay we did it. That was hot. I don't know okay is that let me go over
something very quickly you guys. So before the stream started somebody I don't know who you
might even still be here. Somebody said dude you should do the whole stream in a Boston accent.
And I keep thinking back to that person and I'm doing it because I'm thinking about them
saying it. All right here we go. Like you're in my head. All right what is this? Armory logs. Force
flog the flogistinator pistol. Force flogisticotron pistol status functional untrained
personnel must attend site safety seminar before using as a seminar officer is not currently
available recommend permanent secure storage ammunition entry is not found where do I get
that uh where do I get the flogistinator plasma carbine what's that do acid steeper there it is
energy cells I think that's all there is to do in here I could keep going down is there anything
else in here there's something else in rose way the stress signal the schematics for orson's
prototype would likely be valuable to gladis the stress call from the broadcast tower and
company secrets schematics yeah there it is so there is something down here maintenance logs
is this too much info no it's not there's one sentence we don't have a replacement someone
tried to disable the mandatory consumer broadcast on 17 the thing got stuck in maximum volume mode
until we factory reset it 12 it's serious malfunction today we shut it down for now
no response on the behavior modules for the time being we'll have to just uh hype in the chat
whatever it says where's your uh belly why don't you not have a belly everyone you keep seeing
everyone it's just me mono lens oh boy the cartridges okay let's get the schematic
um detailed drawings of an advanced pistol revisions and comments are scrawled across
the image in mostly illegible writing except for the name orson shaw scribbled in the corner
the schematics depict a flog pistol from a brand name force which is not native to the halcyon
colony it is unclear from these plans what a flog does okay i got plans energy cell what's up here
okay investigate rose where to find potential company secrets that could be sold to the highest
bidder so i have one of the company secrets but there's also this distress call and i want to see
what it's what's going on over here so we're gonna go that way i'm not just gonna skip everything i
want to just i want to see what's going on this is a lot of shit you know that you didn't check
literally half the room i don't have time for that here they come what are you doing out here
guys what the fuck kill him where's my where's my guy where's my guy ow what okay that was just
gurr from invader zim sorry i didn't mean to kill you gurr that was an ambush annoying
me distress call we can't leave not yet is that the dumb robot dog yes except it's not
dog it's a robot that's in a dog costume because then he can blend in as the dog and
that's like you know you've seen the show and then sometimes sometimes he goes
and everyone laughs everyone thinks it's fun
don't they go that's right don't mess with us and then sometimes he'll go i want pancakes
runs out of the room it's not a bad show the sign don't open raptidons raptidons what is a
raptidon and lemonade boss fight incoming it's a raptidon boss fight i got that info from my
you good right it uh i don't think we can do anything about this i think you just have to
stay there should i shoot it so just to put it what happened that's summoned god that was weird
well how do i i can't get rid of it i can't i can't explode anything
are there people over here no this is monsters may the law have mercy on you i won't
huh oh shit you're not
everyone all right
all right well i'm done with you because you don't you're not doing anything check everything
people get really mad at me if i don't check everything they go he didn't check the boxes
over there there was stuff in him he didn't check the scientist's bodies he didn't open the chest
that was over here i know i understand burk corporate recruit wait so we're good
are they bad are they good bad or good they're probably good hello i don't have enough of this
shit i'm just the fucking tarmac guard no one said nothing about fighting no raps uh did you
send a distress call distress call from here shit they told me that weren't allowed
what wait what got me i just do what i'm told i was told not to do such uh who's in charge
scientist name anton crane someone said he's panicking inside the comm center it actually
looks pretty calm out here alarms went off raps broke loose and i hightailed it in here to get
a wall between me and them beasts you said the raps broke loose did you have them in a cage
um forget i said anything about that okay oh before i forget anti-cleo's i see anti-cleo's
better than nature anti not like that crappy basers choice i had it right actually i think
i need to do something here don't i uh solution uh distress signal no no no long tomorrow
no i thought i could get uh oh it's a doctor i like you if you've come to end my life
let's be on with it oh not actually one of them are you no did you send the distress call you kind
of look like the guy that sent the distress call right the first time i hear to end your life
if i knew who he was he'd already be dead what i um i'm anton crane the lead scientist here
i must apologize if my call diverted you i may have panicked everything's under control now
though truth be told what did you think i was why one of our attackers of course obviously they
were drawn here in an attempt to make off with my research why cancel the distress call my research
may not quite fall within legal parameters illegal dead i'm under orders to maintain wireless
however having your head used as target practice can addle one's thinking
i cut the call immediately once i've gathered my width so it was a home office can't know what's
happening here oh yeah tell me what you're actually doing here or i will let them know myself
and take great joy in doing so i might add thank you doctor max i appreciate that if i don't get
that research back my life has got me backed up we were tasked with formulating a new and improved
dental gel dental gel yes i see very important uh what's the dental gel toothpaste one cannot
exaggerate the benefits of good dental hygiene may i continue please do while doing research
on enzymes specific to the raptidons digestive system we developed an additive which we
subsequently discovered to be the most effective appetite suppressant ever uh you can couch it
however you like it's still just toothpaste uh diet toothpaste not just any diet toothpaste
the ultimate diet toothpaste that's like discovering the best rocket fuel ever
oh i'm certain it could be made into that as well with only a few changes to its molecular
i'm just the ogre from warcraft you're missing the point let's focus for a moment shall we
even if you disregard the obvious value of auntie cleo's apazap diet toothpaste in and of itself
we're talking about my career here toothpaste oh how absolutely adequate toothpaste good
that's i'm speaking twice with two different heads uh auntie cleo's apazap diet toothpaste in itself
nice is it not came up with that myself oh yeah an ogre mage almost as befuddled as my co-workers
here what do you want from me hours ago a group of vicious malcontents fell upon us
shot up our labs and loosed our research subjects the raptidons if those cretins get their hands on
my research well they'll need not kill me remove the cretins retrieved this research check you want
should i handle your rapidon problem yes but don't kill our mother if it's avoidable we've
need of her to replenish our stocks i think there's gas in the lab somewhere that can be
used to put them out the research is in the safe in my office you'll have need of my code and key
card the lab's entrance is in the side of a hill you can't miss it if you just follow the road
you'll pass by the town's original by the grand architect jameson he's in the old lab who's jameson
my protege i sent him to retrieve some metabolic precursors and i forgot him how do you forget
what you forgot him you left him to die you should be ashamed of yourself don't you think it weighs on
me he was my responsibility all of them were ah regardless of their thinking on the matter yet
you send me to do this if he has died too many have been lost too many black marks against my
name and far too much paperwork yeah yeah you're gonna have to give up your swishy latex doctor
uniform hang it up i don't like you much but i'll look into further i'll find them rescue james
important message please read that's a really important message you're right thanks for sharing
that oh i watched the like the i watched the uh-oh video by the way and i was just sitting there
with just going okay okay i i laughed once i laughed one time and it was just only because of
when he goes like i'm just like okay this is like fucked up that's it the other like three
minutes of that video does i'm not happy that i watched if this jameson is fated to die it'll
be pointless to intervene let me get made it to save him good that's a good take okay we need to do
uh buy his bootstraps jameson is missing yeah fine and you've been asked to recover research
data from the safe and anton crane's office and its office is an auntie cleo's corporation's
secret lab which lies at the end of the paved road out of the way eliminate the outlaws deal
with the rap raptidons i'm just gonna go get it now this he's down there too anton's research
sounds like it'd be valuable to gladys art so these are all kind of in the same they're in the
same spot let's do let's move oh we're in a right cleaning machine let's go do that first
why does he got why does he look like a recently escaped dentist patient
patient no he looks like it he looks like a recently escaped dentist the batman villain
no this is a bio shock villain all right it's right here this is easy let's go with uh i need
to use some of my other weapons i stole the best weapon revolver time there's a lot of vending
machines here what the fuck whoa i don't have any money wow that looks cool auto whoa okay
very important you guys have a lot of very important messages for me tonight i appreciate
them i appreciate those messages just like i appreciate you i appreciate you thank you for
those important appreciated messages thank you very important i appreciate you who am i talking
to though i'm seeing you singular but it doesn't that's impossible install the asset steeper
initiating sequences customer this sam unit is unable to locate your registered information
would you like to register your sam yes registering new owner captain uh
uh welcome to the crew sam sam units live to clean and clean to live
wait where are you going where are you going where are you going where are you going
battery levels are fully charged uh sam i'm decommissioning you from service you're
fired good work sam customer all cleaning tasks have been completed scheduling next round of
cleaning to commence in four minutes uh where'd you come from all sam units travel
fully assembled in a 12 by 12 corrugated steel box no i mean i want to know more about you
did you know sam units are capable of equipping regulation grade flamethrower nozzles upgrade
your attachment today and get to firing away hmm uh what do you say sam you want to help me
clean up this colony got stubborn stains leave them for sale this is a south park voice
got stubborn stains leave them for sale okay um back to work skills all right here we go
i think i'm thinking of doing let's get uh 10 points available i'm at 60 to lie
i think it's time to do let's get a
62 i'm doing 10 points in the handguns lock picking nah but hacking and
was it 25 is what you need yeah 25 is what most of these are at isn't it and that makes me a 30
hacking okay i can sell goods to the vending machine now doors and containers requiring one
mag pick to unlock are free to open and then this sneak attacks attack unaware enemies will
crouch to deal bonus damage i mean i'm 60 handguns let's do get that and then let's do the rest of
handguns sounds good to me new perks important what's important uh the image of my face on a
computer screen with my teeth zoomed in that is really important you're right i
okay you can keep this all right so how do we get let's go sam what is sam's uh inventory
all right let's do bad let's go pass to anywhere we need to do uh go find jamison
did he just can he just come with me he doesn't use normal guns yet
what there we go okay cool let's go i have my two companions now look and we're even color
coordinated this is perfect okay sam you do can i give you a hat i can i can i can give him a hat
sam's equipment is permanently attached to his frame and cannot be removed never mind uh let's
do threat generated yeah i want you to be the tank so we're gonna do base health or let's do
threat generated intimidate that's actually pretty good too yeah more threat all right look
we are we're the dentist team i love it let's move save jamison sam sprays toothpaste really
that's so cool what a lovely team all right fine jamison so that's new in the other fallout games
you can only have one companion then even in fallout 4 was the one other fallout games this
is not a fallout game all right all right okay yeah okay this is not a fallout game it's not
this is not a fallout game and not even close it's not even close you're right
i correct my statement about this is not even close hey help do something do something
what happened to the dentist did he get crushed i just quick saved it right here like a fucking
idiot oh my god i'm gonna die okay we're good dust accumulation analysis 2.5 years go back to the
ship sam but there was the way there was a crash ship over here so i want to see what the hell it
is can i do anything with the ship can i go inside the ship can i look inside the ship i cannot let's
go all right slow down can i not walk over this scout the area yep one that way one over there
monsters and shit over that way let's go over here how does sam sneak i guess you just don't get
him toothpaste him nice oops special move let's see what's up good work sweep of the area epic
level all right let's go save jamison come to me coming over to you okay there's a lot of shit
in here that i have to do remind me let's take out the revolver for this part i don't need any
of this stuff i thought heels do i have eight that's kind of low but not too low i don't even
know i'm picking up plasma rifle i'm gonna become over and oh hack okay all personnel please report
to assign workstations tired of itchy acid burns try anti-cleo's artisanal borst scented moisturizing
cream lock hallway door unlocked as his protocol unauthorized entry we marked in site supervisor
crane a's records got messages here uh i guess there you go screenshot screenshot screenshot
so you can read them on your own time okay let's move actually important question what
am i doing for thanksgiving streaming let him fight let him fight let him fight let him fight
let him fight might kill in the name of the law whoa uh because uh already we already did
thanksgiving we did it a little early because i have some dietary restrictions now
because i have an endoscopy coming up in a few days so i couldn't really eat thanksgiving on
thanksgiving if that makes any sense because yeah i picked a bad time i guess to have an
appointment skip but yeah i didn't that kind of just how it played out but yeah i have i have a
couple of dietary restrictions starting uh now so yeah it was it was good that was part of the
reason why the stream was only like four and a half hours last night because uh we did all that
experimental notes screenshot it screenshot it wait no no this is important no that's not important
that's not important either minor stomach pain and nausea safe major stomach pain deliberate
debilitating nausea vomiting unsafe so don't drink this all right jamison is over here
wait where's the mother don't have to save the mother don't kill the mother right how do i tell
well who's a mom that's a great acting for justice to prevail cannot use while in combat
am i still in combat what's still fighting us messages from crane please feel free to enjoy
one 10 minute break between your normally scheduled three o'clock and four o'clock patrol
shifts this guy's a dick seriously i'm working for this person oh can't get it any more of those
little things i'm gonna run out of room here oh there's one right here shit should i do it
i'm doing it shock cannon i gotta uh i'm not over encumbered i'm gonna be getting close here soon
okay let's go pick the lock hey did someone lift the lock down me what do you got in here
what else you got in here anything else what are you storing in here take it okay what's that money
is your personal stash good come with me what how the hell did you get in here i've walked i'm
very sneaky who cares let's get you out of here i care about the front door this is an egregious
breach of protocol how'd you get it uh truth be told the raptidons did most of the work on the
door not sure they know what a lock is uh anton sent me to get you can't use the centrifuge without
supervision can't file reports without him double checking their every word can't save myself from
mortal peril it's like he thinks i'm a child his hands-on management style is coming to a point
of contention i tell you you're upset that he sent me to rescue you take it up with him if you'd like
now go before my before more wraps find this place yeah like take it up with him i have nothing to
do with this wait there's other stuff here well it wasn't even real all right there's other shit to
do here uh jameson is pissed off otherwise fine head back to rosway to give in the news
fine and and safe eliminate the outlaws deal with the wrap raptidons okay return to gladys no
okay this one no it's this one so eliminate the outlaws and the raptidons so that's downed
in the lab i guess maybe somewhere we're gonna go take a look is there a way for me to go down
there is okay uh do you think here's a little trick i learned in prison
you went to prison live watch out he can do this very often
anymore i think that's it no you're going the wrong way okay so let's get this get this
get this oh a hack i can hack this anti riot gear i'll take it all right now over here i have to
deal with the raptidons don't kill the mother i'm gonna fuck this up the mother's probably gonna die
right over here wait is it just up there hold on it's just in that room i guess it's just in here
oh this is the wrong lab wrong place oh okay all right all right all right all right well
all right can i fast travel anywhere wait a minute fine and safe so we're gonna go back this way
wrong planet you're on the wrong planet that would be stupid all right truth be told
this weapon is the only weapon i have that's worth using the revolver isn't doing much damage
don't i'm dead okay i'm not dead i can't believe you guys made it slow
i just like watching them do it okay here we go there's a scrap mechanic thing over here
deal with the outlaws right i think i have to kill the everything we'll find out
i wanted to sneak into a secret lab by crawling through the fence like they do in the cereals
i guess not let's go cohort lab that's my signature for falling off a cliff is saying don't
yeah i can sell all these shotguns save it okay i need to do gas on the mother
do i have any do i have gas that's a huge splash damage too are we good
wait that's the last of them okay ma thought it said mother i was like well that's great
all right got tail i did so the way to go down but let me just let me look around well it's not all
about going as fast as possible sometimes you just need to take a minute and pick up everything
and either sell it immediately and not even i probably not even gonna look at it in my inventory
once but it's money
so eliminate the outlaws and then the raptidons and then the data is over there so let's just go
let's do the raptidons first all right well i guess we're doing this first that guy's got a
heavy machine gun burning with the toothpaste nice work what you got can i take that thing
jeweled ring i think he had a heavy weapons gun in parts good all right uh outlaws uh
raptidons this way messages good news and bad news bad news is that we've got a sprat problem
the good news is that my have fastos hammers clobbered your precious rizzo's rangers would
you care for some anti-cleo's trip kale pasta sauce with your humble pie okay you'll need to
sedate them manually bring a few canisters of sedative and hook it up to the auxiliary
terminal in the main research chamber bring a few canisters of sedative and hook it up to the
auxiliary terminal in the main research chamber after don okay i have here a form proving the
relocation of our raptidon mother to the main hall a form signed by you first of all the structural
integrity of our raptidon tanks are not nearly sufficient to contain an enraged raptidon mother
secondly raptidons are notoriously territorial and extremely protective of the young please
stop me if i'm using too many numbers for you seeing how you don't seem to realize that
raptidon mother plus raptidon tank equals murder all right what's this sedative canister
is guaranteed to render even the largest raptidon unconscious been no less than six
hours and has a refreshing antiseptic scent all right okay there she is so
where do i put the canister in to knock them all out i guess we'll find it eliminate the outlaws
wait just shoot it all right turn it on you need three sedative canisters
run run run what's quick load uh so i need three canisters i get more money if i do it this way
i've walked by one and i'm never looking at it and going that looks a little odd what's that thing
damn it can i i'm not sure i can they're inside there's another one okay so that's one two
i need one more we see one let me know there are two more inside wait inside the actual chamber
so i just run up can i wait you guys wait here can i tell them to wait i just ran past two of them
oh i didn't what are you talking about where so i have two one two three
i would do they actually have one coming back up in here let me see no no no
that all right easy hey over here oh good you're not shooting at me
doing fine and safe it's been a bit of a day so i'll get to the point yes i have crane's research
no i'm not giving it back sorry to disappoint you what are you talking about who the fuck is crane
i suppose it does not matter either crane sent you or you are some scavenger come to
rob me in my moment of weakness let's make a deal i'd like to go on living you'd probably like to
make some money no i'm not out of here and i will pay you for your trouble
okay uh or i could just shoot you and skip all the hassle make me a deal your life is in my hands
right now a good turn trust me i'll make it worth your while but that's uh you need to
my while is worth a lot i am good for my word you will be equitably rewarded on my honor
but i will not haggle or bargain with you until you help me
huh well why are you down here the same reason you are more than likely i imagine we picked up
the same tip secret research facility minimal security i like how that was a lie even though
you as your character are too dumb to even remember who crane was yeah it could be either way but it
is if you're just if you're dumb and you don't remember is not remembering a lie
we've had that conversation on this stream before if i said something i don't remember it did i
lie about it or was it just too stupid to not to not remember it now i'm not a bandit like you
oh please i'm not shaking down valuables from hapless travelers i'm stealing corporate secrets
this is an underground lab off the radar that means their research is secret
and secrets are always valuable granted diet toothpaste is not exactly what comes to mind
when i imagine it's too stupid to not remember it so you remembered it no other way do you like
diet toothpaste can you imagine a more pernicious example of corporate materialism i do not know
what is worse working here or dying here i've been watching the vod and your tarot rant made
me really sad can't believe people don't fucking read on the toilet thank you welcome welcome back
to the stream thank you all right you went through all this trouble to steal a formula
for diet toothpaste i already know the secret what matters is that i have been lied to i was led to
believe this was a high priority corporate facility hiding valuable research this job was
not supposed to end with me stuck in some wretched lab smelling like rats so i would be very much
obliged if you gave me a break what do you need the first thing i need is a key card to unlock my
door then i'd need you to clear me a path out of here there are two ways out the quickest is
through the front door but cleo security's bottled up in there if you don't want to shoot them i
suppose you could talk to them the other way out is through the loading bay but you'd have to clear
out the wraps for me then i could just slip out the back side unseen kill her and take the recipe
for diet toothpaste yourself you will be the best dumb space dentist uh and it was a word you might
have made off of this research even he even called you cretins all right i'm gonna need a good reason
for the risk my neck because crane is a tool because no good deed goes unrewarded because doing
me a good turn is the honorable and decent thing take your pick okay um we're going in a circle
why should i do this for you i am willing to go halves with you halves not good enough
and i will gladly negotiate with you but only why should i do this for me because of this well what
do i need to do you need to do this well why should i help you because i'm gonna give you this money
well that's not good enough what why do i need to do this well because of this well why should i do
that i'm going around a circle all right let's go you might be the first stroke of luck i've had
all day whoa whoa wait what i'm in your debt recover the data that's i can't recover i'm this
is the data uh don't flatter yourself on my honor you will be well rewarded okay sit tight take your
time i am to my chagrin not going anywhere no you aren't all right so now i have to i have to get
you out of here so we have to clear the rat okay raptidons clear i need one more of those uh one
more of those things one more canister i'm gonna do the raptidon way this person friendly i could
i said i could talk to them okay um i'm supposed to give her the outlaws why are they not attacking
me now i what because i talked to her carry on i treated new vegas like a joke treating outer
worlds like a super serious role playing game well i have one rebuttal to you and that is there's no
console command to spawn easy peets so what do you want me to tell you there is why did you just tell
me that i played new vegas fairly normally until i spawned a deathclaw and then the whole game was
ruined like after 12 hours in the game i don't have squad leader how come i can't talk to the
squad leader i could get that could kill two birds with one stone here eliminate the outlaws
all right what what seriously what do i what do i care let's go ready guys i've had quite enough
of you wait i didn't it wasn't my command he just did that on his own
i've had quite enough no no max max settle down oh shit okay do it do it do it
this person's getting that person's still playing the arcade machine okay why are they running this
way holy shit the knees go go get them that's just an upgraded version of you you can do it
oh no no you can't this is 862 damage on the reload again jeremy what the fuck oh shit okay
okay bandits currently being eliminated i don't work with bandits i'm sorry i just don't no you're
literally working one with one right now you don't know that you don't think why i'm not going to
double cross this person this person's not my best friend print security key card
key card deployed thank you for using argos i have an escape route release cassandra
not yet open this too grenade launcher oh boy that's a good one that's considered a long weapon
isn't it i hope so look at all the stuff that's in here it's actually easier just to tap
then hold excuse me all right i want to do the um over encumbered i knew it was going to happen
eventually uh we can break down some stuff let's go to uh what do i have that i want to break down
these security blades who cares i don't need them break them down security blade break it down
this ore oh that's pretty good okay get rid of i have to tactical shotgun just get rid of it
tactical shot i'm not going to use it i really am not i already have one
uh light pistol i already have one assault rifle i already have something better
my shovel i might need it uh for anything okay what about armor look at all this crap
i'm all right i'm not in comfort anymore all right so now
pendor eliminate the outlaws and i wanted to wanted to rapidon thing
i need to find one more of those canisters scream if you see a canister it's important
the fastest way for me to time people out without doing anything hello
i smite you in the name of you get in there oh like this i smite you in the name of the law
i don't need to be using my other pistol all right give me another canister
i'm not ready to leave yet who the fuck are you uh you damn turncoat we saw everything
so what do we do guys um should we go negotiate what do you think what should
the three dentists need to come to an agreement here battery levels are recharged thank you
customer you don't have any info we guarantee it's the only sanitation and maintenance unit
you'll ever need okay back to work i'm gonna be ready i'm i'm ready now okay here we go
so door closed door opens and this guy with grenade launcher now you must think me a fool
i was watching on the security cameras you got downright friendly with the outlaw leader
i reckon we got nothing to say to each other you best back yourself out of here nice and slow
it wasn't me ease off the trigger hear me out nobody needs to die at least of all me
ease off hear me out for a second you got one minute starting now somebody's walking around
with a mask i i convinced cassandra to let you leave in peace the labs are wrecked the staff's
half dead the outlaws just want to leave let them go yeah i mean i convinced cassandra let you leave
in peace you convinced her to let us leave in peace listing the ills we've been done ain't exactly
putting me in a mind to compromise yeah look around uh i can't change what's done i can change
what happens from here just walk out i think it's that easy huh you fly in with your fancy ship
say a few words and everyone gets a happy ending i think it can be easy if you decide to let it be
i don't think walking away from a fight's ever easy because andrew can't win you can't win
why throw more lives away i'm the one that wins i let them walk doc crane will be so far up my ass
everything will smell of neither of you get to win this is my video game i don't see any better
solution fine damn it we'll pull out that was easy that was very easy that was extraordinarily easy
easy
what is going on outside what happened who did they think they got attacked
they started killing each other for all they know the person in front of this person turned
around and shot him so then it was like gun out gun out gun out put it down put it down and
today i'll just kill each other that's fucking ridiculous okay well we're still we're good we
don't wear we cosplay of chaos bored go check hold on no don't open that door
eliminate the outlaws okay you have a poison dagger
one of the recruits one of those just random guards was like a spy see i didn't all i need to
do is just sew the discord i didn't need to do anything okay i need another canister look
i'm one second away from just blowing you away where where's a canister i need one more of these
damn things this is in the room is there one in the raptor room not that i can see just eating
people up here um damn it i want to do this it's in the it's in one of the closets in the back
really how do i tell them to stop like stay all right i'm on my way don't move just stay
okay so you tell me there's one down here what about in here no shit okay no this is dangerous
this is too dangerous i'm out follow me heading back you don't talk about in here are you not in
this one are you you talk about in there okay let me try it once if i can't do this then i can't do
it but i'm gonna try to sneak oh shit oh shit okay hold on stop oh fuck i'm i'm spotted dude
if he didn't scream he just he like screamed and it it's over here yep it is over here all right
let's see can i just can i do it all right let me out close the door okay help is it gonna happen
shit where's the where's the mother i thought i could do it from this terminal all right save
again turn around go that way go eat that body okay ventilate gas it's hitting me too okay can
i breathe this in what what's going on what wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait
wait wait wait back it up back it up back it up what's going on i don't have to like pick it up
and deliver it i thought he was like keep that mother alive and bring her to me in one piece
that's not what happened i just have to knock them out they just had to sleep oh i thought i was
doing this for a very specific reason okay we're in fucking combat god damn it why are you guys
following me out here ah so there's no reason to do this this is just like a second way to do the
exact same thing that's kind of boring it's no there's extra money yeah it has to be all right
let's go so they'll just come get it i get it okay eliminate the outlaws part two wait eliminate
the outlaws oh you are an out yeah right uh we're gonna have to do a meeting of the dentists over
here i think dentist huddle so um where's my money i've never been so pleased at the side of an open
door please tell me you've cleared a way out of here multiple ways ask away i have got nothing
but time what do you intend to do with this research of course i don't have any use for the
scribblings of idiotic scientists but whoever gave me this toothpaste assuming i make it out
of this place alive and with my ship out of commission i'll have to leave on foot and hope
my luck changes one problem at a time i suppose uh you act like the corporations are your enemy
what do you have against them from the day we are born we are made to obey never question never hope
never dream of anything greater than a lot appointed to us and in your case never doing
an honest day's work apparently that's right never a dentist day's work expect us to work until the
day we die but they could not give a half bit shit about our lives uh why would you and your
crew raid on i can't throw a fellow dentist under the bus that's not how this work establishment
tells us to live here work there eat that drink this all our choices are made for us so we forget
we ever had a choice she's an anti-dentist i am doing this because i can because it thrills me
because i take a deep and profound pleasure from stabbing at the heart of corporate power
no matter how shallow the wound she's talking shit about us right now
oh she's a cavity
you can't i'm sorry but you cannot expect me to throw a fellow dentist under the bus
yeah so you go ahead i am much obliged and now if you do not mind i have had quite enough of this
wretched place this might be tough ender nice shot fellow dentist
is easy you know fucking i'm not gonna give you a chance this is for the dentists you are
you gonna steal the toothpaste on us don't think so
oh
get the reward what do you mean the reward i have a duty okay but just keep her locked in there
reward then kill i've never been so pleased at the side of an open door
please tell me you've cleared a way out of here what do you mean the reward she's gonna
here don't make me regret it so you have i am much obliged and now if you do not know we're
gonna let this settle i have had quite enough of this the dentist shit is on is high right now
we have a lot of tension here we got three dentists versus an anti-dentist
i'm gonna i'm gonna take the reward take care of yourself out there uh keep the research i want
the reward and we'll see you later max max no max max max god damn it i try to be the
mediator wait i can't how do i get a reward if she's ashes i can't even loot her body
come on you burned the research get the plans from her first oh god damn it wait what's that
save this doesn't look right this looks incorrect why is it different do i have the plans rescue
james talk to okay return to search for where the plans am i am not i know i'm not soft-locked
what is this one well we're fucked we're actually fucked um okay thanks max you just load the other
one seven hours 23 seven hours and 22 minutes wait is this correct other save you dentist hey
excuse me all right we're good all right so don't vaporize her kill her with the revolver
talk to her first get the reward first there is no reward i've never been so pleased at the side of
an open door please tell me you've cleared a way out of here i mean there is uh hold on i quit
i've got questions for you ask away okay i have got nothing but time how did you end up in this
quote why would you in your credit what do you intend to do with this room what are you talking
about of course i don't have any use for the scribblings of idiotic scientists but whoever
gave me this tip obviously does assuming i make it out of this place alive and with
i'll have to leave on foot and hope my luck changes okay one problem at a time i suppose
uh i cleared the path don't make me regret it so you have i am much obliged i did not do this for
free and now if you do not mind i have had quite enough of this wretched place well i didn't save
your life for free good i never trust a freelancer who works for free man if you're good at something
never do it for free come on you're gonna throw it a little extra for the orphans orphans is that
what you are calling yourself now here let it never be said that i do not reward good work
no you don't uh and i'm gonna need you to turn over that research oh really and why
pray tell would i do a thing like that date is worthless a situation is liable to turn ugly if
you don't uh because you don't want a price on your head also i went out of the way for you
you know uh it's gonna turn ugly if you don't it's just you know it's worthless that's what i was
told damn and blast i should have seen this coming here take the damned research
tell crane i hope he chokes on it you did the right thing
high five i could spend hours reflecting on the secret workings of the universe
little else in this colony offers such a relaxing pastime so tell me what's on your mind
i excel the confessional listening yeah never fucked with the dentists what'd you have on you
you lying to me did you give me everything good got what i wanted got what i came for
let's get out of here doom that came to rose speak to anton talk to anton search for secrets
and okay i've done everything except with this dr wanda but fuck it we don't even need to do
that let's go here's something i learned in prison they were three kind of fucked up dentists
we're gonna have to have a quick meeting at the dentist uh that person was hostile that was an
np they should have read name like that see who the fuck are you shoot the thing explosive
there it is good come and get it yeah they were interfering with official dentist business
where's that person come on why am i so hurt dogs i'm dead where was the save point
okay let's do this again fast travel good idea what an excellent idea all right let's go back
talk to anton what's left there that's worth oh shit i forgot about these people you let them
get away worthless the lot of you well you get what you pay for don't you heard there was
some trouble out in the uh front of the building there doc crane better get over himself just
fucked up what happened i heard there was a somebody a spy i heard and shot somebody with
a fuck what that's fucking that's fucked up that no account fool porter and his crew are even more
worthless than i could have imagined they've abandoned their posts this is madness okay
i can't believe this is all about toothpaste that i have your research but i'm keeping it
i'm the real dentist i found your associate james and he's safe that is wonderful news
i'd feared the worst you know there's more to care about than black marks and paperwork
good to hear it's good to hear that you're a thousand dollars your employees actually
mean more to you than your research of course they do please don't mistake my ambition for
callousness okay what should i mistake it for compassion if my colleagues refuse to take their
lives seriously why should i all they do is complain they refuse to see the opportunity
afforded us here uh you just wanted to clear it up your heartless bastard believe what you will
but i'm not the manipulative ego-driven person you think me to be i'm not okay level up
it's you so uh as if my thoughts weren't dark enough already what is it you turned around
pretty quickly uh you're i have your research but i'm going to keep it the outlaws got away
with the research yeah it was terrible that's all manner of distressing there truly is nothing left
for me i suppose i'm uh we're finished here all right bye i thought that was a gun
it's like no no no no no no all right so i got some new info like i can return to gladys
go back yeah i gotta go back to the uh yeah let's go back i'll take your confession now
wait what where did you come from who did this they both died off screen
where is he he's not even in the same room this doesn't make any sense
hold on a second wait wait wait this is important
did you see his face that face was so no that horror that was on his face
that was so horrible i liked it because somebody said do it max and then i
it's such an elaborate cutscene okay the true horror is that max no all right so handguns uh
suck but okay uh meter max that's not bad companion correct chance that's good because
for when we have max do his um long cutscene move that's pretty cool that's all we care about now
and that opens up tier two yeah okay we have some new stuff i feel like it always has to be
a shotgun though because it has so much weight behind it that turn you back to the camera
spin around shoot with shotgun is just way cooler than i mean it has to be a shotgun always you can
use uh you can use this too it's always a shotgun oh okay well let's level you up range damage
dialogue combat effect i'm going to do range damage right because he's going to be doing the
shotgun ranged dps and now you are going to be uh reduce negative reputation for kills when sam
is in the party armor rating yeah i want you to be the tank for a second i thought they already
okay let's keep going we're going to go to gladis now wait this like probably stuff i can do in this
town a vendor of some sort there's probably something right i should sell yeah 17th bar
okay analysis is unexpectedly disgusting
that's a good character all right what do you got i don't think you're supposed to be wandering
around security's gonna tell you to make tracks want to stop yourself before you go
something for the road i'm sorry i bumped you um but what do you got let's see
cleo makes the best pharmaceuticals in halcyon sell i got a 15 discount let's just sell the junk
4,700 bucks what do you what do you have for okay i need to start mixing stuff i have a lot of
random shit i need a third slot how do i get a third slot i have to do medicine again yeah i need
that third slot i'm going to be working on medical next time and then long rifle we good we are back
to the ship but first i have an apple up here uh i guess that's okay tactical damn time dilation
recharge rate plus 50 for 25 seconds toothpaste movement speed plus 20 that's oh that's awesome
hold on movement speed plus 20 melee weapon attack speed 20 i don't really care about that
i care about the movement speed five guys is best burgers that's not true today captain
the stars are the limit that's just that's completely and totally untrue they're good but
they're not the best
they're good i agree with you they're very i would say that they're pretty close to being very good
you know but the best burger i've ever had no they're both coming with me stay still i'm
just going to remove some tartar all right let's move so we've got no
heard from the last down on 22 that you did a contract
were you talking shit person the first person to talk shit is going to get a max wait is this
unauthorized all right uh i don't know gladis so what do i have to do gladis mentions that
junley tennyson the groundbreaker's captain is always willing to put available captain's
work you can check the bounty board in the docking bay for work i mean i kind of already did
everything what is that just go to glass where is it i'm gonna go down all right gladis i've got
some stuff for you let's talk have you had a moment to look into that little opportunity i
told you about on roseway you don't hurry up someone i'll get to snooping around there before
you do i investigated that distress signal from roseway what's that speak up now about those
bug under your desk secrets what'd you turn up i found this fancy toothpaste formula here you go
a nice scientific dental lie i found a formula for experimental rocket fuel seems like pretty
advanced stuff i found schematics for a prototype weapon from force and i'm selling you buying
that's a pretty good science life my stars what i find
fine picking like this deserves an equally fine payout go on dearie and don't spend it all in one
place what are you giving me 3000 i found schematics for a prototype weapon from force and
i'm selling you buying it uh yeah i want give me more money peaches and cream if that isn't the
most handsome bit of lethal engineering 1500 more bits that will go for a tiny some bits
how can i be sure you won't go ratting me out to the wrong people my oh my look at the cysts on you
here consider it hazard pay okay i think that's it are you positive honest to goodness um i don't
think there's anything left for me to do so tell me what i want to know what did i want to know
be sure to come back for magazine club okay bye anytime sweetheart you know where to find me
oh um this person right okay you sold the toothpaste formula what oh right yes it did
well dentist has to make money somehow okay let's go let's go talk to uh jun lee
you wait this is illegal oh fuck if i care i who's key do i i okay i'm not allowed to be in here
close the damn door get in here dentist meeting
holy shit whose stuff is this i don't know whose key do i have oh i can't get that open this one
holy shit it's all so there's so much stuff
okay all right i can get another rest and go key card cool why don't they just let me
oh fuck this is your business imagine hearing somebody go into your back room and
yell out hey we're having a dentist meeting in here closing the door why would you let us go in
there both teams have tested negative for performance enhancing stems a toss all right
uh this glass let's go over to generally tenson i know she's in there who can't keep me out of
there please don't make a scene dr fennhill i am not making a scene doctors you know i used to be
a doctor i was just like you and then i decided to put on a green shirt and i became a dentist
and let me tell you it is so much better you think you're tough waving that thing around
yeah i'm waving around i'm flexing on you how much money did you make in the last week
i had two crowns and i had a couple implants to do that's 60 000 in four days i'm sorry am i
causing a scene see him through we could have avoided all this unpleasantness if
you just let me talk to jesse in the first place uh what's going on let me get one thing straight
jesse and i are not friends i just owe her okay as for the rest i'm trying to figure that out all i
know is that she's been here too long and she's apparently not receiving visitors
maybe i can look into it i was a doctor be my guest if you know something i don't about dealing
with hospital bureaucracy i'll be impressed you talking to the right person you open that door
hey doctor hey doctor open that door what seems to be the problem i'd like to see jesse doyle
please if only my other patients had so many inquiring after them i'll tell you what i've
told the others the records saying miss doyle checked herself in and requested i admit no
visitors requests of our patients are paramount so no you may not see her the records say you
actually spoken to her yourself she's not my patient i'm certain no one on my staff would
falsify patient records if that's what you're implying it is take care yeah have a good day
doctor fucking loser i go where i want i'm a i'm a stand-up dentist i was gonna stand comedian
whatever is a doctor really smoking inside of a hospital are you fucking kidding me
dentist wouldn't do that guarantee it oh i've learned that interstellar crew is called the
condition skip flu and everyone ah yep somebody screenshot that all right where are they pick up
marted id cartridge you found an id cartridge used with the holographic shroud you will now
be automatically disguised entering the associated restricted area that was very very simple i guess
i'm now your holographic shroud is activated giving you temporary access to this restricted
area moving drains the shroud's energy when it runs out personnel will see and interrogate you
talk your way out of the interrogation to reset your shroud it'll get harder to talk your way out
the more you're interrogated what looking sharp why do you look like you're about to
fucking take a swing at me okay so i'm pretending to be a doctor we're looking for jesse all right
you're sure this is perfectly safe i'd rather not die early of an infectious disease myself
where's jesse looking for jesse okay if i do i have to pick this lock i'm gonna pick the lock
this is probably jesse's room nobody in here well there's a lot okay i might not have been
worth it but how do i replenish the shroud jesse jesse jesse i'm a stealth dentist ellie sent me
actually a doctor i'm a dentist got to quit and sorely contagious dentists don't take
open the door before i fucking knock it down
are you disguised what does that mean why did she have like a crumpled up piece of trash under her
name did everybody get in here relocating the truth is i'm not sick but if you repeat what
i'm about to tell you to anyone i will deny it with my dying breath you uh ain't with the board
are you no i owe them a lot i might have missed a payment or two and the other night i swear
someone was following me back to my room so i hold up here to lay low in front of the guard
uh you know i do work for the board actually oh laws wait don't gut me and skin me yet
please talk to bedford tell him i can pay um a part of it and i'm a useful person to know
just ask ellie surely you wouldn't drag me before him i'm dreadful contagious i just
know if i face him i'm dead uh i'll talk to i'll talk to him for you thanks for helping me with
the board you're a real pal or i guess i should say ellie is one huh you're welcome by the way
you're welcome okay okay we saw it i didn't know it was gonna be outside oh what
nothing at all what i'm doing i'm not gonna lie to you i'm doing what the fuck i want
wait what if you do it twice you can't do it twice it's not fall out fuck that's right it's a
different game all right goodbye now let's go talk to worst contact which is this way can i leave
this way who cares if my disguise is gone uh oh we made it let's go any word on jesse uh-huh
she's in debt to the board and thinks someone's after her i'll handle it good luck the board's
got an office on the promenade just before engineering you can't miss it yeah i crossed
over i crossed over the border you have no jurisdiction when i go through the red gel
all right let's go fuck this guy up remember me this is halcyon news how do you do
huh how might i assist you i'm here about jesse doyle i want her debt settled miss doyle owes
the board a significant sum alas the only collateral she has is her organs compulsory
donation is quite legal in such cases can't she work for you until she earns back what she owes
i believe the captain is proposing an indenture contract i didn't say nothing about her teeth i
would know he's got to be worth more than alive than dead you should know that dentist that's
not unreasonable what guarantee do i have that she'll agree to the terms you negotiate
she's hiding in sickbay to avoid assassins i'm sure sir prefer work doesn't have a choice doesn't
show up for work kill her like you planned on in the first place hmm i'm not sure the price
of her organs will allow a profit in that case i expect her liver is uh used goods as it were
i will recall my collection agent tell miss doyle to report to me promptly for her first assignment
now is there anything else you need or can i return to my work no go ahead do you think do
you think i'm not gonna do it i'm not i'm not gonna you can always tell when he saves
yes i just said when he saves then i'm gonna press the c button wish i could say it was good to see
you ellie at least you finally got your chance to square our debt that ought to make you smile
for once huh there's smokes in this game makes me happier than being even it's like 2000 years in
the future cigarettes people still think are cool i think they would have been like phased out in
like 2000 like 140 got word from udom from the hitman who trailed me the other night
seems i'm indentured to the board now yes you are i ain't too elated about going exclusive but it's
better than winding up dead yes it is you sure saved my skin stranger all debts between me and
ellie are cleared good watch yourself now you the good news came through the wireless looks like
you paid my debt to jesse i guess that means i owe you now right maybe tell you what i'm a little
short on bits at the moment but i'm a decent scrapper and a better than average sawbones
if you're looking for a medic i can work my debt off
we're always looking for new doctors and dentists but if i'm being honest and i prefer not to your
doc i was about ready to pick up another contract anyway and you settled this in a pretty tidy
fashion she's a doctor not a dentist you're competent but i was a doctor before i was a
dentist all of us were we just had to put on green welcome aboard ellie you won't be sorry
your green scrubs are in your locker captain meet me on my ship it's docked in the promenade
yeah meet me at the ship traveling in style are we i'll be sure to nab a cabin with a view
dr fenhill glad you opted to join us it'll be good to have a sawbones on the crew
how to be in green all right more skill points what did i say i wanted to do
i said i want to do more medicine right a third drug slot that's gonna take a while damn it
uh i need to do more damage we're gonna do long guns all right so uh i was doing this
i kind of just gave up on it reesee
bounty drone cool how do i get in there auntie's kitchen key card how do i get into where you oh
there's a giant hatch thought there'd be more machinery must be housed on a sub level what
happened to the cool priest i'm sorry fecal matter from alien life forms there's no longer a priest
this is a dentist
junley tennyson i'm captain around here but chief to my friends hope you don't mind the
formal introduction groundbreaker doesn't see many visitors uh junko nice place you got here i'm
captain of the unreliable recently unshackled from groundbreaker's impound good for you hope
you scared some sense into those bureaucrats giving you trouble just so we understand each
other i'm the final word on the ship the mardits the crew the engineers their family i hope there
won't be any problems while you're visiting i'll do whatever i can to help don't go making trouble
and chances are you won't find any that's how i like it here so what brings you to groundbreaker
i'm curious even though nine times up to ten the answers just passing through
um statistics don't lie we see a lot of the same faces coming and going most of them board spies
makes it hard to trust outsiders you seem different so welcome aboard uh you don't have a
lot of faith in the board what's it like being in command it seems kind of warm in here you don't
have a lot of faith in the board you're right i don't the board is after two things bits and power
and they only get it by sticking their nose where it doesn't belong you must not like bedford very
much i like to think of myself as a nice person but if that gaudy embassy of his was on fire
i might hold my breath a moment before activating the sprinkler system the board wants control of a
groundbreaker and leeches like udon bedford will do anything to please their corporate masters
uh how do you keep the board at a safe distance when i have something to offer but i can also be a
real hard ass it'd be a joy if i could kick out the corporate merchants and reclaim the docking
fees in my lifetime too much of groundbreaker's income is flowing in the wrong direction
i'd like to see that change okay you've got my attention well what do i what do you want
what's it like being in command frustrating everything down to the circuit boards has
passed warranty so i have the pleasure of making life or death decisions on a shoestring budget
plus there's no time to train my successor or document fixes in a way that anyone outside the
family would understand okay who has a family business sure is the tennyson's came over on
the groundbreaker my grandmother chief gang kept it together during the crossing and until she died
and my grandfather ben only recently when my mom died then i took the leap from chief engineer to
captain he left behind a really weird watch and we didn't know what to do with we brought it to
antiques roadshow and they said it was 44 dollars so we sold it we didn't know what it was it was
in a shoebox upstairs it was different knowing that i couldn't turn to anyone who could answer
the tough questions for me maybe you can see why i'm protective of groundbreaker this ship is
family it's got tinkerings and bypasses that only tennyson's know about ways to self-destruct
i hope that was a joke captain i really do i gelded that thing years ago it wasn't now it
bruises it wasn't where is it stronger than nan or spank where's the exploding button
recipe aren't you a little young you see any bite-sized tennyson children running around
i didn't think so the next captain won't have my heritage i'll have to foster that talent from
somewhere it's only a question of when okay you've got my attention seems mormon here's radiators
need replacement parts yep here's this and there we go here it is here's the here it is
is only the board has access to new parts go install ac into the window sure thing they want
us to sweat thinking that'll soften me up for a bad faith deal if you'll excuse me they can go
fuck themselves the board isn't helping and my resources are spread thin if i don't get those
radiators back online groundbreaker everyone on board will be cooked alive you need a contractor
there i could where i could do this easily reasonable huh that's the best news i've heard
all day according to my grandmother's old schematics the parts we need should be in the
back bays uh what the hell is that sorry i forgot not everyone knows this ship like i do
the back bays are on a lower deck long abandoned and a haven for miscreants now
if you tried sending anyone else down there i'll get those parts good once you've obtained the
parts we can proceed to the next phase of repairs okay whatever i'm not doing it for free
that's her family heirloom book it's mine now just download all of her data all right got it all
i can't get in the back room what do you think you're doing i was uh nothing just keep your
fingers to your own self okay okay bye now we need to go to all right where's this thing what's
going on you need to get a few parts for the radiator i've got to do all kinds of
bullshit the incompetence of people in rpg's is seriously mind-bending it's called a quest
no it's called running errands for people they called a quest to make it sound cooler so you'll
want to do it approaches our realm back away now or you'll parlay with the king can we talk
look at this ripe piece of meat just sizzling on the grill
yum yum time to feed the flames it's nothing personal promise
speaking for myself captain i am not of a mind to be murdered by a psychopath who plays with fire
you won't we'll be good you came with the crew welcome we got plenty of space to spread out
but only room for one captain nothing personal kid uh put that down before you incinerate the
entire you're only getting out of this alive if you play nice yeah look at the courage on this one
lay it on me boss give you a taste of that fiery primal spirit i'm just here for some parts kid
tennyson just keeps feeding the furnace don't she we're still playing with her last sacrifice
out back with the crew so i can you're gonna give that you know just ask a king for a favor
when you're standing in his court you bring tribute sacrifices prophecy shit like that
okay well uh sorry for you that those parts are leaking deadly toxins i'll just come back when
you're dead under its skin this ship is all poison and darkness lead bones asbestos muscle
maybe you're right you've got the run of the kingdom up those stairs you'll find the parts
my crew won't get in your way there's something else though lay it on me boss i'm good for it
never mind i was gonna say i could take your money go in my little kingdom
just try not to piss off any of the gestures thank you
dirty dirty you get that automatic patch i'm trying to think of a good name before i wake it up
you're gonna have to fight me buddy do you guys see the power of line
i go where am i going what else is down here holy shit i can just take whatever i want no i can
damn well just look at how many people were here i gotta go up uh ladder or somewhere
can i jump up here can i go on a platform go up do i have to press a button or can i
run or is there a stairwell or something yes save and kill them why would i do that
my birthday fuck your birthday i'm not you want to kill these guys now
fantastic we've got them now we can move on to cleaner pastures all right all right i got your
part this would have taken a long time i'm so glad i could just walk through that was so simple
didn't have to do anything skip that whole portion i've got a part for you you've returned
and in one piece color me impressed now work i'll take those i need you to head through the large
door at the far end of engineering take the elevator down into the machinery shop there's
a terminal in the back activate it when i call up at the ship's pa and bring weapons
there's a slight caterpillar infestation uh all right fine i'm all right with this
the league of extraordinary dentists we use our powers for good sometimes you're not getting into
my room again if i hadn't caught you last time you would have burned all of my books
there's like little snakes what the hell are those here we go nice up and smoke
some more up here where is he he's invisible where is this thing what the fuck
come on up sneak if you like germa say pogchamp prepare
it's okay what's up captain what i kind of just going in all right i guess we'll just go in
sneak don't fight if you don't need to can you see us
dead you guys are good i love not doing anything it's fun to have companions that just do
everything for you it feels great all right it's right underneath us
here they come give me electricity how do you get down there yo stop killing them what i need
to get in there oh god damn it did i seriously flaw spacers choice found a flaw in you during
your adventures things may happen to your character that can trigger a flaw offer taking the flaw is
optional but doing so provides you with a perk permanently crippled your legs have been damaged
too many times and your movement speed has now been permanently lowered movement speed minus
30 and you're unable to dodge why would i ever accept this what no way reject permanent 30
movement speed loss and no dodging ever for one perk point yeah give me five and i'll consider it
shut up i got it coming you don't ever you never dodge anyways yes i do
guys i don't like this we need to be friendly and we need to be in complete cahoots
done my boards are returning to green what a weight that is off my shoulders
that's sam and max dialogue is mucking about in my station's guts but you're all right the
temperature should be dropping as we speak yeah it is i'll see to it the crew knows who kept us
all from boiling alive that's weird time i believe edna has a comms issue that could use your
attention edna also authorized doc and furu to sell you our premium meds oh okay well that's cool
oh okay we got a long tomorrow all right i'm done i did it there's only this one the book
you retrieve for him an emerald veil holds the key to his enlightenment at the groundbreaker
security office groundbreaker are now friendly so i can just walk i could walk around and just take
stuff let's do this first i need to repair some stuff too can i do that for my venue i can read
okay repair how many what does it cost to repair this 20 weapon parts are you kidding me
it's horseshit it's just me or has it been better than usual around here
jeep wants to reduce board traffic let's get it
we have uh is that person gonna see this all right let's get that book hello can i come in
buzz me in good afternoon how's everybody doing terminal down where
wait that's no that's me oops crowbar how do you discuss a giant robot like that what is this
plasma rifle sure okay can i break into this door no damn it do i have any levels up no
all right let's go to that terminal excuse me what was that impact hammer wait this guy
leaves the room steel impact hammer no no not s t e e a like actually take it it's not made out
of steel okay terminal how do i where is this thing sealed how do i get this door to open
can you open this door i don't have time for this oh i'm supposed to lose my disguise okay
how do i get that door open i can't hack it eat food that makes you smarter i have food
that i can eat that makes me smarter breath inhalant movement speed companion ability
cooldown duration armor rating mind attributes plus one what does that mean mind attributes
does that mean mind i just okay just breathe in caffeine and then breathe and drink this
critical damage all attributes minus one that's not good that sucks personality attributes
so i just taking a bunch of caffeine and open the door does this count hold on candy base health
carbohydrates personality just charm the door
all right i'm gonna do mind attributes plus one i'm gonna eat one see what happens okay here we go
fizzy t okay got it i'll do the rest uh eject confiscated goods modified pistol detailed a
freelancer who was a cagey about his business confiscated his personal belongings while he
waited for questioning he had a modified pistol hatchet metal hoop prayer beads locked container
he fled before we could get it down he left his things behind so we're stored in the back of the
security station all right i got those give me the disk now that we have the data cartridge
i can finally find out where that scholar i'm looking for ended up good all right break what
i have to talk to you got it his name is reginald cheney and he joined a sub-light salvage crew
only he's not listed on the return manifest must have made landfall somewhere he wasn't supposed
to sam have a companion quest there's a domicile on monarch in fallbrook rented to the same bit
card he used to buy his seat on the salvage ship i should have guessed what better place to lay low
if you wish to avoid the authorities okay oh you hesitated there what aren't you telling me
oh it's nothing i suppose i really didn't have much faith and actually finally in the galaxy
was a bit of a long shot wasn't it this is pretty convenient i admit it was a bit of a long shot
but when you've spent as many hours as i have in contemplation of the universe's secrets
you sometimes get a sense for these things okay uh let's go what do you think you're doing
whatever i want don't complicate my job okay let's go workbench repair everything is pretty good
let's go tinker all right i have to think about some of this right now breakdown
then get rid of the hatchet yeah i'm not going to use this ship plasma rifle i don't think i'm
going to use it impact hammer plasma carbine light machine gun i don't know if i'm going to
use any of this stuff get rid of the shotgun give her the hunting rifle how many bolter pistols do
i have this one and this one bucket uh keep the how many of these do i have two
there's a shock cannon keep that one tinker i'm gonna tinker the stuff i currently have
i have 14 000 money right now so let's make this better tinker 216 do it again
again 234 do it again 252 do it again 270 dps one more time one more this thing tinker
time signal okay so this thing is a beast now i have 11 000 12 i have 12 000 dollars
this is the revolver oh no no these things kind of suck look at all this shit all right
first of all let me just delete all my junk no i can't uh what do i have modify my
now tinker okay helmet let's make it a little better 124 yeah okay that's good this thing will
be 215 will make this be 11 armor okay uh sell my junk yeah i can't do that here though
keep this all right i'm gonna sell stuff all right this thing is insane let's get out of here
all right track down reginald cheney that's my name now okay i've done all the optional shit
the only other stuff i can do is just secrets of rose way which i did most of them there's
probably one more i can't i didn't do i could do this one the sickbay one yeah let's do sickbay
i was just in there watch where you're walking you glorified broom
dr dorset you stop on my foot and i swear i will turn you to jump wait the captain will have to
order another sam unit to clean you up how do i get it out all right hi wait you sell me premium
goods uh hello julie called up from engineering said i should let you buy medical supplies from
our stores now is there something you're a glorified broomstick max a better selection
than you'll find on the promenade deck an equality commensurate with a friend of the station
okay sell junk i didn't have very much junk apparently sell engineering plus 15 damn
inspiration all right let's get rid of this stuff so i'll just sell four 15 this has medium armor i
i know i can never take off the stuff that i currently have on it'll cause a huge problem in
the chat room i know that for a fact can i sort hold it flip sort yeah let's like sort this shit
what do i have okay get the dentist close for the doc yeah i will all right i got two i have two i'm
wearing the priest outfit heavy armor tech skills that stealth skills get rid of it
elite troop armor block and stealth skills are bad i'm not going to use persuade now let's not lie
these helmets engineering mining gear stealth cares sort by value oh shit
what the fuck all right so the yeah i'm not going to use it sneak plus i might need that
eventually at some point long guns plus seven i'll keep that it's heavy armor i don't want it
inspiration will keep one of them science no keep the lock picking one get rid of this
those two dentist outfits keep those no what about weapons all right i got a bunch of junk here
sort by value all right plasma carbine i think this thing's dead this thing's just done get rid
of the i'm gonna get rid of these who cares just taking up space give me one of the hammers get
rid of the shock hammer i could keep that bolt pistol all right plasma rifle plasma rifle i have
two of them keep the shock cannon or what about just dump like junk just dumb shit this stuff is
this stuff is expensive this is 400 and 400 bucks oh i gotta put this stuff in all right
that's good i'm gonna buy i actually do need to get some of these how many do i have
how many of these do i own just get 10 oh this one's a good one enable pog coward why call me
coward all right let's go talk you can't say i've seen you before i take it you're a freighter
captain if you're here to better yourself you'll have to wait we're having a spot of trouble with
our delivery service we need it uh we'll see the shipment will be coming in soon
he must be referring to erion i'm sure the fool's gotten himself into another scrape
i'm beginning to wonder if i'm ever gonna get my service mechanicals at this rate
ah i could find him i'd be grateful if you'd spare the time we need his delivery soon as yesterday
last he told me he was taking a shortcut by silla an asteroid in the carib diskill every human
being that's where i'd start where i the adventuring type you can't do quests anymore you look out
though the place is probably crawling without laws would at that point do you just role play
and make your own missions all right it's time yeah let's go it's time to tell gladys i'm done
okay gladys i i got nothing else to do okay gladys if you're here for this week's magazine club
meeting you're a touch late i almost just clicked that uh i did all the distress signals i'm done
speak up now that's it are you positive honest to goodness i'm done yes i'm certain there's nothing
left to do can't say i wasn't hoping for more but i suppose it can't be helped law bless you for
doing the legwork sweetie don't forget your pal gladys now you can come visit anytime anytime
sweetheart you know where to find me what are you talking about all right 60 long guns headshot
weak spot plus 20 lockpick maybe all right so we're gonna do all right lockpick is at 30
and then we're gonna do long guns to 65 i gotta all right now i get a tier two this is gonna take
me a minute uh when you critically hit a target you have a chance of immediately resetting the
buff chance to reset a companion's cooldown 25 ttd restored per kill that's pretty good
plus 50 science weapon damage 25 more movement speed 15 plus 15 health restored per kill that's
a huge bonus damage to plus 20 bonus to extra headshot weak spot damage while time dilations on
can carry more vendor prices dialogue skills just have can you have like 110
lie that means you're the best liar in the world i like this this is i like this one i need this
so i have to wait so i have to what do you mean i have to buy my way sitting down for tea
anytime because i didn't do the third thing from roseway is that what this is about got the shroud
talk to bedford okay where's the key where is it where is it i'm just gonna take it is it in there
um it's in the safe well great this is just wonderful uh no i can't kill everybody in this
room steal it and then lie about stealing it it's almost time for today's episode of the chairman's
children care to listen with me you need to lockpick it all right i'm gonna try this
let me just see what happens i'm gonna lockpick it steal it and then lie
okay where is it i i need some of those uh things what can i get one of those how do you do
and oh rest and go rest and go we used to be the go and rest but folks never knew when to leave
sorry business the moon guy anything to occupy the time all right you just you're making me sad
i'm gonna all right where is he where's the moon guy over here where's moon guy other way
there he is i almost just jumped off and died that would have been bad all right uh i'm just
gonna take it from me they're back here somewhere right all right i'm gonna steal this is the point
ready let's get by three of those things break open his back door feel an extra chilly steal
everything in the back room to help yourself to a piping hot frozen dinner have a look okay so i'm
looking for where what do you got you got it do you sell them i don't think he sells them
does he no he doesn't sell them who sells those things he has it but it's locked what why can i
oh i have to buy them from the vending machines that wouldn't excuse me waste disposal what's in
here bell's shells what do you have back here that's like worth taking uh the vending machines are
locked too so okay what about can i i know what finneas is pay me money i'm just gonna pay it
okay i'll pay it i'm gonna pay it i'm gonna pay it i'm gonna pay it because i don't have locked
picks let me look at this one more time passage to anywhere in order to revive your fellow colonist
strain colonist stranded hibernation dr wells needs you to travel to stellar bay on the terraformed
moon of monarch monarch is interdicted by the halcyon holdings corporate board so you'll have
to procure a nav key through unofficial channels monarch all right can i just go what if i don't
have a key though well let's just go uh how do i get back to my ship where's my ship just run
find scholar right then run there am i a nudist i'm a private nudist
this used to be in the docking base no look who it is i just want me to make sure you know
that you're not coming with us all right let's see if i can just go there isn't he a lock picker
oh your face is a site for sore ocular process okay so we need to go to monarch wanting dangerous
what do you mean fucking dangerous or rather your head care you acquired prayer beads yeah i know i
have them wait important good that's a good that's a pretty good dentist outfit uh you'll be um
let's do medical sure and let's get you that actually you that weapon's pretty damn good
yeah it's a dentist doing a procedure with the thing things to put over their eyes to see closer
like the magnifiers all right i'm just uh we're just gonna go here and see what happens let's go
land message from dr wells we'd like to congratulate you on finding a route to monarch
cascadia is utterly seething with dangerous highly aggressive creatures more than capable of
tearing you limb from limb you'd have to be a lunatic to land in cascadia and i'm reasonably
certain i tested your brain for incipient signs of insanity trust me talk to gladys cult kelly
uh i'm going to fight my way over land to stellar bay tell me what you need
you'll need to speak with hyrum blithe he's known as the information broker and for good reason
if anyone knows where i can find those chemicals it's hyrum i need those chemicals to revive the
hopes colonists they can help us fight back against the board they can help us set things right
if we don't put a stop to the board they're going to drive this colony toward a complete
societal collapse you'll see what i mean when you arrive on monarch all right you sound like
you've been to monarch uh tell me what you want me to do you'll want to hire the services of a
skilled guide i recommend a hunter by the name of neoka frequents the drinking establishments of
stellar bay very hard to miss once you have everything you need make your way to hyrum blithe's
compound okay best of luck everyone on the hope is counting on you captain an unusual
wavelength is coming through monarch's aether wave frequencies the eternal is in us all the osi would
have you believe that your place in society indeed in the universe is preordained a man who works in
the mines of Hephaestus coating his lungs in mercury dust for not but a few bits a night
this fate is set in stone when he dies young coughing up black blood his part in the grand
plan no i say greatness is in everyone not just those so fortunate as to have been born into
prosperity that was unexpected it's a long way to say you don't have the key all right uh that
was something like a bunch of nonsense i am inclined to agree with your assessment by which
i mean i have been systemically programmed to do so okay goodbye cool let's go all right who's
coming with remember that you are not insured should we try out another dentist
okay let's go now why is this so dangerous some key huh what i need you needed a key key
let's go all right so i i can just land here what happens if i actually have the key
do i get to land in a safe place or i'm kind of confused how this all works
because that is hitting me all germs and contaminants have been neutralized
oh the t the key lets you land in the town oh well fuck it who cares you can get through this
plus i'll get i'll get items too just don't fight anything that's too hard
that was a purple mask oh rizzo that's all i got out of that 1241 we can go hopefully there's
nothing here right something's attacking i hear something just don't fight the giant monster just
run around that one's so hard okay now this actually is this actually is not good is there
any other way to go besides the front door that i'm going not really i don't think i can sneak by
this i have to go for it i smite you in the name of the law well they're instantly dead
there's a lot more things over here oh my god okay so that's there um can't kill these guys let's
go is there a way this way i could go that's a dead end i have to go back here then uh-oh
now i have to go this way just eat a bunch of drugs i mean i could go over here but that's
i gotta wrap all the way around no we're going for it all right let's go let's do it i know we
can do it what do i got just do drugs yeah i'm gonna do drugs okay this is uh movement speed
so let's do instead of health let's see tactical time recharge rate 50 and then
super like i don't know whatever i have range weapon sway range weapon spread
you can just use them from this menu yeah but i want to be able to spam them actually these
they last a minute so that's true that's true all right um so here we go let's do recharge rate
this lasts 25 seconds though companion ability cooldown range weapon spread i feel like this is
not really gonna do that much for me regen it's just recharge rate and weapons sway all right i'm
gonna smoke a cigarette i'm going to inhale this i'm going to go kill it kill one on the right
come on kill it weak point hit it dead all right oh i'm on fire am i still fucking burning wow you
take a lot of hits where are my friends holy shit all right we're good come back we can continue
save it right here shooting a grenade launcher at wasps yes yes i am aware it was not ideal
now we can stay on the road there's one of these weirdos here we go oh this is bad you know what
yeah yep yep holy shit getting burned too many times has made you susceptible to plasma
no reject how would you come from i think it's time we just run because this is too much just run
it's sleeping no it's not it's not anymore why am i trying to do this weird bunny hop thing all
right let's go almost there neoka oops where am i going all right i'm gonna go this way and then
wrap around oh no i'm running right into the nest this is actually the nest it's all right
we're almost there okay that's big that's big he's level 12 when he's running away from fights
you saw how long it took me to kill one of these manta queens i'm not prepared for this
okay we're good look once i get a place of business no what am i doing see i told you i'm
trying to prove to one person that i can do it and i can't so go dead end oh no it's right there
i just have to get there uh oh come on i gotta get to that bridge can i not just is this all worth
10 000 no wish i paid it oh you've got to be out of your mind that's so dangerous okay grandpa
and turns out turns out this was a really really bad idea oh fuck get over just get around get
around get around almost there oh come on stellar bay i did it okay nice let me in excellent finally
purchase a nav key to stellar bay didn't need to do that quest completed now we have to do
uh we only have one thing so far to speak with neoka who's over here don't don't just take it
there's no reason to who what happened i think i'm gonna be sick you all right no i just stepped in
a dead man's blood and i think one of the flies landed on my mouth if you're going into the
apartments do not go into the lower one on the right that's where the body is step aside please
now if you'll excuse me i need to go contemplate a hot shower
step aside where's the dead body you startle me don't sneak up on a person like that huh
where's the dead body i want to see it where's the dead body closing of any courses okay look for
clues these are all clues clues that i'm going to keep this is evidence oh if not what not yet
anything else i can take oh several ragged outfits all the same cut and color was stuffed
into this suitcase interesting we have a bed we have a note on the table this betting slip
lists some incredibly bold wagers made for a team called mostly colonists it's from left field toss
ball betting investigate left field toss ball betting find out what happened here i will
probably avenge you unless i get sidetracked which is then i just want who lives in here
it's an inferno side in here what is an inferno side what else you got bye bye wait who are you
you don't look like sub life all right now i can go what should let's go investigate that i want
to do that first man's been killed in a stellar bay apartment it falls to you to find out what
happened yeah i kind of want to know dentist she can certainly pick up her own capinoid
hello dearie why i don't believe i've seen you before and with sweet cheeks like those i'd
remember what can auntie abigail do for you i don't know nothing for now goodbye i have to go
that way where are you left field betting can i bet in here you're the new face wow you must
be up on all the latest toss ball games so who do you follow wait don't tell me you look like
a hammersmith thunder fan no glacial age mammoths i play for auntie cleo's darlings don't you
recognize me i'd heard they'd gotten a new hacker is that why everyone's making such a fuss about
you but what are you doing on monarch well coach said i need some practice hitting things
there are lots of things to hit on monarch that's for sure just mind you don't let them hit you back
so what can i do for you well you say i found this bedding slip in a dead man's apartment any
idea what might have happened to him poor isaac i was wondering why i hadn't seen him in a few days
i'd really like to help isaac was a sweet fellow even if he did have terrible teeth
oh oh oh hold on what what are you talking about they were pretty distinct monarch doesn't exactly
have a thriving dental industry why how is this possible all sorts of bad habits dietary and
otherwise oh i don't like this place sometimes he'd drink purple berry punch by the leader other
times he'd keep betting on a losing team started owing the wrong people money oh what did he owe
i don't know for sure but i saw elijah and his buddies pushing isaac around what do your teeth
look like they're hooligans from fallbrook they sweep into town drop supplies off behind the
warehouse and spend the rest of their stay getting rowdy over tossball games they usually loiter in
the alley behind the yacht club they're not allowed in the bar anymore i bet you anything
isaac ran into trouble with one of them okay thanks for the tip appreciate it please to
hear about it when you're done i know he gets fed up with the fallbrook bullies but there's
not much he can do i'm fucking just utterly revolted right now let's go move out all right
play the slots there is no slot what are the chances of all the times and places we could
have been born yeah we're here light years from earth going about our lives
every time the punch clock peels a worker earns his meals what are you talking about
sorry i thought you were quoting it's a wonderful directorate anything else no that got awkward
he just threw four dolls in the trash what's wrong with you that's weird
a lot of shame no is it behind this all right here we go i gotta be careful
wrapped mask and canid eyes right here please will someone help me my boy is in trouble
how are his teeth well thank you for stopping everyone acts like nothing's wrong like my
little boy isn't at risk of being eaten by some vile creature please you have to help me get my
you have to help me get my little talker back he ran away he's going to get himself killed
oh i just know a raptidon is melting in with acid as we speak okay your child is missing where'd
you last see him oh i just knew you were a good person agnes i said this is the man to save your
little tucky and i was right he ran out into the wilderness a few days ago he's dead i warned him
about the raptidons mantosaurs and marauders there's no way he's higher than me in level
but he didn't listen i have rocket launchers and sniper rifles he's picking flowers out there he's
absolutely dead it's a reward i guess i can't ask you to leave the town walls for free
it is definitely dangerous out there i got some bits saved up for a rainy day i'll give you
every last one if you just bring my talker back to me i won't even be mad at him running off you
tell him i i won't be mad i'll help you find your son oh i know he'll be safe now that someone's
able to fetch him home you look for him in amber height do you hear it's down the road southwest
of town i'm sure he made it that far i just know it and if you find any of them iconoclasts
indoctrinating my boy you punch them in the mouth tell them what i think of them luring little
boys away from their mamas it's immoral okay but first where is this person okay here we go the
back is the back alley thugs berta thug thug elijah what the fuck are you this ain't your alley
oh i didn't know we owned alleys now okay max i smite you in the name of the law
taking care of this is my alley okay shit talk me that's what happens okay we got what we needed
shoot the barrel i did all right we got her let's go we have to go to uh sand jar
bright idea editorial automag with a flamethrower this unit will i'm here could i get another advance
mr nandi just make sure it's properly logged um well new business turns up at last
celia didn't i tell you our new statistics-based advertising model would be a hit
it that you did sir how can yield improvements of 26.7 percent not quicken the pulse
it's not that much 32 cost savings not voice in the loins you've often posed these very questions
clear my schedule this newcomer has a meeting with me i gotta say great teeth uh but you have a
meeting with me to hear that power play celia we don't make them like this anymore in halcyon
i only hope you don't judge me by my handshake now what business brings you here me chart my
own path going where the wind takes me i'm just looking for the information broker it's all i
care about why he's probably still out at devil's peak not that he's had the courtesy to notify me
at any rate but if you're here for him i suppose that means you aren't here for salt tuna
they could always be both if i have to eat one more weird science project past office food in
this sprat fucked colony i'm gonna stab someone it could be both now now there's no need to humor me
i'm used to this particular letdown i had hoped that livening up our advertisements with enticing
figures would draw the other corporations back to our bosom but it seems we're back to the drawing
board uh if you're free of the other corporations why would you want to bring them back surviving
alone isn't as easy as it looks thanks to the so-called hazard clause monarch has been cut off
from the board's resources and protection for 10 years now we've kept ourselves in business by
trading with individual corporations but given the off the books nature of those transactions
such arrangements are precarious and you're tired of scrounging and scraping by is that it
freedom is a tempting ideal but a rather costly paramour exactly intellectualism fuels the train
to mankind's future but the tracks the train runs on are forged from practicality yes it's as though
the good vicar has plucked the very words from my brain so now we're in right so we're gonna we're
in so what do you want to do well mr nandi here has a rather ingenious plan to get msi restored
to the board on our terms mind you returning to the board is your only chance if you hope to
survive here on monarch that doesn't mean it'll be easily achievable indeed not no worthwhile plan
was ever simple that's what i always say and if our advertising scheme hasn't borne fruit
then perhaps it's time we took matters into our own hands this lady knows what's up it's true
our celia is an alarmingly competent middle manager at any other company she'd be wasted
in data entry the plan she refers to is a two-pronged approach dentist and all the
you stellar bay properly defended only we have to have other things besides dentist
references to every piece of dialogue i've got to come up with other things to say
with a bolt 52 cartridge of course if you can get us what we need to rejoin the board starting
the bolt 52 we'll be able to become one of the most productive and secure cities in halcyon
and you'll have a powerful ally on the board farmers only dot what is that
i think i wait is this bolt sounds useful why one of the strongest defenses in halcyon
that's the farmer dating website all right where do i get a bolt in the old arms building southwest
of town which used to be part of stellar bay before we had to move our walls in these days
overrun with marauders and raptidons oh why you saying saying what which way
arms you're saying arms instead of arms that's just what it's called it's supposed to stand for
something but i forget what why am i such a weirdo why do i care about some of these things
i'll see what i can do good enough i know when to settle oh and while you're at it there should
be a terminal in the arms building with some dangerous information perhaps you could delete
it so it doesn't fall into the wrong hands you want me to wipe your hard drive all right
what do we got i want to wait family man okay here we go i still need to do this a fine day
for business isn't it anyway what can i do for you isaac rose is dead i found the people who
killed him but that's terrible what happened i've taken care of it killers are dead but that means
we won't be able to log their testimonies if there's one thing i've been hoping to
reestablish in stellar bay it's proper documentation for legal matters
uh sometimes you take matters into your own hands maybe i could have gotten their
statements if they hadn't been ready to kill me always a shame when tempers get the better of
good sense still your intervention in the matter is much appreciated please consider this payment
for your services okay goodbye let me take a look 40 is tinkering costs minus 50 that's pretty
amazing these guys seem a lot less evil i don't know about that maybe no weapons sway for five
seconds after each kill that's pretty good ah what should i do though i think i'm just gonna
put it into medical yeah but here's the thing about lying i have 70 lie right now
nothing that i've done in the game so far has required more than 40 or 50 yeah this is dentistry
there we go 40 breakdown weapons and armor for 20 chance to attract a basic mod yeah let's just
we'll get that up to 40 i will get to 100 live eventually don't worry you're gonna stack it for
the end game oh i will don't worry we'll get it so there was something else i need to do family
matter look for tucker right i'm gonna do that and then radio free oh shit we're still on
faction quest we're still we haven't even done the main thing yet what is this kid all right
we're gonna go find this kid this is the simple truth we are all molecular machines the body is
a collection of atoms the mind is the consequence of so here's the deal i'll tell you
you ready for the deal hold on to your hat we're going to play this tomorrow not done yet
but we're gonna play tomorrow and at the end of tomorrow's stream we're going to see if this is
something that i'm going to continue playing on stream tomorrow is thanksgiving that's correct
all right hold on 368 do i have any fast travels no so because it's thanksgiving tomorrow
i probably am gonna start streaming a little bit later than usual so tomorrow will probably be a
later stream instead of starting at like one or two we'll probably start not that much later
but just late enough where if everyone had things to do it'll be a later night stream
probably around like four pm pacific then it'll be about seven eastern and we can just chill
because it is fun just to kind of play a game even though you know i'm playing it
strangely i'm still enjoying it at least for now now here's the real question am i going to die
by attacking these hooligans no i won't even need to attack them because i can just run this way
stream title oh you better believe this the stream title tomorrow is going to be
um i don't know like the wizard of oz dentists edition with the wizard of oz director's cut
dentists you know something like that's not about dentists
the dentists of oz they can use a little work i'll i'll i'll put some work into it or it could
just be in all capitals dentists period only period that's not bad he laughed at his own joke
because it was fucking good amber heights let's go repeat the joke it was too good to repeat
it was hysterical tucker i fucking dare you oh don't say that don't tell me that don't do that
that's a bad move that's a bad move i'm telling you well i'll tell you something right now it
ain't gonna be me it's gonna be my boy matt he missed a rare miss he's getting tired he's
getting tired we're stuck well hello and welcome to the home of the iconoclasts i'm rose please take
a pamphlet wow what a bullshit personality this is you'll find everything you need to know about
graham his philosophist truths and the iconoclast way he wrote it himself you know i fucking dare
you oh i'm so sorry yeah bullshit we're out of pamphlets i already i smelt the spoiler of this
area i don't want a pamphlet just get the fuck out of my way we're the only free people in halcyon
no corporations no shackles no problems yeah right where's the kid no corporation means no
paycheck how do you survive without money no problems what about raptidons oh those are just
hurdles we deal with them as they come you're welcome to stay with us so long as you can earn
your keep okay oh one big happy family uh got it hey before i go i'm looking for a tucker have you
seen him the new boy yes he's quite clever he took to our teachings very quickly last i saw
him he was headed into one of the buildings up the hill you don't you get up you don't get away from
me yep let's get the kid and let's get the hell out of here tucker time to come home i'm not the
only new face around here what do i call you stranger i don't know why i thought you were
gonna be like six that's just fine oh come on we like to be friendly around here at the least let
me call you captain whether or not you command a ship if you've found your way here you must be a
leader type so then captain welcome to amber heights oh and uh call me tucker you're here to
join the iconoclasts help us free this world uh tucker you're a new face too huh free from what
you're the little boy i am boy haven't been one for decades no matter what my mama wishes
i take it she's still looking for me i hope she'd accept my decision she may seem like you were in
danger she's offered a reward to anyone who brings you back she said that you were in
danger according to her stepping foot outside of the house in broad daylight is too dangerous
my entire life she crammed a fear of danger down my throat shit don't go play with friends
bantasaurus will tear your arms overprotective mother don't leave the city or cult dons will spit
acid on your face marauders can violate you you'd fall in a sulfur pool i stuck around way too long
ruled by her fears i'm 42 years old but she still sees me as a little boy in need of her protection
i won't stand for it i tell you i'm getting that reward either you go back or i'll beat it out of
her oh my god whoa holy shit she's gonna keep sending people to look for you you're going back
to stellar bay one way or another i'm getting that reward a dent would it okay what's the
the oath that all dentists have to take what's that oath dentist oath the hippocratic oath
do dentists take the hippocratic oath hold on this is important it's a code of doctors for do
the right thing a moral code of ethical conduct and practice in medicine at medical school
graduations doctors swear this oath to leave them with more reminders to where their professional
focus lies do dentists take the hippocratic oath and if not should they have to okay
uh so do they take it it doesn't say although mainly used by doctors the hippocratic oath is
often translated to a dentist's context okay so i think they do no they don't well they can
they use the word patient they use a different one nebula is wrong with you she's an old woman
you threaten my flesh and blood just to get me to do what you want
holy shit shrug we're like ah just kidding i was kidding that was not even close to funny
i was kidding you give me that fucking reward nebula is wrong with you she's an old woman
you threaten my flesh and blood just to get me to do what you want yeah you hey i'm just
fucking around it's not even close to funny i'm kidding don't worry but you're going back one
way or another no that is not gonna happen i spent too many years there smothered by my mama's
fears now that i'm free nothing can change my mind there's really nothing that i could convince
you to go home stellar bay is not my home not anymore i finally found the space to breathe
and that's here in amber heights you better go fucking back what in the nebula is wrong with you
she's an old woman you threaten my flesh and blood just to get me to do what you want
you're real sick sure she drives me crazy but she doesn't deserve anyone getting violent with her
look i'll go back all right just don't hurt her it was a job just a joke i was kidding you don't
have to go you don't have to leave you didn't wait for the punch line there's a punch line
hey didn't wait for the punch line guys but excellent dental work thank you okay return
to stellar bay all right let's go back to stellar bay my fast travel wait wait wait wait wait wait
wait wait captain captain i'll tell you there's one thing that i do miss from the
fallout games and i know i know but listen it was listen to me it just i would like to fall i see
them move around outside the their towns when he opens that door i wish i could just open the door
and he could be walking like they did in the rejected games all right hold on wait no no no
no no now fast travel go back here then all right what's the reward there we are hi tucker
captain captain oh you did it my little boy is safe and sound tell the captain how grateful we
are so grateful captain and don't worry i'm never leaving mama alone she'll be very safe from
anyone who wants to hurt her what a strange thing to say silly boy you know it's my job
to protect you not the other way around lie one i was only one point to lie like this
you mentioned a reward i did didn't i suppose i can't expect you to be content at a good deed
done no well all right here kind stranger this is every bit i've scrimped and scraped for years to
save but it's more than worth it to have my tuk tuk home safe again you've ruined this guy's life
now that i have the money you can go tucker what what are you not going anywhere he's staying here
with me you mean it i can go free and you won't hurt my mama if i do no i don't mean it i'm just
kidding what are you stupid you know you believe me by this point how many things have i told you
that was bullshit what are you dumb i don't know anything about but i think it's time you went
about business stranger you leave me in my i might hate you are you an idiot i have nothing to say to
you you leave us alone so good to have my boy back safe and sound by the way tucker yes mama
that was the punchline that you walked away from nothing can ever hurt you here in stellar bay
only you'd listened here we go what i can't i can't wait how do i holster
he's still hostile everything's back to the way it should be welcome thank you for bringing my
little boy i've had quite enough of you max what the fuck he was over you didn't have to do that
always speak to me first before you do anything like that come on protocol you're going against
the hip of dentist oh okay who wants to play an impromptu tossball match everything's back
to the way it should be let's go what okay we need i need to know i have to know i have to know
just wait violence is the only way oh no you hit him everything's back to the way it should be
thank you for bringing my little boy home he's dead what does it make any okay
is he's not gonna be there for the rest of the playthrough is he
if he is there for the rest of the whole playthrough this is fucking ridiculous
she's just looking at him this is all right this is this is fucking freaking me out we gotta get
out of here is there but do people know do people know oh i didn't i have to talk to you
and the little bastard slippery right on account of its blood goomba stump all over the place
trying to crawl away getting so i can't tell the tell the blood from the mud i'm gonna keep
listening but i gotta get in there gotta get out right in that baby wrap stomach and dig it out
if so much as a drop of stomach acid got on that medallion i
i don't know what i'd do might be i'd hunt every damn wrapped out there right what are you staring
wait you ain't from around here who are you i'm junko certified dentist pleased to meet you
who are you names neoka i'm the best big game hunter on the planet you're also the loudest big
okay for a second i thought that was max and the drunk i was like did did we put
disguises on now because we killed that guy it's like we're in disguises because i don't
what happened being the best well i'm junko are you always this drunk you think this is drunk
damn it you need to get out more sit partake buy me a drink and let's chat sure another round
bartender i told you can get me into an information broker another round
what are you doing in stellar bay stranger i'm on vacation
some hell you've chosen you must really love fish i allergic actually that is a
fucking shame uh listen i heard you can help me find an information broker that's
well well well let's get down to brass nuts then shall we brass wait that ain't it brass rats
let's remember that talk business remember the time you murdered a woman's son in front of her
i didn't do anything you want a guide sooner than that you'll have to get me something to clear my
head two rogue dentists i mean i may have been there i tried to start i said hey a robot fell
on his head after he was shot with a shotgun two times but i didn't do it max did max is the
rogue dentistry all right all right well i'm headed back there after i sober up you want a guide
uh what do you need outstanding our dispensary here maintains a stock of uh well
rightly know what they are steroid or caffeine somethings pill they're very good i'm cut off
for the money on account of needing one just about every damn day but i'm sure you've got your wily
ways that's me one and we'll be all set uh you mean calfnoid that stuff's a stimulant
yeah good good answer good answer good answer the two of them behind me well they work we got a deal
or what you won't find a better deal in halcyon than our special one-time offer for a refurbished
sanitation unit remember if it's dirty it's a job for sam oh what are we dropping frames uh-oh
uh that's sam he uh she uh it helps me stay clean anyway i'll go get those meds
of course it does bye okay we need medicine what's this i was in the eyes it was three or four of them
took down with one shot buy me a drink okay nobody tell him what about that the streams
he doesn't know i know about the internet i have a thing over here that monitors how many
frames i drop i see it all right let's go get something to sober you up caffeine
i would like some caffeine hello again dearie what can i get you been asked to pick up some
caffeinoid supplements as a fellow dentist you should know what that is and what a helpful
young man you are nothing like a little pill to liven up the spirits who's your lucky friend
dearie how did for me i'm so sorry but with the iconoclasts and the marauder filth chasing away
what little trade we get i'm afraid i have to reserve my supply for stellar bay residents
our reserves have gotten so low i've even had to start locking the supply room upstairs isn't
it a shame what some people will do to get a little extra uh you just can't trust people
these days except for you and i can tell you've got one of those faces fellow dentists guilty
is charged an exception for you if i could my little cherub is there anyone else needing a
special pickup from auntie abigail well now that you say that um i don't know auntie you'll have
to pry that secret from my sweet little cheeks aren't you a saucy thing i may not be a fresh young
thing anymore but with age comes experience dearie uh-huh why don't you show me a thing or two
experience i guess you've worked here a long time are we about to
the much as i'd love to my rheumatism is especially fierce at the moment and i'm all
out of my medicine but i'd hate to send you away empty-handed you were here for caffeinoid weren't
you who's it for it's oh her did i pick wrong it's none of my business but i had told her
dr williams would bump up her monthly allotment if i contribute like the rest of us
i'm just gonna go break into the room upstairs anyways and you know me
you're gonna kick the door down and just go grab it and leave doesn't anyone else have this
if so i would love to know where sub light supplies don't come cheap believe me there's nothing i'd
love better than to help you but there's not much i can do dr williams managed the town's
allotments from his terminal upstairs even i can't access we've got a hacker dentist with me uh we
sure can uh enough sweet talk get me caffeinoid or you're gonna need a taste of your own medicine
what i thought you were in charge around here auntie you sure ought to be you should be in charge
here no you flatter an old woman me i'm just here to be a pretty face i'm not gonna threaten
every old lady i didn't even threaten an old lady i threatened an old lady's son
and then he died mysteriously from a robotic dentist okay all right what's the supply room
the one upstairs where we store our medicines oh okay thank you
well i can get into these rooms thank you granny appreciate all the stuff oh you got a balcony view
too nice this is probably a pretty hefty lease where's the caffeinoid caffeinoid okay well our
work here is done oh patient records data storage uh somebody can read this 23 000 words
i'm not oh wait wait wait hold on a second this is like a is this stellar bride is this grandma's
fan fiction you've been ever so kind to me let's just skip to the end he shook his head as if he
read her mind with his perfect reading eyes gail the earth uh whispered letting her breath warm
is here i can certainly find a position for you here oh laws she pressed fingers lips only the
laws love patient records dumb what patient not found please try again oh misspelling the name
create new accounts all right let's go hey grandma thank you for everything come to share a secret
with auntie abigail come to share a secret with auntie abigail the secret what's up what's up
you're back good news bad news good news i've got your magic pills these things are dangerous
don't you know less dangerous than a steady supply of alcohol give it here that hits the spot right
in the uh oh no there it is there it is yes we're in business let's go that's scary uh glad to have
you great where to let's find that information broker oh hyrum i ain't checked in on that man
in an age he's running the giant radio tower we lovingly call devil's peak we'll be going south
and west mostly along the road till we're past fallbrook out there there's a western slope
that'll lead us through some uh some fun okay you like hunting right that's fun a few more
of a spelunker rotting river will take you into the mountain caverns we can discuss options when
you get closer okay what size dentist halloween costume already a crowd i don't mind waiting
somewhere until you got a spot open let me tell you i got a ship at that docking bay
new customer profile created greetings user nioca a ship well look at you i'll find a spot
there to call my own for now find me when you're ready uh do you want to go too i kind of feel like
that was like a thing between us and it sounded really fun and cool and shit and you were just
listening do you like want to go i feel bad well i'll come back and like hang out later
i know that sucks uh bye sorry now let me roleplay well i know thank you sir that sounds
like a lot of fun but i've got a tent in this bar here okay sir have a great day you do now
now i don't feel bad was it who are you a fine day for business isn't it anyway what can i do
for you uh leave me alone okay fine all right i gotta i'm pretty much at a spot here the broker
resides in a station at the top of devil's peak travel there and speak with him what the fuck just
happened what the fuck that's in that's enormous that's a what did you just do 50,000 bits that's
more bits than i currently have in the video game and this is a video game that's 500 dollars in
bits that phylactery liches gave i wonder sometimes what they're doing on holy shit
still still just dropping mad money i hear those rich people in bazaar can pay a handsome bit for
rap musk um bet they also pay to make it stink less that's a lot thank you they say happy
thanksgiving in early christmas germa thanks for another year of being the highest low iq streamer
no one's going near you like it's true uh thanks for the ridiculous amount of money
500 bucks in bits which that's a huge amount of money that you actually spent
i really appreciate it that's completely unnecessary but thank you for the fucking
ridiculous amount of money and that's thousands and thousands of dollars that you've given
like an absolute shitload next time he wants it in cash all right is it time to lie is it a lie time
all right 80 lie but seriously phylactery you've been a monumental contributor to the stream
it's kind of hard to find words thank you science should i do science weapon damage what is science
weapon does that include plasma that's not just bullets right movement penalty to accuracy that's
kind of a big deal what about some of the other ones up here i think i'm gonna do the science
weapon damage i don't have it yet oh never mind all right this one here while in tactical time
dilation you deal increased weak spot damage yeah that's the one now how far away is this one
actually kind of in a shitty spot isn't it science weapons are science weapons you'll know okay
okay let's turn over here and 500 yeah don't worry when i go back to the ship they'll they'll
she'll be in dentist garb when i go back don't worry all right slow down i want to die here
all right this is gonna be bad shooters in the oh my god he's running
thank you you've had plenty of practice to do that move the broker oh i can't go this way
this is a really shitty place to be i can i go i have to go back around here
i hear them but i'm not i knew i heard it how they're everywhere why they're just everywhere
oh fuck slow down slow slow slow slow slow slow slow slow good shot stop using those plasma
it's not effective it's the best weapon i have though it does more damage than anything else
i have against everything until i get something better that's gonna have to stick all right i can
go up left i hope i can go through here what scientist look i didn't mean what i said about
your outfit it's very fashionable i swear hello did i not react in time i could have saved him
oh well too bad can't save everybody that is the tagline okay so i need to go around
and then it looks like there's a door or something i can go through hopefully this opens unseal the
door that was easy that was incredibly easy thought it was gonna be much harder than that
okay who's left shit come on that guy has a fucking flamethrower
what the fuck well it's not as easy as i thought this was gonna be
maybe i can just sneak by this i'm gonna go for it i'm not fucking around
all right that fucking actually gets the shit out of me Jesus that sucked oh hurts now
how do i get i gotta go i can i what wait a minute i can't move so i can't even go this way
i actually can't go this way to the left and then i get no i guess should be able to wait a minute
shouldn't i be able to run this way and then around oh god i'm in here i'm not in here i'm
in here no i'm here so this is a wall i can't go over here yeah i'm screwed well we're going
this way and now from here oh fuck i have to actually go all the way around i thought i could
get in there through here wait wasn't i what i'm so confused because i went through this door
wait a minute go through this door okay so i'm still here now i'm still this is incorrect
uh because now i'm on the other side this is so this is not a way to this is that's like a
mountain or something because i can't go this way all right well um we're just gonna have to
go around so i mean may as well this is probably faster to go from here and we also get to you have
a huge gun good all right what do you have for a weapon that thing is insane uh it's a lying
character more range damage yeah i want what if what if you have i want it give it to me
so here you can have a pistol uh yeah i'll take that please uh 747 damage
where is it so this uh this i okay i'm ready good luck captain all right what do i want for
the dentist crew right we're gonna try new dentists but you need a better weapon
okay i want to make sure you have actual weapons that thing's pretty good that thing's not bad you
also can level up again uh just damage sprayed up damage inventory okay you have 120 that thing
this thing's not good i have to give you something a little better than that don't i yeah you take
this one that thing's actually fucking crazy i didn't know i had that engineering no you need
something heavier than that cost of bribes okay 16 hour that's fine okay the thing is a heavy gun
okay take the assault record for yourself but they need to be not completely just
no i got i have hers hers is amazing the daintier weapons ain't gonna cut
manasaur is required stopping yeah but what's left after you're done with them
just go this way just go this way this way this way this way i can fight one or two of them but
not 10 of them this is far but it's no i have to go that way shit i have to go across the bridge
oh my god i'm dead you can't that way is locked the bridge is locked from that side gosh god damn
it so what the fuck am i supposed to do was i actually going the right way
i got to go like all the way down here is so this bridge is locked follow the road
south to the other town uh there is no town self what like was i supposed to go here and then just
go all the way down here you can't fast travel well there's hostels you can't fast travel there's
somebody 5000 feet away from you you can't do that i can do it over here now i'm gonna just go
straight down and then up this way let's go don't go off don't go up the mountain try to go for a
shortcut just take the road just take the road for it is there the other road okay so there's
another road here i guess we're taking that one can i make it from here or do it am i gonna die
going this way all right fuck it i'm going for it how am i still standing who's shooting
okay road this way go ask her for directions hey got a favor to ask you figure while we're out
here in the wilderness anyhow you might stop in on an old friend of mine preferably before we get
to hyrum's it's on the way don't want you don't seem the type to run off and get yourself killed
and i could use the help get on with it hey it ain't easy for me to spill my guts like a cut up
all right i'll be up front with you i hate asking for help i hate it every time i give someone the
opportunity to disappoint me they seem to make it their most immediate goal but this what i'm
thinking it's dangerous uh what do we do let's do it here i was stealing myself for inevitable
rejection i used to run with a band of hunters friends six of us we were on monarch when the
corporations pulled out and we helped a lot of people pick up the pieces i haven't seen two of
them in years those pills were off are you gonna be drunk again i'd like to gather their effects
and bury them all in the same places with the family we once were how do you know that they're
dead i saw it happen hell one of them was in my arms at the time his name was haze and he's our
first stop i buried him a ways from our encampment i'll show you where he rests he had a medallion in
his effects that's what i'll bring home to bury all right a long time ago we built an encampment
in one of monarch's cave systems trouble is a mannequin showed up and kicked us all out
if we can find rebecca and anders they'll know how to lure her out then i don't want to find
anybody and bury everyone's medallions together all right let's let's go sounds like plan it's
down there all right let's move go nice swing almost all right do your special move
okay that's that's a pretty that's a pretty great special move what's your special move
the thing blocking your head keep going keep going keep going keep going all the way all the
way all the way no you might consider stopping the stream
hmm i considered it and i said no get this thing away from me i think you got it see you have like
a thing blocking your head ammo i remember how bad i was at keeping ammo i don't know how good i got
at the game look northwest that ain't it i'm camp inside the building there oh they're clear unless
you're fancy getting shot westbound still i'll let you know when we can start ascending okay
can we start now is this game good yeah i don't know yeah i don't know though maybe
all right this is tough yeah i mean it is i can't okay let me let me give you a little bit of an
example here i can't say i don't want to play this anymore but at the same time i can't tell you why
i am still playing you know i'm saying it's in that perfect spot of being just enjoyable enough
where i'm not going to turn it off i like the scenarios i like the i like the choices in the
scenarios and the easy to kill npcs that sounds fucked up but it's true it's good it's good
it's good and here's the thing i think that's all right you know what i mean i don't think it has to
be a fucking in perfect incredible video it's just it's good it's good sometimes what you're
all you're looking for is just something that's a good game now again i don't know how long this
game actually is but i feel like there's still a lot for me to do i'm assuming that did you
show you how many planets there were there's probably a bunch of stuff to do on every one
of those planets if you're just looking for a game with stuff to do in it this is for you
you're almost done what are you talking about how can it be almost done
oh we have to be careful all right here we go story is short oh well whatever all right get in there
run dead yeah somebody mentioned this it's almost like it's the halfway point
between borderlands and fallout but not more than halfway it's like they half developed borderlands
and half developed fallout buried near the surface of hayes grave is a small lock box its hinges
rusted through and it's wood almost completely rotted it nearly falls apart in your hands
and medallion bearing the letters sharon all right we got it but long story short
i think it's good i would say you'd probably like it if you played it was the best self-sacrificing
son of a saint i ever met maybe you wouldn't i don't know you've been watching it's up to you
now if we're gonna lure the manta queen out we'll need to find rebecca and danders
they took a udl contract on tera too we never heard from them again i think it's time i call
in a favor with hyrum if anyone can track them down it's him uh all right let's go we're almost
here it's way less action yeah it's good not better than good but good yes what do i feel
about the game no you guys already know how i feel about the game six out of ten
uh i think that's low i do not bad huh oh shit it's the bugs i know how to deal with the bugs
am i just missing over and over again this guy's juking me so hard oh good you're alive let's go
this way all right we need to start ascending germa can't formulate an opinion without seeing
reddit has to say first that's not even true what the fuck all right let's get in here
no i haven't formulated a full opinion because i'm playing halfway through the game
i have a slight opinion but i'm not done this fucking redditor over here oh shit you're
okay i thought that was a bandit
uh oh we pray at night we stop at night best character you want to try to tell me that you
don't think that's a good character now okay why there's too many of these queens
this is death if i try to fight these things oh fuck i didn't know you were there just it's all
of them oh man we have to fight it we have to fight we have to fight it we have to fight it we
have to die there's so many people ow the shock good on you i said it does more damage it does
more damage it does more damage just run and there's bugs and shit flying ants whatever the
hell they are all right super gun there should have been the head are you healing why won't you
just die fuck die after too many encounters with manta paulers and minusors you're not quite
yourself when any of the manta family of creatures are attacking you dexterity minus one minus one
minus one when you're surrounded by them that's worth it i don't care i'm scared of giant monsters
wow that's so strange how odd to be terrified of something that's five times bigger than you and
has claws like a lobster okay i get a free perk uh max meter maybe the armor rating walk speed
ultra beater what are you talking about what does that mean movement penalty accuracy uh walk speed
is good in combat i'll take it you're right my fucking god this sucks how much damage
okay what do i have for weapons this is like fire fire normal normal do i have anything else
what about this but like what about shock let me try like electric shock damage well that's
awful four and they're already dead they're both dead this is wonderful all i have is fire weapons
versus fire type is there a water type no don't run away and get all your energy back oh that's
so i'm clearly behind you i'm not gonna run away from me
oh my god i am dude i can't even hurt these things i seriously can't even hurt them
hit him with something bigger what do i have that's bigger i'm just running by him fucking
mountain oh my god are these people good help help help help help how do i get one of those
guns what did you shut up once it died guys help i'm on fire help thank you streamer would rather
wear funny haha costumes i'm laughing because it's true like i mean that's just
that's real i probably could have like an extra 20 armor each if i wasn't wearing the dentist
uniform that's you're right something all right what am i gonna say like shut up you don't know
what you're talking about no you know exactly you know exactly what you're talking about
carry on they don't have anything to say what wait this is not your outpost
help i need help help everybody get back here come help me what am i getting shot by guys do
something do something help shoot them oh my god the terminator just showed up somebody do something
what what no where they go don't leave stay right there don't move no no no no they don't do
anything do they they why won't they do anything talk to them i tried talking to them like three
times i'm sorry okay talk i already tried to do this this station's under the protection of the
corporate compliance crew you a marauder because me and my sunshine that's my gun if you were
wondering we don't take kindly to marauders uh no a coherent enough response i reckon
must be true you're clear but i would caution you against pressing on ahead
this station's plum crawling with marauders you know what are you doing up here i take it you
ain't met the other c3s me and sunshine are doing exactly what we've been tasked with
you want more details you want to talk to my crew they're guarding a small barracks to the southeast
by the edge of the mountain okay what about you need something talk to oh i try talking to you
don't rile the marauders how am i supposed to get over there can you help me quit bothering me i
gotta keep an eye on the area this person being held hostage in there it's my sneak out
what's my sneak out save it in here turn around turn that way so i can go over here
i'll talk them all the way back over here i had a little trouble there okay now i wait for you to
i don't know what to do and a i wouldn't do that and a i would just walk back and forth it wouldn't
do a pose aim thing come on hurry up okay safe all right let's take this guy out nice and quiet who
needs sneak
i don't have the backstab perk i thought i unlocked a backstab thing
didn't i that's the only reason why i did this sneak attack attack unaware enemies while crouched
to deal bonus damage guys hurry up hurry up and get in here get in the grass in the grass
okay fine easy okay sneaking by don't mind me just don't turn around is this good i don't know
dog dog what the fuck is that noise shit where's it going
talking door sealed uh-oh fuck out of here let's go how does he know we're here
how did we snuck in here how would he know we're in here
huh well he knows now oh i can't get in all right fuck it we'll just get we're going up there
face to intercom where's the intercom i can't tell if you're brave or simply touched in the head
what in the galaxy are you doing sniffing around my station unless you are in fact trying to suicide
by marauder and you been lugging a stranger into my station you could use the socialization you
son of a bitch also he hired me what purpose significant problems i am dealing with right now
marauders herbal berry wine three days ago bloody broadcast i need to see the information broker
about no no no we'll deal with information related business later as i said there are
bigger problems threatening my life and livelihood at this very moment the marauders want me dead
and since my hired hands have clearly turned idle it appears i need you to clear out the threat
as my newest contractor you may call me the broker or we can call you hyrum on account
of that's your damn name and doubly on the account of the broker being a dumbass alternative
no emotion me you're here and your the feed's gone grainy but it looks like you're packing
deadly force i've barricaded the broadcast center but i can only hold out for so long
you double the going rate that's okay easy
just kill everyone in this whole area got it hurry before i have to lock them down again
see what i can do okay kill marauders okay let's get it oh thanks thanks for helping me
going up kill marauders kill marauders i thought that was never gonna die i'm itching
my fucking nose no no no itchy nose god damn it why did like my nose hairs have to like
tingle inside of my nose sort of a good hit right in the mouth what am i doing
what am i doing my eyes just glazed over completely i just glazed over and just
was trying to press c but i already why could i not do both of their moves
okay so v so what happened so why can i do c i didn't even bolt oh it was a bait oh no
he died in two seconds oh that was just like dead oh how did you think you were in the room with me
my weapons suck i have to repair my weapons that's the problem why did you just moonwalk out there to
die what i don't don't know what that was for all right these some of these are missing because the
gun's broken that has to be what's going on is that it and maybe equip some armor that's asking
too much you're not going to show yourself dude your pattern is so fucking weird it's freaking me
out okay fucking finally i have to repair these weapons can i repair it on the fly
i can prepare all equipment can i just prepare individual here we go okay we're good
key card now let's make our way cavern points 100 i have 112 line jesus i don't know why i
thought there wasn't gonna be anybody in here what happened to shaving streams this week
uh i really made mainly meant yesterday and tomorrow tomorrow is gonna be uh probably like
four or five hours yesterday was like four and a half so open the door hello never thought i'd
be ecstatic at having the walls painted in blood but seeing as it's not mine i'd say this calls
for a celebration this ought to square our debt one hefty payment for a highly valued service
but i admit i do wonder why neoka has brought you to me allow me to pose my question in another
manner why in the nebula are you here um you know why i'm here can we continue our conversations
from the intercom if you insist as i was telling you before i am the premier broker for all of
monarch phineas must have sent you he's the only one insane enough to send someone to monarch to
rush me i knew it was only a matter of time before he came a knocking look might be late
but i fulfill my contracts always oh you do do you i have lost track of the number of beers you
owe me for chasing raptidons off your stoop careful i know that line i use it all the time
i take offense to that look okay just it might take me a while this time i don't care caring or
not won't change the facts of the matter i am awaiting but a single incoming transmission
containing the information we desire but msi and the iconoclasts are clogging the airwaves
from stellar bay and amber heights and they're screaming voice yeah they're scrambling each
other's once this is completed i'm taking off this is a problem okay so we kick them off get
them out of here exactly what i was thinking wait they hurt us all with their pettiness who is he
talking about of course has inadvertently affected the incoming port and my livelihood
where in stellar bay my former partner sanjar transmits from his office in msi's headquarters
in the center of town don't let him try to fool you while his messages might seem like gibberish
they are in reality coded business orders to off-world companies i understand why he needs
the bandwidth but we had a deal and he's broadcasting ceaselessly i kind of like that guy though
no they're jamming the limited frequencies we have at our disposal
nothing extra planetary can get in or out until the frequency pollution thins out
the safest thing is to convince graham and sanjar to start transmitting on their end
i could just kill them all i'll talk some sense to that i'll be here waiting on the receiving end
luck be with you i have a feeling you'll be needing a pinch of it plus a vat of patience
uh we need a favor oh great i love doing pro bono work for friends
oh you called us friends i'd normally entertain yourself aggrandizing delusions but this time
it's important important to you is not the same as important to me although i do recognize that you
may have earned some goodwill this guy's boring the fuck out of me once laboring for me
me whoa hey there is zero yeah just do it now hurry up look i'll do what i can all right
rebecca hodges and anders watsworth they took a udl contract back when monarch went to shit
and i need to find them i believed them to be on terra too if udl hired two hunters back then
it would have been for creature clearing purposes round one of their spacers choice outposts
these are the coordinates for the outpost under the last udl contract now scram
and uh good luck say scram all right goodbye neoka pick me up some stimuli lotion and a bottle of
purple berry wine when you're next in stellar bay all right so whatever he said i don't know
whatever it was uh we'll find out tomorrow i'll take all this stuff that's a flamethrower okay
uh so we're gonna continue tomorrow and we will see if the stream tomorrow is going to continue
i might be able just to beat it tomorrow it's possible if i'm like halfway more than halfway
through the game it's possible but i'm probably i'm probably gonna be streaming for about four or
five hours maybe we'll see i'm probably not even close because i streamed this yesterday for like
four and a half hours and i'm probably only gonna stream tomorrow for like four or five hours
this is the one in the middle like today yeah uh yeah i was gonna stop like a couple hours ago
but i was getting into it i'm just getting kind of tired you're into the dentist cosplay
yeah we'll see if i continue it at least some of the because i really probably should just put on
like a real armor we'll see all right but that's uh that's it for today thanks for watching guys
we'll see you tomorrow and we'll see what happens at the end of that stream any news on the green
screen yeah the discord channel is open there's a discord channel talked about yesterday i think
uh for suggestions and actions that stream is going to happen somewhere probably december 10th
11th maybe 12th please put your favorite actions there and discuss them if i do not see tomorrow
happy thanksgiving those of you that celebrate it and if uh by the way stream is probably going
to start a little bit later just to kind of stream after most people do their thanksgiving
festivities so the stream tomorrow will be about 4 pm pacific channel is not open is it not well
it will be it will be very soon like within the next hour probably oh god all right there we go
jacket's on the case but yeah uh i will see you guys tomorrow we'll keep going let me just do a
hard save just in case and we'll move on to bits i'll see you guys soon happy thanksgiving maybe
we'll see you tomorrow that's the end let us rewind the clock to earlier does it work no no
i have to check it every time thank you peaceful hailey for the 250 bits germa how are you hope
you enjoy outer worlds it's a very fun game a bit short but fun i think it's good like i said earlier
it's just it's good enough for me to want to play i think it's interesting enough i will hold final
judgments until i either finish it or get real close but somebody said six out of ten i think
that's low i do think it's higher than that also uh i got fallen order and i highly recommend you
play it if you haven't already have a good night i don't know if you'll see fallen order on stream
depends on how uh how much room there is for content and by content i mean how much room there
is for uh somebody said good good i've heard it as oh it's like dark souls and i don't know maybe
i would probably just do that on my own time but i said that about god of war and i got like halfway
through god of war and i stopped playing it so that's part of the reason why i don't play that
many triple a single player games is because a lot of them are long and i lose interest pretty
quickly if i sit there and play a game for 12 15 20 plus hours usually it has to be really has to
grab me completely or i'm just gonna stop slowly playing it but we'll see i haven't there's gonna
be a lull in content here uh once all these new games come out that's sort of no man's land of
january into february not a whole lot of shit comes out so we'll see oh okay i see what you're
doing right but thank you i have heard it's sort of interesting thank you gnarly for the 250 i
thought i liked this streamer but i seriously can't fucking stand the haha i have a fake boston
accent joke i bet this clown hasn't even been there anyone know how to refund gift subs good night
well i mean i have never been to boston england so i mean a fake boston like england like english
accent that's not incorrect refund this guy's bits no i'm keeping him no keeping him hey martin
had a meme thanks to the 500 bits these bits are for felix what if i just opened up the stream
tomorrow without even introducing the stream there's no starting soon screen and i just it's
a scoped on his head and i just showed him in the head and then i do an introduction i wonder how
many people would be upset by that we'll see we'll see how much of a of a villain i want to play
tomorrow afternoon we'll find out uh maybe it's possible but thank you for the 500 bits
appreciate it thank you plank for the 500 bits i recently joined a band
in one of the songs they play live they shout rats rats because of the rat movie also happy early
flag day germa earth germa heart that sounds like pretty that sounds pretty pog i'm talking i'm with
it uh yeah thank you for the 500 bits plank appreciate it thanks for the and thanks for
flag day i guess uh dr flexlyn thanks for the 250 bits i had a dream where germa pain was a bath bomb
with a bunch of gold glitter it would actually look more like germa pop but yeah was it weird
hey dark soul thanks for the 250 bits you're pretty good at this i'm sure you'll do well on
this platform actually i might have some bits for you myself why don't you come to my place and do
some streams from there it's mostly metroid prime that needs streaming but some megaman battle
network needs attention too i don't have many bits but i can give you some pro tips as a reward
i'm sure you can use them what happened megaman battle network that's something i have not heard
in a long time uh thank you thank you newton for the thousand bits 900 bits here and they
say forgot to add an extra zero appreciate it newton thank you so much for the thousand bits
10 bucks oh it was the porn dialogue okay i get it let's get the credits to roll switch on over
here camera on no thanks for the subs guys all of you much love to you thank you thank you thank
you he hates my joke and then hits me no i did i didn't know what it was
thank you so much all of you that have subbed this channel you're fucking great thank you
phylactery lich for the 500 dollars 50 000 bits in one drop an hour ago also insane
stinky beaver thanks to the 500 bits happy thanksgiving happy thanksgiving to you too
hope you have a good one the plushy thanks for the 500 bits plushy hey germ i recently lost all my
friends and my mother and my dog are dying is there anything you do or think that helps you
through tough times well that's fucking horrible that sounds absolutely terrible damn that's it
that's heavy that's a heavy load there um seriously take care of yourself if there's anything that
anything you do you think that helps you through tough times honestly for me at least and this is
obviously not any professional opinion or anything which i would implore anybody and everybody to do
if you think the weight of the world is too much and you're going through too much shit
please contact somebody that is capable of being able to help you through that but for me i can't
it's for i'll give you just a perfect example of recent right recently i've been having a this is
definitely obviously not even close to a ton of of the issues that you're describing but just in
general talking about what helps you through like tough times right so i've had this medical problem
that i can't figure out it's been something i've been trying to figure out for like a year
off and on it's just been there it's been annoying it's been irritating and it's almost like you have
to look at a telescope in like a year a couple of years into the future and at the end you're
hoping that as time goes along you'll figure out what's going on you can deal with the problems
that you have so for me i try not to focus on the exact moment that's happening and i try to focus
on what's potentially going to be the solution in the future day to day essentially and like jacket
just said therapy is cool if you need it use it please use it yes for me to tell you these things
is not the equivalent of somebody who is equipped and qualified to help take care of some of the
issues you're going through if you're going through shit if you having horrible problems and if shit's
not looking good get some help there's nothing wrong with it there's absolutely nothing wrong
with taking care of yourself that's kind of how i think about it i go to therapy every week trust
me it helps so much yeah i'm glad to hear that i wish you the best i know it's um you know easy
for me to say hey i wish you the best right but i really do i really do hope that you can figure out
all that because that sounds like a lot sub chat sometimes is wholesome yeah it's nice to just hang
on and talk about random stuff because the stream is just kind of streams over right now right and
this is just kind of the the post we just chill i like it but yeah you are number one you you always
should try to be taking care of yourself as best you can and however that means for you to get it
to take the steps necessary to do that you have to take them slowly any prospects on bald coin i'm
holding up for a rally this holiday season um bald coin went to zero there are no exchanges
that even traded it has been delisted from every exchange and there was a one million coin supply
and i burnt 999 000 of them i'm sorry so therefore i put so much money into that
well thank you for this journey that i've been on you've been able to put me on thank you for
the journey and joining me on this journey that i you ever notice when somebody or group or or
thing takes a shitload of money from people at the very end they always say thank you for
doing this journey with me what the fuck are you talking about it's not a journey you took my
money and spent it yeah your journey your journey going to the the outie dealership
and then the journey driving back to your garage it's always so interesting though
our journey together oh you losing a shitload of money i lost 10k on bald coin all right we're
almost done here uh gone to lane thanks to the 250 when are you going to return to dos
soon very soon soon thank you for this journey that we've gone on to play dos
it'll eventually happen uh the gray angel thanks for the 250 if you're looking for a good game
you should try out a hat and time it's a super cute platformer in the same vein as banjo and
kazooie also it's got multiplayer mode that you play levels with 50 people at once that's kind
of insane i've seen hat and time recommended a bunch maybe you'd see it like i said there's
going to be a string with there's not a whole lot of stuff going on early 2020 we'll see hey
medhi marin thanks for the thousand bits right now two minutes ago ten dollars thank you i wish
i had more money to give but i want to say thanks for making content for as long as you have
i've been watching you since middle school even up into college it's becoming a bit harder to
catch some streams whenever i get the chance to stream the perfect way to relax thanks for the
past many years in the years ahead of us thank you medhi it's sometimes weird to think about
that i've been doing this for so long that people that may have been watching the channel
when they were a a teenager or a middle schooler is now in college well people that were in high
school or college might now be married with kids it's a little it's kind of it's interesting
unlike you so not everybody has to get married not everybody has to have kids not everybody has to
thank you for taking this journey with me appreciate it guys what you guys don't you
you guys don't want to live the dink lifestyle double income no kids what are you talking about
that's the best lifestyle to be honest i mean kids are expensive especially multiple kids
we'll see i mean uh maybe eventually somewhere i mean who i have to pass down the the germa
nine eight five uh twitch and youtube channel to somebody that's it's gotta be my it's gotta
be my son or daughter you're a millionaire though i am not a fucking millionaire
germa germa is the point nine eight five percent millionaire nope not not really
not even close actually not even remotely close but you know maybe one day i gotta get
one of those sweet sponsorships and then i'm just gonna blow it all on fucking streams big bits
no no not uh no it's really god damn it i mean like what the fuck it's not a millionaire
okay whatever what the fuck shit what the fuck can we get 10k likes please fuck
if this gets 5 000 retweets it'll make me feel better i just want a million dollars now imagine
i wrote that on twitter how uh people with no context i would get i would get mutilated on
twitter for that that would be i would i would see the wrath for that tweet like he just can't
i can't i cannot like make like a i'm not a millionaire joke that's like just not okay
who gives it who gives a shit no don't you know we talk about the tweets that i'm gonna do and
i don't make them i don't even use twitter i i painstakingly open this thing to like write
about a stream that i'm about to start doing my last two real tweets was a picture that i took
at twitchcon and then two months later telling you i'm not at twitchcon anymore it doesn't even
have an auto setup no i don't trust the fucking robots anyways i'll see you guys tomorrow have a
wonderful rest of your night aka you're lazy i just don't really do it i can't even okay i know
before i go there are people that tweet like five ten fifteen times a day i couldn't even think i
can't even think of one thing to write to you guys a week it's like what am i how do i do that
for me to write more than five to ten tweets a day i'd have to tell you about my bowel movements
well that was a good one i feel nice and uh relieved you know if somebody gave me a challenge
to tweet 10 times a day and they had to be you couldn't just write like a b c d e f g a delete
you could just do the alphabet 10 times like actually write 10 tweets over the course of a
day that would be very hard for me to do i did miss one bit yeah i did from smelly boy thank you
smelly boy for the 250 this game looks very neat also during thanksgiving dinner do you
prefer your cranberry sauce to be the stuff that has actual cranberries in it or just the big
fucking jelly slab i'm a jelly slab type of dude myself uh i will take it both ways jelly slab
is good jelly slab is good to spread over the turkey because it's easy to do that but
the cram with the cranberry chunks in it i kind of like putting that in my mashed potatoes just
like a little dollop of it so it's in the center and you go in and grab a little bit of chunks of
the it gives some the mashed potatoes a little bit more it can be incredibly it's very versatile
jelly slab makes a great sandwich they all do put it on the mash um i don't think of that
thanksgiving dinner it doesn't matter where it is just put everything on the plate and just
mush it up and mix it around spin your fork around in a circle it's still going to be great
put it on the ground then all right guys i'll see you tomorrow we're going to see how far we get in
um out of worlds like i said at the end of that stream we will we will have a meeting of the
dentists to find out if it's something that i want to keep doing if not we'll move on to something
again tomorrow stream i know i'm saying that it might be short
but it probably will be because at this like i know it's thanksgiving and i'm not doing like
thanksgiving on thanksgiving but there's also some stuff going on that i might have to do i got to
make around a phone calls that day and i want to talk to my parents and shit for a while so i mean
when i talked to my mother on holidays i talked to her usually for like an hour or two
we'll see we'll see i want to make sure i get it all done but well i'll see you tomorrow remember
it's going to start later not at like one o'clock two o'clock it's going to be four around four p.m
pacific time enjoy your turkey see you tomorrow guys