Hey, what is going on everybody? Jerma here with a Team Fortress 2 gameplay commentary, and tonight I'm going to be playing as the Soldier with the original.
The original, yeah, you probably haven't seen this in a long time. The original, the buff banner, and the market gardener.
Now before the video gets started, I do not do any market gardener kills. I don't know why this was even on.
I'm pretty sure it's because of the backpack giveaway, and this is like one of the only things left over I had, so I just put it on.
I do a couple embarrassing rocket jumps though, if that's what you're wondering, but anyways, let's move on from that.
This is going to be one of those casual type videos where I just kind of sit back, relax, and talk about the gameplay, some funny things.
There actually is a couple funny things that do happen in this gameplay.
And just go over some things that you guys talk about random stuff, you know how it is.
Sitting back, relaxing, playing some Team Fortress 2, baby.
So let's start now. Let's talk about why I selected the original today or tonight, whatever time it is when you're watching the video.
The reason being is because I have found recently that the original works better for me.
I can aim way better with the original now than with the stock rocket launcher, and I don't know when this happened.
I kind of just put it on for shoots and Googles, as they say, although that's not the correct term.
But you know what I'm talking about. I did it just for giggles. I put it on, and that was all she wrote.
I started to get more points, started to land more shots more frequently.
And I think that middle mechanic, I have a whole video on the original if you haven't seen it, just so you can just search on the channel for it.
But that middle mechanic for the rockets coming out of the middle of the screen, I think, at least for me, is a much better direct one-to-one, here's the rocket, there it is.
It's coming out of this spot right in front of you, coming out of the front of the screen.
I think that's better than the rockets coming from almost over your right shoulder, kind of your right eye has to pick up on it, and you aim accordingly.
Just for me, my brain is having an easier time more recently with the original.
Also, I want to bring this up. I'm just looking at my window right now, and it's catching my eye.
And I want to talk about it, just for like a minute or so, less than that probably.
Right now, it is in the halfway between raining and not raining.
And I think, like, you know, that misty kind of fog that you get sometimes outside your window, I think this is my favorite type of weather.
Now, it might be some weird, that's like pretty depressing, like, oh, I love, it's a beautiful day outside, it's a foggy, awful day.
But for some reason, I think this is the most relaxing, best time of the year when it's kind of foggy, not too cold, but it's cold, and you still got to put a jacket on and go outside.
I love it like this. I love rain, fall, winter, these two seasons back-to-back, I adore them so much.
So let me know in the comments section what you think about that, what your favorite seasons are, and that sort of stuff.
But now I want to talk about the gameplay. This is something ridiculous that happens.
It happens to me maybe once a month when I play this game.
So I blow the horn, get my buff banner crits, come around the corner, shoot this soldier, I gotta slow that down.
So I shoot myself in the face, on the wall, because I got popped up by that crit.
I do this quite frequently, like I said, whether it's a sticky bomb that I accidentally blow myself up with, shooting myself on a wall with the rocket launcher with a soldier,
or even something like jumping off a cliff with any of the classes and just hurting myself to death.
I do these things a lot, so I wanted to show you guys, I want to slow it down and do the slow motion replay, baby.
Because slow motion, slow motion makes everything funny.
I'm not sure if you guys know this or not, but any time you slow something down, it could be like your grandmother telling you her secret recipe for meatloaf.
It's going to be funny, like, for instance, let's just try it.
So the secret recipe for meatloaf is two cups of delicious meat, two cups of baked potatoes, and then three cups of small strawberries.
So with Exhibit A, you can see that slowing things down is not only fun and educational, it's also funny.
So that recipe actually sounded pretty good. What was it? Two cups of meat, two cups of potatoes, potatoes.
That's my grandmother used to say, potato like bodata. That's why that's coming out that way.
Getting rid of that medic right there, the soldier. I get a good shot on this guy.
He does a rocket jump and I time it perfectly, but it doesn't kill him. I wish that killed him.
If that killed him, I would have felt a lot better about the situation that me and this medic are in right now.
We're stuck kind of in this house and doing a whole lot of missing. I don't actually hit any people right here, so this is kind of embarrassing.
But let's just jump out of here. I get the assist on that pyro.
And coming up in the next like 15 seconds is probably the best part of this entire video.
So if you minimized, hey, hey, minimize back up right now. Something crazy is going to happen.
This is a testament to how awesome the buff banner really is.
Take a look at how many people are going onto the cart right now.
I blow the horn, turn the corner, make sure I have enough rockets loaded up, and then hello sweetie.
Look at this. I kill almost every single person that was on that cart.
Get rid of that guy, get rid of that guy, and that guy, and you know, just for good measure, sorry medic.
I couldn't protect you, but it's okay. I get your revenge on that guy.
So I get back to that by spy. Of course that happens.
But you see, that's how insane that item really is. If you can get a medic on you or a couple people turning a corner,
I mean, we still lose the match right here, though don't get me wrong, but that was a complete wipe off.
They had like four or five people on that cart and they were all gone because of the buff banner.
But that is going to wrap up the video guys, so thank you so much for watching. I really do appreciate it.
And I'll see you all soon. Just another one of these casual commentaries, just chilling back and relaxing.
So I'll see you guys all soon, and of course, take care everybody.