Hello. Good afternoon. Good evening. Probably good evening for most of you at this point.
How are you? He's not even here. I'm here. Just because I don't talk for the... I'm checking
buttons and making sure things look okay and checking knobs and
twisties and there's a lot of... I got a lot of buttons. There's a lot of buttons here.
There are a lot of buttons. You know, I can count them. You want me to count how many buttons I
have to pay attention to? Let's do it. Okay, so here we go. One, two, three, four, five, six,
seven, eight, nine, ten, eleven, twelve, thirteen, fourteen, fifteen, sixteen, seventeen, eighteen,
nineteen, twenty. I've got twenty buttons that I need to be aware of at all times and let alone
the keyboard. How many buttons are on a keyboard? A lot. This is probably 75 buttons that I need to
be aware of at any given second. Now, how are you? Good to see you. We're going to talk about a few
things. We're going to wait because obviously this is green screen movie night DLC. The second part
of our green screen button times, I guess you could say. This time we are going to be browsing
through 125 videos, I think to be exact, which will bring the total of videos shown so far
after today at somewhere around 250, 300 out of like 700 plus submissions. So I'm just happy
we might be able to get through half of them and then half of them got to get shown again.
I want to make this really clear. There were so many submissions and there were so many good ones
that if your submission did not get shown, I'm sorry, but I'm sorry. That's just the way it works.
I really, there's no other way I can say it. When there's that many submissions, we have to be
selective. So I'm really sorry if you don't get shown. It's not because yours wasn't good enough.
It's because there were too many really good ones. No, I didn't say sorry, not good enough.
Sorry. No, that's not what I said. He hates us. Yours sucked. And then a quote. That's not what I
said. But Oh God, Freddie dread. I just looked over. I don't say anything. I don't like shout
out subs anymore. You know that but Freddie dread. Holy shit. Freddie dreads. Very talented,
talented young man. Follow Freddie if you don't make some pretty sick music. I've actually hung
out with Freddie in real life. A lot of you maybe don't know that. Maybe now you do. All right. So
I plan. Here's the thing I planned on. I planned on doing a free baseball stream hype session,
but that's probably not going to happen. So what we're going to do instead is we're going to do a
baseball hype session right now. And the reason why I thought about this is because there's not
a whole lot that I'm going to talk about. Right? I was trying to think if I was going to do like
a one to two hour kind of a like ask me anything kind of thing with like we do the dollhouse,
I wouldn't be able to answer very many questions because I don't want to just be like, Oh, this is
this thing that's going to happen. This is this funny joke that I want to do. This is this house.
No, I mean, the whole thing is essentially a it's not like dollhouse. It's a viewing experience,
not necessarily a participating experience. But I do want to make sure that I put enough attention
on it because as Ludwig famously told me, dude, you didn't even tweet when we did the replacement
show. So this is let's hype it up. Let's go. There will be a tweet. I promise there will be a tweet
in the next 24 to 48 hours to really hype up that show. But also the difference between this and
let's say the replacement show. I didn't want people to know I was doing the replacement show,
right? Because I wanted that to be a big surprise that we were doing that. And I think it was pretty
successful. Oh, I want you to know we're doing this because this is a obviously much larger scale
and a lot cost a lot more money and has a lot more moving parts than the replacement show.
But no, I don't know. There were a lot of moving parts in the replacement show, too. There are a
lot of people. Is there going to be merch? Yes, there will be. Okay, I will answer that there will
be merch for the baseball show. It will be specific themed merch for the baseball show.
Yes, they will. And I will tell you this. The let's just go over what the show is. Okay.
It is part of the German Baseball Association. A lot of you guys didn't know that I had a league.
I am the sole umpire of the whole game. And in this exhibition match, it's between
the California circus and the Maryland magicians. I am the only umpire of the entire game.
That's my role. And I'm going to take it very seriously. I'm gonna take it incredibly
seriously. You drop some frames. I did. Oh, shit, I did. Let's hope that's not a problem.
Somebody said you're gonna get hit. Aren't you? You don't know. Listen to me. I think a lot of
people don't understand what this show is. This is listen to me. This is a real baseball game.
Between real baseball players. This is a real baseball game that I am going to be officiating.
This this is not Oh, it's a fake game with No, this is real shit. Real baseball,
real umpiring. And yes, I have practiced. You don't think that I have spent at least the last
few weeks studying umpire terminology, studying umpire stances, studying how to call a game.
You don't think that I've done that? You're not going to give me the credit that you think
you don't think I've done that. I'm going to call a very, very good game. Can we get your best
year out of here? Will there be hot dogs? Of course they will. Wait, somebody just said what
the fuck is an umpire? You don't know what you don't know what an umpire is? What do you think
it's like a judge? I mean, it kind of is a judge. Dude, what is an umpire? Okay, we have a problem
if a lot of you don't even know what an umpire is. An umpire is the referee of the game essentially.
What time is it at 4 30 pacific p.m. at 7 30 eastern time. We need to stream with you explaining
what baseball is. Somebody made a shirt for the for the show. That's awesome. Let me see.
Oh, I'll show this. Well, that's probably really loud. I'm not. It wasn't too loud. Okay. But yeah,
let's see. Where did it just go? Oh, there it is. But yes, this is not this is this is not
official merch or anything, but this is cool. Somebody made this. Let me make it smaller.
Look at that. You're going to wear this during the show. Well, yeah, good. Is it going to be popcorn?
Probably. Sue them. That's the first comment that I read. This is really cool. That's awesome. Yeah,
wear it. Yeah, there's we've got we've got broadcasters. There will be people calling
this game. There are two broadcasters. They are they are professional baseball commentators.
That's very important to understand too. It's a game of baseball. And I know a lot of people
have asked this question. So I'm going to answer it. There will there there are no
special guest appearances on this stream. They're on. This is a game of baseball.
There's no other streamers on this. It's just it's just me, the circus, magicians.
There's nobody else. Not a lot. A lot of people are asking, wait, is this is this person going
to be there? What about that person? Oh, I wonder if this let me just make sure you understand.
It's just me calling it a good clean game of baseball. Are you? No, I'm not lying.
You're a liar. No, I'm not lying. I swear. Just just wait. Just wait for the next one after
baseball. If you want to see some potential special guests, OK, just wait for the next
one after baseball. Is that you know, that'll be something that's talked about very soon after
baseball. Are you playing in the game? I am the umpire. I am the I got to call every ball,
every strike. I'm going to be behind the plate. I'm going to be out there in the field,
making sure I call it correct. You pinky swear. Well, I don't there's nothing for me. I don't
want to give much away and we bet on the game. I'm sure the mods will probably do it at the
beginning. How long is the game going to go for? Well, that all depends on how long it takes to
play nine innings of baseball. Sometimes it depends. It's a big scoring inning, big scoring
half inning. You're talking about probably three to five hours, depending I think around along
those lines. The date is the 19th, August 19th, which if you look at your calendar, that's this
Friday coming up here Friday. Is the umpire the masked guy? Yes.
Yes, the umpire is the masked guy behind the plate. The one with the mask. Yes. There you go.
Hope maybe you guys can get it there. Will you please do a cricket stream for EU? I don't know
crickets or no. I'm going I'm answering as many questions as I can. Is jigsaw going to be there?
No. Why would jigsaw be here? What purpose would jigsaw have at the baseball game?
Are you dropping frames? I am not dropped. I dropped a couple frames in the very beginning,
but I have not dropped any frames in the last 10 straight minutes. I don't know if that I don't
see anything on my end. Right when I turn the stream on, I dropped some, but there are no drop
frames now. I wonder if it's a twitch problem. Maybe try to refresh. It keeps loading for me.
That's weird. Is it is it actually happening? Because I don't see anything on my on my end here.
What if it rains? Oh, then I'm fucked. You know, but here's the thing about rain.
You can you can play baseball in the rain. So just drop some more or buffer. Really?
You can play baseball in the rain as long as it's not too crazy.
Is anybody is everybody having um issues with stream dropping? Because I don't see any on my
end. Is this happening to everybody? Well, I don't. Yeah, I don't see any problems at all here.
What's happening? I don't know. It buffers for a second. It does? Oh, yeah. I this I think this is
a twitch issue because I mean, usually I can see it and it's usually me. Hold on. Let me check
something. Usually I can look over here and see like my stream help and see the amount of frames
I've dropped and I haven't really dropped any. That's kind of concerning considering this is the
green screen DLC movie night. Let's see here. Oh, well, let's write it out for a second.
Let me know if it happens again. People are collectively saying it's buffering at the same
time. So it seems to be a twitch thing. Well, let's hope it passes. My DLC is lagging. Oh,
please walk everybody. All right. Well, here's the thing. This all these calls. Everything is
at my discretion. No one else. When I started talking to Community Jake about this idea a long
time ago is because, you know, usually I write up a bunch of shit. I call up Jake. I'm like,
Jake, there's a thing I want to do. It's like, OK. And we start going back and forth. Jake starts
to figure out what things that we can do, where we can do it. We're hiring the right people,
whatever. Right. So I write a bunch of shit up and I give it to Jake. And Jake came back to me when
I first came up with this idea. And he said, hey, you have to call a whole game of baseball
with this idea. Like, what if you don't know like a certain rule? I'm just like, who cares?
He's like, well, what if you don't know what to do? Like, well, I'll just figure it out. Whatever.
I'll just I'll make something up. I'm I could get a lot of calls wrong, but I don't think I will.
I think it's going to be fine. He's like, OK, like, yeah, like I'm looking at all the things
you've written here. And the most concerning thing is the fact that you need to call a full
real game of baseball. And I'm like, yeah, OK. All right. Should we try? Should we go for it?
You need to wrap it up? Well, I can't. I don't want to wrap it up if people are dropping
the frames every 10 seconds. It's not my Internet. Is it happening in a while? Are we OK?
Should I just go? Yeah, we typically would have gone by now. I just it's not dropping
anything right now. OK. All right. Whatever. Let's go.
Ladies and gentlemen, welcome to episode two of the Green Screen DLC Green Screen Night.
We're going to start. I want everyone to get hype in the chat here. I also want to get hype
for baseball. Get hype for baseball. I want everybody to get hype for baseball. I'm hyping
the show up. I've been hyping it up for two years. Get hype for baseball. Get hype for
video green screen night. You ready? Here we go. The first one we're going to be showing here
is called Through the Germa and Flames. Are you ready? Welcome again to Green Screen
Movie Night DLC. Hope you got some snacks because this one's going to be a good one.
Here we go. Three, two, one. He's pretty good. You're in trouble. You're in trouble.
OK, hold on. I'm having that same problem with the stuff plays through the
the stuff plays through the microphone for some reason. That was pretty good.
I'll give him one sec while I reroute this. OK, that should be fine now. Is it? Let's test it.
It's good. All right. That was that one. Coming up next. We've got Samira, you are letting
Germa lap you.
Lightsaber fight for Germa. Oh, sick. Really? Yes.
Yeah, look at me. Look at me right now. Like that. That was awesome. You guys still effing?
Really? That's unfortunate. Yeah, there is no problem on my end here at all. I have my stream
health thing up. I have no drop frames. I've been at 6,000 up cleanly the last 20 minutes.
That's annoying. All right. The lightsaber fights, I got to tell you, it's my favorite.
Those are like my favorite ones. Bro, it's one guy. I mean, it looks like a lot of guys.
I'm seeing a lot of Fs. F because you died. Oh, oh, well, we need we need a different term.
You know what I mean? There's got to be a different term. This should be like F,
Fs for like stream and like F like you died, right? Let's go claim and Andy. Neverhood edit.
I love this game. Why am I spinning around? Dude, I got it. I got it. I'm all right. Get it. Get it.
Dude, come on. Just get it. Get it. What is on my back? What's on my back? Get it. Just get it.
Oh, my God. It's huge, dude. It's huge. This game is so good. I feel actually all right.
I feel warm. I feel really warm, though. What the hell? What was that? What was that?
I got an 830 res at Dorcia. Great sea urchin ceviche. Dorcia on Friday. I think he's lying.
Is this a regular deck of cards? Is that a gram? You got gotta give you. There you go.
There you go. Playing cards. Pick a card. Any card. I don't want to see.
Pick a card. Pick a card. Very nice. Look at this one. That one right there. Good color. That one.
I'm going to stick it back in the deck right here. Check that out. Cut it. It's very cool,
baby. But that's nothing. Look at this. Nice. Egg shell with Romali and tight. What do you think?
What was it again? What was that card? That one right there, wasn't it? Bingo. Jesus,
that is really super. How do nitwits like you get so tasteful? I have no idea. Not a clue. Not a clue.
But wait, you ain't seen nothing yet. Raise lettering. Pale nimbus. Is that the card right
there? Oh, it's a joker. Bingo. Here's your card. Thank you. You're right. Absolutely. Let's do
this. Pick this up. I'm going to strangle your parents. OK, that's what. I'm really sorry that
people are having problems. I think Twitch is fucked. That was a really good one. That was a
very good one. I hope some of you got to see it. I wonder, should I switch servers or something?
The audio is really quiet, too. It shouldn't be. All right. Actually, answer this poll truthfully.
We're not joking around. Truth only. Truth only. Can I get a poll? Are you having a bunch of stream
problems? Like lagging. Because I'm looking over and I'm seeing a ton of people say they have
problems. And answer the poll honestly. Are you having problems watching this stream? Yes or no?
Answer truthfully. I want it to be answered completely and totally truthfully. Twitch,
it's happening on multiple streams. Shit. Oh, did we just deal with it? Did we just put up? I mean,
this is 20% of all of you apparently are having a problem. That's a lot of people. Is it all right?
Should we just deal with it? Sometimes it's regional. I wonder if this Twitch server problem
going to some of you guys. Because I would tell you, because you know me, man. If I have internet
problems, I will not stop talking about it. If I drop frames, you know for a fact I'm going to be
like, I don't understand. I don't get it. Why am I dropping frames? I don't understand. So I mean,
that's not happening at all. So I hope we're just going to power through it, I guess. So 20% of you,
I'm really sorry. But sucks that it's on this stream. I hope they figure that out because
that's not cool. All right, let's go. I'm sorry. I know a lot of you guys are going to be probably
spamming FS or F for stream, but we're going to power through it. It's not on my end. I'm really
sorry. But we're going. Germ of the grill master. I'm going to strangle your parents. Okay, that's
what's going to happen to them. I'm going to put my hands around their neck and strangle them.
Smoke meats for real old fashioned barbecue. Absolutely anywhere you go with the revolutionary
Red Devil, the portable outdoor kitchen from Quantum Homeware.
It's a beautiful day, isn't it? Just on grilling duty. This is the Red Devil
super skillet. This is what really makes a Red Devil a complete outdoor kitchen.
You simply remove the grilling rack and the radiant. Be careful over there. Be careful. Don't be too
rough. Let them like a beautiful grill. Beautiful day. I say you've got 15 burgers and five dogs
cooking on that big $400 grill that's never going to leave the guy. Yeah. Yup. I'm doing it. I'm
doing it. It's the worst job by the way. I don't know. Nobody can hear me, but still sit up here
all fucking God damn day with 15 patties here. Four of them are going to get eaten.
In fact, let me show you. Here's a meal you'd never dream of cooking on an outdoor grill
breakfast. Now our bacon and sausage need to be cooked on a high heat.
So we're going to put them on the middle ring. Remember that's the hot zone. Does anybody want
dogs? No one wants a dog.
So what's your favorite thing about the shade? Well, I even cook pizza too. I love pizza.
Yeah, you're my boy. Yeah, you are.
It's a fucking idiot. Bill, we've got something you're going to love under this one. Now you
don't believe in barbecue sauce, right? Right. You believe that. Say how many fucking hot dogs
I'm going to make at seven and then nobody eats them. Nobody eats seven dogs. You know, I'm going
to eat one. Those are fucking gross. This is raw. I don't even know what I'm doing up here.
The optional perfect chef grilling fork with a built-in meat thermometer.
What's that? Yeah, you want a burger? You do? Yes. Yeah, come on over here. I got
buns. I got ketchup. I've got mustard. This relish right here too. Please go for it.
Whose kid is this? He's going to Harvard. I'm telling you. I'm telling you. Little
Michael's going to Harvard. I'm telling you. This is what it's about. It's about grilling out here
with the family, with the friends, and yeah. All right. Okay. Okay. How much longer do I do this for?
That was awesome. Who's going to use this? All right, let's go. Let's get it.
Does it feel like that? My whole face hurts. What is that?
The new adventures of Morrowind. Might as well get started. Hi there.
Yes, we've been expecting you. You'll have to be recorded before you're officially released.
How? There are a few ways we can do this and the choice is yours. Wait, wait, me? Wait, me?
I get it. My name's Jerma. Nice to meet you. Interesting. Now, before I stamp these papers,
make sure this information is correct. Show your papers to the captain when you exit to get your
release fee. Those fucking armpit stains, man, are insane. What's going on? A new scent is here.
I won't waste my time on the likes of you. Get out of here.
What was I asking you, pal?
Is that Scoot with Shaggy?
Kitchen Duel, Season 2, Episode 3, culinary face-off.
It's a beautiful day, isn't it? It's good. Just on grilling duty.
15 patties here. Four of them are going to get eaten. Stupid fucking idiots in this place.
I'm going to eat one. I need two chops. I need two chops. Two chops. I don't even know what I'm
doing up here. That was pretty much raw. That was a raw hot dog that I say. I wish somebody
else could help me. I need a little more. Hire someone to do this next time so I don't have to
sit here and do this for three hours. Behind. Behind. Be careful over there. Be careful. Don't be too rough.
Behind. Let them like a beautiful grill. Beautiful day. Yeah, Chef. What are you doing?
I'm looking for the wontons. That's a funny hat. That's a funny hat that you have on.
Where are the wontons? Where are the wontons? Chef, where are the wontons? You closed the fridge
at the beginning of the tournament. Where are the wontons? I need them for my wonton soup thing
that I'm doing. Where are the wontons? I mean, I shouldn't be flipping these as much, but I am.
What are you doing up here? Can I have? Okay. Just flip. Fuck them. He's a maniac. I know.
I take a towel and I say what do you want? Yeah, my risotto is going to be in the oven in just
about five minutes, Chef. Yeah. I've got a creamy cheddar risotto and I also have a creamy broccoli
risotto and I also have a creamy mushroom risotto. Yeah, that's awesome. And then pork chops. Yes.
Sit up here all... I only know how to make risotto, but I'm doing it. I'm doing it.
This is done. All right. Come on. Come on. Come on. Come on. First job, by the way.
Nobody can hear me, but time. Okay. Yep. Hi, chefs. What I made for you today is I have a creamy
mushroom risotto and a side of creamy broccoli risotto with a hint, a small portion of a creamy
mushroom risotto. And then what on the side of that, I also have creamy mushroom risotto
and a side of creamy chicken risotto with a hint, a small portion of a creamy mushroom risotto.
And then what on the side of that, I also have two creamy pork chops that I have created and I
seared to perfection and then finished off in the oven. Yeah. Come on over here. I got 15 patties
here. This is what it's about. It's about grilling out here with the family, with the friends,
and yeah. All right. Okay. You like to talk like you know food, but you actually really don't.
You're just a mean guy that got a bunch of TV shows. You're just a mean guy that got a
bunch of TV shows and I'm not going to stand for it. You like it? It's just delicious.
I'm not leaving. No, I think I deserve to win. I need to break that one down for a second.
My favorite part about the last one was how the guy with the grill is saying,
why don't I hire someone to be here and do this? What do you mean hire someone? Like you're the
chef. Why? Okay. What is this? E-clown poses as driving instructor. It's going to get you two
grades off. You're not getting your license today, by the way. No human drives a car like this. You
can get a chimpanzee in this car. You probably do better than the test than you did. You can get
an armadillo to do this test. You can get an ant. All right. Could you pull this way and park
for me, please? Right there, right there. Pull in smoothly. Smooth it out. Stop. Roll your window
down. You get me an army of ants and get them up to the wheel. Four or five thousand ants. What's
going on? I could train them to do a better parallel parking job than you could ever imagine.
What is going on? Get out of the way. I'd like to try a new chicken. Yeah, I'll take two double
cheeseburgers. Two cheeseburgers. Three McChickens. You don't think I can do that? You don't think I
can train ants to do that? You don't think I'm smart enough to train ants? Can I have no sauce
on the McChickens? No sauce, please? What are you talking about? You can't do that here.
They don't wait. You can't do that here? Sir. I'm working that down on your exam.
Stop sign. Stop sign. Stop sign. Stop sign. Stop sign. Stop sign. Give me the wheel. Let me show
you how it's done. Here, you hold this. Put the gas on. Oh, shit. Okay. Yep. This is how you do it.
This is how you drive a goddamn car. Okay. Well, uh, you got an F? Metal Gear Germa 2 tanker mission.
No, that'll be fine. It's the enemy. I need help. That'll be fine. It didn't sound broken.
Oh, wait. Hold on. Hold on. There's a message. Hold on. Wait. There's a special message from
your look of it. I've got to answer it. Glove. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. That's what I
hear. Shut up. Shut up. Yeah. Yeah. Oh, yeah. Yeah. Shut the fuck up. Stupid. You're all stupid
idiots. Throw him out. Throw him out. Throw him out. When did I ever say that? Did I ever say that?
This is, uh, Ace Attorney. That was Otacon, was it? I thought it was me.
It's a rare one. It's a rare one. I don't even know how this game works, but I feel like I would
like it, but I feel like I would hate it.
Let's go. CTF Andy. You screwed that up. What you needed to do there is you had to.
Stupid. You're all stupid idiots. The enemy has taken our intelligence.
I'm on the way to work right now. We can talk this later.
Hello, I'm Jeremy. Okay. The actor. You know, how are we doing? How are we beginning at any point?
The tension, by the way, easy on the gas. Step on the gas. Little on gas. Step on the breaks.
Easy on the gas. Step. By the way, get four or five points on your license not going to go.
And I am a stickler. Very much so for these points. Easy on the gas. Step on the gas.
Keep your eyes on the road. Break. Easy on the gas. Step. Break. All right. That's enough. That's enough.
What? That was awesome. Here's another Mario Kart. Turbo Kart.
Is this real? Oh, I thought that was my mouse for a second.
So ugly in that bottom right picture. Oh my God. What the fuck? You can grind.
It's out now. Germa Kart. All right. That was awesome. Trail cam footage. J-985.
Short version. Okay. Patient J and E mental asylum was reported missing from facility.
Patient J-985 was diagnosed with severe paranoid schizophrenia and was often seen hearing things
that are perceived. Being held in solitary confinement due to discretion towards other
patients and staff is a matter of security. Okay. Wildlife trail cam? Was that the splatoons?
I can tolerate them when they're in small doses.
Dude, is there something on me? Is there something on my back? Is there something on my back? Just
tell me. Get it. Get it. Get it. Dude, get it. Get it. Dude, come on. Just get it. Get it. What
is on my back? What's on my back? Dude, get it. Just get it. I'll stand still and hit it with that.
I'll hit it with a baseball bat. I don't care. Are you filming? I'm on TV. I think they're filming.
Hi mom. Hey mom, I'm on TV. I'm sorry. I'm sorry. Can I have the mic? No, you don't have to give it to me.
I'm on TV, mom. Look at me. I'm on TV. Oh, I'm on the television. Channel two. I'll leave. I'll leave.
The best part is I have a lav mic on. Like the clip-on lav mic. All right now, how does a train go?
Now then, how does your tricycle sound? Would you like your tricycle to sound?
Yeah, yeah.
What you see before you is a choice. A very important choice.
One that will live with you forever. What you can make and might be able to say to yourself is a key
inside of your eyeball, stick it up with your bare hand, and you can eat it. And spit it out,
You dig it up with your bare hands and eat it, and shit it out.
Shit it out, then only then do you need the keys.
Why would I have a tricycle this small?
Why wouldn't I get one for adults?
Get one for adults.
Not one for children.
Adults can't ride these.
The Direct. The German 985 Direct?
Okay.
Let's see what you got.
Excuse me.
Excuse me, fucking Peter Parker just showed up.
Where's Spider-Man?
I know, I know, Spider-Man's coming.
You're not going to get away, Green Goblin.
Wait, who's that new man?
Oh, a house.
What's new with these Nintendo Switch games?
See you on Friday.
I need two chops.
Two chops.
I need a little more.
Pat, pass me the salt, please.
How are you?
How you feeling?
So it says here you have a little bit of a tummy ache.
Oh, I hate that.
Stop.
Slow down.
I'm going to have to take off a few points for that one.
Wait, how was it?
What?
What is it?
What is that?
What was that?
A release date?
That's not real.
That's all for today's Nintendo Direct.
Thank you for watching.
That was awesome.
Tiny trouble.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
Real funny.
Real funny stuff.
You did this.
And you can fix it too, you know.
Unbelievable.
What a real piece of work you are.
I've got something to say to you.
And hopefully you listen this time.
You know what?
I can't even say it to you, but you know what I was going to say.
I was going to say,
forget you.
That's better.
Forget you.
You are a real piece of work.
Hopefully you can hear me.
So what?
I'm standing in the street.
Oh my God.
My rib cage.
You just see my fucking ribs.
It was my back rib.
You fucking idiot.
But this one's awesome.
Take me to a doctor.
Take me to a hospital.
Please.
You hit way too hard.
My butthole.
I feel like I'm at like a weird audition.
You're as an actor.
I feel like I'm at an audition right now.
There's like three people with clipboards over there and they're just like judging every word I'm saying.
How are we doing?
How are we?
Good?
You can you can begin at any point.
Wait, how?
What?
I'm going to be paying a lot of attention to what you're doing by the way.
I'm an actor and I'm a good one.
A good actor can take a script and can change it and make it sound better in front of the camera.
I'm an actor.
Are you an actor?
Can you do this?
I don't know what that was but
just stay in your lane here please.
No.
I'm an actor.
I act for a living.
I can't just like sit up here and just like fucking do like a one-man monologue show.
Okay.
I'm going to have to take a few points for that one.
It's going to get you two grades off.
I think like I'm just doing like an acting study.
Like I'm not who's going to use it for anything.
All right.
Yeah, we're going to play a new song.
This one is something we've been working on for a long time.
I hope you all enjoy it.
It doesn't have a name.
It's currently untitled.
So that's what we're going to do.
It's an untitled song and I hope you enjoy it.
Maybe you can help us come up with a title after the end of the show.
All right.
That's enough.
Very nice.
Now that was a good one.
And now we proudly present to you the tale of the great King Jeremiah, son of Elvin.
I want everyone to understand that the king made a lot of good things happen today.
Don't you think?
You little jester over there.
You're so funny.
It's like show 200 of my residency in Vegas.
Feed him to the lions.
I feed him.
Don't you think?
I don't know how to torque.
How do you, how do you torque?
Get the crown off.
Don't mind if I do.
The king's treasures are so heavy.
There must be so many things in here.
Let me take a look.
Stop.
Criminal scum.
Yeah, that was, that was seriously like, oh guys, I've got this show in Las Vegas.
I've got residency in this place, whatever, whatever city.
And that's after like 180 shows.
I'm just completely phoning it in.
And it's just like, it's, everyone's giving me terrible reviews on TripAdvisor.
Jerma show trailer.
The world he inhabits is in some respects counterfeit.
There's nothing fake about Jerma himself.
No script, no cue card.
It isn't always Shakespeare, but it's genuine.
It's a life.
If you're not going to make it, you're going to have to.
I don't even want to watch them.
No way, mister.
You're going to the top of this mountain, broken legs and all.
We find many viewers leave him on all night for comfort.
Well, for me, there is no, there is no difference between a private life and a public life.
My life is my life, is the Truman Show.
The Truman Show is a lifestyle.
It's a noble life.
It is a truly blessed life.
Yeah, tell me something I don't know.
All right, promise me one thing though.
If I die before it reaches the summit, you'll use me as an alternative source.
It's all true.
It's all real.
Nothing here is fake.
Nothing you see on this show is fake.
It's merely controlled.
Oh my God.
It's an order.
Howdy.
Good morning.
But in case I don't see you.
Good afternoon.
Good evening.
Good night.
Why?
All right.
Yeah, the whole, all right.
Yes.
Okay.
We had to, for those of you that weren't here last time, I need to make sure I say this.
Somebody edited the entire Truman Show movie and put me in every single scene.
It must have taken weeks to do.
It must have taken so long.
I, and we had to, we had to deny it.
We can't, we can't show that.
We can't show the entire movie.
That's not going to happen.
Truman Show is a beloved movie that's still available to purchase.
I cannot tell you to go do that.
I cannot tell you to watch that.
All I can tell you is that's insane.
That's absolutely insane.
Okay.
How on earth do you balance like that?
They said it took over two months.
Why?
That's ridiculous.
I can't.
All right.
Let's keep going.
This is how on earth do you balance like that?
How do you do that?
How on earth do you balance like that?
I think there, do we, I think we saw this one.
Oh, did we not?
What just happened?
Do you ever get scammed in RuneScape?
That was insane.
All right.
Oh, a magical potion?
This is for me?
No way.
Thank you.
How much do I owe you, stranger?
Ten pieces of gold?
That's a steal.
That hurts a little.
Hey.
Does it feel like that?
It feels, my whole face hurts.
My face is burning.
That burns a lot.
What the?
What is that?
Compact Man Strikes Fear Part 2.
Sure was a block away from where he just was.
He was trying to hide from the cops but got stuck on a park bench.
I think he's too scared to get down or something.
Just get him down before the cops arrest him.
3D movie maker, Pog.
Time streamer in sat, preparing to make an arrest.
Hey, I need you to stop.
Oh shit.
You got...
I ain't touching that.
You know what you're doing.
Jerma, what the fuck?
Are you stuck up there?
Here, walk down and get the hell out of here, dude.
All right, Jerma's on the move and the UFO hasn't shown up yet.
I don't know what's taking it so long.
I called it like 10 minutes ago.
I wonder if there's some sort of transition or something that could make this go by a lot quicker.
Can we watch something else?
It's about to get really good.
Trust me.
Rats, rats, pull you out of racks, work it back.
Those bullies won't bother me.
Hey, we're here. Sorry we took so long.
What's he doing now?
Get him out of here. He's being cringe.
I'm not cringe.
I'm cringe plus.
There's a difference.
Jerma, did you just kill people while you were down there the whole time?
Huh?
Like at that store, you only killed people, right?
Yes.
Did you get any money?
All right. Well, all of our time has been wasted.
I don't know how we're going to end it here or we can-
Well, unfortunately, I have to diagnose you with cringe.
Jerma Life 2, shoddily shortened version.
Rise and shine, Mr. Freeman.
Rise and shine.
Wait, how was it? What?
Not that I wish to imply you have been sleeping on the job.
No one is more deserving of a rest.
And all the effort in the world would have gone to waste until...
Well, let's just say your hour has come again.
Huh?
The right man in the wrong place can make all the difference in the world.
So wake up, Mr. Freeman.
Wake up and smell the ashes.
This got a lot of use.
Hey, mom, I'm on TV. I'm sorry.
I'm sorry. Can I have a mic?
Are you? How did you get in here?
I'm on TV, mom.
Look at me, I'm on TV.
Dude, is this something on me? Is this something on my back?
Is this something on my back? Just tell me. Get it.
Hey, you can see the whole park from here. Can you see?
That's crazy.
Dude, look, you can see. You can see the water rides.
I didn't even know there was a park had water rides.
Jesus.
Get an army of pants and get them up to the wheel.
Four or five thousand minutes.
And I could train them to do a better parallel parking job than you could ever imagine.
Do you see what's in front of us? You do, right?
What's in front of us?
Holy crap!
God!
Thank you for that!
Die, you motherfucker!
No!
Oh, here I go!
What?
What is going on?
Yahoo!
Is this the same video?
No, it's a different video.
What is going on?
Oh, just hit.
Yahoo!
What's he doing out here?
Are you guys friends?
Oh my God.
Shut the fuck up.
This water is so dirty.
I learned this one when I was traveling abroad, right?
What?
That's it?
Wait, what?
It's so hot.
What a terrible day to be cooking in the kitchen.
Didn't even go in the kitchen.
How did you make all this incredible looking food?
That's why I invited everybody here today.
I want to show you something.
Red devil.
I have found that it's so revolutionary.
It has literally changed the way we think about cooking.
When I take a tally, when I take a tally, when I say, what do you want?
Do you want a burger or do you want a dog?
Dog, dog, dog.
I think a fucking dog.
Bill, we've got something you're going to love under this one.
Now, you don't believe in barbecue sauce, right?
You believe that true barbecue should be smoked, right?
Look at this.
Just add moist wood chips underneath the grilling rack.
I like mesquite.
And you can cook meats like delicious smoked turkey, even real old fashioned barbecue ribs.
You know, the super skillet really is the perfect block.
But there's a much more important reason for this curved design.
Ah, that's right.
You see what I'm doing?
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
That's what I'm doing here.
Shut up.
You look like a kick out of chef school.
I did.
Shut up.
Just look at that.
That's great.
But watch this.
Here's where it gets really handy.
Simply connect the stay cool handles, carry the super skillet to the table, set it on the
Red Devil's serving cradle, and dig in.
Look at that.
From cookware to heated serving ware in seconds.
Does anybody want dogs?
No one wants a dog.
Great.
As you can see, you really can cook anything, anywhere with the Red Devil's portable outdoor
kitchen.
That was so funny.
The fact that like, oh, you don't believe in barbecue sauce.
No, I don't.
It's disgusting.
What does that even mean?
Okay.
This is rare footage of Mario's original voice actor.
What?
What is this?
Let me tell you something.
I said no.
And he said my girls.
Drugs.
Or drink.
If anyone ever precious to you.
Or said.
Something.
I don't know.
What the hell?
Swing your arms.
Jesus.
None of this is real.
This is a fictional story.
This is a fun.
This is a funny.
This is just a fictional story.
Not fun.
This is a fictional story.
None of this is real.
None of this is anything.
Wait, look out.
What was that?
Oh, yo, what's up?
Hey, I'm.
Yeah.
I'm.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
I knew you were coming.
So I got you ready.
That's your extra whip, extra cream, extra sugar, extra not coffee.
How much?
There you go.
Take it, man.
Yeah.
How you doing?
I just got a heart attack.
Yeah, I think it wasn't close enough.
Oh, fuck.
Oh, a cookie!
Let's see if you can deal with this!
Rats! Rats! We are the rats!
That's crazy.
Seduce me, Jerma.
Seduce me.
That's not- I'm not gonna do it. I can't do it.
Baby, my heart's on fire.
And if you refuse me, baby, you'll lose me.
And you'll be left alone.
And tell me, tell me.
That I'm your boy.
Seduce me!
Wait, hold on. Wait.
It went too quick.
Okay, Jerma- JermaRPG versus
Jermaaker 9.85
Final boss and ending HD.
Okay, let's start this over.
See you later, man.
I see something horrible.
Oh my god.
Damnit.
Sentry going up.
The room is about to go down.
Sentry down!
Spider.
Here I go, here I go.
Here I go, here I go, here I go.
You!
Who's that new man?
Whoa. Oh. Oh, he's very angry.
I'm sweating.
I'm sweating my ass off of this thing.
Jesus Christ!
Stop!
Okay.
That one.
That was like the creator of Boshi.
Just listed out- just went-
Just listed out every like Recess- kid at Recess's
thing that they're doing in Imagination Land out in Recess.
And made a game.
That was-
I don't even know what to say about that one.
That was just-
It was so much stimulation.
Do you think that when the internet was created,
they ever thought that something like that was ever going to get made?
Where's like the like event horizon of the internet?
You know what I mean?
Like when there's no going back at some point.
It's kind of-
It's insane.
That was unbelievable.
All right.
I open up about my fantasies.
Let's see what this one is.
So-
So, my fantasy is,
this wicked handsome doctor in bike shorts comes in.
60 tall,
lean cut.
And he moves in a false tride.
You know what I mean?
I got it, I got it, I got it, I got it, I got it.
I got it, I got it.
It pulls up a license.
I got it.
60, by the way.
And he looks fucking amazing.
Oh my God.
Let me check to see how he looks.
Cut up-
blemish free, blowing hair.
Healthy?
Very, very healthy sounding.
Very healthy.
Yeah,
I haven't had a headache by the way in a long time. If I fly is not down, right?
I'm not gonna get in trouble. You want to eat some bugs?
And we eat bugs together and have a romantic relationship
of some kind?
Where is that from?
Supernatural?
I can't move. You're a razor burn. What's your name? My name is uh...
My name was not born actually. What's going on?
A lot of fucking weird shit.
You did this.
You did this and you can fix it too. This can't be right.
I'm killing you. I'm killing you. I don't care about anything else. I don't give a shit about anything else.
Back up. Everybody back up. I'll prove it. What is this?
I don't know what that is. My programming is just get... What is this? Why does this exist?
I don't know. This fucking guy is explaining this to me right now.
Shave, Sean.
Are you scared? Yeah, I bet you are. I bet you're scared. I'm not scared at all.
You're in Knockout City.
Round one. Let's start with the basics. Get a hit before they hit you.
Oh, that looked like it hurt. You gotta learn to catch if you wanna...
Like that. This cat's gotta figure it out.
This game looks fun. What is this?
On a quest to be the best. They're putting the skills to the test.
And class is in session, baby.
Oh man, that's just mean.
Is this game fun?
You cool, but some advice.
That's good.
Get yourself a crew.
Going solo in this city will only get you so far.
When brawlers unite, it's like poetry in motion.
But hey, it's not all throws and KOs.
Go the extra mile and define that style.
And as your crew ups its ranking on the streets,
there's an opportunity to claim some serious loot.
Okay, back to the action.
I'm telling you, this city has it all.
Team KO, face off, ball up brawl.
There's many brawls to play and a lot more on the way.
You've got environment second life for you
and weapons that can change the tide of battle.
This took a lot of time.
You can't get the job done.
Well, you can.
There's so many small edits.
Just remember, this ain't dodge ball.
It's dodge brawl.
Up and show me what you got.
I'll be watching.
They will knock out city.
I guess you could play it today if you'd like to.
Oh no.
Not what I want you to do.
Another driving one.
Very important part of your test.
Driving through a drive through is very hard.
Why?
It's a very narrow road.
It's a very narrow part.
It's hard to navigate in there.
Okay.
Right in here.
Pull in smoothly.
Smooth it out.
Stop.
Get out of the way.
I'll take two double cheeseburgers.
Three McChickens.
Two double cheeseburgers.
Can I have no sauce?
On the McChickens.
No sauce please.
They don't wait.
You can't do that here.
I'm working that down on your exam.
Why?
I'm doing McDonald's without sauce.
You can't take it off.
That's okay.
Do you want anything?
Small Coke.
And a small drink.
One small Coke please.
And that's it.
Is the car keyed in?
I have the power of God.
What just happened?
I ain't going to be doing that.
You go ahead and sell that one.
Who's going to buy that?
Are you serious?
No, that company's going under.
There's no way they're going to have them.
Their earnings are probably terrible.
Very much so.
Why is the leash so fucked up?
I have to drive over.
You can merge over there if you want.
Is it alive? I don't know.
So slowly merge.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Behind.
It's not there.
Finishing touches.
Red.
Looks very good.
Very good.
We didn't see very much painter, I will say.
I don't like this.
Buy any company that makes...
What the hell are they called?
I don't know.
For the kids, I'll watch it. TikTok.
Can you buy TikTok? How do you buy that?
My son's into it. Big time.
I may have wanted to cook...
I'm sorry.
I think yours might be done.
More than mine.
Oh no, they all peeped in.
Yeah, I didn't mean to hang up on you that hard.
I didn't mean to hang up on one of your employees.
No, of course not.
I'm so sorry.
I don't want to buy Google stock.
I want to buy the TikTok company.
That was...
That was ridiculous.
Oh my god.
Okay.
This one is called a daytime television show.
Jigsaw is here.
How did he get in here?
You're not supposed to be able to get in here.
No, no, no, no.
Stop, stop, stop.
You didn't make your choice.
Oh shit.
Hi everyone.
My name is Sean Elberton.
I'm the actor, writer, director, producer
and main talent of the
daytime television show
Jigsaw is here.
And I just have something very important
that we all have to do. We have to make choices.
And one choice is for you to watch this show.
Because the ratings have been very poor
and I believe that we are
below reruns of infomercials
at this point.
So I figured we could give you a quick little
maybe you could watch the show if you want.
I think you're going to love it even more now
because look what we can do.
Big, thick, man-sized sandwiches.
Yeah!
I almost just took down the whole camera.
Come on, let's go. Let's do it.
No, no, no.
Oh, hello.
It's a me, Mario.
Oh, bingo.
Oh, haha.
Oh, hello.
It's a me, Mario.
Oh, where's Luigi?
Where's Luigi?
Oh, bingo.
Breaking news tonight is an army of
moderately sized Bostonian men flood
the city streets.
We join our correspondent in the midst of the chaos.
Thanks. Onyx here.
It's complete pandemonium out in the street
where posse of compact streamers
are causing complete
and total chaos.
Police reports state that the outbreak was caused
in a car accident with a mythical streamer
Sherman985 who sent his army of clones
to wreak havoc on our mortal plane.
All citizens are advised to arm themselves
and stay indoors until the crisis is over.
It's TV. I'm sorry.
Can I have the mic?
I'm on TV.
I'm on the television.
Channel 2.
I'm doing a thing.
I'll leave.
Who is it?
Hello again.
Hello. Okay.
I'm here to do something other than ruin my
watermelons.
But you have a choice to make
and it's time for you to make it.
You want a choice?
Let's dance.
So fellas, what do you think?
This is show business.
Nothing about this.
That was ridiculous.
One chef. Hold on. Wait.
We got another chef one coming up.
Was that machinima?
That was awesome.
That kid's going to Harvard.
Alright.
Let's do this one.
Chef Jerma goes on Hell's Kitchen.
One chef is just lost.
Hi chefs.
What I made for you today is I have
a creamy mushroom risotto
and a side of creamy broccoli risotto
with a hint, a small portion
of a creamy chicken risotto
and then on the side of that I also have
two pork chops that I have created
and I seared to perfection
and then finished off in the oven.
Yes chef.
It's not good?
What do you mean it's not good?
It's a perfect
risotto. It's perfect.
It's a perfect risotto.
Creepy mushroom risotto and you don't have
a fucking talent to save your life
you fucking idiot.
You dirty pig! Get out!
Get out!
No, we already saw this.
You can't just put it in again.
Okay, everybody settle down.
We already did this one.
Why is it in here again?
Not again.
Hello.
Guess what? You can hear me, huh?
You can hear me pretty well.
Don't put this in here.
I'm not going to drink it.
You didn't finish it this time.
No, I'm not going to finish it.
Isn't that what they wanted?
Sneak? Practical problems.
I don't know.
Times two speed is still two and a half hours.
And you know that you have rights?
Call me.
What is it again?
Times two speed.
Pretend not to understand and throw it.
What is wrong with this guy?
This mustache shirt guy has been doing a lot of fucking weird shit.
I was going to do routine where I shake my balls.
Okay, we're done.
We're done with this one.
Where am I?
What's going on here?
See you later.
Skyrim, but everyone is me.
I made things happen.
I raised taxes on everybody.
Every single person now owes 40% more taxes.
That means more money for the kingdom.
Oh yeah.
Well, it's not the common cold.
I unfortunately have to diagnose you with cringe.
What's that?
What did you say?
I'm going to feed him.
Feed him to the lions, don't you think?
You're in trouble.
I have the power of God and anime on my side.
What are those pictures in the background?
Is that AI shit?
Let's go.
Sire, get down.
I've been a Jedi agent the whole time.
Get down, Sire.
Home run.
Is it me, Mario?
I want to talk to you about drugs.
It's me, Mario.
Oh my God.
You are a real piece of work.
Did you see what I got to deal with back there?
I may have caused it, but I'm not going to deal with it.
I'm not going to deal with it, you are.
Yes, yes.
Kill him.
Oh Jesus.
Turn for the twisted.
Oh my God, am I a good Spider-Man?
Let me fucking tell you.
Peter Parker's here.
You're out of your goddamn mind.
Green Goblin.
Gotcha.
That's not Green Goblin.
Who's that new man?
This is all in your head, you're sick.
Twisted.
Aesthetic psychopath.
Activate laser sight.
I'm wasting my time.
What is this from?
New man.
Can't I just put on a different costume?
I can be Mothboy.
See you later, man.
Oh, that was ridiculous.
Thing.
Hi, I'm Saul Goodman.
And let me tell you something about Saul Goodman.
Did you know that you have rights?
And so do I, Albuquerque.
I'm here to fight for you and to fight for your rights
and fight for you in a court of law.
Give me a call.
Better call Saul.
Better call Saul Goodman.
Close enough.
Oh yes.
I'm sounding like Cookie Monster.
I'm doing Cookie Monster, not in Mario Kart.
Reset.
I'm glad so many people
used the Mario Kart stuff.
Oh, just here I go.
I'm Cookie.
Cookie.
Let's see if you can deal with this.
Hi, ladies and gentlemen.
I'm Super Mario.
We've made a lot of jokes here today.
We've had a lot of fun.
My head.
What did they do to my head?
This VHS is so scuff.
The music ones are awesome.
The reason why the music ones are so good
is because they're kind of a nice interlude
between the insanity.
They're nice.
All right.
Let's catch our breath a little.
That was awesome.
Speaking of catching our breath a little,
after this one,
we're going to take a break.
I'm going to go pee, get into the water
and we will do the second half.
Let's watch this one.
Yeah.
Why am I spinning around?
Dude, I got it. I got it.
Hey, coffee. Coffee.
Anyone want some coffee? Coffee.
I just brewed a fresh pot of coffee.
Hey, coffee.
Hey, who wants coffee?
I got a fresh pot of coffee.
Whoa.
All right.
Let's take a break. I'll be right back.
Go refill your water or whatever else you're drinking.
We'll be back in like two, three minutes
and we'll start Derma Goes to the Bar.
See you in a minute. I have returned.
Hello.
I'm going to pick up right where you left off.
Derma Goes to the Bar. Are you guys ready?
Are we good to go? Okay.
Give everybody some time to come back.
Three, two, one, let's go.
That was terrible.
Absolutely terrible.
Oh my god.
Fucking god. Terrible.
Hey, what's up, bro? How are you doing?
Coffee.
Fucking weirdo? What?
I'm blue.
Why would you do any of that shit?
You're a fucking idiot if you think that I can do that.
Fuck you, man.
How do you get mad at Minecraft?
Most people order their fucking coffee.
Usually people order milk.
Hey, wait.
They can't even hear me.
Hey, everybody.
Everybody, look over here.
Hey, you. Wait.
Look.
No, I ain't going to do it. No.
Hey, two, three.
Yeah.
What the fuck is that?
And when I say let's play,
I use that term pretty loosely.
Hey, chummies.
So you're telling me this guy comes here every week?
That person's a fucking weird person.
Let's live in it.
I've got my money.
Let's spend it all.
Onion ring. I've got an onion ring.
What a psycho.
Damn.
Absolute perfection.
No ifs, ands, or buts.
This fight here
is absolute perfection.
That was fucking awesome.
If Dermot was saw,
gas fit with video, apparently.
Okay, I'm interested.
Now, I know how much you don't like smelly smells.
I know how much you think it's disgusting.
Beetles and bugs, you were a child.
Now you must,
because if you cannot be in this room
for more than one minute,
gas, gas, gas, the gas will start flowing.
Only after you puke, though.
I gotta make that really clear.
I've been talking for a while.
If you puke in that toilet,
gas will fill the room.
Gas.
What?
Gas will fill the room.
Make your choice.
Will you stand the smelly smells
for ten minutes,
or will you puke into the toilet?
Fill the room with gas.
Gas fill the room with gas.
Gas.
Make your choice.
Adventure to 7-Eleven.
Hey, who wants coffee?
Hmm.
Guy got coffee.
I just brewed a fresh pot of coffee.
Fresh pot.
You want coffee?
I just got a fresh pot of coffee.
Coffee.
Those are the best.
Ah, that hurts a little.
That's supposed to feel like that?
It feels...
My whole face hurts.
My face is burning.
That burns a lot.
What the...
What is that?
And...
I feel actually alright.
I feel warm.
I feel really warm, though.
What the hell?
What was that?
I'm going to lie down.
I don't know who gave it to me.
Why am I blue?
Is this all you have?
No.
You got another card back there.
You're going to have to bring it in.
See, that's it?
Yes.
How much?
That's $49.
Put the card in.
It goes the other way.
The card reader, it goes the other way.
You have a chip on it, right?
The chip goes chip-facing it.
How many stores have you been to in your whole life
that you don't know the chip goes the other way?
Peter and Harry?
I'm going to put some dirt in your eye.
Sire says that you're in big trouble, Harry.
Oh, yes.
Of course.
Oh, he's very angry.
Sire, Sire.
That was awesome.
Pat, pass me the saw, please.
What's worse than this, my enemy
Swear to the sympathy
Every devil worse than this, my enemy
My enemy
No, no, no.
What?
What the fuck?
I love this card coming up here.
I chop you into me, liar.
That was awesome.
Wait, there's another Truman Show?
Edit?
Those last two were awesome.
Here comes Jerma in the Truman Show.
I don't know if this is related.
Why don't you let me fix you some of this new mo' cocoa drink?
All natural cocoa beans from the upper slopes of Mount Nicaragua.
No artificial sweeteners.
Wait, what?
I've tasted other cocos.
This is the best.
No, no.
Wow.
Spoilers for the movie.
This is what it looks like up close.
Yeah, I mean, you're gonna get spoiled.
From back there, it could have been anything.
You can speak.
Real funny.
You did this.
Hopefully you can hear me.
Are you in charge of this?
I am the creator of a television show
that gives hope and joy
and inspiration to millions.
Interesting thought process.
Look at me, look at me.
What a real piece of work you are, huh?
Oh, you created everybody.
Did you though?
You know what?
I'm gonna twerk.
Yeah, I'm gonna twerk.
Say something, god damn it.
You're on television.
I'm on TV, Ma.
Look at me, I'm on TV.
Oh, I'm on the television.
Channel 2.
Hey, in case I don't see you.
Good afternoon, good evening, and good night.
Bye, Mom.
Pasta tonight.
Pasta tonight, Mom.
I don't know what movie this is from.
Our TV show.
This is probably a movie.
I don't know.
I've never seen this movie.
But here it is.
Spoilers?
Oh, it's the Titanic.
Don't splash, please.
Throw him up.
Oh god.
I'm getting away from him.
Those who want to hear another song, follow me.
Oh Jesus.
This is fucked.
is fucked this is fucked this one's called the mandalorian theme song damn oh my god no no
i can't oh my goodness that was so fucked up
so
what is happening oh that was a good one oh shit artist oh an artist one finally an artist one
take a little bit of this it looks good don't you think uh how you say it looks very
looking pretty good and this is an among us character i'm gonna scream is masterpiece
no no it's masterpiece no no what do you know about the art you know nothing about
art you don't know anything you know nothing about art
oh yes yes yes yes yes i did a little bit of this i hate this character by the way is the worst
character of the green screen extra green touch what do you think huh what do you think about
painting more like belongs in the trash you do not like my art work but you are stupid very stupid
and she tried to set your face in your cooking head that is a masterpiece right here fucking
dope idiot at at instructor how we doing how are we good you can uh you can begin at any point
i'm gonna be paying a lot of attention to what you're doing by the way you can you can go ahead
you can come out here and take a right you can go you can get on the highway here stop stop slow
down i'm gonna have to take a few points without you didn't signal when you went right and that's
the first thing that we're gonna do here by the way if you get four or five points wrong here
your license is not going to come through you can start to you can merge over here if you want
so slowly merge slowly merge way too fast very nice now that was a good one that was
actually a pretty good merge hi i'm saw goodman and let me tell you something about
keep your eyes on the road here perky i'm here to fight for you
and to fight for your rights and fight for you in a court of law
better call sal careful better call sal goodman do you mind just go ahead let me go i got this is my
car you just hit you hit it you hit it back up at a 40 degree angle turn around back up drive
straight turn right at 45 degrees pull in you learned this already you're not getting your
license today by the way got very clear i've not what i want you to do because i want you to pull
with that mcdonald very important part of your test driving through a drive through is actually
very hard i was gonna say how are they gonna do that it's a very narrow road it's a very narrow
part of it's hard to kind of navigate right in here right there right there stop roll your window
done get move out get out of the way double cheeseburgers
yeah two double cheeseburgers three mcchickens yep and can i can i have no sauce
on the on the big chickens no sauce please a large number three
they don't wait they don't you you can't do that here i'm working that down on your exam
uh no that's okay that's all right uh can you uh do you want anything can you do this
and a small drink a small one small coke please okay
hello my baby hello my honey hello my ragtime gal send me a kiss my boy baby my heart's on fire
and if you refuse me baby you'll lose me and you'll be left alone and tell me tell me that i'm your
welcome to jet records that's so cool i always wanted brothers this costume i think it's two
left hands like hold can you hold on i'd rather not talk about this crazy right i'm crazy or not
right look at his face dude that's a good question my thumb i can't put the thumb over there
what the fuck all right let's do this there we go that's a bite there it is there we go
had a dream last year we became like a mainstream celebrity by pioneering a new type of stream
we would play a game like i'm sure about that how we doing how are we i've been waiting to ride
this one man you can uh you can begin at any point i'm gonna be paying a lot of attention to
what you're doing i'm not scared though are you scared yeah i bet you are you you can go
ahead you can come out here but you're scared easy on that easy hold it back a little long a little
longer you just hit it you hit it you bumped his bumper it's all right i'm all right i'm all right
i'm all right yeah yeah yeah yeah you're not getting your license today by the way
i'll throw him out but here to present stream game of the year is germa x sus at the streamer awards
oh god who is this germa this is an audio test what's up audio test testing the audio
hello come on dude and a fart simulator 2013 which is a great great game by the way i suggest
you all download it the winner of the best stream game of the year is
mike so there's nobody there's nobody here to accept art simulator 2013 so we have to oh jesus
this is still the same video how are you how are you feeling
that you would need to do is you need to you need to relax you step on that gas
when did it start what the fuck was that last weekend okay any bloating in the gas
any uh flatulences that i need to know what is happening how often are you uh
how often are you using the cringe drum look at what i have for you look what i've made for you
it's beautiful it's beautiful no the colors it looks fantastic it's one of the best i've ever
painted well he's taking the subway don't mind us she just needs to use the elevator
wait who are you you know who i am i do drugs and alcohol all right everyone i'm peter park
that was insane that started and ended completely differently sort of griffin steed 2 yes this is
creepy pancakes three o'clock in the morning and you're near the link hash house ago though
best pancakes best cheeseburger i've ever had best burger i've ever had that fucking haircut
i keep it here make sure mp is the shit like you and then i'm doing something fucking dumb i get
you you know this was welded with dragon bone i don't know if you can tell but looking at that
they call it dragon stone steel you think you can handle that
you think you can handle that let's find out why don't you come over this way and let's see
come on
i got a lot of help you violated the law what is going on what the fuck is happening
what is this what is going on i wouldn't even hit that i'm gonna get away green goblin
i wasn't even in that video what was that video okay well i that was that was a fun video all right
jerma meets the green goblin you're not gonna get away green goblin wait a minute that's not
fuck you spider-man i'm the green
hulk
whoa hey hey hey you can see the whole park from here can you see
that's crazy dude look you can see you can see look at you can see the water rides
i didn't even know the park had water rides
oh man that was a good one
why are there so many scary ones
hello please leave a message after the tone
what the fuck do you want to know something funny have you guys seen have you guys seen
the the meme thing where it's oh oh man jerma it's it's a different jerma look at the different
eyes the different face shape from 20 like 13 to 2022 right i'm sure you've we've all seen it
right the funniest part about that it's like they're trying to show my eyes like look the
angle of his eyebrow bone is different his chin is a little different it's sagging a little more
after aging 10 fucking years what they are describing in that meme is human aging
my face does look a little different of course it does because i was 25 to 36 yeah it's called
human aging it's called my skin is a little saggier because i'm not 25 anymore anyways let's go
are you laughing at this one all right more spider-man more spider-man um there's probably
a lot of spider-man spoilers in this but like okay whatever i hope you did a lot of
transformative action here good spider-man let me fucking tell you
do you want to play games are you guys seeing this yeah who's that no that's someone else
harry potter class is in session right now i don't know it looks like he's charging
and if you're going to use your wand i might as well suggest you use it
so you're a little shit and you always were but you didn't know harry that i have lightning
oh oh i killed him i think i killed him oh i should uh harry harry are you okay harry
uh the second half of the spider-man no way home movie felt like a college humor video
oh was that not a bad opinion but a part of me almost felt like some of the scenes
in the new spider-man movie like the director was just going to start walking around on the set
hey run
and by the way spider-man
the deal is not on the table anymore yes it's a me mario let me tell you something if somebody
want to tell you to take drugs always say no you say luigi try to drink and do drugs one time
and i said no and he said mario and i said no
peter parker's here all right hold on i need people are saying what the fuck what's that
opinion your opinion sucks i'm just saying that the second half of no way home felt like a saturday
night live sketch like if i was waiting for the audience to laugh with like a laugh track i'm
sorry i'm sorry i did i like the movie i thought it was i thought the movie was fine i'm a huge
spider-man fan i am a massive spider spider-man is like my favorite character spider-man and venom
but i like i almost felt like i mean maybe i said this before but i'll say it again it felt like
at some points in that movie they were going to look into the camera like jim from the office
like it would have actually made more sense to me if like toby maguire sometimes just kind of
looked in the camera like yeah i thought the movie was fine i like the first two better i like the
first one probably the best the first one as in of that trilogy right nice reddit taste i'm it's
just my opinion okay but i just i it took me out of the movie a few times i think you're wrong so
that's all right you you are free look i like the venom movie okay i watched the venom movie and
when i was done i went that was a good movie i liked that was a good movie right so like you
could you could go holy shit dude what a fucking moron right that's fine i mean the the venom the
venom movie was was a terrible movie but i liked it that's fine you can think i'm stupid that's
fine we all have our opinions on movies mine just happened to be correct what you were talking about
me and my kingdom just a little too a little too harsh no this was welded it's dragon bone
i don't know if you can tell by looking at that i remember i was there when this i almost fell
backwards i remember i was there when this was crafted in dragon blood they call it dragon stone
steel you think you can handle that you think you can handle that let's find out you want to duel
you and me dragon bone steel with whatever you have there whatever that is what's that again
stainless steel yeah we all know how we all know how sturdy that is why don't you come over this
way and let's see come on why don't you come here that hurts a little that's supposed to
feel like that it feels my whole face hurts my face is burning that burns a lot what the
what is that i feel actually all right i feel warm i feel really warm though
what that what was that what was that what was that
i'm gonna lie down i don't know where i where who gave it to me
i thought i was like what can i what's happening on the screen right now
was that another player can you see what i got dealing with back here you think i'm gonna do that
shit no you do it you go do it you deal with this no i'm not dealing with that i might have i may
have caused it but i'm not gonna deal with it you are you're the one with the money
what does everybody gets wrong to me just about quarter to five and take a look at this viral
video all right vivian gomez wrote on facebook that her security camera captured this on sunday
morning there are people on facebook who say it looks like dobby from harry potter or a ghost or
an alien or a kid in flip-flops and underwear we think it looks like lisa doing her sunday morning
dance i don't know lisa were you in la junta on sunday i know she was out of town give it away
the video has been seen by 11 million people that's gonna be the new dance craze right there
oh shit what you see before you is a choice a very important choice one that will live with you
forever but you can make it and you might be able to save yourself i'm of course talking about drugs
and alcohol hi everyone my name is uh sean elwardson i play the character jigsaw on the
daytime tv show jigsaw is coming for you i wanted to make sure i did this quick little psa
that um we all have a choice to make and that's drugs and alcohol no reason to do
drugs is something if you ever approached and pressured make your choice
and say no no to drugs now let's get back to the show i love the drug psa is this so good
wait what i didn't read that how are you i just moved in yep new to the neighborhood
what are you doing here let me in your house can i come in oh yeah okay right of course
i have some dental work done and can i come in can i just come in
and we'll i have to come in though can i come in your house no sir please leave oh this is back
so sweaty take a little bit of this oh that looks good don't you think oh don't pretty good
don't look at it don't look at it it's masterpiece no you know anything you know nothing about art
touch what do you think huh what do you think about painting what i have for you made for you
beautiful it's beautiful no finishing touch let's add a little bit more red oh
i don't like this i don't like this part right here let me change it
magnetic absolutely magnetic magnetic last final touch i swear i will not touch it again
oh beautiful beautiful painting you don't like you do not like my artwork but you are stupid
very stupid you're fucking dope idiot yes you know you know what's crazy uh the range in
submissions here we go from mario oh whoa oh personal best speed run to murderer shit one
after the other this is a german burger boy play a scary game i think this is the one where burger
boy pukes please don't appear in the elevator this game's awesome this game's great oh you didn't
show when he puked those of you that don't know burger boy throws up in that video he pukes like
kind of back into his cup i think he's done more than once all right germa cart facing the wrong
way easy on the gas easy hold it back a little uh little on the gas there you can go you can
get on the highway here this is a big turn stop stop slow down i i'm gonna have to take a few
points for that one why is he here keep your eyes on the road here please you can't step on
that gas oh you you screwed that up what you needed to do there is i'm not happy about it
slowly merge slowly merge oh way too fast actually too fast
yeah oh you're leaving out of my time told oh the misery
i know it's been hard for you and i don't believe in screen
oh hi i'm not sure of a really nice house so come over your house and i would you'd let me in right
again steve actual voice actual voice acting oh shit wait that wasn't that wasn't from a movie
trailer or something that was actually i was gonna say yeah the audio was was that's pretty
fucking cool german rides his tricycle why is everybody driving like crazy to my beautiful wife
to my adoring husband adoring what about handsome i like adoring hey yo uh you gotta leave
you gotta leave now i'm not ending here fucking big big big dick's coffee i was gonna say it's
big dick's coffee fuck out of here there's a hundred and four days of summer vacation
so the annual probation is finding a good way to spend it
building a rocket or fighting a mummy or climbing up the eiffel tower
discovering something that doesn't exist
surfing tidal waves creating nanobots or locating frankenstein's brain
finding a dodo bird painting a continent or driving our sister insane as you can see there's
a whole lot of stuff to do before school starts this fall so stick with us because
phineas and ferb are gonna do it all so stick with us cuz phineas and ferb are gonna do it all
the chuck e cheese
look at me i'm on tv oh i'm on the television channel two auto hey oh can you count with us
auto yeah i can count with you absolutely my name's auto how many treats are on the table
one two three four auto count again auto try again no just four one two three four
it's connected to that's a that's an ethernet cable yes i know how the ether works gear more
no ethernet it's gon play no no it's just asleep arise arise what is arise again control alt seven
what you're failing to understand is the ball ache that we both had trying to get this from inside
there to out here that would make a lot of sense to me a giant heart yeah okay but how were we
supposed to see the big red button when we were inside you're right idiot um
best buy menu word i've got it did see them and you why am i muted wait how did i just get muted
that was weird i didn't press any buttons oh how long have i been muted for how long have i been
muted for since the start of the video oh shit i was i was asking like where the whole thing
what i was just like ranting for two straight minutes why was i muted oh okay i was saying
where am i i was like where am i why am i not in here this is what and then the mods were lighting
up it was like just this is to add add it's not supposed to be here oh okay all right well
whatever let's go this is just this is just an ad what we do in the shadows it's just like a funny
clip from the show is it that's funny oh shit really the ultimate showdown
excuse me why it's time for you to pay such a bad road how much you're going down full 60
fps not 30 not the 30 bullshit are you ready you don't look ready
i don't know who wins i'm gonna say two two was by far the most unhinged without a doubt
oh where's louis where's
oh my god
i see you down here
you do it you go do it you do it i may have i may have caused it but i'm not gonna deal with it you
are i'm gonna do it you're the one with the money someone else come on because we can't just stand
here all day dude wait i got shit to do come on come back yeah yeah okay yeah look at me look
at me right now yeah i won oh shit dude you know those movies it was a movie
when it fucking popped up from the top it's a boom microphone isn't that funny what are they
talking about oh oh my god we've got a fast turbo and purple alien video i am actually very very
excited for this one there's an entire saga entire what did i did a boston accent for five seconds
i got rid of that let me try that again there's an entire saga here let's go hey the seat shitter
ready yes are you ready you don't look ready i have both of my hands in my back pocket
yes like oh are you ready because i mean very clearly we gotta go no i ain't gonna do it no
no no why not popcorn machine i've been waiting to ride this one man yeah you know i heard this the
scariest ride park i'm not scared though are you scared i'm not scared at all yeah i bet you're
scared no okay okay yeah dude hey yeah dude hey yep yep yep you're gonna scream no no
you're gonna scream though no I ain't gonna scream you're gonna scream no I am
I'm all right. I'm all right. I'm all right. Oh hey
Hey.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, hey, you can see the whole-
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, you see it?
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
It's right there.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Dude, look, you can see it.
You can see the water rides.
I didn't even know that they park had water rides.
Wee!
Yeah, dude, hey.
Let me give you a better one.
This is what I would do on a roller coaster.
I wouldn't be saying wee.
I'd be screaming.
No, I ain't gonna scream.
You're a man.
You travel.
You fish.
You survive.
You're a man.
I'm a man.
You travel, you fish, you survive, you fight, you conquer, you don't let anything get in your way,
Ford, because you're a man. Here's another, another scary one. This one's going to be scary.
This guy's sexy. Oh, hi. Hey. I'm new in the neighborhood. It's nice to meet you. I
have a really nice house. Thank you. Yeah. I'd love to come in. Could I come in? Could I come in
your house? I'm sorry. I don't. I'm new in the neighborhood. My family just moved in down the
street. Yeah. And I just was trying to meet the neighbors. I mean, I just trying to meet the
neighbors. That's all. Yeah. Yeah. But like, I don't know you. I mean, yeah. That like breathe in.
I love what you did with the yard, by the way, that beautiful grass,
the grass looks beautiful. How do you get up that long? I don't know if you give some pointers.
You can't come in my house. Can I come in your house? You've been here for an hour.
No, no. You dance inside my house every day. All right. Call me if you want to talk. Call me.
I don't have your number. Can I come in? No, I'll wait here until I can. No, it's all good.
Don't worry about it. No, I barely sleep. What the fuck? Do you like drugs? I've got a lot.
Just let me in your house and I'll give you whatever you want. Bleed. Coke. That's all I got.
I don't got anything else. But you know, call me. Let me in your house. Let me in your house.
Let me in your house. Jesus Christ. Can I take a bite and will you guys get over this?
If I take a bite of this, will you get over it? Not as bad as I thought it was going to be.
It tastes kind of like shit though. Wait a minute. Got it back. All right, folks, take your seats.
We're going to be starting here in just a moment. We're going to be running a quick audio test and
then the show will begin shortly. All right. Ready? This is an audio test. What's up? Audio test.
Testing the audio. I'm going to scream. So turn down your volume. I'm being dead serious.
Hey, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa. That was probably horrible. I just got these microphones
like a day ago. My apologies to everyone. We have no idea who that guy was. I'm sure we'll get that
sorted. Our first performers of the night are the Banana Bros. Dirty. Hello, ladies and gentlemen.
Thank you. Thanks for coming out. Yeah. We got a new song that we're going to play. I learned this
one when I was traveling abroad, right? All right. Yeah. We're going to play a new song. This
one is something we've been working on for a long time. It doesn't have a name. It's currently
untitled. So that's what we're going to do. It's an untitled song and I hope you can help us come up
with the title at the end of the show. It's going to be peppy. It's going to be a lot of upbeat. So
hopefully see somebody out there dancing. Okay. And a one, two, one, two, three, four.
Oh,
sounds like before a band, a orchestra starts playing.
Last one. Don't thank yourself. No, that's broken up. We've been working on it for like what?
Two weeks, three weeks now. Yeah. John, John came up with the lyrics. What the fuck?
On September 22nd, 2007, the Albertson three were planning to perform at the Sus Grill,
a local bar in Conchester. It was also on this night that they decided to film all their
performances, having the Albertson three also in this compilation. What you're about to watch now
is the real tape of the performance. Hello, ladies and gentlemen. Thank you. Thanks for coming out.
We got a new song that we're going to play for you here. A new song for context. It was the previous
year where they released their commercially failed album in the dollhouse. So hearing new music come
out is exciting for some of the people in the crowd. I hope you all enjoy it. It doesn't have a
name. It's currently untitled, so that's what we're going to do. It's an untitled song and I
hope you enjoy it. Maybe you can help us come up with a title after the end of the show. Another
thing the crowd noted was the absence of the lead singer, Jeremy, making only two on stage. However,
in a Twitter post from earlier that day, it was confirmed he wouldn't be coming down due to sickness.
And so the two instrumental team would shortly begin. And a one, two, one, two, three, four.
It was terrible. The crowd was so very shocked by what they were hearing right now. Not real music.
It was time for them to get off the stage, but not before doing this.
Thank you. Jeremiah was struck over the head by Jeremy's guitar. Crowd goers were obviously
frightened by this altercation. And now you could see an unconscious Jeremiah
laying on the floor as the cameras are shut off. And the interviews would begin.
I was in the chair. I was in there. I was five, 10 minutes straight. Just add the TikTok UI
to that whole thing and it'll be a 10 out of 10. It'll be a literal 10 out of 10 and add music to
it. I'm coming for you. You're the one I'm going to get. Are you coming back to this grill? No.
Okay. What if you would? No. What if you were offered a free? No, absolutely not. Okay. No,
I ain't going to do it. All right. No, sorry. How much did you have to pay to get in? $12.
$12. That's right. Wow. All right. I'm assuming you really enjoyed that offer of $12. That's
equivalent to like a pack of cigarettes. $12. That costs way, way less than that. Really?
Even the manager of the Albertson three came out to get an interview.
You deal with this. I'm not dealing with that. I may have caused it, but I'm not going to deal
with it. You are. And in the matter of a day, the Albertson three were absolutely abolished.
That was crazy. That was a good one. There's been so many good ones that like, it's hard to even say
that was a good one, right? That was a great one among great ones. It's hard to even decide,
like what's a great one. They're all great. It's crazy. The quality of the submissions
has been just too high. It's been so high. All right. This is a Derma Combat.
It's warping time. Huh. We're supposed to be discovering fire. This is inappropriate.
Oh, that was the good one. I'm not scared though. Are you scared? Yeah, I bet you are.
I bet you're scared. I'm not scared at all. Hey, you can see the whole park from here. Can you see?
This is really high. Every wooden roller coaster.
Yeah. Or do you were talking about me and my kingdom? Just a little too, a little too harsh.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah. That's what I hear. Shut up. You want a duel? Shut up. You and me.
Dragon bone steel. Shut up. With whatever you have there. Whatever that is. What's that again?
Stainless steel. Yeah. We all know how, we all know how sturdy that is. Shut the fuck up.
Why don't you come over this way? Let's see. Shut up. Come on. I have the power of God and anime on my
side. Oh my God. Let's go. We can't just stand here all day and do it. Yeah. Okay. Yeah. Look at
me. Look at me right now. Yeah. Duel of the DMCA. I mean, it's DMCA. We're trying to avoid it,
but you know, the VOD for these two streams are just probably not even going to be available
anywhere. It's going to be really hard. I know that there's a, the archive channel is working on,
has worked on it, but you know, it's tricky. It's tricky with the amount of copywritten material.
We continue. Jerma watches TV. I see something horrible. Come closer. A dire thing will happen
to you. He will spill your water on the table and it will drip, drip, drip over the edge down to
the ground. Next weekend, you're going to get invited to a party on Facebook. You're going to
say maybe, and you're going to be kind of excited to go, but they're going to cancel.
They're going to cancel it. Oh, yup. That one is bad. Hot, hot, hot.
Something that's not completely biafoo. Drugs and alcohol. Hi everybody. I'm the actor that plays
Super Mario and I just be on your best behavior. Be on your best behavior. Yeah. Yeah. I'm up.
I don't know. What's the context of this one? This is okay. This is literally just a shitty
that somebody got last second from a bag. This is going to be fucking loud. Damn. That was awesome.
Yes, I, of course, as you enter the dark woods, you come across three goblins.
Roll for initiative and put your miniatures down. You are not going to go by me more.
You're first. What do you do? My wizard cast fireball on the one on the left.
Nice job. Vinny, your turn. I shoot the one in the middle. Roll to hit. Shit. Natural one.
Ow. Jerma, your go. I hit with my sword.
Okay. Nice job. Now it's the goblin's turn. It will try to hit Jerma. Stop. Stop. Stop. Stop.
Oh, critical hit. I'm sorry, Jerma. It kills you. Mark back to you. Wait, where are the miniatures?
What the fuck? Okay. That took me to almost the end of the video to realize that those were AI
voices, especially criticals. I thought I thought critical did a thing where he did like a D and D
thing. I was that that that was convincing. Wow. That's insane. Guess what? Very much unhappy.
No, really. I don't want you to guess. You do shut up. What? Shut up. I know for a fact. Shut
the fuck up. I'm sorry. Please don't speak to me like that. I'm simply saying shut the fuck up.
Shut up. Shut up. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. That's what I hear. Shut up. Shut up. Shut up.
Shut up. Shut up. Shut the fuck up. Shut up. Shut up. Shut up. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Shut the fuck
up. Shut up. Oh, yeah. Yeah. Shut up. What the fuck? My name is. My name was not Borden, actually.
I want to make this video really quickly to say.
I have to do a drug BSA. Okay. Let me tell you something about drugs.
Try to pressure to do drugs one time. And I said, No, you should never take any drugs. Never.
What is going on? Toad, stay away from them. If somebody tries to pressure you into drinking or
smoking, tell them with the hardest of hearts. No, I don't need to do that. We can get back to
the playing and games now. Let me check and see. I think we're getting down to the end here, I think.
Let me check to see. We have. Okay. We're getting down to the final 25 videos. There are 25 videos
left. Just so you know, we're down to 25. Hold on. Let me get this over here.
Okay. Here we go. Final 25 videos. Let's go. What is this? Spider-Man.
You need to go and close them all before the knock on the door of your mother finds you.
You have one minute. Make your choice. First, this one over here. Oh, no. That was good.
What was that? What was that? Hold on. What was that one? What the fuck was that?
I'm actually so confused. Was that part of a different video?
Oh, okay.
My first Mario Kart win.
It's so stupid.
This level sucks.
That level is such a piece of shit. Seriously. And the music is just.
Behind. Don't say it. Don't say it. Behind. Come on. Behind. Behind.
Slow ahead. I can go slower ahead. Come on down and chomp some of this shit. Behind. Behind.
I said leave. I don't even know where half of these movies are. Behind. Behind. Behind. Behind.
What the fuck? Play for now. Okay. What's up? I fucking quit the goddamn game. I exited the
fucking game. No, I didn't. I'm still in. Close the door. All right. I'm good. I can't believe I
actually played this. Are you still there? What the fuck are you still doing here? You dick.
What the fuck is happening?
What am I saying? Air to the what?
Air to the. Air to the what? Air to the. Air to the. Air to the. There's something wrong with
your fan's brains. Why are you saying that? That was like incredibly well done detailed and the
music. It was. It flowed perfectly. What are you talking about? All right, ladies and gentlemen.
Let me check. We are getting down. Oh, there are about 15 or so left. We're getting to the final
15. Ever. Well, not ever, but you know, for today. Oh, yes. I love the MasterChef ones.
Hey, Bob. Hey, Bob. I'm on TV. I'm sorry. I'm sorry. Can I have the mic? No, you don't have to
give it to me. I'm on TV, Ma. I'm on TV. Jammer. Yes, Chef. Stay there for a minute. Yeah, I'm
currently trying to make sure that I have enough of the seasoning on here. Just step back. Look
at the mess. But it takes up so much less space. It's not in one space. It's from there all the
way down and all over the place. Look at the cupboard. This takes. Let me tell you one more
thing. If you were in any of our kitchens, you'd been fired six months ago. Dude, I looked over here
and it's a mess over here. There's like 75 items over here and then I'm looking over here.
There's a door right there and there's a big exit sign. I'm just looking back and forth like,
oh, me. That is a disaster. What is that? What it made for you today is I have
a creamy mushroom risotto and a side of creamy broccoli risotto with a hint, a small portion
of a creamy chicken risotto. And then on the side of that, I also have two pork chops that
I have created and I seared to perfection and then finished off. And it's served on a
bed of raw flour, right? Yes, Chef. I actually just had it before you did. I just had some before you
did.
What do you mean it's not good? It's a perfect risotto. It's perfect.
You work in a mess, you produce a mess. I'm struggling to identify what the hell you're
doing. I really am. You like to talk like you know food, but you actually really don't.
You're just a mean guy that got a bunch of TV shows. You're just a mean guy that got a bunch
of TV shows and I'm not going to stand for it. How about enough? I've had enough. I'm not leaving.
No, I think I deserve to win. Get out! Out! I f*** this competition. I don't care.
Dude, somebody in the chat was saying, why would somebody make a risotto pizza?
A risotto pizza omega lul. That just kept popping in my head and just doing it.
Let's go! I'm killing you. I'm killing you. And here I come!
I'm going to smash your f***ing head with a mallet like Gallagher used to.
You big b***h, I'll put you in a meat grinder!
Life is pain! I hate-
That game was awesome. It was really hard though.
Okie dokie! Nice!
F*** out of here! F*** down!
That's awesome.
Damn! Sentry, going up!
They changed the clothes.
Oh, excuse me!
Yabba dabba doo!
Look at me!
What do you sound like?
Hey, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa!
Why, you motherf***er!
There it is. F***ing boink!
Damn.
I'm not even winded.
F*** Dr. MD.
Just got done with a quick bike ride.
Kickstand. Comes in.
Just like sweat just glistening off his forehead.
So, what brings you in today?
Well, I have a little bit of a headache.
It's kind of like a migraine-ass kind of deal I got going on here.
One second.
Takes the bike helmet off and just pairs.
It's like at least 16 to 20 inches of hair.
He pulls up the license.
60, by the way.
And I'm like, oh wow, look at that crazy thing!
That's, wow, you got, what a head of hair!
He's like, yeah.
Haven't had a headache, by the way, in a long time.
You want to eat some bugs?
Final Fantasy V?
We haven't seen a Slytherin mustache guy in a while.
Lightning hands!
That was awesome.
Hello, boys and girls!
Good time!
Suck a fart out of my ass!
Oh, hey, what's going on?
How are you doing?
Wait, are you summoning?
Watch out!
Oh, I thought the video froze.
That was awesome.
Hi, chefs.
What I made for you today is I have a creamy mushroom risotto
and a side of creamy broccoli risotto
with a hint, a small portion of a creamy chicken risotto.
Is that normal?
Amazing Bazzini's risotto.
Wow, that's extraordinary, no?
Yeah.
It doesn't even move.
Well, I mean...
Well, maybe that'll look better up there.
It fits the colors.
Mess.
And absolutely disgusting.
And that's what my mom taught me, you know?
It just tastes of mush.
It's not good.
It's just so bland.
Honestly, I mean, it's just greasy.
What do you mean it's not good?
It's a perfect risotto.
It's perfect.
The crap and the gunk on top of it is just hideous.
Perfect risotto.
It looks like re-fried beans.
You like to talk like you know food,
but you actually really don't.
Unbelievable.
Now I know the problem.
You're just a mean guy that got a bunch of TV shows.
And I'm not going to stand for it.
I'm not leaving.
Get out of here!
Right, go then!
Okay.
Melted ice cream?
Creamy mushroom risotto,
and you don't have a fucking palate to save your life,
you fucking idiot.
Yeah, why am I leaving?
It's so good.
Whatever.
I fucked this competition.
I don't care.
Jesus Christ.
All right, so people are saying,
why do you only know what risotto is?
No, but in every one of these shows
and every one of the competitions,
they're always like,
oh, of course I have a creamy mushroom risotto.
It's like they always do that.
It's just like the thing that they all make on every episode.
There's always a risotto.
Okay, volume 985.
Jeremy catalog.
Not much.
How are you doing?
Not up and I'm just,
I'm curious as to why you're like the worst creamer on the planet.
Oh, is that what you think?
You think that's what you think?
You fucking idiot.
What my god.
We could stop at five or six different stores.
Just one.
Oh, and now we're to Mario.
Here we go.
A scary one.
No, it's me.
We're back in a fun Mario one now.
This game is sick by the way.
Mario Yahtzee.
Good block.
Perfect dodge.
Bowser needs to understand.
Boys and girls, don't do drugs.
If you do drugs-
Where are my legs?
You end up like kick bouncer over here.
Dead.
Where's Luigi?
Bowser.
It's a Bowser.
Not this fucking level.
No, it's me, Mario.
Okay, I'm done.
I can't, I can't do it.
I can't, that was it, that was the end.
Firm with a window cleaner.
Hi mom.
Hey mom, I'm on TV.
I'm on the television.
Channel two.
I'll leave, I'll leave, I'll leave but-
Oh, hey.
Hey, you can see the whole park from here, can you see?
That's crazy.
You're gonna scream.
I feel like I'm at an audition right now.
There's like three people with clipboards over there
and they're just like judging every word I'm saying.
Again?
Really?
You're gonna do this again?
You did this and you can fix it too, you know.
Words cannot even comprehend how Zaya says
you're about to be in very big trouble.
Oh, you've got a mouth on you, don't you?
Oh, he's very angry.
Zaya, Zaya, he's angry.
I'm coming down there and I'm gonna fuck you up.
Hey, come on out here because there's bugs everywhere.
I don't like when the bugs are everywhere.
Find the red truck.
Use your eyes.
Dude, is this something on me?
Is this something on my back?
Just tell me, get it.
Zombies!
Get it, get it, get it.
Oh my god, it's huge.
Dude, it's huge.
Would you like to see the notes?
You can see it if you want.
Would you like to see what I've written down?
Go ahead and look.
Do you see what's in front of us?
You do, right?
No human drives a car like this.
You're not getting your license today, by the way.
Make that very clear.
Oh, damn.
Find the red truck.
All right, where are we?
We're down to the final.
Oh man, the final like seven.
No, there are eight.
There are eight remaining.
This one is called Lucio Malfoyle's First Lesson.
I wonder what it is.
Okay, he's all right.
He's fine.
Everyone's laughing if it's fine.
My name is Lucio Malfoyle.
I'm the new teacher in town.
Hey, you and me, you're evil too, right?
We're probably going to be really good friends.
If we could all open up your textbooks and go to page 200, please.
Yes, yes.
Ron, please.
There's nothing in here about using defensive spells.
Page 200, we're going to be making a frog breath potion.
You know all about that, don't you, Harry?
Hermione.
The one you used when you killed Lucius?
Isn't he Lucius?
Shut up, Malfoyle.
I'm in the middle of teaching, Harry.
That's not the time to use that spell.
And how's theory supposed to prepare us for without that?
Didn't they ever tell you you only use that spell if you mean to kill another wizard?
And yes, I'm aware that your old teacher has perished.
Dr. McGillicuddy.
It was murder.
Voldemort killed him.
Now you're going to be floating in the air.
Down.
Well, class, it's been a pleasure.
Absolute pleasure.
But you all don't understand the power of the Dark Lord.
And for that reason, I'm out.
Just like that show, Shark Tank.
Invictus!
He's an idiot.
You're a little shit, and you always were.
But you didn't know, Harry, that I have lightning hands.
Oh!
You have no idea what's in store for you, Harry.
Me and Malfoyle are going to destroy you.
Scrappy stuff!
Oh, that was a good one.
That was really good.
Frog's Breath Potion.
Imagine dying to Frog's Breath Potion.
How would that even fucking hurt you?
That doesn't make any sense.
How would that even, how would that hurt you?
What is that?
What spell is that?
What potion is that?
That killed, wow, what a terrible wizard you were.
What a shitty wizard.
You died from a frog's breath.
That's like the joke, cartoon, goofy part of the movie.
When it's like, oh, I got bad breath.
That killed Lucius Malfoyle.
What a shit wizard.
Okay, let's go.
Why don't you come here?
Come on, come on, do it already.
Let's go, because we can't just stand here all day, dude.
Wait, I got shit to do.
Come on.
Hey, who wants coffee?
Guy got coffee.
I just brewed a fresh pot of coffee.
It's amazing.
Hold on, let's see that again.
I'm sorry, we have to see that again.
This one has flashing lights and blinking lights.
Flashing sounds and lights.
Just so you're aware.
Okay, this is flashing lights.
You ready?
Flashing sounds.
We're always striving to make you feel as comfortable as possible.
Which is why we have the complimentary breakfast.
And the pool.
Also, a golf course.
But don't take it from us.
This is a bunch of stock footage.
Take it from this testimonial from our esteemed guest.
Wherever life takes you, we are there.
Best Western.
What is going on?
Hey, I'm just hanging out.
Who's talking?
What are you up to?
How are you?
Hi, how are you?
Good to see you.
Oh, I'm clean now.
Clean Andy.
Prove it.
You got to prove it.
Okay, I'll prove it.
All right, I didn't tweet yet.
I have to send a message.
What I thought you were saying is pour ice down your pants.
Prove that I was just in the shower.
There it is.
No more face cam.
Not today.
Don't see the stupid face burned onto their thousand dollar TV.
What do I do?
My dad saw a video of yours.
He had a heart attack.
You know, no, no, we're not going down this road.
It's literally just a wall.
Dude, it's going to live a long time.
It might.
But what was the last thing I did?
I gave tablets.
Okay, okay, okay, okay.
Cool, cool, cool, cool, cool, cool, cool, cool, cool, cool, cool, cool, cool, cool, cool, cool, cool, cool, cool, cool.
Good.
Excellent.
Keep the horror.
I don't have that image anymore.
There we go.
You want to keep the horror?
Here.
Oh, shit.
Holy shit.
That was fucking crazy.
That was awesome.
That was really good.
That's a clap for that one.
All right.
German 95 attempts to survive and vampire survivors.
Okay.
Are you ready?
Oh, that was disgusting.
It's warping time.
No, no, I'm sorry.
No.
Hey, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa.
All right.
German 101.
That's enough.
You got an F and you're not going to get your license.
This can't be.
This can't be right.
Wait, what did that say?
What did that say?
If I chop you up in a meat grunt and the only thing that comes to your mind, you're probably dead.
My name is Lucien Malfoy.
I'm the new teacher in town.
And yes, I'm aware that your old teacher has perished.
This is arc.
Hold on.
Wait, wait.
I want to go back.
What did that say?
Chop you up in a meat grunt.
Death note.
2020 baseball stream.
2021 baseball stream.
July baseball stream.
Hey, August baseball stream is not written down in here.
I think we're fine.
I think we're good.
All right.
So the next one is infinity war spoilers.
Like it matters, but okay.
This is arc.
I don't feel so good.
That was stupid.
To be taken like this tie is so long.
Can you see this?
I look like a 10 year old wearing dad's suit to work.
This is ridiculous.
This shouldn't be like this.
I feel like I'm two feet tall.
I heard that the second game had four to five minute loading screens
when you went outside or inside of a building.
So that's why I never played it.
True.
Witches.
I'll not drink with weaver laws freaks.
I'll take a drink.
Beg your pardon for those thugs.
You don't know who I am?
Geralt of Rivia.
You should know.
Two orange juices.
I'm gonna drink one now and one later.
Thank you.
Done drinking.
Wait, hold on.
Let me do my like my patented move that I do.
You.
That's right.
Any witches?
No, nothing.
I just wanted to take you aside
without cluing the others into what we're up to.
Sneaking upstairs to make love.
Heard you were a witch.
I got a letter from the king of Rivia that said that you were a witch.
Are you?
I've never played this game.
I don't.
I have never played any of the witchers.
Suddenly I have an immense desire to drink.
Oh, I hate those motherfuckers.
I think we're down to the final two.
Let me check.
Yeah, so we're down to the final three.
There are three more.
This one, one more, and one more.
Here we go.
Derma gets a coffee.
I think I still fucking got it.
Hey, what's up, man?
How are...
Hey, what's up?
There's the cream.
Why'd you pull a chair up?
There's the sugar.
There's the milk.
Hey, what's up, bro?
How are you doing?
Yeah, I got a coffee for you.
Brewed it right before you got in.
I knew you were...
I know your order.
Come on, I don't know your order.
That's my new...
That's freshly brewed, by the way.
Hey, how you doing?
That was good.
That was a good one.
Final two.
Derma barbecue.
Grill master.
There he is, the grill master.
Yeah, yeah.
Because nobody else wants to fucking do it.
So I do it.
And I sit here all day.
I want to...
You know what I think?
I want to be back there.
What's that?
No, no.
You're doing a great job out there, son.
Pete, don't climb that.
Don't get down from there.
Don't climb that.
How do you mind?
He's a maniac, I know, right?
He's my son, right?
Yeah, I know.
You want...
You ready for a dog?
You don't want a dog.
I love how much this...
You want dogs?
Oh my god.
All right.
There is one more.
Final one of the evening.
Oh my...
Okay.
Why did you put it...
All right.
Okay, everybody settle down.
Settle down.
They're sneaking him in.
This is the actually last one.
Hello.
Yeah, and guess what?
You can hear me, huh?
You can hear me pretty well.
Not like it was before.
Well, while this plays out in the background,
we'll skip to a random place.
Thank you everybody that gave any submissions.
This is some of the best submissions we've ever seen.
I don't know who gave it to me.
But yeah, incredible work.
That's just about almost 250, 300 videos.
I can hear my heart.
Out of hundreds and hundreds of submissions.
Yeah, I'm floored every time we do one of these
just because of how good and how creative
and how much actual time you guys put into these.
Will green screen ever come back?
I mean, it's tough to say because I have to be into it, right?
The reason why I did it again
was just because I got that urge to do it.
And I have to want to get in front of that green screen
because that's where I have the most fun.
So it's just going to happen.
It might just happen again.
I don't know.
But I never want to just be like,
no, I'm going to do it next week.
Because I've got to want to do it, right?
Thanks to anybody that participated,
anybody that sent anything in.
Yes, the playlist, there's two playlists.
There's DLC and there's the original playlist.
Both are going to be available for you to watch.
And then for the other submissions,
I don't know if there's anything
going to happen with the other ones.
It's tough to kind of be like, all right,
should we do a third playlist
and put it in the Discord or something?
Or should we let people just put their work into the Discord
and maybe just share it with each other?
Stuff like that might be something we might do.
But obviously, no guarantees or anything.
But that was amazing.
And everybody, get hype for baseball.
That wasn't in the Death Notebook.
All right, shut this guy off.
August 19th at 430 Pacific.
That's this coming Friday,
is the Germa Baseball Association presents
the California Circus versus the Maryland Magicians.
It's going to be a full nine innings of baseball.
I'm the only umpire in the whole game.
It's going to be fucking wild.
I'll just tell you that.
So that's one I don't think I'd want to miss
if I were you and I were here
and I was watching this channel.
The Germa Baseball Association is a go.
Friday, this Friday at 430 Pacific.
I wonder who's going to win.
I wonder who you guys are going to root for
because they're both going to be awesome.
So I'm incredibly excited for it.
You know, every four or five months or so,
once every six months,
try to do something really extravagant.
And this is one of those things.
It should be a lot of fun.
Hey, whatever happens,
it will be fun to do regardless.
So I hope you enjoy it.
The next time you will see me,
we'll be on the Germa Baseball Association stream.
August 19th again.
Don't forget it.
I'll tweet about it too.
It's probably tomorrow, the next day.
Type it up a little bit more.
See you soon though.
Yeah, Grump will post the video playlists
in the Discord too, probably, I would assume.
That concludes the green screen movie night.
The second one.
What about the dog video?
Will there be baseball merch?
Yes, there will be baseball merchandise around the show.
I promise you that.
I'll just keep the dog video in there.
Why not?
Yeah, who are you rooting for?
I don't know.
I think you have to wait till they're on screen
before you find out who your favorite team is.
It's going to be very, very hard for you to decide.
So many people are like,
oh, the circus, the clowns.
Oh yeah, the magicians.
Just wait.
Let the first hour of that stream happen
before you figure that out.
Have you been physically preparing for this?
Yes, I have been physically preparing,
both mentally and physically,
because I need to know.
I've been studying umpire terminology and umpire rules
and how to regulate and keep a baseball game going smoothly.
Can we bet on who wins?
Yeah, I'm sure we could do that at the beginning.
The mods will be on top of it.
Mods will just do it.
Maybe before the game starts in the pre-show,
like kind of while you guys are hanging out,
maybe we can start one.
That sounds like a plan.
Is merch going to be after the stream?
Yeah, it'll be after the stream is over.
It'll be at 50% exactly.
California Circus, brute for your team.
Go magicians, go.
How long do nine innings take?
Well, in a regular game of baseball,
it could take somewhere between two and a half
to three and a half hours,
but this is not a regular baseball game.
It's regular baseball, but it's not a regular game.
That's all I'm going to say,
but it's going to be nine innings.
What will you do if it rains?
Well, it's not going to rain, so stop saying that.
We're not going to, we don't talk about rain.
There's a rain delay in baseball.
If it is raining, we wait.
We will have, we'll have to wait
for a rain delay potentially.
Or if it's light enough, we just go.
That you, people, they play baseball in the rain.
I don't think it's going to rain, so don't worry.
But there are plans in place.
Are there going to be any special guests?
No, that I can tell you for sure.
What if it snows?
That would be strange.
No, there are no special guests.
Unless you want to say that the baseball teams
playing are the guests, which I would say, yeah.
But those are, I would say, special guests.
What if the baseball stops working?
We'll just get another one.
All right, that's it.
Just, just show up on Friday.
That's all I can tell you.
What if the baseball won't fit?
Just, everything's going to be fine.
Just show up on Friday.
With that, I'll see you later.
Wish, wish us luck in the pre-production
here over the next week.
There's a lot of moving parts on this show,
kind of like we've described.
There are, it is a full baseball game
with two full baseball teams.
So there's a lot to do.
So I'll talk to you guys soon.
See you on Friday.
Take care of yourselves and good night.
Friday, August 19th at 430 Pacific.
Go, go, go, go.
Good night, guys.
Make sure to call your mother.