Hey, too early? That's right. I've got to be better at this stream starting soon screen,
I think. Because here's the thing, I feel like when I sit here and I'm ready to start streaming,
I press this turn on stream button, start streaming, and then I'm ready to stream.
So I feel like I should just press that button and then like go get... but I'm here. I'm ready.
It's kind of an awkward situation where I press the button and I'm just sitting here just looking
at chat waiting to unmute. And like should I do it now? Should I do it in like two minutes?
I guess take a sip of my water. There's a maybe a handful of scenarios where that screen's been on
and I've had to go to the bathroom quick. Some streamers do a full 10 to 20 minutes of a starting
soon screen. I've seen like five minutes starting soons, 10 minute, 20 minute. I feel like that's
too much for me. Some do 50 minutes. An hour? A full hour? Holy shit. I guess it makes sense
for people that stream very long on Twitch. I guess if you press the start streaming button
and you stream for like 12 hours, it's not that big of a deal. And there's another argument there
where, well, most people don't even come to the stream until 30, 40 plus minutes have gone by.
So I guess it makes sense. Some people are just hopping in on notifications after 10, 20 minutes.
I guess it makes sense. But my attention span, if I press the start streaming button... I don't know.
I'm concerned. If I press the start... I just got burped murdered is what happened. Somebody just
came up behind me and murdered me and burped at the same time. God. All right. Anyways.
So anyways, what was I saying? Right. I would be afraid that if I had my stream just going
on my computer up here for like 35, 40 straight minutes, me internally would always think that
is a mic on? What if they hear me like singing in the shower? What if they hear me blowing my nose?
What if I... There's a lot of mic unmuted scenarios that could happen there. But no, usually I usually
do about two or three minutes and then about five minutes total until we do it like that.
So today we're going to do Spooky's Jump Scare Mansion HD remake HD renovation.
The reason why we're doing this instead of Darkwood is I just want to break it up a little
because I want to play more Darkwood, but I don't want to play Darkwood like three days in a row.
I'd rather do this first and however long if this takes five, six, seven hours, then whatever.
We will go back to Darkwood tomorrow. But if this is like three hours or less, if this is only a
couple hours, I've heard this can range between like two and six hours. So whatever the case is,
we're streaming tomorrow too. We'll see. It has this music that's just playing.
This is a very highly requested game. I got this request a bunch of times and if I don't like the
game, then I'm just gonna play Darkwood. If the game is short, I'm gonna play Darkwood.
Gonna play Darkwood tomorrow. So we'll see more Darkwood. I 100% guarantee if there's no Darkwood
tomorrow, then actually I can't say this. What if I like break my leg? Okay, so if I stream...
Never mind. I'm ready. This is Darkwood. It's not Darkwood. This is Spooky's Jump Scare Mansion.
I don't know much about this game. All I know about this game is that
I don't want to play endless mode. You have to go through a bunch of rooms and they all jump scare.
So by the way, I need to make this very clear. This game is going to flash you. It's going to
make loud noises. It's going to scream and it's going to flash the screen and shit. So just be
aware of that. Be careful. Okay, the mansion. Renovator version of the original. Why don't
I just do that one? Unlock the secrets of the strange hospital. Build your own mansion. All
right. We're going to just do the regular one. The one that... This one. Is this part of the game?
Do I actually like fight the controller? Okay. So, uh, welcome. We're in room zero.
Is there a punch? First jump scare. Okay. I have to do a thousand of these.
I gotta turn it up. This is too quiet. Yeah, I... Jump scare is on. What if I turn them off?
What's the point of playing the game? I'm going to play Spooky's Jump Scare Mansion.
But, like, story mode. It's just baby mode. Put it at 69. No. I'll do 50 where it should be.
This is... I turned off motion blur. I would... I had to tell you about that, too, because that's
fucked up. Uh, apply. Better. No, it's louder for you now. I'm turning it down. All right, let's go.
Uh, Jump Scare Mansion. Turn the DPI down on my mouse, please. Is there a DPI button? Input. Mouse.
UI. No. In game. Where's my DPI reducer? I missed it. It was there. In game. Oh, it's...
Look down. 1.0. Okay, I'm gonna... I... You do eight. No, seven. Let's see if that's better.
Yeah, that feels better. All right, let's go. So, um, this is Jump Scare Mansion. I'm going to assume
that every single room screams at you. Is that for real? Because, I mean, I'm... I know that's
gonna happen now. I know that somebody's gonna scream in my face, right here. You've kind of
given away the whole point of the game. Is this it? What'd it say? At first, this place just seemed
cute, but I've been here for days now. Feeling quite parched now, and I keep getting this feeling
like I'm being watched by something. This is not romantic at all. It's Jump Scare Mansion. Thank
God I only had one coffee today. But that's the thing. If you know it's gonna happen, how do they
get you when you... Okay, pumpkin's in the walls. Person in the ceiling. Something outside? No. It's
a cloud. Can I open... draw? Something's gonna come out of the... draw. No. That's nothing in here.
I've been playing too much Darkwood, which, by the way, it's coming back soon. In a day or so.
What's that? This is a puzzle game. I have two ways to go now. Uh, left or right door? Is this...
Is this a bigger room? Oh, okay. Pick the middle one. I got the bad end. Choices matter. Is that...
Are you kidding? Or is that real? All right, I'm almost, um, 1% of the way there. Right? This game
takes four hours to beat. I guess that makes sense. You just have to walk through a thousand rooms.
All right, I'm gonna go... I went left before. I'm gonna go right now. What's... I have a health bar.
What's the energy bar for? For the Jump Scare Mansion, you've got one jump scare in 13 rooms,
and it was pumpkin. Can I go back through the other door? No. There's got to be another
jump scare coming up. Was it every, like, 20 rooms? Every... Yep, there it is. Here he is.
I know something is following me, but I feel like I'm prancing through the same rooms over and over.
Right? Hopefully leaving notes as breadcrumbs will prove I'm making progress in reaching some
destination. I just hope I don't run out of ink. I'm dreadfully thirsty. This is me leaving these
notes because I'm stuck in a time loop. Pumpkin scared him more. Yep, because pumpkin made a
noise. It made a loud, like... The skeleton just showed up. Oh, maze time. Okay. 18. Holy shit,
that's a sprint. You can sprint, and it goes too fast. I'm not using the sprint. There's a lot of
doors here. This one. Bed. Are there items? I don't think so. I think I get it. I think you
just keep going. It only happens twice. Wasn't I in this room before? Oh, please don't tell me
this is one of these games where you have to... It's like a maze, and you have to figure out the
maze. I went in the left door last time. Or... Am I going... What's wrong with my neck? Somebody just
said neck. Your neck. Your neck. What's wrong with it? I think I'm doing something wrong. Yep, I have
ink. Not quite quenching my thirst. Taste is terrible. Stains are terrible. I don't think
drinking it was a very romantic idea. Why is everything romantic? I am leaving these notes
because I remember the little skeleton body here. He's gonna jump up right now. No? Okay.
It's gonna happen like a hundred more times because it doesn't matter if something's scary
or not, or if you know it's gonna happen. If somebody just jumps in front of you and yells,
you're gonna be like, oh! See? I know they're happening, but it doesn't matter. It's a
startling thing. It looks like they've increased the frequency of these. You can always tell when
I really actually get scared by something. We talked about this yesterday during Darkwood, but
if my hand comes up and I start to play the guitar in the air, that means that's a real reaction.
Any other time, if I'm like, whoa! No, that's bullshit. Bullshit. I start playing an invisible
flute. Oh, yeah. Terrified. I've only done 36 of these. It's the constant running that I think
gets you because your brain is going forward and then it... What's that? I found something today
to satisfy my unromantic thirst. I woke today from a brief faint and found before me a bottle
of red wine. This is me. I'm not sure what brand or year, but there is no label. All I gather is
that it tastes strongly metallic. Okay. I'm gonna pre yell too. I think that'll help too. If my body
is ready and I'm like tensed already, if I scream beforehand, I won't scream at the actual jump
scare. I think it works. People are gonna think I'm fucking crazy.
I need to test my hypothesis. You have to exhale too. No inhale. Exhale. Because then you can't go...
I'm just gonna do pregnancy classes. Locked. Okay. Keep a little pep in your step.
I'm just waiting for everything to do it. You can do it. We can help. Papa John's. Papa John's
sucks, by the way. Oh, it's a save point. All right. It does not. I mean, it does. It's not
very good. Papa Gino is way better than Papa John's. Like a thousand times better. Those of you
that don't know Papa Gino's, you don't know the true meaning of like chain pizza. It's because
his name is Gino. No, that's not why. I mean, that helps. It's not the reason. Can I crouch?
Okay. 51. We're almost 5.1% of the way there. You are here. Where? I think that's the point.
This is a good map. Sounds like something's at the end of this hall.
This is why I can't do these games. And you wonder, whoa, where's Scare Saturdays? Scare
Saturdays used to hurt me. That's why every Saturday I would just be like, I have to do
another one of these and I don't want to do it. But it was Saturday. So I had to do it because I
said, I'm going to Scare Saturdays every Saturday. After doing that for like four or five, six weeks
in a row, I was like, I, it's Friday and how do I not do this on Saturday? I thought it was fun for
like eight weeks in a row. He hates streaming. No. What does it have to do with streaming?
That has nothing to do with live streaming. It's scary jump in your face games. They make me ill.
That's like saying, oh, that chef really doesn't like stabbing himself in the chest with his
kitchen knife. He must hate, he hates cooking. He hates cooking. He hates, he hates streaming.
Slime. It's going to pop up. Or it's that, this is a red herring. This is a, this is a red herring.
It's going to come over here. Yep. This is a red herring. Spouting, splashing, soaking, innards,
ingest, invoking, nailing never stops the choking. I told you, I told you it was going to get up.
Uh, this health in the game, they have a health bar. Wait, they all get up. Wait,
they, he's following me around in every room. No, he's not. Please, please. You think I'm going
to pay attention to the little ghost? He is chasing me through every room. There's no jump. Oh, good
thing I didn't go to the chair route. I'm good. How long does this last for? This is not just for
the rest of the game, right? Another, another, like, like 932 floors of this. Hey, I can't go
in that door. I think I'm safe. Okay. I got it. Fucking dot on me. He's taking poison damage.
I can hate this. I don't, it doesn't matter. I, there's a thousand of these rooms. Why would
I do this? Of like the four to 5,000 of you that requested this. It was, it was actually like six
people, but still. Wait for that to recharge. Seven. He just really doesn't. He just hates
streaming. He doesn't want, he hates streaming. It's like, I think that's like my favorite comment.
It'll last like a week. Almost 10% of the way there. It's been 30 minutes. So that's a hundred
rooms in 30 minutes, which means that's 10%. So three, six, nine, 12, 14, 18, 21, 24, 27, 30.
This is going to take three hours. That was the easiest math problem ever. And I made that so
much more complicated for no reason. Oh, there's another one of these guys. This is how many? Two?
All right. Just stay ahead of them. Here comes, we're going to be one in the hallway here. It's
going to be like boom. Almost at a hundred. Ninety-five. Floor a hundred. 10% of the way
there. Keep that blood pumping. I'm actually all right. So I've completed 10% of the game.
This is your breather. Every 50 rooms. I saved it, right? Yeah. This is going to take you five
hours. Why would it take me five hours? I just have to go into different halls and open doors
900 more times. So there are only 60 minutes in an hour. So one room per minute. No, it's one.
No, that's not how it works. Why would I spend one minute in each room? What happened to the
little ghost person at the beginning? It was just like, hi, welcome to my castle. And then they've
gone. New environment. It's beige now. Cat dos. What do you mean cat dos? Should I enter cat dos?
Press it. Enter cat dos. Access specimen database. Modify house layout. Specimen one. Cat dos. Type
docile. Total fatalities four from heart attack. Cardboard cutout figure that springs out from the
walls. Prove not very effective against healthy subjects. Cat dos two. Active. 137 fatalities.
Method physical tearing. A mostly semi-solid base specter that frequently changes matter states.
Prove very effective against weaker or slower subjects. What was spoiler three? Hidden testing.
43 infectious bites. A test specimen being developed at GL labs should prove useful when
released. Trials have shown it is adequately effective to average subjects. Method consumption.
A 14th century spirit that was contained and relocated here. Tests have yet to reveal origins,
but all relevant information has been placed into testing chamber. Proved effective, but not
greatly more than previous specimens. A creature found inside the church of a small town. Subjects
are lost after contact with the specimen. The bloodbath of killing is unknown. Proved extremely
effective against subjects with mental issues or weak wills. All right. Modify house layout error.
Exit program. And one of these is going to be in the room. Not in this room. There's going to be
all kind of this. There's going to be five different cat doses. Is this one of the cat doses? Bang! Up
against the wall. Yep. No, come on. Do it like sprint, sprint, sprint, sprint. What's that in
the distance? Sprint, sprint, sprinting, sprinting, sprinting, sprinting, sprinting, and then wicked
close. But wait, are these are these YouTubers that have been scared by the game? All right.
That's, that's so funny. Why am I not on that wall? I, because I've not, I haven't played this game.
I had nothing to do with this game. What do you mean you're next? No, I'm not. We are almost,
we are almost 11% of the way through this game. Green room. Music's getting louder.
Green room two. Something coming up out of the water. No, something coming up on the left side.
It's going to be here. It's going to be in here. I mean, you don't have the fog. Well,
that was the door. I know what you're going to do. Just do it already. Ding, ding. What do you mean
ding? Ding, donk, donk, donk, ding. So it was right, left, right, right. That's a double ding.
Straight, right, right, right, right, ding. One and fifteen. Music's getting louder.
I thought they got rid of these because they were more effective. These are more effective
than the monsters. Look at my reactions I had to the green I'm going to kill you monster versus
the paper cutout that's like an emoji sticker. Not this time. I don't think that was wine.
What was it? It's the test poison that you drink in it. I'm not going to just use filler words and
just use words just to talk, just be talking instead to distract myself from what's happening
on the screen. I'm not going to do that because doing that would mean that I'm trying to fill
air in my head to distract myself from the thing that's going to jump out in front of me in about
15 to 25 seconds give or take maybe a little bit there. Same thing. This is new. Needs a key card.
Please. Uh oh. I made this character in that wrestling game. That's the gum guy.
They're going to break out of these probably or something.
Geez. Yeah something broke out. See there's an empty one. Okay PG YouTuber activated. Oh crap.
Oh no. Oh oh goodness. What the heck happened? Blood. Subject five is growing more and more
restless. I told Spook we need more funds for sedatives but she just laughed and flew into the
ceiling without more chemicals to keep these things docile. I'm not sure how much longer
we can keep them here. Got the key card. Subject five is growing more and more restless. I told
Spook we need more and more sedatives okay. He does this joke every game. I got it. I gotta keep
it going you know what I mean. It's tradition at this point. Look behind you in real life. Well not
every game. Only games where I have a facecam on. All right I'll give you that. If I have a facecam
turned on I'm going to do the YouTube person with 400 episodes. Yeah that's what happens.
You have to deal with it for like the two or three minutes that I do it out of like 12 hours.
Come on. I believe subject five is loose. The glass around its container is shattered and I
can faintly hear clicking coming from the ceiling. I don't know what will happen now but it's out
and alive. This is probably my last report. The clicking is getting louder now. It's behind me.
I want to see what it looks like. Oh there's a bug.
That was pretty funny. All right they come out of these the clicker ceilings.
He's fast. He just keeps breaking the doors. Great. Oh great. Oh great. Oh great. Oh no. Oh crap.
There's like a hundred of them. Oh no. Oh jeez. Oh crap. I do that every fucking stream too.
I gotta get the fuck out of here. I know it's behind me. Just don't even look at it. This is
a good way to burn through rooms though. It's the same exact room. You do it too early. You missed
your cue. 150, 150, 150. So I can stop this mute of these. Is he here still? Get the gunk out of
your ears. What implying that I didn't hear you say something? That's what you say to somebody
that's not listening to you. You're talking to somebody and they're not paying attention.
Hey what time is the bus? What time are we going? What time are we getting on the bus?
Hey get the gunk out of your ears. And they're like whoa what the heck? What are you talking
about? Really dry lips. Will you pay attention to the game please? Saved it. Hang in there. We're
only at 15 percent. What do you want me to click while I have a second here? Look at the link.
Click this link. That's pretty. Okay that's pretty fun. But I wasn't playing a scary game there.
150 let's go. That wasn't me playing a scary game. That was me putting tape all over my body
without a scary game. Get scared or riot. Chop till you drop axe. What was the image? I missed it.
Well you missed it. Sorry. All right let's go. I'm speed running my way to one uh for 200.
Now this is different. It's not that bad. It's not that bad. I'll do it. I'll get to a thousand.
They're gonna introduce more monsters. There's gonna be one in the ceiling. There'll be one in
the rafters. There'll be one coming out of the wall. Oh shit. What the hell is this? He's still
behind me isn't he? You take 160 floors to introduce the flashlight mechanic. Oh shit. This is like a
classroom read. Read the notes. Something's gonna be at a desk. I can't get out of here. Something's
gonna be at a desk. What is in the desk? A key card. Something. There's nothing in here. I just
rewound a YouTube video. I didn't want to miss my favorite part. Okay there's a note here.
Matsuri never came to class today. Oh she made it home. Okay. Hey what Harry? What? I looked at a
picture of a cat. It hurt me. That's great. Cool. Could really be true. I thought the fairy tales
about the ghost that eats children who sneak in after class was just to keep us from disobeying
but Matsuri is still missing. But where's the key to get out of here? I'm lost. There's a shadow over
there. Somebody in the corner. I see them. Is that me? What? That just hurt me. Okay I need to start
paying it to get some logical reasoning here. Which way am I going? This is back towards the
front. So it's here and then bang a left. Then bang a right. Out the door. Thank you. All right.
Okay. All right. Okay. All right. All right. All right. All right. All right.
Three. Oh Undertale. Oh shit it's actually flying at me.
You are you bad at your cue. You missed your cue again. Shut up. Thank you.
This is how this music's too happy. I don't know how much longer I can go on. I haven't seen
any of my previous notes. That means either I'm getting somewhere or someone is taking them.
Chair. Don't go chair route. I've already got this taken care of. This way. Damn it. Wait. No.
Nothing. You got it taken chair of. I wish I came up with that but I didn't. Nice work.
I hear breathing. I'm not even at floor 200. Fucking idiot. I think this. I think this is
my last note. I'm going to die having never found my escape but really that's not true. This place
was like my escape. My escape from everything else in the end. My death is kind of romantic.
This romantic thing has really got me all twisted. This is a live stream twisted. So now I can read
chat for a second. What's up? This is romantic. How's that iced coffee? Oh it's not iced coffee.
This is water that I sprayed a little bit of lime lemon juice in. This is just to stay hydrated.
Bugs. It is water. Get this wrong. Okay. Chair. Which is the right... I didn't see it.
Going as fast as I can. Get out of here. Yeah. I know we're both playing Gmod Deathrun and I'm
going too slow for you but fuck off. I'm trying to enjoy the game. Nice. I almost hit 200.
200. What was that? This thing's looking at me. I'm not gonna say it. No. I'm not gonna say it.
Somebody else did. I refuse to say it. All right. So how's everybody doing? How's your day?
Make your face came bigger. Wow. That's not necessary. There you go. There you go.
200. Make it bigger. No. That's as big as it's gonna get. 204. Yeah. Any chance I can get to throw
that in? You better believe I'm gonna. Uh oh. This is like Slender Man graphic on me.
Why do I have like the Slender static? What? This is... This was such a surprise that there would
be another entry. Another actual entry. One I could admire but then as suddenly as it came it left
and now you disband. Your influence and inspiration will never leave me. Such a surprise.
Is that code for how I have to? Oh my fucking jaw hurts.
So that's what that means. Okay. That... It took 208 rooms. That was a real one for me.
It took 200 rooms to have that be a full-on... Like I was not ready for that one. Jumpscare mansion.
Oh fuck. Don't even... What's this? Hey. The darkness is slowly consuming us now. I don't
think our rituals will appease it much longer. How were we supposed to know this would happen?
Ah shit. Ah shit. It's not really our fault. We just did what mother has told us to do in
this sort of situation. Mother is not pleased with us but how were we supposed to know that
that girl wasn't pure? He's reading lore in the game. Yeah. I kind of want to know what's going on.
It's not really our fault. We did what mother told us to do.
This is probably... One of these is going to have somebody in it. The girl wasn't pure.
Ah. That's where I came from. If I cross my eyes like it won't be scary because I won't know what
it is. Except that hurts. Did it work? Kind of works. Safety squinting. What the fuck is happening
to you? All right. All right. All right. All right. All right. Give me the 220.
Two... There's somebody... There's something following me. I don't know what it is.
I just want to see what it looks like. It's got a knife. But when it sees you it changes
your environment to be all fucky. Oh no. This is not good. Get out of my way. I... You are
meaningless to me now. I have to be honest. When I crossed my eyes like that for more than 10 seconds
I just... I... This hurts. My head hurts now. Oh nice. Arcade games. How do you control it?
It's gonna scream in my face. Oh I'm here. Wait. I have to... I'm the ghost. Hey! That's not very
nice. I can't believe Pac-Man is fucking dead. Wait. No. I'm the... Oh. I'm the ghost. Where...
Why am I doing this? I didn't even stab anybody.
Automatic plus letter grid. Now technically speaking I'm not driving the car. My character
is. This is a... This is a pretty good song. I'll give it a half letter grade for that.
Fucking... What are these people doing? Why are people just spinning around on the road?
What? What do... Oh. I'm... Okay. It's a big turn. Oh. I can run over stuff.
This is a good song. Here comes a demon face. Yeah. I know. I'm certain of it. That's why
I'm getting ready. How do I win? Here's the sad part about this. This is a better game
than any of the iPad GTA clones I played like five years ago. Do I have to eliminate all the
other cars? Alright. That's it. I win. I haven't... I didn't win. Checkpoint. Nitrous. How do I
activate nitrous? Every time I destroy a car my point... I... My time goes up. Just don't...
Don't kill any... Don't stop killing anybody. What? There's nobody else here. That was fun.
I can't leave the game. There's no exit. I can't walk this way. I'm driving the car backwards.
I'm holding the... I'm holding it like this. It's doing a Naruto run. Alright. 15 seconds.
Here it comes. It's gonna go... I just got achievement. It says meta gamer. This one's
out of order. Okay. Well, that was cool. Make your room darker. No. I can't make my room darker.
Same reason why I can't go see a movie during the day. When... If I black out these... The curtains
and I turn all the lights off. My... It's nighttime to me. I don't like going to see a movie during
the day when you go into this theater and it's like, oh, it's so dark in here. It's... There's
the big screen. Oh, big... And then you walk out and it's like... Sun is out and... Oh, I was just
sitting in a pitch black room for like two and a half hours. No. I don't see movies during the day.
A movie is like a... After dinner, you go out to dinner and then like a seven to nine p.m. showing
is perfect. Now, there are scenarios where going to a movie during the day is not a bad idea because
sometimes you save money. You know, if you go to like a noon showing, sometimes the tickets are
cheaper. Do they still do that or... I've been to one movie in two years or two movies in three years.
Do they still do like seven dollar matinees? Okay. I'm just making sure. Well, there's something new.
Is that supposed to be me? Like my brain stuck in this simulation? Put furniture pads on your
furniture, please, guys. Don't be like this fucking idiot here. Those floors are expensive. Don't
ruin them. This place is finally starting to affect me. I've seen enough horror movies to
know how to survive a simple ghost or two, but these monsters keep getting faster and stranger.
Almost at 250. And I have not died yet. I swear, man. I have to do a cross-eyed thing.
My eyes hurt. My mother warned me so many times. Don't do that. If you do it long enough,
it's gonna stay like that. Not this again. Left, left, straight, left, left, straight, straight.
If I was a puzzle designer, that's exactly what I would have done for the second one.
In fact, I would do straight, straight, straight, straight, straight, and then just really mess it
all up. That's the sound. I haven't seen anything major in a little while, so
don't do it. Don't, don't, don't. Hello. Hello. Hello. Hello. Hello. Hello. Hello. Hello. Stop it.
Stop doing that. Five nights at Freddy's. Don't look directly. Don't look directly into the fan.
Hello. Oh, it's your first day. Hello. All right. I tried to look. I looked directly into that fan.
What just happened right there? I just, I had to do the, the, the hello. Hello. Hello. Hello.
Hello. I'm doing it again. I just got like stuck. 50. Oh. Hello.
Just keep going. Should I take, should I take the gift? Should I take the gift from
a third of all Twitter avatars? What do you think? I can save first.
That was funny. That was cute. I'm gonna retweet that. That was fun. Password is pumpkin.
Pumpkin. For what? We're good? Oh, this is bad.
That was another thing. No, Jeremy, you're bad. Oh shit. There's something else. Nice turtleneck.
Right. It was wrong. It was wrong. It was wrong. It's all right. I made it with just a little
scratch. What's up tonight? What's going on here? Jeremy, Jeremy, you're almost at 300.
You idiot. That's a face I just made into the camera.
Wow. It's that one worse than anything. Come on. You're almost at 300.
This music is just messing me up. It just feels like I don't want to, I don't want to hear this.
I want Yoshi's Story OST to play in the background of my streams.
Why is everyone talking about my neck? Leave me alone. What's wrong with my neck?
My neck? I'm 34. I'm not like 20. You understand? This isn't what a real neck looks like at 35.
What do I care? But what do you guys have to say? I'm almost at 300.
He's 35 and he still gets voice cracks. That doesn't even bother me. Yeah, guess what? My
teacher. I told teachers in high school that their voice would crack because they were speaking
continuously for like six hours. And at hour number five, they'd be like, and I, uh, you guys,
sorry guys, I'm a teacher. That's cope. I'm giving you guys way too many like screenshots.
Sometimes I forget that like you could just rewind five seconds and stop at a single frame
and press a button. What? It's got to go faster than chair, not chair route.
Ah, this is making me sick. Did he fall off? I think he fell off the edge. Oh, no, he didn't.
His power stopped. Oh, Oh, Oh, Oh, Oh, Oh, 300. Anything I need to know?
Anything I need to know? That anyone's just saying anything? Somebody to know.
You're doing good. Thanks. There's somebody behind you. No, it's not. I mean, it was that.
Better ingredients, better pasta. That's the power of Home Depot. Papa John's thing.
That's Papa John's. I don't like that pizza. Is that so wrong to say I don't like that pizza?
My religious man. Um, not really. He's a, he's Mormon. Where are you getting the idea that I'm
Mormon? Yeah. Oh shit. Okay. This is where it gets real at 300.
This is a good game to stream. Yeah, I'm having a good time. As much as you can have a good time,
just having things yell at you every so often. Yeah, that's been a minute or two.
This reminds me of Dreadhalls. So I can like go into these too. Nice. Sick. Sick Windows 95
adventure game music. Blasted. It's perfect. Now bring back the like the dunks and I just,
am I reading this out of order? One day a strange merchant came to town. He sold handmade puppets
and trinkets and all the children loved his store and his gifts. But the town couldn't support his
store because the other shops were failing. The other shopkeepers became jealous. So one night,
some of the town's people took all his puppets and threw them in the river. But just afterwards,
he came running to the river crying and wailing that his children were being drowned.
He dove into the river trying to save his possessions. The townspeople, bitter and still
angry, watched him frantically thrash and dive into the river until he never came back to the
surface of the water. That's a huge key. I thought the key was a pair of scissors. That's where it
came from. Use the key. How many stars do I have? That was slow to get up. Somebody in here. Although
not what they wanted, the shopkeepers were satisfied. Years later, the children of the
town began to go missing. And as more and more children disappeared, people began to find more
and more puppets in the forest and around the river. These puppets seemed almost to look like
the missing children sometimes. Open door. This door looks different than all the others. Why?
Okay. All right. So it teleports. Hey! I'm dead. I'm dead.
No! No! No, I can't do eye shit. I can't do eye shit. I can't. I can't. I can't do eye shit.
Harshness of choice. Now nothing you do is your fault. Now you belong to something. You belong to me.
Game over. Your soul wanders an endless maze. I think I just heard like my dog bark.
Hold on. I think he's like, maybe he wants to go in a room or something. Give me one second. He's
like, hey, come get me. I don't know. He just kind of was, he's eaten. He ate today. He's gone out
today. I think he was just annoyed with me that I wasn't playing with him. He was just like,
what are you doing? I was like, why are you in there? I said, hello.
And we'll see. We'll see what he does. Play with him. I just did. I played with him with a toy
and I gave him a snack. So he's good. Show auto. On my next BRB, because he's like awake. So
when I leave, I'll go bring him in here. You can say hello. No, not now. Not right now. In a little
bit. All right. So this guy, I have to run as fast as I can. I have to do this dumb stuff again.
Get the key and open the door and 305, 306, 307, 308, three. It's not the same. This is different.
Wait, why is this different? There's another cat dos. Physical punctures. A wooden life-size
puppet found floating in a reservoir where a town had once been. Specimen is active despite
appearance and has proved very effective on subjects who disregard it or have vision
impairments. Disregard it? Disregard it. So I get it. I don't know what that is. Like a painting.
Specimen is constantly changing form and attributes depending on subject's personality.
The most common form resembles a wall of moving anatomy symbols. Only effective on subjects with
past trauma or a history of psychological issues. Okay. Floating figure that appeared in a test
chamber a few years after it was filled with what was believed to just be unusually violent
deer. Specimen seems to engulf subjects and absorb them into its torso region,
proved extremely effective on violent subjects. So don't attack this one. Exit program. Here it is.
You'll get the key. Puppets. Watch out for the puppets. This person used, this person was a
puppet. And they are now. They used to be a person, but now they're a puppet.
So watch out and look at them because he's, he gives reactions to people that do not care about
them. The hell did I just do? Key. All right. Let's try this again. Do I kind of like level up my
stamina bar? All right. So I, he gets mad if you don't pay attention to it. Whoa. His eyes just got
angry. Oh, he's angry. That's actually pretty scary. Where, where, where, where, where, where,
where? Oh, where, where is he? I hate that face. It's fucking horrifying. I'll go to the chair
route. I did it. He's gone. Nice. He's not still here, right? Okay. On to three 50.
I'm seeing this brain room again. That dude's coming back. That dude's coming back. I'm certain
of it. He's going to just appear in front of me and I'm going to have to run away and turn around
or something. Yup. I knew it. I knew it. Oh, it's this, it's this lady. Okay. Oh, he instantly died.
Find out. I'm not going to find out because I looked over at chat. I thought, I don't know,
I thought that was like one of you guys coming at me. Where's my checkpoint? Oh, that's not good.
You get a checkpoint every hundred now. Of course. Why would it be any video games?
I've played these already. Jeremy, could you please keep it down? I've had a horrible cold
the last few days. I need to rest. Go take a bath. What are you doing here? Go season your bathtub
with epsom salt and make it hot enough where it's, it's our, oh, it's silent. No,
figure it out. Watch this. How do I get out of here? You got to do a backwards long jump. Yeah.
What am I thinking? I have to go and fly through the fucking ball. Pay attention. That's just on
the wall now. What does that mean? That actually just scared me. That was like a scary thing.
Stop. It's like sticking your beds on the wall. What's that? Sick. Ah, it's back. He's back. He's
back. Um, oh fuck. Which way is it? Is it left or right? This guy, I hate this guy. He's fucking
horrible. I have to go left. It's a goddamn chair route. Don't die. Please don't die here.
You motherfucker. You motherfucker. Get away from me. Oh my God. Oh my God. I have, how many more
from this is it? Oh shit. God. That guy's scary. This is face. When that guy gets close to you,
he does that face and it's just horrible. Don't die now chair. He's close though.
Right this time. Right this time. Another one of these. Why? Okay. Always left.
It's left every time. Except I did left before and it wasn't during the puppet guy. 400. Bingo.
We got it. Yes. Yes. Keep that blood pumping. GL Labs. 40%. Pretty cool. Anything else,
anything I need to know. So there's an image. Let's see what it is. I got a nice clean tongue.
Auto. No, I'm auto. I'm not going to get auto right now. I'm going to get auto at my break.
I'm not going to need to go get auto. He's doing just fine. I'll get him at my next break.
And then he's probably going to just hang out in here for a minute. I don't want auto in here,
by the way, because, oh, yeah. Let me, let me put, let me put my dog in the room and,
oh, hey guys, there's a little bed for you right here. And every 45 seconds,
he's going to be like, what the? I don't want to do that. That's like, I'm just be scaring him.
He scared me. Yeah. And imagine if you were a dog that was like sleeping over here, lying down.
Imagine you, imagine if you were sleeping and you've heard that. All right. I gotta pay attention.
It's the brain again. Scalp is itchy again. Just happens. I thought they got rid of you.
I thought they got rid of you things. I thought you didn't do that anymore. I don't,
I didn't think they did that anymore after floor 300. Why are some of these doors locked?
Threshold of consciousness. Oh, it's a cat. That's all it was.
It's like a test of endurance. This game is a test of endurance
to see if you can get to floor 1000. Oh, that's, I just was over there. Don't touch them.
I have to pick a side. Strawberry or vanilla. Oh, this is tough. Strawberry. Strawberry ice cream is,
wait, this is important. Strawberry ice cream is terrible if it has strawberry chunks in it.
But if it's a smooth strawberry ice cream, no bullshit, just smooth strawberry flavor,
that's the best ice cream you can possibly buy. That's just a regular ice cream. Vanilla on the
other hand, it's, this looks like vanilla bean. So that, this is, okay, so we have smooth
strawberry ice cream and vanilla bean ice cream. That makes this a lot harder because vanilla bean
ice cream is way better. I think I would still want the strawberry, smooth strawberry. Yeah,
I'm staying with the smooth strawberry ice cream. How do I say yes? I don't think it does anything.
Does that floor look smooth to you? It's pixelated. That's, this floor is pixelated too.
Should I touch all this stuff? All right, well, whatever. I chose mint chocolate. No, pistachio
without pistachios. One of the best ice creams is pistachio ice cream. What without, I just spit
them out. See me and, me and Kim, we do this thing where when I get pistachio ice cream,
I just eat the ice cream and then I, I spit out the pistachios and then she eats them.
That's not weird. I eat, well, look, let me tell you, I eat around the pistachios and then like,
they just, I just don't eat them. I will save big chunks of ice cream with pistachios in them
and I make a little corner that's like, that's for Kim because she likes, she loves pistachios.
So I make, there's like 12 pistachios just sitting in the corner with like ice cream around them and
she just eats them. I don't like, I mean, I don't like spit them out, Mr. Q. That's disgusting.
Yeah, just, telephones are ringing. Telephones are ringing. Ah, become, follow the group.
Free come more than yourself. Be who you are. Follow the group. That's what it says. Be who you
are to others. Oh, the dev is not a three. I thought it was like a three. How did I see
that differently? I saw three E. It was fucked up. No, it was fucked up. See the backgrounds changing
behind this sometimes. It actually, clip it and look at it. You'll see what I'm talking about.
Trust me. Also, butter pecan ice cream falls in this category as well. Butter pecan ice cream is
absolutely delicious, but get those pecans out of there. The actual butter pecan flavored
ice cream is incredible. I just want to buy just the ice cream. Why is that so strange?
And then they decided they were going to come up with something called butter crunch
and it's that butter pecan ice cream. What's happening? It's the bugs. Okay.
Okay. Butter pecan ice cream turns into butter crunch and then they turn the pecans
instead of pecans. It's now these chunky, crunchy, buttery, tasty, sweet things. And that's all right.
That's a step in the right direction, but you need to go full blown only butter
flavored ice cream. The butter pecan flavored ice cream. That's blood. Knowing your shadow can
greatly help you, but be ready to see what you'd rather not be. Knowing your shadow. Watch out for
your shadow. It was scary until you added the Mario sounds. What is that? What the fuck is that?
What was, what is that? What's that thing? What do I do about the, oh, it's the wall guy.
It's the wall guy. And now the Indiana Jones river is flying over here.
What do I do with wall person? Do I step? I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. What do I do
with the wall? I just heard auto again. All right. Hold on. I have to like, let me, let me go try to
like see if he wants to go out. I'm going to take like a few minute break here. Oh shit. Uh oh.
This is like a countdown. Okay. All right. All right. All right. All right. I got, I've got to
go see, I've got to go take out a lot. I'll be right back again. Sorry. I need to see what,
I need to see what Otto needs. I don't think he's hungry. I think he's been fed. All right.
I'll be right back. Let me see what's going on. Okay. I'm returned. Uh, he had to take a big dump.
That's what happened. And he didn't want to come upstairs with me. He was like running around. He
didn't, he took, he did with that thing where he took a big dog poop and he was just so happy
to have taken that dog poop that he was just like, everything is great now. And he just
sprinting around. He didn't want to come up here. You'll see him today. Later. Not there. I don't
want that. That's not, I don't want to bring him up here during the scream game because what,
because once I bring him up here, you know, he's in the room and he's hanging out and he's like,
it's all right. All right. Now you're out of here. It's like, well, I, you just brought me in here
to hang out with you. Sorry. I don't want to scream and have you hear my screaming while you're
trying to sleep. Bring him up during the outro. Yeah, I know you'll see him. You'll see him later.
You will see Otto on this stream or I'll do a 24 hour stream. By the time this stream turns off,
you will see Otto. All right. That was left, left, right, straight, left, right, left, right.
See, I'm a puzzle master. That's how I knew how to do that. All right. Don't, I don't want to get
cocky or anything because it really is, it's every hundred floors, rooms, whatever. I forgot
to apply my lip balm. Balm streamer. Yeah. Somebody said you have dry ass lips and I was like,
fucking I'll fix it. I get dry lips, especially out here in Vegas.
Vegas. Yeah. I live in Las Vegas now. Yes, I do. Really? This whole time I've just been
living in Massachusetts. I think this room, last time something jumped out there.
Oh, it's the, it's the girl. Where? Why am I? I'm going back. Oh, my head. That just like short
circuited. Oh no. Where's this exit? Am I insane? Why are you still here? It's going to be the puppet
guy again. I knew it, right? What's that thing? What's that mean? That's new. That's new. That's
a new sound. What's the cardboard? Oh, there was the cardboard did late. It screwed up.
This thing, their cues all the time. What's that one? This means something, right? Oh, it's a bug.
Okay. Anytime you hear the, it's the big caterpillar. Get out of the way, coffee.
Okay. I'm good. No, I'm not. No, I'm not. What is this? What is that?
Oh, it's this thing that makes everything all weird. Oh shit. Okay. They're almost there.
Almost there. Almost there. Almost there. 484. Not going to happen anymore. You're not going to get
me, but it's like 15 times you've gotten me. Not going to happen again. Am I good? I'm good. All
right. Thank God. Halfway point coming up. Little shit. Didn't get it. Okay. I'm good. Go back. Go
back. You don't go back in this game. You only go forward. Can you fall off the edge?
I don't want to test that. I'm so glad nothing's following me. Table ending.
Jeremy, I'm trying to catch up with you playing Darkwood and you're streaming again.
Hey, what's up? And we're streaming tomorrow, too. You'll be happy to know that tomorrow is
Darkwood again. A va de friends. Give me that. 500. Password is.
Well, here you are. Still here. Next door is going to fix up for you. So enjoy and keep moving on.
So pumpkin cheese. Next one's going to be cake and the next one's going to be
latte. At the last floor. Why can I not save the game? There we go.
Pumpkin cheese. 500 rovers. I saved it. I'm good. I'm good. I'm good. So this one's out of order
and this one's not out of order. I mean, you go to the one that's out of order.
Never mind. Let's go halfway there. Why is this 52? I don't know if this means anything,
but I just got logged in and I got logged out and logged in on Steam.
Save corrupted. Room 53. No, this is scripted. This is scripted. This is scripted. I'm going to
get to like floor 100 and it's going to be, it's going to be like, oh, you made it. Why'd you go
that way? Now walk into this portal. The cat's going to come back and I'm going to go to like
portal and go to five, like 50. That's definitely how this is going to work. He's lost it.
Yeah, this is a different room too.
MonkaS. Can you only talk in the auto voice till you get to floor 100? Yeah.
Edward002313BFBGEL. Cannot release twice. Exit through express. I told you guys this
wouldn't happen. You didn't get to 100. I got to 100 five times. That's 500.
You got to hear it. Good. Good.
Good. Good. Bugs. Bugs. Bugs. Good. Good bugs. All right. God. Open. Yeah. I don't even, I don't,
they just get me because they're just annoying. They just get in the way.
And of course I have to react because I have to get out of the way.
531. All right. I can't fucking do that right now. I'm trying.
My, both my ears are blocked. I can't do anything.
That's yeah, that's the bank of fucking America. What about it?
This is new music. What is that? I don't know what this new music means, but I have to move.
Don't attack the one. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. Preparing for it. Whatever it is.
Okay. We're outside. There's a cabin. For a while, I thought I had really escaped this place,
but despite the trees and flora, I think this is actually just another room.
I did hope to find deer, so I might at least get to eat and make some strange sounds though.
This is the deer enemy, which I was told do not attack the deer enemy. Don't attack the
What the fuck is wrong with you? I don't know what they are, but those are definitely not deer.
No shit. I tried sneaking up on one the other day to kill for food,
but it saw me as soon as I got close. I was barely able to get away from the thing.
I've managed to board up most of them. Hopefully I can find another way out of here.
Don't get, don't get near them. Do not go near them. I thought I said don't attack them.
What? We're inside of a computer. They don't follow you into rooms, right? I hate this music.
It's like an untuned piano underwater. What the fuck are you? Hi, what's happening? How are you?
Who are you? Who are you? Who are you? Who is that person?
Oh, no, no. It's the person that runs in front of you. I don't know what that means.
What does it say? Is it a Borg? Toast. It's the guy. It's the guy. Oh, no. This was the worst.
This was worse. This spit on me. This spit all over my mouth. This is blood. I can't tell.
I have like a big spit wad on my mouth. You need to get your submission
is forfeit to me. I will devour your flesh. That guy wasn't as scary as this guy. What?
I need that heal. Let's go. You did it. You actually, you did it. You did it. Hello. You
were at, you did it. You did the thing. You did it. You did it. I didn't do it. You did it.
You actually did it. I knew it. Break the fan. Don't look in the fan. I've been
600 Romans. It's 60% of the way through this. 600. Oh, dude. Oh, pog, dude.
Pog. All right. This is Pillar. Make like a tree and die coming this fall. Interesting. I still
have the axe, right? That comes with me. What are most of those never-ending hallways that I
came across? Don't hurt them. Well, what are they doing? If a guy's running down a hallway with an
axe, I don't think it's smart to jump out in front of them and yell. I would stay closed. I would
not open. Especially if the person was like panicking. Oh, shit. You don't want to start
off a panicking guy with the axe. That's just, that seems like common sense. Oh, this is not
good. I don't know where I'm going. Oh, that doesn't work. This whole place is somehow even
worse than the new GL labs. Although it seems to have been constructed with a much larger budget
than the new lab, nothing works quite right. I can see why it was abandoned so quickly.
I wonder if there really is anything here worth salvaging. Reset.
Reset. Power's back on. Go this way.
This is loud. This is very loud. Make it louder. I don't, you don't want this to be louder. This,
not this, not this, not a vent. Not a vent. The easiest horror game environment is the vent.
And it is the most effective. It's the goddamn vent. Spooky just said that there were things
we needed to salvage from this place. I'm starting to worry that a loose specimen may be included in
the list of things for us to retrieve. The power just shut off again. Is everything broken in here?
I don't know what to do. I can't think while I feel strange. I'm hiding from that thing.
I feel like something is growing on my skin. I can't seem to tear it off fast enough. I'm
losing a lot of blood. That thing. Can I please go in a different room now? Oh.
You have to keep it close. It becomes something else when it gets too far away.
Something I can't outrun. I'll, I'll give it a try. I'm going to give it a try.
Stay close. Get over here. Stay near me. It hurts. Hey, it said keep the thing close.
It's turned into an animal. Jump scares always distance 242. What does that mean?
Okay, so I need to keep it close. I can't kill it. So just back around. Why am I wearing two
headphones? You monster. Well, because if I have one headphone and I can't hear them come around
corners, and it is a horror game and there is a face cam on, so I might as well really, really go
for it. 604. Shit. Keep it close. Here we are. 607. 608. What? 609. Wait, what's that sound? I
forget. This is it. Okay, I made it. All right. All right. So just keep it close. Just back away.
Turn off my lights in my room. No, I'm not going to the movies. I'm not going to the movies during
the day. Lights off, you're a coward. During the day. Okay, here we go. This is all just for show.
Nothing happens in here. Stay close, but not too close. Yes. This is it.
Where's the fucking door? Follow me. Follow me. Follow me. Follow me. Follow me. Let's go.
Hi. Where's the door? Where's the door? Right here. I want you to look at me.
Look at me. What's my range? I'm not very good. I wonder what happens if I sprint around the
circle, but I don't want to lose. I want to find out. Is it getting faster? Come on. Come here.
How long is this going to go on for? Still following me.
Oh, this guy sucks. How far is too far? I wonder. Watch the door. You're doing an escort mission.
Yeah, that's what it feels like. All right. The scare factor on this dude is gone.
No, you're just kind of sad. What the fuck was that? He's gone. What was that? You are here.
622. Who is it? What is that? It's you again. I thought we were done with this. Not for another
20 rooms, apparently. Just ditch him. Just ditch him. But it said that if I go too far away,
he'll turn into something that it's impossible for me to run away from.
To wait for you. No, I'm not going to ditch him. I don't even know where the hell I'm going though.
How far is too far though, I wonder. Let him grab your butt. Do it. I'm not going to do that.
But what if he kills you instantly? Going this way. It's going to be a pop-up thing.
Come on. You're slowing me down. I did so many rooms so fast. Now I have to do it like this.
Let's go. Needed a few extra punches there. Getting tired. Snorlax, whatever his name is.
What am I doing? No, I guess that makes sense. What's the thing from Star Wars that eats the
people? It looks like that big circle. The Snorlax. I said you're looking tired. I didn't mean
like Snorlax tired. I meant like Sarlacc pit. That's just what I called him. I didn't mean to
make that be actually like Snorlax. Guys, I'm bored and I have to walk with this toddler back
here. Thank god. Not that way. You dare. No, you dare come in one of these rooms.
Where that monster is going to be a pain in the ass is when I don't know what's about to happen
and it happens and I'm just running. That's going to be bad. He's closed when he first comes
in a room and then he opens. So that's what he looks like. 640. Getting there. Dev in chat. Dev
in chat. What's up? What's going on? I wonder what happens when I get to a thousand. They spread him
out far enough that you just forget that it's even possible. All right. Wait a minute. Wait a minute.
In order to survive this house, I need to keep writing notes. I must do everything a central
protagonist would and hope this is one of those stories. Insert obscure horror reference that
no one gets and misinterprets as instructions somehow. It's me. It's me writing those notes.
I'm just getting weirder and weirder as I go. Come on. Come on. You don't think you try to make
yourself laugh when you came around the corner for like a hundredth time. I don't know what this
means. Oh, it's just the your flesh will be mine. Oh, I this is this is such a this is that the
person runs in front of you. Here we go. They remember this. You have to go around like three or
four times. Sprints and screams at the screen like right now. I missed it. Good. I didn't see it.
There wasn't even any music. Their music usually starts. They have a whole song. They have a
soundtrack for these monsters. Clicking. Is that what it is? He's right behind me.
What? Oh, isn't this the that's not the music for the I thought that was the music.
No, I don't have I can't do it. I have to run.
Time to sprint sprint. Go. Go. Okay. Okay. I'm gonna get hurt. It's okay. I can take a few hits.
Almost 700.
Those can be attributed to somebody just sticking a fork into your back randomly. Like I know they're
in the room. Like if Kim was sitting behind me right now with a fork and every like 12 minutes
she just went like that. I'd be like it would scare me. It'll be like fucked up. I know you're
back there. I know you're gonna do it. But I don't know when or why. Why is everybody writing single
twos? Oh, no. It's dark. It was way too dark. Oh, that's horrible. I don't know where I am.
What the fuck is the door? That sucks. Pog. Hey, Pog. That's all I gotta say. That's all I gotta say.
Anyone notes? Wrong way. LOL Pog. You don't Pog after an LOL. Actually, yeah, maybe you can.
Depends on the scenario, I guess. Thankfully, no one's here. 700 coming up.
Just gotta make it to 700. Still don't understand what that's for.
Okay, don't fight it, right? Just run.
Your submission is- You! I keep cutting this guy off. He's just like,
I- You're- Because you're freaking me out. You don't say your submission is inevitable.
And then why are you running? Your submission is inevitable. I will devour you.
Why are you running away from me? Fuck off. Well, I still haven't died,
so it appears I might be the protagonist, but I'm not entirely sure. I hope I'm not some side
character that leaves notes for pointless exposition. Also, I found a strange computer
that gave descriptions of the monsters, and it seems like they are called effective based on how
many people they kill. Shit. Left. Right. Right. Right, left, right, left, right, left. Floor 700.
That much closer. Keep that blood pumping. All right, anything going on?
This is my time to interact with you guys. We only have 300 rooms left, yeah?
Auto. Get auto. I will be at the stream. I missed 666. I was being chased by a monster,
and I didn't want to go back to 600. All right, let's keep going. No, I said by the end of the
stream, if auto wasn't on it, then I would do a 24 hour stream. So, I just have to show auto
before I turn off the stream. 701. Let's go down. Notes.
I want to see the computer again. I feel like there's a few specimens I need to take a look
at that I don't know about. Restaurant? Taste the beef. 100% beef. What's on the menu? I can't read
that far. That looks like shit, actually. An old egg McMuffin. Fun rules. Okay, well, I need a key.
Behind the counter? One, I was anxious getting a job here at first, but it seems like things
are getting better. This chain is really expanding, which is a shock. Because just last week,
I heard this company was going broke. Every day, more and more people show up to eat here.
Something still sets me off about this place and its food, though. So, I'm going to try and not
eat anything from here. Into the freezer. Today was a weird day. The average number of orders
continues to rise as is, as it has been. But I don't know about the number of people. Today,
I saw someone else, someone use the drive-through and order a lot of food for one person. And then,
about 10 minutes later, they were back. They ordered the same exact meals, and then they left
again. Then after another 10 minutes, they were back again. Maybe they're just delivering food
for a party or hotel, but it worries me for some reason. I've done that plenty of times.
You guys have never done that before? You've never driven to Wendy's? You get two meals.
You finish both of them. You park. You just literally park your car and sit and eat in the
parking lot. And then you just want to make sure that you're still not hungry. So then you go back
and you get a soda or you get a frosty or something if you want. Or a small bacon cheeseburger. What
do they call it? The small ones. The ones that everyone loves. Junior bacon cheeseburger. Maybe
you want one more. That happens often. Why? What? Somebody was in here? Did I take too long? I took
too long in here. Thankfully, it's 700. I stood still for too long. Okay. Anyways, I've done that
before. Lost to Wendy's. Something like that. Wendy's Wheel. All right, let's go.
I want to get to 800 by three hours and 12 minutes. That's it. That was that was 12 minutes from
what I just said. Okay, into the restaurant. So I was in here. Can I go in any of the bathrooms?
Well, I broke my one rule today. The management doesn't give out actual lunch breaks.
So I can't go anywhere and they won't allow outside food here. I mean, they actually screamed
at the last customer who did that. Anyway, I had a burger. It wasn't bad and I don't feel sick. So
I might get a few every now and then. Got a key. It was in here. Yep. They're probably,
they're probably eating people. Yeah, this is a weird day. It worries me. Somebody came over here
and they ordered the same thing three times. Well, that's the way in. It's this one. This is
strange. I had a dream last night about this restaurant. I know I was here, but I also felt
like I was in another place at the same time. Everything looked so wrong. Nothing was the right
size. And I kept hearing these strange animal noises. Almost like wailing. I guess I just feel
guilty for eating that burger the other day. Also today I saw that man again, the one who kept
ordering every 10 minutes. This time he never even left the parking lot. Then he just got his meal
parked and then back in line. He must have done it at least eight times. He must be this tall.
No screams. Look out for snakes. No alcohol. No diving. No hiding. We will find you.
Laugh it up. Shoes. All right, let's go. There was a horrible accident today. At least that's what
the managers are calling it. One of the other employees brought in some outside food and got
into a fight with the manager about it. No one's coming in here, right? The employee said that the
burgers here smell like sulfur. I then watched the manager grab the kid's neck and shove his
head into the grill. The employee got up and ran out before anyone could do anything and I'm told
that he's fine, but that really shook me today. I can't sprint in here if you're curious. I think
because I'm crouching. This is still the same room too. Oh, give me a break. There's something in here.
What is this?
Get me out of this. There's a key. Okay, got the key. What's that key for? In here? The freezer.
Hey, one of these is gonna wake up and I hear somebody behind me. I can hear somebody here.
I got another key. I hear somebody behind me. I hear somebody. What's that music supposed to mean?
One of these is gonna grab me. What's the what's the fucking key for, folks? What's the demon?
What the fuck am I supposed to do about the demon? How do I get out of here?
Whoa! What door is it for? That's the entrance. I'm dead. It's the Burger King demon. Did I just
break the game? I don't know what that specimen does. I don't understand. This looks like somebody
in the room. Is somebody in this room? No. He hides the doors. You dastardly motherfucker.
Oh, no, no. It's too hard to get away from people when they're...
Hey, just go, go, go, go, go, go. Don't stop for nothing. Unless it's the squid person.
Oh, not you again. I'm actually not scared of this person at all.
I don't even know what this thing does, but it doesn't scare me.
Oh, don't get...
They float, they float, they float, they float, they float, they float, they float, they float,
they float, they float, they float, they float, they float, they float, they float, they float,
go, they float, they float, they float. Oh, this is bad.
Okay, this sounds like when your English teacher has, they have a Halloween event
and like Mrs. Stevenson recorded some scary lines and it's played over the school haunted house.
Your flesh is mine. No, but you know what I'm saying. It's like a...
I made it. Weird fucking teachers. No, no. Unlimited stamina. Thanks a lot.
I told you it was going to be pumpkin cheese cake latte. I told you this and I, it's, I told you.
Eee. It's going to be pumpkin cheesecake latte and then someone's going to be,
a scary ghost is going to be drinking a latte at the end and that's the joke.
If I got it, don't tell me I got it. Infinite stamina. Oh, well, here's the, the kicker here
is the stamina. There is no, there is no sprint. I can't run. I think the effectiveness of the
specimens is also somewhat related to the souls of the people that they killed. Anyway, I'm still
alive and strong, but I feel like the most, the inmost cave of my journey lies ahead. I wonder
what the antagonists will look like. I hope they're cute. No more sprinting. That's not good.
He's clenching his ass. I probably will be in about a hundred rooms. So how do you get away
from things if you can't, do I have to seriously run and like walk in a circle to bait around in
a circle and not get stabbed somehow? How does one do this? This is impossible with some of these
monsters. I have to kill. Infinite axe attacks too though. That's right. That's a good call.
Just jump on them like Super Mario. Thankfully, it's 750. They, they did that because this would
be a pain in the ass to walk through all these again. So I get it. Let's make it not happen to
me. Pac-Man's like my favorite character. Why would I do that? Oh, I can move again.
Big mistake. Giving that back.
Finally, I get a computer. Finally, I get some extra computer time. Let's see. Specimen. Where
were we? Eight. Okay. A float guy. I have to get closer. I have to, I'm too far away from the
screen. I'm standing all the way back here. Like, hold on. Stop. Get out. Back. There we go. Get
close. You guys have ruined, you've ruined me because that said eat ass in my brain for a second.
Total fatalities. One. Take the dead. Two. Take the dead. To take the dead. To take the dead.
That doesn't really help me at all. It does this thing. Parasitic infections that form change a
creature that is believed to be extraterrestrial though was not officially proven. Proved very
effective on most subjects but deemed too difficult to contain. The specimen broke out
of its containment area due to frequent electrical malfunctions. That's the thing. A
floating red figure that was found inside a secret area below a large abandoned corporate office
once owned by a restaurant franchise. The specimen is extremely violent and also seems to leave the
house at will despite various containment methods. Victims vanish on contact with specimen but
sometimes remains of the victims have been found inside the testing chamber days later. Proved
not effective as victim's souls do not remain after contact. What does that mean? I want to
see what this thing is. Proved extremely effective on violent subjects and you just you have to just
run away. Seven six five. Let's go. Almost the big 800. More of these tubes. What's the lightning
strike for? I just realized that I never had a mentor figure. Trial or leaving home scene.
That means the story isn't following the archetypes to make me a traditional hero.
Which means I could be killed off. Well it was nice for a little while at least.
I haven't seen a special infected in a while. It's gonna happen soon. Holy shit. Holy shit. I
wasn't prepared for you to be here. I hate this motherfucker so much. Oh fuck. Where is he gonna
be? I don't know. Somewhere over here. Oh fuck. I've ruined everything this way. Why?
Why is it giving me these same shitty rooms over and over again? You dickhead. Heal. Heal for a second.
Go. Oh fuck you.
Okay. Look for an arrow. Look at the fish. He's gone. 800. Come on. Don't fuck around. Just get
there. There's gonna be another thing that's gonna pop up. I don't care. I don't care.
Special effects. Two. See ya. This is the English teacher.
All right. No more. No more getting stuck on that one. So English teacher. See ya. 800. 200 more.
Norma's there. Norma link please. Norma please say hello. Like hello? Why? I don't understand.
Why? Why? That link didn't open by the way. Click this link. All right. Hold on. I'm gonna
put this on the screen. I want to read this one. Hey! Did I save the game? Did I save the game?
I don't think I saved the game. I don't think. Did I save it? Wait. What happened?
What is going on? Wait. Wait. Wait. Wait. Wait. This is like a... I can't see chat room. What
happened? Chat is broken right now. Why did it open like five doors? Streamer fatalities. Method
bad jokes. This specimen likes to make funny noises and bad jokes in order to satisfy the voices in
his head. Escaped confinement throughout the use of a hot air balloon. Actually insane. Avoid all
contact. Use the word boomer if approached to drive it up. That's a pretty good one.
I hope I saved the game because that would be a no- I would hate to have to go through
those 50 zones again. 800. Thank god. Saved. 800. Got the axe. I'm ready. Let's move.
I'm gonna find out what the real story of this game actually is. Did I make it to 800 in the time
that was a lot? I didn't realize that guy had a unique kill screen in save rooms. That's
completely new to me. Yeah. That was kind of weird. Yeah. Day two. Food supply depleted.
Water supply at 30%. Mental health deteriorating. Leaving notes behind to help others and mark where
I've been. Is there more? No. Day two. Room 800. Well, I'll be fair to the game. I've been streaming
for three and a half hours and gone through 800 rooms. So, I mean, that's- that makes sense. It
would take you that long if you weren't sprinting. Did I always wait till 809? 709? Okay. It's still
the same room somehow. Broken. This is a big room. This mansion is strange. I think the bricks and
wood are actually just painted on. Everything still feels kind of fake. Also, I keep hearing
movement and voices below me. Maybe other survivors are hiding down there. That's strange. Locked.
Probably go up the stairs. Broken. Okay. Damn library. Someone's gonna be here.
I can hear him coming down the hallway. I need to hide, but I don't know where.
I now know this is not an exit or a resting place. It is just another specimen room. I think he's
outside the door now. Well, where do I hide? Where do you hide, huh? This is a terrible- this is a
two-year-old hiding spot. He gone? Where is he? Look up there. His head's gonna be poking over
and he's gonna go, hey! And it's gonna be terrifying. Let's go upstairs. Locked doors. I can't hide there?
I somehow managed to get away, but I don't know for how long. I hear him. Even when I know he's
not there, it's like he isn't even real, but instead my own fears manifesting themselves and stalking me.
Hide. So what? He's not real. So that he can't hurt me. So I'll be fine. Confront him. I need a key.
Both these doors are broken. Come on. Every room looks the same. Every room's the same room.
That's one squeaky gamer chair. I'll tell you, I don't think that guy could lift that side.
I don't think I have anything to worry about. That looks a little too heavy for you.
Can I recommend a sickle? Can I recommend- can I recommend a knife? It is a sickle.
There's a side. The side- a sickle is a small side. The side is huge. The side is- it's like
a harvesting side. Pick up a key. Get the library key. Nice. So that's bedroom, bedroom, library.
Currently looking for a library. Locked. Is this the library? No. The library is probably-
let's try this one. Hold on a second here. Library. No. Library. Library.
What the fuck is happening? None of these are the library.
That's not the library.
What? I- I don't know where the library is. Where is it? Stop it. Stop- I've been in every
single door. I've been in every door. All the same room. Oh my god. There's a book missing.
Other- hide, hide. This is the relatable content that I come here for. Thanks a lot.
I feel like I could just go push him. That's a full four and a half seconds for you to lift up
that. I could just shove you to the ground. Do it then, because this is taking way too long.
I'm just gonna go. Are you going? I didn't hear the door open. Picked up the book. Go replace
the book in the library. Secret door. Finally made it out of here. What the fuck does that mean?
I'm still in room 810? Man. Oh, remember when the note said I can hear people running around down
here? Was I hearing me? What does that mean? Why is this music changing? Oh, give me a break.
I'm still doing laps upstairs. I get a note down here. I can hear somebody running around in circles
upstairs. It's really odd. I wonder what they're up to. This is all one floor. I hope I make it
to 850, because I don't want to do this whole thing again. Exit. Exit key. What do you mean the exit
key? I don't know. I know. It's the door. It's the door. It's the door up here. It's up. And then
it's somewhere. I have to remember. Goldfish, goldfish, goldfish, goldfish kid. Goldfish kid.
Go up. Out. Out of here. Out of here. Out of here. Oh no. I'm gonna get lost again.
That's what somebody, that bagpipe player face. Don't make me laugh right now. A bagpipe player.
What does that even mean? Give me 850. Ah, shit. Hello. Why is everybody linking me saying hello?
Nobody was. I think one person did actually. One person linked me saying hello. And I said
everybody. I just lumped you all together. Only like 10 more. What is it? What is it though? What
is it? Okay, stay close. This is thing blocking me. I'm so glad I only have to do this for like
six more floors. He doesn't know. No, I don't. I, I, I do not. You're right. I don't, I don't know.
49. All right, let's go. 50. Oh, this is bad. Okay, I have to do all 100.
That's not good. What am I, what am I doing? I got complacent for like 30 seconds.
Just run now. No, I'm good. I didn't go away. I didn't go away far enough for long enough.
I really just don't, I don't want to do this again. So I need to be locked in to get to 900.
At least this gives me a minute to relax. I think this is locked. I may have made a mistake coming
back here. This is locked, I think. Check it. No. Attack it. No. I'm not gonna. He's still here.
He's still here. He's still here. It's this way. Good thing I did it. It's either way. It doesn't
matter. Just run. You cannot run. Come on, guys. Don't you know this by now? I can't run from this
thing. If I run far enough away, it turns into a mother monster that I cannot run from. Now we're
good. Almost there. Not long now. Just go faster. I have a stamina bar. I can't do that. I'm just
waiting to hear that pound. It's a ding. It's a ding donk. Left. Left. Three lefts. And then a
straight. Three lefts and then a right. I'm good. Game room. I already played all these. 30 more
rooms. Is it? Oh, it's this thing. I forget. I remember. I forget what this one does. I have
to go back and then run this way. It's gonna scream. Get ready. Here comes the scream. It's
gonna scream at you. Just do it already. All right, sit up. Don't lose it here. I can taste it. Come
on. What is it? What is it? What does that mean? I don't remember. There's too many monsters to
remember. I looked at chat for a second and it was one of those poppers. What is it? Monk! I'm
actually okay with this. I'm all right with this. That's fine. It's just not knowing what it is.
I can't believe I'm actually going to do this. I'm gonna get to the floor thousand.
Four more and I get to 900. Almost there. Come on. Two. 899. This is it. This is the home stretch.
Only 100 more floors. And that's it. And I beat the game. Here we go. You're still on the first
island. You used that one last night. Left, right, left, right, left, right, left, left, straight.
Okay. Day three. Hallucinations are manifesting at increasing intervals. The cause is probably
sleep deprivation or a gas that is being pumped into the rooms. I've not yet been injured so I
don't think the cause is a brain injury or blood clot. It's this thing. Oh no.
Counting how many times I've said oh no. Or what does he do? What does he do? What does he do?
Research report. More whales are being shipped to the facility tomorrow. Wow. One for a health
inspection and two that are already dead for autopsies. That thing's gonna attack me from
somewhere. More and more beached whales keep appearing around these islands and I still can't
find out what's causing it. I don't even have a flashlight or anything. I am going to get stuck
here. Whale 15D has died much sooner than I expected while I was away on holiday. I regret
not being here but I had estimated it would live much longer. The team that did the autopsy said
nothing seemed to be wrong with the lungs but the stomach had a circular hole about two feet
in diameter all the way through to the outside of the whale. This pretty much confirms a parasite
is the cause of death. There's the whale. What is going on in this game? And now I have to deal with
this stuff. I have to try to remember this. It's so dark. I'm gonna get so lost. The research
facility is now in dire need of more engineers. We have a whole block that is flooded and some
vital staff are missing. Is there a key or something? Shit. Can we get a sweat check?
It's gone. It's going. It's oh it's it's going. It's still alive but gets into fits of thrashing
and is surfacing more from the natural. Something wrong with its lungs. I will have to allow it to
die from whatever is causing it and then do an autopsy. Whale 14D has strange small bite marks.
They appear from another smaller mammal but the strange thing about them is their placement.
They're in even rows inside the whale's stomach all about five feet from the bottom of the stomach
lining. I just got a lantern. This thing doesn't run out of gas right? Excerpt 4132 and then I
watched carelessly as the sea rose above the sky casting waving shadows over the world. I saw the
silhouettes of creatures both familiar and forgotten and suddenly I found myself falling
upwards towards an ocean of darkness. All right four one what was it four one four one three what
four one three four one two three there it is read I hear a girl or an animal or something
singing to me pleading that I come outside my locked room and let the sweeping waves comfort me
water pump control restarting pumps what is uh where do I go what does that even do
what does that do what's that even do though what's that do
is the whale did I did I drain the pump did I drain the whale this was the same place twice
there is one two doors here this was under water is it going to be like a killer whale
if the whale is going to be on here there's nothing in this room did I try every door broken
it's broken did I miss like a key on the ground or anything on anything in here
at all I don't think there's anything in here why would I be able to come in here though
nothing in here either funny joke what the hell are you talking about what do you mean funny
joke I'm trying to go in all these doors there's nothing in any of them there's a key on the box
what like in this room okay let me be fucking real with you for a second that key is painted
on the top of the box it's all good all right where's the locked one there's a locked one here
you can't go in that locked one and there's nothing else in here so this is a key for a
different door back here you're legally mad and you're internally sad what about over here broken
come on who the hell are you whoa you're an enemy and you're now in the am I safe here
I think I'm safe here holy fucking hell I'm safe on the boxes wait for full health go
this way and then this way it's not so bad once once you know what you're doing
there's even more of this shit at least the numbers are going up
box steps what happened to the whale oh let me see a box I don't see a box
I think I just screwed myself nope right here let's go right how many more of these do I have to do
919 920 am I just stuck down here for the rest of the time that I play this game
I got out of the water I'm starting to lose track of time the battery on my phone became very low
so I delegated to save it in case I find an exit where is it a phone all that was an axe
holy shit it's the guy with the thing in his arm what you I thought it was him I thought that was
him by the long way I'm good we you stream confirmed I have to hide I think no what do
we you all right give me something at 950 I don't care if the last 50 rooms are absolute hell I
don't care give me 950 give it to me you five I don't want to go through that whole whale shit
again there has to be a checkpoint at 950 right that would make sense I could be on my a game
okay I haven't seen you in a while it's darker
I don't like this one whoa he's behind me
no don't play this music right now not appropriate time for the music
not another long hallway he's fast he's still chasing me
okay I'm fucking scared dude let's go almost there I'm almost done walking through a thousand rooms
the last 10 it's gonna give me something at the last 10 it's gonna do something
fucked up it's gonna throw a bunch of stuff at me here we go no nothing 999 see I told you I told
you why is this here no old victorian mansion that seems to build itself around its environment
specimens sometimes chooses a host to possess and uses them to attack the subject with various means
depending on the host's characteristics not much is known about the origin of the mansion but
signs occasionally show an earlier massacre a tragedy has taken place within the mansion
we're very effective but varies itself too often to be reliable method of extraction
so the house is alive this is not a time to use the computer this is not a time to use the pc
this is time to leave and go to a thousand the dev the dev what about what do you mean what
what about the dev what dev in chat dev actually in chat ignoring dev they're offering to add to you
you mean on the wall on the wall take a screenshot from that I'm gonna be on the wall that's fucking
hilarious or take uh what's better that or the me looking really angry into the camera or the
bagpipe face we need something high res the full screen really angry just like pissed off like
lunging into the camera I do a high res version okay I got like chapstick all over my mouth
okay here's a high res version now don't look at a camera I'm supposed to be playing a game
okay like what do you want how should I do this how about this oh you can use that one play it
like this I'm acting yeah this is acting angry I don't even know what the bagpipe face was
that's one or how about like how about this how about this one use any of those it doesn't matter
he's an egomaniac did you see that fucking face that use that one use that that's the one
no that's the one I took a frog mouth yeah that's the one take it how would it be I'm
playing I'm supposed to be getting scared I'm so glad that the game was paused all right last
five floors I'm ready imagine that's imagine scrolling through that wall it's like oh here's
like the youtubers here the streamers and then you get to that one you're gonna be like out of the
four of them that one's the worst make mine like a little bigger though make mine like too big
1996 well I'm gonna give it a date 1990 I did it you thought I was stuck here look at it's perfect
it's a beautiful world wow I am small I win Mr. Sky Fiddler the fake sky screen
server has been disabled no so was that one take all right here we go the final test
it's the english teacher oh it just opens let's press my face against it okay
what door is the real door that's the question none of them 731 this is room 731
hello yeah you're all right what happened take to the dead take to the dead I just spawned the
final boss of the game let's go motherfucker let's go let's go Ganondorf it's a scream stream
hey yeah uh hit his hand wait this is a silent hill boss oh oh the screaming the screaming
let's do it I'm good do it just twice do it stop I can't see those damn it all right come on
don't screw this up they travel the same speed come on don't mess it up that's not it
why am I fighting myself I don't know that you just spoiled the end of the game for me
you just spoiled the end of the whole game what
good job by the way making it this far so buckle up soldier
because now I finally think we have enough troops to invade
what I'm like a mushroom or something I'm gonna be like a cupcake
did you really think it was going to end seriously kind of you I did one I won
that was spooky's jumpscare mansion HD renovation they were here they were here
it was this music this is kind of this is good shit so yeah I went through all thousand rooms
this DLC is there screaming man we gotta give we gotta give it to screaming man for that
performance that was actually a full-on I'm just gonna hit record on audacity and scream into the
mic as loud as you can gotta give it up time to show Otto it streams on over stream it's not over
and then I thank you for playing it was it was jumpy it was very jumpy I'll give you that it
was very it was very jumpy it was good but hold on new game unlock the secrets of the strange
hospital wait why am I in 995 every day is Wednesday this is alternate timeline
yes it seems to be that way I don't know where we ended up I don't know if we'll find out there is
no floors there is no rooms it's just go still have the axe yeah there are no rooms this is
just a standalone no rooms let's go to the far one now well goodbye yeah this this game is this
game is a show of endurance I mean you want to get jumpscared and things popping out of walls
for a thousand rooms it's a show of endurance I'm putting this on my gamer license card
the hospital all right I just got a treatment for doing that water bubbler this is where you
save the game at the drinking fountain that's nice okay there's a bathroom let's go here
can't go here let's go here can't go here broken oh you need to go to the doctor
um immediately hopefully within the next 10 minutes because that's not all right
I'm so glad that that you added flushing toilets in the DLC think of a joke quick there isn't I
wouldn't there's blood in a urinal I mean it's an improv class let's do uh blood uh in a urinal
and you're at the hospital and um and there's a banana involved okay well gotta use the bat
no that's gonna go bad it's getting scary never say no to an improv session I don't know how
poorly I would do it an improv session I'd probably be pretty bad it would be bad I would
be doing stream references and all the people that were there watching the improv session would have
no idea what they were I would throw that you'd see at least like one or two like look at me
and the people watching would be like that's not funny wait hold on uh patient displayed
increased depression after informed of their terminal disease I prescribed an antidepressant
to regulate this but was later told that I had canceled the prescription no memory of
canceling the meds nor the quantity of evidence that my orders were tampered with
okay now it's a yes and a string I remember playing SCP with these stairs um let me check
the other rooms that stream would start out with a bunch of people watching and then after they
realized that this was not a good improv session half of the people would leave they would be like
wow an improv session on twitch the wits is so interesting wow that's so cool and look at me
look at me I got a banana here oh whoopsie and it would be like this I ain't a professional
I'm a professional clown hey no I can't move that way broken and it might be fun though
office key seems we're losing patients due to surgical complications much more often than
normal what have the doctors been doing half these procedures seem completely unnecessary
I know the doctors and surgeons are above me and probably know many things I don't but this is
getting strange oh by the way this is just coming out of like left field here but um I know I
mentioned it yesterday but I'm getting in front of the I'm going in front of the green screen again
in probably like at some point after Halloween at some point after Halloween like maybe like the
first week of November or something I'm gonna we're gonna do a green screen part two DLC for
free edition where I spend like another five to six hours doing all the things that anybody wants
me to do that's after Halloween after Halloween do six hours of look at me I'm not gonna do that
all right I gotta I got the office key that's that all right it's upstairs and I think it's
one of the ones I couldn't do before so there has not been a monster yet which is the one that
was locked stairs broken now remember wash your hands remember wash your hands everyone
of uh remember wash your hands remember wash your hands everyone of
clean your workspace I'm attending to the office work hard and have a nice day I don't know
I can't read that any of you guys in office which one of you guys is an office
none of you are in office so where's the office back here looks like an office
it seems the other me has been giving him large doses of hallucinations they have
worsened the depression and he is now constantly screaming and expressing terror at seemingly
random intervals I've tried using a diet out assist machine it to remove some of the drugs
but it seems futile office what's that looks like something goes here so there's a little
thing that's got to fit in that slot a little circle broken nothing in here I don't know
another note I was just informed that the procedure to extract the patient's liver
became fatal I don't know why why did we take his liver there are no donation requests and he was
showing signs of improvement the surgical staff told me I personally demanded the liver be removed
for an emergency transplant and the worst thing is I found it I found his liver his entire liver
just sitting on my desk maintenance key that's horrible maintenance diff deformity wing looks
fake it's electrically sealed I blacked out today while driving to work one minute I was driving
down the road and then in an instant I was standing outside my car staring down at a dead cat
I must have hit it with my car and felt sorry the image of the dead cat has constantly unnerved me
today how did I manage to hit it in such a way to make the body completely twisted around like that
that's not good all right I have the maintenance key now maintenance save it so we've got two
ways to go here this this is not open but where's maintenance because these are
hospital rooms the stairs going down was it another stairway was it downstairs because this
is locked I would feel like a maintenance room would be down here maintenance room the generator
powered down uh it won't turn back on oh this is good why did you do that to progress the story
to progress the game I definitely have to just go back upstairs so this is not so much a this is
like a whole new little mini game huh great where was that tendril wasn't there a tendril
there was like that big like uh amorphous thing you guys know what I'm talking about
remember the thing I was trying to hit with the axe it was down one of these hallways fake okay
okay just paint it on nope patient did not recover from the blood loss I feel like there is a monster
inside my head and it's pushing me away while it works on something I woke up in the patient's
room standing over him while an arterial catheter was in the patient letting him just bleed out into
the floor ah something gonna happen here something is happening what's what's going on why is it
happening other than what the numbers are there numbers I feel like I shouldn't move yet
that was cool maybe I have to do that eventually for some other reason
wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait where's this
happening it's screaming man encore just a couple of bags not a big deal you better believe that
guy's gonna start following me around
stairs fucking halls it is a hospital so I guess that makes sense just looking for a note
anything to explain anything back here I still need to find that thing that goes in the
wall these stairs they go up or down they go down this is the thing I was talking about it's down
here right here see that's what I was talking about nothing else I can do down here go back
up there walk through it I don't think I can all right so I need a medallion for the office
why did he not check the one right path um I I'm trying there's like 50 doors in here
stairs and there's the guy standing in front of the door with the bags what the hell to do with
that guy though he's not there anymore the morgue what else is down here just the morgue
and then the isolation room somebody has like a key on him or something you there it is yep now
I'm gonna be chased I just activated guy is now coming after you forever now I know I knew it I
knew it was gonna fucking happen I've told you I said it out loud I said it out loud I have to
turn and run the other way I think uh folks that's what has to happen I don't want anything to do
with that I have a misplaced camera oh shit sorry about that I didn't know all right office I need
to find that guy with the thing behind his computer that room I think it's this one no it's not which
one is which office room is that not this one not that one save the game oh fuck you're right
I'm gonna go save I'm gonna go save the game I didn't save the game I'm gonna save the game
it's left and then no it's over here
I'm
what year is it okay I saved it you guys just took fucking three years off my life
making me save the game I look scarier than the game does hey that's loud I'm gonna get lost down
here I already don't know where to go I don't know where I am but I do hear that
is that a picture of a baby shit it's
what about his play down here like this what was that
did I just did I just find where to go without looking yeah it's sunshine yeah I love it's in
the air you have transferred from your high school in the states and cannot wait to take your new
classes here as school or who be your dream will come to fruition within these red halls
your mother has packed you a lunch thanks mom day one hello there you must be the new transfer
student from America ah do you like it so far it's okay I guess there are a lot of cute girls here
I miss my home it's okay I guess well don't worry it's sure to get better
and let's by the way my name is Ume Ivtov Ume Ivtov
school bell Ume oh that's the bell I've got to go talk to you later oh oh hi Ume oh hi
have you started liking the school yet uh class was interesting this place is starting to grow
on me I wanted to see the rest it's starting to grow on me it's fine Ume glad to hear it
Ume to tell the truth I've had doubts when I first came here too Ume my dad lost he's not a caveman
yes Ume my dad lost job and we had to move and stay with my grandparents that's sad uh at least
you see your grandparents a lot glad to hear it that's a sad story is it all bad
and uh after a while I've learned how to enjoy myself here
we'll see tomorrow how's your second day have you things gotten better yet everything is disgusting
here I think it's gonna be fun all hearts I think it's gonna be fun everything is disgusting
everything I think it's gonna be fun well okay anyway today is a new day and full of new
experiences I can't wait the that just I almost just threw up because for some reason I thought
I wasn't controlling this the flies are can't fit anymore what the flies are can't fit anymore
the flies are I can't fit anymore yeah well class is at least interesting today I had no idea how
many perfect spirals existed in nature you're perfect flirt I thought it was boring I've known
all along I knew the whole time I knew all along I like that one hey do you live down this road too
nope uh do you live down this road well I live right down there at the second house on the left
it's an old house but it's the place I call home it's like my whole body is trying to peel apart
from the inside ah what the fuck is this hey what's the matter it's so slippery drip splash are you
feeling all right you're you doing all right no I like how your skin is pulling on your skull
what's this isn't a dream a fog what if this isn't a dream a fog or a lost memory
don't be like that what's wrong all your water is leaking those eyes shine like a house fire
you are in hell your blood is soaking through your eyes don't you know your blood is soaking
through your eyes is this what you wanted in order murderer you wanted to be you wanted to
talk didn't you do you really think this is real I'll always love you what's wrong I'll always love
you you are marked choke choke choke choke choke choke choke choke choke choke choke all right all
you wanted me to talk didn't you you're marked you're marked your blood is soaking through your
eyes what's wrong your blood your blood my blood you're in hell I'm yours you're in hell what's
wrong chug murderer I'm yours you wanted me to talk didn't you hell chug choke you're marked
I'm yours choke choke choke choke choke choke choke choke choke choke choke choke choke choke
choke wait I'm not I'm not choking right I am not choking I'm being called murderer
choke is this real how do I get the fuck out of here he's slowly disappearing hello why
what's wrong with you I got a text uh well they're not there anymore you have to play this until the
batteries die well if it's anything like the old game systems like game gear it'll probably be
about 28 minutes it's getting softer have you guys noticing that okay I've had enough of that
oh it was just it was just a glitch I had to restart the game all right these are hide boxes
um there's nothing else in this room this is back at the beginning it's going right hey hey hey hey
hey hey this is right right broken fuck then this is right left from the entrance
this is the left door I don't I can't keep track of that many doors left right right left right left
left now what right I don't know I have no idea this this is this is it I just circle what are you
doing what are you doing got isolation ward key run
go I don't know where I'm going we're good is that supposed to be hard
I was hoping it was gonna end just keep them coming you can't nobody no human can do that
for more than eight seconds all right isolation room key now that's a fun story called where
the is that a he said fuck I did isolation room that's this deformity wing that's the exit
I didn't say the game is about to be a monster why do you don't have this why why this is a pg stream
mom said have to leave well your your mother should know that we're playing a scary game
and sometimes you get terrified where is he there he is this bag doesn't seem very fast
and he doesn't seem hostile okay he is hostile but he's very slow he hurts a lot though
isolation where it was down right wasn't it down wasn't it down it was down wasn't it I passed it
no I didn't no it was down yeah it was down in the morgue so this is incorrect it's the one that
has the blood on it where was that because there's this one through here I think it's this yeah it's
this one right here down to the isolation room which is here we are okay open note it wasn't me
I swear it wasn't it may have been my body and my hands but I know it wasn't me
what is me it was just my body my hands and my intention but I didn't do it it wasn't me
that's not a really good defense will the defendant please rise and state what they just said
in private I stabbed him and I strangled him and I said in my I was like I'm God want to
strangle you and I stabbed you but I don't I don't I didn't do it though somebody else did
and who is this other person you your honor and then I fucking like right into the camera
I found out how to stop them you see they are in my head and can control me for a time
but if I keep using the radiology machine to dose my head with radiation then they go away for a
while this is fucking crazy how big is this area this place is huge another note no I went
backwards sorry I went backwards that door is locked remember it where the hell is this
yeah yeah well this is that's a second month an alien behind me it's an actual alien that's an
alien down here which way is he I don't know if he's all right okay he has pretty he's pretty slow
oh no okay this is where I have to go whoopsie it's a goddamn mace beater it's a mace beater
okay that was kind of funny I think I got it no I think I don't got it um there's a bug on my head
it's just that's okay that's not a rumor that's in the game I thought that was two
rumors back to back well here's the fun part they're lost too we both can't find each other
got it I'm so sorry my little angel I tried hating the man that took you from us but in the end the
only person I hate is myself you always like to scare people especially when they didn't
understand something I was confounded no one understood your costume but I guess people don't
read Poe anymore even with the new Price film that man clearly overreacted to your fireworks
we can only blame PTSD suffer so much what exit key I have to go through the maze again
through the maze again no I don't go where's that exit it's over here somewhere yeah
I am not in control anymore that's a bad ending that was bad ending what about the
the weird like organic material that was in the hallways
but could I not do anything with those things oh that's actually the good ending
oh you have to beat the game boy game wait ghost cow let's work build your own mansion that's going
to be fun you're going to be able to make your own little scary story mind him wait don't
numb you what thanks for the reminder uh all right I think um is there anything else what
does this one do it's just actually endless mode holy crap can you imagine doing this
past floor like 100 this is hard mode now yeah I'm sure there's somebody that has 10 000 rooms
they pause it go to work and come back and shit and it's just constantly doing it
no notes no nothing yeah where's auto I will get auto I will I just want to get to room 10
no like room 20 just to see the first enemy there's some stuff that's revamped in endless
mode that's pretty cool we'll see if we can see anything all right here comes somebody
oh we've seen this a thousand times no 24 hour stream thanks chat
there's five monsters that are exclusive to this mode read note read note they've already
read you've already heard that note auto is greater than a 24 hour speed run
why does it have to be a speed run how do you speed run 24 hour streams ah you can see what
I look like nobody wants that that's a donk that's a ding that's a donk ding donk ding ding ding
straight all right almost at floor 20 he legit looks like 44 years old right now
and full moon it's a goddamn full moon all right this is 420 let's see what happens
looks like more of the same but hold on 25 or how about okay how about this the next time I
go like the next time I get actually just scared it's over the tooth got me it was the tooth it
was the thing that's on the wall at every dentist office for children they're getting they're
getting why is it doing this it's just getting bloodier no I don't know the mechanic of this
thing he's gonna get you um something in the room I it's like I got stereophonic sound
just get to 50 I'm just gonna get to 50 once I get to 50 this straight it's over streams over
when it's 50 what was that it's just like something it's just breathing on me what's what's wrong with
me what's wrong with me what's wrong with my character where the fuck did that person go
what is am I hallucinating get out of here I'm getting hurt I think I'm choking my health is not
recovering why I'm too scared to incubate what's the matter with me I'm running I gotta I gotta
pass I got a passing grade I'll take a D I don't know what was hurting me though all right that
was fun D is passing yeah that's all right that's it's good oh uh yes it is time for auto so uh
join us tomorrow I was thinking about playing Darkwood after this but I was only going to do
that if this only took like a few hours to do so I think this is a good time to stop
it will be live tomorrow tomorrow we are going to do more Darkwood I want to try to beat the
game tomorrow if it's possible if I do not beat Darkwood tomorrow then I'm not gonna do five
days in a row but I have to finish it whatever I do when I come back uh after the weekend
if I don't beat it tomorrow then we'll just get it out of the way before I do anything else
so I'll see you tomorrow if you're uh this this is kind of the end of the stream I'm gonna go get
the dog well I you see I didn't end the stream yet so me saying this is the end of the stream is
not as funny for our stream tomorrow stream's still on so I'm gonna get auto I'll be right back
we're gonna say hello and we're gonna uh we're gonna call it there I'll be right back I'm just
gonna wind down for a little bit I have returned I have returned with auto I turn he's like he's
like smelling the microphone I tell uh I need to turn this back to here hello I know
well you can't see you will in a second hey I don't what are you doing hey can you not see
come over here I tell you come over this way come this way he's like I don't wanna look at
here you go do full cam here you go good boy say hi I don't he's very tired he's so tired
he doesn't not want to be in here good dog okay there you go no 24 hours stream tomorrow
in fact let's call this here put this down did it work did it actually work this time
does he smell oh yeah he's he's got that sleepy dog smell I got a lot of shit for that by the way
uh let me let me just put him uh out of the room give me one sec lazy dog he loves lying around
he's active too he does a lot of running he does the both the best of both worlds running around
going outside and then sleeping how old is auto auto is eight turning nine uh early 2020 but why
is the music not playing is the music not playing it's weird should be oh that's why
all right see you guys tomorrow come on work session top session let me try this one more time
session no why is this still pulling data wait is this real this may have happened
hold on a second now it's still pulling from like a week and a half ago
what is this this is uh all right yeah the sub train sub train clock how does this even do
always shows zero when inactive all right well get that shit off the screen but anyways thanks
everybody for watching we're gonna do the bits and everything if you're new to the channel
at the end of a stream we do a wind down where I go over all the bit messages that were certain
threshold because I do not read messages on stream I do not read subs or bit messages on stream
unless they are of a very large denomination and it did happen somebody gave 5 000 bits earlier
somebody gave 50 dollars earlier and I didn't see it it was a little too locked in to the horror
game but back we had a I missed this too uh Tyler McVicker I came in with a raid earlier so thank
you appreciate that if you had a good stream if anybody was stuck around from that channel thanks
a lot I lied about Darkwood what are you talking about playing it tomorrow I said if I still had
time today I was gonna move on to it but I'm just gonna play it tomorrow what what don't let Darkwood
become the new dragon's dogma I'm playing Darkwood tomorrow that is the stream tomorrow huh I'm going
to complete Darkwood hopefully tomorrow I don't believe you so you admit the dragon's dogma is
never happening no it's not it's not I'm sorry get your Pluto's out you ever lied about Darkwood
I said if I had I said if this I said if this game took me like three or four hours then I would play
Darkwood for a few hours but this took like almost six hours so that's we're just gonna put it on
I'm just going tomorrow everybody just relax Martin had a meme thanks for the 250 bits
appreciate it I'm a big fan of the private school bully who constantly brings up how much money his
dad is worth hair get out of here thank you green bog for the thousand bits thank you today's my
birthday I'm a 22 year old depressed and neat I'm learning Japanese because I like cute anime shows
which helps take away the pain so I might be some translator or live in Japan it feels romanticized
but it is my only chance at experiencing real life well let me tell you something very very very
very seriously if you're doing something that you like if you want to be a translator learn Japanese
and live in Japan go for it do it grab it by the horns and do it and go for it there are a lot
let me tell you something there are a lot of companies that really do look for translators
and look for people to kind of be the middle person for a offshore companies like for instance Kim
speaks fluent Vietnamese there are a lot of opportunities for her to just be the middle
woman for a Vietnamese client for different companies it is it's a skill it is a thing being
bilingual trilingual it that's that's a skill it takes a lot to do that to know like two three
or four languages fluently completely so what you're describing is potentially a real thing
go find it I really hope you do happy birthday by the way 22 years old you have plenty of time
you're still young very young so don't worry do what you can I wish you the best of luck take care
sticks renegade thanks for the 250 unfortunately pappaginos and d'angelo's are beginning to close
down that's a horrible thing to hear there's three left near me d'angelo's in this place and
pappaginos here and one more here I miss five dollar unlimited pizzas why is pappaginos closing
down they had the best chain pizza I've ever had pappaginos is disgusting goodbye omega lull
all right for one second I thought you were saying that like pappaginos is disgusting all
right goodbye I'm gonna get banned like bye omega lull like I gotta get this out before he bans me
for saying this give him two minutes that's unfortunate because I really do like pappaginos
pizza I would not choose pappaginos over some non-chain Italian restaurants in some local
pizza places way better but if I had to pick a chain pappaginos would probably be the best one
but yeah that's that's sad to hear thank you pigeon for the 250 this is a thought I had in
the shower whose customer service was or is worse cox or comcast cox cox because there seems to be
so many people that work for cox and none of them talk to each other at least with comcast so I had
comcast business and cox business and comcast business when they sent somebody out that person
at least was in communication with somebody else that they needed to be in communication with
to help fix a problem the cox support they just they're none of them talk to each other
so you have like the tech guy the mechanic you cox has like five character classes
the phone support phone maintenance supervisor it's it's there's so many people
sales you'll get a call from sales and all of them have no idea what the other person has just told
you I would get I would ask questions right for I'm going to give you a very specific example of
this so a technician a maintenance technician told me a straight-up maintenance guy in the truck
said hey if you get a static IP it actually is going to push your traffic to the front of the
line possibly and might help out because it's a static IP okay that's really cool let me call and
talk to somebody about getting a static IP hey if I get a static IP yeah I want it because it's
going to put my traffic potentially in the front of the line no it isn't who told you that um the
person in the truck the pride and then you would say a name I don't know what that is we don't know
what those people are I also asked if business lines and for cox have priority over residential
and I was told by three different fucking people yes no yes and then no by the guy in the truck
that's the problem with cox and half the time it's a salesperson that just wants you to buy
the product and will tell you literally literally anything you want to hear yeah business gets a
priority traffic and uh yeah it's uh they do different parts priority oh that's awesome
yeah I'll take it it sounds like a crock of bullshit no it is it's stupid it's hard to even
get a question answered about if you go further than reset router and
then if you go further than that that person does not know what to tell you
Comcast business was it still sucked don't get me wrong here this is not this is a contest
of who made the worst pie not who made the best pie this is a who made the best disgusting shit
pie that they shit in and then put it in the oven it's Comcast is better damn yeah it's a it's a
joke just make your own pie that's all right gross let's go I could sit here and talk about how
much I'm not a fan of cox and Comcast and I've said it a thousand times for even people that
might be new here I would pay triple if any of you guys work for Verizon or you know somebody
that works in Verizon management tell them I would pay quadruple what they are offering right now
for their fiber if I could just have it rich streamer no I'm do I don't think you understand
of the Fios internet from there was a package a while ago I'm not sure it might have been a
promotional thing but this shit was $39.99 for a symmetrical 35 35 connection I think that's
correct but but like I just can I have that one the ship was $40 a month 35 35 is all I need
I mean if I wanted to bump it up to like have a little bit more download whatever but still
that's really really pretty damn good certain streamers have had almost as many issues on
Verizon but has it was it fiber was it Verizon Fios to the home Verizon DSL and whatever internet
probably sucks asshole their fiber connection is from my understanding it's one of the best
connections in the country well fiber is dedicated line yeah well that's what I mean
Fios is amazing only thing I miss from DC my family has files it's amazing yeah
tell the pistachio ice cream story again
Fios and DC is amazing that's all I hear all I hear is yeah files is just incredible files
just like the best I actually um the the guy that's that's been producing a lot of the events and who
will continue to um for the streams and stuff said that he had files as well and he told me
that over I believe it was two years the connection went down once and it was because it was a
scheduled maintenance for like four hours they just were like upgrading the network
and it's the only time it ever went down in two years and I'm just sitting there going just
Verizon like just and then and then here's the sad part of this
Verizon recently has decided that they're pulling out of the west coast
Verizon is not going to expand anymore they're pulling out of the west coast I believe they
sold off all their stuff to a couple of other companies out here somebody correct me if I'm
wrong the frontier I think that's right they sold off all their stuff to frontier it's taken them
yep see that's just so sad but the good thing is I will be on an actual fiber connection
in a couple months depending no I'm staying in Vegas not going back to Boston he's going back
and I I have asked and it is true fiber it's not one of those fiber to the neighborhood and then
copper to the street and then copper to the house and then coaxial to your modem no no no no this
is the real deal what the hell is this suppose that united bank offers to lend you ten thousand
dollars for one year at a nominal annual rate of eight percent but you must make interest payments
at the end of each quarter and then pay off the ten thousand principal amount for the end of the
year what is the effective annual rate on the loan I don't care I don't why do somebody will
answer that for you apparently I don't know it's not gonna be me don't do it don't do the math
homework hey super marauding bear thanks to the 500 bits germa doesn't afraid of anything except
for cupcakes that jump in your screen hey charbork thanks for 300 bits you should play lost in
vivo actually was looking into that one there are another three or four horror games that I
want to play some of them are a little less polished than others and I was looking at that one
as well a shitty view bot is the one that gave 5 000 bits earlier a long time ago 50 dollars
from shitty view bot and they say because you know the correct flavors of ice cream and you
produce some good streams I guess always nice to see a fellow smooth strawberry lover it's always
good to see that there's other people out there that are really are into the whole smooth strawberry
good stuff you got to spit pistachios like watermelon seeds no pistachios are good
but I just don't like to eat them thank you freudian weapon for the 750 bits happy thursday
it's always hilarious watching you get scared playing games not at the cost of your health
though so take care of yourself random question what do you think was your worst ever halloween
costume I told the story before but I was going to be a power ranger I was going to be the red
ranger for and you know back when uh in middle school everybody gets up from their seat and
walks to every other classroom around in a circle with their costume on well that and
it was a huge deal it was that was the that was your time to shine I forgot to wear my costume
I forgot to pack it or I my memory cannot piece together the reason why I didn't have it but I
forgot it somehow it was in a bag on a counter and I didn't take it or I didn't have that there was
some reason why and I didn't have a costume and I felt really bad about it and one of my teachers
at the time don't know what her name was but god bless her soul because she pulled me out of the
class and said hey because you know I mean I'm upset I wanted to be the red ranger hey okay I
can do something for you here do you um hold on hold on and she she went she got construction paper
and she cut with a red construction paper like a lady bug vest and like lady bug ears and she said
here you go you can be a lady bug and I didn't have the heart to tell her this is the worst thing
I have ever seen and I want nothing more than to not ever wear this so I put it on and then I walked
around as the lady bug made out of construction paper well a few of my friends were all the other
power rangers and then obviously I even younger me appreciated it and I was like I don't thank
you yeah yeah thank you and then years later obviously I look back and that's that was like
so nice it's just trying to just trying to make that kid happy you know don't remember what their
name was though you should still say I'm the red ranger I'm gonna take care of something real quick
why can I not purge this comment did I lose I can't purge that comment somebody said uh
bcp just in low all lowercase just trying to fucking get me going uh then we had two four six
eight ten twelve twelve dollars from somebody whose name is a bunch of numbers one six eight
two four one six two six hundred five two six five six seven five five that's a very large
number username and they just did qrs or qr whale lord and then germa sour all right they didn't
even put the s thank you moss line for the 500 bits use this money to buy a silly straw to replace
your boring straw okay all right sure we also had I'll do it we also had uh superintendent
chalmers gave 250 bits they say here's a g an emote concept for germa seris planet for a planet
is this germa seris um I think planets are going to take a little bit of a vacation here I don't
think we're going to add any more planets not for a while there's a bunch of other things I think
we should be there instead but I do appreciate it thank you thank you for the emote concept
uh freddy dread gave 2 000 bits thank you freddy appreciate the 2000 20 bucks no message just
2000 also rogue of mv gave 3000 bits thank you rogue mv for that large money drop thank you
they say really been enjoying the dark wood streams over the last couple of days they've
been super comfy and listening to them has helped me get through a rough week at work
keep being awesome we continue tomorrow thank you so much for the 30 dollars 3000 bits
it means a lot if you're working tomorrow we'll be back in it really appreciate that though
jisu gave five community subs thank you jisu bala koala back-to-back 2500 bits 50 bits
no 5000 bits which totals 50 dollars from bala koala and their messages germa sour finger
pointing down germa sour finger pointing up but thank you for the 5000 bits bala koala appreciate
the sour tower is that what that what is it called sour tower did you guys coin that phrase that's
not bad that's not bad time to clean this up hey gnarly thanks to the 250 this game reminds me of
a less quotable clock tower 3 also auto some of that did remind that especially the guy with the
scythe i think that was probably supposed to be inspired by clock tower seems like it in that
mansion bala koala thanks for the 500 bits top dono dab all right there you go top dono it is
time to roll the credits all the subs thanks everybody thanks again for supporting the stream
as always there are a lot of you do you see your name up there if you subscribe during the stream
you will thank you though almost at the end we have a few more bits to do we have 250 bits
from snooze and copter thank you snooze and copter they say hey did you see my new badge
apparently i'm one of the first 25 people that subscribe to you i'm officially a germa veteran
oh yeah they added that right they added that 25 anyway i forgot if i wanted to say something
interesting or if i just wanted to brag oh yeah if this badge is customizable you think you're
going to do something with it like a golden germ or something also my wounds are almost completely
healed so i'm fine again can you believe you're almost 40 in six more years maybe but glad to
hear that after that horrible horrible accident i'm glad you're doing good remember you talking
about that before that's scary shit glad you're doing good but yeah the first 25 people that
ever subscribed to this channel have a special badge now i don't know i don't think they're
customizable at least not yet but yeah that's a long time if you were subbed if you subbed the
first 25 people and you're still here that's really awesome it's a founder one of the original 25
founders oh i see it there it is founder 42 month subscriber holy shit there it is
awesome thanks again and now it's weird knowing that i'm almost 40 it's true 42 months we also
had 500 bits from flug boy uh they say they say here's some bits germa hope you're doing well
thank you thank you thank you thank you they also say uh hey i just wanted to publicly call out
sticks renegade for committing a sin by playing megalovania on a child's piano hope you have a
good night on a what like one of those little sesame street pianos how do you even do that
there's not even enough keys there's like seven keys on those things but thank you flug boy for
the 500 bits i told you i would uh-oh getting called out hey cat attack thanks with 300 bits
thanks for showing auto i'm living away from home and miss my senior docs and terribly they're great
dogs they are the best dogs that's why i've had a dachshund back to back and i probably will do it
again they are my favorite dogs sorry to hear that you're living so far away from your baby
thank you for the three bucks appreciate it thank you flug boy for the 500 bits i work part-time
at an ice cream parlor and we have soft strawberry it's the best can i send you a quart of it please
say yes i don't accept anything in the mail i have a p.o box uh maybe i will have a p.o box
in like a decade and that means no send ice cream in the mail what you mean to say is can i send you
flavored milk but no i don't have any plans ever to do any type of send me stuff like p.o box or
anything p.o box is free content it's that i you guys realize that that p.o box wherever it is
it would get so full and i would not keep up with it and i would get calls from this post office
saying hey dickhead you have a p.o box here we are you have boxes here that are taking up the
whole room we don't have room for any of this stuff you need to come get this stuff honestly
just completely honest it's just something i just don't really want to keep up with
because it's hard enough to do anything else just my complete honest opinion on it but thank you
for the milk potentially thank you permanent marks for the 300 bits i'll buy you another sonic
corndog if you let my family go well that's i know this is fake because sonic corndogs are gross
and i would never order one so you're implying that i've eaten one already that's how you know
that's a lie how do i know because i've had sonic before i've had i've eaten all this i've eaten
bit sonic a few times and every time i just go i should have just went to wendy's i've been told
you don't order food from sonic you order the drinks from sonic and like wow you're doing it
wrong you're ordering food from sonic doing it wrong sonic has good burgers though i've never
had a sonic burger i've had a bunch of their other stuff that was not very good fuck you jeremy
so my own girlfriend is in here fuck you jeremy sonic is great oh my god sonic tater tots are good
every time all right and it's when i say every time i mean the two times that i've been to sonic
and ordered those items the cheddar tater tots were cold soggy and unappetizing they all came up
at once when you picked up one tater tot all 30 of them came up at the same time they were like
shitty nachos i used to work there and i wouldn't trust the drinks either to be honest
look if you put a blindfold on me and you put me in a car and you said we're gonna go get food
i'm not telling you where oh okay and you drove and you took the blindfold off and we were in a
sonic parking lot okay i sure i'll eat here but i'm not going to go out of my way to go to a sonic
ever again i would eat it and i'd be like all right i ate it that was all right that was okay
i guess it was like kind of blah it's good whatever it's food it's worth it i guess
auto is sleepy and sloppy and loves tater tots so what you're like speaking
anyways thank you uh thank you spooky spitfire for the 250 germ i literally got her at the end
of the stream when you were showing auto so it was worth it also i just got to the old hunter's dlc
and there is a boom hammer hunter with more health than the cleric beast and i don't know
how to feel about that it's tough that first area in the dlc those guys are no joke blood
boys dlc by the way is the best dlc of any video game that's ever been made it is the best there's
a there's one or two small missteps but you dlc is a misstep by a design choice so come on but
that's wrong well what it is is it's adding here listen you make a video game and you add dlc okay
fine but a lot of times that dlc ends up costing almost as much as the original game did for
70 to 80 percent less content you'll spend like 30 40 bucks sometimes on some of these dlcs
and it doesn't add as much as you play it already in the base game but you're paying for nearly
like 60 70 sometimes like 75 percent of the base game that's kind of i guess now dlc i think is
also another one of those things that it has to exist because if you make something that people
really like you want to do more of that thing for the people that really like it and it gives you
a reason to go back and play that it's not especially in a single player sense it gives
you a reason to go back and play it again and experience some new stuff the sims games cost
like 500 for the full experience and train simulator is like 2000 wasn't there a calculation one time
it's 7 000 no it's not it's not seven grand but i i enjoy dlc it's just sometimes you'll
there's no standard of how long or what needs to be added for dlc so that's why it gets weird
because oh buy the season pass all right i bought the season pass you get everything for 40 dollars
cool but what what if you don't do like a season pass what if you just buy i want this just this
single thing that you came out with now oh well that's 25 dollars okay well it's an hour long
when are we gonna get the germa dlc it's coming out i'm not anti dlc i'm just like what do i get
for this and sometimes season passes are so vague you really don't even know what the hell you're
buying you're buying a thing that you don't even know what it exists yet it's not even like
pre-ordering pre-ordering game when you pre-order a game you know what the game is that you're going
to buy at least when you buy a season pass it's just hey something gonna show up here you don't
even know what it is and you know here's another part of this if you buy season pass for a game
and that content comes out like six seven eight months later almost probably a year later what
if you don't even play the game anymore what if you don't even know you don't even pay attention
anymore yeah i want that season pass like a year and eight months goes by and i'll say you like
you forgot that the game even came out that happens that happens that happens pretty often
i'm sure well maybe maybe that happened to me with borderlands yeah i mean a good look good
content is good content i will gladly pay like i have many times for dlc but by its very nature
it's it can be sort of predatory in a way it's like promising something that doesn't exist yet
especially if you sell a season pass it's kind of it's season passes is what i have the issue with
not like actual dlc packages that come out just it's in header it's inherently predatory it's
just that some dlc is actually good yeah and there are a lot of companies that do put a lot
of time into it they really do but where there is a yin there is a yang as they say we are no we're
not i thought we were done we're not done all dlc should be free see i disagree with that because
how do you pay the people that made it you know people that made the dlc they you have i mean
like the concept artists the the people that made the dungeons the people that do the character
design the 3d modelers the programmers like the these the people aren't working for free
imagine paying for games don't they get paid by a contractual basis i i am not i'm not going to speak
on how this works in the games industry because i have no idea and i don't want to be one of those
people that gives you spitballs a bunch of shit that's just not true so i don't know but thank
you for the 300 bits from hannah has bits hannah has a bits say i don't know if i'm i don't know
if i'm cheering right this is the first time i've done it i got told you don't read your sub messages
my sub message was talking about how i've been having a really really hard time and i was just
wanting to hear you say it would be okay in a reassuring voice and following you for years
and i'm not trying to be weird but i really wanted to get that out there before tonight ends
well i'll give you two parts to this if you are having a really really hard time
and me simply saying that it's going to be okay is going to be enough for you i really just want
to make sure you understand that that might not be correct and you should try to figure out what's
going on and also maybe seek some actual potential professional help because it's it's very easy for
me to do that you know what i mean but i want to make sure that you're okay that you are okay
and me simply saying those words is not necessarily a magic wand to do so and no it's not you're not
trying to be weird it's not it's not weird just make sure you're doing the necessary things
to make yourself feel better and get better you've been following the channel for a long time so
obviously i don't want people that are following this channel and that say some like stuff like
this sometimes i don't want you to feel terrible i don't want you to feel bad i want you to feel
like everything's going to be okay but just be careful putting essentially that power over here
because i might not actually have that kind of power and me telling you that might it's a you
know what i'm saying it's a weird scenario where i might not have that power but please please please
follow up with this if you really are having a problem in a hard time talk to the people that
can really help with that i wish you the best much love to you take care of yourself i'm sorry that
you're not having a great time but i will also say this was a two-parter where i said this part
here oh well i haven't said it but i'm about to regardless of that if it is if it does make you
happy and staying here and hanging out here makes you feel better that's good and i'm really happy
to hear that but that should only be a piece a small piece of that puzzle thank you so much
for your 300 bits your three dollars i wish you the best and please take care of yourself take
care moving on from that we have 500 bits from super or super tentorium super tentorium thanks
for the five dollars here this is my quadra request for you to play kerbal space program i
loaded up kerbal space program and could not figure out anything in the first 30 seconds
and realized that this was i was never going to learn and i exited the game in fact i can tell
you i mean that i'm embellishing right so let's see how much time i have in kerbal space program
kerbal space program let's go to games on steam l m n o p k there it is okay so i have 20 minutes
in kerbal space program and probably seven or eight of those minutes we're doing menu stuff
i probably only have about 12 to 13 minutes actually trying to make anything
that's embarrassing i i'm just told i'm being open with you you stopped before qrs yeah so i'm
not going to play kerbal space program there's plenty of people that do great hilarious fun
content with that game you've probably seen it a bunch before you would be very you'd be so
irritated watching that stream i wouldn't be able to do it i tried i put 10 minutes i put 10 i gave
it 12 minutes so you know i gave i gave it a shot thank you also uh death gamer thanks to the 250
hey germa i was wondering what happened to the modern warfare 3 grandpa vids do you still have
them or are they gone forever that is a machinima problem machinima i made those videos for machinima
so i was essentially contracted out by machinima to have them put them on machinima respawn
and then they just privated all of them for seemingly no reason and then machinima has now
been completely liquidated as a company they don't exist anymore and those videos are gone yeah so
i do not have access to those videos they are potentially gone forever in fact i think they
are gone forever which is too bad because that's that's really where i got my actual start kind of
gaining in viewership and having a channel that was more you know comedy oriented though that
first like grandpa video did so much like that i did like 12 episodes that did so much for my
channel that is kind of a shame that they're just gone forever but i didn't i'm not my youtube
channels are not under contract with machinima anymore so i have no connection to them at all
yes i there are still a few on my channel i still have like uh maybe three i think there's two or
three that i uploaded even though you really weren't supposed to i kind of got a pass on a
couple of them i think because they were i don't know why but i know you weren't really supposed
to do that but i do not have access to them currently no that is two or three computers ago
and those hard drives i've brought along with me but then they weren't worth putting in the new
computers i have two computers from that computer i didn't keep them anymore and they were hard disk
drives i went to full solid state those hard drives kind of ran out of gas and i didn't really want
to use them anymore so they're just kind of gone but thank you door cube for the 250 bits i was
thinking today about how this community is the first one i've ever actively participated in
and how i have made some friends for life here and i'm still looking forward to the day i meet an
in real life germamite anyways will we get some bf bugleberry content for halloween
i don't know i don't know ask me again ask me again in a week right now right now i have my
i'm biting my bottom lip and i'm raising my eyebrows like we'll see but yeah i'm glad people
can make friends here discord's open to the public if you feel like just chilling playing games with
people hanging out talking about whatever just keep it civil that's all i ask spooky spitfire
that's a little bit of a spooky spitfire thanks to the 250 germ forgot to mention that there is
a new souls game being made oh it's elden ring is what you're talking about uh it's potentially
open world with more build diversity and all that fun stuff even more than dark souls oh yeah i'll
be playing that day one george r. martin is involved in that project who leaves is probably
making the game world he's writing the characters probably or creating the world i don't know what
his involvement is but that's gonna be day one like just like sakura was and then finally we
had slumpy stumps thanks for the 500 bits thank you thanks for all the laughs no other online
personality has given me so much free laughs entertainment is you been watching and laughing
since high school and hope to continue doing for years to come love you man thank you thank you
for the five dollars 500 bits i hope you still feel that way years from now i hope you still feel
that way tomorrow i'm glad you still do thank you and finally 420 squid right now just came in with
a thousand bits ten dollars for 420 squid here's a handful of bits for a hole in one streamer
thank you also the janitor was mocking my reactions throughout the entire stream maybe
consider legal action the janitor he cleans this he's just he every people keep throwing the tomato
and throwing popcorn and shit can you guys just keep the food on your laps please i'll see you
guys tomorrow we're gonna do dark wood see if we can complete it if we don't complete it in like that
five to seven hour ish time frame then once i get back from taking a few days off
for the weekend i will be back and we'll do it there we'll finish it i promise i'm not
going to get to the 95 completion of a game and not do it the same like hollow knight i beat like
six bosses in hollow knight and didn't play it anymore this would be like as if i beat
30 bosses in hollow knight and didn't play it anymore not the same anywho good night everybody
we'll see you tomorrow take care thanks for joining thanks joining us dark wood
put it on the calendar for tomorrow good night guys