Alright, I'm back. What's up? I got the music working again, aren't you happy?
Fucking better be. Alright, Street Fighter 6, let's go.
So I have to tell you, I need to make this very clear. I am not a fighting game player at all.
You've seen me play stuff like multiverses. But traditional fighting games, I don't play them.
I'm not really super into them. But Street Fighter 6 caught my eye for a few different reasons.
One of which is the single player mode. That is the reason why I bought this game,
is because of that. Does the title still make sense for this game? Don't adjust your TV set.
Yes, I'm actually playing. I guess that makes sense too, because why would I be playing this?
Alright, so I need to make a character and I apologize that it's probably going to take about
at least 30 minutes. I got no timer on this. The character creator is kind of ridiculous
from what I've seen. So let's go for it. You should see it right now. You should see it right
now. There we go. Alright, so what I want to do, I want to do this. This is World Tour.
Create an avatar and embark on a journey to discover the meaning of strength. Take the
plunge and experience the world of Street Fighter like never before. Let's go. You ready? Go.
I think I'll make Shikidian off of it. Make Miku? Well, let's get in there first.
I'll turn it up.
Honestly, Capcom doesn't miss lately. Capcom doesn't miss. I don't know what happened.
What happened? Capcom doesn't miss anymore. That's kind of surprising. I know, yeah,
I said fuck Capcom that time, but it didn't mean it. I was in a fit of rage. I did say that.
A couple years ago. Well, now it's love. Bless Capcom. Cool. You can remove screen shake in
this game. Already did it. Kids, take a breather. This is Buckler Security Services. I'm Luke,
the coach around you. New character, new character. Alright, here we go. What do I make?
A new you. Creating your avatar. Bring avatar for World Tour mode. It will also be used in the
Battle Hub. OK, I think I have to do this. The length of your limbs and size of your body matter
during battle. Having long limbs makes it easier. So I have to just have wicked long arms?
Make Golem? We have to live with this character for as long as I play this game.
We have to live with this. OK, presets. So where do we start? OK, wait, there's more.
Alright, I think I'm starting here. Oh, come on, don't. I think I have to start here. OK,
body preset. Moving the point of the triangle after making the settings for interview. OK,
so just telling me that it. OK, how big do I want to make this guy? I kind of like that.
That's a good start. We can change it after. Blend face. No, no, no. Light and proportions.
Well, that just doesn't look right. How tall is this? Sitting height where I could just
changing your height to the minimum or maximum. OK, so there's a certain value where it becomes
kind of screwed up. Oh no. OK, I'm going to hate this after 10 minutes. Let's have a long ass
torso. All right, I think it's fine. Upper body. No, I could do neck length. So he said crash
bandicoot. OK, we're making crash bandicoot. We're making crash bandicoot. That is exactly
who this is going to be. Wow, that's what a great fucking comment. This needs to be up way higher.
We've got to cover the head because we need to put crash bandicoot's face on his chest.
Oh, my God, you crash his voice. OK, um. Whoa, it's like that, right?
He's kind of like he looks like a flounder. No, no, no. I said big. Make the arms big.
How big a crash bandicoot's hands. They're actually kind of long. They go down this far.
These arms are way too thick, though. That's better. Shoulders are too thick. This is just a
Titan from Attack on Titan. Yeah, that's what everybody is making. OK, everybody is making an
Attack on Titan Titan. That's what every person you've seen play this game does. There are no
normal people made with this. No one. Not a single person is making normal people. Abdomen bulge.
OK, hold on. Sometimes when you stare at your face long enough, wonder if that beauty mark's
always been there. Forehead protrusion. Eyebrow spacing. OK, that looks fine. Brow depth. I like
the higher brows. Surprised or angry? Angry for sure. 100%. Yeah, this is all right so far. Along
to the jobby. That's a lot of neck. That's mostly neck. Oh my goodness. With a huge underbite. All
right. Jaw shape. This kind of has to fill into the neck a little bit. Maybe not. No, pull it back.
That's fine. OK, cool. Hair. I actually kind of like this one. OK, it might be this one too.
Oh my goodness. All right. Is it just a middle part? That's good too, though. Oh, that's really
good. That's good too. OK, wait, I need hair color. Am I fucking this up? Is it red? Does it have
wicked shiny hair? Wait, how many colors can I do? Why is it red? Why is it just getting redder?
Am I mixing the colors together? Hair color one. OK, there we go. All right, that's fine.
Oh, color mixing. There it is. All right, that's fine with me. Eye shape. All right, we have to put
the eyes down really low. OK, that looks fine. Eye size. Wait, what did I just do? No, no. How
do I? Oh, right here. OK, I like the big eyes. Intensity. Whoa. OK, that's cool. Do we just give
them undertaker eyes? OK, yep. I like it. When somebody with blue eyes looks at you.
You make them bright. Oh, no, too bright. OK, lashes. Just no eyelashes. I'm thinking no
eyelashes at all. No eyebrows either. And no eyebrows and no eyelashes. OK, here we go. This
is where we start to really make the face the face. I don't like this at all, but I guess we're
living with it. Now I want to go and zoom into his face. This dude's hitboxes are going to be so
fucked. Oh, that's right. Oh, well, the nostrils are all the way down here. OK. OK, I think I'm
all right with this. All right. Mouth position. Probably all the way down. Right. I want the I
want the lower. Oh, that's all right. Mouth corners. No, happy for sure. That's terrifying.
OK, that's fine. I think that looks good. All right. Facial hair. That's all right. My goodness.
Wow. That's long. Wow. That one's great, too. Holy shit. OK, I Gandalf. We need new hair then.
If this is Gandalf or this is, you know, we need new hair and hair is Gandalf have.
I guess it's kind of like this. Why is it so like, oh, it's the there we go. OK, he's way too
fucked up. You know what I mean? A lower body. We can fix everything. All right. Hold on. Huge
waist. No, no, no, no. Huge pelvis. Oh, no. It looks like a refrigerator. All right. I'll keep it.
I'll keep it. I'll keep it. We need to make them as square as possible. Oh, yeah. 100 percent.
No, everything has to be the same. Oh, my God. What? Why? Oh, this is too. This is too much. OK.
What else we got? Muscle definition. Wait, metallic, metallic. I can just be shining.
That's going to be so annoying to look at. No, I'm sorry. I mean, that's pretty damn cool,
though. I mean, that's pretty cool. Maybe not so metallic. That looks good. Oh, hair quality one
or two. We're going to have some back hair. OK, I think. Oh, you are kind of. All right. Wait a
minute. Sitting height. This has to be, I think, as long as possible. OK, he's kind of a piece of
toast. He's like a piece of bread. OK, I'm happy with this so far. Body paint.
Oh, I can get. I don't need that. What do I have here?
OK. All right. Hold on. It's it's got to be. OK, how about this one? Is this one cool? I don't know.
Nice one piece character that you made through. Oops. What do I do? Oh, shit. I screwed it up.
Um, what am I? What is this? I don't know what setting. Oh, it's my lips. OK, this is a mold.
Then how do I get? I want to take that off. Shit. How do I get this off? There we go. OK.
OK. Body hair color. Yeah, we did this already. All right. Voice. Let me hear those vocal. See
what you've got. Put on a good show. Let's see what you've got. Let's see how you do.
See what you've got. Think you can take me. Here I go. This one's good. You got the skills.
Let's put on a good show. Let's see what you've got. Let's see what you've got.
Oh, that's a good one. That was somebody getting trapped in a combo.
Let's see what you've got. I like that one. Play the game. Relax. I am not to be trifled with.
This is half the game right here. I like it. OK, current recipe. Download recipe. No, I just
know I'm ready. I think we're good. I think we're good. Forget your name either.
Flatline Greg. It's going to be his name. Give me your Sunday best. OK.
OK, sounds good to me. What do I have to do? Take a look. Let's go. Oh, goodness.
Honestly, the people that make normal characters, you have a lot of mental fortitude.
The mental fortitude it takes to not make your characters nose four or five inches off of their
face is incredible. I can't believe that you're able to do that. All right. How do we play Street
Fighter? OK. All right. Yep. There are three movement speeds. It just doesn't fit at all in
this entire universe. I hate this character already. His head is too small. I'm going to
know. I'm not going to. I'm going to hate it. OK. Press A, B, X, Y while holding right bumper
allowing you to control the camera even while using a controller that has no right stick.
All right. Well, that's fine. Great. Operate the camera. Use right stick. Easy. It's for arcade
stick. OK. You look like a door. Show me how you are with your fists. All right. There are two
control schemes for battles in World Tour mode. Modern and classic. Cool. Modern is a four button
layout that allows players to enjoy a more freeform approach to combat. Modern is the only control
type available in World Tour during Chapter one. OK. So it's not. I looked into this a little bit.
Yeah. So it's light attack, medium attack, heavy attack, special move. I get it. Might as well.
Yep. Holding back is blocking, right? All right. I punched. I did it. Jump three times. I know how
to do that. Up. Nice. You should just do modern. I probably will just do modern. Crouch. Don't. The
beard physics are way too distracting. Yeah, but we have to live with it. It's fine. OK.
Light, medium, heavy. Yep. Tackle jumping multiple times. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Got it. OK.
Three special attacks. So these are special moves like a duken, but you don't have to do like
down, left, down, right, left, right, left, right, left, right, square, left, right, square. Right.
You actually just press one button. I actually like that a lot. So I'm sorry if I'm a casual
apologize in advance. OK. So it's just in a direction and that it's like somebody
said it's like Smash Brothers, huh? OK, cool. Oh, that's the point of modern. Go throw Luke
three times left trigger if you're using modern control scheme. Oh, modern's fine. Yeah, I'm not
worried about it. I'm not really a fighting game player, but that means I can have fun, too. Cool.
Can you play with a modern style online? That's how the basics are. Simple and do you have to
go against other modern players? Even the biggest rockets need a stable launching pad for takeoff
or else they're just going to crash and burn. You get me? Coach, how is any of that? No. Interesting.
You do less damage with it. Modern and classic can play each other. They're intended to be balanced
to both are viable. That's cool. All right. We might have to take the beard off. It's actually
is way too distracting. Yep. Yep. Yep. Yep. Yep. Yep. Yep. Decrease every year. Yeah. Yeah.
Declare victory. Decrease. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Let's do it. I can't believe you got hit in the tutorial.
Modern does less damage. Really going to be the type to jump before you think. Coach, that was
the kind of situation I want to learn to deal with. You're not here to punch bags either, right?
This is fun. He signed up with the same regimen you are. When does he play golem? I already did.
I already gave it a rating too. It was a 5.3. Golem is a 5.3. No, actually it's like a 4.8.
That's generous. That's way too high.
You can cross that bridge when you get to it. You two are still my plucky little trainees.
Give it a one. Listen to what your coach says and put your hearts into your training. Game was 60
bucks. Oh, it was. Oh my God. I completely didn't take. I did not even take that into
consideration. I just death stared. You wanted something more. That was a you're dead at some
point in this story. I'm going to kill you. New content. Billionaire streamer does not care
about the price. No, I told you I did. That's why I was like, wait, that's true.
I cannot wait to play this. Those of you that don't know why I'm excited about a street fighter
game when it's like, when does he ever cared about this? It's this game mode and just wait,
that ass is huge. It was distracting. Holy shit. Okay. What was I? I don't remember what I was
saying. It's open world and you can just kind of fight anybody. It seems really cool. Your
character fits right in. I don't know about that. Oh God. Those feet looked like cactuses.
They look like cactus. What was going on there? Actual hands-on experience on the streets.
Beating up the bad guys around here should do the trick. Sorry. Did the joke fly over your head?
At any rate, I was told this would point us toward our next steps. Oh, hang on a minute. I'm getting
a message from coach. There's an app on your device. Check it out. You get anything? You view
all sorts of information by pressing. Cool. Okay. You can view messages sent to your device by
selecting messages. Luke, let's get you started with some missions. Sending you training exercises
to the missions app. Check it out and follow any instructions that pop up there. Missions. New kid
on the block. Welcome to the streets where you go and what you do is entirely up to you. But if you
like to get a feel for how things are and usually done somewhere, there's no quick way than asking
the locals. Look for a person named Alice. She'll show you the ropes. Let's go. Basically, it's a
to-do list. The first thing we need to do is talk to that person right over there. That should be
easy. Let's get going. Your mission destination is denoted by a red mark. Try making your way to the
destination using the mark as your guide. Yep. This person's level nine. What level am I?
What do you think of my performance? Exciting, right? When you're performing, what matters most
is technique, tempo, and a mindset that practically commands onlookers to behold.
It's Lucifer. With that in mind, I'm going to teach you a pose to harness that very same mental
fortitude. Emote acquisition item. Check me out. Okay. Now that's a mindset you can set your watch
to. It all hinges on how you're feeling, friend. All right, let's do this. Alice. And you two must be
a couple of rookies who just want to get stronger. I take it. Right on the money. How did you know
it was us? Seriously, come on. It's practically written on your faces. That would have been four
dollars in gold. He asked me to assist with your training for a bit. Your little mission to come
talk to me was a smashing success. Next up, how about we have ourselves a fight? Okay. Don't hold
anything back now. I'm a lot stronger than you two. Okay. Plan 10 hits. When playing using the modern
control scheme, assisted combos can be before it by keeping right trigger pressed while attacking.
And then attack with right trigger X or right trigger A. And you can follow up with a combo
by simply repeating the button press. Okay. Okay. Okay. Oh, I see. So you hold right trigger.
It's Luigi mode. That's fine. You're getting one of the first to get to level 100 in Diablo 4.
I played a little bit of Diablo 4. I have a few thoughts on it. Can't give you my total opinion
of the game so far, but what I can tell you is this. So I find it funny. And I don't know why.
A lot of games have been doing this, I think, nowadays. But maybe minor spoilers for Diablo
4. If you don't want to hear it, just mute and come back in 30 seconds. But they'll tell you
something. Okay. Ready? Here comes spoilers for it. Three, two, one. Oh, you just missed her.
Oh, Lilith was just passed through this town and she would fucked a bunch of stuff up.
Oh, you missed her. And you go to the next town. Oh, you just missed it. She was here and she ate
somebody and then she killed three people. At the next town, I feel like she might be going there
and you walk to that town. Oh, you just missed Lilith. She was here. She stole one of our swines.
She stole one of our pigs. And then it's like we've been, I don't know, we're kind of just
walking and chasing Lilith. And at some point, there's even a sequence where, and spoilers,
we're still talking spoilers. You end up going to this place and it's like, oh, I know where she
went. She went this way. Oh, we have to chase her. She went to the next spot. Oh, she's passed
through here. You end up coming back to that town and it's leveled like shit. She actually fucking
came back. Why is he spoiling? I just told you we're talking Diablo four spoilers. That's the
entire Diablo two storyline. I think the reason why I don't mind it in the Diablo two storyline
is because you only get to hear that like three times total, not every new town you go to.
Do you know what I mean? There are a lot of towns in Diablo four and it's almost like, oh,
yeah, this is town number 15. Where'd she go? Find her. Follow the trail. Quick adventurer,
defend me while I open this door. I can read the runes. Oh, quick adventurer. Here they come.
I feel like that's happened quite a few times. But, but, but it's pretty fun. Yeah, it's fun.
But it's fun. I'm having fun with it. Street fighter. I thought you said street fighter four.
Whatever fucking game this is. Street fighter six. Somebody I I'm fucked up. I can't read what you
said. I have one other complaint about Diablo four and I'm going to give it to you right now.
All right, here we go. Yeah, call me stupid. Call me. Well, he needs like something explained to
him. There's a lot of if they're fours in Diablo four. There's a lot of like if this than that,
then this like lucky hit chance. If if somebody standing in your poison and then you do chilled
to them, then if there's lucky hit percentage going off, then 10% critical strike chance
will go up. It's like I like too many. What the fuck even does over what does overpower even do?
What does it even do? Well, you see, it's 3% chance to have your health and your fortification
combined data be used as a damage move. It's kind of confusing. Your brain is cooked eggs.
I'm sorry, but I don't want to look. I just want to hurt. I want to punch things.
You need modern Diablo controls. I gave you my Diablo take. So you're saying stir was right.
I don't actually don't know stirs Diablo for take. I wonder what it is now. Nice microwave egghead.
OK, when you when you get a legendary that drops and you look at it and you you need to read.
I didn't even know what lucky hit did until I was like fucking level 25. I wonder what and even
still I read up on it. I'm like, what the fuck is that? What does that even mean? What's happening?
All right, fight and beat two people. Here we go. He does need modern controls.
Oh, here he goes. Here he goes. He's here. He goes. Let's fight Hugo.
Hugo, you can use items during battle. OK, I don't need items to fight a level one.
I love this guy was just probably on his way to work. Stop jumping. Yeah.
That would be so weird. Try fight the level nine.
All right. Is the level nine going to kick the shit out of me? I'm going for it.
I'm barely hurting this guy, but every straight fighter thing I've ever seen is just keep the
person over here. Just keep them over on this corner. It's not fighting back.
Why is he not fighting? He's not fighting. Why is he not attacking me? Is this a stream sniper? No,
it. Oh, no, it's not a stream sniper. Don't you have to like juggle people to in these games?
All right. Well, there it is. Are there damage numbers?
Sturer said the campaign is the worst he's ever played in any a RPG, but the gameplay loop is
pretty fun if shallow. Really? Oh, you level up, right? Right, right, right, right. OK,
you gain skill points upon leveling up if you access the status app in your device and choose
skills. Oh, he said stirs stir of liked anthem. So, oh, what do I do? Where's my where's my phone
settings? Emotes and shortcuts, standard emotes. Oh, I got check me out. OK, cool.
Where did I level up? Customize your device can be personalized by changing your wallpaper.
Let's do blue. Looks good. Items status. Maybe check your styles and equipment gear.
I don't think I have any gear. Luke's style is the only one I have. OK, I don't.
Ah, this is where you change moves. All right. Well, I only have two.
Here we go. Skills. You level up. Cool. Carries over. You would like to redo how you've unlocked.
OK. All right. So we got increases the row strength. Yep. I'm just going to be a throw Andy.
I'm going to be unfucking bearable. Punch. Not like wasting points, am I? Cool. All right. Who
holds their phone like that? I did what you asked. Gotten a feel for fighting yet? Nothing beats
trying it for yourself. When you're out and about, not everyone you run into will go easy on you.
So if you're going to start a fight with somebody, pick your opponent wisely. Anyway,
I'll catch you two again sometime. OK, sometimes you got to talk to folks on the street and ask
them for a fight. Think of it like saying hi on the streets. Only lots more punching.
And if all that punching works up an appetite, go ahead and get yourself a bite.
There's a food truck nearby. You'd never guess from the look of it, but they do a killer pizza.
Pizza. Eating food is part of our training, too. Is coach just messing with us?
Let's do what he says. OK. Let's go, motherfucker. I want a free pizza.
Pepino. Watch out. That's funny. Yeah, he's not fighting either.
Look like the Beast Titan. He does look like the Beast Titan. Nice. All right. I just beat the shit
out of the pizza restaurant guy. Is that a bad thing? There's an X now. Is that bad?
All right, now we're just going to eat. OK, there are two types of food used immediately
and food used during battle. Food lineup changes from time to time. So check your map
screen to see what's on the menu. What the hell am I looking at? It's always pizza.
Pizza covered in asparagus and. Oh, no, no, no, no asparagus on pizza.
No, we get pepperoni. I ate it. This is not the kind of food that athletes like this eat
every day. It says clearly like cheating or something. How do you compete with cheese?
This hot and gooey as they do. What I tell you, bomb pizza, huh?
All pizza is good pizza, but the pepperoni gets my vote any day.
Ever run low on stamina, eating something will get you right back on your feet.
Some food will have you hitting harder, moving faster, the works. Food can power you up in all
kinds of ways. So don't be shy about expanding your palate. Now that you're done filling up,
why don't you pay a visit to that nearby alley? I could be an actor. I could be an actor. I could
be an actor. OK, go to that alley. OK, by the way, that pizza was fucking gross. One move, Andy.
Whoa, what's going on? Why is he? I'm disintegrating him. He's being fucking
pulled out of the universe. What's wrong with them? Level up. What are you looking at? Oh,
shit. Who's next? You're beating up a granny. What the hell are you doing? Piece of shit.
I'm smurfing. What does it look like? Oh, I can put points in. I have six points.
I'll do Max Vitality. Oh, it's all right. What was the other one? Defense. It's kind of the same
thing, just different ways, right? This is more complicated than Diablo for his skill tree.
Oh, oh, I'm in a fucking weird mood today. I'm sorry. I haven't streamed in like two weeks.
I need to wait to give my full opinion on D4. Look, I'm one of those people and I'm sorry about
this. I apologize. No, this is how I feel. Fuck it. Diablo 2 came out and nothing can ever compare
and look, oh, you're old and oh, yeah, everything can't be as good. Rose colored glasses. Shut the
fuck up. Right. I get it. But honestly, I don't think they can even come close ever again. I
don't think anybody could come close ever again. Nobody could ever come close ever again. It's
just unfortunate. It's the way it is. I'm playing Diablo 4 right now and having fun.
I'm like I'm having fun, too. I didn't say I didn't like it. I didn't say it wasn't good.
That's backtracking. No, I just told you that I need to like I need to play it more to get like
a real opinion. It's like a fucking 700 hour campaign or however long it is. That map is huge.
Wait, when getting into battles in the city, you find yourself against multiple opponents at once.
Okay, well, it's like 2v2. All right, this is interesting. Well, that guy was these guys were
weak. A giant Capcom symbol. Hello, you two. We meet again. Let me introduce you to my brothers,
Tracy and Ryan. Luke asked us to give you a hand with your training. You know, get the whole family
on board kind of deal. Hold on. Someone's someone's calling me out here. I got to read it. You don't
like Diablo 2 because it's better than the new games. You like it because you did it when you
were a teenager after school instead of getting yelled at for doing it wrong by like 10,000 people.
You can never go back to the mind you had the first time you played it.
That's like, that's a good point. You know what I mean? That's true. The skill points that needs
to I don't know, there should be more of them. I don't like the five skill points that add like
2% damage. I just gave me more of that. I can't give you an opinion until I beat it. I need to
give you a real opinion. Diablo 2 is probably number one ever of all time ever for me. I love
that franchise. I love it. Give me some time to give you a real opinion on it. Because I don't
know it could be much more in depth than I'm giving it credit for. He wants 10 skill points
with 1% damage. It's not what I said. We're imitating the thugs around here. They hide
their faces just like this. They're attacking folks left and right. So be careful out there.
They're random battles. That's funny. Okay, I can't give you an opinion gives an opinion. Well,
that's my in in process opinion. Right? That's my like review in whatever they call it.
Review in progress. There you get attacked on site. Their names are colored red. That's okay.
And the street will bring the fight to you. Bust out the self defense. Trust me, there are some
places you do not want to wander around unless you have got the chops. Okay. See the sign for
the apparel store. I want you to do something. Do some shopping there. Okay. New clothes. He's a
fast texter. It's all about the fight. Okay. Buy clothing. Do I have enough money to buy clothing?
Cool. All right. I want a pair of jeans. This is the only thing that's available.
This is the only thing I can buy is this hat. Okay. Well, all right. We both have the same hat.
Are you going to kill five boars already? Cringe incoming. What do you mean cringe incoming?
Talking about me? Cringe, cringe, cringe. What's going on? Chop till you drop.
Doesn't even matter if you're the fashionable type, to be honest.
A little bit of attention to your outfit can make all the difference in a fight.
And hey, doesn't it feel good when you find out that outfit just speaks to you?
Cool. Let's wrap things up for the day. I'm wandering around the city as we speak.
See if you can find me. Okay. His ass is reading. What? He's not playing. He's not really playing.
What are you? Yes, I am. Hi. How's the city treating you? Getting some practical experience
on the streets? Coach, are we really getting stronger by running around like this? Doubting
the wisdom of old Luke Sensei, are you? Let's see where you're at then. Don't worry about taking
turns. Both of you. Let's go. All right. Let's go. I'm going to jump. I'm going to jump, kick,
only grab. You do grabs only. Jump, kick, only grabs. Grabbing, grabbing, grabbing, grabbing.
Grab. I thought that guy in the back was about to jump in and punch us. Nice. Rising up for cut.
What are you going to do? Shit. Get in there and you do something. Oh my God. I keep getting caught.
God damn it. Level 10. Do you know how to block? This is a, you're supposed to lose this. You hold
back to block. I know how to block. I played Street Fighter one when you were, when you were
in a crib. Okay. I played Street Fighter one when you were in a crib. He's crying. It was a bad voice
crack. It's okay though. You just got to take it one step at a time. Yeah. I got to get rid of
this beard. That first step you both took just now, it's something to be proud of. Man, you two are
great students. Okay. Enrolled. We did it. You became Luke's student. You can now use his master
action. Becoming the student of a legendary fighter, let's grant you access to their style,
which you can turn, in turn use in battle. Each style includes moves specific to that
legendary fighter. Seek out legendary fighters and find a style that works for you.
Unique attacks are normal moves that possess special properties. How many you have and what
they do depends on which master's style you're using. Attacks can be performed by using the left
stick and an attack button together. But if you'd rather not worry about doing them accidentally,
you can always remove them from your move list altogether. Just keep in mind that they're all
usable by default. I have to read it. I have to know what I'm doing. You got a grade four reading?
Go watch my sorcery playthrough. You tell me how good I am at reading and dictation.
Then the two of you can go and travel the world. You can really get to know each other
and take on all comers. Seriously, you'll have a blast. Speaking of which, I'm sorry. I can't.
I need to be strong and I need to be it now. I'm not like you. I can't go around treating
this like a game. Bosh. Come on coach. I'm done with the course. Look at that hat on.
Things I need to take care of. But you're right. This did give me some confidence. Thank you.
My fight ended in a draw. Wish we could have had a rematch.
The cinematographer hates this character and never line up a shot correctly.
It's always going to look wrong. I think he was hacking at Bosh. Chasing after his strength in
a mad rush is a recipe for disaster. Let's just hope he doesn't stumble down any weird rabbit holes.
You know, to be honest, I don't consider myself much of a teacher.
Rez said I was too much of a hothead and had me teach new students to help chill me out a bit.
I'm giving it the old college try, but maybe my methods could use a little work.
Maybe that does it for today's lesson. I'll contact you using this sucker moving forward.
Ah, that's right. If you see Alice tell her I said thanks for helping out with the lesson plan.
Yeah. She's got a ton to teach you. So I hope you two don't beat each other up too much.
Nah, nah. All right. Yeah, not that impressive. I beat this guy's ass 10 minutes ago.
Came all the way over here just to thank little old me. Come on. It's been my pleasure.
Your character sucks ass. Start over. No. Guys, this is like Elden Ring.
I'm going to make like 15 characters eventually, right? I'm going to get my first move in Elden
Ring and just be like, nah, fuck this. I'm doing something else. I'm playing. It's like I'm doing
pyromancy. Never mind. You're not touching this game after the stream. Oh, yeah. What a pull up.
What a pull up. Will I play this game again after today? Yes or no. What a pull up. Let's put your
money where your mouth is. Let's see it. Yeah. Now cut to me. Cut to me at Evo. I've been screaming.
The crowd is fucking electric and there's a thumb cam down on my controller. Just like
everyone stands up. Everyone's standing and I flawless victory every opponent.
Well, I'm not going to do that, but it'd be fun. Strength is something we all must find on our own
and in order to find it, you've got to talk to people just like you're doing now. Okay. Legends.
Take my style. For example, I learned it from a fighter named Chun Li.
If you're looking for a guidepost towards strength to call your very own,
be well worth heading to Chinatown to meet with Chun Li and learn her style.
Actually, we had another raid. Yeah, I didn't even see it. I was too busy talking about
Captain Planet or something. That was Sips. Sips came in with the raid. I don't know how long
ago that was. 10 minutes maybe. But welcome. Thanks for the raid. Welcome, everybody.
Points called miles are earned throughout the game by performing various actions.
Ooh, whoa. Wow. The city can save a wealth of things to see and do. You can chat with the people
you meet, do part-time jobs for Zenny or even find rare items in the most unexpected of places.
All right, let's go. I'm ready. All right. What do I do first? Let's go. Why does he keep? Why is he
only fighting pedestrians? This is a level five. It's not my fault that it's not my fault that
that character stinks. All right. What do I have? Items. Hard candy. You can lick your way to its
nutritious center. Oh, this is in battle. Oh, iron hard caramels. That sounds awful. Okay. So
we need to go to Chinatown. Okay. Break your teeth. Yeah. I can use the phone. Hey, you're
going to travel all over to get stronger from here on out, right? Probably as good a time as any to
take the bus. Chinatown's that away. Hard to miss its big gate. Anyway, good luck out there.
Okay. I'm getting a bus stop for the first time. It'll become available as fast travel location.
I can view the map and your device will allow you to travel there. All right. So it's fast travel.
Cool. So make sure you unlock every bus stop. Okay. Wait, this Pete's over here.
I have a car. Whoa. Fight the mime. Where's there a mime? Fight the mime. I don't see a mime.
Where's this mime? Is a mime like the pizza guy again? No, I've already beaten him up twice.
Oh, here's the mime. Like, do people know what I'm about to do?
Do people just fight each other? Stop running away. The mime is not fighting. Oh,
the mime is talking. That's true. Oh, punish counter. Level six. Let's go. Okay. Earning
enough styles at EXP will cause that style's rank to increase. If you increase your style rank,
your master in that style might teach you new moves the next time you talk to them.
Oh, okay. While exploring the city, you may sometimes notice citizens with
master icons attached to them. These citizens are talented fighters who use the moves of that icon's
corresponding legendary fighter and will yield a large amount of style experience. Ooh. Okay.
Anybody have that? Who are you? No. What about you? No. Uppercut somebody. I missed. All right.
Let's go to Chinatown. So, where's the bus? How do I? How do I? Got a metro free pass? Yes. Oh,
I don't. So, this is now just a travel point. All right. So, how do I get to?
I just walk, I guess. Can I get up there and fight these guys? That's terrifying. Oh, shit.
Watcher, I'm a hero. I protect the city from the shadows. I sense destiny in our meeting here.
Care to talk shop? And by shop, I mean justice? Yeah. Allow me to begin. There was once a young
man seeking strength. He traveled here to Metro City. On his first night, he went in search of
food to sate his empty stomach. But along the way, he encountered foul ruffians who stripped him of
every of his possession. If the story ended there, it would be just another tale from the mean
streets of Metro City. But all my friend ended did not. A martial artist intervened, aiming to
strike down the rampaging ruffians. And strike them down he did. And they all lived happily ever
after, perhaps, had the story ended there. You see, the fighter chose to re-leave the gang members
of their money. It was their reward for winning, you see. In that very moment, the young man had
an epiphany. Martial artists and gang goons are cut from the same cloth. Strike down evil is a
righteous act. All right, you want to go? That's not enough. One's reasons for striking down evil
and their sportsmanship afterward are equally important. When you raise your fist, you must
do so for just and meaningful purposes. You're a fighter, hmm? Is there meaning guiding your
fists? I don't know yet. Hmm, I see. You'll find a clear answer to that question in time, I imagine.
You must never forget to fight with a spirit of righteousness.
Sorry for the trouble.
Ah, listen to me blabbing, I'm sorry about that.
Here it is. Thanks for listening to my story. No need to be shy now, take it.
Ooh, okay. Fully restore his vitality and drive gauge. Well, now I'm going to kick the shit out of
you. Capcom, man! Back up. All right, this is bullshit, but it's working. All right, would I
get booed? Would I get booed if I was doing this in a tournament? Whoa, what happened? Oh, he
countered it. Not if it was working. A win is a win. Okay, yeah. Are there any diminishing returns?
I'm going to level up like five times after beating this guy. Oh my God, what am I doing?
Am I actually going to level up a shitload of times? Uh oh, bad. This is bad. This is really
bad. I don't know what he's doing. Why did I go against, why did I go against the fucking formula?
Why did I do that? That was stupid. I could have beat him. I don't know why I got bored.
Let me continue. Somebody resident sleepered and I freaked out and had to punch him twice.
I'm not even going to look at chat. God damn it. Whatever. Okay, well at least it shows them on the
map. I'll be back. What did I just do to that guy? Who am I fighting? Oh, it's 2v1. All right.
That was not even, that was simple. Nice. That looks awful. You were at the very bottom of the
bag of cheese and you were like, you know what? I already have the dough out and I already have the
sauce out. I have to, I have to make it work. There's like 15 strands of cheese left. Stop
being mean. I just don't like that. I don't like pizza like that. I have to have the perfect level
of, perfect level of cheese and sauce. 3v1. Oh shit. This guy's level 14 and 15. How am I
going to beat this? I'm kind of doing it though. Is there another one? How many people are there
in this? That was pretty good. No. God damn it. I fucking knew it was going to hit me.
Shit. Guess level 15. All right. I'm going to Chinatown. Oh, that's right. I have items.
I can take them in the middle of a fight, right? When are you going to play the actual game?
This is the game. Are you asking when I'm going to play multiplayer online matches?
The hell? I don't know. This is what I wanted to play. What? So you can stream snipe me and
beat me in fucking 10 seconds. That's what you want. That's why you want me to do that.
You're sitting there hovering over the join match button. It's like, Oh, help I get queued up with
them so I can literally do one combo and kill them. Of course you can fight with your creator
characters. That's awesome. I'll definitely do it. IRL street fighter. Whoa. I'm disappointed in you.
It's on Lee. Could I get a selfie? Just real quick, real quick. Sorry for the trouble involved.
I'm Chunlin. Is there something I can help you with? Teach me. It actually, there actually is
a selfie system. That's funny. Okay. I had a long career as a fighter myself, faced all kinds of
opponents that includes seriously powerful foes and friends forged in the fires of competition.
I'm apparently uninterested after all these years of fighting. I decided it might be time for break.
So I'm here teaching the locals Kung Fu. I can't promise it will provide you with the strength
you're looking for, but I happen to teach you a thing or two. Okay. This really is just a random
character. Every button was pressed and randomized. There was no thought that went into this at all.
All right. Oh, not good enough. Not good enough. Wow. So epic.
All right. So now I can use Chun Li's moves. Ooh, spinning bird kick. So you have,
you can only use a certain style at once. You can't combine moves. Okay. Oh, wait, no. All right.
Ooh. So I can combine them. Oh, shit. That's actually pretty cool. All right. So let me do
that. Special moves. So do I want rising uppercut or do I want the flash knuckle? I think I want
the range. I want this. I like this move. All right. So this is forward and this is just standard.
Okay. Let's try it. Let's go. All right. How do I do it? How do I do it? Whoa. How do I just do that?
Am I missing something? Hold back and then forward. Back, forward. Back, forward. Back, forward.
Back, forward Y. Back, forward Y. Back, forward Y. Back, forward Y. Back, forward Y. Forward special.
Forward Y. Forward Y. What's happening here? Do I have to charge it for a bit? Oh, that was weird.
How did I just do that? Yeah, but I'm on modern controls. Okay. Hold on. Let me go. Wait.
Back, forward. Yeah, but isn't it modern? Oh, hold back, press Y. Hold forward, press Y.
It's just forward Y. Forward Y. Forward Y. Forward Y. How's it not working? Hold forward Y.
I'm just, I'm doing it. Hold back and press special. It's not doing it either.
I don't even know how the fuck I just did that. I just tried, I tried every single combination.
Hold for one second then forward Y. I did that like probably 30 times in a row.
I don't understand what's going on. You weren't holding back for long enough.
How come I'm all the way back here? Where's the moves list? I'm so far away.
Charge inputs are not easy. I wasn't, I wasn't holding back long enough. I'll figure it out.
Okay. You can check who you're studying. Got it. All right. Let me try this again.
One. Okay. Holding one. I'm holding back. Forward Y. Hold forward, back Y. Don't move at all. Press Y.
Back, forward Y. Back, forward Y. Back, forward Y. Forward, back Y. Down, back Y.
One, two, three, forward Y. I don't get it. Press Y while holding forward. That's what I'm doing
right now. All right. I, I, what just happened right there? Hold Y. Forward. Okay. It's, you have,
it's only, it's only walking forward. It's walk forward for two seconds and then Y. Not back,
forward Y. Back, forward Y. You have to, you have to walk forward for a full almost two seconds.
Like that. Or back. Nope. Back does not work. I feel like that's not very good. Yeah. If I,
okay. I'm hold, I'm going to hold back. One, two, three. Doesn't do anything. I'm holding forward.
One, one, two, three. Yeah. It's forward only. I feel like I would want to do the regular controls
for that one. I wonder if I could do it. I probably should just play with the regular controls.
Hold forward while crouching. Ah, now, now you got it. There we go. Yeah. You bumped into me.
Sorry, buddy. Forward. What? Yeah. I don't like that at all. I think I was going to play with the
regular controls. Do I do it in here? Controls, right? Uh, modern. Let's do classic. Let's try it.
So four back Y. Forward, back Y. Forward, back Y. Forward, back Y. Forward, back Y. Forward, back,
backward. Forward, back X. Forward, back X. Forward, back X. Forward, back. Wait, what?
Why did they get rid of my, did take it off? I need to re equip it. That combo Omega Lola.
Relax. Okay. I don't play Street Fighter. I don't play Street Fighter. You need to calm down.
Don't Omega Lola combo me. I'm going back to modern. Some people don't make fun of me.
I'm going to go back to modern. Some people don't like make fun of me. What's wrong with that?
Learn new actions from every master you study under. Cool. Street Fighter chat is toxic. No,
what the hell can you do? What? I kind of want to learn that. That seems ridiculous. Okay. Well,
I definitely want to do that. All right. Special moves. What happened? Oh, this is how I do this.
All right. All right. So forward, back, doesn't do it back. It's only forward. It's only Y.
I'm going to get you. Ouch. Ouch. Ouch. Now I'm angry. Ouch. Ouch. Anybody know what that is?
All right. How do I get out of here? All right. Down, up. Yeah. Wouldn't that cool? All right.
So how do I do it? It's forward and Y, right? Oh shit. I'm going to lose. No, we're good. We're
good. All right. Cool. I'm just leveling up. All right. I'm going to, we'll do a little bit more
and then I'm going to take it online and they get destroyed for a little while and you can all laugh.
Everybody can clip the moments where I get flawless. Didn't you know what I mean? Like
we'll do that in like 10 minutes. Am I not on Chun-Li style? Oh, are you ready? Holy shit.
Hold forward and Y. Oh, it's different because it's different character.
Dude, Jerma sucks at fighting games. That's fine. I'm going to have my fun playing the game.
You can get good. You can get to rank two, whatever you want to get to.
Almost level 10. All right. Anything else to do? Oh, you sup. Get to rank 10.
Should I do the thing that people are going to be so pissed off though?
When I play online, you guys are going to hear a lot of this because I'm,
I'm just going to hit every single button. And I know that people hate that, but he's a masher.
I know I'll try. It's okay. I do that too. Yeah. I think a lot of us. Okay. Well, you can discover
the style that's truly yours. And the only time you can do that is in combat. I got to put some
clothing on. Do you mind keeping an eye? Uh, talented. Okay. All right. That full body is.
All right. I can at least put pants on. There we go. I still have to learn how to do supers and
stuff and drive gauge. And I don't know how to do any of that. Okay. Okay. You don't go,
you don't get it till chapter six. Should I take it online? What do you think? We're taking it
online. Let's go hit up the basic tutorial. All right. I love this mode. I'm definitely
going to play it off stream. But did you guys do a poll to determine if I was going to play
this ever again? What was the, what was the percentages? Okay. Most people online space to
play. Okay. Let's go. 66% said no. Okay. Quick join. Okay. I think I'm going to do quick join.
Okay. I'm not ready. I am not ready.
Not in a bad way. Of course. In an amazing way. So this is where I'd usually say you can go
wherever and do whatever. But wait, is these other, are these other players? I'm sure you're
going to have a lot of questions. This is your first time, right? He's going to rage quit.
No, I won't. Can we have a face cam for this? You want to see me my face when I lose? Yeah,
we'll do in a minute. Hold on. The various points around here. Each one has a handy little
instruction pop up. So don't be nervous. Look at that. Look at that devil. Look at that devil.
Go explore and have some filter usernames. Oh, should I? Okay. Okay. Okay.
Somebody made a puppy. Okay. I like puppy. So where do I go? Look, I can tell who installed
the game 20 minutes ago. We all have the, you installed the game 20 minutes ago pants.
Whoa. Hold on. Come here. This is awesome. This is so cool. Let's go. Oh, whatever. All right. Who
wants to fight? Does anybody want to fight? Okay. I think, can I challenge somebody to a duel?
How do you fight people? How do I? All right, let's do it. I'm ready. No, no, no. I want to fight.
How do we fight? Oh, who did I just fight? I don't know who this is. Apparently,
they're an extreme rookie though. That's good for me. Let's go. Oh, shit. I got grabbed. I'm
gonna try. Oh, that was a grab midair. What just happened? Good blocks. Good blocks. Good blocks.
Shit. Don't do this to me. I won. I won. I did it. Oh, fuck. I fucked up. I fucked up. I'm sorry. I
fucked up. That was my fault. I fucked it up. I fucked up. That's my fault. I screwed up. That's
my fault. That was my fault. I did that. That was stupid. But we're fine. It's my fault. He's back.
All right. Let's go. And everybody can come and swarm me again. Come and swarm me. I was worried.
Yeah. That's my own problem. I crashed it out. All right. I'm ready for a challenger. If anybody is
there, please. Ezfan was here. Wait. Did Ezfan raid right when I did that? Oh, that's unfortunate.
All right. Let's go. I'm ready to fight for real now. What happened? I accidentally turned my
fucking internet off. Don't ask me how. This first just destroyed me. What? I closed out of OBS.
I turned my fucking internet off. I just fucked up. It wasn't a rage quit and it wasn't a bit. I
promise. All right. I got that too. All right. Bring it back. Shit. No. Are these the people
watching us? No. Did I beat him or did I? Oh, that's too bad. No, rematch, rematch, rematch,
rematch. Let's do it again. Okay. That was good. Shit. What the fuck, man? Come on. Oh, my god.
Damn it. Wait, his arms are longer. Fuck. How do I do moves? Shit. All right. I'm doing something
else. No, that was fun. Good game. Good game. Try a new character. How do you even play as a
different character? Can we just take everybody to the arcade or something? Like, can we just go ride
rides at an amusement park? Oh, my goodness. How do you even make that? It kind of is a Roblox
lavia. Wait, what? Wait, we can play these? Can we play those together? This is really cool. Level
66. Holy shit. All right. How do I play with a different character? Can I pick a different
character? Press X. Oh, okay. Here's the battle settings. Character, choose your character,
fighter profile. Okay. Who are these? Oh, all right. Okay. So who's good? I want to try this
character. Oh, Blanca. Title setting. Let's do this. Yeah, that's fine. Okay. Did I confirm it?
All right. I'm ready for a challenge. Anybody there? This person has three win streak.
Yeah. Oh, it's. All right. All right. All right. All right. All right. All right. All right. All
right. All right. All right. This character is distracting. Yeah, it's playing a platform game
and that this bro has five. Why did you get all this health? Look at this person's health. Is this
for real? Nope. Is that their health bar? What? You don't have three health bars, do you? This person
has three. How is this possible? How do I do that? How do I do that move? That's so unfair.
This guy's got two extra health bars. What the hell? All right. I'm going to play as a different.
I want to play as a character. Okay. Character. Should I go just to the main menu? Go to a cabinet.
Fight against other players. Oh, okay. I joined Q. Um, reserve player one side.
Am I doing it right? Okay. Spectate while waiting, I guess.
You need to. That felt weird. All right. Nice. Nice. Oh, this is you can fast forward. Wait,
I just gave a thumbs up. Do you know that you're not playing? Yeah, I'm in the queue to play.
Beautiful fight. I'm queued up. All right. All right. This person knows how to play.
That face. Holy shit. Wow. That was cool. Hey, somebody said, Hey, is there a streamer here?
Yeah. XQC. That's not. So what the fuck happened? Well, I know. All right. All right. I'm going
change character costume. That's fine. All right. Am I ready? No, I want to get away from this one.
All right. Sit down. Yes. Just queue for a match on the mat. This is me. This is me. All right.
This is me. This is me. Oh, mirror match. You got it. Shit. What did I just do? What am I shortening
my butt to him for? What does this do? Oh my God. I need to, I need to do the tutorial of the video
game. Okay. They didn't. What? Ow. Whoa. That was a cool move. Whoa. Oh, somebody learned how to play.
What's wrong with me? Ow. Oh yeah. Well, what about this shit? What's wrong with me? Why am I on
drugs? Why am I on fucking crack? What's wrong with me? How do you do a super? How do I do super?
Oh, Y and B at the same time. You mean like that? All right. It's all right. It's all right. It's
all right. Adorable. Jerma thinks he can play. Yeah. It's fine. I don't know what the fuck's
going on. That doesn't matter. I'm having fun. All right. I want to play as a different character.
All right. I'm going to sit at this one. You all fell for it. Okay. The tutorial would help you a
lot. Yeah, I know. Cause I know there's like a parry. There's that paint move where you paint
there's a whole super meter thing. There's a whole, there's a whole thing here. Shit. Shit.
That did a lot of damage. Holy shit. Ow. What the fuck? The only way to get good is slamming your
head against the brick wall. Oh, air grab. What does that do? Give me that grab. Give me the grab.
Oh no. What was that? All right. I'll be back. I'm going to go do the tutorial.
All right. Everybody come over here. Stand right here. Facing this direction.
Right here. Facing this direction, please. Okay. Stand here and face, uh, face me, please.
No, not in front of me over on the white line. Okay. So everybody come over here. Only like 10
of you are actually listening. I feel like I've had dreams where this was what was happening.
Okay. You ready? I'm telling you, we're going to play something here. You ready?
Simon says walk one step forward. Nice. Nice. Okay. Step back. Ah, you, you moved a little.
You moved a little. All right. Now let's fucking go. How do I challenge? All right. Simon says do
a full lap around the whole hub back here. Well, y'all lose. He's taking a picture, taking a selfie.
Oh, hold on a minute. Oh shit. I just hit like five people. Is that bad? All right. I'm going
to go learn how to play the game. I'll be right back. I'll be right back. I'm just going to learn
how to play the game. All right, let's go. All right. We know how to do this. We know how to do
this. We know how to do this. We know how to do this. We know how to do this. What's this?
Let's do a quick review of drive impacts. If your opponent's in the corner and you hit them,
the drive impact. Okay. Okay. So there are some situations where this crush date won't occur.
Okay. Well, I think we have to go back a few steps. Here we go. All right. The drive gauge.
These are powerful up special moves that consume two drive gauge blocks. I'm using a special move
that has an overdrive version. Press. Okay. Instead of one of the. All right. Overdrive
arts have different properties than their standard counterparts. Just do the first one. God fucking
damn it. Okay. Dashing. Yep. Why am I on classic? How come I can't change this? Why does this keep
changing? Why does this keep changing? You pick the classic tutorial. Oh, come on. All right.
I'll get it in 10 minutes. And then I'm going back in there and I'm going to dominate. Yep.
It's dashing. Cool. Cool. Jumping. Yep. Okay. Good jumps. Normal attacks. Yep. Yep. Yep. Yep.
Uh huh. Down. Yep. Jump. Yep. Yep. Standing block and crouching block. That's good to know.
I didn't know that. Uh huh. See, I'm getting it. Okay. Crouch block. Yeah. I don't think
you would have figured that out right away. Yep. Okay. Throw escape by pressing X and A at the same
time. Check your timing. Escape my throw. Oh, that's how you do it. All right. Nice. Okay. Yep.
Special moves. Rising up a cut. Nope. Okay. Here we go. This is it. Three levels. You have at least
one you can perform a super art. Level one super art. Okay. Level one super art with either of
these. Forward B and Y. This is a level one super art. It's forward B and Y. Level two short range.
So it's away from your opponent. So you got to go like wham. Okay. Yep. All right. So you got to go
like wham. Modern control scream. Omega low. No, that's fine. Look, if you know that I'm already
using modern controls, you probably, you probably left the stream like an hour ago. That's fine.
It's all good. So you go wham. All right. I get it now. So that's how you do that. But what about
the left bumper thing I was pressing? Sure. We'll get it right now. Okay. There it is. All right.
The six bar display shown here is known as the it indicates a fighter's concentration energy level.
Utilizing this gauge lets you perform unique actions. Okay. First off is the drive impact.
Press left bumper to perform a powerful attack. Just left bumper. Got it. So that uses one cube.
They can absorb two attacks from the opponent, but there are some exceptions. When you're in
trouble, use the drive impact to break through an attack. Oh, so that's how you could, that's how
you stop somebody from doing a combo. Okay. Didn't I just do it? I'm not doing it. Press A dude. Oh,
while I'm blocking. So it goes through block. All right. So it's mainly to get out of combos.
I was using it as a, like a punch drive parry. Okay. So that's how you replenish the gauge.
They cannot defend against throws. Try them out in real fight. While I perform a drive parry,
press X and A at the same time to throw me. Yep. Okay. You don't want to use it in combos.
Perfect parry is performing a drive parry. The moment an opponent attacks, it's you. Okay.
All right. Drive impacts are powerful to use for any fighter. Okay. So drive, you can use drive
parry. Got it. Too much information. I'm going to go hit my sandbag. So parrying is insanely
important, especially if you're in the corner. Okay. Yep. Okay. Burnout. The drive impact and
drive parry are great uses of the drive gauge, but continuous use will drain the gauge. And if
you drain it completely, you'll be unable to use it for a period of time. All right. So that's why
I thought I was like on drugs and you get stunned. Okay. All right. When a fighter is in burnout,
they can still be stunned even if they block a drive impact. Remember chasing someone into the
corner gives you more chances. All right. I get, I think I got it now. I think I'm good. Okay. I'm
ready. Yeah. I'm good to go. Name one move that was introduced. Drive parry, drive gauge, drive
impacts, special one, special two, and special three. Special two is a hit back and press Y and
B. Special three is crouch and hit Y and B. I paid attention. And that person for 25 minutes.
There it is. There it is. I got it now. I got it now. What happens when your drive gauge is empty?
You get, you get into dazed mode and you get, you can get stunned. I win. And that person for four
hours. Go back to the hub. I love that you can just kind of hang out here. Doing tournaments like this
would be so much fun. You actually can participate. I definitely don't want to fight the person that
has three boss health bars. Hey dude, I bet you can't recite the first 20 lines of, of, of pie.
Um, the pie, the math problem was a three, um, three point four one five nine two six five three
five nine. Stage select. Ooh, hold on. Where do I want to go? Coliseum. Wait, I think I'm still,
I'm still Blanca, aren't I? Wait, no, no, it's this, it's this guy again. I don't want to fight
this person. They have too much. All right. Well, I learned a lot. So let's go. Wait, I don't have
any drive powers. This is just a leveled up version of my character. Shit. I'm wicked fucking
unpredictable. Oh no, no, no, no, no, no, no. I still have health. Damn it. Why can't I do
special moves anymore? I'm pressing why it's not doing anything. What the fuck are my moves?
I don't have any moves. Got him. How do I not have a move to do? Oh, it's because I'm story locked.
All right. I get it. I don't even have a super meter. Oh shit. Okay. I got to get out of here.
We got, okay. Let me play the regular game now. Jesus. I'll try Blanca again. All right. Here we
go. Now I know how to play. What? What? Oh, I'm not even in matchmaking. This person might have
a hundred hours in this game, right? Is that accurate? LOL. He's using, no, I'm not getting
better. Shit. Ow. Ow. Ow. Ow. No, it's not fair. I'm going to matchmaking. I'm going to matchmaking.
I'm going to matchmaking. That was fun. Everyone. Good job. All of you. Thanks for playing. All
right. I'm going to go do matchmaking to play against the real players of my skill level.
It was very, very good job. Nice work. But just do it from the pause menu. Can I do it from here?
Is he won a single game? Press X. Oh, ranked matches on like that. All right. What's the
character I would want to play with? Maybe Guile. Hmm. E Honda. I know if I play this character,
I'm going to spam X and people are going to get really bad at me. Oh, all right. I'm doing E
Honda. Fuck it. Let's go. Okay. I don't want to hear about spinning bird kick anymore. Get me away
from them. All right. This is a real challenge now. Let's go. All right. Good. Good. Nice hit.
Nice hit. Oh, good counter. Shit. Nice lock. All right. So we start. Let's get started. Let's go.
Land it. Oh, what? All right. All right. All right. Good throw escape. Good job, dude. All right. I'll
get it too. There we go. That's first one of the night. First win of the night. Thank God.
Finally, I do a rematch. I think you're right. This is a computer. How is this computer?
It's for placement. Oh, all right. I get it. Oh, I'm going to get put like,
I'm going to put in chicken league. No, I'm not. That's fine. It wasn't terrible.
Look, I could do more grabs. Way more grabs. Shit. You're getting better. That's good to hear. It's
fun. Back special is your best move. Okay. So now that's it, right? Quit. Uh, previous mode. How do
I just keep going? You got to learn the headbutt. Okay. Ranked match. I think it's still happening.
Okay, cool. Let's swarm his body and vibrate him to death like we're bees.
Okay. Hello. This is a real fight. This is a real person. Shit. Oh, he's caught up in a combo. Caught
up in a combo. Stop screaming for no reason. Like I'm, what am I doing? This guy's quick.
Ow. All right. That's a grab. What kind of move is that? How about back in YB, right?
Why won't he do it? How come I can't do my special move back in YB, back YB, back YB. Why is it not
working? Why is it not working? I had three bars. I, why, why couldn't I do back YB? I had three bars
back YB is two bar. Didn't I have three? You're on the right. I was doing, I was,
I was doing back YB. I'm promising you. It's different inputs for every account. Oh, come on.
Really? All right. Well, I didn't, I have no idea how to do them. God damn it. I'm just not fast
enough. Come on. Jesus. What the fuck? This guy's got insane zoning moves. It's just like an S tier
character. I feel like he is. I just did back YB and it didn't do anything. Whatever. There's
a genre of video game that I've put maybe collectively four hours of time into.
It's Street Fighter. I almost did it. I need a new character. Don't clap for me. I didn't win.
That should come out. I can do that too. Yo. Oh, good. Good counter. Oh shit. Back it up. I'm stunned.
I'm stunned. I'm stunned. I got to back it up. Shit. That's bad. Let's go. I won. I won one match.
I got to figure out how to do the other move. Oh, all right. I should have blocked it. Oh,
this game's fun. Even if I'm not very good at it. I'm learning though. I'm getting, I'm getting
better. Oh, nice job. Good job. Shit. Shit. Jump. Jump out of the way. I'm dead. All right. That was
better. I got to do combo try. Yeah. I mean, I could learn really genuinely how to play a character,
but I'm just having fun. It's all good. Got it. It's down. Shit. I almost blocked it. Shit. No.
Good. Good. Good. Good. All right. Okay. I need to figure out how to play the game.
I got to figure out how to play better and play combo trials. Here we go. And who do I actually
want to play with? Let's see. I don't know. Maybe character guide. It's DJ. Who's DJ? How
to play DJ. Okay. All right. Moves I can use to control the rhythm of battle.
Faints. Oh, that's cool. Seems fun. That's a lot of fake outs. Is that it? Okay. I'll try it. All
right. Rebeat combo. That's just X, X, X. Sure. DJ special board. Was it X board? I'm doing it,
right? Oh, whoa. Okay. A, B, B. Cool. Cool. Okay. What button is he pressing? Show inputs. Whoa.
Okay. Trial display method. Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait. There's too many buttons.
Command display. Oh, there we go. Okay. So what is it? Hold right trigger and then X, X.
Okay. Then it's cool. Whoa. This more of this. Holy shit. Okay. Well, I didn't do any of that.
It was cool. That's so cool. I just have to press one button. That's so fun. Okay. And then it's down.
Okay. How fast do we have to do it? There it is. Okay. Nice. All right. Intermediate
during a forward jump. Ooh, that'll catch people. Oh, there's more. Why? And then why? Why? Holy
shit. Okay. Well, connected with the special cancelable move. Forward, forward. Whoa. This
one's going to be hard. That's a lot of presses. Shit. Shit. Shit. Really? I can't string the
bottom B together. Did that work? That's going to be way too hard. Ooh, no, it's not. And then
it's right trigger A. I keep forgetting to hold right trigger. That's actually kind of hard to
do that. Holding right trigger and pressing A is kind of weird. Really? Shit. What is it supposed
to be? What is it? Let me see the move. After down B, what does it look like? Okay. You just have to
do it really fast. All right. No, I'm done. I'm going to sit here for like four hours to get that
done. I'm going to take it to the computer. Go to the beach. Who should I go against? Dengue?
There was more in the character guide. I pressed like A. We come up together. That's funny.
All right. X forward down B. Whoa. Okay. I just got to learn the combos.
That was close. You know, going the other direction is impossible for my brain to do in fighting
games. That combo I just learned has to be from left to right. You know what I mean? It's like
reading. I have to like do the whole thing backwards. It's funny. God damn it. Focus on
fundamentals first. That's true. I can't wait to watch people play because I like watching people
play things very well and they're probably going to do very good at this game. One time I played
Mortal Kombat, the newer one from like seven or eight years ago, and I sat in a call. I believe
I was in a call with like boo stealth stir and just practicing Kenshi's combo over and over again
for like four straight hours and just sitting there and just trying to get it burned into muscle
memory. There's something about that that's really fun, but we'll do a few more and then I'm going to
call it. This is really cool though. I think it's really good. Let's go back to the hub. I did that
for years because I didn't have good online. Yeah. It's fun because once you actually get a combo
and you do it in a game scenario, it's like, mom, get the camera. Okay. Let's do matchmaking,
right? How do I set it to matchmaking? Oh, character. I need to get my character. Wait, what?
What? It's on ranked. All right. Let me see if I can put something together here.
Shit. That's not good. I'm already out of juice. Damn it. This lost the CPU. Yeah. I get it,
but I don't get it. You got to get your hands to agree with your brain. Yeah. How are you guys
liking it though? How are you guys actually liking the game for street fighter seasoned veterans?
Is it good? Do you think it's a good one? It feels like it's fun to play. It's hard,
but honestly, I like it. Oh my goodness. He's just destroying me. Oh, I said a fake out.
Shit. Oh, no, I can't lose to the CPU. I was looking at chat.
It's fun. It's really fun. Maybe I'll learn it. Maybe I'll just sit on the couch and learn some
combos. You know what I mean? I don't know. It's definitely really fun to play. I like the modern
control scheme. I think it's a good addition to the game. Just learn easy combos and do those.
You don't need to do big combos yet. That's true. That's very true. Just do whatever you like doing.
Just never tell yourself that you have some artificial limit on your skill. You can be as
good as you want to be. Oh my God. The street fighter community is so nice. Are you serious?
Wow. You guys are great. Look at you guys telling me that I could learn combos and I'm doing good
and doing better. Holy smokes. Wow. All right. Thank you. You guys are great. Real ranked match
now. Vibes are immaculate. We're going to face a good DJ. I'm kind of concerned.
This is really nice. This is cool. All right. Let's go. I got punished really bad. Oh my God.
I'm already empty. Oh my goodness. I'm already empty. That was a lot of early damage. What the
fuck did we both just do? Get out of the corner. Oh, not good. Oh, I just like punched him in the
fucking balls. No, no, no, no, no, no. Oh, that's bad. Oh, he got me right in the corner. Shit.
I was too scared. Oh shit. Oh my God. How many times is he going to do that move in a row?
Oh, he had so, he had so much drive. He almost got me with the drive. Let's do it again. Shit.
All right. I got to be careful. Ouch. Oh shit. Now you're in trouble. Oh my God. I'm just doing
the thing. What am I doing? I'm throwing so hard. I just kicked in the wrong direction like three
times. That was close. What happened? Oh, this is bad news. Oh, it's a bad day to be a cheesecake.
Good game. Oh no, there's one more. Oh, come on. Oh, that's bad. That's all right. Shit. I forgot
how to do the fucking super. I was hitting back YB instead of forward YB. One more. Oh, you never
even learned what the supers were for this character. That's true. That's true. How do you
do them? Forward YB is one. Down YB is two. What was the projectile? They're the same for everybody?
Really? All right. Come on. Come on. Come on. Come on. It's all right. It's okay. It's okay.
The supers are the same for everybody. Cool. Cool. Cool. Oh, what? He actually blocked it.
Nice job. Whoa. Oh, I just got fucking destroyed. All right, let's go. This is the one right here.
It's okay. It's all right. Oh, I'm like stunned now. Oh, shit. Nice job. God damn it. So, okay,
my two super, I have to chain it together apparently. I guess. Do I have to just press X
or something? Shit. Not good. It's based on rhythm really. Oh, it's hard to hit. But we both
have three. This is not going to end well. Oh, I got it. All right. Now he's going to do his like
right now. I'm going to flee. I'm going to be a coward. I got to play like a coward for a few
minutes. Did I jump over it? Oh no. Wait, what? I got away from it. Shit. Should have countered
with my own. Shit. Oh, damn it. No. I got outplayed. Oh my God. I just got so outplayed.
I panicked five times in a row. I had no idea what the fuck I was doing. Fuck. I got the
comeback you got in your head. You know what I need to stop doing? I have to stop pressing
left bumper as if it's punch. I keep doing it. I'm like, oh, left bumper. Yeah, that's a big
punch counters. Don't use it as offense. Go for grabs too. That's true.
Whoa. Nice. Okay. All right. Oh my goodness. I got fucking annihilated. Oh, he's trying. He's doing
something. I saw he's doing a fatality. I saw him do like down, down, down, down. This is fun. I just
got to learn. Just have to learn and I'll be good. Are we good? Are we good? No. There we go.
I main DJ. He's a blast. He seems fun. Oh my goodness.
What? Damn it. Oh, yeah. What? Oh, damn it. No. I parried it. What? No. Oh, well, that's a lot of
exes. I got to be more aggressive. Shit. Shit. Shit. No again. Oh, I can't finish the job.
Oh, that move. How do I get away from that move? Did she just take my super away? I'm going to lose.
What is she doing to me? She's taking all my shit. What the fuck? You're just panicking.
This game's too hard. Throw fireballs. How do you throw a fireball back? Why also can somebody help
me? I feel like I'm always like zero drive, even if I don't use the meter, even if I don't
use the bars. Am I doing something wrong? Do the move. What? Oh, I'm okay. Jesus. The ex moves
burn drive. Those are happening automatically though, aren't they? Because of the modern
combat system. Hmm. Oh, okay. Wake up from a knockdown. You need to block more.
That's the drawback of using modern, less controlled than meters. Hmm. That's good to know.
How do I do my free move? I couldn't do my three super. I did down and YB. It didn't do anything.
What the hell? I was hitting down YB, down YB, down YB. I'm just going to learn how to play on
classic. Oh, I had one meter. I'm an idiot. I'm looking at the bottom left. Try to mix it up.
Yeah. All right. Here we go. Oh, it didn't do anything. No, he wants to e-haunt me right now.
I know what you're going to do. I know. I know what you have. You have your triple combo thing.
I ain't fucking around. He wants to do it so bad. I know he does. No, no, that's all right. All
right. One more and I'm done. Last one. Last one. Last one. Last one. One more. Last one. You're being
more patient. Yeah. In fighting games, I just get in my own head and I go just press every button,
even if you don't need to, and just run and jump five times in a row. Okay. New character. I haven't
seen before. Oh, cool. Okay. All right. All right. All right. Good. Still, I could have lost it there.
Does that drink do something? It's not just a taunt.
Fuck. Come on. Break out of it with your thing. Do your thing. Oh, my goodness. He gets new special
moves. Oh, boy. That's not good. Hey, stop relying on the auto combos. Yeah. Well, now that I know
that it's using meter, it's using bars. I'm trying not to use it that frequently. Oh, that was weird.
Oh, not good. Use RTY more. Oh, you're using RTY too much. Okay. Oh, who did it? Oh, all right.
You got your three. I'm terrified of you. I don't know how the fucking move works. No. He's just
ducking. Oh, my God. I used it all. I used it all. How did I do that? I used that. I went to drain
it to zero. What does CA mean? Critical Art. Oh, okay. That's a good game. Nice fight. It's level
three. So I probably would have got killed by that. Damn. All right. Actually, last one. I mean it.
Last one. I appreciate all the help, though. I'm very new to this. It's really cool. Appreciate it.
You guys have been really nice to me. I was going to look over. I was scared I was going to look
over and it was like, oh, no, they hate me. All right. I rank up opportunity. All right.
All right. I tried to be really patient. Shit. Why are you still bad at this game?
This is the second time I've seen this character play. I don't even know what this guy's... I know
he drinks alcohol. You know what? Time that person up for five seconds. Holy shit. He just fucking
destroyed me. When somebody gets in a rhythm, it's just like, I don't even know what to do.
What the fuck was that? I'm trying to throw fireballs. Why did he just do that? Really?
All right. We can do it again. Shit. I don't know what's going on with him, but he seems
very angry and very drunk. It's been a lot of screaming. Sorry about that.
Okay. I got to pull together here. I did like no damage to him. Oh, my God. He hurts so much.
This guy's fucking crazy. All right. Okay. That's enough. I had fun. That was fun. All right. Last
one. Chun-Li. Okay. You're going to end on a loss. I know that's... I'm going to use this philosophy.
One of my earbuds fell out. Disaster. I was a little scared there. Oh, shit. I got caught
in the corner. All right. This last one. Shit. Shit. Okay. Well, I just got fucking annihilated.
Okay. I keep forgetting you can do the grab parry. I forget it. All right. I didn't mean to even do
that move. Fuck. Oh, okay. All right. One more. It was one and one. It was one and one. Damn it.
I still got it. Everyone's either playing Diablo or this. Well, they're two new, cool, fun video
games. I didn't mean to do that. Oh, my God. I got to stop doing that. I'm just... Oh, I fucked up
everything. If you don't know how to do the move, don't pretend to do it and spam the move
three times and then just burn all your meter. Really? Oh, I'm so screwed here. Damn it. All
right. All right. This time, don't go back wide, back wide, back wide and have no fucking squares
left, you dummy. That's bad. That's game over. Should have blocked. Yeah. All right. Last one.
All right. No matter what happens, this is the last one for... It's over. One more and that's it.
I should have ended when I won. Oh, no. Not this guy. That little head tilt at the end. Whoa.
What the hell is that? That was crazy. I can't grab this guy. How close are I going to be?
Shit. What the fuck? That did like 35% of my health. Is that just a regular grab? I missed it. Oh,
my God. Shit. Come on, dude. Oh, my God. That sucks. It's not over yet. Oh, my God.
I don't know how far it went forward. I thought it went much further than that. Shit. Damn it.
It's all right. What the hell? Oh, my God. Bad idea. I'm getting fucking dominated right now.
I didn't even throw him. What? Oh, that's not good. All right. At least it's something okay.
I'm starting to understand it. He's super good at zoning though. That's the...
I'm saying words. I don't know what they actually mean. I'm just saying them.
Oh, I try to catch it again. Bad idea. That was really stupid of me. That was really dumb of me.
I don't know why I did that. Oh, my God. He's un-fucking-bearable. He has moves that go across
the screen. He's got moves that are close. He's got things to shoot from the fucking ceiling.
All right. That one doesn't count. I got to end on a win. All right. No matter what happens,
this is the final one. I promise. I'm done after this. Everyone's clapping. Hey, thanks.
I wish you well in the world of... I almost just said StarCraft. Street Fighter.
All right. This is the one right here. I'm going to try as hard as I can. I'm going to be quiet
the whole time. Here we go. Three, two, one. Quiet. I just tried as hard as I could.
Nice. Okay. Okay. All right. Okay. Okay. All right. All right. Okay.
No. Why did that not connect? I don't understand StarCraft.
Did it. Okay. What? Stream lagging? Oh, it shouldn't be. Nice. Okay. All right.
That was a good parry. Oh, shit. I just got perfect in the corner. Shit. Oh, my God. My face is
sweating. I forgot how to play the game. I'm in trouble now. Whoa. That was laggy. So good,
though. What? Why did that get animation canceled by every fucking move in the game?
I did it. That was close. All right. That's it. That was really fun. Street Fighter 6
is great. I could see how people could dump hundreds of hours into this game.
I completely get it. That was awesome. Oh, shit. I mean, we have to do it. I'm just here.
Didn't mean to. I just, I tried to exit. You saw me hit the button.
Sorry I turned the stream off halfway through. That was really stupid of me.
It's all right, though. We had fun. I never did face cam either. We'll do it next time.
All right. This is the one here. Right here. Shit. Oh, I somehow pulled that out of my ass.
Shit. I can do that too. Oh. All right. We have to do a revenge. All right. Easy. Hold on.
Oh, that was, I blew it. Sorry. I blew it. It's fine. Shit. Oh, I fucking lost it in this last
round. Big time. Now I forgot what the controls were. All right. That's a, that's a 1v1.
That's I-1-1. That's, yeah. We gotta go for the whole thing. Gotta go for the whole thing. This
is the World Series right here. God damn it. I can't do anything. Oh my God. I'm getting
fucking screwed. All right. Aggression. Let's go. All right. That was, that was like I handed the
controller to somebody else. No. Oh, no. Shit. I just didn't know what to do for a follow-up.
I just was like, what do I do? I, what do I do? It's like, wow, I put it all together and oh,
he's just, he's lying on his back. Okay. Oh, B. All right. Last one or I'll delete my Twitch
channel. This is the last one. If this series, whatever the series ends up being, I'm playing
against this next person. Even if we rematch, that's fine. But that's it. I'm out. What the
hell? What was that? Stopped saying last one. Well, I, I was supposed to leave. It's time for
dinner. I'm only leaving because I need to eat. Let's go. You got garlic bread down? Oh, I got
garlic bread. I gotta get out of here. Okay. All right. Oh, what happens? What happens now?
What just happened? I caught him right in the chin. I don't know what happened, but that was
pretty crazy. All right. Cool. Hmm. Oh, what? I grabbed him. All right. I got, I got a lot of
meter. I'm good. All right. That's all right. That's all right. All right. That's it. That was fun.
Oh, I can see how people just delete weeks of their life to this game. I never got into,
I didn't really care for them. They were always too hard. Well, not hard. It just, it was always,
oh, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no. I gotta get out of here. Thanks for playing whoever played.
That was a lot of fun. I will see you guys in a couple of days. I'll see you on Wednesday,
Wednesday the 7th. Gollum, 4.5 out of 10. Street Fighter 6. I mean, I don't know, like nine.
This is great. I actually really liked this game. It's cool that people think that this is a good
one because I'm having fun with it. Yeah. Four o'clock on Wednesday. Yeah. I promise we'll go
over a gen lost stuff. I kind of got addicted to this game. I forgot about everything because that
was an unbelievable experience. So I definitely want to talk a little bit more about it. Yeah.
I'll see you guys on Wednesday. Take care of yourselves. Why is my voice gone? Have I just
been yelling? Oh, every time I get KO'd, I went, Oh, right. I forgot. Thanks for watching. See you
later. See you soon. Let's actually, let me quit this correctly. That's Street Fighter 6. Yeah.
I'm sweating. Sweaty game. See you soon. Thanks for watching. How do you exit the game?
I don't know how to leave. Where's the quit game button? How do you leave? I don't know how to leave.
Menu. Exit two. Okay. You have to press. Okay. Exit desktop. There it is. All right. Call your
mother. See you later. Otto's doing better. You don't know Otto had a bladder infection. He still
does. And yesterday I wanted to make sure that we monitored him. I can't even talk right now.
That we monitored him because he had to go outside every 45 minutes or so. He's drinking
a lot of water, but he's on antibiotics. Seems to be doing much better. He's good. Yep. Wednesday
is the next stream day. I might play more Street Fighter. Would you guys like it if I actually
learned the game and actually learned how to play more and play it some more? I had a lot of fun.
Yeah. Just jumping off for like a couple of, I'm going to learn some more combos.
I might play with some other characters too. Get better. Take more creative characters. Yeah.
Thanks for being so, I said this earlier, but that was, it was like no toxic chat members.
It's unbelievable. I don't think I've ever seen that before. No, they were. They were. Somebody
said there were plenty. I just wasn't looking at the right time. That's funny. They really were.
It's okay. I don't, it doesn't bother me. I don't feel pressured. No, I, I really, look, I know what
I'm capable of doing. Fighting games are usually not one of them, but you can call me, you can call me
a shitty player. That's fine. It's your opinion. You're allowed to have it. You can call me a,
you can call me a modern Andy and then say that I fucking smell and that I'm bad at this game.
But if you do that, you, you're going to get zapped. Just telling you.
The fighting game community loves you. Really? Thanks guys. They didn't know that. Well, you
can't, that's a, that's a very big blanket statement. I'm sure there's plenty of people
that don't like me, but I appreciate it nonetheless. All right. Good night guys.
See you later. Call your mother. Goodbye. See you Wednesday. See you later.