Zoe looks terrible in this poster. She looks huge. She's got the same body shape. She has the same body shape as a pyro.
Alright boo, introduce this. Death tool. Hell came to earth. These four are gonna send it back.
That was awful.
Why did you say it like the demo man?
I had like eight different accents.
Let's pull this off boys.
Alright, I'm a boomer. I'll do what a boomer is.
You don't want to return to lobby.
Oh, like ping? Oh, ping, ping, ping.
Like who cares?
Oh, I don't know if this is... Well, okay.
Do you got to change the server?
But Zoe looks terrible in this poster.
You know what? She looks like the pyro.
I hate you.
What a stupid comment to make. Looks like the pyro. Get out of there. Get out.
Death tool. Hell came to earth. These four are gonna send it back.
I can't wait to play both those back to back. Like I'm gonna show the first one too.
You are the worst.
Those things are pretty horrible.
Oh, is it really?
Our things are great.
Sorry, I'll say no.
Alright, we're gonna try this one more time and that's it.
I'm sorry that they're awful.
Oh, gosh.
Welcome to Left 4 Dead 2.
You know what? I really think...
You know, she really looks like the pyro in this picture. Don't you guys think that?
I mean, she looks exactly like the pyro.
It's crazy.
How did the hell they get... Oh, okay.
Yeah, buddy.
Oh, what the heck.
My ping is too high.
It did kick me out.
Oh, it's made me be the tank.
Your ping is too high.
My ping is too high as well.
I told you.
I told you we just need to play against other people.
I was like, I was wrecking some bulls as a tank.
Dude, I got disconnected.
Your ping is too high.
Well, that works.
You know, we definitely should hang up by the docks.
Only because they can only really come from two real areas.
Like they come from straight.
They can't like climb. What are you doing?
I wanna go for a swim.
What are you doing, you idiot?
Well, okay, that answers that question.
The dock is not safe.
What did you do?
I thought he was gonna at least like grab on.
We will eventually have to jump down.
I will come to the rescue.
Of anyone who gets pulled off the roof.
Alright, let's do this thing.
Stay together to survive.
I immediately regret going on the roof.
There's a charger up here.
When can they climb?
Oh, I just fell. Awesome.
Spinner, watch out for the Spinner.
Oh my god, there's so many.
Oh, you're inside now. I'm coming for the rescue mission.
Good thing I didn't like edit my volume.
And me shooting the gun is louder than my thoughts.
Hobby Hamburger saved you.
Hamburger.
There's a lot of fire on the roof.
Yeah, I accidentally created all of them.
Why is the burger joint on fire?
Alright, try and regroup. Get back on top.
Regroup, get back on top.
Alright, is this a safe time to alt tab?
So I can talk to people?
There comes a tank.
Hunter down there too, Hunter.
Oh god, the tank does not like me at all.
Alright, sacrifice yourself and stand in the middle of the open
so we can shoot the tank.
Let me just do that right now.
Hunter on the roof.
Tank is jumping back down.
Watch yourself, Boo.
Where are you?
The tank is made of bricks.
Oh, just keep running in circles.
It's not fire.
Yeah, I have two health.
Tank down, tank down.
Charger on me.
Protect us.
I am protecting the healer.
Alright, let's get back.
Take those pills and get back on the roof.
Secret ladder.
Wish I saw that earlier.
Are we all up here?
Yeah. We are now.
Nice.
I am going to heal up.
Yeah, heal up. We will protect you.
Hey, where do we get that ammunition stuff?
Down there.
Yeah, ammo is downstairs I think.
Okay, let me just go down there.
Yeah, thanks.
So far so good, so far so good.
We are alright here.
Halfway, towards like any sort of credibility.
Yeah, tank down there.
Tank coming up front, tank coming up front right now.
Oh, I am getting stuck.
Oh, I am on fire now.
There is a lot of fire.
Tank is up here.
Oh, he just clubbed me.
I just fell down.
Uh oh.
I am down the back side.
I need ammo, I need ammo so bad.
Oh, my tank.
No, give me the ammo.
Get the hell away from me.
You bastards, you rat bastards.
I am getting smoked, he is on the roof.
Thank you, nice.
Oh, 110 shock, oh my god.
No.
I will not die in vain.
I tried, Jerma.
There is a tank near you.
I am resisting.
I am alive, I am still alive.
Oh, you are in the spit.
I am going to throw the pipe bomb.
I am still, this is unbelievable.
I can't believe I am still alive.
Oh, there is a tank on the fence right there.
He is right behind me.
Wait, the tank was behind me?
The tank was behind me?
Thanks, bro.
Alright, let's get on the roof and evade all the zombies.
There is a ladder around here.
Hey, you guys got 40 seconds and we got the bronze standard.
I got hit by the tank.
And his rocks.
It is alright.
Did we both just throw a pipe bomb at the same exact time?
Well, it is double the amount of distraction.
I think I threw a pipe bomb.
Also, there is a big mean tank.
Oh, and a charger on me.
There is two tanks and a charger next to me.
20 seconds, 20 seconds, you can do it.
Oh god, not towards the water.
Run in as many circles as you can.
Approximately 10 seconds of circles.
Oh god, invisible wall.
No!
5 seconds!
At least we tried.
That's unfortunate.
I should have taken a spill or a swim.
Yeah, I should have just ran towards the water and teased him.