Hey, what is going on, everybody?
Jirba here with a Team Fortress 2 gameplay commentary.
And tonight, gonna be playing as the Engineer with the Southern Hospitality,
the Frontier Justice, and the Short Circuit. So,
what do I want to talk about in this video? You probably saw the title already.
You probably are wondering what the hell that means.
The TF2 movie, Valve working on a TF2 movie.
Let's back up for a second here, because this is some incredibly exciting news
that I got tipped off on a couple of days ago.
Somebody actually sent me a message saying this,
and I was like, really? Is this really gonna happen?
So, let me back up for a second. According to Valve,
according to Gabe Newell himself, he actually was on a podcast
no more than two or three days ago talking about this.
He said they are currently working on a Team Fortress 2 movie.
And he said that it initially started as a 90-minute feature-length film,
but they decided to scrap all that. They said that was a little too much work for them.
But my goodness gracious, guys, we are getting a TF2 movie.
Now, there is not many details about this, really, at all.
And a lot of us were wondering, back when they did the Adult Swim promos,
and when they started working with Adult Swim and Cartoon Network,
a lot of us were thinking, my God, are they gonna start working on a TF2 show
for Adult Swim or a TF2 show for Cartoon Network?
That's what was going through the cogs in the brains of a lot of us fans
and a lot of us enthusiasts of this game.
But nothing really ever came out. Nothing really came to fruition with that.
And I don't want to say that they might be working with Adult Swim,
because I don't know. I'm pretty sure, according to Gabe Newell,
that it's going to be in source filmmaker.
It's not going to be like a cartoon, an animated cartoon,
like an animated feature or something like that.
It's going to be in source filmmaker.
And it's going to be at least 15 minutes long, according to Gabe Newell.
So this could... I don't know what route they're going to take with this.
Are they going to set up a system where we could have potential sequels,
where this could be a monthly or a bimonthly, yearly?
Nobody knows at this point.
But all we know for certain is they are currently working on this.
And I want to get your guys' opinion on this, because this is huge news.
I'm actually pretty surprised that not very many people are talking about this right now.
This is massive news. This is not just a little thing like,
oh, you know, Meet the Pyros are going to be coming out at some point, like in the...
No, no, this is going to be an entire story.
It's going to be a beginning, middle, and an end.
A 15 to 20, 30 minute. Who knows how long they're going to make this.
But this is big deal. This is a big deal.
I don't know where they're going to go with it, though.
If you guys have any idea what they could potentially do,
are we going to start over with the Meet the Team videos?
Are they going to come out with like Meet the Engineer again,
but have it be 15 minutes long?
Are we going to get like new Meet the Team videos?
Or is it going to be, here's the team, you already met the team,
now here's what they do on a daily basis.
Like, oh, here's the engineer going and buying like a ham at the grocery store.
And there he is. He's checking out right now. $22.99.
Is that how much a ham costs? I don't know. Probably not.
It's probably more expensive. I don't know. I have no idea.
But anyways, where are they going to go with this?
I'm so excited because this means that not only is Team Fortress going to be as a series, a game,
but now it's going to be seen as an entirely new media.
It's going to be seen as a movie, as a television show, as a complete full force media front.
Team Fortress is not a game anymore.
It's a piece of freaking art.
And that's why I love this so much. Games are becoming not just video games anymore.
This is becoming whole series, whole entirely new ideas, new fronts, new media.
It's, it's, this is so exciting, guys, to see this because think about it.
Really think about this for a second.
This is probably going to be one of the first.
Well, actually, I guess you could say red versus blue and a couple others in the machinima category.
Because remember, not machinima the company.
I'm talking about the machinima, the term machinima, where you take a game engine
and you create some type of media with it, like a short film or a movie or a show.
That's what I'm talking about here.
And with something like this, when a company like Valve puts together these machinimas,
because essentially that's what it is, it's the source filmmaker.
They take their in-game engine and they make a movie from it.
If this takes off, if they for some reason blow out some deal
where they have like a 15-minute movie or like a 30-minute movie and it goes on Adult Swim,
or even if it doesn't, it doesn't even have to go on some major TV network.
It might just be on YouTube.
Nobody knows at this point.
But let's just say something like that happened.
Let's just say you see you turn on your TV in like a few months or six months or whatever.
Whenever they finish this damn thing, who knows when they're going to do that.
But let's say you turn your TV on and you see, oh, Team Fortress like 8 p.m., 7 p.m. Central Time.
Like make sure you tune in on NBC.
That is going to change the world because so many people that have never had any idea
what this series was or what this franchise was or what machinima is and what gaming videos are.
This could change the world, guys, when it comes to gaming content as art.
And we have been making strides.
I actually talked about this in a video before about video games.
They're not video games anymore.
We are not playing a video game anymore.
What this is, this is turning into a whole new form of expression, a whole new form of media.
And it is incredibly exciting to see that.
No longer is it just, oh, what's little Billy doing over there?
Oh, well, he's just playing that Super Mario, brother.
It's like, no, that's not what he's doing.
That's not it anymore.
It's not just pick it up for 15 seconds.
And did you beat the level?
Yes, you beat level two.
These are completely, this is completely changing the world.
And I'm so happy to see this, guys.
And that's my time.
I think I'm over talking now, but thank you so much for watching everybody.
This is exciting news.
If you knew about this beforehand, then awesome.
But I did not know about this till at least like three or four days ago.
So it's interesting to know that they're working on this and we're going to get a TF2 freaking movie.
It's actually going to be a thing, guys.
But yeah, I'll see you guys all next time.
And of course, thank you so much for watching and I'll see you all soon.
Take care, everybody.