Hey, what is going on, guys? Jerma here with a Team Fortress 2 gameplay commentary, a one-life commentary at that.
Gonna be playing as the Engineer tonight with the Default Jag, the Strange Frontier Justice and the Strange Pistol.
And before I get into any of this, do this, guys.
When you come out of the spawn, if you've got plenty of setup time, get one of your buildings built already out of the way.
Because then you can get a full Level 3 Dispenser or a full Level 3 Sentry.
Then you can just drag it out there, drop it down somewhere that you want it, and be fine.
A lot of people don't realize that just because the setup time goes down to zero, that doesn't mean anything.
It's gonna take the other team at least 10 to 20 seconds to get over to where your Sentry Gun even will be in the first place.
So it's alright if you're like, oh no, I don't want to do that because you only got like 4 seconds left on the clock.
Don't worry about it, you'll be fine.
And before we get into this gameplay, guys, I want to show you something that happened earlier when I was trying to play Sniper.
So I came into this gameplay, I wanted to play Sniper, I wanted to do a gameplay commentary for Sniper.
And look what happens right here, okay? This is ridiculous.
So right now, there's two Snipers right here, right?
And as anyone will know, it is very difficult to counter-Snipe two Snipers when they're both aiming at you.
So watch this. Aim down. I missed this shot, but watch right here.
Bang, headshot, doesn't kill him. Bang, headshot, doesn't kill him.
Like, wait, what happened right there? And then look at this!
There's four Snipers right here.
I was looking down the sights at a firing squad. They're all aiming at me. Look at how ridiculous that is.
I couldn't believe it.
So let's get back into the Engineer gameplay. I just thought that was insane, so...
Got my buildings all pretty much secured, need a teleporter.
Here is a tip for this spot. This is a great spot.
Build all your buildings back here, but leave enough room for you to fit back there.
It's really hard for a Spy to get back here and backstab you if you hang out back in this spot.
You'll see a couple of times a Spy will come back here, and he just gets screwed,
because they have to jump over things, they have to get really, really up in your face to be able to even get behind you.
But don't leave too much room, guys, because if you leave enough room for another person to fit back there,
you're going to get backstabbed. You want your back to be stuffed right in the back of the wall.
Also, make sure your teleporter is your number one priority in this type of situation,
because if you take a look to the right, that metal, there's 200 metal, like five feet away from me.
So my dispenser is not really that big of a concern. I want to get it up to level three, but that's not priority.
Get your teleporter up there first.
And here we go, here's that Spy I was talking about.
Notice how there's not any room back here for him to decloak and find a little situation where he can be safe.
He's stuffed in the back of the wall with all of us, so there's no way he's going to be able to do anything.
Where that situation goes really, really bad for most engineers,
is if that dispenser is five or six inches up from where it is right now, a good Spy will always kill you.
So if you are having lots of problems as an engineer getting backstabbed every single time you build a sentry,
or every single time you try to do something, try this technique.
You really want to stuff your back against a wall.
If you're against a wall, they can't do anything, they have to just shoot you with a gun.
Pretty risky move I just did right there, I pulled it off though.
Sometimes that works, sometimes it doesn't, but I am a risky bastard, you guys all know that.
What I'm trying to do right here is I am the only engineer on the team.
So if there is no structure, no defensive structure right there, they will just cap it with no problem.
Looks like they were going to cap it, so I brought it over there, want to try and get some defense on it.
It does a little bit of work, but you can't really be in two places at the same time.
I'm trying to be two engineers, and it just doesn't work out so well.
Sentry goes down, but I end up with a large amount of revenge crits, and I put them to very good use.
Just peeking around this corner right here, making sure no demo men or soldiers were shooting any stickies across the map,
because sometimes that will happen.
Sentry ends up going down, like I said, and I got the ten revenge crits, take out this heavy medic pair with a couple of shots,
miss this one, but he's running away, get him right in the back, boink, get the pyro as well, doing work.
So this part right here is an enormous mistake, I should not have done this.
What I should have done is gone right back to my sentry nest, make sure I can get some ammo, make sure build another sentry to full completion.
Instead, I'm trying to go for some shady business here, try to drop a sentry in the tunnel.
Look what happens, Spy drops a sapper on my stuff, I don't end up getting there in time.
Major, major mistake right there, I should not have been doing that.
Trying to get my nest back up to square one, get a dispenser, get a sentry.
It's not worth it though, they are encroaching way too far on this point right now, so I say screw it,
I'm gonna come out here and kill some people with my revenge crits, and I get a couple of kills, get that demo man, get that Spy.
Not going after a heavy, that's a dumb idea.
End up jumping down to this little area on the right side, see a Spy freak out for a second, and then these guys just kind of go in front of me.
They didn't even know I was there, and at this point right now guys, I am freaking out,
because look it, there's only one minute left on the clock pretty much, and there's no defenses here.
And they start to get onto the point, and I'm just like, oh my god, oh my god, oh my god, I gotta do something.
And it's all for naught, because I end up just dying right there, and that Spy saps the sentry, and they cap the point.
That is gonna be the end of the gameplay, the One Life as the Engineer.
Thank you so much for watching guys, I really do appreciate it.
If you liked this video, go ahead and shoot me a like, and I will see you all next time.
Take care, everybody.