How are we doing? Good afternoon. How are we doing? Good, good, good, good, good.
You are currently joining me and us for a Black Ops 2 tournament. It's being hosted by Myth.
I'm very, very scared. I don't... I played Call of Duty a little bit. I was a kind of a Call of Duty
player for... I want to say just to desperately make YouTube videos.
It's like, oh, I know. I'll just play like Black Ops 2 or something. And I made some terrible
fucking videos. I played for about an hour. This is the perspective that you want to watch if you
want to make fun of the streamer. If you want to ask like, oh dude, what the fuck is this guy doing
here? You know what I mean? I'll be the pin cushion today, right? If you want to come talk
shit to somebody today, just stay here. If I go 0 and 30, I'll get at least like a dozen kills,
okay? I can promise you that. I will accept... I will be the vacuum for all the negativity today.
It's going to be really fun. I'm actually excited. But I actually might surprise you. We'll see.
I might surprise you today. We'll find out. Currently just running around in the... We're
doing a free for all. Get the ear wig ready. Dude, I don't even know what guns to use.
In chat like 20 minutes ago, I was like, what's a good weapon to use? I don't know.
I genuinely have no fucking idea. I just have a rapid fire extended mags sub machine gun.
That's it. I'm just going to hold the button down. I'm going to play Pyro.
Can you guys hear the game? Let me see how we're doing here.
They just stuck with it. They would have gotten the big one and all even out.
We're still kind of preparing. Don't worry. I will show. I just got a kill. I actually just
got a kill. You just didn't see it. Should I even use grenades? All right. I'm good to go.
What's up, everybody? I'm just hoping to get one kill this whole entire event.
They're just updating it real quick.
Just want to make sure I was not behind. That was not me.
You just hear like... Are we playing zombies? No, actually, I don't know the format.
I think we met team. Team deathmatch. Domination, probably. Yeah, we're still preparing.
You have to play zombies. Wait, wait, wait. Do we have some advice here?
From experience, cigarette smokers perform 20%... I'm not going to read the rest of that.
Thank you for the comment, though. The game's too violent. I don't know if I can watch.
I think we're going to get started. I have... I don't know what to say.
This is going to be fucked up. Did they ban rivers of blood? Oh, yeah, it's banned.
We're missing a teammate? I'm pretty sure a couple people had to drop just because of the
change to this week. So we have a couple of new teammates, I think, from my understanding.
But we'll get started shortly. Somebody just dove out of the window.
I would be showing this, but I think we're going to restart the server, so... Oh, yeah.
All right, you know what? Do a prediction. How about this? Will I place at one point in the top
two of... No, top three of my team. Will I place in the top three point-wise on the team at any
point during the entire night? No, sorry, King. Who is he talking to? You! I'm talking to you!
So should we go to our team channels now? I think... Who's on team two?
I don't know. If you're on team two, let's hop down to team two.
Which is team two. Yes, chef.
Yes, chef. Event info.
All right, I'm in the team two lobby. All right, here. Let's start streaming, huh? What do you say?
Okay. Jerma. Hey! This is our first time playing together, I think. I know. Well,
wait. No, we did the battleship tournament. Oh, yeah. I totally forgot about that.
You absolutely destroyed me in one of our games. It was actually pretty close.
Pretty close, actually. How much of a Call of Duty guy are you?
I played when I was 13. Yeah. And that's about it. I'm kind of sad I couldn't get my
controller to work with plutonium, but... Oh, you were going controller.
Well, okay, this is kind of a weird thing to say, but if you use controller in this game,
you get aim assist. You do?
Yes. So like, your crosshair will just lock on to them. If you're like slightly off, it just locks on.
That seems amazing. I should plug it in. Does it work?
Yeah. If you can get it to work, it's definitely a lot better.
I first was standing still and I couldn't even kill him. I'm so bad at this game.
I can get it to like do everything, but walk around. What? Xbox controller?
I love the Switch controller. It's kind of weird, but...
Wait, you say Switch controller? Yeah. Yeah. I like the Switch Pro controller.
Oh, okay. I don't know why I was thinking about the... I thought you had Joy-Cons in your hand.
I don't know why for some reason. Oh, not that. I mean, the Switch Pro controller.
It's pretty much an Xbox controller, but slightly smaller.
Yeah. That's like the best controller that you mentioned it.
Yeah. I think I have one somewhere.
Yeah. It depends on hand size, but for me, it's like, I like the Xbox controller,
but that one fits my hand a little bit. So it's kind of...
Yeah. PlayStation 5 and 4? My thumbs bump into each other all the time.
Oh, God. Yeah. That's me with the PlayStation. Yeah.
Yeah. Not my favorite.
Not bad, but... Oh, you just got me. You got me right in the head.
It was in the head? Yeah. Amazing.
Okay. So, wait, have you played Call of Duty before?
That was pretty good. That was pretty good. Yeah. Just a little bit.
There's a cheese build in Call of Duty that used to be all the rage for highlight reels
called quickscoping, where you just get a sniper and you run around and try and snipe them really,
really fast. So you're a quickscoper?
Well, I like doing it, but I'm not good at it.
Dude, I had a... That's what you would see
in all the highlight reels, though. I had a video series on Machinima Respawn,
like 10 years ago, where I played Call of Duty. And it was...
You liked it. I mean, I was playing a character.
It was not really me playing. It was, but it wasn't.
Oh, right. This gun is disgusting.
What is this thing? Should I use this? Oh, that's an LMG.
Okay. I'm going to be honest. The guns I recommend is the Fall.
I think it's an assault rifle. That one's pretty good.
Yeah. Let me see. I got the PDW57, Scorpion, Type 25, LSAT, and the SVUAS. Are those okay?
Yeah. But I'm telling you, the Fall is insane. You're on my team, right?
Yeah. Yeah. Yeah.
The Fall OST or something. Fall OSW. It's an assault rifle. It's a single fire.
It's pretty much the best gun in the game. Oh, it's single fire.
Is this the game that had the akimbo... What was it? The akimbo scorpions or something?
Oh, I don't know if this specific one has it, but one of the Call of Duties has that, yeah.
I remember people were like, one of that bands. People freaked out over that.
Yeah. So the Fall is actually also banned. Oh, it's banned?
In the old tournaments of this game, it was banned because it's pretty much objectively
the best gun. It wasn't the least amount. When I go back, I might put it on. I might
leave and put it on. I would definitely put it on,
but I mean, it depends. If you're like a sprayer, it's not good for spraying.
Yeah. I'm kind of a hold the button down and hope that somebody dies.
Yeah. Yeah. So if you're a sprayer, maybe I'd go for like the AN-94 solid. I mean, honestly,
none you're using is pretty decent too. It's just reducing.
Yeah. So somebody in chat just copy and pasted this build and I just put it in here. I was like,
yeah, sure. I'll try it for a little bit. It was just a copy and paste.
I mean, I think the thing about Call of Duty is you can't really go too wrong because every
gun kills in like two seconds. Not even two seconds, honestly. So it's like just how it goes.
Kind of. Did the game start yet? Wait, we don't play. Oh, okay. I was like, wait,
we're playing. We only have you and me here. Yeah, we're killing each other. So
surely we're not playing yet, right? Hello. Hey. Yo. Oh, hey. We got half the team here.
Are you guys ready to win? Oh, okay. So we have half the team. Okay. Cool. So now I'm not in like
a huge rush to make class real quick. Yeah. I've got about maybe 12 total hours in Call of Duty.
I'm going to need a hard carry. Oh, no. That's more than me, honestly. So you know what? I think
I might surprise a lot of people, though, once I get in the game mode. You know, if it means
anything, I've never seen you be bad at a game before. I'm okay. I can be okay sometimes.
Is everything good on your end? Very humble. We got to play multi versus. Okay. Yes. I got everything
figured out. That's just mad at the resolution. Oh, okay. Is the resolution wonky? Yeah. You just
fix it in settings though. Oh, sick. Shit. Okay. Are we doing a server or custom class?
Uh, server. So if your classes have to be made under the ranked setting and then make your classes
there and then we'll go to server browser and then. Okay. Okay. Oh, I got a medal. Ooh. Wait,
Mithy, you're on our team? Yeah, I'm on your guys' team. Ooh. Let's go. Okay. So I'm kind of the
equivalent to John. And so I think it actually, the balance is actually pretty good still. Okay.
Cool. Cool. Cool. Ooh. I'm glad you're on my team. I just killed like four people with a knife.
Well, I'll make it five. Oh, I forgot the shotgun thing. Okay. The knife is an instant kill no
matter what, right? The Moss Borg. Yeah. The knife is an instant kill. It's kind of OP.
I just flashed myself. Wait, you're like doing drop shots and stuff. Jesus. Sure. You haven't
played this before. That's the first time I've clicked that button. I think the whole time we've
been here. Oh, okay. That's it's like a thing people would sometimes do. They randomly just
lay on the floor to try and dodge bullets and stuff. You're killing people that are AFK. No,
I'm not. Everyone's warming up. Yeah. Yeah. We're mostly just trying to get used to our key binds
and sensitivity. I mean, it's not like it started. It seems I am not the only spy. You know what you
could do? Make one of those ballistic knife, like running builds or whatever. Oh, you like
you shoot it out, right? Yeah. Yeah. I'm good. I keep hitting R with the LMG and that's not good.
I got to keep. I had to do that more often. That works it in control. When you start shooting
people like in what case and what scenario just anytime I'm firing at anybody, I just hit control
when I go down. Is that smarter or stupid? Bro, I haven't played this since 2012.
It's so funny. Half our team is just like, oh yeah, I played Call of Duty on the toilet one time.
It's like 2012 this game was released and I don't even think I played it on PC on top of that.
Yeah. Like all like console or something. Hey, it's all right. We have a couple people laying
on hard carriers. Yep. Yep. Yep. Yep. I'm really hoping I can lay. I haven't even gotten
warmed up yet. I'm still making my classes. Is scorpion any good? Should I try scorpion?
Oh, scorpion is pretty good. Yeah. It has a really good time to shoot super fast.
I think it's good. I could be. I haven't played this in quite some time. I'm never taking this off.
Bro, there's no way you just. You run out of ammo so fast. What happens if you run out of ammo?
Well, you should. Is that it? I think if you have scavenger on, you should be fine.
So the strat is to get someone else. Are we doing S and D? Yeah, what's the game? What do we do for
game mode? I'm guessing it's fivey five. So I'm guessing it's an S and D. Yeah. Right. Oh, no.
So just go to the tournament browser or the browser and then it's the server on there.
I think I'm going to use this. Sorry. Was that not the question that I come in?
All right. I was saying like the the this is times two. Oh, the game. Oh, so it's going to be
a hard point. Dom and S and D. Oh, OK. We almost ready, Kelly. Yeah, I'm almost done making my
classes. Sorry. OK. Well, that's really bad. Hello. Just hear me. Yeah. Yes. That doesn't
fucking my audio. My mic is like bugging. Should be fine, though. You sound pretty clean. You're
here. All right. Cool. I can hear you. All right. Let me make one more class just in case. And
then nobody spawn here. You don't spawn in line at line of sight. Oh, oh, all right.
I look like a fucking idiot. I I'm I'm baffled. I'm just walking into walls. I was testing
something. Look, what am I doing over here? I'm worse than a bot right now. I do like this gun,
though. I'm going to keep it. Yeah. This this thing, you just have to just let the game play
for you. Why are you using target finder? What's that? What do you mean? Do I have
target? What does that mean? I hope I didn't make a mistake or anything.
How has it been 10 years and some of these guns are still not fixed?
I mean, it's been 10 years and their game client has never been fixed.
I was like AFK making a sandwich. 360 no scope me. I got hit. My knife button is weird. I'm
going to change it. I'm just working on my sensitivity and then I'm ready.
OK, you guys get disconnected from the server. Use your radar last time. That didn't work
last time. Well, they don't work. Oh, my resolution. Oh, is it just mega fucked?
Oh, fuck. I'm sorry about that. So what is search and destroy?
I was I was played. It's kind of like Valorant. All right. For someone who would explain a game
mode to someone that's never played Valorant. So basically one team is defending a bomb site
and then another team is trying to attack it. OK, and the the team that's attacking has to plant
the bomb. And then if the bomb detonates, they win the round and the defending team has to defuse
the bomb. So it's like Counter-Strike. Oh, yeah. That honestly, that would have been such a better
example. And no response. Yes. Yeah, no response. So you die, you die. OK. Till the next round.
Counter-Strike is Valorant. I have not played Valorant. I played Counter-Strike maybe a little.
Why are you making fun of how I'm saying that Valorant? What's what's what's wrong with that?
Valorant. All right, Kaylee, is it ready to go? Please tell me everything. Did I get the kill?
That would have been funny on the screen. Is there any way that we can help?
Valorant. No, no, no, I got it. I'm figuring it out. I'm just kind of like
up like that. OK, OK. Well, we're just whenever everyone of you guys are ready,
let's go up to the team one and then we'll start up once everyone's on the server.
All right. So so are we playing on Newtown first? You know what you're doing.
Me? Who? Yeah, you know. Yeah, don't don't mean me. Yeah, you know what you're doing.
I mean, I played when I was like 13. So I mean, I've played once or twice. Like riding a bike.
Wait, Dean, you definitely know what you're doing, too, right? No, no, I missed like three
times. Are you using the DSR 50 or the ballista? It's one of the preset it.
You're using a preset. Yeah, it'll probably be. I wasn't trying to use a sniper like during this
situation. Yeah, I'm not confident to use anything that requires any amount of skill to aim.
Not now. Yeah, that's it's honestly respectable. I mean, I'll go in 20 and be the embarrassment.
Like there's no like prize money or anything, right? I mean, I think it's just fun.
OK, yeah, yeah, just making sure just it's bragging rights doesn't have to be for money.
It's for bragging rights. Oh, I mean, I already take a picture of me shooting symphony and killing
him for myself. You know, I'm just I'm trying to pretend to be dead. Oh, shit. Hello.
Just quickly, we're just checking that everything's OK. And does anybody need advice
or help of anything? I think I'm it's working for me. Yeah, my my resolution is not wanting
to do the thing. No worries. Do you want to I'm not sure if we can, but did you want to put
into the general voice channel and we'll try and get into well, I think we're watching your
screen, to be honest, so we could probably try and offer some help screen resolution.
Honestly, fuck shit. I mean, it's fine. Just I can count the pixels. I mean, if you want to
spend two minutes with us to see if we can sort it, that's fine. We're happy to do that.
Otherwise, if you're happy to play Minecraft on Black Ops 2, then you know, I really don't.
Wait, I'm being told to change it. Maybe it's that's probably a good shout.
Oh, oh, oh, wow. Holy shit. OK. OK, well, we figured it out. Cool.
It was like you put on glasses. Yeah, I'm going to jump scare strap. Yeah.
You guys have a good and enjoy. Thanks. Have you? Oh, no, that was the server. OK,
let's say you to tell me this is a good scrap. You just pretend to be dead and nobody even cares.
Oh, we got to start this. OK. Give me one second. I'm joining. Yeah, I just did the. Oh,
yeah. You too. Yeah, you too. Oh, I'm going to do this right in the fucking doorway.
You've heard that guy. I'm a fucking moron. Oh, no. How long were you there for?
I'm doing the jumps. Oh, wait, we're supposed to be up to the channel.
Just be like frozen that long. It's crazy. I'm doing the jump scare strategy. Oh,
what you doing over there? Boob's key. All right, we have everybody in the channel.
Are you ready? What's up, y'all? Yo, yo, yo.
OK, I think you just need to join the server and then we can start it.
That score that was sixty nine, sixty nine.
Sorry, I can barely hear anybody. What's up? It was crazy. Oh, shit. Whoops.
I think we're starting soon. Silence. Oh, I'm very ready.
This is going to be fun. This is going to be fun. OK, they had a game with confidence.
I don't think people know what the fuck I'm talking about.
I think people are just like, oh, that's the weird guy.
OK, well, I don't know what he's what he's what he's saying, but got him.
Um, is it the tournament server? Yes.
Is it the only one showing up? I want to make sure.
This is like fun. I'm having more fun than the tournament.
Oh, it is. It's the yeah, it's the only server we got.
OK, are we green light to start this bad boy up for game one?
Are we ready? Ready to go.
All right, I'm going to go confirm.
Let's go. Trying to make it look like I fucking no idea what's going on.
All right. Wow, I'm sorry.
It's going to start up here and then there'll be 60 seconds.
And then we just go to your team to go to team two.
Wait, what now? I think are we are we are we going here?
This is it right now. This is it. This is it.
All right. This is it. I got to go two headphones here.
All right. Let's go. Let's go team.
All right. What's what's the strategy?
Going with a cheese class to start. And if it doesn't work, I'll switch.
Oh, God.
Can I just tether to somebody that knows where they're going?
Oh, my God. Yeah, absolutely.
All right, I'm going to I'm literally going to walk just behind you.
Yeah, get my cover. Get my get my back up.
You got it. Let's go. We're playing.
We're playing hard point here. So this is there's going to be a little site
that we just kind of have to sit on. And if you get points, it's king of the hill.
Basically, it's not searching the story. It's not.
Oh, this is king of the hill. This is like this king of the hill.
Yep. All right. All right. Right.
Is it friendly fire? We got this. We got this.
No friendly fire. All right. Nades across. Nades across.
Oh, my God. Oh, my God. Let's go.
You said nades across and I just did it.
What? Yeah, my point is online.
And the guy just got insta killed. I got bodied.
OK, they got control. We got to take control of that.
Got a person off of it. Sniper in a window behind us.
Yeah, the spawns just constantly change.
Yes. Keeps you on your toes.
I hate to say it, but my settings fucking resets.
Let's go. Let's go. Yeah.
Honestly, if you just want to take a second in the game, like I don't feel free.
Yeah, I am right now. Yeah.
Oh, God. Not the shock.
I'm going to fucking mega sweat right now to get us some fucking points.
I have no ammo. We need stuns on Sightman.
Why is the motherfucker running around with knives? Who is that?
We're not going up. Next point online.
I got somebody. Nading the room.
I'm going to nade the room also. I'm not going to nade their spawn.
I'm going in for the point. Going around back.
Oh, he got a collab. What?
You got a collab. Are they upstairs?
Not one on the car. Oh, they're coming into the room.
They flashed me out. Oh, I got them.
Let's go. Where do I go?
And are they in a circle?
The left, you know, you don't.
He's camping behind the thing.
Did I get somebody?
They got hardpoint control still.
I'm nading it and I'm going in.
Oh, John is just sniping it back in their spawn.
Like a little bitch. All right, we got hardpoint, though.
Sorry, I freaked out.
You're good. Defend this shit.
It's comeback season.
All right, everyone's up. Buddha down.
We're good. We're good. Just pull together.
We can do it. We got it. We got it.
Yeah, we're getting the lead.
Wait, somebody's contesting me.
Oh, I got him. I smoked him.
Oh, Val's on a hardpoint.
No, he's holding the right spawn.
Yeah, dude, I can't get in there.
Okay, got him. Spawn's clear.
Going in for the point, coach.
Put me in, coach.
Oh, I got sniped.
I'm locked in right now.
Oh my God. John's just killing everybody.
Yo, Jerma, I'm trying.
I'm trying as hard as I can, baby.
No, I see you trying as hard as I can.
Hell yeah.
I don't even see where they're killing.
That's what I like to see, dude.
He's an FPS gamer.
I'm a gamer sometimes.
Hell yeah.
What matters?
Wait, they're ahead?
Yeah, but it's going to come back.
Yeah, yeah, we're going to come back.
We get this point.
So this point downstairs, careful.
We got control outside right now.
Second floor, second floor, second floor.
No.
There we go, there we go.
Oh no.
What is this, an FAL?
Oh my goodness, the whole team's here.
Take a point.
FAL.
Fuck, I'm off point.
Is it busted?
All right, point switch, point switch.
Yep, we got to get my way over.
We got to recap.
Yeah, they're on this shit.
Big ol' faxes.
Unlucky.
I'm 3 and 12, love my life.
Oh no.
Fuck it, it ain't over.
It's far from it.
We got a shot, we got a shot.
Yeah, still got a chance.
My game started off so bad.
Unlucky.
No, fuck that.
I turned around three times.
I don't know where I am.
Hey, hey, okay, we have to give them a little bit of hope.
You know what I'm saying?
Aim down, what are you stupid?
No.
All right, we got a point.
Yeah, yeah.
Oh my, so many stuns.
Recoil.
Yeah, we just got to fight for it and wipe them and then take a point.
Because they're just fucking going to throw stuns on that shit instantly.
I got one with me.
He's Buddha's cross.
Riding down on the ground.
Teen cross.
You got Buddha?
Not any good.
I'm going to get him right now.
I got you.
Go get him, yeah.
Go get him and then I'm going to push in.
He's dead, he's dead.
Excellent.
Got Ray.
Can you flash your own teammates?
No, it sucks.
I didn't get time to warm up.
Oh no.
Now we're good, we're good.
We'll pull back.
Start spamming.
What button is fucking default for nation?
I got point, I got point.
No, no, like a utility.
We're good, we're good, we're good.
We're good, we're good.
Big points on the board right now.
Big points.
I killed myself.
Somebody get in there, somebody get in there.
I'm holding, I'm holding long.
I'm holding long.
Next point, where's that outside?
All right, I got to pull it together here.
I got to pull it together.
Yeah.
We got, he got all of us.
Every single one of us.
All right, let's go, let's go a different way, you know?
Yeah, let's go, let's go.
Across.
I'm trying to get Buddha.
I can't move.
Got him, got him.
Oh, they're holding inside the house.
They're holding the house.
About to kick him for inside the house.
One outside by car.
Going inside of the house.
I'm fucking running right in there.
I got control.
One more, one more.
Right next to the house.
You stun-grenading fucking bitch.
I'm holding car, I'm holding car.
Yeah.
Dude, I'm going to fucking, who is that?
Hold that, hold that, hold that.
I got car.
How did I not get the kill?
I don't understand what the mathematical equation was.
That's a big three.
Oh, God.
Oh, it's four.
I'm back on point.
I didn't have any fucking bullets in my machine gun.
What?
Right.
Inside the car, inside the car.
Bitch.
Oh, God.
It's okay, it's okay.
Excuse me.
We can get this still.
I'll take it.
Oh, fuck, I can't move.
No, it's a stun-nade.
I'm tired of getting stunned.
Next point up.
Shit, Jermall, let's go.
Jermall, that's me.
What?
That's you, that's you.
Oh, I thought that was a bad guy.
Oh, they're all over that car, man.
We'll even fuck out of it.
I got to, I was, I started so well.
Come on.
They got one.
They got two players playing across, one going into our spawn.
Watch out.
Oops.
All right, point.
Yeah, we're back on point.
Second floor, second floor.
Oh, don't go for two back because you're flipping spawns.
Yeah.
So if we contain mid control and just hold them out and spawn, we should be fine.
Come on, we should be fine.
Next point up soon.
I couldn't see there's no smoke.
New point, our point.
All right, we defend, defend, defend.
I'm holding this fucking door.
Ain't nobody getting through here.
Chad, how the fuck do I use my goddamn stun-nade, man?
Oh, I didn't see him.
Flank, flank, flank.
Oh, I was out in the open.
Oh, it's four.
God bless.
Where are they at?
On point and they're spawning.
Across.
Oh, one is.
Gotta get in there.
I'm going in, I'm on point, I'm on point.
Fuck, he was behind me.
Nice, nice.
Oh, god damn it.
Nade it, nade it, nade it.
Oh.
Nice try, nice try, nice try.
It's the first game on.
Oh, god.
I got my settings figured out.
So we got the next one.
Hell yeah.
The settings.
All right, we're good, we're good.
Team one to talk shit.
Not bad.
That was not bad.
Definitely, we could have done worse, that's for sure.
Definitely gotta do tasks, Matt.
Should I stick with this?
No, I don't know.
Yeah.
So wait, are we going again?
Nice job.
Good game, good game, everybody.
You don't fuck with that, you don't fuck with that.
I didn't even talk shit.
I just went up there and said, good game, everybody.
That was it.
Nice, nice.
I didn't do anything else.
My god.
Is all good to go for the next one?
Yeah, I'm ready, I'm ready.
All right, let's run it.
I'll just do this.
What's the next game mode?
Let me double check real quick.
It is going to be...
Oh, god.
Yeah, where are we going?
Domination hijack.
Ooh, should I use that?
That's the one where you take the points, right?
Yes.
Basically try to hold what, A and B?
A and B.
How do COD pros do this?
I don't know, it's a tough game.
It's a very, very quick game.
We're having fun and I'm stressed out.
I can't even think about a goddamn actual...
Yeah, it's tense.
There's absolutely no way I don't have diarrhea later.
Like, there's no way.
It's absolutely guaranteed.
I'll go for A here if we want to send people to B off the rip.
All right, I'll go to B and I'll go...
You know what I mean?
Yeah, I'm going to just push B.
Yeah, yeah.
I'm going to go to B and just go...
Good strat.
Nice.
Oh, okay, they're hard pushed left.
They're going in, they're going in.
Roger, stun aiding B.
Pushing out left.
They're right in this little area here.
I can't see anything.
What?
I got somebody.
How am I still here?
Capping, capping, capping.
I'm holding...
I'm going to cap it.
Oh, no, I'm not.
I'm going in.
We got to get a wipe on them and then we got to go for it.
Oh, they're in the window up top.
Oh, they pushed through.
The fuckers.
Nading.
Got them out, got them off of it.
One is in our spawn.
They're behind us.
What?
Yeah.
Oh my God, the whole team's on B.
Excuse me?
Hey, this fucking guy's symphony, man.
They still haven't gotten B though yet.
We're still in this.
Yeah.
I'm going to go from the outside of the boat.
I'm going to get a little flank on.
They have somebody holding them across.
So as soon as you go to B, he's like...
I got those here, I got those here.
Yeah, I got them crossed.
Good shit, good shit.
All right.
I'm getting on site.
We're getting on site.
Oh, they just threw a nade.
Ready to play good D?
I got one that threw a nade.
Oh, it's half capped.
Fuck.
Oh, right behind...
Oh, wow.
You know what I'm going to do?
I'm going to go for C cap.
I'm on it, I'm on it.
I'm on cap and B, cap and B, cap and B.
I need some support.
Oh, I'm dead.
I'm coming.
I'm pretty low.
I'm going to stay alive.
That's all we're going to do is stay alive.
True.
I think they're going left heavy.
Yeah, no, that's all they keep going.
Not the head camera on the right side.
I'm going to look long.
I'm with you, okay?
All clear.
Oh, I almost got it.
Fuck.
On site, on site, on site.
Nade site, nade site.
Nading.
Oh.
Oh, I missed.
They're going to cap it, I think.
No, they're getting that.
No, I'm not.
I'm nading.
I'm nading, nading it.
Nice.
Oh, hit him.
Oh my God.
He's not dead.
Or spawn, or spawn.
I think we're going to flip.
Oh, they're at the right side, right side, right side.
I got to pull together here.
On the outside of the boat.
Got him.
Good shit, good shit.
All right, I got a...
I got three down.
Fucking the bitching window, man.
All right, good shit, good shit, good shit.
All right, I'm going to push through and try to hit B.
Hard right, hard right, hard right, hard right, hard right.
I'm watching them as they come out of the right side here.
I'm going to try to hold down.
We might be able to get on site a little bit.
Oh, there's somebody on our side, second floor.
Fuck you, John.
Oh, I hit him in the head.
I'm in our window trying to hold it down.
Behind, behind, behind.
That's on my own team, man.
Good shit, good shit, good shit.
I'm trying to hold for you.
I'm right there.
Fuck.
No, no, no, no.
It's okay, it's okay, it's okay.
I'm here.
I'm going to go inside mid to your left.
I got one.
Good shit, good shit, good shit.
Another time.
Now is our fucking time.
I'm pushing inside.
Behind, behind, behind, behind, behind us.
Behind where?
Behind B.
Our window.
I'm holding, I'm holding.
Almost there, almost there, almost there.
All right.
They're on top of our yacht, by the way.
I got him, I got him, I got him, I got him.
Oh.
Got one.
Where am I getting shot from?
Fuck.
Okay.
There's so many chairs in the fucking way.
Did you try to push around?
I got him.
Wait, we have sight.
Yeah, no, I got it.
Wait, that's good.
I think we could actually make a comeback here.
Let's hold on to it.
Oh, no, we didn't.
We didn't hold in long enough.
Oh, I did bad.
I was very bad.
No, it's okay.
We go other side.
Thanks for the raid, Connor.
So, you swap spawns.
Thanks for the raid.
Yep.
Currently playing Call of Duty.
I did much better last game.
I was in like second or third place on the team last game.
Nuketown was my map.
Somebody's just having a fucking match here.
Let's go.
Thanks for the raid.
Welcome, everybody.
I think all he's been, he's just been a little rat.
I'm going to hit C here.
I'm going to go long.
I'm going to try to play flanks like Sim did
and try to cut him off of his bullshit.
So, I'm going to just try to hold left.
The symphony is crazy.
No, no, no, no, no.
I'm going to fucking put an end to him.
Up the window.
Their window.
Their up window.
I'm taking A.
Yeah, do that.
And I'm going to go for B.
I got him.
Nice, nice, nice.
Got it.
Where are they spawning?
Oh, no, this is scary.
Well, we're going to triple cap.
Holy fuck.
Let's go.
Go, go, go, go, go.
It's XC.
They're behind, behind, behind.
They're near A, I think.
What's ours?
You got A and C.
I'm going to see them.
I got C, I got C, I got C, I got C.
They're capping B as well.
What the fuck?
Could you get them off?
Oh, wait, wait, wait.
He's going back to C.
He's back on C.
Back on C.
Yeah, see the soul.
What the fuck, man?
I'm on B.
Oh, shit.
I just don't know this map.
I just don't know where they're coming from.
Can they spawn behind us?
Not when we have, like, C cap.
They're just running here.
Look, we just need to have people on both lanes.
Oh, my God.
Second floor, second floor, second floor.
Across from theirs.
All right.
When you guys spawn at C, I want everyone to push out
of the right side for this next one.
They're inside of, like, the windows area
with the fucking mattress going in.
Yeah, somebody's holding in that little cubby.
There's two people in there.
We need to clear out that room.
We have to clear out that room.
Oh, they're on C.
They're on C.
They're going to make us flip.
Yep, they made us flip.
I'm going to take A then.
We have B.
I got that.
Right room is clear.
One more in there.
Oh, no, nice.
Nice.
All right, we're getting A, right?
I'm going for A right now.
I was.
I almost got A.
Two entering.
I'm on A.
Nice.
I don't know where anybody is.
I'm coming to help you.
Halfway, halfway, halfway.
They're wrapping around the side here.
Got it.
Nice.
I'm going to just help hold down B.
Yeah, hold down B.
Hold down B.
I'm going to look long.
On B, on B, on B.
Oh, one's on B.
On B, on B.
There's two of them on B.
Good shit, good shit.
God, good shit, you know.
Oh, God.
Capping.
Second floor, underside.
No!
Where?
Oh, just worse.
Oh, we got B, though.
We got B.
We're good.
Oh, they're taking B.
They're taking B.
Nade, nade, nade.
No, no, no.
I'm here, I'm here.
Nobody's here.
Oh, they haven't taken A yet.
Oh, they're on A.
They're on A.
They are on A.
Okay.
Wait, wait, no, they're not.
Long.
Wait, what?
I just got something behind me.
Yeah, he's coming into B right now.
He's coming into B right now.
We're good.
Okay.
We're clear, clear, clear.
I just got shot at A.
Yeah, we're good, we're good.
Yeah, I got shot at A.
They're taking A.
Okay.
Got him, got him, got him, got him.
All right, one's inside.
He's going to A right now.
He's going to A.
Oh, they're on B, man.
Good shit, good shit, good shit.
Anybody got a B?
Anybody got a nade on B?
Oh, shit.
Why did I throw the grenade?
All right, we're going to take it back.
We're going to take it back.
Shake it, shake it, shake it.
Go, go, go.
Oh, behind you in the fucking window house.
Oh, they're coming left side.
They're in the left house.
Yes, yes, yes, yes.
Nice.
They're back on though.
We just need a nade in there.
We just need it.
Oh, they're taking it back.
They're taking it.
Oh, God.
They're holding long.
Shit.
They're fucking holding that shit.
Damn it.
I'm playing so bad.
This dude is shot at 360.
Don't scope right now.
Jesus.
Oh, God.
Sorry, I had 13 kills.
Now this series.
Yeah.
So they took series one.
Oh, my God.
It's one of those maps where it's just there's so much sight
that somebody can just be like 70 and 24 down like that.
The right and left hallways.
Symphony is single-handedly carrying that team.
They're in a Jansport backpack right now.
I think all of us literally outfrag the entire team
if it wasn't for Symphony.
Hey, I did all right the first game.
Second game, I just kept getting picked off.
All good.
All good, all good.
I just looked like one of those people that was about to like
you knew that I was about to hold down the voice chat
and be like, hey, the microphone symbol
was about to appear above my head.
Maybe lost connection.
Good.
Holy, I need to seriously put on.
Just got banned.
No.
Wait, are you guys still on the server?
No, I'm not.
Oh, yeah.
No, Call of Duty is really fun.
I got to get like in the only way you can really play
Call of Duty is if you just don't blink for 30 straight seconds.
You know what I mean?
Like you have to lock in and just be like
it's the only way you can play that you don't take.
Oh, game crashed.
Oh, hold on.
Crash.
But you just have to sit there and be like.
It's like you just see like the matrix symbols.
Okay, I'm going to open it back up.
Yeah, the second you blink and Call of Duty
is when you're at the response screen.
Stop, you're embarrassing this community.
Nobody can hear me.
It's just only you can hear me.
You're embarrassing yourself in front of you guys.
I like popped off in that first game, though.
I did.
I got to get that back, right?
You got to get that Cod mindset back.
And it's called don't fucking throw grenades
and walk into the room, right?
Like I've done that like three times.
I'm going to try this weapon.
We're back in, right?
We're back.
Oh, my God, I'm terrible.
Maybe just turn my sensitivity down.
You guys remember when I hosted the 13 and 7 kill command gameplay?
In like 2013.
Oh, I thought there was somebody lying there.
Yeah.
Yeah, I think I remember.
Oh, shit.
Sorry.
I thought I was muted.
Oh, no, no, you're fine.
You're oh, you were talking to chat.
I was just talking.
Okay.
No, that's fine.
I was just I was like, I don't it's a long time ago.
So you play multiverses, right?
Yeah, a little bit.
I'm not great at it.
What do you like the first?
Oh, what's up?
What do you play with?
Oh, Shaggy.
Kind of cool.
It's a good pick.
It's the only fighting game I've ever really gotten into.
I feel like Smash was too complicated for me.
Yeah, no, it kind of is a little too many.
Too many particle effects, too.
I feel like there's a steeper curve when you first learn Smash kind of thing.
There's also like 150 characters, right?
So yeah, learning what every single person does is kind of hard when you,
you know, there's like 80 characters.
There's a lot of headshots and no kills.
Switch the gun.
Knife.
Does this gun suck?
Okay.
All right.
This is chat makes my gun.
Okay.
Chat makes my gun.
You've seen how I play.
You've seen how, what I do.
I need you guys to, I'm going to make, I'm going to go class.
Okay.
Please help me.
Please.
Okay.
We're going to go here.
Let's just take this.
What should I use?
I'm seeing a lot of MP7.
MP7.
Every time I get a knife, I think of Among Us.
One's in the chat if I should, if MP7.
Definitely, definitely what I think of too.
Or MSMC.
I'm seeing a lot.
You know, you're joking.
MSMC.
If it's from the back, it kind of reminds me of, yeah.
Okay.
I've seen a lot of, I've seen a lot of this.
What attachments for the MSMC?
Yeah, Jeremiah, you almost ready?
Or are you doing some class stuff?
I'm just changing class.
I'll be maybe two seconds.
Okay.
It's all good.
Just whenever, just whenever it is that you're ready, join the server and I'll know.
Yep.
To run it out.
All right.
Attachments.
What am I putting on this?
Long barrel.
Okay.
And laser, laser and laser sight and long barrel.
What about perks?
Quick, hurry, hurry.
They're waiting on you.
Ghost.
Lightweight.
Okay.
Toughness.
Scavenger.
Okay.
And hurry, hurry, hurry.
Tactical mask.
All right.
Dexterity.
And that's it, right?
We're done.
We're good.
That's it.
All right.
We're good.
What's this?
Oops.
Where we going?
Okay.
Go, go, go, go, go, go.
I'm ready.
Okay.
Let's go.
All right.
I'm coming back in.
Chad has a good selection for me, I guess.
Yeah.
I mostly just left mine the same.
This thing's a piece of dog shit.
Thanks, guys.
They made...
Let me change one thing.
What would they make you do?
Can you just make...
Okay.
Sakuna, they said the M...
What's this thing called?
The MSMC?
Yeah, that's a good gun.
Oh, okay.
That's pretty good, isn't it?
I think.
With a long, long barrel and...
Long barrel and laser sight.
Laser sight.
No, maybe I'll try that one, too.
Oh, all right.
And it's...
Yeah, I mean, if Chad said it's good, it's got to be.
I usually trust him.
Chad's never wrong.
That's got to be.
I'm going to try it, too.
I love these stuns, man.
They last 10 years, I swear.
Team, you guys good to go?
Yep, I'm ready.
I think so, yeah.
All right, cool.
Starting it up.
Somebody said, why are there NFP ads on my stream?
There aren't.
What are you talking about?
Right.
If we hold mid, this is the easiest fucking one of our life.
All right, let's go for it.
All right.
Let's get it.
Mid control.
Play your life and control mid.
Name of the fucking game.
Let's get it.
If I die three times in a row, I'm changing back to my tried and true.
Yeah, same, same.
We're both trying the MSC thing?
Yeah, MSMC with long barrel and laser sight.
I'm doing that early.
That'll work.
84, 89?
94.
Okay, so the laser sight, I'm assuming you don't scope in anymore or...?
I don't know.
Oh, baby.
I want to get a fucking cross map, Nate.
Set us off right, you know?
You just throw the Tomahawk.
Cross map.
Me too.
Is that mid cap first?
I got traded.
Holy fuck.
Watch that left side.
Nated.
We got control left.
I'm going mid here.
I just couldn't see.
Point in the back, point in the back, point in the back.
Nice.
I feel like we flipped spawns, right?
Oh my god, the stuns.
We did, we did, we did.
The stun.
I'm holding mid.
Got one.
Let me know if you guys need cover right.
Watch out, we're on the fountain.
Got him, got him, got him.
Good, good, good.
I think we flipped again.
Symphony, suck my dick, bitch.
All day.
On these fucking nuts.
Where's the ammo in...
I sound like a baby.
I spawn on new...
Mommy, where's my ammo?
Where's the ammo?
He's pulling it back out of the fountain.
I'm on point, I'm on point, point, flip, point, flip.
I got you, I got you, I got you, I got you.
He's gonna be left side.
This is good for us right here.
Stuck this dick, Simp!
Hold that fountain.
I got you, I got, I got, I got point, I got point.
All day.
Hold that concussion, bitch.
Behind, behind, behind, behind.
Behind point.
Oh, are they moving?
Fuck, they got point.
Up 40, let's take that shit back.
I'm down to take it from street.
The left side with Shikuno.
I'm with you, Syke.
Yeah, I don't see it.
All right, I hear somebody over here.
Oh, that's two.
Jesus, Symphony's crazy, man.
Point flip, point flip.
Oh, right here, right here, right here.
I got him on a leash, Syke.
I got him on a leash.
I'm behind.
Got one.
I got two in that room.
Good trades.
Nice, nice.
I just watched you do that.
I'm coming to help point.
Oh, he's on point.
I can cuss one.
Behind the truck.
Behind, behind, behind.
Oh, yep, it's Sim right there.
Nading site.
Let's wait till we all respawn and make a push together.
All right, let's do this.
We're grouped.
Got one, I got Sim.
Good shit, let's go.
One back, three back in the right side spawn.
Oh, I got hit right in the fucking head.
Why what?
Oh, no, Blau just teared us apart.
Hardpoint switch and going offline in 10.
We play for the next one, which I think is mid.
So let's just get mid control right now.
Fuck this next point.
Or fuck the point that's currently up.
I'm on it, I'm on it, I'm on it.
Mechanical damage, I'm dead.
All right, rolling with you.
I see where they're rotating from.
Oh, I need to switch gun here.
Let's go, Dean, I'm on you.
I'm with you, I'm with you.
Yeah, I got you, I got you.
I'm on nade in the side.
Together, bro.
Oh, my God, was he in that room?
Oh, nade inside, though.
Oh, he was holding that.
He's in the back.
He's in the back alley, back alley, back alley.
Got one.
Okay.
Oh, God, the stuns.
I'm going.
Oh, shit.
What the fuck?
Where did he come from?
One coming in.
Nice.
P.O.P.
Let's hold this shit down.
Yeah.
I'll watch the back side.
Got one.
He went back alley, back alley.
Symphony went back.
There it goes.
Roger.
Oops.
I got blah on it.
Nice.
We're up, baby.
We're up.
All right, we got to take over mid again.
Back left.
Oh, God.
Okay, I'm going to push out mid here.
Yikes.
John, your fucking knife, man.
I'm nading.
They're like, I'm sorry.
I just ruined you.
Sorry.
No, it's okay.
God damn it.
I'm being so careful.
And all of a sudden, I get instantly killed.
Got another.
He's back.
It's clear.
Got another.
One more, one more.
On side, on side, on side with us.
I cleared, I cleared, I cleared.
All right, good, good, good.
Coming left, left side.
Oh, no, I'm stunned, I'm stunned.
It's all right.
We got points still.
They're just mad stunning that bitch right now.
We just get off for a second.
Got one.
Got another, switching guns.
Fuck me.
I'm nading.
Back on point, baby.
In that house.
Oh, I just got murdered.
We're still in the lead.
We're good.
Pushing out.
All right, we need, we need to, yeah.
Fuck, I got, I got demolished.
Oh, it's Anthony who's holding that door.
I'm rocking with you, Sakuna.
Let's do what we did last time on the streets.
Anthony's holding right if we're pushing towards it.
Yeah, yeah, let's go left then.
Blasted, Mike.
Wow, holy shit.
He's holding this door outside of the market.
Electronic shop.
Oh, got a hit with that stun.
Got a hit with that stun.
Oh, oh, oh, they're very, they're very concussed.
Nice, nice.
All right, next point going up.
Should be what?
Electro right here, right?
Oh, yeah, back here.
Stem is on it.
Oh, bro, where are my bullets going?
Where?
Oh, why did my gun switch?
I got, I got blowing on site.
Okay.
Oh, God, there's somebody holding it back with a knife.
All right.
One got stun, one got nade.
Swinging, reloading.
What?
Reloading, and then I'm going to, I'm pushing into site after this.
I got him, I got him, I got him.
Let's go, Dean, let's go, Dean.
This is it.
We got you, Dean.
We got a fucking knife, man.
Oh, this fucker John is playing like a rat.
All right, next point coming up.
Oh, God, I just got lased.
It should be mechanic shop on the left side of the, yeah.
God!
Watch out behind us.
I'm never inviting another fucking OTB member to this.
So the fucking, this is mad shit ever again.
Oh, my God.
Going through the fucking content knives, dude.
Fuck off.
I don't care.
I don't give a fuck.
I couldn't even see where I was.
All the way in the back.
I got sim, I got sim.
It's fucking free.
Go in.
I don't know.
Go in, you dumb bitch.
You fat ass character model.
Oh, my God.
Why can I go in there?
It should be mid.
Stop feeding.
I can't help it.
You just ran out, jumped, sprayed in.
Come on.
So remember, this mode, it has no time limit.
So we can still come back.
Oh, fuck.
Okay, next point.
It's mid.
Where?
Mid, mid, mid, mid, mid.
How did I not see him?
I've got metal gear solid NPC vision apparently in this game.
Oh, sim is going in the middle right now.
I'm holding right.
Oh, God.
He's very nice.
Nice.
Don't somebody's next to me.
Oh, God.
All right, I got you with defense.
I got you with defense.
Oh, God, I'm so stunned.
I'm so stunned.
No, no, no, I got you, I got you, I got you.
I got you, baby.
He's on the other side, other side.
What the fuck?
He's on top.
We fucking got this.
Another one, another one.
Oh, my God.
There's another one prone.
It's okay.
We got this.
Our point, our point.
Yay.
Oops.
Oh, nice, nice, nice.
Nice.
All right, all right.
Keep it, keep it, keep it, keep it.
Next one.
Yeah.
Yeah, next one comes up.
We got to start defending for next one.
I'm going for the next one right now, I think.
Yeah, they're already rotating toward it.
Oh, my gosh.
You sent me to the back, right?
You sent me to the back.
I got it.
Yeah, I got it.
Oh, fuck.
They don't have stairs yet.
Oh, no, there's somebody behind me.
Running.
I'm busting through.
No, oh, dude.
Oh, my God.
I feel like it's so much closer than it is.
I just died so fast.
It felt like it was pretty close.
It was the jammed support backpack of Symphony, man.
Nah, but like.
No, it is.
Bro, brother, look at the kills.
Yeah, but I'm right there.
I'm toe to toe.
We got more kills than them total, I think, bro.
They're fucking nice on objective play right now.
Legit.
I think we're actually, we have more kills total.
Oh, yeah, you're right, you're right.
Next one, SMD.
It was a good round.
That's what I'm saying.
We're out fragging them.
It's Symphony.
Hard carry.
Unbelievable.
I'm going to have Brooke like unplug the internet real quick.
Have Symphony route through the VPN to like around like a circle around the globe
and then hit back to here.
Give Symphony like 400 ping.
One, two, one, two, four, five, one, two, three, four.
So much change in their class.
I'm going to go yell at them.
Feel free to come with me and talk shit.
What's next, anyway?
Hold on.
What's up?
I'm just adjusting.
I'm just adjusting stuff.
Chats, chats, metagaming for me.
Did you call me?
Yeah, I called you.
What the fuck?
Hi, coach.
How's it going?
It's going awful.
I don't like you.
What's up?
It's going great.
Master Yoshi.
I do not like you.
What did I do?
What the fuck?
You fucking, you got your little knife hiding in a little fucking corner.
Dad, you don't like my jet belt?
He's a gentleman.
What do you feel strong?
Are you low playing as jet and call of duty?
What the fuck?
And then I'm double smoking site and then I flash it and then I go in.
I'm gonna blow up my house.
I can't escape the Valor, man.
I have an itch.
Okay, it's not my fault.
What the fuck?
It's a problem.
I know.
I'm aware of it.
Jet.
Hey, Sim.
What's up, buddy?
Yeah, you like that?
You like that map a little bit more?
Yeah, I started calling out, bro.
You should have heard my comms.
Oh, crap.
No shot, man.
It looks like I so badly want to participate in like the trash talk,
but I just like don't know how.
And I just I just want to be heard on everybody else's stream.
You know what I mean?
Like, what the fuck?
It's me, Jerma talking by the way.
It's Jerma985 talking.
I just like so badly want to be on other people's streams.
That's like what I'm doing.
That's what that is.
I just like want to be heard on that stream.
All right.
I'm going to get 20 kills next game.
Just you watch.
No, GG though.
GG indeed.
Next game.
Oh, I think we're going to do.
We're going to do SND next map.
That'll be interesting.
That'll be really interesting.
Yeah, I think SND will be a lot of fun.
Let's do this.
Fuck.
By the way.
I'm pressed after that last one.
I'm not even going to front.
For those who don't know.
For those that don't know.
Honestly, you guys had a good lead for a minute.
I was like, oh, fuck.
I'm the sus guy.
For those who don't know.
I'm fucking muted, guys.
Relax as a joke.
I didn't do that.
I've been muted almost the whole time.
Don't you get it?
I would never do that.
That's so stupid and embarrassing.
Why would I ever do that?
I honestly, I'm going to sound like a fucking weirdo.
I wouldn't do that for 10 grand.
I don't think so.
If it was like, hey, dude, I'll give you $10,000.
If you announced to all these streamers that,
hey, just in case you guys want to know.
I'm the sus guy.
And like, don't make it a joke.
I wouldn't do that for 10 grand.
I wouldn't do it.
Or I might.
All right, we're going to run it up.
Next one is SND, by the way.
God.
Can I change my my loadout really quick?
Hold up.
Do it for free.
I thought this was Michael Myers.
I thought that was Michael Myers.
I was like, what the fuck is that?
I don't know.
But the more that I think about it,
would I want to make all these other streamers think
that I was like this fucking nerd?
Like trying to be wicked funny.
Like, shut up.
Shut up, dude.
Get out of the lobby.
Fucking get out of here.
I think I'm ready.
Yeah, I think I'm good to go.
You guys want to want to make it crazy.
So this is search and destroyer?
Yes.
And then so we're just doing something with the class
and then we're running it.
I'm done.
I'm ready.
Oh, I'm going to use the weapon I had before.
I feel like I was better with it.
It's going to be same.
Same.
I want to be honest.
I switched to the same gun that Symphony uses
in hopes of being almost as good as he is.
Oh, I hope it works really good.
I'm using it.
Yeah.
Yeah, that's what it seems like.
Guys, what SND maps are new Plaza or Raid?
Raid.
I don't know.
I was just good, but it's just really it's just really big.
Raids.
Raids a throwback.
Raids the throwback.
Raid is a throwback.
Let's see.
Raid SND.
All right.
Stuns got me moving in slow motion.
Got him.
I feel like we're going to win this one.
Yeah, surely we'll win this.
Surely.
For all I think we're not putting up a bad fight.
No, I don't think so.
Yeah, we can't win it.
This game is fun.
It really is.
It's just so hectic and fasted.
Oh, here we go.
So is this a big map like long range or short range?
Long range.
Now that I copied Symphony's gun, surely I'll be half as good.
So is this it?
They're going to fix it.
Oh, okay.
Yeah, they're going to fix it.
Yeah.
Am I bugged?
My scope doesn't work.
Oh, yeah, because everyone's lagged.
Like definitely having some kind of sites.
Say la la into the lobby.
I wouldn't do that 10 grand.
No, is it up yet or is just me?
No, it's not up yet.
They're restarting the server, I think.
So is this so with this, this is going to be search and destroy, right?
Yeah.
So when you're dead, you're out.
So we've got to play careful.
Yep.
Make sure you play really, really careful.
Goku.
Is that a is that a Dragon Ball line?
Yep.
That's a Mr. That's Mr.
Safe Dragon Ball.
Wait, what?
No, no, no, no, no.
Really?
Never watch Dragon Ball.
You're lying.
Not lying.
Is that bad?
I mean, it's bad.
How old are you?
Oh, 23.
23.
Yep.
I Dragon Ball.
I mean, like Dragon Ball Dragon Ball or any.
My parents should have had me earlier.
28, bro.
Why the fuck that?
What the bro?
What the?
That's 28.
Bro, I thought you were 28.
Come on, man.
Oh, shit.
I look like a boomer.
I thought you were 28.
How old do you think I am?
Let me take a guess.
28.
25.
Who's closer?
You are both very far away.
No way.
Incredibly far away.
18?
Incredibly.
No way.
18?
Way higher.
Oh.
38.
A little bit lower.
35.
A little bit higher.
36.
Yep.
That's it.
Wow.
I would not have guessed.
Well, I mean, yeah, I didn't guess.
Don't tell anybody that, though.
I don't know if you guys are streaming.
Hopefully, you're muted.
I keep that.
I don't know.
I say I'm 32.
I've been 32 for the last five years.
I feel like after a certain age,
it feels all about the same.
Eating the same oatmeal.
Yeah.
After 30, it's just like whatever.
I always thought when I was like 25, 28,
I was like, oh, man, I don't want to turn 30.
No, fuck.
I'm going to be so old.
Anyway, I dreaded it.
Like, you know, did you used to be a cod YouTuber?
No.
Why?
You used to be a League of Legends YouTuber.
Chat's lying.
Chat's just camping.
I'm 29, bro.
Yeah, don't worry.
After 30 doesn't matter.
I used to be a League of Legends YouTuber back in the day.
Solid duty.
I mean, that's pretty different from cod.
Yeah.
I mean, I played it before, but I wasn't like a cod YouTuber.
That's for sure.
All right.
We're good to go.
Am I in the game?
Am I?
Why are you?
I was just spectating for some reason.
I don't know why.
SNG, baby.
Remember, the secondhand embarrassment is killing us.
Stop.
I'm muted nine out of 10 times.
We get video once.
We're just having a good time.
Relax.
I've played before, but.
Secondhand embarrassment.
Hey, well, then good, because my tweet, that's what you're here for.
Yeah, I mean, I've played the game before, and that's like, and like, not even a lot.
Like, maybe once.
That's about as far as it goes.
You're clapping them, though.
You guys think I'm saying half of this stuff into the public lobby here?
I think anyone who would call me a cod YouTuber is
got to be horribly confused.
Gotcha.
All right.
Maybe we should split up where we're where we defend.
I'm thinking we would go like to to to a to be Dean and Saikuno a a a.
All right.
Alien.
Alias.
Sounds good.
Rotate.
Wait, Valorant.
Valorant.
Oh, he's your juice then, right?
I think that's good for.
I hope I hope I hope.
I'm pretty sure that's.
Yeah, that's like long, long sites and shit.
Let's hold the bombs down and let's fucking let's clap these kids.
Yeah, I'm not afraid.
I'm not afraid to take a stance.
Oh, oh, we have no one on B.
We're heading over there.
It's a first floor.
They're on B B planning.
Yeah.
Oh, I'm dead.
Thank God they're on B.
Oh, I just didn't get it.
I've never played this game mode.
I just got shot from the second floor.
Didn't even see him.
I've literally never played search and destroy ever.
Fuck one inside of a window B.
I'll just do.
Yeah, I'm dead.
Turning corner with a grenade.
My eyes closed.
Besides, I think we're attacked now.
I'm not going to lie.
They're literally playing this like Valorant and not like S&D.
I don't think I've ever had it.
I don't think I've ever played an S&D thing where people just instantly went and planted.
We gave them B site, though.
We had no one there.
Just thinking bomb.
All right.
I'm thinking I'm thinking we try to like work A here.
Do I have to be holding this?
They're going to be holding this hard.
Just rush in guys.
Just full speed blast kind of thing.
One's on the rocks.
I have mid control.
They're on A.
Hold up.
They gave me a lot of space here.
Could we get bombed down?
Yeah, putting it down.
Doesn't matter where.
Basketball court.
Nope.
All right, it's done.
Oh, my God.
He knifed.
I got one.
They're playing up.
How many do they got left?
One.
Nice.
One's prone.
That's John.
He's only got a knife.
Where?
He's he's he's proning next to the I don't know.
Is he happy with whatever?
He fucking did it.
I died with a knife.
He shot.
What the fuck happened?
He hit you with the ballistic knife.
Why?
Let's go.
Yes, we got it.
Oh, my God.
Oh, God.
Here's this fucking ballistic knife.
Jet main, dude.
He's actually playing like he's jet.
It's so good.
He peeked around the corner and I just went like it's dead.
All right.
Let's make sure.
Let's have some B defense at the start here.
Nice.
I'm going to hold A like you said earlier.
I like this.
Yeah.
I'm on A.
I think they're pushing B hard.
Yeah.
I'm in the window.
That's them.
They just leave mid open.
I have a hot flank.
Yeah, I'm working.
I muted.
What am I doing?
The grenade.
Let me run around the corner with a fucking.
It's a FPS video game.
Single player.
I'm the enemy.
Moving up.
That's what they do.
They come around the corner and they fucking lob it like a softball.
Let's go.
We got it, baby.
Let's go, baby.
Nice job.
Let's go.
One up.
We're S&D'ers.
Look at this shit.
Oh, man.
I'm not going to lie to that initial burst right there.
Yeah, we're not talking about that, but you know.
That shit was clean, my boy.
Thank you, my boy.
Come on, let's get two up.
All right, let's go.
Let's go.
What do I got?
Zero kills.
They leave mid dead open, bro.
It's literally a glitch.
Everyone mid.
Everyone made it.
Wait, no, no, no.
Okay, fuck it.
We got it.
Yeah, this is where we're going to be.
Oh, here's mid this time.
Good job.
Let's go B.
Yep, yep, yep.
Window, window.
I'm watching it rotate.
I like regenerate or something, right?
I mean, I think.
I'm scared.
Yeah, you're regenerating, I think.
That's okay.
All right.
I think we go bomb A.
Go bomb A.
Go bomb A now.
Oh, God.
I'm dying, man.
I'm dying.
I just don't know where anybody could be.
A game like this, you need to know where people can come from.
And I just put a fucking bat on the ground.
Put it on my head like this and just went in a circle.
Spin, spin, spin, spin, spin, spin.
Sick.
All right, where is he?
Where's the bad guy?
I don't see the A player.
We step outside.
They have one left, just sim.
Basketball court, basketball court.
Okay.
Yeah, let's go.
I'm sorry.
I'm an idiot.
Okay.
Oh, it was the basketball court.
Sakuno taking out symphony.
Oh, there it is.
The 1v1 challenge.
There it is.
Just peeking him.
That's great.
Isn't it so funny that they're not hearing me freak out every time?
All they're hearing is like, let's go.
Oh, sick.
Keep this shit hot.
All right, I hear a lot of stuns, eh?
Yeah, I'm looking.
I'm here to help you defend.
Let me know if they hear push up.
I'm going to watch mid still.
They're smoking, probably planting B.
That's all right.
It's a B rotate.
Behind, behind, behind.
In our spawn?
That was weird.
Fuck, man.
Is there a head there, man?
I just have no idea where people can come from.
Don't look at your teammate.
Guys, I don't know even where to walk.
Fuck.
Oh, shit.
He was the nicest guy.
It's close.
I didn't even see him.
Yeah, NT, NT.
It was three of them up.
It's okay.
We got this.
Somebody said, what the fuck?
Call of duty.
10 year old Andy.
I think it's a first to six.
Do you mean the game is 10 years old
or you mean calling me a 10 year old?
Because this game's fun.
PK again.
I got the bomb.
Oh, two fucking peeking mid.
One A window.
Symphony's pushing B.
He's probably going to try and go flank.
What the fuck?
I'm so confused right now.
That's me, that's me.
He's in the building.
I can't play.
Why do you guys think
I've never played Counter-Strike?
Ever.
And Valorant?
I won't even open it.
I don't want to die.
I'm dead.
Oh, Dean.
I whipped so hard, bro.
I didn't come in there.
You know, I'm going to pretend
I totally didn't see that.
Nice job.
There it is.
Hey, hey, but the comms though.
But the comms though.
You know, sometimes,
you know, it'd be like that sometimes.
Everyone has one.
Yep, it happens to the best of them.
It really does.
Only up from here now.
Wait, wait, I hit rock bottom?
I don't know, man.
Let me chow mid.
One's going A, one's going A.
I didn't see anybody.
They got like two mid control.
I'm going to go help out A.
You go B, K.
Thanks.
Yeah, let's go, let's go, let's go.
B, B, B.
He's down.
I don't see anybody at B yet.
A window, A window, A window.
Behind you, behind you.
B.
Oh, fuck.
Two mid, one mid.
One in that window.
I think Syke could be like in our spawn and shit.
I don't know.
They're on B?
B, okay.
Where?
He's tapped out.
I hit him a bunch of times on B.
There's one left.
Just mass, just John.
He's behind van.
Blue van, blue van.
Let's go, Jerma.
Let's go.
Good shit, K.
Here we go.
You got to do a 360.
Why are you doing it?
Because that's how the cool people do it.
Facts.
Not a controller player.
Somebody said, dude, you got famous on FPS games.
This is like 12 years ago.
People didn't even know how to tie their shoes in FPS games.
Yeah, of course.
I was fine back then.
I'm on the leaderboard.
Hacker who?
At least Jerma is out fragging Buddha.
So web that for us.
I did okay in that last round, I will say.
No one's peeking mid.
That's us.
Oh, I need to grab bomb.
I'm going to grab bomb for us.
Yo, let's end this shit right here.
Let's play safe.
Let's play tight.
Let's play right.
I'm going to go A with bomb.
Once I got him up a few times.
There's somebody on the right side.
I'm going to push out here.
Careful.
There's one.
He might have backed off.
B ball, B ball.
Yeah.
No, he's he's up in the corner out there.
At their window.
You'll see him to your right.
Yeah.
As my first YouTube videos, I had like boogers coming out of my nose.
You whacking son of a bitch.
It was a different world back then.
If we had some held there, you won that.
I was just like.
Hey, guys, I'm playing as the spy, I think.
I don't know.
Whatever.
All right, bro.
Let's get the all orbs.
Our defense is too mean.
I think we got it on defense.
Definitely 1A.
100% 1A.
Roger.
He's on site.
OK, OK, OK.
Falling back then.
I'm going to play with you.
Yeah, I died from window.
There's two bottom and then one up top.
Yep.
They're on the right side here.
Fuck.
Try to stun him out or some shit.
Oh, shit.
He's down, down, down, down, downstairs.
I thought he was still upstairs.
Are you able to get defuse?
No, I couldn't.
Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait.
Oh, you got it.
You got it.
Nice.
Let's go.
Let's go, baby.
I yelled as you defuse.
I couldn't hear it.
Just in case there was a ghost was coming on the other side of him.
You know what I mean?
So true.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Got to make sure they're not breathing.
I'm adjusting for lag.
There you go.
You outfragged him.
Let's go.
As long as you're outfragging them.
That's all that matters.
Nice.
That was fun.
Apparently, she fell off the map.
Wait, what?
That match?
I don't know.
Apparently, she fell off the map.
Newtown domination is next.
Oh, man.
It's going to be insane.
You guys up for it?
Yeah, yeah.
Let's do it.
Let's get it.
All right, let's go.
Is this domination?
Yeah, this is domination.
We got our first win.
Now, our morale is high.
I'm going to tell you right now, I'm going to pop.
I'm going to pop.
We're going to pop off.
Check this out.
Gamma's going crazy.
He's going crazy for sure.
To all the doubters.
See you in 10 minutes.
You do Gamba in your stream?
Or not Gamba?
Like, you know.
No, I don't do like slots or anything.
Like predictions.
Predictions, I think.
Oh, that's bad.
Yeah, they got one going right now.
Oh, really?
It's not popping up for me.
I got to farm my channel points.
We up, we up.
All right.
That's time.
All right, now we win.
We ain't going home yet.
Let's go.
Yes, get it in.
Oxen agitation.
I'm going for B, I'm going for B now.
Yep, yep.
I'm just holding the window, champ.
They're coming from A, A, A, A.
Coming from A side?
Coming from A, yeah, yeah.
I'm going to take back A fast.
I got one.
Actually, we don't need A, just keep seeing.
Yeah, we don't need A, yeah, we don't need A.
Okay, gotcha, gotcha, gotcha, gotcha.
He's on B, he's on B, he's on B, he's on B, he's on B.
He's wrong, he's wrong.
We're good, we're good.
Nading it.
Good shit.
Take his ass out.
Yeah, I'm going to hold garage.
I need somebody, I need somebody on the car side.
Whoa.
I need somebody on the car side, please.
I'm looking.
I'm going to get up, I'm blowing it up.
No one's out there anymore.
One mid car, I'm B, I'm B.
Got him.
Oh, he tried to light it.
I got you, I got you.
I'm B, I'm B, I'm B, I'm B, I'm B, I'm B, I'm B.
You got to make sure you clear site.
Yeah, I got you, I got you.
There you go, there you go, it's good now, it's good now.
Suppressing fire.
I'm holding garage.
John's going to fucking come out of that smoke on site.
Got two, I'm dead though.
On site still, on site still.
On site, on site, on site.
No, he fucking killed me.
Oh my god, I can't.
I got him, I got him, I got him, I got him.
Oh, fuck, we're suppressed here for a minute.
Let's play out now.
Getting into window.
Kill the dude that was playing car cross.
One in the window.
Mid car, mid car, trailer.
We got two, we're up right now.
Sim dead, I'm going for site.
It's prone, prone on car.
Yeah, he's prone on the floor.
I'm still alive.
Yes.
I'm not leaving.
All right, shake it, shake it, shake it.
Don't push too hard, don't push too far.
Come on, flip.
Just holding this fence.
I think it flipped, I think it flipped.
Yeah.
He was in the house.
Yeah, it's flipped.
No, it hasn't.
Wait, no, no, no, no.
Oh, my goodness.
I'm backing out of the spawn.
Fuck, I think I fucked it.
Not yet, actually.
I'm on a fucking beamer, yo.
One in mid.
Fuck, dude, that's a big twit on me.
Yeah, we're good.
We're playing the objective real nice, man.
Oh, I got some, I fell down a trip once.
He ran across, he ran across, he ran across.
Got one on B.
We're clear, we're clear.
Don't have spawn, all right, kill the Buddha.
Another one B.
Let's take a seat, let's take a seat.
Flip it, flip it, flip it.
Oh, god, I'm fucked.
Wait, they're still spawning.
A though?
Yeah, sometimes it messes up.
Yeah, that's real luck.
I'm going to cap C, I'm going to cap C.
Just play for B.
Playing for C, play for B still.
Even if you spawn A, you should be able to retake here.
Okay, I'm in here, I'm in here, capping B.
Try to take car.
Holy fuck, man.
Got truck.
Oh, I ran out of ammo.
Oh, god.
It's too much smoke.
Fuck the smoke.
Going for cap.
Once on, yeah, two.
Shit.
Threw that nade away.
All right, it's tied up right now.
Oh, yes.
You got to run at the end, let's go.
Comeback season.
Close one.
We actually won.
That was good.
Yeah, we're up, we're up.
Look at, look at, hit tab.
We're out fucking fragging them.
We are better mechanically, it's just the fucking truth.
We do have mechanics, we do.
Okay, there's two of them on site, two of them on B, two of them on B.
Nading it.
I'm pushing B, pushing B.
Get in there, get in there.
I killed him off of it, I killed him off of it.
That was a, that was a big explosive.
Whatever that was.
He's in the corner, there's two in the corner.
NB, NB!
Hell Mary.
He's still in B, let's go.
Got him, got him on B.
In truck.
Wait, he capped it?
Oh, no way.
He's always proning near that fucking box, man.
Oh bro, those stuns are next level.
Alright, we gotta take car. If we push car, we have to angle on him.
Oh my god.
Dean, push car for us.
I got you, I got you.
Okay, let's slow down a little bit.
They're making mistakes, they're pushing up. One on car, one Dean.
That fucking cheeky spot.
Oh, there's another one, there's another one covering him.
Alright, I gotta wait for you guys.
It's too much.
Buddha, it's holding long.
Oh my goodness.
Oh, I shot him a
million times.
Oh my.
Where's my
fucking sensitivity?
Okay, I just got a knife.
Emma's dead, he played up.
I can't even leave.
I can't do anything.
I need help on B.
We can make this happen, we can make this happen right now.
Got one.
Got another mid.
He's up in the window.
Yeah, I'm on site, he's dead.
I feel like I'm in times two speed.
Oh, he's on site.
I got him, I got him. Got another.
Let's get this site, this is ours.
Dean, prone, prone, prone.
Get it, get it, get it, get it.
We're doing good.
We take this, we take this.
He's right behind the sign.
He's like right behind the sign.
What the fuck?
He's down, he's down, he's down.
I'm prone, I'm prone.
We need to push past the band.
On this next respawn, let's try all going left.
What the fuck?
How do I lower this?
There you go, let's all try taking left.
Symphony's in our spawn, being a fucking rat man.
So is Blau.
We're getting spawn cap sword.
Yeah, they're inside the house.
You think they're close enough
for us to flip,
but we're not.
No, they're holding it real good.
Killed one, killed three.
Inside trailer, trailer, trailer, trailer.
Outside of trailer now.
Oh, John, I forgot about you
and the fact that you're only playing one fucking corner
because you're a fucking bitch.
I'm inside.
No, the sensitivity is too low.
Good push, good push, Syke.
We're good, we're good.
I'm getting B right now, I'm getting B.
We got it, let's hold it down.
Hold it, hold it, hold it.
Where?
Outside, running out mid.
Oh my god.
I got trailer, I got trailer.
Is it too late?
Fuck man.
Bro, they're on C.
Is there one more round, or are we done?
We lost this game?
Two series, yeah.
It was a good try, good try.
It's a hard game.
Yeah, especially on Nook Town.
E.G.'s though, guys.
We did pretty decent-ish.
I think it crashed.
No, that was fun.
I have this problem with Call of Duty
where I feel like, I'm actually crashing.
I feel like the game is in like times five
speed sometimes.
It's like, I have two times
speed on a YouTube video, and I'm just like
where do I, I don't even know where my eyes are supposed to go.
This way, oh, oh, oh, oh.
I'm dead. It's such a, yeah,
it's a crazy fucking game.
Your sensitivity is 5x.
I'm on 1.0 sensitivity.
Yeah, thanks for setting it up.
That was fun.
That was a blast.
That was really fun.
Let's do it again, it was really fun.
I actually enjoyed it. Yeah, GG's everybody.
GG's. GG's.
GG's.
Bye-bye.
See you guys later.
Shit! I was a bottom bragger!
No, that was fun, that was fun.
I'm not a good Call of Duty player, but that was fun.
Sometimes you gotta play COD.
Do zombies? I don't, can you do
zombies through plutonium? No, I have
fun. How do I do it?
Yes, I can. How do you play zombies?
Do I do it? Is there a different thing I have to do?
Is it a different launcher?
I've never played COD zombies, I don't know how it works.
Really? Can I just play it by myself?
I did? When did I play?
Whoa, that didn't work.
That was a hard crash when I tried to open zombies.
Good job interacting with others, we're proud of you.
Hope it was entertaining. I had fun.
The first game I got a bunch of kills.
I just get so
flustered. You know, I need
a seatbelt. I need a seatbelt on this chair.
You know what I mean? I need a seatbelt
and straps here
on my elbows to keep me here.
Because every time I go to shoot and I
miss, I start moving and
jumping around and like shaking my head.
I need a seatbelt to make it so I can't
do that. No, a seatbelt.
Like you're in a rollercoaster.
Can you imagine if I had like a thing
over my shoulders? That'd be so stupid.
I can't open
zombies. I just like
you should play mortuary assistant.
Should I just go to mortuary assistant?
How long is it? I don't know for how long I'm going to
stream for. Should we just do it? Yes.
It's only a couple hours? Is it only a couple hours?
It's like an hour or two? Alright, yeah, let's do it.
Let's go.