What is going on guys, Jerma here again with a Team Fortress 2 gameplay commentary.
This time I'm continuing the One Life series that I started a while back.
Like you know you've seen it before.
Gonna be playing as the scout on the first one and a spy on the second one.
Two One Life gameplays and somebody asked me, they said,
Jerma, if you call it One Life, you probably should only do one class in One Life.
A real One Life gameplay.
And while that may be true, I don't really like to upload very much content that's less than 3 or 4 minutes.
I mean my vlogs and my video logs and stuff like that, those can be under 2 minutes.
But a gameplay, a real gameplay like this, I want it to be at least 5 or 6 minutes.
I hate uploading 2 minute gameplays unless it's a short or I'm announcing something.
But I don't have an announcement for you right now.
I just want to talk about the gameplay, talk about some strategies.
So let's get right to it.
King of the Hill Harvest is the map we're playing on and I gotta tell you something guys.
This setup, this shortstop, Mad Milk, and the Candy Cane setup,
Oh my god, it's my new favorite scout setup by far.
I love this setup.
This was the first time I really played with this setup.
Sure I've played Mad Milk, Shortstop before, but I've never done Mad Milk, Shortstop, and the Candy Cane.
Because the Candy Cane, if you don't know, when you take damage from explosive damage,
Well that's kind of redundant, but if you take explosive damage, it hurts you for 25% more.
So it's kind of scary. You could potentially get one shot by a rocket or one shot by a grenade.
It's very possible when you have the Candy Cane equipped.
But the really cool part about the Candy Cane is when you kill somebody, anyone with any of your weapons,
you get to pick up a little small health pack.
It just drops right onto the ground.
But you gotta remember, you're not the only person going after it.
Your teammates and your enemies can both pick it up.
Which can get kind of annoying, because you'll kill somebody, and one of your teammates will just be waltzing over it
and not even see it, and just grab it like,
D'uh, sorry, I...
And it can be really, really annoying sometimes, because you'll have 10 health,
and the person running over it will have 195 as a soldier, and it's just like,
Yeah, come on.
It's a really good setup though, I suggest you try it out.
If you've never tried it before, it's really fun.
And also, in this gameplay, I break my kills record.
Now, don't get all excited for that, because it's not a really big achievement.
Scout is my least...
I do the worst with the Scout, let's put it that way.
So, my kills record was 13 in one life before this, and now it's 15.
So, I guess that's okay, but I see people do a lot better.
So this Engineer looks like he was having lag issues, or he ran out of ammo with the Widowmaker.
Not really sure, but speaking of ammo, I ran out of mine,
so I'm running around with the Candy Cane, swinging around like a jerk,
and I got nowhere to go.
Come around here, I pick up the ammo, and now let me give you guys some Scout tips.
This is a very, very important tip for the Scout.
How to effectively double jump, and when to use it, and where to use it.
Watch right here, I kind of go this way, and then I double jump, juke over to the right,
and shoot the Heavy.
He was probably expecting me to be at ground level at that point,
so you really, really need to mess around with people,
and get them to think that you're going one direction,
and then jump a completely opposite direction.
It really, really throws people off.
You know why I know that? Because it really throws me off.
And that's the end of the Scout gameplay right there.
One life, 15 kills.
Try to practice your double jumping, because it can really screw people around.
That's where you get most of your kills, by deception.
Moving on now, this is the second one life gameplay.
It's the Spy on Gold Rush.
It's really interesting.
I don't really kill a whole lot of people in this one, guys,
but oh my god, do I destroy a lot of buildings.
I destroy three full level three sentry guns by myself,
and it's within about two and a half minutes.
So let's watch and see how this goes down.
First one, I believe, was a level two, actually, now that I watch it again.
So I get two level threes, and one level two, bang, Engineer goes down,
and I just single-handedly took out all their defenses in about 40 seconds.
So I thought that was a really, really interesting achievement.
I wonder why they don't have anything like that in the game right now.
I would really like to have seen a Spy achievement,
where if you destroy two or three buildings in a row,
or four or five buildings in a row within 30 seconds or something,
I think that would be actually pretty cool.
Forgot to tell you the loadout for the match.
The loadout for this gameplay is the Kunai vs. Kunai, or the Stinga, not E-R-A-H.
I renamed it the Stinga.
So it's the Stinga, the Ambassador, and the Dead Ringer.
I actually wanted to use the Diamond back in this gameplay,
but I didn't think there was going to be any Sentries,
because the gameplay before this, there wasn't very many Sentries,
and I don't even think there was an Engineer on the other team.
So look at what happens in this gameplay, though.
I destroy a ton of buildings, and there's like four Engineers.
So that would happen to me, obviously, right?
Refilling my cloak on that Dispenser.
A lot of Spies don't know that you can do that.
So guys, if you were unaware, if you didn't know,
if you stand next to a Dispenser as a Spy,
whether it's an enemy one or it's a friendly one,
you will refill your cloak.
So right here, I just say hello to this Engineer.
How's your family? How's your wife and kids?
Sentry goes down, and right here, I thought this was the end of the game for me.
I kind of crouched to sort of accept my fate,
but I ended up getting the shots on that Sniper,
and I ended up getting away.
So I was really happy about that.
So still being alive, I decide to pretend to be on the other team,
whip around, see the Medic, and completely miss the Side Stab.
I'm not even sure I was going for a Side Stab.
I think I was going for a Chaos Stab.
I think I'm going to coin that term right now.
A Chaos Stab is when absolute nonsense is going on,
and you're just swinging around violently,
and you happen to get a Back Stab on someone.
So that was me trying to go for a Chaos Stab,
just stabbing the guy in the face,
and hopefully maybe getting some lag compensation or something.
So now I just want to give you guys a quick little tip
on how to deal with a Dead Ringer spy.
As you saw right there, I just got air blasted across the map,
and that's something you really don't want to do.
You really don't want to air blast Dead Ringer spies,
because number one, it's going to make your teammates
a lot less accurate when trying to shoot them.
Because you know that when you take damage as a Dead Ringer,
it's 10% of the normal damage you would normally be taking,
so you really want people to be able to focus fire on the Dead Ringer spy.
Rather than launching them around all over the place,
you really want to be able to have focus on that one target.
So don't air blast a Dead Ringer spy.
Just try to do as much damage as you possibly can.
Coming up the left staircase here,
I was going to go for a Jumping Stab on this Heavy.
Decide to just go for the Sure Thing,
because I am really, really bad when it comes to Stair Stabs
and Trick Stabs and Jump Stabs.
So I just went for the Sure Thing,
got my Dead Ringer to activate.
Coming up the same staircase,
and I see that there is a Sniper now on the right side.
Kind of just wanted to shoot him in his face,
and that's what I end up doing.
One in the face, one in the body.
That is going to be the end of the gameplay, guys.
Thank you so much for watching.
I really do appreciate it.
Take care, everybody.
I'll see you all next time.