All right. Hello. Sorry about that. Sorry about that. I was in pre-stream chat talking for a
little too long. I didn't manage my time well and I'm technically 50 minutes late. Although,
I did update it and technically I'm 20 minutes late. It's all right. It was good talks. It was
a good talk. It was good talk. It was. Yeah. Hello. Welcome back. If you were here yesterday,
we're going to do the same thing we did yesterday. Going to keep going through Resident Evil 4.
I think I'm about halfway through the game. Seems like I'm about,
there's probably another 12 hours left. So after tonight's stream, if I stream for,
you know, five to seven hours tonight, there'll probably be maybe one more at some point midweek
next week. After I finish Resident Evil 4 remake, we're going to go back into Breath of the Wild.
I'm not going to promise that I'm going to complete Breath of the Wild in this time period next week,
but I'm going to continue progressing through it. Maybe one or two streams of Breath of the Wild
and we'll see. I don't want to rush through Breath of the Wild. I don't want to sprint as fast as I
can through it. I saw some concerns saying, hey dude, you're going to sprint as fast as you can
through that because you want to just be done with it, don't you? And I typed yes, but then I
deleted it and said, no, that's not going to happen. So I'm not, I don't want to do that.
No, I'm kidding. I'm going to take my time through it. Like I already have.
When does a new one come out? May? May, May 12th. I got plenty of time, but I'm not going to play.
I don't think I'm going to play the new Zelda game the day it launches. There's plenty of time
to play the new one. I don't know. Maybe I don't. Do I? We'll see. Breath of the Wild came out in
2016. It took me like seven years to play it. So I don't know. Well, I don't know. We'll see.
I'm already setting him up for disappointment. I'm already setting you guys up for disappointment.
Well, you know what? It took me six years to play the other one. Like what? Why wouldn't it take me
years to play the new one? There's a lot of sadges in chat, I think, after that one.
2017. Yeah. What about Hilux 2? Oh yeah. I don't care, bro. Actually, that's like kind of cool.
Yeah, that's like, that doesn't bother me. To me, you just said, hey, man, I don't even care.
Do whatever you want. All right, thanks. The one guy of the year. That's one guy of the year for me.
I care. I care. It's all right to care. Hey, I care too. Yeah, I'm already really late. So I
don't we're gonna we're just gonna go. What was the last thing I did? I'm already late. I stall for
20, 30 minutes every stream anyways. So let's go. I was in the castle. There he is. Yes, face cam.
Face cam. Yeah, I turn it on. This is the time to turn it on. I told you guys the 2023 philosophy.
I feel like turning it on. I'm going to turn it on. I feel like I felt like turning it on
the last couple of weeks. Going off real goddamn soon. All right, let me take a sip. Oh, okay.
So what was the last thing we did? Head for the ball. All right. Yeah, yeah, yeah. I just did the
shooting gallery shooting game thing. What is in here? Oh, it's none of these like square key
things. There's three of those. Thank you. Want a tip? If you want to do a good laugh,
a good kind of laugh like I just did. A lot of people think, oh, breathe in.
No, no, no, you do it. That's not correct. Get a little bit of air out first.
Because then it's literally just like your diaphragm doing the work. Don't go too hard,
though. Be careful. He's doing theater lessons. Yeah, theater lessons. Dude, your breath smells.
Yeah, so here's the difference, right? Listen to the difference.
Which one sounded better? The second one. Yeah, it's all about, you know, breathing control and
diaphragm control. Now that that does not mean go and like choke. It's all about just breathing and
diaphragm. I'm not expelling that much air when I do that. What is he talking about? I don't know.
Who got us on this? All right, we're going to go this way. Cool. Sweet. Turn it up for me. How's
the volume? Is it kind of low? Turn it up a little bit. You did. Sorry. All right. There's the head.
Oh, it's one of those people. Oh, yeah. You almost started a new sandwich. I'm in a
fucked up mood tonight. I'm sorry. It's already starting. Where is he? Oh, you piece of shit.
Whatever. I know where he is. No, stop backseat gaming, Ashley. Come on. Stop backseat. She's
backseating. Quick die. What is this head made out of? Fucking metal. What is? Oh, my God. This is
a bad start. This is off to a really fucking bad start. This is a bad start. Did he suplex me?
All right. That was a bad start. That was a bad start. It's a bad start. I was a bad start.
My arrows are bouncing off of his head. They were just bouncing off of his face.
All right. This time I'm not going to let him do that. We're not gaming tonight.
Nowhere. I gotta just get back in the swing of it. I'm taking this guy out immediately.
Eat this. No. Blow it up. How do I blow it up? How do I blow the mine up? Why doesn't
take the food out of the microwave? How do I do that? How do I blow it up?
How do you blow up the mine? How do I blow the mine up? It's a proximity mine. Oh,
it's a proximity mine. So what if I attach it to his body? Does that count as movement?
Yes. So I just have to aim better. Okay. Here we go. He's still alive. Oh, my God.
Get up. I thought she said she was okay. She just dropped. Stop. Why is this so stressful?
What? No. Are you dead? She keeps getting fucking suplexed. He's finally dead. Ow.
Must have slipped. That was so horrible. You hurt? I'm good. Thanks. You know that move
that they do in wrestling where they take your body flat and you're lying kind of down,
facing down and they press you up and they hold you there and it's like,
then they let you go. That happened to her like five times. They just like push you up and then
let you go after a while and you're just like pancake onto the mat. Yeah. It's called the
griddle press. Yeah. Wasn't that the ultimate warrior's finishing move? The ultimate warrior
would sprint. Oh, the ultimate warrior was ridiculous. The ultimate warrior, if you don't
know what his shtick was, he had like this superhero symbol was painted on him, whatever
it was. I don't know. I don't remember. He was in a speedo and his entrance music, he would sprint
as fast as he could into the ring. He never spent, I don't think it was ever more than three seconds
they took him to get to the ring. He would just sprint out there running as fast as he can and
then he would just be going like for 20 minutes in the beginning of the fight and he would grab
the ropes. He would grab the top ropes. You know, those three ropes. He would grab the top one and
fucking shake it like this like four or five times during the match. It was fucking crazy.
And that was that was his finishing move. He would press you in the air while doing the
and they would fucking let you go. That was enough to like kill you apparently, whatever it was.
Oh, old wrestling was just so out of control. This dude loves violence.
He loves murder. Wrestling is, I mean, those guys, they put their bodies through hell. But to me,
I always loved wrestling because it was sort of like a series of real-life Looney Tunes gags.
Just kind of chained up together. There's a lot of athleticism that goes into being a wrestler.
I just loved the, it was like a cartoon. It was like a living cartoon with real superheroes.
It was great. All right. Is there anything else here? Well, 20 more of those are in here. All
right. There's only two more. Did I miss any other items? Maybe. Did I already go up there?
This bullets I didn't get. Where is that? I think it's on the actual thing over here.
Yeah. Are you frozen? It shouldn't be. If I'm frozen on your screen, then I might need to refresh.
All right. There's that one. What? It bounced off this guy. But this guy, honestly, it's the tank.
You know what? Yeah. You specked into tanking. You already have a tank behind you. You ruined
the party. And look what happened. The overzealous DPS ran in, took one hit, fucked everything up.
The tank went in front of the tank. Then the tank dies because there's no DPS. It's just,
just absolutely. They're probably swearing at each other in a discord call right now.
We're talking real friend ending shit right there. Uh, let's go here. I got everything in it. I'm
going to go save it though. You could cosplay as Leon and pull it off. Uh, I would need to wear,
uh, tall shoes, I think. Isn't Leon like six, two or something? It feels like six, three.
Welcome. Where would it, what can I do you for a lot of money?
Ruby's all rubbish. She makes no difference. The price. Well, that's our choice to make.
He's five 11. He's five 10. Really? Next time then. Oh, maybe he is. That's all right.
I don't know. Like there's only like three inches that I need. I could do that.
All right. Let's go. I can't go that way down this way. Probably be five 11. Well, I'm five
seven, five eight with shoes. I love wearing dress shoes, dressing up for an event because those
things give you at least, at least like 0.8 inches, like at least one full inch. That's great. I walk
around like I'm fucking boss. I mean, I'm saying I wear dress shoes and I got that extra inch,
extra inch and a half. I walk around like I'll fucking own the place. You know what I'm saying?
Oh, a lot. Do I have enough to finish this right now? It's three square, three. I could put it all
in here and probably make a hundred grand. Should I do that? All right. What's better filling this
with only reds or taking those over here and finishing it? It's just filling the crown up
and selling it. We're better than just putting all reds in here in red, all red, all red. If you have
all different colors, it's a hundred K. I don't know if I'll be able. Oh, wait a minute. I can do
that. I'm going back. Hold on. I can do that. I have enough to do that. Come on. I think I have
enough. I don't know. Yeah, I do. I have green, purple and red and then I have red and wait,
can I not do it? I need a blue gem. I wonder if he sells one. What does he sell? Okay. So we got
green, purple, red. Oh, then red. Wait, I can red yellow. So if I had a blue instead of this
red one, it would be worth a hundred thousand. What does he sell? All right. I'm going to hold
onto it then because that I don't think I've ever done that before. I need a blue gem. That's a
guaranteed hundred K if I can find a blue. Pretty sick. Pretty cool. Come on. No problem.
It's an achievement as well. Oh, cool. We're here. Talk about a fox in space again. Yeah.
I had the privilege of cameoing in the second episode of Fox in Space. Can we get a link to
it? Give one of the mods, put it in the chat. It was really, really cool. I don't want to spoil
anything, but it's very quick. It's like 10 seconds, I think. So if you see it, you'll see
it. It's really, really cool to be any part of that at all. So there it is. Do more voice acting.
Yeah. I, over the years, so I had a lot of passion to like do like voices and stuff and make sound
effects. So you guys know that it's like 70% of every live stream. But I think my, my happiness
and my passions lie in kind of doing it here. Like I just have fun doing it in front of you guys,
rather than other characters or something. I think just fun to do it. I know three voice Andy,
three of four voices Andy. I know, but it's still fun to do it here. I have like more fun doing it
kind of here rather than like in a studio booth or, you know, under a recording session or I
actually have more fun doing it. Just walking around. I don't want to miss anything. Somebody
asked like how did I might be making this up and somebody to say like, how did you learn that you
could do that? Or how did you like want, how did you know you wanted to or something? Um, I've
always just been an incredible, incredibly high energy person. Even when I'm sitting around and
that's ADHD, right? That's part of it. But it was always, I just like had, I just had to expel
fucking energy. And that was kind of the way it did it. And that sort of led into my adult life,
which is kind of weird, but I just, I always just had a lot of energy and it was actually kind of
a problem when I was younger. It got me. Hold on. Oh, they're climbing. They're climbing. What just
happened? Put me out. Put me out. Do something. Put me out. Oh shit. Well, Ashley, what are you
like a grenade? No, no, this is auto-saved. Wait, I knew I heard it. Take that damn mask off of
Ashley. I, it's a unlockable. It's only been off for like two minutes. Why don't I
open this? Hey, stop that. All right. Come over here. Are you all right? Thanks. I got to go kill
the guy that makes all the blog. That's called come out of your head. I guess got to die now,
like immediately I'm sprinting right to that guy spread out and you know what? Stay back. Don't
even come over here. Where is the mage or whatever it is? Where's the mage? With me.
Where's the mage? Oh, oh, you're dead. All right. Cool. I guess I accidentally killed that person
with a grenade. Finish the story. What was, what was I saying? Give me like one keyword and I'll
help figure it out. What was it? High energy as a kid. Oh, I mean, enemy, that kind of stuff gets
into trouble, right? Like trying to not be, not being able to be quiet and always having to like,
I needed to move around all the fucking time and it was kind of a detriment. So a lot of times,
but over the years I've obviously gotten a little better. I don't need to be down here.
I think I had high energy as a kid, but I was better at masking it. Yeah. I mean, everybody is,
everybody's different, right? So my situation versus your situation versus somebody else's
situation is always going to be different, but I had a lot of, you know, communication with,
you know, doctors and family and it was, uh, everybody's different. That's why it's kind of
a, usually a case by case basis a lot of times. All right. Where am I? I wonder if I need to go.
I'm going the complete wrong direction right now. How did I end up going back here?
Why did I go back here? I mean, it was cool. I got some kills, right? But what was it? What am
I doing over here? I'm sitting here explaining how I've had, Oh, ADHD over the years. And I've,
as I've been walking fucking backwards the whole time, that's just par for the course. I think,
isn't it? I rode the train all the way back here. All right. That was actually a nice,
that was actually a lot of help. I appreciate that actually.
Forget how to parry. No, I just feel like people have been behind me the whole time.
All right. Let's just, we're going to wait. Let's go. Just go, just go do the suplex. Oh, I will.
I tried to parry that and you can't parry that. Get out of here. I'm getting money at least.
I am just, I could have taken the cart back. Yeah, it's all right. I'm walking through the
whole game again. This is just absolutely quintessential. I know where I'm going.
No, you don't. I'm already in too deep though. I have to keep going. At least every door is open.
Hi. Are you all right? Yes. I seriously went so fucking far. I have to go through the whole
maze again. Should I just restart? No, I can go through here. No big deal. It's just a straight
path from here, is it? Is it a straight path from here? Through the left. Let's do a factory reset.
No, I'm just going to run. We're good. Glad I came back. It's 200 bucks.
Oh, I did not think that that was going to be here. Hey, we made it and I got the,
the uh, the goat head or whatever it is. This took us an extra five minutes to start.
Ah, this shit is ice cold today. Perfect. Okay. So, uh, I was going the right way.
I went back here from the cart, which I did not want to do that. I need to go up this way.
For a reason stranger. You're here. Maybe this is locked. It's locked. Here we go. Rats have
infested a section of the castle and are gnawing away at all the precious books. Uh, get rid of
the rats in the grand hall library. Imagining that's in here. Yeah. I don't know. I really
don't like doing this, but I'm gonna really don't like it. I don't want to shoot these rats.
I don't like it. That's something sacrilege about what I'm doing. This is, I don't like this. I
really don't like it. I don't like it. Statue of some snakes. I don't like it. Betrayed. Betrayer.
Dining hall. Oh, here. No, thanks. Puzzle time. Okay. The stork is looking at that chair right
there and that chair is sitting across from these drapes. These drapes are spread open. That means
two, one and two on either side, which is these two, these two are exactly 15 feet apart, which
is 15. Count to 15. One, two, three. That counts as four, five, six, seven, eight, nine, ten. There
are only 10 seats. So subtract 10. So that means five. The answer to the door is five.
E is the fifth letter of the alphabet. All right. I'm done. It's like grandpa's birthday picture.
Are they eating napkins? All right. Two knives, fork, spoon, three knives, two forks, spoon. Okay.
And it was, that's his. He had two knives, eating a napkin, two knives, fork, spoon.
No, no. This is it right here.
Have a seat. No problem. Looks like we figured it out. Take it. Serpent head. The last one is over
here. I probably unlock it somehow. What is this item? Oh, it's this. Put this back on. Looks like
we're still missing a piece. There's a symbol on the wall. You hear it ticking. All right. I need
the, uh, I need the last head and it was in line. All right. I need the lion head. How do I get this?
Oh, should I miss an herb? What season are you? Uh, I like summer and winter both equally the same.
Where's this red herb? Oh, it's on the table. Summer and winter are my two favorite seasons.
Although if you're talking about smells, all smells the best. All has the best smell.
All has the best smell. Summer has the best body feel. Spring has the best visual and winter has
the best togetherness. There you go. I had a big raid. We got a big raid came in. Linkus. Thanks
for the raid, Linkus. Appreciate the raid. Welcome everybody. Togetherness. Yeah. That means usually
you can't really, winter is a kind of an indoor, um, season. I mean, unless you're, you know,
going skiing or you're out, uh, you gotta really bundle up. To me, winter is more like I'm drinking
a hot coffee or hot cocoa or something and I'm inside and we're watching a movie. You know what
I'm saying? I think that's pretty accurate for me. Maybe it's not accurate for you. We're different
people. This dude's addicted to coffee. I mean, probably. All right. What am I? Where's this last
head? We're here? Is there a door here? Oh, look, there might be a door there. They actually might
be. Yeah. Welcome, Raiders. There is a door there. Hey, Leon, there's some armor. Bet you could use
it like a bulletproof vest. Little old fashioned for my taste. Too bad. I'm pretty dashing. These
are going to move. I don't, I don't remember what happens in here, but we'll see. There is one more
of those right here. What is making that sound? I lost all my channel points voting for a turtle
in pre-stream. Sad. I don't even know the context of what you're saying. What does that even mean?
We were, where was there a turtle? There it is. What the hell? I need some yellow herbs. Ashley,
stay up there. Hey, be careful. These guys move. These guys move. There's no way these guys don't
move. Get all the items first. That's Resident Evil 101. Welcome to class. When you touch the thing,
25 enemies are going to run after you. Collect everything first. Everything. That is Resident
Evil 101. Welcome to the lesson. We're clear. I'm ready to start the encounter. Can't be serious.
That count? Oh, you can't parry that. That's not getting parried. Jesus. Oh shit. Oh shit.
Oh, you can parry it. What did you just do? What's going on?
Dude, I'm out. I'm out. I'm going to have to switch over to this. Damn. I'm almost out of
everything. I got no ammo. I'm almost completely clean out of everything.
Is this where this weapon is going to really shine? Because I got nothing. Time to utilize the weapon
that has infinite ammo if you're good. Stop minus twoing Leon. That's kind of rude. Yeah. Stop.
Oh, there it is. I got the cube. Hold on. I forgot to blink for like 45 minutes. Oh, damn.
Damn it. I need to save this ammo. There's one more somewhere in here.
One more wrap. Hook up a shock collar to have minus two and plus two activated.
If it's really bad, I just get electrocuted. How would that work? If there's more than like
500 minus twos in chat, I get shocked. I don't think so. What happens if I get a bunch of
plus twos then? What's the reward that I get? You get candy. A cookie. A candy dispenser.
A candy dispenser? What kind of weird experiment is this? There's just like a device that's in the
corner over here that if I get enough plus twos, like a little candy comes out and I'm like,
oh, I run over there and I unwrap it. What the hell kind of, what is the stream that you're
referring to? That's the idea. Matilda. I don't like it. I don't like first fire.
I always land the first shot and the other two just miss. I'll hold on to them for now.
I'll buy most anything. I don't always have this in stock stranger. Stocking up while you can.
Say something. I'm fine. I need to do a big turn in here. I've got like $200,000 worth of
shit in my inventory. W A S D Q E. Okay. I need that on the bottom. Is that correct? Yeah, that's
it. Where's the, there's another one of those. Where is it? It's over here, isn't it? That's it
right there, right? All right. It's somebody, I don't even know what the fuck that person's saying.
All right. This, that's it. It's, it's, it's back there. I'm going to take the car because I want
to go do the other cube thing because I will forget and I will not do it. It also might be over here
too. Why not yourself? Okay. Time to go on the car. Just behind me. This way. Okay. What do you
say? It's a fancy car. I don't know. Melt that thing down and go rebuild a fucking school.
You know what I'm saying? Like this thing, that could be made out of wood. It could be made,
it could put some nice gold trimming on it. You know what I mean? Like does that gotta be a $10
million? It could be a $1 million card. Does it gotta be a $10 million card? All right. Where is
it? Or is it up or is it across? Is it across? I think it could be a $5 million card. That could
be a $5 million card. All good. He's malding over golden pixels. I ate breakfast this morning. If
anyone's curious. No, he's supposed to fail. He's supposed to fail those puzzles for 20 fucking
minutes. I wasted my candy. Where's the candy dispense? Okay. But acting superior. Hey, this is
it. Imagine if I ever have a Disneyland ride to go to the kitchen, pause the movie and go to the
kitchen to get the popcorn. You need to get on a Disneyland ride to get there? I don't know, man.
I think that's a little, I think that's a little much. I think that's a little much. I hate big
fucking spaces. They piss me off. I don't know why. I do know why. Cause I lose shit all the time.
I need just a few rooms. You know what I'm saying? Too many places for me to, I would get lost.
Got to take Splash Mountain to get to your living room. I mean, that's like fucking funny.
That would be so annoying after a while. Okay. Well, what if, what if you do the Splash Mountain
ride to get to your, get to the kitchen and then you take like the, you know, the monorail back to
the living room and then you realize I left my fucking phone on the counter in the kitchen.
You have to ride Splash Mountain again. That would suck. You'd be like, I don't want to ride that
again. Or is it a case of you have so much money that you, there's a phone in every room?
You know what I always did want? This is back, um, back when cell phones really weren't a thing.
I always wanted one of those phones next to the toilet. I thought of, you know how much shit I
would be able to get done? I'd be able to get so much stuff done. This is loud. What are you getting
done? Meetings. That'd have to be a bunch of sound dampening. There's gotta be a bunch of sound
dampening in that room. In that room. I just said run because I'm about to run and my brain
replaced the word. Um, God, hold on. Ah, shine forward. That sounds like, um, like motivational
speak. Shine forward. That rat was fast as fucking, oh my God. Is that a clock? Resting
forbearers answer to the chosen time. It is it. If it is the Lord's blessing you seek,
have courage and fear. No darkness. Chosen time. What time is it? I got a watch. You know,
it's really, really interesting about all this. Are these real, are these real paintings from
or were these made specifically for the game? Think about the time and the effort that an
artist went into to do this. And it lives as this set piece to create this environment.
It's really cool. You just don't, you don't really even think about it, right? So as I walk through
these doors, somebody had to make all this. Somebody had to put all this here. That turtle
was placed here very particularly by somebody. I think we kind of forget that a lot. Sorry about
you losing all the, uh, all your money or whatever happened to you. Wait, why? I'm sorry. I just
ruined that whole moment I was having there. I hate that. I don't like when they're under that
hidden staircase, a secret room or something. Shit. I don't have that device. Bunch of keys.
Break this. Ashley can't kick that. God damn it. It can't get in here, right?
Oh, my God. It's this one. Whoa. Close the door. Close the door. Close it. Close it. Close it.
Close it. Close the door. Oh, shit. No. Leon, help. The key to getting out of this confounded
place is the Salazar family insignia. To find it, I must venture to where that cursed armor
awaits the underground mausoleum. Oh, merciful Lord, enact your righteous justice upon the wicked
surfer, the maniacal monster Ramon Salazar. May your blessed blue light protect your forever
faithful servant. Ooh, wait, what time is it? It is exactly almost four o'clock. Oh, wait,
do I know what this is? I mean, hold on. Let me, I don't open that yet.
1104. 1104 o'clock. I bet that works. I didn't use one of these keys,
so I missed out on something, but whatever. One hundred thousand dollars. There it is.
Let me save it first. I don't think I did. All right. 1104 is right here. Give me a candy. Yeah,
I got a blue gem. Give me a candy. All right. The other one is 1104. God damn it. The power
of the blinding light. I sentence you to hell. It works. Oh my God. It works. I forgot it worked.
I thought I was making a stupid joke. 1104. 1104. Quickly. Am I good? Am I safe? This is the scream
stream I've been waiting for. Well, just that section is just. Did they take that? Did they
take the elevator? Oh, I thought they took the elevator down. I was like, why do they have
intelligence like that? All right. Don't press any buttons until I know what the hell's going on in
here. OK, bird, moose, seahorse, snake, bird, moose, seahorse, snake, bird, bird, whatever, snake.
That's true. That's the best line of the whole game so far. This sucks.
Whoa. Oh my God. This doesn't close. That person. Wait, there was a gem in that eye.
How do I get it? I don't know. I need the. I get it. I get it. This sucks. That was great delivery
too on that line. That was very. That was like 10 out of 10 delivery. Is that correct? I need to flip
these. That was an insane puzzle. Oh, I don't even. I don't even have the thing. I don't even have
the lantern. Did I? Did I fuck that up? Oh God. What am I? The only one I haven't used. I just
almost exited the game. Holy shit. What the hell? Come on, come on, come on. Oh, that sucked.
I wonder if that's harder on a professional or hardcore. It's not over yet. God damn it.
God damn it. OK. Oh shit. I don't know where to go. Dude, I don't know where to go. I have no idea
where to go. Where do I go? Around this way? This is wrong. This is the wrong way. It's over here,
isn't it? Straight. No. Wait, it's not right here. Are you serious? No, I'm going the right way.
Stairs with a diamond is the right way. Oh, I knew that. Go. Thank you. Thanks for the help.
Change the outfit. I will. That was terrifying. Elpers. Oh, you need to be really sure about that,
bro. I can catch you. I think so. Oh yeah, there are the two weird predator enemies.
God, about that. That was a long chapter. That was all the hedge maze and everything. Time for
break? No, not yet. Maybe like another half hour, 40 minutes. Maybe like an hour. Sorry, nothing yet.
But my little helper is creating quite the commotion. Everything will work out just fine.
As long as you can keep your dog under control. Seven minutes. He's a good boy. Predictable.
Fine. Change your mind yet? Aida. Assuming you haven't. I've got a tip for you. How about a
FaceTime call? Seems like something big is about to go. Babysitting is tough. Hey, Aida. Aida.
That's such a funny concept. Now you're getting FaceTimed by Aida in this situation. It's like,
yeah, all right. Hey, you do the thing where you're like, hold on. Wait, I need to make
the corner way bigger so I can see how ugly I am. Hey, Aida. You know what I mean? Like,
you gotta make sure I look all right. Okay. I have $100,000 waiting for me over here.
I'm about to do a cool thing. Here we go. So we've got, she has it. She has it in her inventory.
Oh, well. Welcome. Got some rare things on sale, stranger. Well, this is the ultimate shotgun.
Body armor is less expensive now. Yeah. Look at all this stuff I have. I have to sell something.
I'm MinMaxAndy right now. I gotta sell, I have to sell something.
She dropped it. They're on the ground. What? Is that for real? She dropped it.
Oh, I am so glad that you said that because I, she didn't do that. She didn't say,
hey, Leon, turn away a little sack over and else she threw us the key. All right. Well, good to know.
Let's do it. Green, purple, red, blue, yellow, 100,000. It's a full two times bonus. Yeah. I
think this is the best possible thing you can do in the whole game, right?
Is there another five slotted item? All right. I could do this one too. I need, I want money.
I'm doing it. I want money. This can be filled in. You can do all red on this one,
which would be pretty cool. Look at this. Quad bonus. Oh yeah. That's, I don't think I've ever
seen that much money in the game. Here we go. 100,000, 60,000.
Ruby's all rubbish. It makes no difference. I just got an achievement for that.
All right. Now we're going to make some decisions here. I'm going to sell this shotgun. It's
another 152. Wait, I'm going to put the thing on. Hey, brief 4k is three or 4k. You know what I'm
saying? Three or 4k is three or 4k. I'm doing it. Oh yeah. All right. I have $292,000 to get this
thing to be ridiculous. Semi-automatic shotgun.
Oh, okay. Hold on. Oh my God. It's so expensive, but it's crazy.
I need some reload speed.
All right. This thing is disgusting right now.
This thing is filthy. You just emptied your whole account. Yeah. Into this.
You don't have any ammo for it. Fix that right now.
Welcome stocking up while you can. I knew you too. Pleasant.
Wait, I want to put the shotgun ammo thing on shotgun shells. Craft bonus. Okay. Shotgun
craft bonuses on six. This thing has 18 shots. Damn. All right. That's the, I can't wait to
use that thing. That thing is disgusting. You can hold 25 and I still remember I still have
what? Like 20 shots in the revolver. I've got 20 shots. I am ready to kill any boss in like four
hits. All right. How are we looking? Got some decent heals. I got pretty bad on ammo, but that's
why I'm going to use this for a little while. I'm going to replace, let me put this in a better spot.
All right. Let's move outfit change after this next little bit here. So where to? I did that.
Now the idea is I have to go this way. Let's go in. I want to go into the library back this way
because I want to open, I want to get the cube thing and then it's open to the right, right?
Right. Ashley is literally dead. Ashley is not dead. Wait, what's this? This is game progress
over there, but I don't want to do that yet. I seek a brave soul willing to dispose of that monstrosity
of a knight. Be warned is much stronger than the other as he cut down our best of the singles to
defeat the strong threat in the mausoleum. I don't think I need it. I don't need it.
I don't even need it. That's done. Yes. I actually do need to do this because I need
ammo and there's a lot of stuff to break down here. Let me turn this over. I missed every
single shot. Every, I should get an award for that. I should be given something for that.
Hi. I'm trying to save ammo. Oh, right in the throat. All right. I'm missing a couple of
arrows. Where are they? Am I missing arrows? Okay. So the thing is yellow diamond. Nice.
Not quite that way yet. I'm looking for that cube cube thing. I think it's actually upstairs.
They never break, but they can go out of reach. There it is. All right. What the hell's in here?
Oh my goodness. CQBR assault rifle. Damn. This was free. He uses rifle ammo. I'm probably
going to sell this and just put it all into the striker. That's really cool though. All right.
What else we got? I'm going all in. Yeah. That's how I play it. I don't spread it out. No, no, no.
I take, I pick one weapon and I put a million dollars into it and it kills every enemy in one
shot. Yeah. I got to be careful. I got to aim the shots well, but it kills every boss in three hits.
Just put a million dollars into one weapon and you don't have to worry about using other weapons.
Use other weapons. Why? Having 24 shotgun shots that deal 5 million damage. Why use the rifle?
I don't need to do that. All right. Let me go out this way. There's another one up here too.
It's in here. Yep. There it is. You can only kill 24 enemies. That's not accurate.
Golden links. Nice. Oh, the boss, a boss. It has a lot of help. I could finish this right
now. Or I could finish this one too with the triple. I wonder what's worth more. I think that
does it. So now I'm going to go this way. That's the game progress route. You are so bad. Why?
What are we talking about? Oh, you don't want to have like an omega shotgun. All right. Triple
37k. That's pretty good. 37, eight versus 40. All right. It's more economically viable to do this
one. It isn't 1.2 versus 1.4. This is going to affect the economy. It's fine. It's all right.
It's fine. It's fine. This thing's worth 20k. What is it to make the shotgun ammo? I need the blue one.
Thank you. Try that on for size. Let's go. 16.2 damage. Anything else I place in travel.
This thing is disgusting. It's going to kill everything in one hit. Stryker is the weakest
shotgun by far. I'll be, you'll see. I'll be fine. You'll get it. I made a new save file just in case
I completely fuck myself here. Magnum's already on and shotgun is already on, right? So we got
shotgun melee crit hit rate and Magnum crafting. The first shotgun has 25 points when maxed. Yeah,
but you can't go gung, gung, gung, gung, gung, gung and get the cut scene. You know what I'm saying?
Boss. I make the boss drop down to one knee. The Plagas comes out. Boom, boom, boom, boom, boom,
boom. Cutscene. I think I'm going to be all right. All right. Back to it. Here and then left. All
right. We'll see. Somebody said, all right, we'll see. I got to sit closer to my desk. I have to
like reach over to get my drink. I'm too far away. The people want a new outfit. Oh shit.
I'm saving ammo. Look, look at how good I'm being. Fucking monsters. You just chose the
most controversial weapon in the Resident Evil community. How do you feel? Um, same as I did 10
minutes ago. What do you mean? Why is this? What do you mean controversial? Why is it so controversial?
Ow. That was, oh, okay. That's fucked with me. That was a really long window. I did not think
that window was going to be that long. I committed then I didn't commit and I committed and I didn't
commit. Lost an arrow. Take a shot in the ceiling. You must smell awful. I don't think so. Shotgun.
This thing doesn't even have a full slugs. Oh, good. I have a lot of health. All right. What's,
what, what's, what's controversial about what I did? Remember, try not to make every single
chat message as mean and referring to him challenge. Now, if one of these birds just went
wham, that would be scary. Oh, purple herb. That's max health, max ammo, and a full heel.
I can't fucking believe I found one. All right. July 2 years since my awakening,
Master Ramon has bestowed upon me a truly righteous undertaking to improve upon the flaws of our human
form, to seek perfection as observed in our anthropodal siblings. This cause I shall willingly
devote my life. January 4 years since my awakening, my efforts to transfuse the black liquid into the
body are at a precipice of success. The womb is the key. If your soul proves to be a highly
malleable and adaptive subject, and then a bunch of other bullshit that they did or something,
well, you can read it on your plate. It really was like another paragraph or two.
All right. I promise I will read the notes from now on. I will read the notes. I promise from now
on. Hey, oh my goodness. I didn't even fucking flinch. Where is this last one? Where is this?
This gave me a headache. I have a fucking headache. Where even was he?
Nice. Ow, my finger. How do I get over there? One, it's been like 15. I don't want you to die
there because I won't be able to get the item. I don't think they stopped spawning. What the fuck?
That thing was made out of stone. Get out of the fucking way. Get, get. Okay. There's still a
treasure. Where's the treasure? Get away from, I'm trying to get the treasure. Fuck off. Oh my God,
you're an annoying little shit, aren't you? Okay. How do I get out of here? That way. Oh wait,
I want all the items, everything. Come on. I want everything. Give me everything. I feel like I've
been walking around here for like an hour. How long have I been walking around this place?
Did that not wait? What did that just open? Did that not open this? Wait, what just happened?
I didn't, I didn't open that gate. There's one on the other side, isn't there? Feel you right behind
me that way. I have to fight up the ladder. I tried to parry it. I just suck. I'm getting so
many blue sapphires. Finally. Pretty good, pretty good farm spot. Yeah, I'll take it.
Got a lot of handgun ammo. How come you skipped the night boss? Oh yeah, I did. I didn't mean to.
I forgot. Why is it painted? Oh, you're able to go back right now? I really don't want to run
through all these bugs again. Are they, are they gone? No, they are not. I missed it. Sorry,
I missed it. It's all there is to it. I missed it. It's okay. Another time. Oh shit. Oh shit,
that's those. I was silent before. Now I'm not. Oh, okay. Okay. I'm not quiet anymore.
They just, they got up. They're out. They're out. All right. This is why I,
this is the reason why I got this weapon. Just like I fucking planned. It's got to be the boom,
boom, boom, boom, boom, boom, boom, boom in the back. And I'm going to kill one in a second.
Ready? Here we go. Flashbang going out. What is this? What? What happened? I couldn't shoot him.
It's not hitting him. What's going on? Is the armor on the back have to be taken care of?
I think it's the armor on the back is not gone. I shot the wrong one.
Whatever. All right. It's the point still stands. That would have been awesome.
Okay. And dude, only use this. They can't hear this. It's silent.
Just wait till they come over here. Take them out one by one. Quietly.
Only headshots. Only. I gotta go. Can I pull them out of his head? Quiet. We have been silent.
We're very good. Extra bolts. I hate it. No way, dude. Somebody just threw something at me.
I think they just spawn forever. They do. They just spawn forever. Okay. Well, you know what?
Then come on then. Come on then. Come on. What? Why can he hear me?
I don't want to use it. Oh my fucking God. Okay. All right. I got a fucking, I got a,
I got a flashbang. Nice shotgun. I haven't even had an opportunity to use it. Don't even give me
shit for that. I've got to make the floggers come out and then unload. I'm just going in.
I'm going in. Yeah. Yeah. I thought he was dead. I fucked it up. What the fuck just happened?
I'm made out of fucking. All right. I'm going to do it fucking. I'm going to do it for real now.
I'm going to do it for real and not get shit. Push four. Why can I not press a
button on my fucking keyboard? I always press like two accidentally. Get out of my fucking way.
Yeah. I got a beer back. I shit my pants. All right. Two unicorn horns. That was so scary.
Does anybody else have this problem where you got one, two, three, four on your keyboard
and from W going from W to three or two, I always end up going like this. I hit just like three of
them, but I just, I can't do it. It was worth it. I got to use the mines. No, I made this bed. I
have to sleep in it. Remember the Magnum that you're never going to use. I will use it. I'll
use the Magnum just wait. I just like stabbed myself in the eye with my fingernail. I was,
that's so annoying. I so badly wanted to scratch my eye with my other hand when I
could have just used the right, the actual, the left hand too busy gaming. No, we're good.
What treats do you want? Um, I'm good right now. I think I got everything. All right. Let's go.
I also didn't even have a working knife that whole time. Turn the lights off. They're already
actually.
Just kind of mask on this.
Kennedy.
Hang in there, Ashley. I'm coming for you. I'll be fine. Give up the ghost. Anything down here?
Oh, I remember this part is so scary. If I remember it's when, yep. Oh, I hate this part.
This is the sewer, right? Oh, it's the worst. It actually is awful. Talk about sticking the landing.
Bugs. Get the fuck away from me. Where is that? Where this place? Lots of blue gems though.
You guys weren't lying. Don't do that. Oh shit. Okay. They move so fast through the water. It
sucks. Probably an item down here. It's going to run item. Run, run, item. Run. Really? Nothing,
nothing at all. I guess a little bit of these things heal for a hundred percent health.
If I put that keychain on, maybe I should farm a couple here. There's another place to go.
Yeah, there's an item over here. Do this IRL. Twix or payday candy bar. The people need to know
Twix every day. Twix all day every day. I can't get that. I really, really want that. Which,
which, but left or right Twix. I open the package and close my eyes and just like spin it around
and spin, spin, spin, spin, spin, spin, spin. And then I just take one. I can't decide.
Probably drop down here. I'll read it. Another one dead. How long has it been since I was thrown
down here? The meager scraps of food provided in the beginning are gone and they don't give us
anymore. The pains of hunger and thirst are unbearable. Most have resorted to drinking
the black water. The first to turn was Herminio. He was so weak that he couldn't even walk,
but then suddenly became mad. By the time his rampage ended, two were dead. I think we shouldn't
drink that dark liquid. Dear Abelardo has passed, though he fought until the very end. The only thing
I can do now is honor the bodies and pray that their souls find peace. Oh Lord, why do you test
us so? Another crown. Another crown. I can do a triple in here. We'll see. Okay. I really do badly
want that item down here and I'm going to get it. There we go. Okay. Finally. No, no, no, no, no, no,
I already have one made. Cool. I need to repair this. This thing filled back up. Very nice. Give
me a break. It's this part. I hate this part. I'm just going to warn everybody. I'm probably going
to scream at least five to 10 times during this part. Um, there's nothing I can do about it.
This is where the game turns into a granny like and it's a granny like on crack. Uh huh. It's
not going to be fun. Very much not looking forward to this is probably my least favorite
part of the whole game is this next hour or so. Yeah, well I'll take a break. Let me just do this
first. Oh, that's a lot of gunpowder. You have anything new? Let me take a look at this shit.
Three blues will fit in here and I'll be just fine. Although is that going to be bad for later?
25k. I think it's fine. 7,000. So let's do, let's just get these in here.
But anytime welcome got a selection of good things on sales, a deal well struck.
You've exhausted our normal range of services for this weapon.
If you're interested in something more, well, you catch my drift. Let's see.
Rolls are gross. All right. Here's the problem. It's 30 well tuned weapon can make up for a
this is going to have almost 50 shots in it. You don't even have the ammo to fill one magazine.
I'm all right. I still got money to put into this. See, everything's going to be fine.
You're the worst resident evil four player. No, I'm using a gun you don't like.
Let's just get this. We're starting to get an idea of your taste.
What you see is why I don't always. I use these so often. I'm just going to use it. You know what
I mean? Yourself killed now. Very cool. I could put the thing on and just use this and get a full
heel. That's what I mean. Let's top myself off. I'm going to get topped off. Okay. I'm going to be our
bee. I'll be right back. And from here, I'll put on a new costume and we'll be right back.
Give me like two, three minutes, maybe five minutes or so in a minute.
Okey dokey. How are you? Refilled my drink. Got a little bit of stretches out of the way.
Move my legs a little. Preparing myself for this part coming up. I'm talking this up like crazy.
Watch this. Not even be a big deal. No, there's no way it's not. Okay. Hello. Can you see me?
Not yet. You will be in a minute. Comfortable. Turn the gamma down on this. Is the lighting fine on
the? I'm a little orange. I mean, it kind of looks like that in here anyways. Whatever. I'm good.
Let me know if the audio is not any good because I had to change it for the music.
How bad would you laugh if in 10 hours I can't beat the game because of the shotgun I have and
I have to go back and do this and get the rifle? I would laugh out loud. Oh my God. I would laugh
out loud. Outfit change. You're right. You're right. Hero or villain? Villain in cut scenes,
I think would be really funny. Let's do villain for now. I guess we'll do that for now. Bro,
take the glasses off. No, the glasses stay. The glasses stay. I look like I'm in the fucking
night's watch. This is going to be so distracting. I already know it. I can't wait to turn it off.
I already hate it. Well, everything's good. Move. Look like a Bloodborne character. Yeah,
the Bloodborne mod. What is? I hear it. Where is it? Here it is. Okay. No more stalling. It's time
to go. But there's a treasure over here and I'm going to get it. Ooh, I think I can make a new
thing. Oh, not even close. Chris Angel. Do you get partial credit for that little side quest or do
you have to get all 16? Dude, you look like a buzzard. You got to get them all. Installation
of the liquid nitrogen showers that were requested last month have been completed.
Caution. Liquid nitrogen is extremely hazardous. Yep. It's this part. I'm not going to scream.
May, nine years since my awakening. Upon the release of this valve, black liquid shall enter
my veins and circulate throughout my entire body. I expect this will be the most painful experience
of my life. I await the trial with great anticipation. It is an honor to suffer through
the holy labor of rebirth. The next time I awaken, it will be as a true servant of master Ramon.
I, Isidro Uriarte Talavera, make this vow. I will surpass the limitations of man and become
a true servant of God. I will find the heretics and serve as their executioner. Their verdugo.
On powder. These people are not right. You have a long time to figure that out, Leon.
Oh, a boot knife. Put that on. Put the boot knife on because I think I can use it to kick,
right? Especially for this part. Hold on. There's more shit here.
Out of service. To conserve electricity, the power has been turned off for some equipment,
including the elevator. It can be restored by flipping the circuit breaker. Look at at the
very back of the laboratory. Great. Where is it? I can hear it. Oh, I'm looking right at it. Nice.
Make sure I get everything. I think I've got everything. All right. I'm not going to scream.
Oh, did I waste it? I can hear this motherfucker. Oh, it's at C. C is the worst place for that.
I can't rely. If we press C, let me get all the items in here first. I know there's probably a
couple. Let's go. What did I not do this? Why did I not do this earlier? Why did I not do this
earlier? Why did I not do that earlier? Press the button. Press it, please.
Oh, my God. My God. Get off me. Get off me. Get off me. Oh, my God. Press the button,
please. You fucking dumbass. Press the button. Where's E? Oh, shit. It didn't work. Oh, my God.
Oh, my God. Fucking greedy. I'm so greedy.
Fucking gross. All right. We're not leaving yet. Imagine that on a higher difficulty. Oh, yikes.
Is my least favorite part about the whole game? Not because I don't like it, but because it's
just so scary and so stressful. It's a granny-like disease just constantly running after you.
Oh, yeah. There was one more nitrogen. I was panicking too much. It's not easy on hardcore.
I do not envy people playing on hardcore or professional against this fight because it
fucking sucks. I want to get in there. This door, right? Good. Oh, I'm really glad I came in here.
You made that look pretty easy. The only reason why I did not lose probably three or four times
there is just because I've done it before. I knew you had to do the nitrogen spray,
but it still kind of doesn't matter. It's still a big scary monster running after you.
I should... How am I doing on items and stuff? Now, here's a little tidbit. You actually don't
have to kill that thing. I think most people's first playthroughs, they'll probably just get away.
You actually don't have to kill it, but I wanted to. You can outweigh it. Yeah. You can just kind
of run around in a circle. That's why I made all the flashbangs, by the way.
Salvation, as you wish.
Coming back to that is just not... You're never prepared for it.
I've already turned. My character has already turned. I've been completely infected at this
point. Oh, you get points for actually killing it. That's cool. Pretty good score. That's pretty
good. I'm not playing on hardcore, but I think that's pretty good. I'll take a 90. Second
playthrough will be hardcore. I don't think I'll ever do professional, though. You need to be
next level with your aim and awareness and... I think it's like you die in like one or two hits,
right? There's no autosaves or anything? Can't you only save like five times or something in
professional? Something awful? 15. This character does not belong here.
Why help me, though? What's in it for you?
No need to be suspicious. I said I'd help you, didn't I?
Nice OC. I haven't got the red contacts in. Make your way to the surface. Everybody's so winded in
the remake. October 11. Today was the worst day of my life. It's my daughter's fifth birthday,
but here I am stuck on a mangy boat heading out to some backcountry dump. If it weren't for the
pay, no one would be willing to work out in the middle of nowhere a week later. Those in the castle
are always reminding us to take care during the excavation, but a few workers collapsed after
inhaling some dust. There's something going on here that they're not telling us. There are too
many secrets. I've started coughing, too. I should sleep. Nothing's really wrong with me. I threw up
blood three more times today, and I'm so weak I can barely move. Shit. I never should have come
down here. I came for the money, but instead I'm the one paying the price. I'm a terrible father.
I'm so sorry, sweetheart. You deserve better. Since morning my- Since morning head don't work.
Why? More blood threw up. Many insects crawling. I hear a voice. This is what I'm talking about.
This is what I wanted. New day. A fine day to work. Digging brings me so much joy. I am full
of happiness. I offer it all to you. Everything for you. Do you know what I mean? This is the caveman
kind of talk that I was looking for. The- Since morning head don't work. Okay, you're having-
Something went wrong. Yeah, your head hurts. Why? You threw up blood. I puked. There's insects
everywhere, and I hear things. We don't need all this. You know what I mean? Me like small word.
Ooh. There's only one. It's limitless, though. Should I just piss off every single person here
and just save for this and just get 50 rounds in this shotgun and that's how I end the playthrough
is just have 50 bullets in the shotgun at the last boss. That's so stupid.
It's 60,000 and that ticket. And I'll have 48 shots in this gun.
Why not? It's stupid and fun. I might as well try it. It's 60,000. Oh, or the ticket.
Oh, I thought it was needed both. I can make that happen. Look at that. 30,000.
So if you kill that, um, that boss, you get 30k. That's pretty cool. Nice.
Ooh, I can make bullets.
Grenades. Nah, I'm a flashbang kind of guy. These are close, although I should probably
save it for here. What's the five, right? Five colors. So I would need to do green, purple,
red. Okay. So take these out. I want another 100k. Green, purple. I need a purple. And then I could
do blue. Yellow. I see a purple. We get another 100k. Be on the lookout for purple gem as I need
one. All right. In the meantime, I think I'm going to save the money, although I might as well just
keep one of the, I've been using this a lot more frequently. Have you noticed that? I think I'm
going to use that. I've been using this a lot. Starting to see why this thing is really great.
Is it worth 27,000? I could always sell it in the end. This could be the difference. This thing
already has saved me at least two or three times with me being able to shoot and not worry about
ammo. So I think it's all right. Oh no. Let's go. I already have enough. Ooh, okay. Nice red nine
and then two handgun only. Try it out. I need to check. We got to check. I need to check this
shit. They hide in the barrels sometimes with the skulls. I wonder if they're in the barrels.
How many are there actually? Oh no, there are no hidden ones. Okay. Come on, dude. You fucked it
up. That's it. No bonus round. Was it not fast enough? Wait for the fucking grenade guy.
Where's the, that's all I fucking care about. Okay. Good. All right. I don't care about anything
else. I don't care. I wanted the gold coin. There it is. We're good. Want the S and we want 100%.
I need those gold coins. All right. I'm not sure. Is this the one that shoots?
Whoa. What the hell? Wait, that's confusing. This thing shoots through people.
You looking greasy? You don't think I know that? You don't think I, you don't think I'll be the
first person to tell me that I'm a greasy motherfucker? Fuck. I got to wait a long,
a lot longer than that. I got to wait longer. It's about piercing eight. There are eight of those.
Holy shit. I don't think I'm doing that. Come on, man. Come on, man. What are you talking about?
Right there. Wait for, you got to wait for four. You got, I got to wait a long time on this one
when they line up. Ready? Right there. I mean, that's, that's how you do it.
Kraken. Kraken. I was just gonna say Kraken. Your feet aren't glued to the floor.
I have, thanks Kraken. Welcome everybody. Thanks for the raid. Playing Resident Evil 5. It's four.
I say, why do I keep saying five? But welcome everybody. I didn't wait again. I don't like this
one. I'm not a fan. I don't like this one. I have to wait too long. I hate waiting. I hate waiting.
I hate this one. Shoot. Give me the, I hate shoot. I hate waiting. I hate waiting. I hate this one.
This is the machine gun one. Throw them away. No. Fucking can't. I hate it. I hate it. I hate it.
Get out of the fucking way. How do I get to the bonus round? Destroy all pirates
in 10 shots or less. Oh, that sucks. One, two, three, four, five, six. Oh no. I didn't get them all.
Which one did I miss? Shit. I wonder which one I missed. I didn't see it. I'm one of the pirates.
Wait, restart it. What's the condition on this one? 10 shots or less. Okay. Let's try it.
Three, four, five. Oh, come on, dude. You got to be shitting me. That was bait. No, what are you
doing? Now I'm just shooting. I fucking hate these. I'm going to eat my fucking microphone.
How do I do that one? I guess it's bait. All right. So some of these are bait.
Fuck. That's three, right? Four, five. What are you talking about, video game? Are you on fucking
crack? I shot it directly in the face. Did it hit the ceiling? Perfect. Perfect. Put your head down.
Put your head down. Get down. That's it, right? I got to have gotten it right there. That's eight,
right? Yeah. Let's try this one more time. What the fuck? How did it hit the guy? It was the
fucking triangle. Fuck. Just wait till they come over here. And that would have been 100%. It would
have been every single fucking one. I'm done. Two, one. Or should I just go three? That's actually
kind of good. I would have loved that earlier. Nothing kind of sucks. Another rare. 30% off body
repairs. That's really good. But is it actually 30% or is it full of shit? The other one was bad.
Dude, Ashley is dying and you're buying gumballs. I mean, I got to relax a little.
Rare. 100% recovery item. Resale value. Like if I herbs and stuff, why would I sell herbs?
Looks cool though. Feels cool. Nice. That's it, right? I forgot. He scared the shit out of me. I
forgot he was here. I just saw a guy with a gun walking towards me and I was like, what is happening
right now? I love the shooting range. I love it. I don't like that other gun though. Green, red,
yellow herb combo sells for 20,000 with that trinket. What do you mean? Hold on. Where's the
typewriter? Let's take a look. All right. Let's, I'm curious. Got a selection of good things on
sale, stranger. I'll buy almost anything. So this is normally 2,000. All right. Let me take it off
and see what it does. Uh, I think I, yeah, the gunpowder one's, I think the one I want.
Melee. All right. Get this off. I'll keep the shotgun one on. I'll just keep the chicken one on,
maybe. Yeah, just keep this. If I run into an egg, I run into an egg.
Beetle, chicken, fish. Yeah, but there's no reason to keep, have this on right now if I'm
not going to be near the merchant. So now let's see. What does that sell for now? Yeah. So that's
pretty cool. I think I'm good to go. Okay. Very, very fun. Very cool. What an exciting experience.
Let's go. My faith in someone who used to work for Umbrella. So you heard, huh? Umbrella's done
for. You don't need to worry about them anymore. You didn't answer my question. What are you after?
I just want to feel good about myself, make amends or something like that. Ooh, stuff.
Oh yeah, this is a mine shaft. Don't you actually ride a mine cart? I definitely shouldn't use this
then. I'll lose all the bolts. What are we doing on crafting? Can I craft anything? If I'm going to
use it, I'm going to use it. Seeing the light on this one. Dynamite has been relocated to the M4
store room. When using explosive, cave-ins are a frequent occurrence. Watch out. That's going to
be a fun puzzle. Looking forward to it. Crossbow's been carrying these last few chapters. It actually
kind of has. I've talked a lot of shit about it. Oh, we're going over. This looks really,
really nice down here. Oh, shit. Okay. Okay. Time for this thing to shine. Are you ready?
This is where this shines. Come on over here. Run over here. Do what you want to do. Watch this.
Hello. It just clocked me in the head with the shovel. I would be out before I...
What up? What's up now, huh? Ow. Stop. How many fucking bombs do you guys have?
Put that down. Put it down. Put it down. Oh, she's just punching. What the fuck are you doing?
I got to press a button or something, right? All right. Where's... There's got to be a lever
or something. Another chainsaw? Why would you knock her out of that? The shotgun is
fucking stacked. Stacked. All right. This way. Do we have to do, you know, throw them up there?
Here we go. What's just happened? Edgar Allen. Oh, looking fast. Shit. Broken. Dynamite.
He just... Sorry. Dynamite. All right. Let's go walk around. Jeremy, can you pause the stream?
I got to go to bed. Um, is it good now? Okay. Time to walk around and make sure I didn't
miss anything, which there's a bunch of shit. Yep. Very cool. Just screenshot the stream.
All right. There are actually a couple of few things I missed. There. Okay. There's one over
this way. Herb. Yep. There's my bolts back. I hear one of those things. Where is it? The other
treasure is up there. All right. Let's get out of here. Just a legendary loot. Oh, I think I got
everything. I have to go around and drop down. All right. Seen like an hour when they finished
this. That's not a puzzle. That's not a puzzle. Jesus. Oh, I didn't know it was going to roll
all the way. I thought it was going to cave in. Wait a minute. Why did it take arrows from me?
I had 12 before. Okay. I just almost freaked out. I was going to say I don't have to do the whole
thing over. Right. Okay. There we go. I got to get all the stuff again. This one and it's hanging
up here. That one. And there's one across there that way. Wait, is it? No, it's in that little
quarter. It's my favorite tea. I really like green tea. Oh, no, I already did this. I like green. I
like, um, I like white tea. Okay, let's go. I should black tea kind of has a very distinct
kind of bitter flavor that I don't really love. I love it when it's here's the thing. I know a
lot of you probably are going to agree with this and we're just going to talk about it for a second.
If I make, if I brew black tea and I put sugar in it or I sweetened it somehow, I don't even,
it doesn't, it's so it's different than if you were to buy an iced tea from the store and drink
it in just a sweetened iced tea. It tastes way better to me and I can never figure out why.
Brewing black tea and putting sugar in it still tastes kind of bitter with sugary sweetness flavor,
but getting an iced tea like a brisk or like a Lipton iced tea or something. They don't,
it tastes different. Is it just more sugar and just more lemon? I, green tea is my favorite
though for sure. I love green tea. You handle yourself pretty well. You sure you're just a
researcher? I'm just an average guy who... Give me the heal. I was like, where's my bass? I ate
that two hours ago. Did I tell you guys it just kind of reminded me? I was like, where is it? I
didn't, where's my bass? I want it. I was, what happened to my bass? Just unlocked a memory when
I was younger. I want to say when I was like, maybe like late teens, I want to say. I remember
I scratched a scratch ticket and one, I won a couple hundred dollars on a scratch ticket
when I was like, I don't know, maybe it had to have been like 19 or something. And I was like,
holy shit dude, fucking 300 bucks. And I kept looking for that money for like a year and later.
I was like, no, wait, I got money. Cause I, I won that scratch, I scratched off that fucking
300 bucks. I got money. And it was like, no, you don't, you don't. It's been spent. It was spent.
It's been like two years, dude. You didn't, the money's not there anymore. You spent it all on
Diablo too. I wasn't even looking and it scared me. I was reading chat. Oh shit. I forgot about
this. This is going to be awful. I forget this is, there's a strategy here. This is an unfair tag
team. I just, I'm dead, dude. I'm running around looting the fucking area. I get stomped. Pay
attention, dude. I get my head bitten off. Oh yeah. I have to do that because I just, I'll forget to
pick up this stuff. Let's go. What? Oh, dump them. Dump them. Dump them. Dump them. Dump them. Get
them to chase. Get them to chase. Over here. Get over here. Come over here. Luis, get him over,
come over this. What are you doing? Why does he keep moving? Oh, fuck you.
Luis, out of the way. All right, there's one. This one. Get, get off. Where you going? Where is he?
Where'd he go? That's a lot of dynamite, man. What do you want? Shoot it. Whoa. No, get off. Get off.
Get off. Get off. Get off. What am I doing? Shit. I was supposed to drop them. I, it was a stupid
indicator popped up on the screen. No, stop shooting him. Stop shooting him. Let him get
into the, stop shooting him. Let him get into the middle. No, he's getting out again. Stop shooting.
Stop shooting. Rip items. Rip items. I don't, I don't get anything for, well, here's the argument
I'm going to make to you. I probably would have gone through a bunch of this ammo, right? So,
technically I saved ammo, but I didn't get like 20, $30,000. Oh, well, it's all right. I actually
have a ton of ammo now. Is that everything? That's everything. That's fun. They only drop rubies.
That's kind of sad because I think I need a ruby. Purple gem. An amethyst doesn't drop from either
one of those two, right? Cause that would actually be bad. I would actually restart for that. It's
random.
Saying that sentence winded him. You just fought two giants. Yeah, an hour ago. Time moves much
differently in this game. I think we're, we're here for like six or seven days, aren't we? And
it's just kind of at each chapter is like another day. I'm making all of that up. You're not
suggesting we ride this thing. He hasn't pissed one time. Oh, you don't know that need a yellow herb.
Very bad. Let's go. Give us a push. What were you calling something on this? It's moving.
This should speed things up a bit. I can't believe I'm doing this. Hey, we're in a hurry, right?
By the way, what now? That was a little drop. Wasn't even scary. Oh, you have to lean.
Why is it going to flip? Why are we going so far off the rails? Dude, dude, shot the gun out of his
hand. Jesus, I'm on it. What was that guy doing? Why are we going so slow? Got it.
That was fun. That was pretty sick. Hold on. I hear like a, Whoa, watch this. Don't ever hold
your hand out like that. You should have, you should have been behind your back or something,
man. Eggs in here. Is that it? There's something else over here. Besides this,
there's something else, right? No, that way. Can I climb that? No. Very cool. I got all my
arrows back. All right. Cart ride part two. Play Donkey Kong music actually would be kind of funny.
I can't really all tap right now though. Do they die from that? Or is it? I don't know.
I just want to see. They really just throw you right in, huh? What the fuck? Are you shitting me?
I feel like that's another player playing Mario Kart or something.
Fuck. What's wrong with Luke? What's wrong with him? What's wrong with him?
Why is he just lifeless right now? We're good. That didn't work.
Kitchen Nightmares sounds, it really kind of works. Kitchen Nightmares.
That's so stupid. Wait a minute. There is a jewel over there. How do I get over there?
How do I get over there? Shit. Did I miss it? Maybe from here? Oh well. Maybe it's under me.
Shit. Did I miss it? Maybe from here? Oh well. Maybe it's under me.
I didn't even see it. I missed. You know what? It's the sound effect for me. It's just the loud
sound. Unexpected loud sound effects. Maybe I can get it. Wait a minute. What's down here?
I definitely can get it from here. That's what I'm looking for. Destroy all the entrances to the
hive. Too many have lost their lives in the never-ending swarm of insects. It's a plague.
Destroy the entrances to their gigantic hive. You got it. All right. Entrances. That's an entrance
right there. Is it not? Oh my god. No. Wait. Is it? That's it. Yeah, it is. That's it. Am I wasting
ammo right now? Get more. Oh, sapphire. All right. Do we need to jump up this? Can we not jump up
this together? Are you kidding me? What the duck is that? I don't know. Good question.
What? That's gone now, dude. All right. There's only one more right here. Hooray. Mission
accomplished. What happened to Ashley? It's a very, very good question. She was taken and then
I kind of lost track after I started doing the gumball machine over and over again.
But we'll be good. There is that over there. There's a gem or jewel over there somewhere.
That was not very good. I could do that better. There's all kinds of gems, jewels. That one's
better. Use that one. That's a weird place for that. I don't know why it's here. Maybe I have
to run back with a bunch of things attacking me. Yes. Can I destroy the hive? Why am I still getting
attacked? Oh, it's in here. Oh, you're welcome. Got a selection of good things on sale. I could
buy a bunch of these. I have learned how many sapphires I have. Holy shit. I'll do two blue
with the one green in here. Change clothes. I will in like six or seven days.
Your fools won't do you much good in the gray. Stranger, I'll pay a pretty penny for that.
Your weapons are in good hands, mate. I'll see you right. It doesn't get any better than that.
It's a veritable work of art, mate. Will that come back any time?
Now the quest to make a shitload of shotgun ammo begins. Okay, I want to make sure I have my
shotgun thing on. Gunpowder is the case that I have on. Go for it. Come on. Come on. 21. The quest
to get this to 50. Don't get yourself killed now. What can I interest you in?
Ruby's all rubbish. It makes no difference. Pleasure doing business with you.
Come back any time. You're wearing a Zoolander outfit. Dude, just wait until I put
48 rounds in this thing. I'm going to shoot 50 times in a row at the last boss and it's going
to be fucking hilarious. I'm going for the comedy run at this point. Let me kill this. Can I not
get up there? I don't think I can do it. Oh well. Oh well. Aren't you cheating at this game? I turn
unlimited ammo on when I have trouble. It's like half the game. Unlimited ammo invincibility
is turned on every few minutes or so. How'd he get the outfit? I paid an extra $10.
We made it all this way. You know it means we're almost... Almost what?
Luis! Long time no see, rookie. Major Krauser? What the hell? Why? Recovering stolen goods
and killing a few rats along the way. Easy work. Ashley, it was you. Catch on quick.
Didn't I teach you? Knives are faster.
One, two, three, four, five, six, seven, eight, nine, ten, eleven. Oh yeah. You fast enough for that?
We are just getting started, rookie. Are you being controlled by that cult?
This has nothing to do with them. I'm a free man who made a choice.
Ow. Getting parried. Oh, you got parried five times in a row, man.
This is a fun fight with a parry.
Good day, my friend. And such a loss to the ladies of the world.
Don't talk. Take this. The key to my laboratory. Go there and remove those damn parasites.
No. I got it for you. I go, smoking is bad for you. Don't smoke. I don't do it.
I lead a pretty shitty life. But now, hey, what do you think Leon can change, right?
Shit. Crazy. A lot of points. Oh, the exclusive upgrade, right? Ooh,
parry all of Jack Prowzer's five consecutive attacks. That's pretty good, too.
I was wondering. I felt like I got those off pretty well.
I gotta pee again. I'll be right back. I'm back. Do you guys like that I do that now?
I give the little... That's not so crazy.
I like somebody said he saw the cigarette and needed to have a smoke break.
No, I just really had to pee. I drank a lot of water. Trying to stay hydrated.
Well, not a lot. That's not necessarily true.
You don't have to hide it. We know you want to cry.
What do you mean cry? Oh, because of... Oh, I see what you said.
Costume change? Yeah, I'll put here on. I just saved her, right? Give me a sec.
Well, might as well just try them all.
We haven't seen Ashley yet, so just make it normal. We had to see all the costumes.
Oh, hold on. You can't see. We gotta see them all.
It's not like we're not gonna do this. After we play this for like a chapter, I'll take it off.
We'll go back to the... Actually, I like this one. This one's actually good.
They're all good for different reasons. They're all fun.
All right, let's go. Sunglasses are going to be taken off.
I know. Shocking. No sound. Oh, shit. There you go.
Don't get away with this, Krauser. Geez. I feel like I should have a sword.
There's lots of... Actually, there... I gotta loot this whole area. This whole place.
There's one other herb over here, right? Okay.
You're a rogue with a crossbow and daggers. Actually, kind of true.
I do have a crossbow. That's right. I am playing the part.
Knight with a shotgun and a cell phone.
Leon, there's only time to say this once, so listen up.
They took your friend to... If you hurry, you might get there before she turns...
So you aren't heartless after all. I guess I should be thankful.
Turn on some fantasy music. What's jarring?
Someone helped me recover a stolen jewel snatched by a thieving crow.
I bet it can be found in the vile thing's nest. It's an heirloom. Okay.
Even the very sight of his image makes my skin crawl.
Do me a service and find some way to deface the portrait of him
in the room shown in the photograph, will you?
I'm not particular about how you do it. Hitting it with something might do the trick.
Where is that? Throne room?
That's your eye.
Leon looks like he's got lost on his way to a renaissance fair.
Welcome. Where would it? What can I do you for?
Still can't do anything.
Hmph. Suit yourself, stranger.
Oh, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no. Did I get everything over there?
Is there... Did I get everything over there?
There's the clock tower. Hang in there.
Shit. I'm going back. I look pissed.
Sorry, Ashley. There's items.
Okay. That was worth it.
You know what I kind of want to do?
Do you remember all the way back, like the very beginning of the game,
where the... Where's the village?
The actual village, village.
I'm kind of very far away from it, aren't I?
There's a couple of locked... It's gone.
Has it gone forever? It's locked off? Shit.
Because there's a couple of locked drawers
that are in the very beginning of the game.
And I was saying, oh, maybe I want to go back and get those.
There are locked drawers back in the beginning.
They probably just have gold bars in them, I'm assuming.
Check your drawers.
Okay. A lot of treasure in here.
All the side missions are back in the castle.
The painting one seems very easy, so why not?
Sorry, Ashley. I'm going... I'm going back again.
Sorry, Ashley. I keep having second thoughts.
I'll do the painting one. The night one is cool, too.
Don't skip the cigarette minigame.
Not down here. Oh, fuck. I was...
I just was on autopilot.
There's an achievement for riding back and forth?
I am really very indecisive ever since I put this fucking costume on.
All right. So where are these requests?
Jewel thief. I already did that.
Defeat the strong threat, the knight.
Maybe I'll do the knight and then this one, too.
I'll do the knight and I'll do the painting one.
Jewel thief takes like two minutes.
How come I rode down and immediately rode back up?
Well, that's because I was confused and I was not supposed to go down.
I was supposed to go that way.
Throne room one is a minute, too.
We go this way.
Can you stop being confused?
That's hard considering that's baked into my personality.
And I don't think there's ever going to be a time when I can stop that.
It's kind of who I am at this point.
So I think I have accepted that.
Understandable. Yeah.
All right. Where's the throne room?
Courtyard, wine cellar.
There's a lot of stuff here.
Oh, yeah. I mean, this is all going to get locked off.
So might as well just do a little bit.
I have keys, treasury.
So what's faster, taking the train back and going this way or just walking from here?
All right. Looking for locked drawers.
I know there's one or two over here.
Okay. It's the grand hall.
How did I not open this?
All right. Courtyard is this one in the courtyard.
Someone help me recover stolen jewel by thieving crow.
There's a nest in the courtyard.
I'm going to go to the courtyard first.
Got it. Is that right?
I just saw a huge bird.
All right. Nest.
There's apparently a nest here.
Bro, get away from me. What?
Oh, there it is.
All right. Scratched emerald.
That's that one.
The knight is in the mausoleum.
I failed that one.
All right. So this one, where is this one?
So mausoleum and then this weird throne room.
Audience chamber.
Audience chamber, right?
Ooh, far right.
It's over here.
Hold on. I'm curious about this.
A lot of shit over here.
Yeah, there's a lot of shit over here.
Okay. I want to check. I got to check.
This way is open now.
No, I need to.
No, there's a bunch of shit in here.
Let's go ahead and get it.
100k. 100,000.
It's already worth coming back here for the 100k.
Whoa. All right.
No, my bolt.
Game is freaking legit.
Yeah, it is.
Nice.
Extravagant clock.
What else is in here?
There it is. Nice.
Big money coming up.
The bolts are not real bolts.
It's in the wall.
Now down here.
Ooh, all right.
There's a bunch of...
I'm just going to go through this.
This game is busting.
Nobody said that.
Yeah, they did.
Why would I...
I just read it.
Somebody said it.
Is the knight down here?
I'm going to run into the knight, aren't I?
I'm good.
Now from here, I could go this way.
There's a treasure down here.
Let me just see where it is.
Is it up or down?
Locked chest or something, maybe?
All right.
It's...
He's totally baked doing side quests.
Huh?
Where's this treasure?
I should never come down here.
God damn it.
All right.
I need to go back or something
because there's like a treasure here,
but I'm just getting stuck.
What was that?
I shot you in the head.
Where do I go?
Okay.
Is that it?
I don't think so.
Try to get a suplex.
Got it.
Finally.
Get out of the way.
It's up on...
It's over here.
And then up.
What did that do?
He can't aim.
Yes, I can.
Nice.
Oh, it's worth it for sure.
Absolutely worth it.
Nice.
I hear...
Where is it?
I don't think I'm going to get them all,
but the germ of bussin'.
All right.
Now to make this...
I think I'm just going to take it.
I'm almost at max health.
Stop saying that.
I'm sorry.
I could probably take one more hit,
so maybe not.
All right.
Now here's a good question.
How do I get the hell out of here?
And where do I need...
What do I want to go from here?
This way, right?
Straight through here, right?
Maybe.
I haven't been this way.
All right.
Another treasure.
Oh, there's a gunpowder.
Nice.
This is a windy out.
What's going on here?
Is it windy?
This person has 100 million HP.
Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait.
I can't get that ammo back.
Why not?
Is that for real?
No, I can hit...
There's a thing, right?
I can shoot.
Usually there is.
Why would you...
Why would...
I can't get back up here now.
What are you doing?
What the hell is this thing?
Let's see.
Yeah.
It's a long way to go.
Oh, it's in there.
Okay, I know what to do.
They fall like the sims.
That is all the treasure here.
I should be able to get across, right?
This gets me all the way across.
And then back to here.
So where am I going now?
Where's the mausoleum?
Should I go across here and just up?
I can't make it across this, right?
It's a place where you were with Ashley.
Get the bolts.
Can I?
I don't think I can go up.
Could I have gone up?
Just didn't see it.
Okay, I can.
Thank you.
Uh, I think they actually are gone.
Shit.
I don't see one of those balls to drop either.
That's unfortunate.
I'm glad it took 12 arrows to kill that person.
Repeat that again.
You dropped the thing.
Fucked.
All right, we're back in here now.
Courtyard.
So from the courtyard, I need to go here, you're saying, right?
Down here in the wine cellar?
Is that correct?
I cleared all this from the three-headed mirror room.
So in here.
I don't even remember where the hell that was.
Oh, throne room is right here.
All right, hold on.
It was great.
It was right here.
It's the grand hall.
So grand hall to...
Can I get in this door now?
Oh, some rare things for sale.
It's the fastest way to get back there.
I got thrown to the courtyard.
Ah, I'm gonna go turn this in.
Thank you.
All right, how are we doing?
I have...
Let's go ahead and get that one hundred thousand dollars.
Boom.
Also, I can do this.
Sell this too.
Green.
And blue is the most expensive, right?
Or is it yellow?
Cool.
And then this one is still hanging around.
100k.
One hundred and twenty three thousand dollars.
Hell yeah.
I'm just gonna get rid of the laser sight.
Yeah, what's the point of having this?
I'm not gonna use it for anything.
I'm not using any of these weapons.
Let's max this thing out.
A hundred thousand to make this thing disgusting.
Or...
You get the ticket.
I can get the ticket.
I think that's the play.
I'll get that after beating the knight.
I need to make some herbs here.
Wait, I already...
Wait, what's going on?
What if I had a yellow?
I don't.
Give me the proc.
There's 30 shots in this.
Oh my god.
30.
We're getting there.
What about the broken butterfly?
Do the ticket on the broken butterfly?
I don't know if I'm gonna have enough money to upgrade the broken butterfly.
Maybe much later in the game.
All right, so we need to go this way.
I need to go right, right, right, right, right, right, right, right,
and go right, right, right, okay, and straight.
Let's go.
Good luck.
These side quests are really, really fun.
It makes backtracking way more interesting.
Hey, hope all is well.
Hey, right back.
Right back at you.
That's the knight.
The golden knight.
I'm loading a fucking bomb on this thing.
Whoa.
Yeah, another one.
Oh, shit.
That hurt.
Pop it.
What's going on?
Blow up.
Why is it not blowing up?
What's going on?
It's on the ground.
Die.
Wow.
Jeez.
What do you get?
You get all three colors.
Stop yelling.
You're gonna wake my parents up.
Very cool.
All right, so that was really cool.
That was fun.
I like these little mini bosses.
That's so, what a cool addition.
Found a use for those.
The mines I think carried.
This thing is so good.
I talked way too much shit about this.
This new weapon, the bolt, crossbow thing.
Is really good.
It's really good.
I talked a lot of shit about it.
Nearly infinite ammo and has bombs on it.
Did I lose the arrows?
Did I shoot them into the ceiling or something?
I think I did.
Rock.
Finally.
There we go.
That's so, I can't wait to shoot this like 30, 40 times in a row.
Now the throne room and that's it.
We've done pretty much all the side things in the castle.
And then we're in the end game, Peter.
I just need to go out through here.
So straight, right, straight, straight.
Straight, right, straight, straight.
Again.
Did I unlock this door?
I hope I did.
Yeah, I did.
And then it's straight again.
What?
Oh, right, right, right.
It's fine.
Got everything here, right?
Yes.
Throne room time.
Did I, I left this place in a pretty sorry state, huh?
Oh my God.
Jesus.
Stop.
Stop running.
Oh my goodness.
Spurs don't even have a head.
Yeah, man.
I didn't have a head.
And he was still running at me.
I'm a mess.
Is something scary in here?
We're eight years since my awakening.
Alas, my noble pursuit progresses to its final stage, the fusion of human and insect.
The housekeeper has graciously volunteered herself for the experiment.
I shall pour my whole heart into this endeavor in order to transcend humanity and make
Master Ramon proud.
March, nine years since my awakening.
A glorious union has been made.
The housekeeper has endured much suffering.
Not for naught.
Behold, the fruits of our labor and all of its beauty.
I shall consecrate this perfect life form with the name U3, where three is the most
beautiful and complete number.
I think ten is.
I think ten is like a complete number.
April, nine years since my awakening.
U3, my dear hound, Pezenta, has been chosen to serve as the right hand of Master Ramon.
But is two not better than one?
Now it is my turn to demonstrate my loyalty.
His humble servant, Isidro Girarte Talavera.
The best things come in threes.
Like, one hundred, though.
Denominations of one hundred?
Like, one hundred, I think, is a complete number.
Ten, ten, one hundred, one thousand, ten thousand, one million, ten million, a hundred million.
There are treasures here.
Why are there chickens everywhere?
How do I make them lay eggs?
Why are there chickens in here?
Why are they in here?
Oh, Master Ramon, with tomorrow's procedure, I shall finally surpass the limitations of
this mortal shell.
What's left of me now shall be gone soon.
Magnificent, the holy body is a wondrous miracle.
The fealty I've sworn to Master Ramon is the sole light that illuminates my path.
Our fates shall be entwined until the very end.
Have you ever known such loyalty?
That's a golden egg.
I'll be taking this.
I'll be taking that one.
Cool.
Now the painting.
I feel like my hair looks like that sometimes.
Where's the painting?
Are you laying eggs?
Where's the paint?
What am I looking for?
Got that one.
To face Ramon's portrait.
Oh, it's just...
Okay, I thought it was a dream.
So just destroy it.
Okay, I can do that.
That didn't work.
I need an egg?
Throw an egg at it.
That's a golden egg.
How do I...
I don't want to throw the golden egg.
Give me an egg.
Egg?
Just wait for the chickens.
Don't chase them.
There actually is.
I'm dressed in the right outfit too.
Elden Lord.
I need an egg.
Is this the right guy?
Lay an egg already.
I have an egg.
I don't want to throw a golden egg.
This thing is worth a lot of money.
It's worth like 10 grand.
Lay an egg yourself.
I'm just going to sit right here.
I'm not going to bother them.
I'm going to let them do their thing.
Shoot one?
No, I don't want to shoot one.
Shoot the air scare them.
They'll drop one.
This chicken does not give a shit.
They don't care.
The chicken?
You can't.
I feel like an egg is supposed to drop here,
but the game does not want to give me one.
Very clearly this chicken's in this room
because we're supposed to shoot it.
I don't...
What if I shoot it and shoot it?
They gave you one.
No, I had to get the puzzle box to get one.
You can actually even...
That's funny.
You can do that.
You can throw eggs at people.
Just wait until a few weeks go by
and somebody does a egg percent.
Or they just farm eggs, fill their inventory,
put on all the egg charms
and kill the last boss with eggs.
This is going to happen.
All right.
Thank you for the eggs.
I appreciate it.
Have a nice...
Get another one.
I got a better idea.
I'm just going to fucking...
I have a charm that heals me 100%.
Two is enough.
You've worked...
You've done...
Good job.
Two is enough.
Three would be great.
Two is enough, though.
Two is enough.
Three would be fantastic.
There you go.
All right.
I wish you very long chicken lives.
Good day.
Very nice.
So turn in
and then we're going to make our way that way.
Back to where we were.
Whatever.
I got work at 6 a.m.
Speed it up.
I can assure you
that I am at least...
At least
6 to 10 hours away from completing this game.
At...
At minimum.
Are you seriously going to do that right now?
You're not going to actually make me take this
bunch of shit.
I can't believe I actually had to do that.
Let me just go turn these in.
I'm going to upgrade this.
No, I'm not.
I'm going to get the ticket at least.
Eight spinals.
Four spinals.
All right.
I'm going to buy one of these.
So now I have it.
And then...
Wait a minute here.
Oh, yeah.
The ticket is pointless.
The ticket is not pointless because
I don't want to spend $100,000 on this.
Essentially, the ticket is worth $100,000.
So if I plan on upgrading this at all anymore
or the magnum,
that's $100,000 that I can actually upgrade a third weapon with.
So it's worth it, especially for the expensive stuff.
Essentially trading this for $100,000.
Okay.
Very nice.
Let's continue.
Next place I'm going is just progress,
which is this way, right?
Yeah.
Yes.
Because I had to ride the trolley.
Okay.
Hang a right.
Straight.
Upgrade.
You didn't use it.
Use the ticket.
What?
No, no, no.
I don't want to.
Not yet.
Oh, I walked in a circle.
Not yet because I want to know
if I upgrade the other stuff,
I want to make sure I have a ticket.
It's called hoarding.
I haven't made a decision.
What if I want to use the ticket on the revolver?
What if I want to use the ticket on the bolt gun?
You know what I mean?
It's called hoarding and it's called
having remorse for selling or whatever it is.
That makes no sense.
Yes, it does.
What do you mean?
Then it wouldn't be worth $100,000.
The tickets do not require it to be fully upgraded.
What do you mean?
No, you fully upgrade everything.
Spend $60,000 on the bolt gun.
I don't have $60,000.
I'm just going to hold it.
I'm going to hold.
I'm holding it.
You can use the ticket on any weapon without upgrading it.
What?
I thought it was either spend money or the ticket.
Hold on.
I'm confused now.
Now I got hit.
Just let me get back up here so I'm not as confused.
Give me a second.
Where the hell am I going?
Is it down and then?
Wait, where am I going here?
What the fuck is happening?
Why is that closed?
Where am I going?
Bro, where am I going right now?
Where am I going right now?
I'm like running back to the...
This room sucks.
They just never-endingly spawn.
Bro, where am I going?
All right.
Let me look at this one more time.
Welcome.
What can I do you?
You have a ticket, do you?
Choose a weapon, stranger.
And I'll make it seem.
So I don't have...
This will upgrade the whole thing.
Knife needs care, everyone.
So this will max the whole weapon out is what you're saying.
No, it only gives the exclusive.
So then what's the problem then?
There is no problem.
You don't need to max it out to get the exclusive.
Oh, okay.
Okay, I say sorry.
There's like music in my ears.
So it just...
You don't have to upgrade it all the way.
I get it.
But I don't...
Do I want to use this on the revolver?
There's three weapons that I want to get to max.
And I don't know what two of them there are.
There's this one.
And then there's a revolver.
I don't know.
Because I've got to figure out which one I want to do that to.
Do I want to do it to the bolt gun and the revolver?
Or the handgun and the revolver?
Or the handgun and the bolt gun?
This is the most logical decision.
So I guess we'll do this one.
But this thing is now amazing.
So now I'm going to focus all of my money into the revolver, I think.
If you want a fighting chance out there, you best tune up your kit.
Well, the magnum.
Whatever.
I should be able to do it to three of them.
Why is the third save point gone?
That's freaking me out.
All right.
I am ready to go and I want to make sure I get this the right way.
So it's...
How did I fuck this up?
It's out here, to the right, to the...
Okay.
Is it from the ballroom?
The autosave was the third...
Oh, okay.
It's north of the bug room.
I feel like I was going that way.
You were actually going the right direction.
Oh, shit.
I just freaked out.
So it's in the bug room, left.
Just don't go up the stairs.
All right.
You know, I thought this was blocked off.
That was my problem.
I thought it was blocked off.
All right.
Time to actually get game progress.
Probably not going to stream for that much longer.
Maybe to the end of this chapter, I would say.
Maybe the boss.
I think we're getting close to the boss.
Straight up here.
All right, Ashley.
I'm finally here.
Sorry.
I had to communicate with a bunch of people on upgrades.
You wish.
At the top of the tower.
Oh, it makes sure...
No one to run.
I wanted to suplex the guy
because everybody was yelling at me to do it.
Cool.
All right.
I am almost out of ammo.
God, I like this gun.
I picked wrong.
I have Settler's Remorse.
Fire's Remorse.
I should have upgraded this all the way.
I'm just going to restart the whole game.
Free!
Probably a treasure from that.
There's a treasure from that, right?
Right?
I don't want to miss everything.
Nice.
There's a lot of stuff in here.
Right?
It's 10k right there.
Simple.
Easy.
I guess that big statue does not drop anything.
I know I'm being map Andy right now,
but I just want to...
You got to check it every so often.
No.
God.
Where's the ball?
That's a slow ball.
You're going to make it, aren't you?
You got to be kidding me.
You actually made that?
That's impressive, but fuck you.
Am I safe here?
Damn it.
All right.
There is a treasure somewhere here.
Looney Tunes.
This weapon is so much better now.
I'm glad I listened to you guys.
I like the bolt gun, but you know, it's okay.
It's all good.
Here's one.
Mirror with pearls and rubies.
Nice.
The other treasure is over there.
Or over there.
I think I can just go.
Nice.
Hey, I got to go to bed.
Hope you're enjoying Resident Evil 4 Remastered.
It is fantastic.
There's one more.
Oh, well.
Did he drop his staff?
Oh, whoa.
Don't fall.
Don't push me off, please.
Let's go.
Don't miss that.
Just a silver token.
That sucks.
Ashley.
I forgot.
It's just...
It's so out of place.
It really is.
I completely forgot that she was in that outfit.
Almost there.
Damn, a rifle would be pretty good here.
Ban that person for five minutes.
No, ban that person for six minutes.
We're going over.
We're going overboard.
Nice shot.
She's getting kicked out of the My Chemical Romance concert.
All right, I got another...
I think I'm at max health.
This should do it, right?
That little bit that's left.
That should give me 100% max HP.
Then we don't really care about yellow herbs anymore, which is interesting.
That's good.
Do I complete the clock?
Red is the shittiest, right?
Not quite.
We need a red or...
I could take the green out of this.
That'd be a poor color.
Yeah, that's good.
I still apparently have...
I didn't use all these keys.
I'll pay a pretty penny for that.
Okay, now the question becomes I have 100,000 gold.
I'm going to pull out the revolver.
What can we do here?
A well-tuned weapon can make up for a lack of skill, friend.
Try that on for size.
I've made my decision.
We're starting to get an idea of your tastes, friend.
This kind of work is about finesse.
I've made my choice.
A little bit goes a long way.
You'll see.
I'm going to max this out.
And I'm going to be so fucked up in the end.
Don't get yourself killed now.
I'm going to be so fucked up.
I'm going to have like 25 magnum shots and 50 shotgun shots
that are all going to come out in 10 seconds.
I could go up.
What is going up to?
What is...
What's up, Doug?
First aid spray.
What the fuck?
Oh, my God.
You got me.
Who got me?
Okay.
Actually, let me save it because I'll forget to do that again.
How's my eye twitching?
I have 15 saves.
I'm such a...
I save every two seconds.
No way I'd be able to ever do that.
This is dark Jerma today.
No, it's not.
I think this is pretty neutral.
No, I'm very...
This is...
I think this is...
This is definitely not dark Jerma.
No, you've seen dark Jerma before.
Here we go.
50 shots in this thing and they all come out in five seconds.
I got it.
48 shotgun bullets loaded.
And just because I want to know,
I want to know.
I want to see.
I want to time how long it takes to unload the whole thing.
I want to test it.
Okay.
Let's test it.
This thing is fucking crazy.
Oh, shit.
I'm out.
So I have to just open the...
You know, when like the eye opens or whatever,
just go one, two, three, four, five, six, seven, eight, nine.
Do that like three times and I win.
Okay.
Let's go.
I want to...
Wait, let me load this because I upgraded it, didn't I?
You know what kind of stinks?
It's not a big deal.
I can't mouse scroll to the other weapon.
I have to press five.
Look at this thing.
20 shots in this thing.
It's middle click.
Oh, it is.
Okay.
Thank you.
Took me to the last third of the game to figure that out.
I've delivered the girl to you as promised.
Do tell our lord to not forget the loyalty of his servant, Ramon.
Ashley!
Such a fool, Mr. Genity.
To have been bestowed with lower subtleties.
You talk too much.
I get failed.
You vulgar, alien civilized mongrel.
Not the bubbling boss sound.
Not the bubbling sludge boss sound effect.
Hey, not fair RNG.
Look at that.
Just give me the go ahead.
Now I'm going to fucking unload on them.
Give me the go ahead.
Give me the green light.
Yeah.
What are you going to do, motherfucker?
What are you going to do about it?
Fucking go.
Let's go.
Cue the cut scene.
He didn't even get a chance to say half his lines.
And I still got half my bullets.
We're good.
It's so fucking stupid.
I made him come out of his shell like five times.
You just got clown makeup?
That was fucking fun.
I told you it was worth it.
All right.
That was fun.
I got everything in the room, right?
Let me just check.
No, I did not.
Just go around and look at this.
All these things that want to be to use.
What's in here?
Handgun ammo.
Oh, I ran out of ammo.
Craft.
What's this?
Oh, a bunch of gunpowder.
Make some more arrows.
Oh, I have to dodge that.
Shit.
Oh, I got hit.
Nice ego.
That was so funny.
I loved every second of that.
I think I cleared out everything.
Yep.
It probably would have been cheaper to buy an RPG
and just shoot him once.
It was the fun in that, though.
It is kind of fun, but you know.
Ashley, no time to lose.
Come on.
Let's start replenishing it.
Already almost there.
All right.
Next save point, I'm going to call it.
And then I'll give you the schedule for this coming week.
Still four chapters left.
Five chapters left.
16.
Wait, where are we?
Number 11 or 12.
We still have this Krauser.
There's at least two or three other encounters left.
First playthrough?
Nope.
This would be well of the remake.
Yeah, but this is probably the third or fourth time
I played through Resident Evil 4.
There is no.
Yeah, we still have the scary chapter or two.
There's at least two or three hours left still, at least.
Might even be like four.
So this would be another stream for sure.
Yeah, the lab.
Yeah, this is at least four plus hours.
Where is this hanging?
Did I miss it?
Yeah, still top 20.
Yeah, I would say.
I mean, the Resident Evil 4 video game is definitely top 20, top 25 games of all time.
I failed you, my lord.
I was unable to fulfill your final commandment
and keep the boy from the path of wickedness.
Got a glimpse of Master Ramon's evil temperament during his younger years.
When he discovered a servant mocked him by uttering,
Pull Garcito behind his back.
He summoned her to his private chambers.
After forcing her to kneel before him,
Ramon doused her face with a vial of vitriol he pulled out of his pocket.
The young master watched with glee when the servant writhed in agony as the skin melted
from her face.
His twisted grin still haunts my dreams to this day.
As time passed, Ramon's treachery only deepened
and that infernal cult soon learned they could prey upon his vulnerable heart.
Curse the fiends!
They've manipulated Master Ramon and turned him into their puppet.
Worst of all, they've managed to use him to unleash his pagas
that the Salazar family has fought so long and hard to keep sealed away.
Lord Diego, first assured I intend to watch over Master Ramon until the very end.
Whatever fate may be foul us.
As a faithful servant of the Salazar family since birth,
it is my duty and my penance to you.
Perfect. Won't have to swim after all.
Yeah, next save point I'm gonna call it.
What's the worst feeling texture?
Damn it.
Chalkboard.
Yeah, there it is.
Okay, no thanks bro.
Defeat five enemies with the iron balls.
Increase your maximum health to the limit.
Cool.
And that is it.
Thanks for watching.
We are at chapter 13.
There are three chapters left.
Each of these will probably be about an hour and a half or so hour.
Sounds like this is about three or four hours plus.
It's about maybe one more stream.
Maybe do some more side content.
Also unlocking the other stuff after beating the game.
Which should be fun to play for like an hour or two.
So here's the deal.
The next time you'll see me live will probably be...
It's 1 a.m. Holy shit.
Let's see.
Probably Wednesday.
Maybe we'll do Wednesday, Friday, Saturday.
We'll finish Resident Evil 4 on Wednesday.
And then we will go to Breath of the Wild on Thursday or Friday.
Something like that.
So I'll see you in a couple days.
The games, like I said, last time, the last two streams.
It's great.
It's just great.
It's great to play this again and just pre-experience it.
It's fantastic.
I love it.
Thanks again.
Wednesday, probably around the same time.
Probably around six o'clock Pacific.
Let me just get out of here.
Okay.
I need to exit the game.
There we go.
There we are.
All right, because I gotta get the music on.
I'll give you a dollar if you keep playing.
Well, I'm gonna keep playing, just not tonight.
On Wednesday.
A couple days.
A dollar?
What about two dollars?
No, I'll give you a dollar oh one.
Keep slaying, Queens.
This man just scammed an innocent viewer.
That proposition was said to me.
And I said that I would be playing it again.
Hey, hey, watch out.
You gotta make sure you ask the right question.
He didn't say.
I'll give you a dollar to continue playing tonight.
Said continue playing.
I would choose your words more carefully next time.
Loki.
All right, good night.
See you later.
Call your mother.
Take care of yourselves.
Have a good rest of your,
what is left of your weekend, maybe some of you.
See you Wednesday.
Take it easy, guys.