Good afternoon. How's everybody doing? Welcome, welcome, welcome to another live stream
right from my house in my room. Welcome. Today we are going to play fake, instant fake stream.
Now today we're going to do the Parappa games. I said when I came back after the few days there
that I was going to do the thing, we're going to finish the thing. I just got too far into that.
It's like nine and a half hours. There's probably only like 45 minutes to an hour left in the thing.
So I figured instead of starting with that, we're going to end with that.
Because those of you that want to watch the end of the thing, you'll, I mean, you might be here
right now and going, oh yeah, I want to see the end of the thing. So I'd rather put that at the
end of the stream. So the beginning of the stream, we're going to do the Parappa games.
Parappa the Rapper one, Parappa the Rapper two, back to back. They're like an hour and a half each.
They're like I'm Jam and Lambie. So it shouldn't take us too long. Yeah, I rolled those off pretty
well. Don't do the Wii game. I'm on the PlayStation 4. There's a Parappa the Rapper remastered and then
Parappa the Rapper 2 is just on PS4, on PSN. So this is not the, they made a Wii version of this game?
Parappa on the Wii? I don't remember that being a thing. Isn't this a Sony? This is a Sony franchise.
The Wii? The only in the US one. Oh, one guy said that. All right. Well, whatever. All right. Give me
one second. While I just make sure this is plugged in correctly, we're going to have to do a sync test
so people don't think I have no rhythm. Because here's, I got to make this clear, really clear.
When you're watching me play a rhythm game, it might not be exactly sync correctly because it
takes 600 plus milliseconds for me to travel to you through the capture card. So sometimes it's a
little bit, it's a little off. But if I press triangle, when it's like triangles on the screen,
it might be like a centimeter off. And people go, wow, he's fucking terrible. He has no idea
what he's doing. He has no rhythm. No, it's the, it's the interface. I'm going through an interface.
Remember that. The next, the next time I fuck up a level, it's because of the interface I'm on.
Not me. He's already making excuses. No, I'm making excuses for you. No, I'm not. No, no excuses.
Let's go. Rapper the Rapper, remastered. I'm on the right. Yeah, that's correct, right? Rapper the
Rapper. Let's go. Lying through his teeth. This is a classic video game. It's an old one, PlayStation
one. I don't know what the remaster, how do you remaster this game? What is there to remaster?
It's just songs and button presses. Is it just updated graphics? Is it the music? Like the music's
at a CD quality, not this DVD quality. Oh, I remember this. This is freaking me out. I played
this when I was like 15. All right, I'll shut up.
This is so 2000s. This game is so 2000s.
No, that's impossible. Sorry.
What are you going to have for rapper?
Next, please. Water. Here it is. Oh, yeah, he just gets a water. I'm gonna say it. I'm gonna say it
with him. You gotta do what? I believe. Zinked up. That was my test. Is it good? Perfect. All right,
let me just make sure I don't look. One, two, one, two, three, one, two, one, two, three. Should be
good, right? What's the menu? I forget. Practice. No, we don't need to do any of this.
There's no excuses for messing up now. Oh, I mean, it's a rhythm game. So it's, I mean, this one's,
I remember this was not that hard. It was still a fun game, but it was very, it was very basic,
at least in the first level or two. Does this get hard? Am I just remembering like 15 year old
gamer god me something you guys have to realize everybody that's in their 30s right now was a
fucking gamer god back when they were like 15 16 years old. I used to drink an entire case of code
red Mountain Dew and top drag every team fortress classic server I went into ever.
I haven't let the pups stay.
There's no need to fear because Joe chin is here. I have traveled the seven seas. I have crossed
every mountain known to man and I know that the mighty powers that I have are enough for jerks
like you. I shall put on my magic gloves of glory and shall take you on a cruise to destroy
all of you. Now let me pay of this one incident at this coffee shop.
Oh, here we go again. Let's go. Bye now. Bye. Oh, he's so annoying. I need to become a hero too.
How could I possibly do that? Yeah, here comes the classic song. Welcome
to the fruits. I trusted you are here to redeem yourself and to acquire
skills that are necessary for your goals. What was the line in? It changes a little.
Kick punch. You all remember. All right. This is a remaster. This looks this looks good.
Kick. It's all in the mind. If you want to test me until you're finding the things I'll teach
you. Let's do it. Kick. Kick. Kick. Kick. Kick. Kick. Kick. Kick. Kick. Kick. Kick. Kick. Kick.
Oh.
Not bad yet. Almost bad.
It sounds off.
Oh
You gotta get you gotta change it up
That's not moving
Oh
Nailed it
Good job, you can go on to the next stage now. Yeah
All right
Hi, that was pretty good. Yahoo
That was an awesome toad. Yahoo
The end of my simple introduction
Put up your fists you evil crusaders. Let me knock you out this fan made now. This is a re-release
You can get this on the ps4 store
Right now, please save your play data
Yeah, sure
Next
I would like to keep playing the game. Yes, I don't need to take a break
Six minutes
You guessed that the Wii was bad
The playstation one wanted you to take a break every like four and a half minutes
Great day today. So what do you guys want to do? Let's go down to the beach
Okay, sounds cool
Don't we need a car to get anywhere? Oh the driving one. I remember this one
Step on the gas step on the brake
I remember this
Yeah, the maximum speed is tuned up to four hundred sixty three thousand two hundred and final panther seats, too
Is this a chad chin whatever his name is? Hi ice
Man, it's fat
too
Not only that it's a convertible and it is capable of leaving tall buildings in a single bound
Would you girls like to go to the beach with me?
Sure, only if all of us can go of course, of course
Come on girls. Sit up top of me
You guys can sit in the back
Everybody hold on
You
Cut to like later on tonight when he's sitting in his bedroom with his laptop looking at his credit card statement
And he's just fucking sitting there crying
He's like
There's a flower like me in a car and it could take sunny anywhere
Yeah, I know
Oh, okay. This is it. This is I love this song
You want to learn how to drive, huh?
It's harder than you think it is. It is you think you can handle it. Try this rap
Do you think you know how to drive rap to me?
Here's your license
You don't even know how to fucking use your turn signal
Let's do it
I don't want to sound this robotic
I always had trouble with this
Now turn to now right
What
That was not bad that was perfect sentence that was a perfect sentence
Now turn to the right
Here it is
That's that's why this game is so difficult actually now that I think about it because
If you it's like triangle triangle triangle triangle l right? That's easy triangle
Triangle triangle triangle. Oh, but the way that he talks
Do I know what we stop the target? It's just uh, it's not doesn't add up for my brain
So I end up like I I second guess like where the sentence is
place
Maybe it is
Shouldn't be
Parappa. Hey parappa. Where are you going with my car?
That shit's fucking illegal by the way
Everybody knows that you get your permit first and then you get the you can't drive
You have to have somebody that has a license in the car. Somebody should be like a licensed driver in front seat
Over 18, do you think parappa the rapper is over 18?
I thought he was like 14
He's not like 12
He's 32
This is really a lot of fun nice if we could keep driving and go someplace far dog years
This he's not even this is eyes closed. Yeah, this is fucked up
I can I can understand spongebob being 30
Spongebob has like a weird old person hobby. He goes jellyfishing. That's like that's an old person
Oh
I hope you're in trouble now. How am I gonna pay for this car? How can I do that?
Yeah, I know. I gotta believe
No, parappa that's so you want to sell goods at this free marketing
Is a new way, aren't you?
I'll tell you right now the most important thing in selling goods here
Is not money is love
Uh, this is not the best song it is close come stop next to me the bathroom song is the best song i'm sorry
That in the line to the port-a-potty or whatever is the best song this one's pretty damn good though
Working in the flea market so early
I've been working here since my mama was a baby just because the rhythm is slow
Oh
Learning teaching like siri had a rep
Come on
Sound of freestyle
Can you hold like l1 and and stay on one word you can't can't you
Before listen this I have never seen everything
I have ever told everything everything
I you have never told everything everything
Windows is crashing
Money money money
I know this is a way you can say the one word that you said last
It's left on the d-pad. There it is. Now i'm gonna fucking destroy this shit money money
This is the cooking one
This is the crack crack crack the egg into the bowl
crack crack crack it do
M i x the flower. Oh, this is this is the best song
I lied. This is the best song
It's sunday's birthday tomorrow and for the party. We need someone to get a present
We need someone to buy a cake and someone to set up
Uh-huh, and how should we decide?
Well, how about junkie good idea?
ready
john
pump
I'll be the setup producer
All right, let's continue john
Ken paul oops one more time
john
Ken paul
I'll get the present and that means you have to get the cake parappa. Okay. Kazzy. Thanks for the five subs everybody
Let's all do our jobs and get ready for it. Appreciate it. Thank you. All right
It's left on the d-pad i'm gonna cool on this one i'm gonna try to get cool on all the stages
437 dollars per cake
Trapper you don't have this money
I'm supposed to be
Getting money for the car
Hi, you're parappa tomorrow's the big day, isn't it?
You want to see the cake that I got for sonny
Look, wow
It's huge
Wow
a long relationship between a boy and a girl and then he turns to walk away and there's like a
It's like a scar where his kidney was
Being beautiful as she is sunny deserves
Awesome relationship
The 42nd floor represents all the sights and sounds that sonny and I will be experiencing in our glorious future
Well enough for now. I should explain everything in better detail tomorrow. See ya, you know
You expect to do without a cake
A birthday party without a cake is like a dance floor without me. Do you understand that?
What should I do?
I'm in trouble now
I'm almost out of money and I need a cake cheap cheap
Yeah, I know I've got to believe I gotta go on a game show
Cheap cheap to cheap cheap the cooking chicken show
Today's dish will be seafood cake guaranteed to catch her heart
And now here she is oh this is this uh, you gotta twy
That's what this came from. That's why that's why everybody says that in twitch chat like the w thing
Every single day stress comes in every way. I ain't got no time for nobody
My style is rich dope fat and rich. We'll make a cake today. That looks rich
Crack crack crack the egg into the bowl crack crack egg fuck into the bowl
Holy shit
Butter butter butter joins the bowl butter butter butter joins the bowl
We're making us a cake that you never seen before
Heat up the oven now we on the roll cheap cheap cheap's the name of my soul cheap cheap cheap's the name of your soul
Let's do it come on
That in which we'll make a cake today that looks rich
The egg into the bowl crack crack the egg into the bowl. What was wrong with that?
Am I going to the bowl crack crack crack the egg into the bowl the egg into the bowl
Mi x the flour into the bowl mi x the flour into the bowl
What is wrong with that? It's bad. That's just oppressing the button
Butter butter butter joins the bowl butter butter butter butter joins the bowl
We're making us a cake that you've never seen before we're making us a cake that you've never seen before
Heat up the oven now we on the roll cheap cheap cheap's the name of my soul cheap cheap cheap's the name of your soul
The other day and that one was good a little turkey, but i'm a chicken
Your beef jerky put the cake in the oven for a while put the cake in the oven for a while leave it there
Come on clean the pot leave it there. Come on clean the pot put the cake in the oven for a while
Put the cake in the oven for a while leave it there. Come on clean the pot leave it there. Come on clean the pot
Let's go
The kitchen is making all the sound
Can't stop while we were shifting around all we gotta do is apply the final touches all we gotta do is apply the final touches
Take off the clam and the perches take out the shrimp take out the clam and the
The clam goes there the perch goes here the clam goes here
The little tiny shrimps just go everywhere the little tiny shrimp just go every every day
Whatever you like's in the middle fiddle whatever you like's in the middle fiddle
She food cake comes just like the little seafood cake comes just like a fiddle
Does somebody say this level is bugged?
I saw it all cast like a spam. The level's actually fucked what is it?
So mad she gives birth
All right, i'm gonna get cool
I
Means you gotta try
I don't remember this level being bugged. It's bugged. You need to press early
You gotta be early bug the remaster fucked it. Oh
Is that real?
Into the bowl, oh shit, I am doing it way early crack crack crack the egg into the bowl
Yes means you gotta try i'm doing this for years but don't ask me what butter butter butter joins the bowl
Butter butter butter joins the bowl. Oh, we're making us a cake that you've never seen before
Making us a cake that you've never seen before
Heat up the oven now we on a roll
Wow
Fuck you
What the fuck
Just what we don't have because money and times is what we don't have a chicken in the kitchen is making all the sound
The cake is done while we were sitting around. All we gotta do is apply the final touches
All we gotta do is apply the final touches take off the shrimp the clam and the purchase take out the shrimp the clam and the
Purchase the crates goes here. The clam goes there. The crates goes here. The clam goes here
The little tiny shrimps just go everywhere the little tiny shrimps just go everywhere
Whatever you like in the middle
No problem, well, how'd you get out the tv?
Oh shit, I put too much oil in the pan
So I had to press those like a quarter of a second early
You're right
You guys are right. Parappa's losing his fucking mind
Why does parappa have a three-dimensional room?
Because it's like 2d on 3d
They used to love this shit back in like the early 2000
Oh, yeah, right. I didn't I didn't wash my hands or something, right and I
Get like diarrhea from the cake
It's something like that
She's like making me have to go to the bathroom
I've never seen you look this way before
Arriving with a big diarrhea coming down. What the fuck are you doing?
Fire
I mean i'm full of gas and not the car. No the car needs gas, but I
Anyway, we have to find a gas station right now
All right. Now this is the best song coming up. This is the classic song
This is an emergency. I need to go right now. So do we oh my
Now what what can we do?
Yeah
Time to rap to go to the bathroom i'm just going to my pants whatever
I'll call i'll call triple a
Get
Uh, uh, no way
Did you check the toilets on the right right? Did you check the toilets on the left?
Did you check toilets on the left? Did you check the toilets on the right?
Did you check the toilet on the right?
Did you check the toilet on the left?
Okay, okay, you win
Here it is!
Blast it!
In the rain or in the snow
I got the funky, but now
I really got to go
In the rain or in the snow
You got the funk flow, but now you really
The toilet over there
Will bring you luck, so give up
I got no time to spare
The toilet over there
Will bring you luck, so give up
I got no time to spare
In the rain or in the snow
I got the funk flow, but now
I really got to go
In the rain or in the snow
You got the funk flow, but now
You really got it all
The toilet over there
Will bring you luck, so give up
I got no time to spare
Ah, I'm here losing it
I'm out of here
Walk the walk, even if you can't
Just talk the talk
I got a call
I am a chicken from the kitchen
And I ain't kidding, although nothing is written
You are a chicken from the kitchen
And you ain't kidding, nothing is written
And you and nothing is
Crack, break, fix the door, you know
I got to go, so yes, open up, you know
Crack, crack, break, fix the door, you know
I got to go, so yes, open up, open
I got a call
I am a chicken from the kitchen
And I ain't kidding, although nothing is written
You are a chicken from the kitchen
And you ain't kidding, although nothing is written
And you and nothing is
Crack, break, fix the door, you know
I got to go, so yes, open up, you know
Crack, crack, break, crack, fix the door
It's all yours
This is life
Wrap against the toilet
Sorry to keep you waiting
I'll drive you home now
He's the same old Parappa again
Oh well
Wrap against the toilet
How would that make any sense?
You can't wrap against the toilet
We're at the end
But I want to try to get cool on some of these songs
Then I'm just going to blow through this
Because then I can freestyle
I'm going to try the Burger Boy technique
By the way, I remember when me and Burger Boy were younger
We played this game
And I'm going to show you what he did
I was trying to play the game
At this level
And I remember not doing so well
And I gave him the controller
And I'm going to show you what he did
And he got cool instantly
Show you
But you can't get cool the first time through
We can go
Anywhere
And then I know
Oh yes we can fly
Almost to a special place
We can find
Just you and I
Is it funny? I've never played
Parappa Rappatube
Never did it. I don't know why
I don't think I have
No, I don't think I have
That's Dad
Just how very much
That I care
For you
Everything's fun
Always worth the see
It's just you and me
My friend and me
You try so hard
It's good
And you believe
This is where we should be
I'm a Marvel reference
I have to make three of those a stream
You can't mind us to a joke you didn't hear
This is it
I remember this is
What you're gonna do
We're gonna put on a show
Out there for this town
Somebody say
Ho ho ho
What you're gonna do
When they come
I gotta be what you're gonna do
What you're gonna do
You gotta do what
He's running up and down
Street with the Jews
Sunny is my life
She's like a dice
I can't tell which way she turns
Till I fight
Whatever trouble he's in
He just gets up and begins
Yeah
And let's all
What's the name of the game for me?
You you you and you
I can't pay attention
This is how this is like how you rap with a migrant
You have a really bad migrant
You still have to go on stage
Let's go
Wait this madness on core on core on core on core on core
Some of the characters here could really be described as baby's first blender experience
I did it. I win the game is 30 minutes. Well now I have to get cool on some of these levels
I'm gonna try the burger boy technique
Again again. Yeah, i'm gonna do I want to do my favorite levels and try to get cool
And then crap the wrap the wrap two is right after this
That's the stream no
They were really late when they bought the tickets online
Like three days ago
PSP wait, hold on a minute. Is this the psp version that they just blew up for the ps4?
Why aren't these guys trying to make another game? They were gonna do a kickstarter. It didn't work out, right?
Yeah, it's gonna be like a like project rabbit
I'm glad i'm that reason but yes. Yeah, that's one but they didn't make enough money
They got eight percent of what they needed. Well, that's really really really low
Mighty number nine killed most of these kickstarter games
What money number nine got like how much did they get like eight million dollars?
How much money did money number nine get?
too much
It was almost four million dollars
All right
It's time to do uh, we're gonna play the levels again
Or not all of them, but maybe some of them. I want to try to get cool on I want to do the burger boy technique
What are you talking about?
All right menu stage select
I'm gonna do the burger boy technique. Are you ready?
This is I handed him the controller and this is what he did. I'm gonna do everything verbatim exactly
I remember it like it was yesterday
The secret trick let's see if it works
This is not me making a joke. By the way, this is really what happened
Let's see if it works
I got
Almost worked in the beginning
Is that
Now take it away
My
For me
I should have done that at the beginning
For you you you you you you you you you you you you you for the whole song
I gotta pee I gotta pee
All right, let's try another one
everybody
Don't you you have to remember the burger boy technique?
works
sometimes
A broken clock is right twice a day. I know
But that's still the clock is still correct. Sometimes when you you know what I mean? It's still correct. All right
What's what do I want to do?
Let's do the cooking one. I'm gonna i'm just gonna i'm gonna destroy this one. We're gonna burn boy technique this one
But it's only correct for a minute and that was probably a minute long that's how long that needed to be right
Every single day stress comes in every way. I ain't got no time for nobody
See my style is rich. All right, let's let's blow this out of the water here
That looks rich crack crack crack the egg into the bowl crack into the bowl
M i x the flour into the bowl
M i l into the bowl crack crack crack the egg into the bowl crack egg into the bowl
M i x i flour into the bowl. Oh, I did it twice in a lot of
wrap second
Now we're on a roll heat up the oven now we on a roll roll cheap cheap's the name of my soul
Come on
I'll get it
That was it
Come on
I fucked it up
All the sound the cake is done while we were sitting around all we gotta do is apply the final touches
All we gotta do is apply final touches all we take out the shrimp the clam and the perches take out the shrimp the clam and
The perches the perch goes here the clam goes there the perch goes here the clam goes here
What strips just go everywhere the little tiny strips just go every everywhere every life's in the middle fiddle
Whatever you like whatever in the middle fiddle seafood cake comes just like the little seafood cake comes just like a riddle
No, I still want
Okay, the stars are just making every
Star it's how it's how cool you can but how'd you get out the tv i'll get it now
Guys I just I just did the burger boy technique got cool in five seconds
Hi butter butter butter
There we go
Come on
Cheap cheap cheap
Clean the pile leave it there come on clean the pile damn it why?
Put the cake in the oven for a while
Come on clean the pile leave it there come on clean the pile
I got a little sample
Here I don't have a sample here
Ample times just what we don't have because money and time is just what we don't have
The chicken in the kitchen is making all the sound the cake is done while we were sitting around
All we gotta do is apply the final touches all we gotta do is apply the final touches
All we take off the shrimp the clam and the birches take out the shrimps the clam and the take take the birch goes here
The clam goes there the birch goes here the clam goes here the little tiny shrimps just go everywhere the little tiny shrimps
Whatever you like in the middle they go
See food cake see food cake see food cake
You're not mashing enough
I'll try it again
You gotta get it really early
Mash harder you gotta mash you're gonna you're gonna like actually mash correctly
Into the bowl
X the flour into the bowl
Flow
All right last one last try and then i'm gonna do a different level because this level is broken in the remaster so
It's not a come on
At least that's what everybody told me
What happened? Why did I just what what the fuck just happened toilet time?
There's alternative tracks
Oh, yeah, there is i'll go check those out. All right, i'm going full on burger boy here
Floor kick punch turn and drop the door kick kick punch turn and chop door door or I will fall to the floor
Oh, I will fall I fall to the floor. Yeah
Kick punch turn and chop the door
La la crack kick laugh and their brains open it
No, you gotta fuck love it now
You got it up kick and their brain open it you gotta fucking did you check and right to check the crap
Did you check the crap did you check the tallest?
Did you check the left crap did you check the tallest right
Did you check the left?
Did you check the right crack? Did you check the end crack?
Right? Did you check the tallest corner end crack?
Did you check the end crack? Did you check the end crack?
Did you check the end right crack? Did you check the end left crack?
End the rail in the snow, you've got the book, but now you've really got an end.
Right kick, punch, left kick, punch, left, did you check the left?
Did you right left right left right right left right left right right left right
right kick left crack left right kick left crack right.
Yangen Lee.
Right, right, left.
One last call.
Left, left, left, right, left, left, left, left, left, left, left, left, left, left, left, left, left, left, left, left, left, left, left, left, left, left, left, left, left, left, left, left, left, left, left, left, left, left, left, left, left, left, left, left, left, left, left, left, left, left, left, left, left, left, left, left, left, left, left, left, left, left, left, left, left, left, left, left, left, left, left, left, left, left, left, left, left, left, left, left, left, left, left, left, left, left, left, left, left, left, left, left, left, left, left, left, left, left, left, left, left, left, left, left, left, left, left, left, left, left, left, left
did you check tall is on the oh i went oh fuck i didn't win
you know oh so yes open up you know crap break big door you know crap i got i got gold so yes open
up you know i went so all yours this is life one line left oh well okay no i'm not trying
to i want to try to get cool on wait hold on where are these other uh options where are the
other stages how do i do that change the language
check the crack options
feel the beat see the beat add on songs stage one music b did you check the crack on the left
same lyrics
don't even need a fucking second let's go
i only have one word
punch punch block get out of here
get out of here
that was cool not anymore
punch punch
i already got cool don't matter i win the coolness was off fun because you can't like
say and have like things said it's just like block punch jump you can't be like it's no you
can't there's no whole sentences to play i got i didn't get the cool ending that's fine all right
what about let's keep going what about uh stage two music stage one stage two only has one song
oh is that different is this different huge bitches came in soup super bruce just gave five
thousand bits thank you super bruce they say hello jeremy today is my two year sub anniversary now
let's make this donation let you know how much enjoy your streams of rock never change unless
i want you to show me yes we demand the face from the thing stream we made into an emote
step on the step on the step break on the break now step on i think i figured this up step on the
gas step boom boom boom you say bam bam bam no seriously thank you i know the one step on the
step on the brakes step on the brake brakes on the brakes step on the brake brakes on the gas
step on the gas come on which way to go but it ain't gonna stop me here we go check and turn
the signals to the right check and turn the signals to the right now turn to the right right come on
do it! Step on the clutch?
It's almost cool.
Get out of my way!
Here we go!
Now turn right, left, now turn right, now turn to the brake, step on the brake, step on the gas, step on the gas, step on the brake, right, right, now, right, now turn gas, now gas, now turn to the brake, brake, brake, right, right, gas, gas, gas, right, left, now turn to the right, now turn to the left, now turn to the right, now turn to the right, now turn to the gas, gas, gas, gas, gas, gas, gas, gas, gas, gas, gas, gas, gas, gas, gas, gas, gas, gas, gas, gas, gas, gas, gas, gas, gas, gas, gas, gas, gas, gas, gas, gas, gas, gas, gas, gas, gas, gas, gas, gas, gas, gas, gas, gas, gas, gas, gas, gas, gas, gas, gas, gas, gas, gas, gas, gas, gas, gas, gas, gas,
gas, gas, gas, gas, okay.
So that's that- what about, uh-
Toilet, No I already did a toilet, but what's the new music though?
This one is awful I get out of my way immediately!
Did you
Did check on the left, did you crack? Did check on right, did check on the left, did check on the right, did check on left, did check on right, did check on left, did check on right, did check on right, did check on left, did check on right, did check on left, did check on right, did check on right, did check on left, did check on right, did check on right, did check on right, did check on left, did check on right, did check on right, did check on right, did check on left, did check on right, did check on right, did check on right, did check on right, did check on left, did check on right, did check on right, did check on right, did check on right, did check on left, did check on right, did check on right, did check on right, did check on left, did check on right, did check on right, did check on right, did check on left, did check on right, did check on right, did
check on left, did check on left, did check on right, did check on right, did check on
left, did check on right, did check on right, did check on left, did check on left, did
check on right, did check on right, did check on left, did check on right, did check on
right, did check on left, did check on right, did check on right, did check on left, did
check on right, did check on left, did check on right, did check on right, did check on
right, did check on left, did check on right, did check on left, did check on right, did
check on left, did check on right, did check on right, did check on left, did check on
right, did check on right, did check on right, did check on left, did check on right, did
check on right, did check on right, did check on left, did check on right, did check on
right, did check on right, did check on right, did check on right, did check on left, did
check on right, did check on right, did check on right, did check on right, did check on
right, did check on right, did check on right, did check on right, did check on right, did
check on left, did check on right, did check on right, did check on right, did check on
right, did check on left, did check on right, did check on right, did check on left, did
check on right, did check on right, did check on left, did check on right, did check on
right, did check on left, did check on right, did check on left, did check on right, did
right, did check on left, did check on right, did check on left, did check on left, did
check on right, did check on right, did check on left, did check on left, did check on
right.
Stage three.
Is music, new music, on stage three, cool.
I'm really confused.
It's like beach music.
Working in the flea market so early I've been working
since my momma was a baby Jumping on the rhythm is
That don't mean that you can't flow
In the rain or in the snow
Gotta, gotta funky flow
All you ever need is to be nice and friendly
Remember, strike it rich, the key is low
Save everybody from way above
I could sell a bottle cap like this
I would try to sell a cap like this
You're the number one ruler of the 70s
The skunk over here will bring you luck
The bump over here comes with a jump
Yes, I had a lot, a lot of fun
I made a lot of bucks, I know what's wrong
In the rain or in the snow
Gotta, gotta funky flow
Gotta, funky funky flow
Do it again
Do it again, do it again, do it again
Do it again, do it again
Listen this
I have never sold everything, everything
I have never sold every, every, every, every, everything
You have never sold everything, everything
You have never sold every, every, every, you, you
Get up!
You don't understand what you're doing
Get out of the way! I have like 10 seconds
Wake me up if you're having a trouble
Here we go
Money, money, money
It's all you pretend
Yeah man, yeah man
Now you can get a better car, that's what you
Got a big yard, right?
Uh, uh, sure
But I, I need to get any car first
At least I, uh, got to see it
Oh well
Money, money, money
Alright, last time, this is it
I'm moving on, I'm gonna do this
I'm trying to get the chicken one more time
With different music
And then we're gonna move on to Parappa 2
Uh, this is weird
What?
Here we go
Alright
Here it is
Oh, I was, it was perfect
What?
Shit
Fuck
Alright
This is it, I have to get it right now
This is it
No!
Let me try it one more time
Last try, actual last try
You gotta get it very, very, very quickly
Yeah, this remix sucks
This is like the first thing in the drop down menu
Oh my throat
This is the first thing in the drop down menu
For YouTube's royalty free shit
Nah, I fucked it up because I was talking
Alright
Oh, that was it
That was it
Oh no, this level's fucked
Oh fuck
Come on
This is it
What the fuck, I, why?
Why?
So, ah, last one
It's never gonna make it
Now run with this bugged ass, broken ass
Bugged up, bugged ass level
No, start it over
My god, it's so off beat when you do it the wrong right way
Oh my god
This music, the music sucks too
It's the, the song sucks
It's so distracting
Just fail
Fuck that song
What does feel the beat?
See the beat
You tell me I could've done 16 by 9?
Oh, no, it's already on 16 by 9
Alright, let's do Parappa the Rapper 2
The fucking chicken level just tilted me to a point where I wanted to do the other one
Big bitch just came in right now, hold on
To Parappa the Rapper 2
Click the touch pad to use the selected
Oh, it's cause this is not a remaster
Right
This is just a full on
They just ported it
I think
But somebody just gave, that was Ishanji for the 5000 bits
50 bucks from Ishanji, thank you so much
They say cool on cheap cheap level or riot
Only hit extra buttons on the beat
Look at where the dots are
It's usually easiest to do at the end of the lines with this extra
Oh, fuck that song
Oh, this is loud
Much louder than the last one
But thank you Ishanji
I'll get cool on some of these
Ow
Loud
Oh
I gotta turn this down on my end
What the hell is going on?
Alright, Parappa the Rapper 2
First I liked it
But now
Donut?
I don't even wanna look at it
The only thing that gets me going
Is the lovely Sunny Funny
And her sweet smile
Her name is Sunny Funny?
I'll do anything for her
I didn't even know that's what her name was
Believe
I can't believe
You were such a baby
Hey
Little did I know
This was the beginning of a long
I actually don't know what the hell happened there
Parappa the Rapper
Was this on PlayStation 1?
Oh, PS2
I don't remember
I think it was PS1
Alright
City Hall
Load and save
Or
Stage 1
Single play
That's what we're doing
Little 17 year old Jeremy
I don't
No, I didn't play this one
Beard Burgers
A Parappa Town tradition
No noodles
Beard Burgers
A Parappa Town tradition
Don't do it
I know how to do this
When can I stop this?
How do I get out of here?
How do I leave?
Holy shit
You have to restart
Don't freestyle
I can't help it
I have to
You know what I want
A traditional beard burger
Me too
And I want 10 of them
Noodles again?
What?
Traditional burgers
We're terribly sorry
For some reason
All our burgers turned into noodles
It's really not that bad though
You should try it
That's not the point
I want a hamburger
I see
Well, sorry
But we don't have any right now
If only our president were alive
Yeah
We can't have no baby run in the store
Baby run in the store
I appreciate the freestyle there
Baby?
You're telling me to stop freestyling
When the people in the game
And the cut scenes are doing it too
I have a name with a real man
You babies can stay home
And play with your toys
I'm going to grow up
Still a bunch of babies
I put my whole life into opening this store
And look what happens
The moment my son takes charge
Here
Let me show you
How to make a real Parappa Town
Traditional burger
Watch
Listen
Learn
And play exactly as I do
Really?
Yeah
I know
I gotta believe
Alright
No freestyling
That's like saying a fish shouldn't swim
Come on
Give me a break
Ooh
Meat
And toast
Toast
You got to
You know how to
Eat
I wanna do
I have to freestyle
Toast
That was plus 52
Cut
Is a shake or a friend
If you're hungry
Simply line up at the end
Come on people
Gather round
We got everything you want
From all around
To lettuce
Cut
You got to
Heat
To grill
Toast
Toast the bun
Cook
The bun
It says
It's Spongebob
Cook the patty
Is out
Cook the fries
What is that
French the fries
The mustard
The salt
And the pepper
Put it on
Right guys
We got no extra
You watch the grill
Control the flame
Guys
Follow the rules
Think of the fries
And cook those burgers
Cook those burgers
Watch them fries
Better execute
It sounds like Spongebob
To the ketchup
It's spongebob
Don't forget the cheese
Bring the mustard
Bring on the mustard
And the liquid cheese
Burgers
I'll be having mine
It cooks the best
You better get in line
Now put it on the tray
Is it for you to go?
Any which way it tastes good
You know
Cook those burgers
Don't forget the cheese
Cook the lettuce
Hot to lettuce
Don't forget the cheese
Cheese
Cook the buns
I'll be coming
Come on
Fun in five
Three
The ketchup
Yeah
That's what I'm talking about
And it's Mr. Krabs
And I'm going to cook those burgers right now
All right
I'm off to a good start
That was a fun one
I like that one
Turn the patio
Okay, save system file
Checking slot one
Oh it's just virtual machine
I get it
It seems pretty accurate
Saving system file
Oh it's just virtual machine
I get it
It seems pretty accurate
Saving system file
Saving now
Save complete
Okay
Stage two
It's getting timed up
We're doing a bit off
Yeah well you can't
You can't say it
This is where the phenomenon known as noodleization is taking place
All the food being served in this town is turning into noodles
Even ice cream?
Whoa
Hey
I can't eat this
We have to stop this noodling thing
Maybe I do
Oh
Well
BOB
SHIT
Well
What
I think
Why
Oh
your favorite any which way we've got to think of something not to worry look at
this this will denutilize everything oh the
formal straight-a student saves the day so what is it well push that green
button on the TV remote control the TV yeah it's the same one I thought it'd be
convenient just push that green no not that one the greener button oh why do I
reference that that's what it's called that's the cat wash green but square
button this it better be it yeah that's it here goes
honey we shrunk ourselves
button again so where's the remote control it's not the same after talking
back and forth where's that well let's wait for it
hey this is a good shit fuck is happening makes you feel like you lost
40 pounds in a week this one's a little dragged out let's try it okay no I don't
need practice skip just as long as this thing doesn't go to another episode of
guys know what I'm talking about it's fucking twice we poke each other's
eyeballs out put the kiddies to bed I'm jamming lambie strictly for adults for
what this is great fun kids you guys said he was 32 young children relax it's
okay if you learn the brand-new romantic karate invented by me you will soon
enter the world so here there are no rules just punch and kick
let's try yeah I know all right I guess we're gonna go do this
never pending or is the boss to make a move this time we kept down nice and
smooth
their parents are right here
nice punch
I wish everybody had the same you meet me at the corner
freestyle
getting better
TV is judging me yes it doesn't make any sense it's just like squash blood
all right
very smooth very very romantic I love you see you next time much love to you
too sensei
boy just punch like in space let's go how'd I do 757 points I don't know what
that means is that good checking slot one the airplane guys in this game
apparently are you sure you want to overwrite saving now save complete
level three let's go this is the timeout stream everybody gets timed out
hey grab that remote control how much TV do they watch for a level
you didn't hear that
home everybody's so stupid like you is the whole town gonna do this here we go
hello package delivery
you just doing this on purpose
small and that's what you guys are you keep shouting you want to grow big you
want to grow big do you really understand the meaning of big this is
the best song this is the actual best song okay you see you are very small
your very existence is tiny
I hope he likes this new shirt that I got him it might be a little bit too big
for him but I can't believe he didn't show up but to become imagining that
can't just follow the rules you must create your own groove groove on
because that's the only way to grow all right best song coming up this song is
for me I can't wait to laugh out loud
what's my name what's my name
I just wanted to guide everybody to this and go with the ride
oh this is great
do it
we're back to being small again
come on
this is a good song though
I fucked it up big time but sorry
that wasn't that bad
big big big big the best part of the song
oh
I went cool exists don't you have to play through the game once before you can do
cool or is it not the same hey you're pretty mature than I thought I didn't
play this good go thanks but you're still bigger than your normal so you can do cool okay
you're right that's only the first case mom again okay now that I know that you
shouldn't have said that because now I'm gonna be freestyling every song
checking slot one you sure you want to have a right saving now save complete
wait somebody said was that actually that's De La Soul is it really I'm gonna
just said that is that real one person said that it's not I was gonna say
that's fucking awesome De La Soul did the intro it is they did a track for the
game I believe a single by De La Soul really that's awesome I did not know
that at all you guys don't know De La Soul you gotta do yourself a favor and
just go listen to everything they've ever talked about
for what you believe in
some fools trying to turn every fool in our town into noodles now we must
terminate this action and protect the precious artistic foods that mankind
has produced such as sweet cherry pie spongy moist cake with frosting
destructively sweet chocolate brownies strawberry jam donuts roasted marshmallow
caramel ice cold movies you can't forget those colorful jelly beans custard cream
hot and so we have assembled the special force to act against and stop this
criminal movement the future lies in your hands now begin mission
ha if only pop-up a rapper can finish that de-noodle izer I don't want spoilers
for the song please nope you guys go that way special armed forces training
camp will turn you into a real man a real man
having diarrhea buying flowers for a girl what the fuck is happening in this game
yeah
all right we go this game is weird
come on let's do it do it do it speed fuck me I was almost there
Yoda
let's begin
come on 2162 watching the stream in 160 pieces truly experienced the classic
game it's not a bad idea checking slot one are you sure you want to overwrite
I'm certain complete thought how many guys are gonna get banned today just for
that 30 minute timeout good job men but never forget training in real combat or
two different things always keep up your training yes I hate being stiff yeah my
brain
civilians are held hostage at a hair salon get out there immediately and
rescue what this just train what we sang a song for four minutes what I skipped
that meant the game was all right check that out everyone's heads turning into
noodles
I was gonna make the noise
do you like my new hairstyle I had it done at the hair salon what was I
supposed to do
let's see who can create the better hairstyle but it better not sound like me
create your own style if you win I'll redo everybody's hair but but but but I
never cut nobody's hair before
you can do it because it's our we're gonna get an unjammer when we hear it
we played the games in reverse unfortunately playing air drums feeling
this month I'm feeling this one a lot
I just keep hearing fun fun fun fun every time
I'm ready
all right I need to say die really fast
I'm redoing this level. I have to see this.
die didn't come up again but if I go die die die die die die die die die die
checking slot one are you sure you want to overwrite saving now save complete
we'll do that one again but not yet we're gonna go through the story first
that was a fun song
I'm just waiting for the one that's after this this one here this machine
must be the problem let's have perhaps dad check it out
whoa this is rare whoa oh my this game is really rare hey this is no time to be
talking about games this game seems to be the nerve of the neutralizers what
if we can overcome this software maybe we can find a solution but this game
never hit the market why is that that's because wow I didn't know there was a
room like this in my house dad has a Dexter's laugh there was a strange
rumor going on
that was a lot of inputs
a little concerned about this one
boys
we have to do this machine yeah but uh this is dangerous for kids I'm not
gonna let my baby son do this why is everybody doing the walk freaking me out
all this time I've had many many great teachers help me out but for me to
become a real man it's time I do this myself no dad I'll do it once this game
starts no one can help you are you aware of that
VR doing a bicycle VR
that is
come to your knees
hold hands and hold hands
forget the book
it's coming
the world
TV
baby
go all the way
because you're the one to bring out the original flavor flavor for my people
come on
there it is
okay I'm gonna bring it back I gotta bring it back graphics get burned oh
shit
that's my boy thank you dad I'm proud of you too I want to see cool I'll get cool
on at least one level I promise
there's no rhythm or song here just react to the people holding up stuff
oh
I just don't want to do it I just don't know I want to just grab a kick punch
chops his way into five homicides
checking slot one are you sure you want to overwrite how many people are gonna
get banned now save complete I think there's only one or two more levels left
there's only one spot for one more after this why are people getting banned
because they're writing capital a like 30 times
save file what's happening good job son just in case you need to know now what
do we do with this now we use sweets to confront noodles then stick this rom
into this unfinished de-noodle izer now it's complete
somebody broke this down warning warning we are under attack
level 2 warning the noodle syndicate is attacking our town warning warning
yes what a noodle syndicate tank on the streets hello what noodle syndicate took over the music store
the guitar strings turned into noodles
somebody wrote rat movie
alright that's fair noodles into noodles at the Chinese restaurant
it's showtime men hey why don't you use my past inventions
okay here we go everybody going to war I guess
airplane missiles on it
who's who's driving who's flying the airplane
who's flying the airplane
Lammy no Lammy's not flying the plane
this is one of those dreams that you have that is so wild and ridiculous
you want to tell somebody but it's so fucking strange
and fucked up that you can't tell anybody
it's not working okay men switch to sweets attack
sweets attack
you know if you look like kickball and they put their head down on the bat and spin around
and then they try to kick the kickball they spin around like 15 times
they use that script writing in this case
hey these guys are dummies
what check it out what are those wires sticking out
it goes that way let's follow it
I hated that shit
putting the bat on the ground and putting your head on it spinning around
I always just half-assed it because like I'm not doing that shit I hate that feeling
in fact if I see somebody spin around more than four or five times
I go stop stop stop it makes me like anxious
don't don't don't do that stop please stop
I chipped my tooth doing that
yeah I hate that
snack burgers for breakfast burgers for lunch and burgers for dinner
even at my own birthday party hamburger cheeseburger hamburger
cheeseburger bacon burger all my friends hated me for that
even even my mother she ate so many burgers that did she pass away
no she turned into one
but see I always like noodles more than burgers
actually I love noodles that's why I'm going to have
I'm going to have noodles take over the world noodles are the flow
noodles are the groove and I'm gonna make everybody understand that
so let there be noodles I represent for noodles baby
you know that I know I'm right I know
oh I know I gotta believe
hey that's mine that's my line
yeah yeah what's this y'all I'm gonna let my man
up with all that noodles rule the world yeah
that little slippery thing tastes so good all the time yeah yeah that's right
noodles are a little something like this stay with me now here we go
like this like this in parentheses let me stress the fact clearly
no matter what the deal I crave for this dearly the so-called noodles that you find in
spaghetti are sweeter than idols do damage like machetes without a doubt
I got the flow coming at you live bring the place alive every single day I jive
with the thought comes my direct actions ask my followers
they'll say it's an addiction floor bit suck it I know you all like it
flip it suck it I know we all like it like it smell it taste it
pasta in the market smell it taste it fruit in a basket
Chinese Italian Thai or Jamaican Mexican Egyptian
English Korean anything goes even Hawaiian
anything goes even Alaskan
the best things in life taste good with chop suey eight minutes to boil
and two minutes to eat admit it kid you know noodles can't be beat
whoa what the
fuck
create your own food create my own spoon
there are douchey burgers they all taste good
pizza as long as there's many things cool
a wrap like this like it is a spoon for tonight for even chopsticks
come on kid get down with the met
great taste
noodles you like yes I got it any type of sweets you like you like yes I
got it you like I'm just lying on the ground
maybe
full of prime glory way up above cause here I come y'all
full of noodles and love noodles are the best no doubt can't deny
taste better than water but ask me why noodles are the best no doubt can't deny
taste better than water but don't ask do I no then again
many things can't be tasty corn, red potatoes, rice and even pastries
but then again many things can't be tasty corn, red potatoes, rice
and even pastries so why do I love noodles so dearly?
it makes no sense I must have sounded real eerie the part of you love noodles
so dearly it makes sense you must have sounded real eerie
what the fuck that was 300 points
welcome brother for letting you understand that the man must understand
and keep talks open welcome noodles
aren't the only food around you know yeah you're right
I'm up for some noodle sushi yeah
you ever see this show on I think it's on TLC called freaky eaters
this is just a freaky eaters episode remember there was some lady that ate only cheesy
potatoes that's it every day
breakfast lunch and dinner it was cheesy potatoes for like 20 years
checking slot one are you sure you want
to have a right saving now save complete
dead no no this is real go to okay what if you get some time
just go to youtube and type in cheesy potatoes freaky eaters
this is a real person you can't make me well that's why I said
like if you have to just if you feel like it go watch it this is another
level you're gullible to think that's real what it's
a made up scenario it's not made up
it's scripted
so
there are doctors on that show
freaky eaters
stage hey sunny
I've tried so many things to try and grow up but I don't
think I really did so for today's show I'm just
gonna do what I always do don't be silly
you're man enough already if you keep trying and never
give up you're already a grown up yeah
I gotta believe
the last song
that is ever in a parap again you're about to hear it
and then they did a kickstarter and made like
$41,000 out of a million
I can't
get everybody on
stage all of you this is the finale
finish it out here come on please
fuck you
get out of here final final song let's go
I can't even hear what he's saying I can't even hear what he's saying
I have no idea what he was saying
what
happened
party or what
all right so when I had cool all I heard I swear to
god this is the only thing I heard
I didn't hear anything it was like the crowd yelling it was like I couldn't hear shit
I was trying to string together a sentence I couldn't I don't know what the hell was going on
and so that's the end of this funny adventure
peace is back in forappetown
is your hog on?
he's got cool ones
but as for dad he's still coming up with those practical gadgets
and using up all his family's money but as for me
I'm on my way to Sonny's for dinner
I can eat anything now anything but cheese
I want another lifetime to buy
cheese sounds pretty great actually
just shaking
yeah this does sound like when you put like a song into
G minor it just sounds evil that cheese to melt
G major is the evil one yeah that's what it does
cheese pizza ending how is this a bad ending
that is actually kind of gross
it's gross it's in the shape of
forappa the wrapper
forappa the wrapper two okay now
is there any bonus stuff before we move on to the thing
I kind of want to see if there's any bonus material
I'll play three well that's technically um jama-lammy but um jama-lammy is technically two
so we played it out of order it goes in the
canon it's forappa the wrapper one um jama-lammy
we played um jama-lammy already so this is technically three
checking slot one are you sure you want to
overwrite saving now save complete
I'm surprised they didn't do a third game
even like 2002 nothing after that you would think they would kind of round it
up with a trilogy all right what we got I can do
what stage do I want to do this one I like this one this is okay
these two are my favorite songs these three
one two and three not in that order one
two three in this in that order
all right I want to try to get cool on this one single play
ranking does that mean is that hard mode is that what that means
what does that mean ranked oh all right let me try to get cool
what's my elo in forappa
yes I can
blue hat means it's harder oh
okay that's it good luck see how badly I get
shit on here new hat same jerma
it changes the notes too
revolutions all the time people changing the world with
crime with violence and anger hunger whatever
I find that ridiculous if not meticulous I do
my best to guard my own premises what's your name
what's your name fool what's my name name what's my name
fool fool what's that sound who that be huh
what's that sound who that sound huh hey big kid
is your desire to grow back again
is my desire to grow back back again you came to the right place
I'll make you big I came to the right place you make me
big now oh that's part
what's this what's this a trick with a twist somebody do something for somebody
and make it quick I'm sorry I lied just wanted to
guide everybody through this and go with the ride
whatever or whatever right now right now push push push
button and get you out of this I'm big
what's going on
SOS SOS please handle me with care
SOS SOS please handle me with care dammit
I'm almost up close to getting the lever to pull
I'm straight up legit always in control
his controller broken no to get cool you have to do style
points
I'm going for burger boy fucking
No, I didn't press L
I
Can't take it no more I need to get out of here
Think I'm big. I'm big. I'm a big kid
Choke I just did it. I did it and got to the end of the song
What do you mean choke that I mean what he meant to say is nice job winning uncool
Huh?
Checking slot one
Are you sure you want to have a right?
Saving now save complete
All right. Now I want to do
Winning on cool is all the batters. That's true. That's all the matter. I ever got
Come on relax
How do I permanently delete this character
I
Make no sense
Got I had it in the beginning I'm trying to hit the star
You did you told me to
Sounds like a remix. Yeah, you have to do
To get cool. You can't just do
Cut your hair do a perm. It's got to be cut to cut the hair
Yeah
That's how you do it. You got to do it on the stars
Checking slot one
Are you sure you want to have a right saving now save complete
Let me try this other one. Let me try my other favorite song. I hold l1
Perm and block the hair
Hold both L buttons while selecting let you well you guys got all this conflicting info
Hold L hold both L's
Try again, no, stop
Hold both L's I'm holding both L's did it work
You guys feed me some bullshit info
Oh my god, I'm trying to skip this and it's pausing the game you can't pause
I'm trying to skip this cutscene because it's a cutscene
I'm just trying to skip this and now I have to redo everything again
I'm like holding this fucking control with my whole palm
I
Can't the cheat where if you press in the right stick and point it down before selecting single-play and letting go once you start
here, whatever you said I
can't follow that one I
Have no idea what you're trying to do
All right, what last month don't even save it one more
What's the one I want to really try to get?
Um, I like this one the hamburger one hold R3 guys, I'm holding every button
After this I'm gonna take a I'm gonna take a quick break after this
Crap of the rapper has been really fun. It's a great game great franchise
Well, we're gonna move on to
Burgers
I added some and it's bad. I'm gonna try it every half beat
Yeah
What the fuck I'm just doing it more time
The shape or a friend
Drink
I
Don't forget to be
How do I get more than 20 points
Do I have to be like
You're getting dog hair on the burgers
All right, that's it. That was per appa. I feel like I want to do like one more. All right
I'm just gonna fuck this whole thing up
Do two player. I
can't
One controller
I'm just going for this one. I'm just gonna fuck this whole thing up
I'm just gonna go just try to do as many fucked up freestyles as I can
No matter what the deal I crave for this
Or Jamaica
Oh
Like yes
I
Was that not an almost borderline cool
Welcome
You're right for some noodle sushi do it again, I can't
All right last time you got one cool this whole playthrough that's not true. I didn't like three or four times we talking about
I don't know on like three or four of the stages
You can get it in the first two bars
Comes my direct actions as my followers
I
Don't get it in the next like four bars
Yeah
It's just so all over the place and you see what I did there, how the fuck did I get any points for that?
Come on
That shouldn't have actually that should have been zero
You understand that the man
And that one was zero
I'm not doing it again
That was a nice trip down memory lane for after the rapper do l on every half beat
Yeah, somebody else to figure it out. All right, i'm gonna take a quick break. I'm gonna come back. I'm gonna play the thing
You have one cool in this game the rest were in the first it's not true
Now that's completely made up. That's complete fabrication
I got cool on at least three of these levels
That's the total fabrication
We can see the crown. What are you talking about? I got cool on the other ones
I got cool on this one for like 10 seconds. I didn't finish the level on cool. I finished the level on cool in this one
I got cool on this one
No, I did it. I remember. All right, i'll be right back. We're gonna go back to the thing
See you guys in a minute