Hey, what is going on, everybody? Jerma here with some more Hitman Absolution.
This is the remaining footage I had before the holiday rush, which is why you haven't seen very much Hitman on this channel lately.
And I want to tell you what I'm planning on doing with this series.
To make this go a little faster and a little more smoothly, I'm going to livestream the rest of this game.
You will know there will be plenty of announcements. I'll put it on Twitter and on my Steam group, on YouTube.
There will be an announcement saying I'm streaming Hitman.
And what I'm going to do with that footage, the footage that I get from the livestream, is going to come over here in full unedited onto YouTube.
So you might see an episode of Hitman Absolution that is like an hour and 45 minutes long, but it will be like five or six missions in a row.
And I feel like that's a better way to do this, because a lot of you guys want to see episodes more frequently, and I feel like this is the best way to do it.
So rather than have you guys have to wait like four or five days for another 15 minute episode, I can throw up a super episode.
And then you guys can dictate when you want to watch it, how long you want to watch it, do you want to watch like 20 minutes of it here,
and then wait like till later tonight, later tomorrow, whatever, to watch the rest of it.
I can dictate that up to you guys. And there will be no ads during the middle of it.
There's just going to be one ad in the beginning and one ad in the end.
I'm not going to throw like 10 ads in the middle of the video, so don't worry about that.
I just feel like this is a better way for me to be able to get this series out to you guys quicker.
And as always, please let me know what you think in the comments section if you like this idea.
And I'm going to let the live commentary play out now.
This is, like I said, just the tail end of the last remaining footage I had before I decided to do this change.
So I'll see you guys all soon. Take care, everybody, and enjoy the show.
Are they going to run away or what? Go secure the top floor like you were just asked to.
Let's go out here and make it out of the crowd. Oh, I'm in the crowd, baby.
Stand still to hide in the crowd. All right. Use control to see the crowd that's hiding you.
Oh, it's this crowd. Okay. Let's keep going. Where's the exit over here?
Walk my way over through this crowd. I'm standing this one.
Police officer over there. I think I can make it to this one, maybe. That's going to be tough.
Hey, guys, how are you? We're all waiting for the train together. That's a fast train.
That thing just went 5,000 miles per hour over here.
Let me play the video game. That's good. There's a cop over there.
That's all right. And there's a cop over on that side.
Got to go up. How am I supposed to go up? I can go in here, but there's a cop in here.
Is something going to happen here? Is this guy going to come out?
What does that say? What does that say? I want to see what it says.
This might provide a safe access to the control room.
You tell me all these people aren't going to see me do this? That's kind of suspicious.
Holy...
Right.
I'll pass the window for one second here.
Get in. A ladder right there. Let's make it out.
Climb the ladder. Another checkpoint. Perfect.
Checkpoint. Got to activate this train. Let's do it. He's busy.
Objective complete. Go to platform B and wait for the next train. Let's do it, then.
Ooh, hold on, hold on, hold on. There's a dude right here.
Is he going to come in this room? Wow. No, he's just hanging out over there. I should be fine.
Don't want to go that way. Let's head back out the way I came in.
Keep off tracks. Electric current. You will die.
Nobody there. All right, I'm back.
Hi, people. Looks like blending in with the crowd.
Wait a minute. I got to go over on that side.
How do I get over there? Is there a way to get over there?
There has to be a way to get over there from over here, maybe. I don't know.
I probably should have stayed up there.
Let's just check over here first to make sure.
There's not a way to go over there.
I'm not seeing any points of interest.
I wonder if I can just walk by these officers.
It's going to be risky, but I can try it.
I got a checkpoint up there in case this goes wrong.
Let's go for it.
Hey, how are you, officer? There's another one right here, too.
Oh, boy. This ain't going to work.
Oh, this ain't going to work. Oh, this ain't going to work.
Wow.
I'm standing in the crowd.
One cop there. I don't have any instinct left.
This is going to be difficult.
That guy's not paying attention. Neither is this guy.
So let's keep moving.
I wonder if I can just play this game and this guy won't do anything.
Let's see.
Perfect. I'm covered in mud.
Get out of here, man.
All right, turn. Let's go.
Oh, this guy's coming back this way now.
This guy's coming back. This guy's coming back.
Made it.
Beautiful. Beautiful.
Platform B is under close surveillance. Timing is crucial.
Good to know. So where's that train?
Where is that freaking train?
Waiting for the train.
Do I have to go down there for the train to come?
Where's the train? Come on, train. Let's go.
I don't got all day.
I'm going to have to do it.
Right when these two turn.
When these two guys turn around, I'm going down there.
This is going to be really hard.
Holy crap.
Time to go.
Time to go. Time to go.
The train will arrive in 60 seconds.
60 seconds. I got to wait here.
Oh, this is going to be so hard.
This is going to be so hard.
Oh, man. Come on, train. Let's go.
45 seconds.
I'm going to make this a little bit more difficult.
I'm going to get in this crowd right here.
Come on. 30 seconds. Come on.
Come on, train.
This is okay. This is okay.
Cops are nowhere to be found.
I can just chill out. Perfect.
15 seconds.
Start the countdown. Come on. Let's go, train.
Nope. Nobody coming.
Oh, I'm out of here. I'm in the clear right now, guys.
This is it. Beautiful.
Get that train in here.
Oh, boy. He's coming back. Crap.
Come on. Before this guy gets over here, let's go.
Get on the train.
What? What? What?
Oh, boy.
Hello.
How are you? Let me just get in the train.
I'm just getting
in the train. Oh, no.
Let me in the train.
Let me in the train. Open the doors.
I made it in the train. I made it in the train.
Yes.
All righty. Here it is,
ladies and gentlemen. That was a
long mission. That took a long time.
I only had one restart.
Dual welding expertise, cool.
Pure instinct, cool.
Hand-to-hand, cool.
Okay, let's take a look here. Burning Hotel, the library,
Xing Riya train station.
35,000 points.
This one, this
Xing Riya one got screwed up.
Because I had to kill like five people.
Well, actually one person, but you know, you get the idea.