I'm not thinking about like the numbers and ga... I'm thinking about like the conference.
You know what I mean? That's all I care about. I just care about the Square Enix
video game live conference. Anybody getting hyped up in the chat in here? Anybody getting
hyped up in here? Yeah, I'm sorry. I've been drinking all day. This is just... I've been
drinking booze. So I mean like a big fucking glass of water IQ. Damn. Shave? Probably lay
after tonight. Alright, so we're gonna do one last break and then we're gonna do the
Square Enix conference. I'm gonna get myself in the right position. Let's get it on screen
just to have it here. That was MS-DOS stuff. It was fun. Glad we got to play some of them.
They were interesting. Now let's close this window out because we don't need it right now.
Glass of water. It's kind of peeing out on my intelligence. I bring in so many nutrients
and I just pee them out. Alright, where's that browser? We're gonna, yeah, T minus like 15
minutes, right? I can change my category again and not be like the guy that's sitting in
the wrong category. So this is, is it just, what's the, let's see. Is it Square? Twitch
like Square? What's like the actual Twitch page? Or is it Square Enix? Square Enix. Okay.
No, that's wrong. Pay no attention to this. It's wrong. I wonder if we're gonna get
anything good here. We good? Am I pulling it? Why not? It's weird. Is there a live feed
right now or is it not up yet? Let me see here. It should be up, right? Square Enix,
there it is. Yeah, it's live. So where the hell is it? Well, finally. Okay, that was weird.
Alright, Square Enix is coming up. I'll be right back to pee. See you guys in a second.
Good evening. Welcome to Square Enix Live. No, no, no, no. I'm not ready yet. Please
take your seat. I'm not ready for this. The show will begin in 15 minutes. Oh,
alright. Thank God. They had a countdown on the screen too. They're going all out.
Feel like I'm watching a live stream. I am watching the live stream. Something in the
water today. What's going on right now? Something in the fucking water. I'll be right back.
Where's the countdown? Oh, I thought we were going. What the hell's happening?
Alright, I'll go back into the E3 special event category. Square Enix. I can't wait for
Quiet Man to come back. We're not gonna get Quiet Man. They're gonna go bury that in the
landfill somewhere. 12 minutes. What am I gonna do for what? What do I do for 12 minutes?
Just hang out? Smart. Like, you're not getting that privilege back. There's absolutely no way
I'm gonna give that back to you. Tell us my favorite story. Jack and Jill went up a hill
to get a patch of water. Jack fell down and smashed his crown, and Jill fell down
afterwards and hit her head on a rock. Then they got up and they drank the water
and they were fine. Do I wear shoes indoors? No. Why? Okay. This is why I don't do face
games. I told you. Like, boogers almost just came flying out of my fucking nose.
Like, that's what we care about right now. It's like, oh, Square Enix. What are we gonna
talk about before the... Oh, AMD. Oh, right. Never mind. The markets aren't open.
This is what we talked about before. Conference. You have to act like we're there,
right? If we were in the audience right now, you and I together, we're hanging out before E3
and then here it comes. We got 10 minutes. Are you gonna lean over to me like these people
are leaning over and go, hey, do you wear shoes inside or do you just have bare feet?
It's like, what are you talking about? You're not gonna have that conversation.
I might ask you that. No, but you know you are. All right, I need to change the
lighting here because it's Square Enix. What's Square Enix's color scheme? Red and,
what is it, red? Look, I am there. I get to pretend that I'm here. Good evening. Where
would I be? Welcome to Square Enix Live. Welcome. You have 10 minutes. The show will
begin in 10 minutes. Sit down and shut up. Turn the lights off. It's the middle of the day
still here. The lights are off right now. We came to the movie early and I hate when this
shit happens. I don't like doing this. I don't like coming to the... Oh, no, get to the
movie. Let's get to the movie early. Because you go like this and you watch the same
fucking ad about like three or four car assurances. There's nobody in the seats.
And you're just like, okay. Just waiting. And then you gotta watch the previews. I always
show up like two or three minutes late doing that. Talk to your friends. Hey, I'm not doing
that. Have I seen Elden Ring? Yes, I have. I don't go to the theater by myself. I mean,
whatever you do, you do. The last movie... 7,500 people watching the countdown. Yeah,
we got to the movie too early and it's going really slow. I was gonna say fast,
but that was not true. Best game of E3 so far? I mean, it's easy to say Elden Ring.
We didn't get to see much of it, but it's one I'm probably most excited for.
Best game that they've actually shown gameplay of? I don't know. That's tough.
Yeah, Doom did look pretty good. Either Doom or... I kind of do want to say Watch Dogs 3
only because I want to be the grandma. It's not about the gameplay. It's about the character
that I get to play as. That's it. That's the only reason why is because of the grandma.
And that is extremely biased. They may as well... You could have the shittiest game ever made
and there's a clown character that you can play as and run around and punch people as a
clown. I would be... Right off the bat, I'd be excited for it. Just like, oh, I could be a
clown? I could be a grandma? That's fun. Cool. You just ate 500 grams of apricots. Well,
you're gonna have diarrhea in about 14 minutes. Is it too red or is it just red enough? Your
face will look lovely in that golden frame. Dude, I can't believe I'm here right now.
I'm facing the wrong way. Am I on the stage? Are they all here from, like, looking at me?
Hey! Well, there we go. Now I'm in the audience. This music is scaring me. Well, it's scary
music. Only five and a half more minutes to kill. Put that on your wall. All right. The
next... Every time somebody says Five Nights at Freddy's VR, I'm gonna fucking delete
one minute from tonight's stream. Good evening. Welcome to Square Enix Live. Please take your
seats. Wow! That's a lot of minutes. That's a lot of minutes. It looks like I'll be out
of here. I'm gonna have to be taken off after the conference, guys. Oh, and it's
about tomorrow too? Oh, you guys are deleting time from every... You know, I'm not even
gonna... Shit. What the fuck am I gonna do now? Delete the bots. I feel like I should be
doing something. I can't do this. I'm not very good at this. I'm very bad at just, like,
looking. I need to be, like, moving. Do you guys mind if I move around?
I can't look at, like, a countdown. We should have played Commander King for, like, an extra
20 minutes. What? Not Commander King. What the fuck is that game? Uh, Doctor... The
Island of Doctor Moreau, whatever it was called. I just gotta fucking move around. I just can't
sit here. I would be doing this in the seat too. I'd just be like,
go get a drink. I've already got one. Do a backflip. No, I ain't doing that again. I
gotta be drunk to do that. Three minutes of improv? All right, give me a topic. Quick.
Give me something. Give me something. Let me get a, let me get a setting. A setting. A place.
A place. A place. A place. Place. Place. Uh, okay, come on. Come on. Come on. E3. I got E3.
E3. Uh, give me, um... Give me a theme to E3. Give me a theme. What's going on? What's
happening at E3? Give me, give me something. Let me see if it comes up. Quick, quick, quick, quick, quick.
Uh, a game. A game. A presentation. A game. Square Enix presentation. Give me something else.
Give me, uh, give me, give me, give me a clothing style. Give me like what I should be wearing.
Fancy. Fancy. Okay, we got E3. We've got a fancy clothing style. We've got a presentation
for a video game. Uh, and give me, give me an adjective. Give me an, give me two adjectives.
Boring. Okay. The boring. Stalling. Okay. All right, so we got boring,
stalling, E3, game, conference. All right. Okay, let's see what I can do.
Boring. Boring, stalling, E3, game, conference, fancy clothes.
Stalling. No, okay. Okay, just give me a minute to prepare. Let me see what I can do.
Me, me, me, me, me, me. Okay. All right. I'm gonna, here we go. Okay. Boring, E3, conference,
fancy clothes. What was the last one? I should have done this joke two minutes
before. Not three minutes before. Stalling. Right. Self. Go in the frame. Quick. There.
10 seconds. All right. Here's, here's like the here's your improv joke. Here it comes.
Did it 45 seconds too early. Are they serving booze here? I hope it fucking blue screens.
That's so mean. I'll be, I'll be quiet. Please welcome Yoshinori Kitase, producer,
Final Fantasy 7 remake. Are we ever going to see what this game looks like? I feel like
they've been making this game remade like for the last 15 years. Project, gotta speak louder.
I am very happy to be able to introduce this long beloved title once again.
After 22 years, the familiar characters we love have returned while becoming more
beautiful and captivating than ever before. To our long time fans, we thank you
for your support and patience over these years, and we look forward to embarking on
this journey together.
Remaking Final Fantasy 7 has allowed us to dive much deeper into the world and its characters
than ever before. The game design was optimized for this title as well,
and we anticipate two blu-ray discs worth of gameplay content.
The first game in this project expands on the story of Midgar and is such an
elaborate retelling that it has become a solid standalone game in its own right.
Through the content we are about to unveil today, and through all that we have yet
to unveil, we will not disappoint your expectations. Your reunion with the Final
Fantasy 7 you know is near. To newcomers who never played the original,
we present to you a completely new Final Fantasy and a perfect starting point
to explore the world of Final Fantasy 7. Please welcome Neil Pabon, Senior Manager,
Product Marketing, Square Enix.
is a swing of Cloud's Buster Sword. Cloud attacks, dodges, and blocks all in real time.
His standard attacks do some damage, but they barely scratch the surface of Cloud's
true potential. Succeeding on the battlefield requires much more than just hacking and
slashing. Cloud needs to be tactical. He needs ATB. Two ATB bars are displayed in the
lower right. These fill up slowly over time, but fill much faster as Cloud lands
standard attacks. Once an ATB bar is full, you can enter a tactical mode where time slows
to a crawl and you have the opportunity to choose actions from the command menu.
Katase-san, I've had the pleasure of seeing you play the game, but tactical mode never
gets old for me. I could just sit here all day long and watch this beautiful slow motion action.
I think the audience would like to see more. Isn't that right, everyone?
Good point, good point. Well, once in tactical mode, you can choose to perform various
abilities, such as Cloud's Braver Attack. So you couldn't do this in the other one, right?
Using an item in battle will deplete an ATB charge, and if Cloud has the right
materia equipped and enough MP, he can use ATB charges to cast spells. Of course,
this being a remake, we're sure to see some familiar faces. The use of his iconic gun arm,
Barrett is able to target enemies at a distance. Barrett's standard attacks generate
ATB charges similar to Cloud, but his abilities are entirely different. Switching
between characters in combat is done with a single button press, which makes rotating
through party members a snap. Speaking of other party members, Katasia-san,
when are we going to see Tifa in action? Maybe soon. All right. Characters will continue
to fight even when you're not controlling them correctly, but it's up to you to choose
how and when ATB charges are used. You can maximize your effectiveness by switching
between characters or issuing commands to characters with full ATB bars. Every enemy
has a focus gauge that fills up as you do damage. When the gauge is full, the enemy
becomes staggered, and you'll deal bonus damage. Tactical mode evokes the command
selections from the original Final Fantasy 7 and allows players to enjoy battle while taking
the time to think strategically. For players who prefer fast-paced action, abilities and
spells can be bound to shortcuts for immediate execution. Shortcuts make combat extremely
dynamic, with the choice of using them is entirely up to you.
Have you ever played Final Fantasy 7?
That's right. The game has been made so that you can choose how to play.
I hope players get excited about this.
Well, that's a brief introduction to combat in Final Fantasy 7 Remake, and we look forward
to showing you a whole lot more in the coming months. For now, let's see how Cloud
and Barrett do against a more formidable foe.
All right, now show us Cat's Set.
This is more inclined to Final Fantasy 15, right? This is kind of how that game was played.
It looks pretty fun. Turn-based is really outdated now. Yeah,
it is, at least in a mainstream setting. No, it isn't. Not very many AAA companies make
turn-based games like this. What's a turn-based AAA game that's come out?
I wouldn't call Persona 5 mainstream AAA game.
Pokemon, maybe. It is now. Persona 5 sold a million copies.
It's a long fight. It's kind of cool, though. It's good.
There's nothing wrong with a boss battle. Boss battles should be harder, more interesting.
This is just a normal fight. I thought that was going the whole time.
I got to press the button, Crab.
All right, are we going to get a Cloud or Sephiroth cosplay on the screen?
Final Fantasy 7 Remake.
Thank you for joining us, Nomura-san. It is an absolute honor to have you here.
Kitase-san, how do you feel working with Nomura-san once again on Final Fantasy 7 Remake?
It depends. I might be interested. I didn't play Final Fantasy 15.
I'm happy to see that he's working hard on this game.
Nomura-san, please comment.
I've been waiting for a long time. Thank you so much for all the support you've been giving me.
This is the first time you've seen me play on the screen for a long time.
I think it was a little different from what I had imagined.
So first and foremost, we wanted to extend our gratitude to those who have been waiting so patiently
and have been supporting us for such a long time until now.
And also, we've taken a look at gameplay right now and we've fairly showed you a good bit.
So that's why I thought you'd all be interested in playing the game.
Would you like to actually play the game?
And I was wondering, do you guys want to actually play the game?
So we actually have playable demo kiosks available at the Square Enix E3 booth.
So I hope you have the opportunity to try it out.
What did that person yell?
So finally, there is something that we wanted to show you.
Yesterday, we showed you a short version of a trailer at the Final Fantasy 7 concert.
Today, we have a longer version.
You're giving me the trailer?
All right, please take a look.
Oh, this one already was out, yeah.
That's the popcorn.
These sewer rats appear to call themselves Avalanche, sir.
I'm saving my life.
You think he's a keeper?
Oh my god.
Have they shown-
Oh, red.
You all gotta look at the bigger picture here.
Nothing worth fighting for was ever won without sacrifice.
Not yet.
No red and no pizza, correct?
Oh, it's her.
Who's that?
Oh, it's Axel.
That's probably gonna be good.
If you're a big fan of Final Fantasy 7 and you've really, really, truly have been waiting,
you've been waiting for this for a long time.
There are a lot of people that have been seriously waiting for this.
It's taken like two decades.
And you get a motorcycle.
It's only like $64,000 for that whole collector's edition.
People are still screaming things.
A new chapter of Life is Strange?
Oh my god, this is so exciting.
Oh my gosh.
I love the setting.
It's so beautiful, man.
Time to hit the road.
I like the superpowers in the-
I'm not gonna give spoilers, never mind.
Sorry.
I wanna see what his power can do.
Come on, Daniel.
You got this.
He's starting to be able to control his powers.
What's going on?
What is that?
This is not part of the video.
What the fuck was that?
It's still coming out.
It's coming out of my nose.
This game is awesome.
Isn't Life is Strange 2 already out?
What is this?
Never did I imagine that it could be so bright.
The Terminator has asthma?
What are you talking about?
What the fuck are you talking about?
Keep the adventure close at hand.
The journey now unfolds on smartphones.
Final Fantasy Crystal Chronicles Remastered Edition.
This winter, embark on a new journey once more.
Eh, no, that's fine.
Whatever.
Lead us on our way.
This should be fine.
This world is full of mysteries.
Kind of just a lot of ads, huh?
This game's out.
Now the true lesser begins.
The hunt is on.
This is the beginning, your end.
I'm just fighting.
This will certainly be the end.
My blade protects those in need.
This entire event is an ad.
E3 is a giant ad.
Strike you down.
This is our chance.
Yeah, this whole stream is an ad.
Yeah, but yeah, like somebody just said,
normally it's an ad for new stuff.
New?
That's why they removed it from Steam.
That was on Steam, right?
And they removed it and it was like a big deal.
Is this cool?
Let's find out.
Dragon Quest Builders.
The Children of Hargon, the vile cult that worships destruction,
has outlawed the building, cooking, and creation of all things.
And captured the builders.
All hope seems to be lost until you,
a young apprentice builder,
manages to escape the clutches of evil.
Washed up on the deserted shores of the Isle of Awakening,
and with the help of your spirited and mysterious...
This is a really nice looking game.
It is up to you to doth your mallet and club,
unravel the rules of this land,
and defeat the hateful Children of Hargon.
Travel the diverse islands and discover your true potential as a master builder.
There is a land of adventure with many islands,
offering unlimited building combinations.
You will have to master new crafting skills on each island,
with more to do and even more to create.
Everything in Dragon Quest Builders 2 is much, much bigger.
Build huge structures in a larger world with more variety and options than ever before.
And with a little help from the eager islanders...
This kind of looks fun.
The world is humongous, and you'll need your wits about you to get around.
Run across open fields and explore ruins.
It is, and it looks like it could be.
It looks like it is.
Die in watery depths to discover hidden treasures.
Climb the highest mountains to catch the sunset.
And glide home to rest up for your next day of adventure.
But beware, monsters roam this land and will need to be dispatched with cunning composure.
Luckily, accompanying you on your quest is the enigmatic Malrog,
an aggressive amnesiac with a fondness for fighting foes.
Use powerful attacks on the battlefield to take down monstrous beasts.
Yay!
Work together with your villagers to till soil, plant seeds, and raise a multitude of crops.
Can you do this in multiplayer?
Be sure to customize the way you build your fields to support the kind of crops you're growing.
Harvest anything from the humble cabbage and wheat.
This is speaking my language right now.
Tantalize any tasty tomatoes.
It's harvesting fruits and shit.
Big projects require big, big help.
You and three friends can team up online to build anything you can imagine.
Let your creativity run wild.
The only limit is your imagination.
So call on your friends and build your fate together.
The road you build is paved with peril, young builder.
Only you can defeat the children of Hargar to destruction.
June 27th.
Luminary.
I've never heard of any of this shit.
I mean, I know Dragon Quest, but...
Dragon Quest 11.
Do I have to see the first 10 Jason movies to understand Jason 11?
Quiet, man.
They're going to show three frames of Quiet, man.
Or do they leave it off the list?
No, they don't want to put that on the list.
This is Carolina.
Alberto.
And Carlos Mastretta.
We're a family of motorsport fans from Mexico, and we're the founders of Original Fire Games.
Over the last few decades, we have seen a fascinating evolution in racing games,
and nowadays you can drive almost any type of car on amazing recreations of the best
tracks in the world.
However, we will reach time to try something different.
We want to do this by reviving a style that pioneered racing games decades ago.
Bob Sledding.
The game mixes top-down racing with a classic sharp arcade look and tactile driving physics,
which brings together a whole range of styles and eras of motorsport.
We are delighted to share this moment with you and show a sneak preview of our game,
which Square Enix Collective will publish in 2020.
Join us for the ride and see you again soon.
Micro machines?
Reminds me of those little cars.
But you had the remote control and if you held down the button,
the harder you held it down, the faster it would go.
It would just fly off the track.
Is that what they're going for?
Battalion 1944 recaptures the core of classic competitive first-person shooters.
You'll need to quickly coordinate strategies with your team on the fly.
Whilst keeping your movement nimble and your aim precise if you hope to beat out the competition.
There are multiple game modes for you and your team to dive into.
Test your skills in domination.
Capture the flag or team death match.
And perfect your tactics in the highly competitive wartime game mode.
You know what this reminds me of?
Uh, like Day to Feet.
This competitive toolset is fully integrated into the game.
Bringing world-renowned competitive matchmaking.
Day to Feet was fun.
Tournaments, rankings, and leaderboards.
Kill enemies, win matches, and rank up to demonstrate your Battalion 1944 prowess.
And unlock visual customization rewards.
Each season will bring challenges for you to complete and medals to unlock.
Whilst tracking your in-game accomplishments.
And providing you with an easy way to compare them against your friends by in-game leaderboards.
Come on Terry, Terry you can do better than that.
Hold the Axis Offensive in their tracks with the rapid fire PPSH.
Or take fire with pixel precision with the Mosin Nagant.
And a whole host of new weapons just as deadly as their owners.
With a range of environments to test your skills in.
And a variety of weapons at your disposal.
Play as a team and compete to be top of the leaderboards.
They don't look bad.
It looks like a kind of no frills just shooter.
It's already out.
Okay never mind.
No frills shooter.
It looks terrible.
Look I'm trying to keep an open mind here.
I'm giving you what I really think.
He is going to blow her eardrum out.
I guess it's...
They just added it to...
They added their soundtracks?
Oh is this Mickey Mouse?
Why is there no voice acting?
Did that remind you of when they first showed that first trailer for Kingdom Hearts?
And it was missing music and audio files and stuff.
They're really not that great at making trailers for these games are they?
Quiet Hearts.
Kingdom Hearts 3.
Remind.
A developer could have just sat in and just
gone like this.
She doesn't have voice.
Shadowbringers.
Final Fantasy XIV.
That's like 50 weeks.
It's been six years since the release of A Realm Reborn in 2013 and over the years
we have surpassed 16 million total registered users.
Plus we have reached the highest number of active subscribers in its history before
the launch of Shadowbringers.
This is all thanks to our players, our warriors of light.
Registered users.
How many players does this ever need to have?
Two.
Play experiences that are comparable to a brand new standalone RPG title.
Over 9 billion served.
Over 100 billion capsules sold of our vitamin.
Bottles.
Capsules.
Skip this.
I don't have any master controls here to skip this.
We are excited to bring Shadowbringers as the latest installment in the
Final Fantasy franchise for our fans to enjoy.
At least until 2020 March 3rd when Final Fantasy VII Remake comes out.
March.
We need the mind eraser from.
We are pleased to bring a world premiere of the launch trailer for Shadowbringers
releasing on July 2nd.
I'll help you.
God damn it!
I did it to myself.
Square Enix.
What happened to Square Soft?
Between realms.
Time, space, war, and land in...
Holy shit.
Graphics approved.
What O'Riorge saw was the future.
That's how the Zenitists came to be.
They were once living creatures with people that were caught in the path of the flood.
I certainly do not know how to do math.
There is no going back.
The eternal light of these creatures has confounded us for nigh on a hundred years.
For each we have put down, another has risen up in its place.
Born of the self-sane Aether relinquished by its predecessor.
He's having another episode.
That's him.
That's Valkyrie.
Zenitists are part of Yulmur society.
But they must be fed with Aether.
Living Aether.
This world's beyond saving.
Like those who try to save it.
This world has had its fill of heroes.
Wizard 202.
He gave.
What was it for?
I like that guy.
We did for this moment nothing.
Final Fantasy XIV Shadowbringers.
And sacrifice.
The will of the star was made manifest.
I'm staying on script.
I'm sorry.
I can only assume I misheard.
But it sounded an awful lot like you were implying both Zodiark and Hydaelyn are not gods.
But they are gods after a fashion.
Yes.
The eldest and most powerful of primals.
I had no idea what was going on that whole time.
They like just opened a book two-thirds of the way through it instead of reading.
Techland.
Dying Light?
No this is um this is the other zombie game.
There are a lot of them.
No no no.
Dead Island.
That was so different than the last Dying Light trailer that I can't believe that's the same game.
That was the parkour jumping around and flying around like that.
That was they were two different games.
Say the funny line.
I'm not gonna say the line.
Saga?
No I don't want to be I don't want to be like the washed up actor at the fucking convention.
That everyone's just like do it!
He's like okay I'll get after it.
Coffee, Cheetos, Chicken!
Everybody screams.
I don't want to do that.
The guy that just goes to every comic con and he has like the one line.
He did it.
Let's go.
That's all you were here for.
Time to get in line for the next signing.
Oh what's your name again?
Oh Gregory.
Cheetos and Chicken.
I write it on every single fucking person's pamphlet.
Who's your name?
Diane.
Copy Cheetos.
Enjoyed by fans the world over has surpassed 39 million downloads.
Now Square Enix proudly presents the international reveal of a new title born from the FFBE universe.
War of the Visions.
Final Fantasy Brave Exvius.
These two titles FFBE and War of the Visions will be the pillars of the growing world of Lapis.
War of the Visions.
Final Fantasy Brave Exvius.
This is the story of Ardora, a continent of Lapis.
A tiny spark here ignites the flames that would embroil the entire continent in conflict.
Conflict.
By the way guys the entire continent is in conflict.
The whole continent, everything, everywhere.
War of the Visions possesses the power of visions as well as twin princes.
The great western kingdom governed by a policy of peace and its brave and wise king.
Venice where the king of the savages has organized the barbarian tribes into Ardora's
mightiest militant state.
Weset the great eastern kingdom over which reigns its icy desolate.
How many more kingdoms are there?
Crystal Sanctum, a religious city-state with believers throughout Ardora.
Founded by one who claims to be god.
Can't you all get along?
How many kingdoms you got?
Each burden with its own dignity.
Thus is the curtain drawn on a struggle in which the fate of the nations rests.
Is for one's homeland.
War of the Visions.
Final Fantasy Brave Exvius.
Now in development.
Final Fantasy Constant Conflict.
All right.
Okay.
Impressive.
Outriders.
Welcome to E3.
Where all of our trailers could be any fucking game.
Close up of somebody's like burnt scratched face.
Long shot of three or four of us standing in front of different buildings.
And laser gunfire.
Guess what it could be.
Who knows?
Please welcome Sebastian Wojciechowski.
Studio head.
People can fly.
Good evening ladies and gentlemen.
I'm Sebastian Wojciechowski.
Studio head that people can fly.
The studio behind Bulletstorm and Geese of War Judgment.
Yeah.
Any Bulletstorm fans in the house?
Which one of these didn't cancel?
Wow.
Let me tell you.
It feels great to be here.
It's amazing to be able to finally announce.
Outriders.
The whole person was happy about that.
Looks like Bulletstorm in here.
I'd like to thank the team at People Can Fly.
You guys are amazing.
And I know that some of you are watching this live.
Even though it's 4 a.m. in the morning in Poland.
So make a noise for them please.
Thank you.
You should tell us to wake everybody up across the world.
For the help and support as we work together on this exciting new IP.
You know over the past few years.
People Can Fly has grown to over 200 developers.
And four studios across Poland.
The UK.
And most recently the U.S.
To bring you what is our most ambitious shooter to date.
To present more.
To present more of our vision.
I would like to take this moment to introduce a short video.
From our game director.
Am I right?
Bartek Mita.
So thanks a lot.
More on Outriders this winter.
Thank you.
Shooters are in our DNA.
It's our passion.
And it's what we do.
Didn't your room get any darker?
Outriders draws on all our experience from all our previous titles.
It's a game we wanted to make for a very long time.
We describe Outriders as a dark model shooter.
Built with traditional bodies.
By that I mean we are creating an experience with a strong story.
That you can enjoy with your friends or on your own.
We want to tell a complete story.
I already forgot.
We are confident.
We are building a shooter with a powerful gunplay.
Sliders.
Incredible weaponry.
Long sliders what is it called?
We want to spend many hours in.
It's a game we've had in our heads ever since.
Outsiders?
No.
Outriders is a one-two or three-player drop-in drop-out cop shooter.
In our game you recreate your own Outrider.
And journey across the hostile planet of Dino.
In search of the source of a new strategy.
It's a pretty dark and unforgiving world.
And yes there is a lot more depth to the game.
But I can't say too much more right now.
Is William Neeson jumping over a fence or what's going on here with these cuts?
Come on that was that was that was fucking with it.
No gameplay unfortunately we don't get that.
Reincarnation is the foundation of our way of life.
For a second I think somebody about to make your room smaller.
How the fuck am I going to do that?
And offer up prayers for the next.
It is grief of death which shackles the living.
And causes the dead to stray.
Indeed there is no greater affront to reincarnation.
So we turn our grief to joy as we send off the dead.
But the souls of those who held back their tears in life.
Still need salvation in death.
This is a new PS Vita game?
A duty that falls to the Watchers.
PS Vita is discontinued.
The Watchers sever the bonds that tie the lost to this world.
And send them off to the next.
They've been working on this for a long time.
Unfortunately the code was already there for this to be on the Vita.
They prize life above all else.
Looks pretty fun.
This looks pretty cool.
Alright everybody hold on.
This is the story of one Watcher.
I'm not even going to taste.
That's the thing that sucks about a lot of E3.
Like they don't even give you a taste of what this is going to be.
They just put the flavor in a fucking diluted spray bottle
and like spray you in the face twice.
And then they run.
Does that mean I want to taste it?
Final Fantasy.
This is Final Fantasy VIII.
Final Fantasy Skate.
Final Fantasy VIII.
Is this a, are we getting a re-release onto Steve or something?
This week?
Final Fantasy VIII.
Green map.
That didn't look very green actually.
That looked pretty, that looked really similar to what it looked like when it released didn't it?
Well this, okay hold on.
This is the Marvel game.
The Avengers.
Thor.
Tony check it out.
At once.
Try to keep up.
Who's the villain?
She's just got a whole lot more interesting.
Or is it a group of villains?
That was just a guy.
That was the pilot.
He's just.
Is that a joke?
He's like a superhero power.
They got pulsar tanking.
Oh shit.
Some say they were set up.
Others call them murderers.
Do the Avengers pose a danger to society?
That was the question Bruce.
That was the question.
Well why did Thor have a lowly Halloween costume on his chest?
That's not how this story ends.
Well what are we waiting for?
Is it Galactus?
Oh he's huge.
Please welcome Sean Eskai.
Creative director Crystal Dynamics.
And Bill Roseman.
Vice president and creative director Marvel games.
Thank you.
We love you.
Yeah.
Thank you.
Thank you everyone.
We are incredibly excited to reveal Marvel's Avengers to the world.
They look like they're gonna fuse.
I don't like this whole weird stage setup.
A few years ago.
The curtain's gonna go up and it's gonna be like a trans-blogger fire behind them.
Original Avengers game.
One that combined epic action adventure.
They're gonna switch brains.
A game where we as players can experience in both single player and co-op what it's
like to be Earth's mightiest heroes.
Do I have any true believers in the house?
Yeah awesome.
Because you will instantly recognize your favorite superheroes and villains.
But you'll also see that they're unique to this game.
As this is Crystal's interpretation of these iconic characters.
Our story begins at A day.
What does that mean?
San Francisco celebrates the opening of the Avengers West Coast headquarters.
And the team's custom helicarrier outfitted with a strange experimental energy source.
However the day turns deadly when an attempt to steal this new technology
results in massive destruction.
Blamed for the tragedy the Avengers are outlawed and our heroes disband.
Five years later a horrific evil threatens the world.
And our only hope is to reassemble Earth's mightiest heroes.
You'll play as your favorite Avengers in an all new original story.
Showcasing authentic Marvel heroism and humanity.
It's about losing what matters to you most and fighting to get it back.
I wonder what the villain's gonna be.
I feel like he got that from a Hallmark card.
That was like a pretty good tagline.
Most importantly this is a story about self-acceptance in the face of adversity.
About embracing our individual powers and learning that together we are mighty.
You'll lead the team as the legendary super soldier Captain America.
This is a work email I got like five years ago.
You'll call down the lightning as the Asgardian god of thunder Thor.
You'll channel the anger of scientist Bruce Banner by unleashing the Hulk.
You'll gather intel and strike swiftly as the ultimate tactical spy Black Widow.
And finally you'll blast through the sky as a charismatic Tony Stark.
Known to the wider world as the armored iron man.
To bring this incredible story to life we've assembled an all-star cast.
I'll let them introduce themselves.
Here they come Robert Downey Jr.
So here we are.
Avengers assembled.
Chris Evans.
Who are you people again?
Hi I'm Troy Baker and I play Bruce Banner.
Hi I'm Jeff Schein and I play Captain America.
Hi I'm Travis Willingham and I play Thor.
Hi I'm Laura Bailey and I'm playing Black Widow.
Hi I'm Nolan North and I play Tony Stark.
There's certain characters I don't think you ever have to be uh talked into.
You know so we'd like to have you play Tony Stark Iron Man.
Yeah yes.
We are we are the Avengers of voice acting.
We're in every fucking single game.
We are the Avengers of voice acting and games.
I think he's one of the most vulnerable guys.
I think Bruce is just such a cool character.
A lot of people are really quick to bring out the big green
but I think that that Bruce is a super complex character.
He's fun and I've never played him before.
What is very relatable about Natasha is she's extremely capable
but she's at the core she's human.
She's surrounded by all of this larger than life stuff
and she has to step up to it.
I feel like Thor got really interesting in the last like 10 or 15 years from for me.
I like where he's kind of landed in the public eye you know.
One of the things I think is cool about Cap is I never feel like he uh
he necessarily wants to be a leader.
He accepts that he is.
I feel like sometimes the best leaders are the ones who don't necessarily want to be
but they're right for the job.
Having an original story to tell as well
what they've done at Crystal Dynamics is great so
I think everybody's gonna be pretty stoked.
The Avengers are at their best when they are all together
but the chemistry is do not shake.
Thanks everybody for joining us.
Can't wait for you to be able to play the game
but right now you don't have to wait for some exclusive content.
By the way it's me.
I sound like exactly the guy on the other side
but it's not him it's me talking now.
When he talks it sounds like me talking.
Do the Avengers pose a danger to society?
That was the question Bruce.
That was the question.
Did you even check the science?
It was a heist Bruce.
No.
We were outsmarted.
The Terrigen reactor was unstable and you knew that you knew that
and you still paraded it before the entire world.
So what?
We just give up.
We didn't give up Tony.
We failed.
At least I can admit that.
We failed him.
Who's him?
Please welcome Scott Amis, head of studio and Megan Marie,
senior community and social media manager Crystal Dynamics.
This game might be pretty good.
Hello E3.
You've just seen a high level view of the cinematic
and character-driven campaign of Marvel's Avengers
but launch is only the beginning of this adventure.
Marvel's Avengers delivers a narrative over multiple years
with exciting new content released at a regular basis.
Like the Avengers, you and your friends are stronger together.
You'll assemble into teams of up to four players online
where you can master extraordinary abilities,
where you can customize a growing roster of heroes
and defend the earth from ever-escalating threats.
Oh, yes.
And to make sure everyone on this journey with us,
we're incredibly thrilled to announce
that every new superhero and every new region
will be delivered at no additional cost.
Our promise to the community
is that we won't have random loot boxes
or pay-to-win scenarios.
I love how that's such a selling point now.
This game represents a collaboration across Crystal Dynamics.
It's like going to the fucking dentist.
And he's like, let me tell you something.
I promise not to use the drill on your eye.
Oh, thanks.
I love Montreal.
These guys are here.
Nixie Software, our new Crystal Northwest studio
and everyone at Square Enix.
So our game is about embracing your powers
and living your superhero dreams.
It's bad when the other dentists do that.
We have an exclusive game play demo in our booth
that will show you more of the core campaign.
It's original story.
This would be $5 per stamp.
So Marvel's Avengers will release worldwide
on PS4, Xbox One, Stadia, and PC.
When?
We got you covered.
And we're excited to be partnering with PlayStation
to bring some awesome surprises
to the PlayStation audience.
Google may as well just pull the fucking zipper
off the top of the ceiling
and drop the fucking money.
They want it.
They want you on there.
That will be revealing in the future.
Just sprinkle it across the whole crowd.
But before we go,
we have one final glimpse into our world,
including when you'll get to play this game.
This is what's next for the Avengers.
Thank you, true believers.
We're going to release date?
Damn it.
I have a plan, but it's risky.
Hank, that doesn't look ready.
Come on, Tony, live a little.
Unbelievable.
It worked.
Hank?
It's sort of cute when they're small.
Ah, I didn't doubt you for a second, Hank.
Release date, come on.
Here it comes, here it comes, here it comes.
Whoa, whoa, I don't agree to any of that shit.
I don't agree to that.
I didn't agree to this.
Hey, thanks for watching the show.
All right, I'll tell you, I'll tell you one thing.
I, Final Fantasy VII was kind of cool.
I'm really not interested in, like,
anything else that was shown today or here.
Final Fantasy VII looks pretty good.
I'm not really into really any of the other stuff.
The Dragon Quest building game looked kind of fun.
May 15th, you idiot.
Respect the streamer!
So, uh, play the first one.
I really am, like, in a dark corner, huh?
E3 was pretty, pretty bad this year.
Am I going to do Nintendo tomorrow?
I don't know, I don't think so.
Because, let me, let's get like a,
it really is dark in here.
Let's, let's figure out what's going to happen.
I don't think I'm going to do Nintendo tomorrow.
Because Nintendo really is only like,
what, like 45 minutes?
It's an edited thing.
I'm not sure I'm going to do it.
I didn't do Devolver.
I kind of, I'd rather just watch, like,
the 40 to 50 minute presentation, whatever it is.
It's just for, like, Smash.
It's probably going to be Smash and
shows up for Bethesda and Square and Ubi,
but won't do Nintendo.
Oh, this is about to, like, turn off.
Show it up for AMD, but won't show up for Nintendo.
Yeah, but come on.
I didn't do Nintendo last year.
Did I do Nintendo last year?
I didn't.
I did Nintendo last year.
All right.
I'll do Nintendo.
We'll do, all right.
I'm going to do Nintendo.
You're here?
I just confirmed it.
It didn't last, all right.
I'll do, all right, all right, all right.
Tomorrow, tomorrow is going to be a quick one though.
Tomorrow I'm going to do,
it's going to be a short stream tomorrow.
It's at 9 a.m.?
Oh, fuck no.
It's at 9 a.m. Pacific?
No, it's not.
I ain't waking up for that one.
I'll try.
I'm going to, I'm going to, okay.
I'm going to, I'll tell you,
I'll tell you what I'm going to do.
I will tear myself out of bed.
I will, I will rip myself out of bed
and like fucking get over here in a bathrobe
and stream for an hour.
That's the plan.
That's what I'm doing.
You can't get up by 9.
No, it's not that I can't get up by 9.
It's that when your body is so used to waking up
at like fucking 11, 12, 1 p.m.
I wake up late.
I go to bed late.
It's hard to get up at like 8.
I don't, I'm not waking up at 9.
I'd have to get up at like 7.30.
I got to go to the bathroom.
I've got to eat food.
I've got to shower.
It takes like an hour and a half.
I'm going to wake up at like 6.
The big boy sleeps late.
No, we'll do it.
I'll get up.
I'll do it.
I'm going to look like shit.
I'm not going to be like fucking,
I'm going to look terrible.
I'm going to be unshowered.
I'm going to be unshowered, unshit,
and like unshaved.
So I hope you're ready for that stream.
By the way, that stream is going to be
literally fucking an hour and 30 minutes.
We ain't doing a long one tomorrow.
I'm going to just go back to bed.
I'm going to watch the Nintendo conference,
give you my like terrible dog shit takes,
and then I'm going to go to bed.
No makeup.
Yeah, no makeup involved tomorrow.
Lazy boy.
Guys, do you understand how bad my takes are
for these things?
Persona 5, not even like a mainstream game.
It only sold like millions of copies.
But Final Fantasy VII, who's that character?
Axel?
I don't know shit.
I know two things.
How to remove a wart.
You put, I know how to remove a wart.
And the best way to clean the toilet.
I don't know anything else.
I know about conflict.
You freeze it.
You get a little freeze thing.
You're like, I just did it like a week ago.
I had like 12.
I had like one, two, three, four, five, six, seven, eight, nine.
They were all over me.
I keep like breathing in frogs and I can't stop.
They're all over my hands.
I have like 25 frog pets.
They're the best.
How do you clean a toilet?
Wouldn't you like to know?
What's your secret to removing warts?
You have to get the witch to come over
and fucking de-curse you.
You lick the bowl.
You guys are fucked.
Hey, skip this guy talk.
Where's the next trailer?
Where's the next E3 trailer?
This guy sucks.
All right, I'll see you guys tomorrow.
I'm going to wake up.
I'm going to get up and I'm going to,
it's going to be painful.
I'm going to, you're going to see me
at my absolute worst.
Okay?
When I'm going to turn,
I'm going to rip myself out of bed
and I'm going to press the stream button.
You, it's going to be me
at the very, very base level of person.
Like it's just going to be me.
I forgot about five nights at Freddy's.
Well, that person just removed
a minute from the broadcast.
So that's it.
I was going to give 60 more seconds,
but you know, let's back it out here.
Thanks for watching.
Hope you enjoyed E3.
See you tomorrow for Nintendo.
Hopefully you're excited about some stuff.
Some of that look pretty good.
I actually really think Watch Dogs 3
might be fun or Watch Dogs Legion.
Sorry, at least for a while.
Let me go like this,
but we'll do the bits and the subs.
Thanks everybody.
See you bright and early tomorrow
if you get up for it at what?
Something like eight or nine AM Pacific?
Whatever it is.
The suss will be correct.
I will see you all tomorrow.
I'm going to oversleep.
No, I'm not.
If I confirmed it, it's happening.
I hope you had a good time.
It's always fun to hang out
and stick around with the chat for a while.
So what do you say?
We do the bits from earlier this afternoon.
So from earlier we had
we had $2.50 from Dorkcube.
Thank you Dorkcube.
I hate Jerm.
Liu Da Wang did a stream yesterday
where she made probably
the most accurate depictions of you.
She may have also given you
a sans undertale eye.
I have so many monitors.
One of my monitors is a triangle.
That's fucking hilarious.
Chatter 7369, 69,000 bits.
Ah, funny meme reference.
He doesn't know.
LOL.
What is a meme?
I do this all the time.
I'll put it on the screen.
Every time we have a stream
I have to go back and like
fact check my memes.
I can't believe that that's a real thing
that I have to do.
That's not it.
What are some of these pictures?
There it is.
Two o'clock and you get the
two o'clock in the morning.
That's perfect.
Sometimes later.
Is that Kim?
Wait, why?
There's like a spilt shit
all over the place.
I'm in A's.
Why is she on the floor?
Thank you for this.
This is fucking awesome.
That's good shit.
Thank you.
And thank you door cue for the 250.
Hey mouse, thanks for 250.
We can achieve the goal of having
an only elderly hacktivist organization.
I'll try it.
When that comes out
I'm only going to do old people.
My whole gang is going to be
all elderly.
We can try.
Thank you SGH for the 15 dollars.
Love you Jerma.
Just finished cracking up
with your last upload.
Never change.
Thanks for the 15 dollars.
I don't have any capability to.
So I can't change.
It's too late.
So thank you.
I really appreciate it.
Thank you for the 15 dollars.
Jerma lied about Taco Bell
thanks to the 250.
Devs keep putting celebrities
into single player storylines
for like five minutes to drum a pipe.
For five out of ten cod rip-offs.
What?
Oh, thought too much conflict.
You know what?
I am really excited
for tomorrow's Nintendo stream.
You know why?
There's not going to be a whole lot
of constant conflict on that stream.
Wow.
Nintendo may win the conference
just because of that one reason.
That depends on what they show.
Smash Brothers is all constant,
is all conflict.
Uh oh, you're right.
Don't worry.
Don't worry guys.
Guys like Toad's going to solve
a couple of puzzles in his new game.
So that'll balance it out a little.
Hey, thank you to
Demonic Cucumber for the three bucks.
The purple light
and the slick back villain hair
makes Jerma look like Mega Mind.
Thanks for the compliment.
It means I'm pretty smart.
But thank you.
Thank you also to, uh,
Kyari, Ky-
Kyari 5.
No, Kyari, Ky-
Kyari 13 for the five dollars.
There you go.
Uh, for the Gungeon Cab Fund cabinet.
What would you guys do
if you seriously,
if the stream turned on
and right behind me,
I turned the webcam on
and the Enter the Gungeon
five thousand dollar cabinet was behind me.
I would post the PogChamp emote in the chat.
But then what would I do with it?
You know how much of a pain in the ass
it was to get that TV out of my room?
It was so difficult
and so hard to get that television
into that room
and out of that room.
Me and Kim brought that big
300 pound TV down the stairs.
We almost like died.
The two of us were just like,
no, no, no, no, just look out,
wait, wait, wait, I gotta put it down,
put it down, put it down.
I think I threw my back out during that
and it's never healed.
When we were bringing that
down the stairs into that room,
I think I have never recovered
from like hurting my back
like a year ago.
It's because Kim did all the work.
No, I didn't do the thing.
Look, I know everybody
thinks I did the thing
where like here, oh my God.
You all right?
Yeah, I'll think I did the thing
where here's a big heavy item, right?
One person's here, one person's here
and maybe three of you lifted it.
And you do the like
we're over at a sleepover
doing light as a feather,
as stiff as a board
and I'm just like pretending
like I'm putting pressure here.
But really I'm just making you
you two do all the work
while I go like this
and just like pretend to lift it up.
I know that you thought that
that's what I was doing
but that's not possible.
That's not possible
in a two-person scenario.
In a three-person, four-person scenario,
yes, I do that all the time.
And I'm not a strong person.
I just like to people
to think that I'm helping.
Why is this so heavy?
What the fuck's happening?
I know this thing's really heavy.
Yeah, this is heavy.
Fuck, it's like hurt my arm.
You guys good?
I don't do that.
It's a joke.
You thought I was Jack?
No, I just it's air.
I was inflated.
I was wearing one of those
cheap, goofy, inflated suits.
Spongebob.
Yeah, Spongebob arms.
Anyways.
Thank you to Germalight
about Taco Bell for the two dollars and fifty cents.
You can't rob a bank
live stream the robbery
and expect to get away with it.
No, that's why I know.
That's not going to happen.
Why is Slow Mode still on?
Because there were a lot of people here today
and yesterday too.
So Slow Mode was on
pretty much the whole time, yeah.
How did I react to Destroy All Humans?
It looks, from what you can see, looks good.
I didn't, I saw the trailer
where they, everyone gets hypnotized.
E3, E3 attracts a lot of people.
I hope they had fun here.
Sometimes, yeah, you look over and you
say, holy shit, wait,
there's like 8,000 people here.
Like, hopefully they liked it.
Hey, thank you Rad Sully for the five dollars.
All this E3 talk is getting me
hot for the epic Jerma Khan.
When is it?
The epic Jerma Khan.
I forgot about that.
Maybe, soon, possibly, in the future,
you will see a get-together.
Possible, it might happen.
Don't quote me on that.
Don't hold me to that.
I know what it is.
I wasn't like trashed.
Hey, thanks Mr. Comcast for the three dollars.
Hey Jerma, John Comcast here.
Just letting you know that I'm sitting
in the audience at E3
and I found it weird when you showed up
on stage completely naked and drunk.
I found it very disrespectful
when you DDT'd the other host into the audience
while shouting about how tight your ass is
when you flex it.
I found it weird when you started
to push your way through the audience
taking their wallets.
The police showed up but you managed
to sneak out the back door
while holding a box of AMDs.
A box of AMDs.
Just the letters, not the graphics cards.
Well, I thought they were valuable.
Thank you Mr. Comcast for the three bucks.
Thank you Demonic Cucumber for the two fifty.
I don't think you thought
this MS-DOS game thing through.
You sorted it by best games
and are picking three
and then scrolling down.
Meaning that you're actively skipping
more than 70 percent
of the top-moded games on there.
Surely you should play more games
towards the top seeing as you're
sorted them by best games.
I can always go back.
There's so many.
And look, we don't have to play
the best games, you know?
When we sorted by not by popular,
we got some classics in there.
There's a lot.
Oh, there's forty-three hundred.
There's a lot to go through.
We got to see Pizza Worm.
It's pretty good.
Although Pizza Worm
may have been really popular.
Go back and do games that you missed.
I probably will.
It's just, it's hard to,
because there are so many of them.
It's almost like we just have
to throw darts for a while.
And then later when we go through
and get, I think there's like
an exhaustion period with that kind of site
where doing another three,
four, five, six times.
Maybe we will just go back
and pick out some of the classic ones
to just play.
But we're in dart phase right now.
But thank you.
Also, thank you, Mr.
Comcast again for the three dollars.
Hey, JermaJohnComcast here.
Just letting you know that I saw you
again after the E3 conference.
You were still naked,
but you had two AMD chips
glued to your nipples.
What the fuck are you doing?
You started yelling at passersby
about how your AMD stocks plummeted.
And that you were broke.
I found it weird when Keanu Reeves
showed up and you started
throwing swears at him.
Shouting that it should have been
your skin added to Fortnite.
The police showed up again
and they caught you
because you stopped to punch.
Thank you, Mr.
Comcast.
I really appreciate it.
Thanks for the funny little,
you know, laughing about it fiction.
Thank you, girl revolution
for the five dollars.
This is actually the very first
video game I ever played.
Thank you for reminding me.
I'm not sure what game that was.
Whatever game it happened to be.
I'm glad you got to see it.
Mini clips.
Thanks for the 10 bucks.
The look of a mad man.
Me?
Yeah.
The mother goose one?
Oh, that one was cute.
I would have played that
for like 10 minutes.
But thank you.
Mini clips for the 10 bucks.
Oh, what?
What?
Freage.
Thanks for the 15 dollars.
Cheater streamer loses
Wheel of Fortune anyways.
Not very good at Wheel of Fortune.
I'm good at Family Feud.
That's the one I'm pretty good at.
Thank you.
Freudian weapon for the 250.
Lost to Fortune Wheel.
Literally, yes.
Literally.
Sure.
I'll let that one slide.
And we also had Flug Boy.
Two dollars and 50 cents.
A German full disclosure.
Dragon Quest 11 is probably
one of the best in the series.
I've been playing since DQ7, probably.
And I highly recommend it
if you're interested.
I would say it's definitely
an off-stream game though.
Much love.
Yeah, they look cool.
It looks fun.
It looks interesting.
I just never got into any of those
in the years that they've existed.
Do I play games off stream?
Sometimes.
I actually just downloaded
Slay the Spire for the Switch.
Just was hanging out
playing it the other day.
It's pretty fun.
Frank Leo Wright.
It's another one of those things
that I will just never live down
for the rest of my life.
It's like I have live
time-stamped clips of Leo.
What a pee pants moment.
It's all right.
At least it wasn't the slap.
That was by far the worst
thing I've ever done on camera.
Let me remind myself again
to keep myself grounded.
Jesus fucking God.
Nobody can do this.
I saw a comment of somebody saying
that this is not possible.
It has to be fake.
I agree with that person.
It's not possible to do what I did.
It's impossible.
Little do they know.
Yeah, I saw that comment.
I'm just like, fuck.
It's I know.
I know.
I want to like come in there
and be like, I know.
I know.
I trust me.
I know better than anybody.
Hey, Tora T.
Thanks for the $15.
Jeremy, you better do it.
Don't lie to us.
I'm gonna do the Nintendo conference.
We also had Hack It Fast.
Had five community subs.
Thank you, Hack It Fast.
Some more community subs come in.
We had Hack It Fast gave five.
Bala Koala gave some too.
Thank you guys for your community subs.
And thank you Tora T for the $15.
That was your first ever stream of me
and I slapped myself
within the first 10 minutes
of you watching it.
Welcome to the channel.
Hey, you still here?
How do you do?
Good to see you.
That's how you reel them in.
Oh God.
Dabs for dinner.
Thanks for the $2.50.
You showed up for the Nintendo showcase
in a bathrobe last year.
So it's only fitting that you do it again.
Yeah, and I was on East Coast time last year.
It's three hours behind in Vegas.
It's gonna be even harder.
I'm gonna look horrible.
I couldn't even get up at like noon.
God, I'll be fine.
I'll be here.
Don't worry.
Thank you SleepTiner for the $3.20.
Thanks for the stream.
I hope you enjoyed it.
Thanks for watching.
Snoozingcopter, thanks for the $2.50.
Derma just said he never lies to us.
That means we're finally going to see Ace Attorney.
Also really disappointed that we didn't see Babylon's fall at Square today.
They just teased it last year and now it seems forgotten.
Even though it looks so cool, it was co-developed by Platinum Games.
Yeah, I wasn't really grabbed by much of the Square stuff.
Not this year at least.
Except for maybe one or two little things.
I felt kind of bad because I was kind of just like sitting there.
Watching and like I don't really have much to say about any of these games.
But I just kind of just didn't really have much to say.
The cute deer game looked interesting.
It did.
You're right.
But thank you Snoozingcopter for the $2.50.
I lie all the time.
So Ace Attorney is encompassed in the lies.
And Clueless Sniper, thanks for the $2.50.
Smelly Boy, thanks for the $2.50.
Do you have a video on the main channel that points viewers to the second channel?
If not, why?
I don't know.
I just kind of don't.
The last video I made on the main channel just said that I was going to be streaming full time.
Or like at least a lot.
That was the doctor's appointment.
Spider-Man hasn't took a year for me to find Jerma 2.
It's weird because part of me feels like if I make a video on the main channel that says,
hey guys, remember me?
Well, this is not a video.
This is me telling you that there's another channel.
And oh, by the way, I'm still streaming.
This is not a video though.
I feel like that's like the hermit is coming out.
Like the rock is moving and there's like a crowd of people just waiting.
It's like a theater.
There's a giant rock in a cave.
And there's like fucking thousands of people all sitting there with popcorn
with like 3D glasses on waiting for the cave boulder to move.
And like here it starts to move.
Oh my god, it's moving.
And everyone fucking sits down, shuts up, turns their phones off and starts watching.
Holy shit, the boulder's moving.
And the bright lights hit me in the face.
I have a huge beard and I'm just like.
Here he is, he's back.
Hey, just going to use the bathroom.
And I grab a newspaper and just walk across the audience
and just go shit in the woods.
And then go back into the boulder and push it closed.
That's what that is.
No, I feel like I don't want to really do that.
Just do that as the video.
I feel like that would piss off so many people.
If I did that and I actually uploaded that,
people would be like, are we, what, I'm the audience member?
I'm like just sitting here waiting for you?
You think I'm just going to sit here and wait?
What, you think you're that important?
No, no, no, no, no, no.
Okay, fine, dick.
Just upload that.
What if I just did that?
Before I go to the cave, I'm just like, oh by the way,
there's a second turbo channel if you want to watch it
and I stream from inside this cave.
There's like this, you can peer over the shoulder
and zoom in a little bit.
There's like a streamer set up.
Cave office.
I would watch that.
I would too.
You aren't funny, stop doing voices.
You are, what is this like, what's this coffee pasta?
Oh shit, it's two, it's two, I'm fucked.
That's 100% more than the typical one guy.
Well, I can't stop doing voices
because too many people live up here.
I don't even know what you mean by voices.
This is just other people that are up in my head.
Sometimes they just kind of come out.
Legal ramifications of tomorrow?
What do you mean legal ramifications?
Chat lives up in my head, rent free.
Nah, it's not rent free.
Do they pay rent?
But somebody, I mean, they said like,
you're not funny, stop doing voices.
I mean, I'm sorry.
I have to disagree with you personally.
As the streamer, I was interviewed
by youngbostonfunnycomedians.org
when I was like 14.
And I almost won like the RU as funny contest.
So when I was like 15.
And I was in Beauty and the Beast as Gaston.
So I think I have some credentials.
Yeah, I was Gaston.
Was that really?
Of course I was.
And I did this great voice.
Let me tell you.
It was a really, really good voice.
No, I'm done.
I'm done.
No more of this.
This is the auto voice.
Oh shit, I just have to rock this.
No one, I'm not gonna read that.
Do it, do it.
You played yourself.
I play myself every day.
But let's move on.
I'll fix you though, don't worry.
Doesn't matter.
I could say anything.
And it's gonna just turn against me.
Thank you too.
Where are we?
Hey Jamie, thanks for the $5, Jamie.
Appreciate it.
Is no message.
Jamie2803, thanks for the $5.
Thank you Slater Ashby for the $5.
Jerma, I want to thank you.
Appreciate the $5.
Thanks for that.
Anything else show official?
Thanks for the $15.
Thank you.
Anything else show official?
15 bucks.
Hell yeah.
Had fun watching your drunken stream today, Jerma,
while I was sick with bronchitis.
But a bilateral ear infection and sinusitis.
So I hope you're glad you gave me some laughter
while I was dying, coughing, and sneezing today.
Well hopefully you're feeling all right.
Hopefully you're not like actually in like any pain or anything.
But I wish you a swift recovery.
Thanks for the 15 bucks.
Getting sick during the summer is the worst.
Yeah it is.
Because you just don't feel like you're supposed to be sick.
You feel like it's like sunny and nice out.
So it's just like why?
When it's cold and wintery and shitty out,
it doesn't matter.
It's like good I'll stay in bed.
But sorry to hear that.
Hopefully you get a swift recovery.
Thanks for the 15 bucks.
A vertebral giant.
Thanks for the $5.
Thanks for killing it with jokes tonight.
By the way, Twitch tweeted out your Christopher Walken joke
about Keanu Reeves.
Have a good one.
That was the worst joke I made yesterday.
That was such like a flat shit joke.
And people probably clicking on that gale night.
This guy sucks.
The person that said that my jokes suck
probably came here from that tweet.
Now I get it.
I understand.
No, it was fun.
That was fun.
But it was kind of the equivalent of me being like
pee-pee doo-doo.
Like poo-poo.
There it is.
Hilarious.
That's it.
That's what I do normally.
If you don't think this stream is funny,
I hope you find somebody that you think is funny.
Hope you find something to enjoy.
And if you enjoy not thinking that I'm funny,
I'm glad to have you.
Thanks for watching.
So we had a couple more from smellyboy250.
Disregard my last comment.
I eat ass.
Will do.
I will, I guess, disregard that comment.
Thanks.
DubskiDude, thanks for the 250.
I love the Dragon Quest series,
but I would say the constant puns
are extremely painful to read.
It's spine breaking.
They really localize it poorly,
but otherwise it's pretty fun off stream game.
Maybe I'll get it.
Maybe I'll give it a try.
I kind of need a new game just to lie down.
Just stare at a screen with...
Can I get that on?
What can I get that on?
Let's see.
Oh, let's get the credits on.
There were a lot of subs.
Let's show them.
I don't know what it is with these E3 streams,
but they like are killing my voice.
I mean, I've been drinking water.
Have I been talking more than usual?
I don't think so.
Not more than usual.
I think I'm just getting old.
Yeah, maybe I am.
But here comes the credits.
These are all the subs that were here today
on this stream tonight.
See you tomorrow morning for the Nintendo conference.
And then we'll probably hang out for like a little bit after that.
I'm going to show up late.
I can't.
I can't be late to these
because they start without you.
But thank you again, everybody,
for your continued support of this stream.
Hopefully you've been having fun on these E3 streams.
They're fun to do.
They're fun just to hang out.
And let's finish up.
There's only one more bit to do.
Or is there?
I think I already got it.
But yeah, I already got it.
So you mean you're only late when you can be late?
I mean, kind of.
But I mean, that's why I have the window now
to make sure that I kind of can't be.
But I'll see you bright and early.
Those of you that are going to be awake or around.
Have a great rest of your night
if you're going to check out some more of the E3 stuff.
I think there's...
Is there anything else going on tonight?
I don't think there is, right?
The Square Enix was the last one.
Am I only interested in the building one?
No, I would play Dragon Quest XI.
Don't think I would stream it,
but I would probably play it.
NVIDIA and Intel subs.
Well, somebody gave them subs.
Leo.
It is what it is.
I'm just glad I did the Dr. Island brain games
without too much of a problem.
That was a meltdown waiting to happen.
Leo Peepo dance.
Take care, guys.
Holy shit, there were a lot of subs.
You guys, generosity never ceases to amaze...
Oh, by the way, let's take a look at this
because I'm doing this next week.
Actually, not next week, but I'm doing this this weekend.
Yeah.
So after tomorrow, I will be live on Friday and Saturday.
Yeah, after tomorrow, I'm going to be live Friday, Saturday.
And we're doing this shit.
You want to show up to like a drunk asshole stream?
It's going to be this one.
What do you think we should do first?
Tombstone Express?
I mean like Tombstone Express?
What else we got?
The Squeak and Sausage Unlock Adventure
or the Exotic Expedition.
We're going to try to beat these.
These are card games that you play with yourself
or with a friend.
But we're going to do that.
You and I are going to do this.
It has an app that you sit on a table
and you essentially have to escape from the encounter.
It's going to be a wine stream.
If you're of drinking age, maybe you want to hang out.
Escape the encounter.
It's Tombstone Express Wild West Dinosaur Expedition
or Squeak and Sausage Weird Fucked Up Circus Climb.
I played Squeak and Sausage.
Please play it.
It's awesome.
We'll pick.
I'm going to I bought them all.
I'm going to do them all.
Can chat play too?
Maybe.
I'm going to see if that's possible
because you only have 60 minutes to escape.
So I don't know if it's possible that we can.
That might take too long.
We'll see.
This is going to be let's see.
Yes.
This will this will be Friday and maybe Saturday
if there's still time to do them.
But it absolutely will be at least Friday night.
And that's my time.
Thanks for hanging out for E3.
We got one more conference to do tomorrow
in the morning early.
Have a great rest of your night.
See you tomorrow if you're going to show up.
Take care.
Good night guys.