Hey, what is going on everybody? Jerma here with a Diablo 3 video.
And this is my first Diablo 3 video. If you're watching for the first time on my channel and you scroll back all the way to this video, this is the first one.
And before I say anything, I gotta tell you, this game has lived up to a lot of expectations.
Now, I could do a total breakdown of what, pretty much a review of this game, but I'm not gonna do that right now.
I wanted to show you this because this is the fun part of Diablo. This is me, Shibby, 2142.
Star and MLC Stealth. All four people max people in a game.
And we were doing Act 2. This is Act 2. And it does need to be mentioned that there are going to be some minor spoilers in this video.
Because, of course, we're gonna kill the Act 2 bosses.
And if you don't want to see that, if you don't want to hear that, if you want to plug your ears and say la la la la la, that is totally fine.
So when we get there, you're welcome to do that.
I'm actually gonna put an annotation on the screen when a somewhat of a pretty important spoiler is about to happen.
So I will put that on the screen for you.
And my full Diablo 3 review slash breakdown, that's gonna come in probably the next couple of weeks.
Because I do want to play through as much as I can, get through Nightmare, get through Hell, try Inferno, before I really give a last final assessment of this game.
So look for that in the next couple of weeks. Maybe a little sooner, but I'm just not sure yet.
So besides that, the view schedule, the video schedule for this particular game is probably gonna run like this.
Because this is such a massive game, because there is so much to do, I don't think I'm gonna make a Let's Play where I upload 500 videos or something like that.
Like, oh, here's episode one of 10,000. I'm not sure I'm going to do that.
What I'm going to do is probably live stream this game.
Take what I get on the live stream, put it over here on YouTube.
So you might see, oh, we're in Nightmare this time, or we're in, oh, this is Hell Act 3.
And I'll make sure to label it, make sure to annotate it.
And the streams are gonna be a lot longer now. That's one of the things I did want to talk about.
So instead of the one hour or two hour long Team Fortress and Binding of Isaac type streams, they're now gonna be like six or seven hours long.
And hopefully I have my 720p streaming set up for YouTube, because if that's all set up, that's gonna be perfect.
Because what'll happen is right when the stream is done, if you don't want to sit there for the whole stream or if you have something to do, we all have busy schedules,
you can come back later and watch it in 720. Rather than lately, it's been about 360 for all my streams.
But that is the plan for Diablo 3, at least right now. I have another idea in my head that might come to fruition later.
But for now, check out this video. It's gonna be Act 2, the end of Act 2 in normal.
This is the first reactions we had, so if you're wondering why I'm freaking out at certain points, it's because we never saw any of this stuff before, ever.
So enjoy the live commentary, guys, and I will see you guys soon. And take care, everybody.
We're like single file. Look at that. We're like, look at Brett just nodding his head, like, yeah.
Which one's me? I'm inside freaking Jerma's shield.
We're all like, we're like cowering on each other.
We look like Scooby Doo and the gang, which is like all like, riding up on each other.
All right, so hold on. Let me go through my skills book and inventory.
Don't do it.
Hey guys, good boss fight.
Dropping that shit.
I picked up whatever you just dropped. I don't know what it is, but I wanted it.
But I wanted it, I wanted it, so I took it.
I wanna go in. I'm going in.
Okay, I'm going in.
All right, I'm going in.
Aw.
Accept. Start. Accept it.
I thought I did, maybe.
Oh, you did, you did.
Okay.
Here we go.
Let's do it. Zoltan, cool. I'm going around. I'm going around.
Is that a bad idea? Should I not go around?
Oh, they're slow bubbling me.
Come on, let's do it, Zoltan.
What do you got, Zoltan? I'll take Zoltan for a ride.
There we go.
He's leveled up, too.
Oh, Zoltan, what a jump.
Yeah, I know. Look at this punk it destroyed.
What a jump.
All that build up for this guy just to take all this heat.
Yeah, I know, all that power.
Yeah, I thought you had a bunch of power.
Well, all in a day's work, we just did it.
Are you kidding me? What?
Annihilated.
Dude, is it like, now my true form, or is that was that it?
Oh, that was it.
And now my true form.
That guy got so messed up.
Dude, the butcher was hotter than that guy.
The get hurt skill.
Oh, man, I'm getting like lag right here.
That was bad news, bears.
This game.
Whoa, whoa, whoa.
Yeah, I was pretty disappointed at first that you couldn't have like eight players in a lobby.
Yeah, thank you. Thank you. Thank you for that.
Thank you, Blizzard, for not allowing that to happen, because that would be literally, it would be unplayable.
You would just be right clicking and not even know where you were.
Yeah, because everyone has so many skills they could spam now.
That's why I turned on low effects. I couldn't take it.
Doesn't really change a whole lot anyway, though.
Yeah, true death, true death.
Oh, everything's already dead over here.
Even the ground is fighting us. What is, I don't even.
Man, I'm not even sure what I'm attacking anymore.
I'm just just walking.
Things are just dying.
Those were blue monsters, but who knew about it?
I didn't know.
We just we're just too super late for them to handle us.
Just over here.
Nothing good.
Oh, they start doing the move again.
I thought we were trying to encourage her to do it.
Oh, boss.
That's not. Wait, wait, wait.
Are we fighting?
I need to go through my inventory.
We might be fighting for a while. I don't know, dude.
Cancel, cancel.
I need a moment.
You guys.
Shifty.
Update.
Oh, God.
Drop free again?
Drop free.
What if we kill them?
Legendary drops and the server shuts down.
Oh, they're about to shut down the servers right now.
We better make this quick.
We're too good.
They caught on.
Skip this.
I want to hear what he has to say about his stones.
It's so funny because I really want to know what he has to say.
I can't even hear a word he's saying.
Me too.
Dude, last time this happened.
What?
Server shut down.
We have 15 minutes.
He is Belial.
I expected that.
Wow.
He's the Lord of Lies.
You expect Belial would be complying?
I didn't think he was going to be a kid.
He's Joffrey.
Joffrey was always a prick.
So yeah, we have 15 minutes.
The ladies were fine.
When did the servers go down?
Did it say?
15 minutes.
That's what it just said.
We can do this in 15 minutes.
Let's do it.
Are you serious about the servers going down?
Yep.
How do you know?
It said in the bottom-off chat.
All right.
We're fighting Belial right now.
Oh, see.
14 minutes.
All right.
Just rape him.
Oh, my gosh.
This guy's dead.
Belial, you are not.
You are a bad, bad Belial.
I think we just all combined have way too many things to stun people.
He's either stunned or frozen or dying.
There's no in-between.
Hey, get over here.
Oh, great.
Now his true form.
Remember we said we talked about this?
Oh, his true form.
Oh, he's like, Zarbond.
Zarbond.
Oh, okay.
Oh, my God.
Oh!
This is terrifying.
Oh, we can...
What do we do?
I'm running.
I can't shoot that far.
Oh, my God.
Oh, he's going like getting Jerma.
How does this work?
Oh, my God.
Come on.
Come at me, Belial.
You are the Lord of Lies.
I'm dead.
Lord of Lies?
What the hell?
Yeah, I'll just whirlwind his ass.
Can I be revived mid-combat?
No, you can't.
I think you can.
Can you?
I think somebody needs to be a monk jumping.
Oh, nice.
Bring him back.
There you go.
Oh, dead.
Insta-dead.
Don't stay in the poison.
Jerma, give me up.
You have the most health.
You can get me.
101.
What the hell?
Hold on.
I'm getting somebody.
I don't know who it is.
I'm doing it again.
Here we go.
I am running for my life.
Hold on.
Use your potions.
Oh, my God.
You guys are all dying instantly.
Just running for my life.
You ain't got nothing.
Oh, I blocked it.
Oh, my good God.
It looks like my bubble's actually getting him.
Yeah, I think as long as you're on the outskirts, you can hit him.
Oh, he had better.
He had better.
That almost killed me.
Oh, oh, oh, no, no, no, please.
Fortunately, ice armor is totally balanced.
And fair.
Legendary.
Oh, come on.
What's he got?
We got nothing.
Holy shit.
Oh, that's cool.
Oh, I see.
No, no.
We got a rare H.
Oh, I see.
Oh, we got a rare H.
We got a rare H.
I was really hoping for something.
I got three yellows.
Damn.
Well, that was cool, though.
I got two yellows and like three blues.
Derma gives him nothing.
I got a couple of yellows, but you know, whatevs.
Whatevs.