Hey, what is going on everybody? Chirrma here with a Team Fortress 2 gameplay commentary.
And tonight's gonna have two one-life gameplays back-to-back here. I'm in a one-life mood.
I really don't know why, but the last couple of days it's been all about the streaks, less about the full gameplays.
But today, I have a very, very special guest. And it is, of course, you probably guessed it by the title,
Grandpa. Because, of course, Grandpa is an MLG pro, is returning to Machinima Respawn tonight.
That is right. Well, actually, let me rephrase that. There's gonna be a trailer tonight for the second season of Grandpa.
And it's pretty crazy. I had a lot of fun doing it, a lot of fun making it.
So, 8 p.m. Eastern Standard Time tonight. I'm not sure when this video is gonna go up today,
but 8 p.m. Eastern Time is when the Grandpa MLG Season 2 trailer is gonna be on Machinima Respawn.
So, check that out. Please everybody go support it. Like you always do, you guys are incredible.
But, let's break down the gameplays for a second before Grandpa makes his appearance.
So, the gameplays, of course, are gonna be Scout and Sniper.
Using mostly the defaults, because, of course, my final 33% of my backpack was given away.
So, all I got is a bunch of strangers and a couple of untradeable hats and stuff.
So, I'm working my way back. Let's just put it that way.
So, it's gonna be the regular Scattergun, the Mad Milk, which apparently I still had, and the default Bat.
And for the Sniper, gonna be default Sniper Rifle, the Jurati, I think. Yeah, the Jurati.
And the Shiv, the Travelman Shiv. That was a nice derp moment right there.
But yeah, anyways, I hope you guys enjoy those. They're gonna be in the background.
But I am bringing on Grandpa right now. Yes?
It's time for me to come on.
Yes, you are coming on right now.
Yes.
So, we want to talk about Season 2. We want to talk about some frequently asked questions to Grandpa.
These are all for me, right?
Yes.
They're all for me.
None of these are gonna be for me. These are questions all for you.
They better be.
Okay.
I'm not gonna sit down here if they're not all for me.
These questions are frequently asked, and I gotta tell you guys.
To you guys for all the support you give me in my video game shit.
It's very, very awesome.
And let's start with the questions, Jeremy.
Okay, all right.
So, question number one is, what is your favorite Team Fortress 2 class?
The Heavy. It's the Heavy. There's no doubt in my mind it's the Heavy.
Because you just hold the right mouse button down, and you just annihilate people.
Why would you ever play as any other class?
Why is it not just all Heavies versus all Heavies?
I don't see a reason for anything else.
I mean, why wouldn't you? You're the most powerful thing in the game.
It wouldn't work. Team Fortress 2, it says it right in the title.
It's all balanced around the certain classes.
If everyone went Heavy on one team, there would be two snipers that would just have a field day.
No, that wouldn't really work.
Spies, too. You'd get one spy on the team. It would kill nine people.
No, but you're wrong.
Because if you have two Heavies, one standing in front of you and one standing behind you,
you're not going to be in the fucking sandwich. Oh, I forgot. I can't swear on your channel.
That's okay, but keep it to a minimum.
So, anyways, okay, so Heavy's your favorite class.
So the second question is, what is Grandpa's favorite video game?
It can be from ten years ago or yesterday, whatever came out. I don't know.
No, that's an easy one. That's Call of Duty 4.
It's Modern Warfare 4. It was called something like that.
That's a good rest of the best game I've ever played. It was perfect balance, perfect kill streaks.
That's my favorite game. College 4 is my favorite.
You got a second favorite? Because, I mean, mine probably goes Team Fortress, Diablo.
I mean, I got a lot, so I got like probably four or five favorite games.
Well, it would probably be College 4 and then Leisure Suit Larry, the first one.
What? No.
Yeah, that was a fun game. It was a point-and-click adventure game, but it was really screwed up.
There was all kinds of adult stuff going on. That was my favorite game, I tell you. I had a lot of fun playing that.
All right, so Call of Duty 4 and Leisure Suit Larry. That makes perfect sense, apparently.
So one more question before the video is over. This question gets asked all the time, Grandpa.
This is asked the most out of any of these questions.
Let's hear it.
When are we going to see your face? When are we going to get a Grandpa face cam video?
Oh, you want to see my face, huh? You want to see my face? Okay. Put a date and time on it.
We are going to see Grandpa's face on December 22, 2012.
Because if the goddamn world doesn't end, then I swear to God I'll do it.
So be sure to be ready to say that. December 22, after the world collapses.
So that's a good thing to look forward to.
I would probably also say that, too.
Thank you for showing up here, Grandpa. The video is over.
So guys, make sure to check...
Make sure you check out my Machinima Respond series on Saturdays at 8 p.m. Eastern Time.
And that's Grandpa's and MLG Pro Season 2.
It started May 12th. So get your ass over there and go watch the trailer.
Okay, bye.
Alright, see you later.
See you later, bye, asshole.
Okay. Thank you guys so much for watching. I really do appreciate it.
And I will see you guys all next time. So take care, everybody.