Hey, what's up? How are you? What's going on? What's going on? Oh, it's because the AC is on.
Hold on a second. Oh, shit. Uh-oh. Oh, god. What the fuck? Disaster.
What's going on? Is my gate too low right now? Hold on. I'm gonna change this. Give me one second.
Is it like fucked up again? Hello? Hello? Hello? Hello? Hello? Hello? What is going on? Hold on,
listen. What? Hold on, I need to like hear this. What the fuck is this? What's this for?
Let me be able to hear it. I can see. Yeah, this is, this is not, you hear that? It's like
here. I gotta, okay, hold on. There we go. There we go. That's better. Okay. All right. Perfect.
We are back to normal. That was really weird. Okay. So, um, let me turn this down a little bit.
Just stop the stream. I'll put the audio back on for you. Okay. Hi, everybody. Welcome. Sorry
about that. That was a quick little change I had to do. Oh, I almost just unplugged my fucking entire
setup. That would have been so bad. We're gonna do something different today. Well, not really. I feel
like I'm the guy that has streamed every microphone video game. We're getting close. That's what we're
doing today. We are going to be playing. It's really not that different if you think about it.
We're gonna be playing a game called Old Gama, which, it could be great. It could be awful.
It's a game where you control troops on a battlefield with your voice while you play
pinball on the battlefield with a gigantic fucking boulder. So this is either pog or,
we'll find out. Let me change back to what I was doing. That's the first thing we're gonna do.
If it turns out this game is really fun and I want to play it forever, then that's what we'll do.
We'll just sit here for a while. But if the game sucks, then we're gonna pivot to Pokemon. That's
right. Pokemon. Well, I mean, not necessarily actually Pokemon. I mean, it's a Pokemon game
where you fucking watch TV with your Pokemon friend. It's a TV watching game. So it's not what
you think. But, you know, it's Pokemon React. Pokemon React. I can't wait to be like a React
Tuber on the Pokemon game. Anyways, um, oh, wow, this can stay on. Here's the microphone.
And here's, I was setting it up to make sure it worked. Hello. Hello. This is a test of the
microphone. It seems to be working pretty well. It works pretty well. I got the GameCube controller.
I think I'm ready to move. Fake voice. He's peaking his mic. Oh, fuck. No, I don't want to
break this. Should I lower it? I don't want to break it. If I break it, I mean, like, it really
fucking matters. There's like four games that utilized the GameCube mic. Two of them are Mario
Party. One of them is this. And the other one is a game we've already played, Chibi-Robo. I didn't
even know. I think there's four games that actually use this. Now, this is fine. It's not peaking the
mic. That just means you can hear you very well. How do you use it in Chibi-Robo? I have no idea.
I was actually going to look it up. All right, let's go. Can you guys hear this? Why can I not
hear this? I should be able to hear this. Oh, there is no sound. Oh, okay. That's like fucking
Resident Evil sound. This is like that. I just thought I was playing Resident Evil. That's the
sound it makes when you move items around in Resident Evil 1 and 2. Okay, let's go. I did a
little testing to make sure that this is Odama. What's with that? Why is there, what's going on
with this? Like the sadness right now. Why is everybody so sad? What's with the sadness?
Why are you guys doing sadness? Why are you guys so sad? What's fucking going on here? Oh,
because of the quarantine. Oh yeah, that is true. That's fucking not good.
All right, we'll watch the cut scene. I'll be back in a minute. Is this the opening cut scene?
This land has been governed by Lord Yamanouchi Nobatu. When Lord trusted Vassal with, he betrayed
him. Lord Yamanouchi took his own life rather than bear the shame of defeat. I feel like I'm
a shitty translator at like an event. Okay, and he also says, I can't wait for next year when
you all show up. I feel like I'm a shitty translator. I'm getting off the screen. Come back. What's
going on here? There are two secrets that their longtime foes knew nothing about.
Well, if this is an actual dub, it'd be more like this. This giant ball was said to have been
legend held that when unleashed in battle, the Odama could inflict untold damage to foes or
grant great power to allies. But these legends remain untested. The other secret was the doctrine
of Nintendo. The word Nintendo is formed from the first kanji of three proverbs. Ninja,
Mushin, attend to one's duties. Tenzai, Korin, those in heaven will descend. And Doji, Sumi,
moral action is a da- The way of Ninten illustrates the mindset of the Kagetori army,
soldiers who have entrusted themselves to the heavens. It's going too fast. It's going too fast.
Larry. Larry, I can't keep it up. You're going too fast. Slow the fucking thing down.
Remember the power of the Nintendo?
Dive into the dungeon of Onosamaki and your victory will ring throughout this land.
I'm gonna bring the can back. Just hold on. We're watching the opening cutscene.
You'll play this but not Nioh. Nioh does not have a comedy microphone. If Nioh was controlled with
a comedy mic, maybe I would consider it. This looks like a fucking e-cigar. Don't you think
I'm gonna like fucking just go like this and just blow a fucking cloud over here?
The e-cigar! Nintendo! Are we done? Wait, wasn't that just- Yes, yes, yes.
Let's go. Okay, I'm ready. Kuruwa Plains. Start. Now my lead. Off to battle. Why do I feel like
this is the Wiimote in the nunchuck? I'm the nunchuck in this scenario. I have to talk.
How do I do this? We must first meet our foe on the Plains of Kuruwa. Look closely, my lead.
The plains are bordered by hills and by the rapid flow of the Kuruwa River.
Okay. The enemy attempts to halt our advance at the far bank of the river.
We are to cross- close the floodgate first.
This will stop the river. Once the river is blocked, we can cross without fear.
Okay, we must ensure that the Ninten Bell passes through the gate at the far end of the field.
When do I use this? Keep as many troops as possible near the Ninten Bell.
As many troops as possible. Oh, almost forgot.
We must win this battle by sundown. Why is there like a Mario fly hat symbol button over there?
Hit the ghost by sundown. Hit the floodgate with the odama. All right, so it's right-
three, two, one. All right, here we go. It's fire- wait, it's firing?
Move! I'm killing my own troops. Watch out for the ball. I have to have to break the river.
Why is it- what am I supposed to do? Where's the ball?
Fall back. Send back up. More troops. I gotta break that. Did I do it?
What? You don't have commands? Advance? No, that's- yeah, let's practice, please.
Okay. Place the cursor over your men and give them your orders. Clearly into the microphone.
It's pinball with extra steps. Is the cursor over your men?
Okay, advance.
How do you play with both hands? This is like- this is playing games while eating simulator.
You know, you're like- hold on a second. Like, I can't- this is gonna be fucking impossible.
Fall back. Fall back. March right. March left. They're going right.
Please. Wait. Don't tape it to the- hold on. Don't touch this with my mouth. Did I- did I sanitize
this? Oh, it was in- it was in a package. It was in plastic. Okay. I think we're good. It was in
brand new- but this is brand new. I'm the first person to put this near their mouth. I lost. Yeah,
let's try it again. Wait, the ball went down. I have to start the whole fucking thing over again.
All right, I'm ready. Carry the ball through the gate. All right. Oh, I can aim it. Oh, let's go
all the way- no, no, no, no. Over here. Try to break that gate. Done. Okay, now I got commands.
Here we go. You have learned the command, press forward. The command orders your men to press
forward and repel the enemy. Place your cursor over your men and say, press forward. Your bell
crew will summon every last ounce of strength to push through the enemy forces. Will it still hear
me if I go like this? My pants are kind of loose. That went all the way down the underwear.
That went like straight down over- like to the underwear. Only troops who pass through the gate
will join you at the start of the next battle. Any troops rallied at the bell when you give the
order. Wait, okay, so any- you- you- press forward. All right. I have to play like pinball. All right,
just press forward. March left. Press forward. Fuck, I'm so bad at this. Oh, I just killed
everybody. Advance. Advance. Advance. Advance. Advance. The floodgate is open. The water is
not flowing. What? Press forward. They're coming at me. Can I hit them with the flippers?
Advance. Run- crush them. Crush them. Run them over. Advance. Oh my god. Advance. Advance.
I can't trust our liege. What? Advance. Attack. Press forward. Press forward. Press forward. Yes.
Press forward. I'm trying to help you. Tell your men you love them. What just happened?
You have- you learned a command called flank and destroy. This thrilling command orders your
troops to engage the enemy. Oh, what the fuck have they been doing this whole time?
Flank and destroy. Flank and destroy. Okay. Flank and destroy. Flank and destroy. Flank and destroy.
Fall back. Fall back. Fall back. I'm killing all my own people. Advance. Advance. Prove we can trust
you. What the fuck are you talking about? What? Prove we can trust you first. Okay. What does
deploy mean? I- wait. I can- advance. Push forward. Fall back. Fall back. Fall back. Fall back.
Fall back. Fall back. I didn't know I could- I didn't know this was like fucking Clash Royale.
Advance. Flank and destroy. Where are you going? What? What? What? Go forward. Fall back. I gotta
close the gate. Fall back. I gotta hit the fucking flood. Okay, here we go. Hit the- close the gate
so this is the- advance. Advance. Advance. Flank and destroy. Come on, give me more troops. What
the fuck did I just do? Get up there. Get up there. Get up there. Advance. Flank and destroy. Hit the
bell? I can't. I'm trying. Flank and destroy. Advance. Advance. Flank and destroy. Advance.
Advance. That plan sounds bad. Go in the fucking door. Go in. Why- what's with the traffic jam?
Go in. Advance. What was the plan? What am I- I already forgot what? Press forward.
What is- what is- what is advance and press forward? What's the difference?
Advance. Okay, we advance. Press forward. You go forward. That's advanced. That's advancing.
Okay, lie in the ruin before your might. Can somebody please give me an edit? Somebody please.
I know one of you will do it before the stream ends. Just- just please do this. You know exactly
what I'm looking for. You know what I want you to do. Okay? Just hold on a second. Fucking been
waiting for this shit. Kind of skipped though, right? All right, that's all I want. You know
what I want. You know what I want. That's all I care about. I don't care about anything else.
I just want- I need- I need you to do a ton of vapor coming out of my mouth. That's all I want.
I don't care. I don't- that's all I care about. Here we go.
It's coffee!
Holy shit, there's new mechanics here.
The bell crew cannot climb this hill! The bell crew!
Our troops must prepare the way by setting a ladder?
Okay. Knock the key- oh, knock the key free with the I. Three, two, one, oh fuck. Get up there.
Blank and destroy. Protect the bell. March right. Buy shit on fire. Fall back. Fall back.
Fall back. Fall back. Fall back. Oh, people just got wiped out. March left. I gotta get in there.
Fall back. Rally. Okay. This command orders your troops to gather in the area you have
highlighted with the cursor. Oh, that's- this is- this is what I'm looking for. Rally into the
microphone. Occupy enemy installations. Let's try it. Rally. All right, let me try this.
I gotta hit the key. I got another ball. Okay. How do I move the cursor? Rally. Oh, advance.
Hit that key. Fall back. There we go. Advance. There we go. Bounce it around in there.
Oops. Are my troops dead? Fall back. Fall back. Rally. Rally. Rally here to grab the- what the
fuck are you talking about? They're all on fire. I- I can't even go up there. Is it up there?
I can't even move the cursor up there. Rally. Get that key. Rally. Oh, fuck. I'm trying to just
get in there. Come on. Rally. So much friendly fire. Well, like I'm thrown on a giant pinball.
Okay. Rally. Holy shit. Rally. Get the fucking thing- Rally. Do they all need to have their own
fucking thought bubbles? Is this roller coaster tycoon? What the fuck? Rally. Rally. Rally. Rally.
Why are they not rallying? Well, we lost. Press X up- Rally. Okay. Fall back. They'll do that.
They won't fucking rally. We lost. Bad general tactics. Imagine if there's a guy just sitting
behind everybody with a fucking megaphone. Just screaming or- how could they even hear me?
No one can hear anything I'm saying. You have to go to the- I was trying to get them to go to the
ladder. They wouldn't go. I was going- Rally. Rally to the ladder. Rally. Fucking microphones.
Here we go. Place the ladder against the slope and leap. I gotta go that way. Knock the key
free with the odama to grab it. We're going right up the middle. I'm not deploying anything yet.
Destroy everything in the middle. Good. All right. Now we bring some group to burn it down. Good.
Fall back. There we go. You fucker. That was good. Advance. Fuck. I wasn't even looking at
the goddamn ball. Why are we so pushed back? Just get it flooded. Blank and destroy. Blank and destroy.
Fall back. Put me out. Can I? Blank and destroy. Look at the ball. The ball's lit up. Come on. Get
up there. Oh god damn it. Crunch. Crackle. Crunch. Crackle. What am I hitting? Advance.
No. Fall back. Fall back. Fall back. No. Bounce it around. Thank you. Finally. There we go. Rally here
to grab the fucking ladder. Well why won't you go? Oh my god. I just- I think I just killed everybody.
Fall back. Where's the ball? Yes. Bounce around. Everywhere. Blank and destroy. I just killed
everybody. Okay. Get that. Get that. Rally. What are you doing? What are you- I'm trying to kill
people. Rally. Rally. They have no morale. Rally. Go get the fucking ladder. They won't even go do
this. Use the C stick? It doesn't do anything. We're all dead again. March left. Move the cursor.
I- It won't go any further to the corner. Look. It won't go any higher. D-pad? The D-pad isn't
going to do anything. Make them march to the left. Bilateral Lich 5000 bits. 50 dollars.
Jeremy, here's 50 dollars. Now march your men left and select the ladder. You have to have the bell
closer.
Thanks for the 50 dollar tip. Thanks for the actual tip. But how do- I can't advance up there
if they all fucking die. All right. Just get them all out there. Oh my god. Why is it so crunchy?
March left. This is a really good start though. This is actually a fantastic start. I killed so
much shit here. March left. March left. I still can't go up that far. March left. I can't even go
up that far still. It's all the way up there. Look at my cursor. Fall back. I can't even go
that far. Fall back. Fall back. Fall back. March left. March left. They have done- they
want to listen to me anymore. Fall back. Fall back. Are they stuck? Fall back. Fall back.
Fall back. March left. Dude, it does nothing to do with the bell. Rally. I can't physically go
any higher the way the cursor is right now. Use the D-pad. Rally. Who's making fucking popcorn?
Take it out. Take it out. Take it out. You're gonna do too much. It's getting all over the stove.
All right. The ladder is in position. All right. Watch out for the ball. Advance.
Press forward. Press forward. Press forward. Get in there. Get in there. Push it back.
Look at that guy right there. That guy's like, oh shit, I hope they don't fucking see me.
I hope nobody sees me if I just stand here. I gave it like one versus a thousand. Holy shit.
I have no fucking idea what's going on, but we did it. All right. So select. It's not like use
the cursor. It's like pick the one out of two spots with the D-pad. I got 164 people. This game
is fucked up. This game is... I'll be completely honest with you guys. This game is stupid. This
game is really stupid, but I'm still interested. I still want to play it. Time for Pokemon TV. Not
yet. Not yet. Not yet. I'm still having fun. It's stupid, but it's fun. Mainly because I don't even
know half the things I'm doing. We're gonna get multiple balls here soon. All right. Now what?
All of our third battle in the distance.
Beyond those gates, we will face a general who will take all our might and cunning to defeat.
Oh, the rivers. This is going to be painful.
It's a pulley to the nearest bug that we can control the flow of that river.
This is a lot. This is too much to do.
Stick the mic up your nose. No. Give me the key. Give me this. Okay. I got a new command.
Close the gate.
What? You can seal the floodgate. Once your men have fixed the pulley to the gate,
order them to close the gate. The gate will fall into place.
Once the gate is closed, say flood the river to open it. Close the gate.
Fart into the mic. Oh, wow. That's fucking hilarious. Flood the river. No, it's not worth it.
It's not worth it. March left. Fall back. I gotta do some work here. I need the spool. I need the
spool. Fall back. Fall back. March right. There we go. There we go. Knock that tower down.
Fall back. I got the key. Oops. Sorry. Grab that key. Rally. All right. I got the key.
Oh, shit. The troops have taken the key. Open that door. March right. Oh, fuck. They're coming
over here. Fall back. Get it. Hit it. Hit it. Hit it. Hit it. Hit it. Put the key. March right.
March left. Flank and destroy. We need to push. Advance. Advance. Advance. Advance. Hit it.
Flank and destroy. Flank and destroy. There it is. Finally. My god. Somebody get that. Somebody pick
that shit up. Rally. This is seriously the only fucking way to do this. Can I put it in my ear?
There we go. Good. Get the key, too. Don't rally there yet. Get that fucking key.
But what a good start. Rally. Fucking noise. So the crunching sounds in that. I don't know
what it is with this shit. Tape it? I could tape it like around my neck. I'm not at that point yet.
Tape. Hold on. Gamer neck brace. Tape it to the controller. Oh, shit. I could have
taped it this way and just hold it right here. Supreme. He's the supreme commander.
Where's my? Oh, my headphones are already in. Okay. I'm ready. It's hard when I swallow my
neck pulses. Okay, let's go. Okay. Good. Good. Good start. I know. I know what the key is. I know
what the key is. Rally. Good. Give me that spool. Flank and destroy. Shit. Rally. No, no, no, no.
I forgot. We've used the key to open the gate. Rally. Oh, that was a good hit.
Don't. Watch out. Okay. The troops have taken the pulley. What's the command? What's the command?
Advance. What's the command? Move right. I don't know. It's not. It's like it's like close the
pulley or something. Close the gate. You look dumb. What's this? Wait, wait, wait.
Game. What are people linking here? Controllers. Game queue.
This is why you always check what's in what the contents of the bag are.
Always check the contents of the bag. Okay. That's very difficult, too. Oh, my God. All right.
Let's go. Get that fucking key. Rally. Rally. The audio. I know the audio is so bad.
Fall back. Fall back. I want. I need to get the spool. I need to get the spool of yarn.
Yes. Come on. Open the gate. Okay. Advance. Protect the belt. Get the. Come on.
Take the audio out of the corn flakes, please. Take the audio out of the corn flakes, please.
God damn it. I forgot. I forgot. I forgot. I saved it. Advance. Blank and destroy. God damn it.
There's people here. Fall back. Fall back. I'm disabled. I'm disabled. I'm disabled. I'm disabled.
I'm trying to hit the stupid fucking spool over here and I can't get it.
What just happened? Why did it fire? It prematurely fired. No, I don't. Don't grab the key.
Wine plus corn flakes zone. Oh, no, no, no, no, no. Now I have to bring people. Fall back.
Rally. Fall back. Fall back. I got to select. I got to select. I got to select. I know. I know
what it does. I know what it does. You don't have to tell me. Fall back. Fall back. Fall back. Get it.
Fall back. Oh, shit. They're over there. They're past the river now. God damn it. Fall back. Fall
back. Fall back. What? All right. Roll back and kill everybody. Here it comes. All right. Okay.
All right. Now get it. Okay. Rally. Fall back. Ball and bag torture. God damn it. All right. Yes.
Advance. There we go. Nice. The floodgates now open and I can't. It's got to hit these guys. Come on.
Fall back. Don't push forward. I don't have enough men. I got to wipe them out with this.
There it is. I'm killing my own fucking people. No, don't turn this shit on. Close the gate. Push
forward. Did that just say he hates us? Did that guy just say he hates streaming? Push forward.
Close the gate. Close the gate. Push forward. Push forward. Press forward. Press forward.
Press forward. There's a lot of fucking people there. Press forward. Come on. Press forward.
What? Oh, shit. Oh, shit. Come on. Come on. Come on. Press forward. Come on. Come on. Come on. Come
on. Come on. Come on. Thank God. Press forward. Good hit. Press forward. Blank and destroy. Blank
and destroy. They have no morale. How do I make them get morale? Holy shit. I just hit everybody.
Press forward. Press what? Press what? I think this is over. Press forward. They got no morale.
Get that green ball. Press forward. This is it. Press forward. Come on. I got a green fucking ball.
Is this? What? Press forward. What the fuck is going on with the ball? Press forward.
Press forward. Shit. Dude, fuck. This is playing pinball with a bunch of people.
That was really good. Press forward. They've no morale. They're not gonna listen to me.
You're losing frames. No, I'm not falling for that again. Press forward. Are they going? I gotta,
like, close this other gate. Trying this one more fucking time. One more time. One more time.
Don't put out all your troops yet. Knock this down first. Boom. Okay. Just so it's available.
Good. Get the key too. That's both now. Hold on. Don't. Get the key. Get the key first.
Rally. What? What am I opening this door even for? What's the point of opening this door?
No, no, no. Close the gate. Close it. Oh my God. Why did that have to happen?
I've tried to aim at that fucking thing a hundred times. Rally. Give them encouragement. There is
no encouragement. The door, the key opens up. Hold on. Push forward. Press forward. We use the
key to open the gate. Flank and destroy. Flank and destroy. Did I just kill, like, how many people
did I just kill? Close the gate. Good. The curse is in the wrong place. Close the gate. Good hit.
Close the gate. Why did they, where'd they come from? They're all, wait, who did that?
Close the gate. Close the, close the gate. Close the gate. Close the gate. It closed.
It hit the gate. The gate closed. It was the other gate that was closed.
That only works on the second gate. Oh, so fuck. Fuck. Okay. Yeah, I know. I know. I know. I want
to at least see the boss. I mean, I want to see the first boss. Okay. Here we go. That one's closed.
Don't hit that gate anymore. I can't even control. Rally. I can't even control where the thing goes.
I'm just going to knock that over and press forward. Press forward. Press forward. Press forward.
Press forward. Press forward. Just swim. Swim, damn you. Press forward. It happened again.
I'm not sending any troops out until it's clear that I've got that settled.
What is this? Bad? Bad what? Bad. This, this, this image just confuses me. I don't, I, I, this image
confuses me. I don't even know. Thinking quickly, Jerma constructs a GameCube mode.
That's like too many replacements here. All right. Don't send any troops out until I got this fucking
clear. Fuck morale. Fall back. Fall back. Okay. I'm in danger. Press forward. Stop them. Press
forward. Flank it. Flank it. Destroy. Flank and destroy. Fuck. I have to beat this level.
Those of Marge Simpson still say things that make me laugh. Right at the middle. Okay. Rally. They
have the key. They have the key. Don't, do not touch that fucking water gate. Don't you dare touch
that water gate. Nope. This is the one. Advance. Advance. Advance. Advance. How do you close the
gate? Oh shit. Rally. Somebody get that. Fall. Wait. He's gonna get in. He's gonna make it.
These nice tube reactions. Oh. Advance. Advance. Fall back. Oh. I gotta get that open. Open it.
Open it. Somebody said use your brain. What are you? I, I, this is so complicated. It's like
random. Let me get the fucking key. Advance. Advance. Advance. This water. How do I turn that
water off? Press forward. Press forward. Press forward. Dude, it's so impossible to like, okay,
I don't know why you got the random chance to turn the fucking well off. Good for you.
Press forward. Close the gate. Close the gate. What are you, what's taking you so long? What are
you doing? Get up there and fucking put it on. Put it, why are they not doing anything?
Close the gate. They, they're fucked up. They won't put it on the fucking door. I'm ready to go.
Close the gate. Oh my god. You fucking. Oh. Rally. Why wouldn't they put the thing on the,
on the gate? I have to fucking do this one more time. I gotta fucking play.
Last opportunity. This is the last one. And then we're watching Pokemon TV. No. I have to do this.
Oh shit. It's okay. No, no, no. It's fine. Fine. Just rush it. Just rush it. Just rush B.
Press forward. I'm gonna lose my fucking mind. I don't give a shit. What, who cares about the key?
It's not even important. Fall back. Fall back. March left. Press forward. Press forward. Press
forward. Rally. No, I want. Rally. What a roll. They wouldn't look at that fucking RNG. Look at
that fucking RNG roll. This is the one. Press forward. Oh shit. Okay. Nobody come out. Nobody
go back. Good fucking rolls here. All right. Close the gate. Look at you. I'm killing so
many of them. This is the one. This is the one right here. Just get them. There's too many people.
There's too many people. All right. Put it in. Put it in. Close. They got it. They got it. They got
it. Close the gate. Let's go. Let's go. Close the gate. Close the gate. Advance. Push forward.
Press forward. How do I turn off that one? Press forward. Press forward. How do I advance? Rally.
Get that fucking ladder down. Climb the ladder. Get up there. Advance. I gotta get some good
fucking rolls here. Press forward. Yes. Press forward. Oh shit. Oh no. They're coming. They're
coming. Here come the, here come the, the, the, the, the clops.
Just kill them. Kill them. Kill them. Kill them.
No.
More of those like tongue out reactions. What do you mean rice balls? What does that mean?
I have two. It didn't tell me about that. What is that?
What is that? What is that? How do I use them? Use the rice ball. Holy shit. Okay, I gotta move.
Rally. Press forward. All right, this is quick. Good hit. Very good hit. Blank and destroy.
Blank and destroy. Oh, fuck! The fucking water is back on. Holy shit, this sucks.
I have to beat this level. I'm so upset. I'm so addicted to it. I have to win.
I can't just give up. No, what do you mean just give up? Are you serious?
I came so close last time. All right, let's go. That's a gambler mentality. No, it's not.
No, it's not. This is not a gambler's fallacy. I paid like $12 for this game. I don't have to
gamble anymore money. Why are you moving forward? What the fuck are you doing? Just, oh my god.
No, no. Just make it work. Fall back. Select the bell. Fall back. What the fuck is even
happening, man? Why did it even turn off? Press forward. Rally. Just don't touch the fucking thing
on the right. I can't even control that. It's a pinball game. Press forward. Get it over there.
Come on. I'm gonna save 30 people for reserves. Press forward. Good hit. All right, close the
fucking gate. Close the gate. Stop showing me this shit. I don't care. Rally. Do it. Here we go.
Press forward. Press forward. Press forward. Get in there. Press forward. Wait, what about the
other river? How do I turn that river off? Press forward. Press forward. How do you turn this river
off? Just don't. Press forward. Press forward. Oh my god, this shithole rolls. Press forward.
Press forward. Oh no. Press forward. Press forward. Press forward. I can't give you help here.
It's a fucking pinball game. Press forward. Press forward. How do I, how do I eat this?
How do you, how do you, okay. How do I eat the fucking, how do I eat this? I have to hit the
bell. Just throw a hundred dice in the air and see if you win a round. Press up. Oh, that's not how
you do it. Tilt it. Dude, the ball moves so stupidly. Press forward. Advance. Press forward.
Advance. Look at how long this is taking. You can't even aim this shit. Oh my god. He's gonna
start fucking mauling. Advance. Just flank and destroy. Flank and destroy. Flank and destroy.
Flank and destroy. Move forward. It won't work. Now they have no morale. I don't know how to eat
these rice balls. Use the, how? Command scroll? Close the gate. Rally. Fall back. But there's no
like, there's no like eat food command. Okay. I press A. Where's my cursor? Dude, where's the,
I can't shoot anymore. Where did it even go? I can't even move my cursor down. Eat it. No.
Oh crap. Press. Move forward. Press forward. Advance. Are you crazy? It won't work. There's
nothing on the fucking battlefield. There's nothing here. Advance. Advance. Advance. Advance. Oh my
god. Get it. Okay, here we go. Destroy those towers. Give them to me. Give me all these people. Oh,
get them all. I just collected like a thousand of those people. Go, go, go. Rally. I hear,
already? What the fuck is happening already? How the fuck am I supposed to stop this shit?
Oh, are you, are you serious? Get the fuck out of here. Advance. Get that shit on there. Give me
that other ball. Give me that green ball. I gotta fucking do something about this. Why are they
crossing? No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no. Put it on. Rally. You're gonna kill those motherfuckers
over there. Get, kill them. Fall back. Go get those fucking people. Rally. Help them. Okay,
it's on, it's on, it's on. All right, here we go. This is the one. It has to be. Close the gate.
Advance. Go, go straight down. Advance. Advance. Advance. Press forward. Flank and destroy.
Press forward. Advance. Press forward. Press forward. Advance. One guy just moved it.
One guy just ran into it with his, all of his might. He just made it up.
Press forward. Advance. Press forward. Press forward. Press forward. Press forward. Press forward.
Dude, that one guy just like superman blocked it and just like pushed it forward.
Holy shit, that guy saved everything.
All right, I have bad morale. I only have 114 soldiers. Okay, here we go. This is the
boss fight. This is the only reason why I care. Dude, I did two or three straight up, straight down.
That guy's huge. The final battle of the Kuruwau Plains. That menacing figure is General Kawai
Apechia. I could have hit him with the ball, don't I?
Wait, it's flipper versus flipper?
So he's playing pinball too. Rally troops had a flipper to seize it.
They're right in the fucking head. Holy shit. Advance. What happens if the ball doesn't move?
Advance. Press forward. Press forward. How do I get the ball back? Advance.
Uh, oops, I just gave them food. Blank and destroy. Press forward. Rally. No, no, rally.
I don't know. I think I'm just cheating. He's destroying his own shit. Whoa, whoa, it jumped
the fence. Advance. I need that green. Advance. Oh, I might be in a lot of trouble here. This is
over. I got the... It's mine. It's mine. I own it. I own them both. Holy shit. Advance. What are the
hands? Rally. Come on, I need that green. I need that green right now. I need the green right now.
Yeah, I need to come down here. Come down here. Oh, I would have gotten a shitload of people.
Fuck. The green makes it so you steal them. Oh, this is funny. Okay, I got it. I got it.
Same deal. Yeah, let's go. Right up top. Okay. Get it stuck over here. Fuck him up. Fuck him up.
Don't even... Oh, fuck him up. Press forward. Rally. I want to just be in control and just
fucking diarrhea on him. Is it mine? Rally. Give it to me. Oh, sweet. Oh, sweet. Oh, sweet.
Is that me or you? Who did that? Press forward. Rally. Give me that. Give me that
morale. Press forward. Don't fall in the middle of this shit. Come on. Come on, you stupid
motherfucker. Oh, you fucking asshole. Green. And I got control. There it is. Press forward.
Get up there. Get up there. Go. Press forward. Get up there. Yes. Okay, here we go. Press forward.
Stay up there. Stay up there. Roll this way. Come on. Take it all out. Press forward. This is it.
This is it. Bounce, bounce, bounce, bounce, bounce, bounce. Take him out of his chair.
Press forward. Press forward. I don't even know where the fucking ball is.
Press forward. Advance. Get the... Come on. I didn't mean to kill everybody. I need the green
up there in the corner. Press forward. I need the green. Come on, you can do it. No, they have no...
No, no, no. Push forward. Do you have to rally for the food? Oh, I'm fucking dead.
This is... I got fucked up from the... Press forward. Press forward. Move forward. It's all
right. It's all right. I can do it again. I can do it again. At least look at these just
flooding people. It's all right. It's all right. It's all right. We go... We do it again.
Gotta start tilting. I keep getting that. We're going... Same deal. Right up the fucking middle.
Start deploying. Go. Rally. Press forward. I just threw him a fucking snack. Press... Rally.
I don't even know what's happening. Press forward. Flank and destroy. Get up there.
Holy shit. I just... I just blew up his hands. Rally. Attack this motherfucker right now.
Good. Advance. Press forward. Where's the green shit? How come I can't control this?
Rally. Press forward. Holy shit. He has so many more troops than I do. I instantly destroyed every
one of his structures. How the fuck am I losing? Press forward. Press forward. Press forward. Press
forward. I'm not fucking tilting either. Look, the reason why I'm not tilting is because every
single time, every video game you've ever played, every establishment you've ever been to,
if you tilt, the game goes, don't fucking do that, and you get in trouble. It's burning my brain.
Here we go. Jesus Christ. I know. I know. I've restarted a thousand times. You don't... We don't
have to do this every time. Press forward. Press forward. Fucking green. Press forward.
Fucking tilt. Tilt the game queue. Let's go. Ah, that was a shit start. Easy. Easy. Don't...
Press. Press forward. Rally. Keep this shit on his side. Can he grab the fucking pinball machine
and like tilt too? I have control. Fall back. Okay, I own it. Fall back. Fall back. Press forward.
Press... Shit. Give up? I'm not going to give up at the boss. I'm beating this fucking boss before
I move on to anything else. Look, I'm going to headshot him right here. All right.
Do it! What the fuck just happened? It bounced over the... All right, you hit it too hard. That's
like when you're playing air hockey with all your friends and they hit it too hard and it's like,
dude, it's like... It like bounces and goes that way. Like fucking relax. That was so good too.
Never pressed forward. Doesn't matter. The ball came back to hit me in the fucking... What's going on?
That's the problem. It was too far away. Why am I addicted to this fucking stupid ass game?
Press forward. Oh, what? It's not fucking fair. Press forward. I gotta go around. Blank and destroy.
Well, that was dumb. That was really dumb. I should not have done that. Just reset it. No,
there's a chance. Rally. Oh, there's one person alive. It can be quite the rally.
Zero morale. One guy. Well, I'm getting... I'm like heating up from this. This is like heating me up.
You know what I mean? Again? Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. I gotta beat this guy. You know what? We're going
to go in the corner. Fuck that. We're going to go into the corner. Stay back. I want to select the
bell. Fall back. All right. Now get that shit. Push forward. Press forward. Press forward. Get in
there. Fall back. Get in there, please. Come on. Bounce around in there. Please. Oh my god. Oh,
now you do it. Now you do it. Great. Good. Press forward. Eat something. Eat something. Eat, eat,
eat, eat, eat. Rally. Eat. Eat. That seriously just bounced back over the fence. Here we go.
We go. Good. Press forward. Oh, it just all just deleted. Oh, there's so many people. That just
got deleted. Press forward. Press forward. Oh, yeah. Yay. Look, it's over already. It's just
fucking over. If you don't get like a good bounce in the first five seconds, just reset the damn game.
Everybody get in there. Press forward. Good roll. Good fucking roll. Press forward. Look at that
fucking roll. Press forward. Advance. Advance. Dude, what the fuck is happening right now?
What the? Advance. Someone made the video. Hit the bell. I know, but you can't hit it. Advance.
Holy shit. Come on. Come on. Kill these motherfuckers. Kill these motherfuckers. Advance.
Fuck you, man. God. What? This was magnetized to my character? That's just don't worry. It's
just the Wii sensor bar. It was just the Wii sensor bar. Wasn't anything expensive.
You can have two goddamn candles and it'll work. I want to watch this video. I want to watch this
video. Where is it? Somebody actually made it. Good. I can't wait to watch this. Hold on. Let me
get the whatgermawanted.mp4. Whatgermawanted.mp4. It's four views. I'm about to be number five, man.
Hold on. I mean, wrong one. Wrong one. I got the right one. Please. Okay, this is what I wanted.
Wrong one. I don't understand. It's this one. Why is it? What are you talking about?
Germavape. How many of these were made? Here we go. I've been waiting for this shit. Why did you add
that? Wait, but hold on a second. Why did you? It was just supposed to be the e-cigar. Why did
you make it an actual vape pen? It comes up for so long. And then, look, it trails off and it happens
again. It's perfect. And all y'all were saying, why is he doing this? Come on, man. Minus two.
Come on, man. That's what I wanted. That's what I want. I'm getting really fucking sweaty.
That's fucking hilarious. I love it. All right, let's go. Wait, to the other one. Oh, there is
another one. This one's much longer than that one. Can somebody please give me an edit? Somebody,
please. I know one of you will do it before the stream ends. Just please do this. You know exactly
what I'm looking for. You know what I want you to do. Okay? Just hold on a second. Wait, did you
not edit it? I've been waiting for this shit. Imagine doing that. You just blow a train whistle.
That's just what you do every like seven minutes. Another one. I'm not clicking that. All right,
that's it. There's a better one. Stop blinking the fucking uh-oh stinky video, okay? I'm not
gonna watch it. All right, that was fun. Let's go back to what we were doing. Me desperately trying
to beat this microphone video game from 20 years ago. 50,000 channel points for a train whistle.
That's not happening. Back to losing at pinball on purpose. It's fucking exhausting.
Press forward. Oh god. All right, give me something. Press forward. Damn, this morale is so bad. I'm
not gonna bring any troops out until it's confirmed that everything's safe. It's that hard.
Come on. There it is. There it is. There it is. Press forward. Press forward. Press forward.
Press forward. Where's the fucking ball? Rally. Rally. Rally. Fall back. Fall back. They're not
doing shit. Fall back. Push forward. Rally. Like this is stuck here forever. Rally. Eat that. Eat
that. Fall back. Rally. Okay. Press. I don't know. Depend. I don't know. Stuck again. Why are you
hitting it? What are you doing, dude? Press forward. Press. It's sideways. I don't know.
I don't know. Press forward. I gotta get this shit up there. You gotta get it up there and bounce
around before he fucking kills all you guys. He looks like he's playing a racing game. Retreat.
You gotta get it up there and fucking smash the fuck out of him before you even send anybody.
He looks like he's riding a horse. The audio is desynced. It shouldn't be. Hold on. We're gonna
test this sometime. One. Two. Three. Hold on. It's a little off. I'm like a couple of- I'm like 100
milliseconds early. Let's try this. Let's try like changes anything. Okay. Hold on. One. Two. It's
way worse. I'm not fucking muted. I think we're good. Is that good? Get that green. And here we
go. This is it. Not- nothing worse than it could happen. Rally. Rally. Rally. Rally. Get it. Get it.
Oh, you fucking idiot. Remember your GameCube mic is muted. Oh, shit.
All right. Rally. Where are you guys going? Rally. How are they getting in? Oh, you fucking missed
everything and now you're stuck. Rally. Get it. Press forward. I got a shitload. Press forward.
Press forward. Attack and flank. Whatever that means. I can't even get the fucking ball up there
again. Fall back. Oh my god. You gotta be fucking kidding me. What a pain in the ass. Rally. Push
forward. Why am I shut down? Press forward. He's down. Opportunity. Rally. Green. Push forward.
Press forward. Get that. I gotta get that. Press forward. Okay. All right. All right. All right.
You motherfucker. They hit a fucking- you hit a goddamn tree and it stopped you. It hit a tree.
It hit a fucking tree. Press forward. Oh, that just fucked it all up. Press forward. Press forward.
Rally. I think I hit that fucking tree. Actually mad at pinball. Oh, wouldn't you be?
Shit. Ball. Ball's fucking reversing. Press forward. Press forward. Get up there.
Fall back. Fall back. Push forward. Rally. Come on. There's nobody fucking there. Did I get it? Push
forward. Press forward. Kill them all. Kill all of them. Press forward. Push forward. Get that green.
Get that green. I need that green right now. Press forward. Come on. Get that green. Get that
fucking green. Get the green. Get the green. There's a wall in front of me. Come on, man.
Oh my god. Press forward. Dude, how many fucking times do I have to roll over his entire army
before I fucking can win? Everyone's dead. Look at how he's just flooding fucking people in. 24-7.
Fall back. Rally. All right. Kill this motherfucker. Fucking kill him. Go. Press forward.
Rally. Kill this motherfucker. Come on. Come on. Press forward. Dude, why does he get to have this
many fucking people? He's just flooding fucking people in forever. Press forward. Press forward.
Holy shit, man. He just deposits hundreds of fucking troops every 10 seconds. Go. Go. Give me those.
Rally. Rally. Kill him. Oh my god. The physics don't make any fucking sense in this goddamn game.
He's actually malding right now. Like, he's malting. Rally. Rally. Just fucking spam that
bell move. Give me some green. Green. Give me some green. Give me that green. Give me the
green. Press forward. Press forward. Press forward. This feeds thousands of fucking troops.
A thousand. Press forward. Press forward. Press forward. Oh my god. This is ridiculous.
Press forward. He's pissing blood. Press forward. Rally. Fall back. Press. Make sure you keep killing
your own troops. Unfortunately, this game, there's a gigantic ball that rolls around the whole court
and it's a pinball game and he can shoot it back at me. It's like, hey, I know you're driving
right now, but there's fucking land mines everywhere. Just don't swerve around those
because I'm going to run over a landmine. I don't know. What am I going to do? Where's the ball?
Oh my god, please. Push forward. Press forward. Press forward. Flank and attack. Flank and attack.
Press forward. Press forward. Rally.
Stupid fucking goddamn game. I have to beat this. I'm not playing after this.
I have to beat this shitty level on principle. Press forward. Flank and attack.
Press forward. Press forward. Get that fucking green. Fall back. Press forward.
Flank and attack. Flank and attack. Holy shit. Push forward. Press forward. Flank and attack.
Rally. Get up, all you motherfuckers. Come on. Rally. Flank and attack. Get that green. I need that
green. Okay. Press forward. Rally. Be green. Get that fucking green. I need that right now. Get
that green. Okay. All right. Okay. Okay. Okay. Fuck. Flank and attack. Flank and attack.
There's none of troops. Dude, what in the fuck is this game doing right now? This is winnable right
here. This is literally no rhyme or reason to anything that's happening. Bring it down. Bring
it down here. Bring it down. Bring it down. Bring it down. There's an extra time. Who gives a shit?
Rally. Give me that fucking green ball. You can't be serious. Here we go, motherfucker. Now we're in
business. Now we're in business. Press forward. Rally. Rally. God damn it, man. What the fuck?
Press forward. How many fucking people did he just get? Press forward. Rally. You can't get up. You
can't. You can't. Push forward. Press forward. I just hit somebody. Press forward. Rally.
Press forward. Press forward. Get that fucking green ball. Get that fucking green. Green. Green.
Green. Green. Green. Green. Green. Green. Press forward. Fucking tree. Rally. Rally. This is it.
Come on. My god. Push forward. Push forward. Push forward. That's the right time. Just 30 seconds.
Oh my god. Imagine having a time limit in this dumb fucking game.
You gotta be kidding me. I am shocked and I am appalled right now. No way. No way.
These fucking shells shot. Why is there a time limit? Why would there be a time limit?
This is such a fucked up game. Oh my god. Damn it, man. Fuck that. Fuck that, man.
Oh shit. No way. I'm so sad. What? Press forward. Press forward. Press forward. Rally. This is
fucked up, man. Fucked up. Press forward. Give me that green. This is a wash. This is a wash.
This is a wash. I can't believe I was just gonna beat it and the game didn't want me to. It didn't
let me. I can't be defeated by the boss. I have to fucking beat this. Okay. In five more
tries. I'm breaking the disc on camera. If I don't do it. Press forward. Press forward. Rally. Give
me the fucking ball. Rally. Rally. Please. Deploy. Rally. Rally. I didn't like the puke. That was
like a burp and then I just made a noise after it. Don't worry. This is gonna be the one. Press
forward. How did it go over the fucking wall? Give me a break, video game. Green ball. Okay,
got a ball. Press forward. Press forward. Flank and attack. Press forward. Rally. Rally. Kill him.
Oh my god. Flank and attack. Flank and destroy. Flank and destroy. Flank and destroy. Press
forward. Rally. Dude, I can't even see. Why would you have text on the screen? Imagine developing
this game and being like, hey, you know what I gave you? I trashed text pop up like fucking The
Sims. I can't even believe it. Rally. Rally. Push forward. Gotta get the fuck in there, man.
Flank and destroy. Press forward. Rally. Rally. Rally. Rally. Flank and destroy. Press forward.
Press forward. Flank and destroy. Rally. Eat it. Sit. Rally. Press forward. Press forward. Rally.
Rally. Press forward. Rally. Rally. Rally. Uh, is everybody dead? Get that green. Oh, you. I can't
believe this. I have time coming up now. Give me time. Press forward. Is that time? No, it's not.
Press forward. Is this even a fucking winnable game? Is this game ever winnable? I was doing
all right there. I was doing fine. I said five attempts. That was one. Rally. Get it. What did
it just jump over? Rally. Rally. Rally. Everyone's dead. I need green right now. Do I have control
of the both? Push forward. Rally. Oh my God. He just keeps feeding people in. Fall back. Green
right there. Green right there. Got it. Oh my God. Absolutely fucking beautiful. Kill everybody.
Fall down here and get all these motherfuckers right now. Yup. Yup. All in. Press forward.
Flank and destroy. Push forward. I need that green. Rally. Flank and destroy. It's so fucking,
it's like, it's so much more annoying than it looks, I promise. Get the fucking bell. Oh my
fucking God. Damn it, man. Flank and destroy. Rally. I have 200 seconds. Come on. Press forward.
Smash that bell. Oh my God. Why do the trees respawn? There's no reason for it. Oh my God.
You're killing me. Why would a tree respawn right now? You've got to be shitting me. Rally.
Press forward. Press forward. Flank and destroy. Press forward. Rally. Press. I can't even keep up
with how many people he has and the trees keep respawning and it bounces me back. Holy fuck,
holy man. I have to kill this motherfucker? Press forward. And I have 87 seconds. Oh,
good thing the trees respawned. Good job, Mike. That's a good fun game. Press forward. Press
forward. Press forward. It's fucking ridiculous. Let's kill the fucking guy. I can't even see.
All right. Kill him. Kill him. It's time for him to die. Rally. Rally. Where are they coming from?
Is it time? Press forward. You've got to get the fuck up there, man. Knock him down. Rally.
Kill him. Kill this motherfucker right now. What the fuck am I hitting? This is fucking chaos.
Rally. Fucking kill. Rally. Why can't they? Rally. Rally.
Wicked witch of the west. What the fuck? Push forward. Rally. Rally. Push forward.
Press forward. Fucking unbelievable. Fucking god damn believable. Press forward. Rally. Rally.
Rally. Rally. Get me in both. Now. Now. What's taking you so fucking long? There's like a
hundred of you up there. What is taking you so long? Rally. Fall back. Fall back. Fall back.
Push forward. Oh my god. Why does that have to be so fucking annoying? Just get in there so I can...
How much time do I have? What a fucking joke. Press forward. Press forward. Rally. What the
fuck is happening? Press forward. Why in the name of god do they respawn? Why in the name of god's
green earth do they respawn? Press forward. Press forward. Now I'm overwhelmed because he has five
million more troops than me because they just keep pouring the fuck out. Rally. Push forward.
I have only 146 seconds, man. I just... All right. We just played. I caught it. Rally. Oh my god.
Please. This is fucking ridiculous. This is fucking ridiculous, man. This is three. I got two more
tries before I eat this disc on camera. Rally. Rally. I don't have enough time. This is the third
level of the game. Yeah. What the hell were you thinking? Did you develop the game with your eyes
closed? Oh, now he's actually getting mad. Now he's actually getting like angry. Rally. Rally. Rally.
Get that green. Fuck. What? What the fuck, man? What are you talking about? How long does it take
you motherfuckers to capture? You captured the left one in five seconds. Fall back. I got no men.
Stay up there. Stay up there. Stay up there. Come on. I need like 100 people.
Press forward. That's not 100 people. You need to write a blues song about this. Press forward.
Press forward. Press forward. What the fuck just happened? Press forward. Can I get a green?
Why does it feel like he has more people now than before that just happened? Look at his front lines.
Press fuck. What the fuck? He's got more fucking humans. Press forward. Press forward. I have no
men. This thing is going to push me back. Press forward. Press forward. Press forward. What was
that? What the fuck? All right. Let's go everybody up. Push forward. Push forward. Press forward.
Press forward. Press forward. Press forward. Press forward. Hey, press forward. Press forward. Hey,
press forward. Oh. Press forward. Why did the green just disappear? Rally. Rally. Rally. Press
forward. Press forward. Press forward. Fall back. Press forward. Press forward. Press forward. This
is it, Ryder. In the meantime, I'm going to snack, snack, snack, snack, snack, snack, snack, snack,
rally. Fall back. Fall back. I can't even get a fucking goddamn fruit snack. Press forward.
Get it. Get that green thing. Get the green thing. And now there's a wall here that's
screwing up my whole game. There's a wall here now that's messed up the whole thing now, son,
didn't it? You messed up the whole thing, son. This is insanity. Imagine getting this for
Christmas and crying because you can't beat this. Imagine how bad your mother or father would
felt watching your fucking son or daughter sit here and cry playing this level to be like,
shit, should have got some Super Mario Sunshine. Oh, should I help them? Press forward. Rally.
Get up there. Dude. Rally. Rally. It's over. It's already over. Put me on. Put me on. Oh, well,
retreat. That's what you got to do. You got to say it's fucking over. You got to talk about how
it's over and it's not over. That's what you got to do. That's what you got to do. And then
the game has to like have a great... Don't even talk shit. Just play. Fall back. Push forward.
Rally. Troops die soon as they come out. Yeah. And unfortunately for me, I don't get to have an
infinite supply like this motherfucker does. See, this dickhead can just spawn as many people as
he wants for the entire duration of this whole fight. I get like a hundred people and then maybe
a green fruit snack ball that I can steal some of his guys. This is infinite fucking dog shit.
No, it's not. One more after this. Press forward. Press forward. Rally. Why did I lose the green
immediately? Rally. Rally. Rally. Fall back. Rally. Why does it take them so long? It takes them one
second to capture the left one. Why does it take so long to capture the right one?
Oh. Rally. Oh, you did it. You finally did it. Fall back. Rally. Press forward. How did you sneak
by there, motherfucker? What just happened? We don't have any more fucking morale. TikTok.
TikTok. There's no more men. There's no more men on my team. Give me the green ball. Give me the
green ball and all things are fine. Push forward. Push forward. Push forward. This is actually the
last time I'm going to do this before I'm going to put this fucking disk in like and put like a
random address and fucking like and like Antarctica and ship it there. I'm going to like middle of the
fucking ocean in Antarctica or something. Get this away from my house. That was fucking such bullshit.
That wasn't even fair. That was not even. That was not even. Shit. That's so unfair.
That doesn't count. That doesn't count. That doesn't. That can't count.
Push forward. Press forward. Dude, the ball. What the fuck are you doing, mate? Rally. Rally.
Everybody's dead. I gotta get it up there. In there. He's addicted. I'm addicted. I'm addicted
to not. I'm addicted to beating this one boss. Fucking audio is killing my brain. Rally. All
right. I need green now. Green. Green. Green. Green. Green. Green. Green. Green. Green. Green.
Give me the green thing. It's not green. Fall back. Fall back. That's what I want. Did his wall just
respawn? Why did this motherfucker's wall just respawn? Fall back. Rally. Press forward. Press
forward. Get that fucking green. This is it. Why did it take it off, bro? Press forward. Press
forward. Press forward. I was trying to roll it over to the fucking stupid time. Rally. Press forward.
Rally. Rally. Three hours of crackling audio. Rally. Rally. I know. There's like explosions
in my fucking ear. I know. There's nothing left. It's just a bell guy. I took the disc out and I
can't even stop. I took the fucking CD out and I can't even stop playing. This game looks a little
frustrating with a happy face. What if you beat it with the disc? This cover is open. If you want
to continue, close the disc cover. No, I don't think I do. Remind me to never play that game
ever again. Remind me to fucking shred the disc before this stream turns off. It's fun. It's fun.