From the spooky sunset, comes two minecrafters ready to do the Halloween special.
That wasn't as spooky as I imagined it to be.
That was not as spooky as I imagined it to be.
That was not spooky at all.
You just kind of like glided across, didn't you?
We were supposed to, uh, whatever.
Hey, what's going on everybody? It's Jerma here.
And Incredible Orb.
Hello.
Gonna be doing a, another timed chaos build.
This time, we're doing a spooky Halloween special.
Oh my god, I'm so scared.
Spooked. What?
So what we're gonna do today, we're gonna, I'm so spooked.
I'm so spooked.
We're gonna do a, uh, a witch on a broom is the timed chaos build.
And I have the perfect plan.
You got the plan?
Yes.
I hope you do because this is gonna be incredibly difficult.
It's gotta be fine, man. It's gotta be fine.
So let's set the time.
You give me the, you give me the, the go sign or the go whatever.
All right. I'll let you know. Don't worry.
Signal.
So we're gonna have seven minutes to do this.
Don't ask me why the ground is like weird color.
I don't know what happened.
It wasn't me.
Orb like blew it up.
Don't ask, but it wasn't me.
But anyways, here we go.
In three, two, one, go.
Oh jeez.
That was like instant.
You gotta be quick. You gotta be quick.
All right. We need, we need the broom.
All right. You, you, you, you do, you do the shaft.
I'll do the old boy.
That didn't come out right.
It didn't come out right.
Just keep it going.
I hate to say this, but we've got to make the broom thicker.
Yeah. Well, make, make sure the broom like comes up and like,
so it's not just like, oh, it's already ruined.
I can't even talk.
Because it's good.
That's good. That's good.
Keep it going. Keep it going.
Okay. Okay. Okay.
I've got to do.
Hey, I need like, I need what?
Oh wait.
Are you missing colors?
No, no, no, nevermind.
This is going to be her legs.
Oh, this is a really short broom.
Well, yeah, that broom is way too short.
What are you doing?
No, no, no.
Okay. Okay. Okay.
I got it. I got a plan. I got a plan.
What am I doing over here?
This has got to come out and then like this.
It started off really weird, but it's got to be better.
It's going to be even longer than that.
Yeah.
I mean, you got to make it thicker too.
But hey, it's not about the size.
Motion of the ocean.
Here we go.
We're making like a Lego spaceship, by the way.
Okay.
This needs to come up like a little bit like this.
This has got to be her legs.
It's got to be like a seat.
See, I'm making like the seat right now.
Wait, what? I'm making legs.
What are you doing?
A seat?
Yeah, that's like, this is like the seat.
She's going to be sitting on it.
Hey, by the way, almost two minutes have gone by.
We don't have a dirty time.
Oh, no, no.
Oh, God.
All right.
Here's her leg.
I'm going to make it.
I'm going to make her shoe.
She doesn't have to be that big.
Okay.
Nice shoes.
What?
Oh, God.
I just dropped.
Oh, you dropped connection.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no.
I just dropped down.
Okay.
So.
Oh, a nice like lopsided bird legs she has, by the way.
Keep going.
From the parrot.
Okay.
So is this like her body?
Yes.
So build it up.
Oh, two minutes have gone by.
She's really square.
It's okay.
We just got to make.
We got to make a face.
We got to get the foundation first.
We got.
We got to make her bigger, though, because otherwise the face.
How do you make a face?
You can't make a face on this.
This looks like a sword going through some guy's balls.
Like, this is ridiculous.
Oh, look.
Great like sword going through this guy's balls.
That's fantastic.
This is the best Halloween special ever.
Yeah.
She's got to be a little thicker.
Okay.
Yeah.
We got to make her.
I mean, she.
Heavy said last.
Yeah.
You don't know.
Three minutes have gone by.
Okay.
Yeah.
See that.
But how big is she going to be, though?
Because you can't be too.
That's okay.
This is her face.
Yeah.
Her face is going to come this way.
She's going to have a green face because witches have green faces.
That's eyes.
Wait, that's eyes?
I don't know.
What?
What does she?
What does she like?
Kermit the frog?
Like, no.
We're done.
What?
What are you talking about?
We're done.
She's got a big witch nose and stuff.
What is?
Oh, yeah.
All right.
Hold on.
This is her head.
This is going to come up like this.
Okay.
And this is her nose.
All right.
There's like a hood.
She needs like a hood.
What are you doing?
That's her nose.
No, that's not her.
Her face is right here.
Oh.
Dude, she doesn't have like, like, like knife boobs.
I once.
That's her nose.
Yeah.
She's got to go to the good like what?
All right.
Now we need eyes.
I was thinking.
I'm going to make her have like a hood.
Hold on.
That's her eyes.
No, but wait.
Her eyes.
Because her hood is going to be black.
So no, make her make her hood black and make the face blue.
Well, she's going to have a green face.
I think.
Oh, she needs like a mouth, too.
It's got to be black.
Her clothing.
Yeah.
You're right.
Right.
So whatever.
Oh, my God.
Hold on.
Why does she have a black nose?
It should be green.
She's got a green face.
Obviously.
No, that's too long.
She's got blue eyes.
It doesn't look realistic.
Come on, dude.
There's her.
There's her blue eyes.
Are they like bulging out?
All right.
She's.
This is the worst.
All right.
Almost five minutes.
We're going to give her arms.
You're going to be holding on to this.
Yeah.
Yeah, of course.
I'm going to cover her back of her face with a cape or a cape with a cape.
No, with her clothing, her hoodie, whatever.
Broken.
Okay.
Seriously.
That's that looks fine.
We got to fix this.
What is this arm?
Is this an arm?
It's her like pipe arms.
And she's got to hold.
What is it?
Is she holding a wand?
I don't know what.
Yeah.
Let's have her hold a wand.
Is that a common thing for a witch?
We don't.
We don't have.
Yeah, sure.
Just do it.
Just do the.
Oh, shit.
Hold on.
I'm not finished making her spiral staircase.
Like.
Actually, this looks actually pretty cool.
You see that?
That's pretty good.
All right.
Let's go to the top.
Here we go.
Like the top.
No, no, no.
Why?
Like that.
See?
Oh, yeah.
That's killer.
But that arm is not.
Yeah.
This arm is not gonna.
This is bad.
Well, can't the arm just can't the arm like sort of come from here?
Yeah.
I just don't understand like depth perception in Minecraft.
Just.
Okay.
So is her feet going to be they're not equally long?
No, but that's all right.
It's okay.
Is there anything like a dude like trying to like cover?
Yeah.
But shoot.
I don't know about you, man.
But you can't ride a broom if you don't hold on to it.
She's like standing on it.
Dude, this is the this is the Statue of Liberty.
We made the Statue of Liberty.
This is the Statue of Liberty.
With a wart in her face.
It's got to make the crown.
All right.
We got the we can work on that.
No, she's got to have at least one hand.
This hand's got to be on the broom.
We only have 30 seconds.
No, no, no.
We got it.
So this has got to come down like this and across.
Why is the broom like weird looking back here?
I don't know.
That's her.
Like, that's her thing.
That's her thing.
Oh, man.
This arm.
We only got 10 seconds.
God.
Well, we got to make it pointy.
I don't understand arms.
Okay.
So this could be.
What is this?
What is this thing?
She's grabbing on.
That's it.
It's over.
Oh, my God.
Hey, man.
I think we did pretty good.
This was part of this was part of my plan.
This is part of my master plan.
I like this.
Hey, the wand thing.
The wand thing.
The red thing.
That was that was icing on the cake right there.
Yeah.
The Statue of Liberty wand was perfect.
That was so good.
I feel like this is better than your bird.
I feel like your bird is very blocky.
Hey, the birds got like a big butt.
All right.
Yeah.
Big booty.
No.
All right.
Well, thank you guys so much for watching.
Of course, you got to give this thing a name and rating and happy Halloween, everybody.
Happy Halloween or scary Halloween.
Thank you for Incredible Orb for his appearance.
Absolutely.
Anytime.
We'll see you guys all next time.
And of course, take care, everybody.