How do you do? How are you? Yeah.
We don't have to do a survival mode or anything.
I just want to go see the new arcade. We're in coin game now.
Did you take a lap around the room to calm down? Yeah, kind of.
So I paced a little bit. All right, let me get into here. This looks good.
That looks good. All right. So where's the new arcade? I'm in birthday mode.
I'm going to need to add this. Oh, there it is. Okay.
So anyone know where the new arcade is? I have my map, right?
You drive cars now or no, just not really. He really did get filtered.
No, I went through the filter and I passed through as clean water.
I got through it. I beat that boss. Go look at the, just go rewind, rewind.
I know you didn't believe it. I know you don't think it's real. I beat it. Uh,
okay. So I think it's the mall. I'm looking for the mall. Uh, yep.
Happy birthday. There it is. The mall. Oh shit. We're just going in the limo.
Cool. Let's go. Can you tell us please what liquid reflexes mean?
I, you're going to have to ask the person that said that. I don't know.
Whoever said that to you. I don't know. We made it. All right.
We made it to the mall. You said that that's, that's not provable. All right.
So here's the new area. Cool. You said it. You did. That's not proof.
That's not proof. Prove it. Then it was on this stream. You're taking,
talk about something I said, like two, three years ago,
like and you're taking it out of context. Now, what the heck?
Yeah. It was literally 32 minutes ago. What the, what the hell dude?
Ah, Gary, I'm sorry. I can do better than that.
Pirate pizza. Jerry's gourmet. Sammy's vacant.
Let's go sit there. Let's go. Can I buy jewelry? Oh,
I'm trying to take them. How do I get those? Can I buy anything here?
Ask for price, gold, fronts, iced, anything, custom rings.
Can I ask? Can I just say, hold on. Yeah. I can't just break it.
Arcade arcade castle. Let's go. There's apparently some new stuff.
I have 300 bucks. I didn't make it. You gotta go.
You gotta get the spot and just do only hundreds.
I'm going to say red is lined up right at the bottom. Let's go all the way green.
No, I'll get it. And I'll do every single one.
Red lined up right here at the bottom or the edge. Go that many green.
A little bit more. Am I aiming too high? Okay. Yeah. I'm aiming too high.
You can't use them. You can't say filter in here. All right. What was that?
Red lined up right here. All the way green. Maybe one yellow.
I'm going to get all fifties. Here we go.
Do the top armored course streamer right now. I might as well be playing it.
This is just as hard. It's it's inconsistent. I think you have to move with it.
I'll take a hundred points. That's fine. That's bad. Isn't it? Hey, all right.
That was fun. I was never good at ski ball.
Add a mech cockpit overlay. Can somebody just give me one that has opacity?
Oh, I'm good at this one. I'm not going to mess it up. I'll get it.
I'm my finger got crushed. Ow, my finger got crushed.
Can we put the, can we put the, all right, here's what I want.
I want, I want the, the crosshair in the middle.
And I want all the HUD information. I don't want like the guns on the side.
I want,
I'm walking around at a mech with all the little UI information. The game lagged.
You actually saw that happen. I'm seeing a lot of copiums, but it really did.
The hell's going on here. It's hard mode. Makes the game just way harder.
I got lucky there, but it worked. Shit.
I was so waiting for it to lag that I was in my own head. The lag,
even with the lag, I still, I had it. The lag,
I was going to scream something. I was going to say like, what the, but no,
let's chill. I ended up being fine. Almost clutched it. Yeah. Almost.
Not quite though. I get it. Clutched it. Feel good about that one.
How many tickets was it? Ooh, that's a lot. How many? 2000 tickets. Holy shit.
That's a lot. What did I get for this one? 162. That's not bad. All right.
What is this? So this is like a coin thing. Coin pusher. All right.
What am I looking for? I want, um, yeah, I want 120 coins.
All right. I have 120. So what am I trying to do here?
I'm trying to just drop stuff. You got it. Load it up.
The blue are worth a hundred. So what do I get for points? All right.
Stomp the mermaids space. What is it? How do I get the bonus?
Play the one with the ball. I'll play the one with the ball. Give me one sec.
This is your best content. 50. I'm going for the,
I'm going with the 50 right here. It's a hundred tickets, right?
I don't have to pick these up, right? There we go. I got 50 points.
I tried it. I'm going to try to get one of the hundreds. This one's the closest.
We're going to spam over here. Hundred incoming. Here it is. Oh shit.
I'm out of money. Oh, it's my birthday. I'll be all right. It's a little bit loud.
Uh, I'll take care of that. Give me one sec. That should be better.
All right. Let's skillfully do this now. Happy birthday. Hey, thanks.
Just want the a hundred and I'm good. Just dangling. Come on. Wait, see,
stop. Oh, I get it. Maybe if I get five points in,
let's see what happens when that five goes in, will it move five paces?
Come on, come on. All right. I need one more five. That'll do it right here.
That's two fives, but Oh, that's unfortunate.
All right. That five right there. That'll do it. Don't drop the 10,
drop the five right in this corner. Watch this. There it is. All right. Bonus.
I got a 237 tickets. Did you get the mech yet? Uh, there's one,
I have one in the mods have sent me, but that's more like,
I want like a spaceship. Look, look at all the tickets. I'm getting another bonus.
Whoa. 800 tickets. Oh, you've got 800 tickets there.
Oh, give it a spin. Oh, a thousand tickets. Yeah.
Okay. I know this one. I'm good at this one.
Let it go around once. Hmm. They may have patched this.
It's possible. This was patched. Shit. Shit. Shit.
Shit. Shit. Dude, dude, dude, I just,
I just got 385 tickets on that machine. Do you want to hang out? Hey, Hey,
Hey, do you want to hang out with me?
I just got 400 tickets on the machine to look. Don't for it again. Oh,
almost. Oh, Hey, two to eight, two in a row.
Hold on a second. This is, this is a kind of like, what is this?
Is this from fallout? Like what is this even from? What game is this from?
Hold on. Okay. There is a mask in here, so that's good. Okay.
So now here we go. What even is this from?
I have to act like a spacecraft, right? This is, this is mech warrior.
Let's go really, really organic limbs that this mech has weird.
It's not lined up that better. Shit.
Add a bunch of robot sounds in the background. Yeah, that has to be there.
Robot walking sound effects, giant robot walking. Oh, let me,
this might be loud. Hold on. The robot mic. Can I even do that here?
Hold on. Does this, uh, does this work? Does this work? How are we doing? Okay.
Okay. Let me just turn it around. Okay. Let's go for it. This one looks good.
It looks okay. Uh, now I will play this one.
We need tickets, tickets, tickets, tickets. Tickets.
Almost, almost a hundred. One more, one more, one more.
Almost a hundred. Is it loud? Oh, it is loud. Why is it so loud?
How did that get so loud? Is it better?
Candy, do you guys have Charleston shoes?
I'm not going to be able to see you. Okay. Was it really that loud?
That looked like it was kind of loud. Hopefully it wasn't too bad. It was okay.
Pick those up. Those are my tickets. It was incomprehensible.
What is this one? Oh, it's one of these. I know how to play these.
You have to like push them down, right? Oh, tickets to your right.
There's a thousand tickets on the ground where I don't see them. Oh, there they are.
That's not a thousand. That was 40. I want to get that cow.
There's more in there. Ooh, tickets. I want this cow. I've played these though.
You have to, you don't try to go for the grab. You try to push it over.
You don't actually want to pick it up. All right, there we go. That's good.
That's good. That's actually a big deal. Okay. Now we go from the behind here.
I just want to kind of nudge it. I don't want to pick it up.
Actually, it might be fine. I definitely got it. There it is.
I got the cow. Nice. Let me look at it.
I'd like to sell this for more coins.
I played this one before. This one's fun. Put it back in the machine.
I know there's another one. Oh, yes.
A hundred percent. This is the worst machine in the Intel.
I almost said casino. Woo. Woo. Woo. Woo. Woo.
What? Oh, shit. It lagged.
I want those headphones. Yay. Headphones.
I'll take that. I can definitely sell these for a lot of money.
All right. What's this one?
Ticket. Oh, I think you get tickets on your forty eight hundred.
I just a moment. What do you mean? Moment.
And they remove those.
I thought they got rid of moments.
Let me get the mega jackpot.
I'll take mystery ball to if he's good.
They didn't remove them yet.
Oh, I see. I just got the jackpot.
Oh, shit. Nice. OK.
I still have two balls.
Give us moments before they remove them.
I just wait. Bonus round.
I want that mega jackpot.
All right.
Yoshi, get in there.
I got another bonus round.
Yay. Yay. I think I did it.
That was fun.
That required no skill at all.
I just watched. Perfect game.
All right. There's another room over here.
I think there's a couple more games that we have not seen.
Otto. Oh, it's called Octo Swirl.
How does this one work?
Ah, right. I always hated these.
He's always felt so particular.
And I'll take 300 tickets, though.
All right. One more.
A jackpot is going to be really hard to hit.
2000. Pretty good.
Oh, there's a Halloween one over here.
Pumpkin pusher.
Ah, here it is.
Here it is.
This is probably the most popular thing in any arcade.
All right.
So the whole thing with this, you have to collect these pumpkin balls.
I've never heard of this one.
There are different things in different arcades.
There's a lot of different variety here.
I mean, I don't really go to the arcade that frequently,
but every time I've gone to the arcade, which is probably two or three times
in the last year or two, these were occupied.
All of them. These were all occupied.
What I get.
OK, I need to get I want another pumpkin.
All right. I want I need to get at least a few of those in there.
It's all about just spamming.
It looks like there's skill here, but it's just just throw dice in the air.
You can guide it a little. Not really.
All right. There's another one.
I think when you get to a few more, it should be the bonus of the pumpkin.
Yeah. You want to try to get in the middle there.
You can because that puts another pumpkin ball in.
Or if you do that, it just shoots other little balls in.
What's the what is it? Yellow.
Can't read. What is this going to do?
Oh, OK. How's my skin doing?
It's a it's very hydrated.
It's very healthy. All stuck.
All right. Here we go. Here comes one.
This is the stuck one. All right.
Push it down. Let's go.
I'll take another yellow.
Oh, it's OK.
All right. Get it down there.
I have two more credits.
All right.
Oh, that's all right.
I keep going.
What do you think? Should I just try to get as many of these as I can?
Yeah, we got to get the bonus. We have to.
I got to get the mega jackpot.
I got to get more orange balls.
So just wait till they are in the middle.
That's made the most sense.
You should do one more AC boss before bed.
That was a good idea.
Do you understand how long I was biting my tongue,
desperately wanting to just scream about the game?
And I knew that I was up against that bet.
So that kept me that kept my cool for a long time.
We should do that every single time
because that that keeps me honest.
Try it again with the mech overlay.
You want to put the mech overlay on top of the mech overlay
or was it the mega jackpot?
What did I say?
Has any human beaten this game yet?
And here's the thing I know that people have.
Look at this.
What's going on here? Look at this.
Oh, something's happening.
Did I do it?
It's pumpkin time.
Come on. Go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go.
That's two balls and then a three going in.
All right. This is that was cool.
You broke the machine.
All right. Look at the yellow.
Yellow is 200.
Now what? Just fill them all up.
What happens if I get yellow again?
Oh, I got it. OK.
It was 250.
So if you fill one all the way to the top.
Oh, it's orange is the one I want.
We got a pumpkin party, though.
Hey, guys, we've got a pumpkin party.
Nobody even came to my birthday party.
I like this one. This one's fun.
You always go to 5000 every time.
All right. We're going to do 5000 three times in a row.
This is kid roulette. It really is.
I had one of these in a local arcade.
And I'm telling you right now,
I would just sit there and it'd be like, oh, come on, come on.
It's going to be green this time.
I may as well have had a cigar in my mouth just sitting there.
No, no, no. Everybody's got to go blue
or it's going to fuck it up for everybody here.
Everybody go blue.
Actually, I think in the old ones you could pick every color if you wanted to.
It just was a credit.
So you could effectively do every single one.
And I think just light up the whole thing.
Little green.
It had a similar soundtrack to this, too.
There it is. Oh, crap for kids.
Just have white come up once.
Remember, if you don't give us a baby green character, we will riot.
I mean, but you want a baby green.
Oh, OK. I feel like that's the movie deal that I got.
And I hate it.
No, we don't want you to be Mr.
Greens. We want you to be Mr.
Greens as a six year old.
Oh, OK. OK, I guess.
No, we don't want Bugleberry.
We want Bugleberry in college.
Oh, OK.
I don't really want to.
That sounds way better.
Oh, Bugleberry's backstory.
All right. I'm I'm walking.
Chat gets to press a button as a treat.
All right. Which one?
Which one you want to press?
Red, green, blue, yellow or white?
Which one? Better call Bugleberry.
How's it looking?
You're all saying white.
So it's I pressed yellow and I didn't mean to do that.
I clicked back in the window.
So hopefully it's not white.
If it is, I'm going to leave.
It's going to be sad.
All right. We all lose. So who cares?
All right. One more white for chat.
And then we're going to play the other game.
What did I say earlier? Cut the crap.
Oh, this one's fun, too.
I love this one.
Thousand. All right.
Can I? This is free.
Thousand tickets.
All right. I'm going to get 10,000 tickets next to me earlier.
The bonus is random.
That's weird. 1392.
Shit. You got to be.
I got to be more impressive than this.
Ah, where's Dizzy Bird?
I will play at least 30 games of Dizzy Bird before I leave.
All right. I promise I will play at least 40 games of Dizzy Bird
before I am done with the arcade.
That's a realistic number.
And that's one that I know I can hit.
Another 1400.
Dude, what does your stream title mean half the time?
I don't know, because I make a stream title
and then I have that window is over here and it's closed off.
And then my moderators take turns.
You're rating me in my title.
So I have no idea what it says right now.
What does it say now?
What does it say?
It's an automatic coin pusher game.
Pocket change at 50 percent.
Pocket change at 30 percent.
No tickets remaining.
I'm sorry, Raven.
Who's Raven?
Is that from Armored Core?
Oh, it's one of the Armored Core characters.
It's you.
Yeah, but it's me.
It's like you didn't even play Armored Core.
I you just saw me beat the hottest boss in the game.
Somebody else was playing.
Hey, you got what you wanted out of that.
You got at least three or four.
And then I complained about From Software for like 15 straight minutes.
You got what you wanted.
Actually, no, I didn't.
I didn't complain about From Software.
I don't think I complained very much at all.
Did I complain? Not really.
I don't think it was a complaint.
Is he talking to us?
No, no. The person behind you.
All right. One more.
And I'm going to do that.
What's it called? One more.
There we go. All right.
Now I can leave.
Probably about 10K, right?
Give the controller back to your wife.
She's way better at video games than you and has plus two RIS.
That's like five, six thousand.
Plus two RIS.
I didn't even see this thing.
What is this? I'm playing it.
Wait, there's other stuff here.
There's a ton of other shit here.
It's not time to go to Dizzy Bird yet.
I hate this one, but I'll play it.
I had it. I had it.
If it didn't freeze, if it didn't freeze, I had it freeze.
Messed it up.
I think that's when you walk away from this one.
Oh, was it basketball in the original game?
I don't remember that.
Let's do it.
Everybody knows the only real way to play this game is you
and two other friends just pick up all of them at the same time.
And then everybody just kind of drops them over there at the same time.
I got the bonus round, though.
That's hard. Six thousand tickets.
No, that's a this is one to play.
And then you're done. You don't play it again.
This one has a similar mindset to.
I wonder how does this work?
Oh, you have to hit the right.
I forgot about the hell.
I got the exact same score.
Quagmire.
I wish the trajectory on this one.
That was pretty good.
I think you play against another player.
All right, let's kick this person's ass.
I'm kidding. I'm kidding.
Let's play. Let's play.
Oh, don't laugh at that.
Oh, it's not going to tell you're trying really hard because I am, too.
Get it. Why did you get so good all of a sudden?
Dude, how are you still home?
I still in this.
What is going on?
We're going to hit the enrage timer and the air is going to turn off.
OK, good.
I think you can actually hit that, by the way.
Can't you tune the game to make it so so people don't just sit around,
just hit it back and forth all day?
Oh, that's right. You can buy scratch tickets.
I'll do a little. I'll do a few scratch tickets.
Why not? After we do this.
OK, that was good.
Oh, my God.
Do not come back and beat me.
What do you play?
This person got bored.
Is it to five or to seven?
Oh, I win.
Nice. 400. That's pretty good.
Have I played this one? Pile?
Does this one work?
Pile. Holy.
That's weird. This is weird.
This thing's very floaty.
OK, always start in the middle.
I got to get something on the left side, slightly on the left edge.
How was I ever supposed to do that?
Do it again. I get it now.
This feels like a jump scare is going to pop out any second.
All right. Now I get it.
I want to get at least.
Oh, that's kind of bad.
Hmm. It's OK.
OK, this last two were rough, but I'm good.
Hmm. A little too much on the left side.
Oh, that's bad.
I guess way too hard.
I guess too hard.
Well, I got all these saying spaghetti and garlic bread.
Oh, that sounds amazing.
Yeah, that sounds that that sounds like a great dinner.
Is that what we're doing?
I just I just beat it.
I'm done. Get that bonus right in the middle.
Do it. Do it.
Oh, what just happened?
Right in the middle.
Yeah, that's not a small amount of tickets.
That's actually really good.
All right. Snowball battle.
Get ready.
Oh, it's space invaders.
I get me out of this.
This always happens at any arcade I've ever gone to that has this cabinet.
Everybody points at it and everybody does like the
everybody has their mouth open pointing at space invaders.
One person puts a coin in to play it.
They die one time and walk away from the machine
because they don't want to play it a second time.
You realize, oh, I went, I've got I got two more lives.
Oh, anybody want to jump in?
It's like, no, not really.
All right, well, dude, I played the punch out arcade machine
and I was so bad at it.
I was I told I told everybody, oh, you guys, I'm so good to punch out.
Punch out my game.
The arcade version is so hard.
It's so much harder.
I just look like a total dickhead because I see the punch out arcade machine.
I'm going, that's awesome.
I punch out for NES, punch out for Super Nintendo, punch out for the Wii.
These are my games. I love them.
I could right now open up the Super Nintendo punch out
and not get hit one time, at least through all the three major circuits.
I could do it right now.
You know how I know that?
Because I did it like four days ago on the couch.
Do it right now.
That's not. No, I just know I can prove it.
Maybe I'll prove it next time I stream.
Maybe not. OK, maybe not.
No damage, but I won't I won't be knocked down once.
In the first three, like beating the regular game.
The special circuit is very hard.
That's a lot less impressive.
All right. So let me let me let me bait you guys with like a really awesome
potential gamer thing.
Get everybody excited and then change the rules right before it happens
to something that's moderately, slightly, intermediately impressive.
I'll take it. All right.
Am I missing anything that I didn't play?
Because it's time to go to dizzy, dizzy bird.
This game sucks. I hate this one.
In the regular arcade, I hate it, too.
Well, what is anything else in the mall?
This is all new content.
Candy. Can I actually use it?
Oh, you can. Oh, eat them.
Nice. Excuse me, sir.
What are you doing over there?
Fuck up. I'm making my own coin pusher.
Those are some stale jelly beans.
Gooey bears.
Gummy bears are not supposed to crunch.
Oh, here we go. Jawbreakers.
Oh, that hurts to hear.
That hurts to think about somebody doing that.
I buy new shoes.
What do you got? I play.
I can't shoot into the hoop.
Yes, I can.
You ignored the spiral game.
Oh, you mean this one over here?
I did. You're right.
Oh, first try.
I just beat it.
I don't do I need to play it again?
Not really.
It's another one, right?
You know what? I want to I want to play mini golf.
Is there a good mini golf game?
No bells and whistles. No bullshit.
Just mini golf.
There's a few.
I just want to play a standard mini golf course.
Golf it. Golf with friends.
I feel like I'm thinking back in the Super Nintendo N64 days.
Scratch tickets.
Oh, yeah. Let's go.
All right. I have.
All right. We're going to get a few of these.
And then we're taking this to Dizzy Bird.
Did I just buy? Where are they?
I got scammed.
No, I didn't. Let's scratch these.
And then I'm going to play 40 games of Dizzy Bird.
All right. Here we go.
Reveal three symbols.
Match three to win the fish.
All right. If I get one more four, it's 25, which I don't want.
I got my money back. Whatever.
All right. OK.
Oh, give me another car.
No, don't give me one.
Stop before it's too late.
I don't have any money left, so it is too late.
I'll take my money back here.
Give me another four.
Oh, no.
There better not be a one right here.
Wait, anything else in the mall?
Islandville Cinema.
I wonder if you can watch movies eventually.
That'd be kind of fun.
Credit union.
Wasn't there a food court or something?
How much is this?
All right. Make my wish.
Aim ramp at Zolbot's mouth.
Press red button to drop coin.
I got it.
Oh, is this? Did I win?
Wait, what did I just do?
What did you wish for?
I don't know. Nothing.
OK, I'll get it right this time.
All right. Here's my wish.
I have to hold it while I make my wish.
What does it say in the back?
Your wish is granted to.
Oh, nice.
I got a pirate pizza.
Just give me that one.
Let me make it. I'll do it.
Get out of the way.
How do I buy a pizza?
I want to buy one.
Oh, here we go. Seven bucks.
Didn't I sit here a few years ago and buy like 100 of these?
Is it done?
I just dumped that on myself.
Eat an entire pizza.
Ooh, tuna.
Ooh, tuna sandwich.
That sounds great.
Oh, man, that sounds amazing right now.
All right. Let's see.
I want a tuna sandwich.
And I want relish on it.
I want going to cook these like little plastic thing.
Look at that milk.
Oh, there it is.
I'm very satisfied.
Lemonista 450.
That sounds great.
Fresh squeezed lemonade.
That might be one of the best drinks.
Like when I think of a treat beverage, I think of fresh squeezed lemonade.
For sure. Yeah. Oh, yeah.
Now you can't play Dizzy Bird.
Yes, I can.
Yeah. Watch this. I get it.
All right. So I think that's all the mall.
Did I miss any stores?
We went to the jewelry store.
Wait, what's this? Nothing.
Spunkies.
Whoa, this.
All right. This is cool.
Spunkies.
Yep. Oh, yeah.
Hoverboards.
I have one of these.
I have two of these in real life.
Not the back.
Go to the back.
Light sword.
OK, you want to know what's crazy?
Think about this from here to here.
You are in a different store at Spunkies.
Do you know what I'm saying?
Like, it's crazy that it's just like, oh, yeah, come on in.
Look at all. There's like.
Oh, Luke Skywalker.
Oh, my God. Oh, look, there's a gorilla's T-shirt.
Oh, where is it?
This is a completely different store now.
This is a different store.
And I don't know if I should be in here.
Don't forget the mushroom posters.
That's right.
And there was always right here, right here, right here on a rack right here.
It would be right in front of me.
There'd be a book where a fart is coming out of some guy's ass.
It's just a little book.
And it's like, oh, there's like a smoke fart coming out of a guy's ass.
I don't even know what the product is.
I just know that it's here.
It's literally right here on capacitor, right next to the edible underwear.
Yep. And if you're wondering, this is definitely where.
Do you remember? This is like four years ago when I didn't I get in a fight
with everybody here saying that there was a product where like you put the coin in
and like the guy like shits his pants or something.
Somebody like farts.
It's like a toy.
And people were like, that's not real.
And I was like, yes, it is.
You put a coin. It's like a little bank.
You put a coin in and it's like
the guy like farts.
It's a real product.
And everybody told me, no way, dude, you're out of your mind.
And then people were like, no, it's real.
Actually, it is real.
This was such a weird store.
Yeah. And also make sure you go right here to grab.
They were always in the front of the store posters for movies
that have not been relevant in 10 years.
Well, I swear there's like an Indiana Jones two poster in here
and it's from 1990 old bands that broke up five years ago.
We're in here.
Yeah. Adam Sandler's click is in here.
Exactly. That's correct.
Hot tub time machine.
Yep. This step brothers posters in here.
What a wild store.
What a fucking crazy place that really is.
Spencer's like I can't imagine like being the person
that was responsible for like, oh, what's going to be in the store?
All right. Yeah.
Well, we're going to have Finding Nemo.
Stickers have to be over here.
And then, yeah, just fill up the back with all, you know,
the thing you put your hand on for the electricity.
But also we have to have the edible underwear,
some of the other fucking pornographic material.
Yeah, I think what's that book?
What's that book about all the sex positions?
What's it called?
Yeah, I want that over here.
Put that like 10 feet to the left of the of the silly string.
It was a wild place.
They had the boobie mugs, too.
Don't forget that. Yeah.
Yeah. What what an interesting thought.
No other store I can think of you could leave
with the funny science experiment.
Put your hand on the globe and a sex position book
in the same checkout counter.
They definitely had a thing of fake poop.
I'm sure they did.
Actually, I think I know what you mean. Yeah.
Wow. Memories.
Did I see all the mall?
Let me make sure I didn't miss anything.
How much longer are you going to be streaming for?
Um, probably not much longer.
I'm going to do Dizzy Bird and probably call it there.
Wait, I want to do this.
Oh, I need a dollar to do the thing.
I know where to get money.
No, no, no. Wrong.
I thought that was the arcade. Wrong.
How much longer do you think you're going to be alive?
I'm making it to 100.
I'm going to make it to 100.
They're going to interview me.
I'm going to have like garlic around my neck
and like vials of manuka honey that I swear by.
Where's the money thing?
Where is it?
100. No, I don't.
I don't know if I would.
I don't know if I'd want to be 100.
I think 100 is I think that's it's I don't know if I want to be honored
at 100. I'm not even sure.
I'm trying to think of how my body would be functioning at 100
because I know how it functions now, right now.
I feel like at 100, if I accidentally close my finger in a car door,
my whole body is going to explode into dust.
I just won't exist anymore.
It'll just be like, ah, just completely gone.
That's when you get I don't know when you get to be 100.
It's like that's remarkable.
That's unbelievable.
But that's when I start to see the person talking
and their teeth come out like that's what happens when you get to be 100.
I don't know if I want to do that.
I'm not sure.
I don't really want to experience that at any point.
I don't want to be mid-sentence and be like,
let me just ruin my teeth around and the teeth are just gone out.
I don't know if I don't know if I want that.
I don't know if I want to do that.
Don't buy shit teeth then.
That sounds like something you would actually love doing.
Actually, like, like, I don't know.
I think that is actually kind of funny.
All right.
Now, what do you everybody stop?
The next time that I am able to present, I'm presenting something.
I'm going to have fake teeth and and I'm going to they're going to
oh, they're going to come out.
OK, isn't Dizzy Bird's here somewhere?
Isn't Dizzy Bird here?
Dizzy Bird's in a few places.
Wait, I want to play this guy.
This guy's shit faced.
That's like a crayon.
We've done this before a few times.
Oh, it's in the regular arcade.
Just Larry's, right?
It's some carnival food.
Carnival food is so great.
What is the best food at a carnival?
Fried dough. That's easy.
Wait, that's not true.
No, that's not true.
Oh, I'm really late to this.
Sorry, everybody.
It's nine o'clock at night.
Oh, it's the it's the hot Italian sausages.
You know, the one, you know, you know, the kiosk.
It's that one.
I remember when I was.
Oh, man, this is such a long time ago.
I'm not making it up.
I ate I think I ate four of those in a row.
I had to have been like under.
I was probably like twenty nineteen maybe.
I ate four of those hot Italian sausages and it was such a bad.
It was awful.
And I knew it was.
But I was like, I have to.
This is only how many times do you come to like the carnival?
Not at once.
It was in a it was it was over the course of it was probably
over the course of a couple of hours, actually.
But it was in a row.
Guys, I'm also that person that makes sure there is a dole
whip in my hand for at least two thirds of the time I'm walking around Disneyland.
So I love my carnival food.
I love my theme park food.
Cotton candy is all right.
I think cotton candy.
I'm I kind of like taking a piece of somebody else's cotton candy, but a whole one.
I feel the same way about movie popcorn.
The way I do about cotton candy.
I'll take a handful from somebody else's popcorn,
but I don't want to buy a popcorn.
I don't want to buy my own cotton candy.
I'll have a piece of yours if you'll give it to me.
What about funnel cake?
Fried dough is funnel cake, right?
Or no, it's a wait. It's different.
Funnel cake is the one that it's kind of stringy.
Fried dough is in one piece.
That's right.
I think funnel cake is better than fried dough,
with one very, very important exception.
One piece.
What do you mean? It's in one.
Yeah. All right.
OK, fried dough is funnel cake, but it's one big.
It's like a big piece of bread.
It's like a giant loaf of bread.
Funnel cake is sort of stringy and swirly, right?
There's one part of a piece of fried dough,
the very middle that has the pool of cinnamon and oil.
You get it. It's right to the middle.
It is soaked up cinnamon, sugar and oil in the middle.
And it's it's heaven.
It's heavenly.
And you fill it with sugar.
That see that chat member knows exactly what's going on.
Yes. You make a little a little island in the middle
with cinnamon and sugar.
I can't even see it. Where is it?
Chat member, aka loser.
All right. Actually, time that person out.
All right. Time that person out.
Actually, that person should get a time out.
Wait, hold on.
Aren't you here, too?
You can't say chat member, aka fucking loser.
But you're in the chat.
Come on, man.
We're just hanging out here together.
We're just chilling.
It was in quotes, too.
That's what that was.
Fucking so funny.
Chat member was in quotes.
Hey, is this Baldur's Gate waiting room?
I don't know. You're going to play it.
What if you want to play?
Go for it.
Have you seen one piece on Netflix?
No, I have not.
And I'm sorry, guys.
I I don't have it in me to watch a thousand episodes of television.
I don't have it in me.
I just don't have it in me.
Can you imagine if the live action version was going to have the same
amount of episodes as the anime?
I hope those actors are ready to sign on for the next 30 years.
So it's going to take 30 seasons in a row.
It'll take so long.
It'll take like 70 years to get there.
They'll have to recast the actors five or six different times.
Soap opera one piece.
Yeah, that's it right there. I got it.
I have heard that the Netflix show is good, though.
I've heard, hey, actually, it's pretty good.
Who said that?
Oh, boy. What did I do?
Oh, boy. Oh, I shouldn't have said anything.
Oh, boy. That's it.
If you're a fan, it's OK.
I just don't know.
I don't I don't know if I'll watch it.
Not because I don't care about one piece, but I don't know.
I just what's a TV show that I really want to watch?
It's not one piece.
Bro, it's good. It's good.
People are saying Mob Psycho.
You know what?
I will watch Mob Psycho before I'm 40.
OK, I will watch Mob Psycho
and the Smurfs movie at the same time on different monitors.
Please watch. Oh, that's right.
I do have to watch.
I got a few movies to watch.
What's the best mini food like mini pizza, mini bagels?
That's mini food.
Um, do donut holes count?
That could be it.
Those are probably up there.
Powder donut donut holes or glazed donut donut holes.
Barry's a very good show.
I've seen the first season of Barry.
I just didn't ever turn it back on.
Kind of like what I did with Critical Soul, which I don't know why.
I really liked it.
All right. How many is this?
Did I do it 40 times?
Because it's time to go.
Oh, man.
I said 40, right?
This one, this is the easiest one to get.
It's like right here.
Oh, so close.
That's not going to make it.
Play till you win.
Ah, all right.
This is the one right now.
Here we go. Got it.
I mean, I got it. I got it.
I'm good. I beat it.
I beat it. All right.
Now, holy shit.
There's a lot of tickets here.
Go two in a row.
Oh, almost two in a row.
That was pretty good.
This is a cozy game.
I love this game.
Is there anything else I want to play last second before I'm done?
Damn, this one's a scam.
Yeah. What do they say?
If any of these have like Nintendo switches in them,
it's like your odds of winning are like incredibly horrible, right?
You're looking for the ones that have like the five dollar gift cards in them
because those ones typically are much easier to hit.
They are impossible.
Just buy a Nintendo switch at GameStop.
I've met people that have won these.
They're definitely possible.
Otherwise, nobody would play them.
But it's got to get really lucky that you get in there
when the machine is like, yep, it's time for you to for someone to win.
Although this one might be only skilled.
I don't know. I'm not sure how this one works.
I got stuck in one of these once.
What? I read that really like that was a very normal occurrence.
Apparently you got stuck.
All right. Well, I hope you're right.
I want to ask how, but I kind of don't.
I don't think I even need we don't even need the story.
Yeah, we don't need the story.
Oh, a glow stick.
I give my shit.
Yeah, I read it and weep.
Look at that. I got the ticket.
And I get a slingshot.
All right. Last game is it?
And then I'm going to call the stream.
I'm going to make sure I get another major prize. Let's go.
Thanks for watching, everybody.
This has been Sunday.
Hope you're having a good weekend.
I got a dragon armor correspond.
This is also fun.
I don't know what my plan is next week.
I would just keep an eye on the sauce.
Probably another later in the week stream.
I might I probably will do two streams at the end of the week.
We might double it up.
Maybe play Armored Core on one of those and go from there.
All right. I got to focus.
Go for it.
Yeah, I don't have enough coins.
Can I sell anything?
Can I see anybody?
Anyone want to buy a pair of headphones?
I'm never going to that piece of shit ever again.
All that place does is take your fucking money.
The slots don't even pay out.
Don't even go in there.
It's not even worth it.
I'll see you guys later.
Thanks for watching.
See you guys next week.
Probably like Saturday, Saturday, Sunday.
I'm liking the weekend stuff.
Weekend streams, I weekends are pretty open and it's nice, too.
It's nice to kind of wind down on the weekend and just play and hang out.
I like it a lot.
Expect more like Saturday, Sunday, sometimes Saturday, Sunday, both.
Sometimes maybe just one.
But I'm imagining next weekend I'll probably want to play
pretty a little bit further into Armored Core six than I already did.
That just scared the fuck out of me.
What just happened?
Oh, right.
Hope you had a good time.
I had a good time.
I'm glad that I got through the water filter release partially.
Take care of yourselves.
Have a good rest of your weekend.
I know it's pretty much over, but see you next week.
Probably Saturday or Sunday or maybe both.
I would say at least Saturday.
Take care of yourselves and call your mother.
What about Darken Darker?
I'm going to do some serious looking into Darken Darker
because I keep getting the urge to play it.
I just want to play it.
Yeah, you keep the sus pretty vague.
Just say this coming weekend.
I also want to play browser games.
I just want to do.
Yeah, we'll do two streams this coming weekend.
That makes sense to me.
At the very least, we'll do it.
We'll just put the sus for Saturday.
Maybe. Hmm.
Just say at the end of the week, pick one.
I want to make sure I'm not thinking, overthinking this.
They might have something going on on Saturday.
But let's see.
What did I just click on?
Yeah, definitely at the end of the week, though.
See you guys later. See you soon.
Actually working on a lot of really, really fun stuff for Offbrand.
I'm imagining that very soon here, be able to kind of maybe share
some of that stuff, because I've been kind of supplementally involved
in a lot of Offbrand's stuff that you've seen, but not really like in it,
in it like I'm going, I'm going for it.
Because when I joined the company,
you know, obviously there was stuff that there was going on
that I wasn't really on yet.
But supplementally, you've seen a couple of shows
that I had some stuff to do with, but not really.
The stuff I'm working on now, that is I'm very, very involved in.
So I'm looking forward to it.
Let's see how it plays out.
What's my game of the year for 2023?
Well, 2023 isn't over.
Pizza Tower, Resident Evil 4 Remake.
I've been I've been writing them down.
My throat is so weird lately.
I have been writing them down.
I wrote Dark and Darker on here.
I think right now it's probably a Resident Evil 4 Remake or Pizza Tower.
Although I haven't played Baldur's Gate 3.
I know that's probably going to change my mind.
Although we'll see.
I'm not a huge fan of top down,
more kind of turn based action adventure type games.
But just what I've heard and seen or what you can do in Baldur's Gate 3
and how stuff happens in Baldur's Gate 3.
What about Sorcery?
Sorcery was more of a book to me than a game.
I read Sorcery.
I don't really play Sorcery.
I probably will like it.
It's a lot like Sorcery.
Baldur's Gate 3 has actual porn in it.
OK, whatever.
How about Starfield?
Starfield is on Game Pass right now.
And I have to I've got to tell you the truth, because all I can be.
I want to be truthful.
I opened up Starfield on Game Pass.
I fell asleep within, I want to say, an hour.
Now, that does not necessarily mean I thought that Starfield wasn't a good game.
I may have been very tired.
I was I was very sleepy.
It put him to sleep.
It wasn't a bad experience.
All right.
I got to the point when, OK, you you get off the ship,
you touch that thing and I don't want to spoil anything.
But like you get off the ship, the guy says,
Oh, hey, you must be new here.
Hey, you can sell items over there on the right at that kiosk.
Welcome to the city.
That's the first 10 minutes, dude.
That's New Atlantis. Yeah.
And then I don't OK.
Listen to me.
I like accidentally attacked somebody and I had to I had to redo a whole save file
because I accidentally hit somebody in the face with something.
And then the whole city starts fucking attacking me.
And even after dying, they still come after you.
And I remember Holly was sitting right next to me on the couch.
I'm like, what do I do if I like attack somebody in a city
and the whole city is attacking me now?
And when I die, they all still attack me.
What do I do?
You have to save scum.
Oh, no, the actions of my own cons.
Put away your weapon and let the cops take you.
Maybe you should think harder about your violence.
You can leave the city for 24 hours to calm most people down,
but you'll still have a bounty.
I feel like streaming Starfield would be really fun,
but unbearable for everybody.
I just won't ever get anything done.
I'll just be throwing rocks at people and get arrested and stuff in the game.
And I'll just never get anything done.
People would be so pissed at the way that I would play that game.
I'm also, by the way, I'll tell you, just walking around in Bethesda games
and just picking up all the cups and newspapers and paperclips on every table.
I'm sick of doing that.
I don't I don't want to do that anymore.
And then you can't you can't move.
And I know it's like, don't then don't do it. Impossible.
When there's so many things highlighted in the room,
I'm going to pick up some of them in Skyrim and Oblivion.
Dude, I would just walk into the weapons merchant place
and just take every single thing from the counter
and just never come back to that town ever again.
I can't play these games.
Hoarder. It's the same thing in Baldur's Gate three.
Oh, no, you're too evil to play them.
Now, I play the game as a good character.
Anytime you guys see me play games like RPGs, I try to make good decisions,
but I do bad things like I will just throw the rock at the fucking wall.
I will just punch the guy in the face.
But I'm going to divert the laser from hitting Earth.
Do you know I'm saying I will go in the back and take every single item
from the armor merchant,
and then I'm going to go help the old lady walk across the street outside.
What is that chaotic good?
I don't know. Is it that's chaotic neutral?
I don't know.
Ball of yarn with a knife.
Oh, the Joker. That's right.
It's called balancing karma.
I usually do the good storyline, but in the good storyline,
I don't roundhouse kick somebody in the head at some point.
Chaotic. Good. That's chaotic.
Neutral. Dear God, dot, dot, dot.
Sometimes you just got to do it.
Sometimes you just have to roundhouse kick somebody.
Yeah. Chaotic. Stupid.
Please play Breath of the Wild again.
All right. OK, OK, OK.
Oh, here's what's going to happen.
You you guys have to be good, though.
You have to be good on.
You have to be good because I haven't played Breath of the Wild months.
So I it's I'm going to be like the control.
Oh, yeah, I can't believe you have to press X to jump.
But I have to press Y to jump.
This game's stupid.
Just just bear with my bullshit for a little bit.
Just just be like, oh, yeah, yeah, yeah, I know it's stupid.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, it's fine.
Just play it and I'll play it this weekend.
What do you want to play?
I want to finish it.
I can't just not that I this one guardian left and Ganon.
That's it.
I'm almost at the end of the game.
I have to beat Breath of the Wild.
I have to at least complete that game.
I can't just let it sit there at two thirds completion.
There's no I can't do that.
Not going to happen.
Final Fantasy 16.
I actually played Final Fantasy 16 yesterday, so I have played it.
I really do like it.
I have a feeling, depending on how I feel about that game
in a few months, if I actually get to the end, that could be up there pretty high.
I might just turn that on, too, and just stream it.
All right. So here's the deal.
We're going to play Breath of the Wild, Armored Core six,
and maybe a little bit of I'm not going to play Final Fantasy 16 this weekend.
I want like an open your mouth and just sit there game.
You know, I mean, Armored Core six is intense.
Breath of the Wild is intense.
I want to I want just to open my mouth, just mouth open,
just eyes completely glazed over, just punch out.
Maybe that's not a bad idea.
Hey, that's a good idea. Yeah. All right.
All right. That's the plan.
The plan for this weekend is we're going to do Breath of the Wild
super punch out, not getting hit once.
Well, not getting downed once.
And then maybe some Armored Core.
I think that's a good plan this coming weekend.
And also, I'm going to try to beat Breath of the Wild this weekend.
So wherever we are in the game, I'm going to try to finish it up.
We will see the end.
Sure, sure, sure, surely, surely.
I'll see you guys later.
Take care of yourself. Thanks for watching.
And we'll we'll figure it out this weekend.
We'll get it all figured out this weekend.
I think that's a fairly good plan.
Good night. Goodbye.
Take care of yourselves. See you soon. Bye bye.