I wasn't late. I wasn't late. I started it at two o'clock, sir. It was two two p.m. And
42 seconds or something. He said on the dot right at two two zero zero. It was gonna start
I didn't count any seconds after that so somebody wrote losing interest. Yeah, I already lost interest in this shit
I don't care anymore
No more quizzes, dude. I've seen enough
Where's chubby bunny for chubby bunny? Hmm interesting concept for a an activity
I will do chubby bunny today. Yes, it's gonna happen today. That's right. But when is it going to happen?
We're gonna pull some American reality TV on you guys. I'm gonna talk about the thing that you care about
25 times over the next few hours and coming up soon
Chubby bunny with germa and it shows me in like this weird cube
There's a glass around it for some reason and there's cameras all over this one like bird's-eye camera and I'm sitting there like
Shit after the break and then the break comes back and they don't go to me doing chubby bunny
They do something else entirely but like two more hours
They do three or four more commercial breaks in that time where they show me with goggles on inside the cage inside of the glass box
Here he comes and don't forget chubby bunny coming up with germa. I look into the camera. I'm like, yo, hey you oh
And then it happens right before the credits roll and it sucks
Prepare yourself. It's a way to keep you here till I'm done. That's the g4. I
Don't remember
But stalling this this whole stream is a stall. Don't you understand? I have 30 plus personality quizzes and
Tests and then we're gonna play a family feud online video game
And we have by the way you get to participate in what's that? Oh, can you believe that?
phylactery lich fifty dollars from phylactery
Thanks for the five thousand bits phylactery. It's huge amount of money. Put the marshmallows in your mouth before we fucking lose it
You'll see it. Hey, it's going to happen before the stream turns off
I guarantee it and everybody thinks I'm gonna like die or something. I'm not gonna look
Let me just be very very clear I am NOT going to do chubby bunny until I die
I know a lot of people are saying dude, don't be careful. I don't care about getting the world record at chubby bunny
I don't care. It's a stupid activity. No one should ever fucking do it under any circumstance ever
I'm just gonna do it. I'm gonna do it for the photo
You know, I'll get some in there and be like
And then it all comes out no one has done this in five years
Yeah, and no one should ever do it full disclaimer. Don't do chubby bunny. It's fucking stupid. It's it's not even fun
It sucks. It's not even funny. I just said it and I said it out loud
I said I was gonna do it because it was just a thing that I thought I was never gonna have to do
But here we are
Why are you doing it then because I have to I made a promise on the Mafia remake stream
That if I took damage on that one mission that I was gonna have to do it
So I'm just taking it for the fucking photo. Okay, but chug stream
I'm so glad that person got instantly tied up
Hey adventure MF Dan. Thanks for the five subbed in borderlines five subs. Thanks both of you guys
Stream is not in 144p. It almost was I almost didn't change it
All right, without further ado, let's go
It's not 144p it better not be did the settings not save I hope they did
No, they did at 720p 60. Okay. Good. I was about to say that's not good. All right, hold on. I'm going
Let me to supply some lip balm
Just go just go just go it's been five minutes man
Stalling stalling. I'm naughty. I'm just hanging out for a sec on my intro screen
We've gone over this before we talked about this a thousand times
How many streamers do you know that they're starting soon screen is like 40 minutes when I turn that on um, I'm here in the seat
I'm ready to stall
Actively stall not passively stall you see I'm an active staller
Not a passive staller would be no screen that just dislike that for 20 minutes when I get you here
I actively do this you're doing that right now. No, I'm actively here
I'm not I'm not passively stalling you
Idiot streamer laughing my ass off. That's a joke from oh, we got a OSTs, right?
I got a cool OST for us to listen to this is called legendary video game music
That's the playlist and I have 30 plus quizzes. We're gonna start right now. How do we transition over there?
Can you see it? I mean wait, I have to hide this I don't want anyone to know what I'm doing
And hide the tabs first
Always job. We start the music. Oh, no, he showed his stream key. Oh
No, it was right on the twitch dashboard
He's handsome today
I'm just gonna get this out of the way
I'm gonna get this out of the way because I know I'm gonna I'm gonna drink out of this can
And it's gonna piss off a ton of people. I gotta get this out of the way
I have no affiliation with whatever this is I have no feel it
I just know that I'm gonna take a sip out of it and somebody's gonna say you'll fuck you
Okay, I know look I get it. It was on sale. Okay, it was on sale. This is why I don't put face cam on
I don't videos delayed. What?
I got a couple
I've never I've this like this first time I've ever had this this is not sponsored for I've just bought it
I knew people were gonna be pissed about this
Look, you're some of your favorite streamers drink fireball for money. I drink White Claw for free
You get it. It's disgusting. I didn't say that you did
Alright, let's do it. We're gonna do a review right now. This is the mango one
It's probably because why I was on sale probably not a high top seller
I kind of tastes like the air inside of an airplane. I think it's like airplane air
like texture it tastes like
Okay, you know when you when you when you have a Jolly Rancher and you get to the very end of the Jolly Rancher
And it's finally gone
Okay an hour later
Like the the spit and taste inside of your mouth if you have not had any more food after that that like you're like
Owned flavoring inside your mouth. You're like you're like coating. It's like that. It's not bad. It's only two
I can't like what I am I gonna have ten of these
This is the first time I've drank alcohol like seven months. No, this is the third time
I've drank alcohol and since February where the fuck am I going? I ain't going anywhere. Where do I have to go?
I'm not going anywhere. I can't have I can't have a fucking
airplane air quality
Drink I can't have one in seven months, you know, all right, like I kind of feel like all right
So this feels like I should have like I contact somebody. Hey
There it is
German that a five's drink of choice. It's not this it's not this
But he'll drink it if he had if he wants to if he thinks it's pretty it's okay
It's pretty good. I don't I think it's okay. I think it's okay. Don't drink it. All right
We're gonna start with my mental age. This is the these are all there's like we gotta go. There's like 40 of these
Thank you, Nidhogg for the five community subs. I had to get that out of the way
I know people are gonna freak the fuck out
Like if I didn't say anything about this and you saw that lettering you'd be like fuck this guy
Now I give you like a 15 minute excuse as to why I'm drinking in the first place. You have one. Okay, let's start
This determines how old I am mentally I guess okay my question one of 20
The whole page is an ad. Okay, Twitter is
Confusing get that book. I don't get that out of here. Oh the music that's better. Okay, Twitter is confusing essential pointless
Annoying it wakes me up in the morning. It's fucking pointless. You find an old shirt in the wardrobe you
Can't believe you ever wore that and throw it up you keep it for decorating you consider giving it to charity
You put it on you wonder how you ever managed to fit in it. Well, what's a wardrobe give charity?
I would have given it to charity well before this
Anytime I get new clothes. I usually do it like a charity thing. It's like, okay. What do I wear?
Do I wear that? I don't charity the don't wear pie go pile goes charity. Sure. You're planning a house party you
Bring the white claw
Think about telling your neighbors. Make sure you got enough chairs
Find out where the cheapest vodka is plan which games to play
I would not invite my neighbors to a party. That's that's mental age of like 80
Nobody talks to their neighbors anymore back in like the day. It was always like oh you need some sugar
Hey, it's me Dave from right next door. I'm knocking on your fucking door. Hey, can I have stuff that doesn't happen anymore?
I would not invite a neighbor to a party. In fact, if my neighbor knocked on my door, I'd be like it get away from me
I don't know who you are. Believe me alone. And then I would
Slam the big slider shut you're not getting into Oz
What's the question? I would make sure I had a no, that's gross
You're gonna serve the gross shit to your friends the cheap shit to your friends. I've got a better idea
You should serve them high quality red wine like a mile like a mile back
Not this you drink this in your house. Nobody knows you're there
I would make sure I had enough chairs people to sit down baseball caps look better forwards
I like where I don't like wearing the cap backwards kind of hurts my head. It's hot. You want an ice cream you buy
It's hot. You want an ice cream you buy a Magnum
I would you buy a Magnum if you wanted to have an ice cream
What I don't how does this game work? I would buy a cone with a chocolate flake
These feel like AI is this AI generated? I buy a chocolate ice cream. I don't know whatever the fuck that is
McDonald's is a good place to meet. Oh, I fucking am mad about this
Righty then
That's the only thing I can think of when I hear this song a sprinter or two
I can never enjoy this halo theme song. Okay, a good place to meet McDonald's is okay for a quick snack
Yeah, it's not disgusting. Please the current prime minister president looks too young
No
Okay
They're all old. They're all these he's like 75. He's old. He's not even a prime minister
This is a UK question. You think a you think a pension plan is
Not what you thought it would be important or something worth considering something for later
I feel like these are all the same answer. I feel like that's like something to consider
Life is fun
Sure, it sure is you get passed on the motorway by a Ferrari like
How fast you think sweet I bet that driver is a wanker they'll not get there any quicker
Where's Avenger, how come Avengers not on here?
Mr. Green, oh you revealed it. Okay, you have forgotten where you put your keys. This happens all the time
Hey, let me distract you with a fucking way to bring you all together
Hey, let me let me bring you all together, right? Oh, it just said like conservative
It said liberal fucking Republican Democrat. Let me bring you all together. God. I love this shit so much. I love it
Oh, what do you think about that guys collectively?
Get out of here. This is my favorite drink
That's not gonna unite all the people against me. This is pretty this is this is banging
All right, you forgot where you put your keys
Maybe once in the last year. I lose them all the twice already today
I lose my shit all the time. It's just a free ad stream
right now you if you if you're on the stream right now and you're
Like the guy that's responsible for this ad you're going like yes. I didn't have to do fucking shit for this
You finish your meal in a restaurant you
Make sure you go to the toilet before you leave. That's weird or to coffee sometimes empty the tray into the bin
Which is like what do you mean? What rest? Where are we?
Finish your meal in a restaurant
Are we had oh it are we out like a fucking in-and-out or are we at a fine dining restaurant?
Imagine like dumping your tray at like a fine dining establishment
Ask if the tip is included
Excuse me. Excuse me. Yeah, you guys do cassoony included. I don't feel like adding any more. So actually you know what?
Sometimes I wish they would they would just do that
Like I wish like the waiter or waitress when you were done at your meal
They would walk up and say hey, thank you for for eating here
Is it okay for us to put a 20% gratuity on top like and that's it and you can leave
Yeah
Sure, do that. I don't want to sit there and do math
Sir, how did you like the the way? Did you like the service?
Did I think it was it was very you very intensive you very seem to be pretty smart
You were very back-and-forth filled all the waters quickly is 25% are okay
Yeah
But what if they what if you don't think so?
I guess that kind of puts you on the spot
You have 30 quizzes
Yeah, what do you think I'm gonna be here for an hour?
We're gonna be for like at least three to five hours
What I can't hang out and talk about White Claw for like 20 minutes. I'm not doing a political compass on stream
No, I would rather
How would you like I'd rather electrocute myself like like up to 200 volts like
Like in the chair then do a put it without kill you I don't think so
He's gonna give himself the chair on stream. How much is too much 200 is too much. Okay. Anyways, I
Would I order coffee after you know, I'll get a cappuccino or so. The iPad is cool. I love my iPad
I use it all the time. I lie in bed. I play Hearthstone battlegrounds, by the way
I've become in the top ten ten times. I've come to the top four a hundred times
I played like I played probably 200 hours of battlegrounds. You guys don't even know that's like my game right now
Well, this is a good one
Dire Straits were air guitar heaven who cheesy not like today's musicians. They could actually play actually don't know who this is
How do I not know who this is? It's weird. I really I don't know. I really don't I like if you presented to me a song
I'd probably like all right, right
Birthdays are a time to meet the family a time to get wasted a time for presence something to ignore right? I'm 35
I don't care
Wake me up when I'm 50
The best way to become rich is to win the lottery to work hard to become a footballer get lucky
It's all about getting struck by lightning five times. What's the matter? I tell hold on cam going off dog wants to leave
No pants
See this guy this guy German on eight fives. Okay, so you see someone fall over in the street you laugh
Run over make sure they're okay. Thank the heavens. It wasn't you shake your head and think
Muppet how far away am I?
Okay, am I am I more than a hundred feet away?
Because it would be be like God. Thank God. That wasn't me. Am I within like 25 feet like it's within 25 feet
Okay, I'd probably be like hey you good. Okay, the best thing on TV is the big bang theory
Nope, the Simpsons family guy. Nope. Love Island expected. No nature documentaries. No, there's nothing on TV. That's any good besides the boys
Check that out if I were you
Okay, Miley Cyrus is like so over I
Don't know
Miley Cyrus is not really did what was last album? I haven't heard. I haven't really heard Miley Cyrus in a while
2015 right
Probably like yeah, it's not
Probably moving on to do other things
like hey
24 this highly accurate age test has looked at your answers and evaluated that you mental age is 24
The test looks at your answer to the questions in relation to your attitude towards social and financial situations
These were just like mean questions
It's quite possible that you will not be happy with your age test result of your younger
You probably don't want to have an age that makes you look older
If you are older than you don't want to have a mental age of a youngster
Such unfortunately is life you have to roll with the person you are and accept your personality
Some interesting stats for those that are interested in these things
68% of people that take this test have a mental age of less than 30
This might be that 68% of people that take the test are less than 30, but it's very high age average here at MMA
We think it's more likely that people have a youthful attitude in life, but that's not jump child
Okay, if you can like if you can order drinks at a bar
Three times over you that's that's three times over you can order drinks at a bar
Yeah, that means like 21 22 23 24. I don't matter no more
You just do what you just hang out people get grumpier as they get older
Kind of kind of all right. That's my mental age is 24. Okay, cool. What's the next one?
All right
This I this is like a test to see if I have like a color imbalance or something in my brain
All right, this is the color challenge. I get the first and last color chips are fixed
Okay, drag and drop the colors in each row to arrange them by hue color complete all four color tests my color IQ
All right, sure. So I just in shade I could do this
I pretty got a pretty pretty good eye. We're going pink to orange
Nobody say anything yet. I haven't done it yet
Negative IQ
We're going pink to orange. That's not that's green. I already took the Myers-Briggs personality test
I got ENFP like ten years ago. I did it on stream too, didn't I? All right. I'm not done. No, that's not right
I think that's it. Do it. All right, that one's good. So we're going green to blue. This is really not this is not hard
Why is this so hard? But people can't do what is this difficult? This is met bad monitor
Do I have a shitty monitor actually gets a little harder on this next one? All right. Wait, wait, wait, wait
That's close. But wait, this one's kind of freaking me out. I don't like this one. Is this that's wrong, isn't it?
I got it. That's right. No, it's not. All right, that one's correct. This is blue to purple
All right, we're gonna go shit because the ones on the left or right are fixed
I can't move them eyes of a 24 year old the white balance of my cameras. We're gonna fucked up. Okay, that's the real
That's the real color imbalance here. Hold on. Okay there you look pink
Let me just hold my face up there. Come on, bro. I'm hold on. All right, that's this is close enough
I don't even care if I get this wrong. I don't care what I can't I can't put like good colored cubes together
Who cares? I can do this some other time. No, it's gonna be this would be accurate
All right purple back here. Do it by go left to right. That's done, right? Yeah, that was easy
All right, this one's gonna be the hard one. Oh, you're giving that much money. Let's get 50 community subs ready dread with the 50 subs
He shit. That's a lot of fucking money Freddy dread a resident billionaire
Gives like three thousand dollars to this for him every few months maniac. Hey, here's to that that's that's huge amount of money
Thank you. All right, let me finish this. I'm almost there
Done why does that look wrong? But it looks wrong though. It's not. All right, I'm done score my test to
Okay, that scared me. I thought that was very bad
Lower score is better with zero being a perfect score the circle graph displays the regions of the color spectrum where your hue
Discrimination is low. What does that mean? I can't differentiate like blues
Means I suck at blue. So what's the height? What's the high end there compare age?
That score for your gender is nine nine nine nine what score worst score a hundred and six what somebody just put it
How do I read this? I don't know how to read that. I don't know what this data is telling me act
Okay, that's my color hue
70 IQ don't worry. All right next I
Was told to do these this is a human benchmarking
All right, let's do this one. I don't know what this means classic coming up
Are you smarter than a chimpanzee click the squares in order according to their numbers the test will get progressively harder
Am I smarter than a chimpanzee?
The squares in order according to their numbers one, two, three four
Okay, how does this get hot? Why does it get harder?
One. Oh fuck. I didn't know that's what happened. Okay, I got a one two, three four chimpanzees done at it
But chimpanzee lost his round two
Oh
One two three four five six seven eight nine one two three four five one two three four five
One two three four five six seven eight nine one two three four five
Fucking Mario the backer turn. Okay, the Super Mario song is fucking me up get the fuck out of here
All right. What's what's the score then? What did I get save the score? What does that mean?
Percentile what does 17 percentile mean? Does that mean that I'm like really smart?
Only 17 percent of people got as far as I did. That's pretty that's top 17 percent. That's pretty good. What's wrong with that?
Okay, aim trainer hit 30 targets as quickly as you can click the targets above to begin
This is messing with my concentration. It's like showing the colors and stuff. Okay, just shoot the targets. You tell my DPI is wrong
520 milliseconds, let's see. I'm better than I'm better than 70% of all gamers. That's bad. How is that bad?
That's bad. Okay, you know who takes this these quizzes like you guys
Who takes these tests besides like gamers and computer enthusiasts? My parents didn't take this. It's bottom 30%
You're looking at it wrong. You're reading it wrong. That means I'm in the bottom 30 percentile. It's because I don't care about Facebook
Anyways
Hearing oh, I got to turn my volume up for this one. I got good ears
You know, I have such good ears because I never have loud sounds in my head ever. I don't listen to music
I don't go to concerts
I don't talk very loudly unless I'm in an environment where I'm a twitch.tv slash German 985 live streamer
I'm gonna get this one pretty good. Trust me. I have like weird superhuman fucking hearing
I swear to God I'm turning volume up for this one. I'm gonna be in like the top 90%
I swear to God trust me you want to see I'll prove that the gamer work went away. Look at that
There's just a little bit of some scar tissue. It'll heal over nicely. It's gone. Okay. This is what is this?
Okay, I can't have Kingdom Hearts music be playing while I'm taking a hearing test. That's fucking stupid. Okay, here we go
High frequency sound will play click as soon as you hear the sound
But I heard it that hurt so bad. I already heard it. That like hurt my head. I could hear it already
I heard it immediately. I heard no. Okay. I didn't I heard that like immediately. I mean liar. It was like
I just like what am I trying to wait for?
Look, I was even I didn't even understand how the game worked it
I'm better than 60% of all you fucking plebs that one hurt. I don't do that one again typing
Oh, was it pulled up one of the love
at the corner
To open the door in the hope of earning a copper
Needed a little minutes warm up there
okay, but was it elbowed away by another loafer who had rushed up with the same intention a
Fierce quarrel broke out which was increased. How do you spell that? I too by the two guardsmen
I'm reading the actual Kingdom Hearts storyline who took sides with one of the loungers and
By the scissors grinder who was not equally hot upon the other side might as well be who was equally
upon the other side
Fucking words in a minute. Wait, what does that mean? Are you sure I'm reading this wrong that okay?
My head still hurts from the hearing test. Is that odd?
Is that I feel like I just permanently caused problems for myself
That means I'm better than 50% of everybody with the stats. Oh, okay. Hold on
Average user. Oh, dude, I'm fucking look at this. I'm right at the beginning of the curve. I sold at the right time
See the people here
You're not gonna sell you're gonna hold it you're gonna it's gonna get to here and you can be like fuck
Maybe I should get out. I that's the perfect place to be. So what about the other ones?
I don't want to give it away, but I have to nobody nobody look at top. Nobody look at the top
Don't look at the top. Don't look up there. Okay. What about this one earring? Okay typing
Really? I feel like I've that was that was dog shit. Actually, that's very average. I feel like that was terrible
Okay, and what about aim trainer look at I'm in like the top percentile here. All right, what about the chimp test?
That's average. That's all right. All right. Let's do verbal memory. We'll do this one
Smash Brothers, all right
I'm gonna do verbal memory
You will be shown words one at a time if you've seen a word during the test click seen if it's a new word click new
Actually a musical help for this one
If you've seen a word during the test say say sorry already if it's a new word click new
and
Mike oh
That's a hot. That's a trumpet. That's not a guitar. That's good. All right number memory. That's my best one
I got the best verbal memory in the world. I've got so but I have so many vocabulary words up here
he's inhuman and all sudden you see my eyes just go like
And then somebody goes I knew I knew all along he was an alien
And then there's like a thousand reddit posts about how fucking actually I'm like a CIA project or something
Just do that one day. I really should set up like an elaborate thing where like my eyes actually go like me and I just don't
Even mention it
That what a way to game reddit posts. Okay number memory. Let's go the average person can remember for seven numbers at once
Can you do more I would smash brothers? I could probably do way more
How many remember how many numbers can you remember? Here we go?
Two here we go. How many four already smarter than fifth grader nine to five
I'm gonna kill this by the way. I gotta shut the fuck up in a leanback. Just get this shit out of me
No, no, get it off. Get it off. I don't like this one. Okay, I had it. I fucking had it
This is Street Fighter music. It's too upbeat. I need like I need like
What Winston Churchill Winston Churchill what's happening?
It was I
One of a million dollars where was I
What are we oh, yeah, right, okay, this is Call of Duty view what we're we doing all right
I don't like that one. This was all right. All right, so we got uh, I could have got better
I got close visual memory. This is yeah, they bring back crazy memories
All right
I have to stop for a second the second level level two when you're in the ship and you're shooting the little
with the side-scroller
This games that this is great Super Mario land one of the best that's the best Gameboy game ever came out
How's that wrong wrong?
That happens in Super Mario land. All right, let's go
visual memory
Memorize the squares I can take photos of things. Oh
Perfect fucking score. Oh
Fuck you see in a pattern here. I have super human like word and visual memory and my hearing is really good
Well, I don't I don't do numbers very well
Okay, what's last reaction time if I don't get the world record first try I will delete
This into the trash the cap after I'm done using it when the red dot when the red box turns green click as quickly
As you can. Oh
Come on. Just saying that's average
Hold on. I got sorry. All right. Sorry, please stop what? All right. There you go. There's my test. He's jerking off
All right. So why did I do so poorly on the chimpanzee test? That's pretty good. Do it again
No, I you got to live with you what you have. I'm not I I'm
That's the best one. Okay, let's move on. There you go. What is next? I don't what is this?
Wait, mind up. Okay coming up next is can you name all 40 of these animals?
See if I can so many tabs. Okay scroll to start. What is the name of this marine mammal known for its long tooth?
Let's say as an our ball. That's correct. Here come all the ad the LV ads
Which name is given to this long-tailed rodent that is not a hamster that is a as a Jerboa
Yep. Okay. Do you know what the name of this black capped bird? That is a
Arctic turn. Thank you. I'll take three in a row. This animal lives in the Mojave Desert. What is it called? That is a
Painted turtle. I was gonna go with the obvious one. But okay HBO. I don't want half HBO
All right. What venomous animal do you see pictured here?
It's a there's a monster. Yeah, what name is given to this canine that also eats plants. That's jackal
This bears Latin name is Ursus martimimus. But what do we call it? How would you not get polar bear?
Holy shit, that's what those look like
That's an accident aardvark actually looks like this. Why are they such a cartoon character? That's kind of like a nightmare animal
I feel like that's what my dog looks like when I have a dream where there's a dog in it, right?
That's like normal for your dog to look like that in a dream. Oh, yeah, that's my dog
Oh, I already know this it's a lynx. I played Chrono cross
What's name given this foot long amphibian? That is an oxalotl. What name is the right name of this cute but tough critter?
That is not a porcupine
That's not wait a minute. Is it a porcupine? It's a porcupine. Yes, it is
Nemo made this fish famous. What kind of fish is that? That is a clownfish
This bird's call sounds like potato chip. Do you know what kind of bird that is like a crunch potato chip potato chip?
What does that mean?
potato chip
Potato chip. That's an American goldfinch. What is do you tell me? Oh, I looked it out. I looked at chat
No, I didn't I'm looking at you right now. So well, he looked at chat
No, he didn't you would you see my eyes go over here. What's the name of this spotted animal? That is a cheeto. That is I don't
place a poison dart frog
What's the name of this creature that uses jet propulsion to swim that is an octopus wait
That was a trick question. You know what this massive animal is called. That is called a bison. It's not an iguana
But what is it that is a chameleon? I would have thought this song was cool like four years ago. Oh, I got hit man. Oh
This is no no fallout. Okay. Now you got me. It's super Metroid. Don't give me the answer
I already know what anyways, it's a fucking lemur. This is which whale is not Moby Dick. Which kind of whale is it?
That is a sperm whale. Oh
Fuck this is not right
Are you able to identify this animal that is often confused for a bear that is a wolverine
Which name is given to this majestic bird?
bald eagle
It's the name of the snake that can weigh up to 200 pounds anaconda. Are you sly enough to identify this mammal? Oh
Red fox. It's a relative of the trout and the salmon, but can you name it the marlin? Oh, fuck you
I don't want to I don't care about it. Stop. Why have the same like HBO HBO?
How much you add space that HBO pay for today, you know, what pack animal you see that is a kayak
No, it's not. It's a gray wolf. You tricked me a little bit here. They have a bigger face
What is the name of this right? What's the right name of this flying giant? It's not an albatross
Wait albatross is a seagull. What is it? Yes. It is. Yes. It is. It's a seagull
And you correctly choose the name for this marsupial that is an opossum. I feel like I've done 200
How many more are there? I feel like it's not so many
Science calls it the marmota monarchs, but what do we call it? That is a groundhog. This cat is a great swimmer
What name does it have?
Ocelot, what's the name of this tropical bird known for its beauty? That is a bird. I
See him likes to like likes to out smell his opponents which that's a lever
I thought that was just a person
I thought I was gonna be like a cheeky little end like oh this thing likes to go in the water on vacation
I thought that was a like a person's like stomach. That's not a common octopus giant octopus smooth skin octopus
Oh, what is this termite eating very he looks like he just woke up
sloth bear
That's a black bear. No, what what is that? That is pre shower bear
That's how everybody feels like they feel like and they look like in the mirror which name is given to this canine member
Oh, that's not a coyote. That's not a hey, you know, that's a dingo. That's a skunk right? Okay
That's a I was a bird. That is a like I don't say this. That's a mamba. That's a bird. It's not an ostrich
It's an emu and you correctly named this I was gonna get one decided against it not into that right now
Okay, the original Smash Brothers theme though. Yes
This is a dove
78% average score seven. Come on better than the average. That's not bad. That's pretty good
Something wrong with this track that was that that was audio is fucked up on that one. Why was that so weird? Okay
All right, I guess everybody that's that's a c-plus
next
Okay, this is
Statistical which character personality quiz this I guess
Assesses who you are as a fictional character. So I've never taken this before. I don't know how much is in here
I don't know what the I'm not into that either. I'm not into any of the Smash Brothers right now
Both Mario and Luigi not into them. I said this is I'm into this. This is all right. I like this one
All right, so let's go. We're gonna find out what fiction. Oh, this is like a big fictional character test
Use the slider to indicate where you fall on this spectrum deranged or reasonable. I feel like I'm pretty free
I'm a pretty reasonable guy. I'm gonna say like kind of I'm more reasonable than I am deranged
No, I'm not completely deranged
You guys want me to have the Tasmanian devil right off the bat because if you do that
You're the Joker or the Tasmanian devil. I'll go here. I am 40%
reasonable a blue collar or ivory tower, I mean I
Angelic or demonic with demonic definitely
Guys, I think I've like praised Satan like 25 times on this stream even as a joke. It's still there
Outlaw or sheriff I
Play by the rules, but on my own terms like every fucking major character that's come out in the last 40 years
Okay, stinky or fresh. That's a 50-50. It really is
Charming or awkward. I'm gonna leave this up to you guys. That could be 50-50 as well
Sacred hearts to fill the void with my soul
Saying adjectives as stringing them together with words. Oh, I already did this joke before and everybody really got pissed off, right?
I I did that before I'd like did like the I say lyric on every single beat and people got really mad and I put
Like much of adjectives like the song has there. Okay
Adventurers who are stuck in them. I'm stuck in the fucking mud right now. You know what I mean? I'm just like now
Leave me be leave me be I have another season to watch
Creepy or disarming. Oh
What is it? What is that? What's the difference? What do you mean disarming? I'm not creepy. You're creepy and disarming
emotional or logical, uh
I tend to I tend to let my emotions take over
nerd or
Hold on though. I have I have that I have that
200 sub like powerlifting video a
spiritual or skeptical
Frugal or lavish
How lavish though? I'm not that lavish you bought you bought a carnival to do a stream
Yeah, but that that wasn't for me. That was for you. Okay, fine. Uh
Stylish or slovenly he's not wearing pants
Not that much though. I'm not like smelly and stinky and shit here. I sometimes am but not really
Masculine or feminine it's 50-50. I like I power lift. I like throw fucking punches
But I also do face masks
That's a bit that's a bit better gonna deck
That's 50-50 betting on the deck
Sometimes I just want to take a bath and like do like a charcoal like scrub and other days
I want to like scream at a wall
Patrick Bateman. All right creative or conventional. Oh, we are going somewhere over here. I think I'm pretty creative
I I'm if you know if I would creative just proved it
Arcane or mainstream
Total corruption total power
Use slider. Okay feisty or gracious. I'm a little feisty. I think that's accurate. Let me just hear this. Oh
This is the Zelda song everybody loves
There we are. All right the song but like I I paid Blizzard. Oh
I paid Blizzard every month to play their game and I even oh I even forgot that it was installed and I played
paid Blizzard like fucking
60 months straight without even fucking realizing and I did and when I finally realized that I kind of just didn't care and I
Was like, well, I don't really care. Oh
Right here. Well, I'm loyal as fuck unless you cross me
Not anymore name one time that I was a traitor. Why did I cross you? I've never crossed you
I'm loyal streamer. I won't let you down until I do and I'm sure I'll hear about it every day
God, this song is fucking good. That's the penis music. I don't want to formal or intimate
I feel like I'm pretty intimate person. Although I am pretty formal though. That's probably 3268. I'm sorry
I don't want to hear it right now. I'm sorry
I know people gonna be mad that I skipped like sonic music. Oh fuck. I forgot but this is what is this?
What is this?
magical piece of Composery
The speed of sound good places to go gonna follow my rainbow
Guys, don't listen. Keep moving on
This right ahead the way to I don't know the lyrics
Keep on
Yeah, okay. I can't say if I don't know the lyrics
Everyone knows that first part. Nobody knows the rest of this is worse singing. That was actually really fucking good
Okay, if you want it, okay
I understand if like don't sing I hate singing on stream
But try and tell me that that was not even remotely. Okay. Yeah, you fucking dunce that was supposed to be for me
But you know, it's a that I deserve that
Selfish or altruistic. Well, turn it back on. It's a good song
You know, I want I want to just listen to this on repeat and just turn the stream off
No, I'm not what come on
My whole life is just chaos. It really is. I know this is like a meme like my life is chaos
I am chaos power. Like I I'm a good guy, but I'm a bad guy
Everything's crazy. I'm not orderly. I don't follow the rules
I know but seriously like I start my stream 20 minutes late every fucking day. I
Have to I haven't cleaned my fucking office in like a year
I I never can stay in the same place at the same time
I'm constantly moving my fucking hands around touching my like self and looking at myself in the mirror
I don't know to eat every day. I find out what I'm gonna eat every single day 10 minutes before I eat it
There's no order in this life at all
Sober or indulgent pretty indulgent. I don't know about sober. I'm gonna start singing. I'm gonna do it
I'm about to do it if this a rule just raw reaction to hearing that phrase your drunk guys
This is essentially a water with like a quarter of a shot in it
It's like it's drinking one beer if you think I look red and sweaty
Welcome to my life. I'm just a sweaty guy. I just have oil coming out of all my pores
All of them all my pores was oil and shit coming on my knees. I have like watering knees
Why do you think I take so many baths? Okay. I'm indulging you. I mean, I'm pretty mmm. This is 50-50
I could not be left alone if I was left alone for more than a day
I would lose my fucking mind like if I didn't like if I haven't stream or something if I was alone
No, I have to I have to talk to I have to talk to somebody
Have to me and my watery knees. Yeah, now we're doing that one again, but it go we're doing that one again encore, okay
I I thought the mouse was a bug on my other monitor as I was moving it around
Cuz I the previews over here and I thought it was a bug. I was like fucking bugging him
I'm a pretty lenient guy
deep or shallow
Shallow how?
I don't know 50-50 poisonous. I'm from toxic personality. I
Might be pretty poisonous. I don't know. I'm not toxic, but I might be poisonous
Okay, just because somebody is poisonous doesn't mean that they're like a toxic person, right?
Like a tree frog is poisonous, but they're not toxic. They're not like calling you names and shit when you walk by them in the tree
It just you just don't just don't touch them or you're fucking done
Last question. I'm pretty bossy. I won't lie. Okay, who am I?
What character let's do it on the breakdown
Rate some characters. I mean rate characters
my fucking results
No way, no, I'm sorry. I have an 82% match with Tommy was so
Kramer
Wait, where's the where's like this Batman?
Where's like the Riddler?
Where's like the Incredible Hulk?
Johnny from the room
Riddaperry from community Cosmo Kramer from Seinfeld
Michael Scott from the office. Go. I'm not a Michael. I'm a Jim
sing
Timon
George Bluth
Rebecca bunch
Pamela from Archer Jean Belcher Ed from Shaun of the Dead
Johnny chase from entourage
Reynolds
crusty the fucking clown
Where's Captain America? Where's spider-man? Where is Homer Simpson?
How do they know this? Oh
Peter Jason Quill who the fuck is that? Who's Peter Jason Quill? What's what superheroes Peter Jason Quill? Who is he?
That's Star-Lord. I get to be Star-Lord. I get to be Star-Lord. I'm okay with that
crazy eyes
Elaine. All right. I'll take Elaine. I'll take Elaine. I
Art Simpson, I can't believe I got Tommy was so D Reynolds, okay
fine
George Weasley
Come on, where's spider-man?
Spider-man Adam Sandler. Oh, no
Stitch from Lilo and Stitch. Okay, Tracy Jordan
Eric Cartman
Peter Venkman now we're getting down to like that. Yeah, you you could tell people that you were that they were on this list
Goddamnit, Jesse from Pokemon. Wait, Jesse and James
We have offered from the stars above Jesse James
Which one Oh jet Jesse's Jesse James not me off though. All right. Well, all right, Carl Gallagher
So goodman from Breaking Bad
This sucks how true this all is
Right. This like sucks that is I have to look at this and be like I am Tommy was so I'm the guy from the room
All right. Hold on. Wait, why isn't no music Minecraft Pog?
Lisa I got Tony Soprano
Soprano why I'm married Mary
Now now that we get this is a stretch. This is now a stretch
Rex from I care. I agree with Rex hound solo. There you go. I get to be a superhero
Do I might every character from the room? Where's the Joker? Wait, that's the Dark Knight Joker?
That's like the psycho weird Joker. Not like the comedy funny Joker from the cartoon
That's the Joker. That's like scary and nobody likes to be around. He's terrifying the Joker from the cartoon has that goes like
And has like jokes and stuff
Music's too loud. All right. I got you. All right. Yeah now this is every single character that's ever existed
Who am I the least like her and Joe Chang from Harry Potter Rita?
Elizabeth from Obi-Wan Kenobi
What I'm not I'm the least like Jorah Mormont. I find that to be
Ridiculous fuck dip get these I get that. Hold on. I got it. Felice your dragons
It's been a while since I've seen the show, but I think I can still do it. I
Was alright, it's been a while with Captain America. It's a Captain America on here
But that guy this is not these are the characters that I that I might as well just this bullshit
Okay, this is like I put this shit on my resume and it's technically true, but not fucking really at all
Oh, it says here Wow, but where where 13 what 1392?
Wow
Mr. Albertson says here that you matched with Captain America in a personality quiz
Yeah, yeah me and Captain America. We're this fucking weird the same. Yeah, exactly. Oh
Okay, look at this guy
I mean if you had been like Tommy Wiseau or something
I would have like thrown this stack of fucking papers at you and hopefully would have hit you in the face
Yeah, that'd be fucking weird wouldn't it Captain America here only Captain America and spider-man and Tony Stark and
uh
Jim from the office. I want to go back to the top for a second
Yeah, it's you're gonna it's your top five anything over 80% is like you can't you can't
Then add relax. Oh
cuphead
Johnny from the fucking room
Michael Scott man, this is just these the top five people you don't really want to be framers pretty solid
I mean, maybe I move around kind of weird I guess
Anyways, we're gonna move on. That's Tommy Wiseau
I got and even the fact that that why that image you couldn't have like a like a like a like a
Attractive picture of Tommy Wiseau like looking at smiling into the camera
One what's next?
I have to do this I have to get this out of the way cuz this was recommended and I'm just gonna do it
Because like fucking might as well like put myself up. That's like a big target people to throw onions at and tomatoes. There we go
I am
35 years and
one month old my height is
five
That's okay, I'm I am I am 23% taller than 22 men on this planet
top 78%
timing on that music
Sad music sad music sad music
Omega law just out of curiosity. What the fuck? No way if you're six feet tall
You're just you're taller than 80% of the fucking population
No, it didn't update
What so what about five eleven hold on five
Eleven, I feel like that's the thing. This is wrong. Is this accurate?
Whatever. I'm taller than 22% of every male. I feel like this music's mocking me right now. I gotta get rid of it
Every that's better Donkey Kong
Okay, this is what animal are you really just sticking the nail in here run after the other this is not even music
No, that's too too too crazy
crazy
Yeah, sure. I like this. This is good. Okay. How big are you?
I am not petite that if I was petite guys, I'd be like five two
Okay, five seven to five eight is not petite. It's small, but I'm sturdy. I got fucking pants on right?
I mean like this is a sturdy fucking man
Understand like this. I'm a sturdy fucking guy, you know, I'm like a kind of a stack of shit. How aggressive are you?
Jesus Christ, I'm very forceful. Don't mess with me. I'm a little hot-headed. I'm working on it
I take a middle ground and only react aggressively when the situation calls for it
I never go looking for trouble, but I'm no pushover. I think I'm I'm pretty grounded
if I need to I
Did move the mic see how fucking fast that was if I headphones flew out of my ears?
Now imagine you were like coming at me. I'd be right in the neck right in the throat and you'd be like
a
Social
You're that that's what you're gonna show for social is two parents like make it out. I prefer the company
I'm pretty outgoing and I'm comfortable socializing with groups of all so I'm extremely going to function or not
Yeah, I can function anywhere. Give me anywhere. Show me up at your party your birthday
concert crowd
Group small group one one person I can do it. I can do it all how attractive do you think you are?
Okay off stream. I click this one on stream. I click this one to make you not not think I'm a fucking psycho
Then I mean off stream. I would yeah, that's me off on stream. Hey guys
Am I above average sure no, that's like better for some of you that like oh, yeah do that again
Well now I've messed it all up. It took me an hour to get this right there we go
I'm not as creative as a monkey playing a guitar. I don't think I'm not one for writing songs or I don't color within the lines
Oh, you do. I don't I'm definitely an out-of-the-box creature, and I love creating in all of its forms
Same jokes. Well, it's the same test
I'm very compassionate usually put the needs of friends and family above my own
I'm cooperative and willing to help friends in need, but I have my own life, too
Someone has to look up at number one. Call me selfish. No this one. Why is it all monkeys?
How intelligent are you? I have a bit of a nerd streak and I love intellectual challenges. I'd score pretty high on
leprity
That's an L. That's not a J. That's very clear. That's that says that's an L
Louder, why is it getting why is the Minecraft music getting closer?
It's like I'm getting closer motherfucker. I'm coming in here. I'm coming your ears right now. You better be ready for me
It's mad now. You've made me mess up my hairstyle. It looked fine. And now I looked crazed
Okay, that's better. Ah
I'm not the brightest crayon in the box, but I'm not a fool. How athletic are you? Not anymore travel and exploration
How do you feel about traveling? I'm a homebody and enjoy staying close to home. I enjoyed
I don't want to travel everywhere. I'm not one of those people. I don't want to go
Like see the world. I don't know. There's like three places. I really want to see I don't really care
But I'm not I'd like to do things where I am
Right. I love going out and doing shit all the time
Like I love going out in my area
But I don't want to get a like a pack a bag and go to fucking London or something
How impulsive are you where I live in Las Vegas, man? Where do you want me to go? Okay, how impulsive?
I'm always deliberate and cautious. I admit that I'm more impulsive than I should be but it makes for great
I thought that's gonna say great content. All right, what animal?
What's what animal what animal am I? I don't want to open this what's going on? I just heard an animal
I just heard an animal. I just heard like an animal yelling. I think that was Otto. Okay about this page won't even load
Why won't this page load? Did you guys crash the website? You had too many people to do with this
Wait, okay. I got speedrun stop opening this website. Oh
God I got out of the box
Cooperative I
May not be the brightest, but I'm not a fool. I
Like to keep fit. I'm I watch TV. Does that count?
Probably I like to go day trips
Okay, now we're getting to the good shit. All right now, um, I'm impulsive. What's the animal?
Anyone want a gift card? That's bullshit. Which neopet are you being with the animal theme here?
Okay, uh, you boy or girl boy. I say it's your last day in neopia ever. What do you do?
I don't know what any of these are
They Tom Bola neomail all of your friends sell all of your stuff collect your bank interest or cry and wave. Goodbye to your neopets
I probably could this my last day in neopetopia
I'd cry and say bye to my neopets
Pick an item any item beef roulade in laugh grenade. I mean, I don't think do I have to do anything else
I don't have to click anything else when you read the neopian times. Which section do you click first comics bunnies?
Who would you pick first to be on your team?
Dr. Death if you were going to start a guild, where would you put it at the?
The Lenny library if a war were to break out in neopia, which would you be?
Minion of sloth doesn't that make me a sloth. I would be a loyal warrior
What was everybody doing monk? Yes, how often do you visit the grooming parlor? Are you kidding? I practically live there
I go there often
I'll swing by a half price day to get like a bargain to get like a shower or something
I don't know you could be the star of any game. What would it be?
carnival of terror
If you could see any band at the Tyranian concert hall, who would you see?
two gallon hats
You are a pink slob
It's a clown slug
Mood, well, I can't say mood to try to connect with the Millennials and the zoomer crowd. Why not? All right
I'm the pink slob. That's pretty cool. It's a clown slug. No, you can't. Yes, I can I'm allowed to do that
Hey, you know
You know chaotic I am do something crazy. You don't fucking agree with me
I'm not gonna talk for this one. Look at how many fucking ads are on this page
Have you ever get bit by a dog? No, how intimidating are you?
Not really. Are you wild calm or somewhere in the middle?
I'm sorry. That's not where the milk. I'll forget for la you I forget everything. Do you have any problems with bullies?
They count if they count you understand irony. Yes. What do your clothes look like?
I look like my I look like my clothes were made for me because they were
They looked stretched because of my bulging muscles. I don't whatever you smoke cigarettes. No, why would that do with a fursona?
What do you like to read poetry obituaries food labels actually accurate?
Newspaper articles food labels. Yeah, I read all kinds of food labels. I love it. Do you cook? No
I'd rather buy dinner. I don't cook choose a wheel skate wheel
Abwheel wheel of fortune. Well, I don't know. I don't care about the elements you want to eat, but you don't have a fork
I'll eat with the popsicle stick. I'll swallow the food whole that's what teeth are for. I guess I'll just starve to death
I'll just suck it up with my mouth
what like
Just on the plate
Okay, what animal would do that? Okay. I would probably try to use some kind of you
I would try to use like chopsticks or some kind of utensil. I'm outgoing and you fly
No
Humans can't fly and you swim I can doggy paddle. Yep. What's your disposition?
Happy-go-lucky. What kind of dance do you do? Where's the fucking floss man?
Too old. I don't know what any of these are. I don't know
Herky jerky, what kind of music makes you feel happy? What food do you like?
Gummy worms seafood. I love seafood
Okay word association just pick the one that looks right was it
Palm tree
Kindergarten you get stressed out easily
No, what do you dream about? He he I can't share it here. I'm not clicking that one. Oh
No, my family usually it's about family friends you wear glasses. No, what kind of art do you like? I like
Modern art. Are you looking for a serious relationship? You're for
Folks
Sore the seagull I get to be a seagull. How is that?
Not the most pog moment of the whole year sure. Okay. Hold on. I almost
Stop with the fucking engagement. I almost was the snake wait. Oh, no, this is what people were
Caw-caw. Oh, why did I just say that out loud which horse?
There's destiny music what horse masters personality, I don't know the guy's gonna skip this one
This is what I don't know. This one's stupid. I just this is I do that. It was an animal theme
What historical figure do you admire? Um, I don't know the warrior queen
Which of these living figures do you admire?
It's Sean White on here. Wait Sean with the snowboarder
You know why I admire Sean White the most cuz he got on this list somehow you enjoy reading. Yeah
Oh, well, do you cook I call for takeout? It's the weekend. What's what's first on your Saturday agenda?
sleeping in
What's your approach to fashion? I spend money on good clothes, but I don't have a signature look
I like clothes that are durable and comfortable. Yep. What genre of music do you enjoy most?
Classical no, that's not even right. I can't change my answer. That's not even right. Why did I know old-fashioned rock-and-roll?
I changed my answer opera. I don't give a shit about opera. Why would I click that?
Oh, no, wait, that's not that's not a pretty rude
I know what I meant to say was I don't like listen to opera not that I don't care
It's a very very hard thing to do. It's like pretty talented people do opera
Which of these would you like most for breakfast eggs bacon took? Yeah
Oh, yeah, what kind of home suits you best a townhouse a simple house a wired one with everything controlled from my phone
That's terrifying. I don't want that. I want the thing that's complete
I want the fucking cottage that has no electricity and you shit in a fucking bathtub 40 feet behind the back door
I don't want that studio. I could clean with a hose. Okay, that's pretty good
Which of these would you most likely choose as a hobby? I already did that so we'll do that one
What's your idea of a good first date? This one is like I would just pretend to know what I was doing
This is the real one. This is the one that I'm pretending. Yeah, I brought I brought you here and I'm very very smart
No, it'd be bowling in like a couple of beers or something. What's a good age to get married? Oh, I did it
I clicked it. How many children do you have or want? I didn't know I can't I can't even tie my shoes correctly
I can't raise another human. Are you close to your family? Definitely. Which of these movie genres do you like the most?
Comedy, how do you feel about marijuana? Let me tell you CBD THC
Pretty much changed my fucking life. I started taking for medical reasons marijuana and I had a lot of pain problems and
Just giving you some anecdotal
Evidence felt a little better. Not too much
Don't do don't be a fucking psycho if it's legal in your area and you can maybe try it
It's illegal and you're not breaking any fucking rules. Don't do anything stupid. Maybe in a safe environment
I did a lot for me. Actually, I would can I I would testify
It's kind of smelly and low rent
What he means low rent it means low rent, how do I delete that? Okay
if you say this
why do I feel like you smoke like cigarettes like two packs a day and
Like you like coke is in your fridge more than the actual drink you get a gift card
This is a how fucking detailed is this to determine what kind of a horse I am
What with this one? I have a halfway what kind of why is it so detailed?
Just this better be accurate. You get a gift card to a well-stocked shoe shop. What do you buy?
Comfortable. Oh, no, I've been comfortable. You've had a fight with your significant other. How do you resolve it? Sounds dull
But it's usually talking out a brood for a while. They've got to apologize. I know it's arrogant
makeup sex
What okay?
Listen, what does this have to do with a horse?
Horses don't talk to each other horses don't like have breakups and then makeup sex
Like horses don't like have like that. It's not like there's no what arguments
Would you have sex on the first date? Oh god. This is some weird fucking data mine
To be honest I have but I tell my kids not to I'm such a hypocrite
I'm sorry. No, not on the first date. Come on
It's gonna take me a few dates to find out if if you like don't want to take like a vaccine
You know, I mean, it's gonna take me a few days for you to be like, oh and by the way
Uh, it's like I think that I think that we're all aliens. Oh
eight number two
We had sex two days ago
This person thinks that we're aliens
Now you want to come back over
Listen to me some of you might be in your day
Some of you guys might be in the age we'd be dating you're talking to people give it a little bit of time
Don't trust me at least a few dates at least a couple of weeks
Then you'll figure that out after like maybe a few weeks and this is a banger
Don't die. It's absurd. Be careful. Be careful
What kind of pet appeals to you dog at what point in our marriage?
Is it best to get a divorce? What the fuck does this have to do with the horses?
What does this have to do with what does this have to do with horses when it's hurting the kids?
I mean if you like if you're just not happy anymore and like I don't know when it's
If you can work it if you can make it work for the sake of the family
Maybe I don't know but like if you don't you don't make yourself suffer
Well on a day of the company picnic you can usually be found anchoring the winning team in a tug-of-war
I'm at home. I don't want to go
No, how important is sex to you? Mr. Oh, mr. Horse
Wait horses fuck all the time. Okay horses fuck more than rabbits. I guess that makes sense
How important sex?
Why is there an answer every time about like being a degenerate and lying about it?
What horse is like fucking and lying to all their horse friends? I don't understand. I keep up a good front
It's it's good. It's great. But like don't don't make a fool out of yourself. Don't fucking just if it's yeah
Don't make a fool out of yourself. What are you gonna? I want to have sex you just relax
Which of these cars would you prefer? None of them. Where's a Honda Civic? I don't want any of these in the hearts
Done done done
That's not what is this? This is legend of this breath of the wild
If I had to pick one of these would be a Tesla and I know like who he wants to just look I didn't say
That I said if I had to choose
Big I don't want to die in a motorcycle. It's fucking you get you. It's horrible. Yeah, I don't like that
I don't I want to I want to be safe. This is too big and I don't know what that is
Which of these popular writers books might you choose for a long plane ride? I don't
Don't want to read that. I've already seen the movie. I don't know who these other authors are
We're gonna go with Tim
If a book is too heavy to lug around airports and planes, can you pick a magazine instead?
You have the entire encyclopedia
What do you mean too big? How many books are you carrying? I would probably read
I don't know like I would look I would pick up a time magazine and just go like this and
Then look at the like the four cologne ads and
Open them and be the guy that opens them and smells them and then puts closes it
I wouldn't read any of the I don't read any of the articles. It's late, but you're hungry. What's a good midnight snack?
gross
Ice-cream this is still going. I can't fucking believe it's still gone
You've got two weeks off from work and a lot of frequent flyer miles. Where are you going?
Hawaii if you took up gardening, what would you what would be most likely? What would you grow with lemons?
No, not orchids not roses. That's that's too generic
Vegetables whiz whiz lemons and limes. That's what I want with lemons vegetables. It's closest answer
Your closest friend would most likely describe you as
Uniquely interesting. That's a way to say that somebody's scary without
Making them angry a lot of fun. I'm a Clydesdale. I'm the I'm the uh
That's the beer one. That's the one that's in the beer commercials. No, it's not
Isn't that the is that the Anheuser and Anheuser bush? Yeah, it is that dad's Budweiser
I've been drinking the same white cloth for two hours. This is disgusting now. I've been nursing this for two straight hours. That's gross
You put the work. All right, this I don't like this music is like too
Ominous. All right, you put the work in workhorse
No one can stand in your way when you determine to get something done
You're really equally comfortable working alone or in a team and when it's the latter you never
Shirk your share of the duties. We also suspect that people just naturally like you
Especially children. Oh and you fuck all the time
You have sex in the kitchen in the laundry room with like thousands of different people
You are fucking every day. All you do is have sex
In fact, you may even have to have had sex ten minutes ago and ten minutes after the stream ends
You're Clydesdale. Thanks for answering our fucked up questions. I remember I this is I'm afraid to do this one
What German nine eight five emote are you? Hi
Hello
Where's your ideal place to travel to?
Japan. Okay, cool. Somebody's I must have somebody right now is going he fucking actually clicked mine
How would you people describe you?
You made this in 15 minutes. I don't chill
What type of day do you prefer?
warning for walks morning to work the time when this quiz ends
Hey because it's exciting day because I am safe night it's calm night for work 3 a.m. Night so I can cry
There's so many answers man. You got you got to make it simple
for a daytime
This nowadays I like to be like awake during the day
you
This song is in Smash Brothers. I was gonna do it. No fucking too many people here to be embarrassed in front of
What social media do you often use none of them? I mean this one. What do you do in your spare time eat play games?
Trade stocks nothing cry read work other
I mean, I kind of I kind of I eat I don't cry eat
Lastly, what do you want out of this quiz? You tell me I hate you
Nothing. There they are. It took me a while before I could see them. I've had enough of that opera
We had a fellow sonic there are 44 foods on this list
And if you eat mayo with more than eight of them, you're disgusting
Okay, french fries. Yes onion rings. No ham sandwich
Yes, tuna salad. Yes. How do you have tuna salad without mayo? How's that possible? Yeah, that's that's I feel like this is unfair
Pick and tenders. No sweet potato fries. Those are disgusting. Well, I'm I don't like the sweet potato craze
I don't I think it's gross. I
Don't I'm not into it. I'm I call me go ahead call me out
I don't I don't like the sweet potato craze of like everything has sweet potato when it's sweet potato fries sweet potato mash sweet potato
This no, it's gonna be regular potatoes. I don't care
I don't even know if yeah, it depends. No on a burger
I don't put it on a hot dog
Fish sticks cuz it's tartar sauce
Sushi. Mmm. No, not mozzarella sticks not on a bagel not on shrimp
Not on eggs
Mac and cheese grilled cheese. No pickles. No pizza. No chips. No steak
Rice no pasta. No toast. No
Salad no
Pretzel no tacos. No bacon. No potato skins. No egg rolls. No pizza rolls puts mayo on pizza rolls pancakes
No
Ram crackers. No bananas. No. All right, my relationship with mayonnaise is normal
Hey, it's soup. I do that
Like just imagine the imagery of it just plopping down into the bowl just say
It'll be disgusting
Thanks a lot BuzzFeed. What playing card are you you feel more like a joker than the ace of spades?
I don't even want to do this one
What suit appeals to you the most and you put it and you put it under an ad you have to scroll down and then
Shit under the ad look at all this
Look at all of this. This is not even a website
It's an ad generating machine. This may as well just this is just a minor
It's just it's just a minor for humans to just just dump
CPM you should get you. I've really looking I've reinstalled windows
So I don't have any like blocking programs. Anyways, my favorite suit is the heart
Which of these games are you more likely to play Texas Hold'em? No blackjack. I'm an extrovert
What would you be most likely to wear to the casino? Don't buy that. It's fucking just your iPhone
You have now is fine. Okay, what would be the what would I gotta wear something comfortable and casual in your opinion?
What's the most important thing in life having fun and making memories having a respected?
Well-paid career being surrounded by loved ones being the very best I can be getting back up when you've been knocked down
It's gotta be having fun making memories the real answer was money by the way
Ah, are you a risk-taker always always I take every risk I can
Where would you ideal holiday destination be as it count if you live there as they count if you live there, right Paris
King of diamonds what I said my hearts was my favorite suit. Why did it give me diamonds?
You're the king of diamonds also known as the king of dices determined and authoritative
You use your wisdom and influence to navigate the twists and turns of life
We bet friends have sought you out for advice on more than one occasion bit of a rogue
You aren't afraid to take chances in life either
The king doesn't take any fucking chances at all ever
The king tells other people to take chances and if they work out then he could be benefits and if they don't then well
They're dead king of diamonds my ass. I'm the I'm the Joker. I'm the I'm the diamond
I'm the part Joker of hearts. I think it's bullshit that they didn't give the Joker a full suit
That's why they throw him out. They don't even see his full potential. He could be anything. I'm the Joker, baby
The sad-ass music I don't want it was sad music
Okay, now this never-ending McDonald's menu quiz is harder than it seems if I don't 100% this I'm gonna be really upset with myself
Okay, what is this? That is a Big Mac. What is this? There's a chicken McNuggets
McFries, what is this? That's a hamburger. Wait. Yeah, that's a cheeseburger
Make a breakfast
Why did they not use that?
That feels like such a better way to say what that is a McBreakfast. Come on to get the McBreak. Why I wish it was
That's a sausage Sammy. What is this? It's a McFlurry. Is this just a fucking just basically pull out basic visual knowledge
That's it. I mean
It's a McFlurry with M&Ms. Is this just can you see or not?
McFlurry with Oreo cookies, what's this? That's a quarter pound with cheese. That's a filet of fish
That's a ham. That's a ham egg and cheese muffin. That's an egg mcmuffin
Down here, I don't even know this is this is on Red Dead something Red Dead related. All right, this is a
That's a McDouble. Wait a minute. That's a McDouble. It doesn't have it McDouble only has one piece of cheese
What's this now? That's a double cheeseburger. What's that? That's not a McChicken. That's a buttermilk crispy chicken sandwich
What's that? That's a sausage mcmuffin. That is a sausage mcmuffin with an egg. What's that?
That's of those of that's a McGriddle. You got a nope. It's nope. I don't get it
What happened your taste in Halloween candy will reveal your greatest fear in life. I'm interested in this one because sour Halloween candy
Sour patch kids are okay, but you can only have a few before they get gross fuzzy peaches. I've never had them
I think sour watermelon slices would be my favorite here. We need it. Do we need a hair appointment here?
Okay, okay pick a chocolate candy Mars bars are amazing. I would say Mars bars
Kit-kats are all right, but Mars bars for sure can on sour gummy candy
gummy bears
Dude, it's just the original Harry bros Harry bros are so much better than Swedish fish
Swedish fish just stick to the top you bite into a Swedish fish and you chew it like three times and it's like
Just that's it's your teeth now
gummy bears a
classic candy
That's gross
Just the kind of shit you find like under the desk at school. No Halloween taffy. No, no tootsie pops
Like a lame Halloween candy our smarties lame. I mean good and plenty is pretty fucking lame, but smarties
They're especially good. I'm sorry mods. That's my fault
um
Pick a heart of runs. Oh, this is tough. This is really hard actually
I'm gonna pick runs because you can never find them anymore
Runs take the cake because you can find jolly ranchers are everywhere nerds are everywhere sweet tarts are everywhere, but runs
only place you can find runs is it's if there's only a quarter of them left in the big fishbowl and it's
50 cents and you get like six-year-old runs, but I like them. I wish they would
Well, I'm just gonna be runs sorry pick a pop culture focused Halloween candy, I love free musketeers
It's just so fluffy. It's the fluffiest candy. Oh
Shit, I'll buy candy sticks forgot about these
That's that that's cool. Pick a healthy Halloween candy if you're giving out skinny pop popcorn on Halloween
You are a Satan worshiper you hand it out and you're like, okay kids
See you later the door closes and you just like start a fucking seance
Probably these
Justin's peanut butter cups. Okay, what's my greatest fear?
Shit, that's true
Your greatest fear in life is loneliness
Nothing scares you more than being completely and utterly alone you welcome death but going to a movie or wait you welcome death
But going to a movie by yourself is probably the worst thing that could ever happen to you. Fuck. Oh
This has been more accurate than any horoscope I've ever read it seems kind of weird. I got it right. I can't lie
What am I gonna say? It was not if it's bullshit. It's absolutely accurate
stock market quiz
Let's put on some Mario music for this. Why is this on here? I don't know somebody somebody linked it in the discourse
I clicked it. Okay pop quiz. What's your stock IQ?
What is the stock market a casino where you can gamble and win a lot of money?
Well to some people it is
Some people at a marketplace where you can buy and sell shares of companies. That's the correct answer place where farm animals are bought and sold
Place it's only for rich people to get richer
Well
Well, who those could be pretty accurate. What's a fractional share?
The amount an entire company is worth in dollars
No piece of a whole share which offers entry to stock market at affordable price. It's that one a class
Yeah, the class I already got you the right answer fractional shares. You can buy a quarter or a third or as much as you're comfortable
You don't have to buy the whole share
What is a bull market the sign of the stock market is closed. No market in which prices are going down. That's a bear market
Sorry, a market full of super aggressive traders true
Residents sleepers
All right. We don't okay bull markets when the markets are fucking increasing the stock prices are going up IPO is a it's a when a company
Puts itself on the stock market for the first time. It's a it's a public offering initial public offering
Coca-cola is the best performing stock at all time. No, it's Berkshire Hathaway
What does S&P stand for standards and pores? What type of investment is the safest? Uh-huh a well diversified portfolio true or false
I should invest in something. I've never heard of it because my friend told me tool you be stupid
What's a dividend a dividend is when you get your payout for owning stock at your share?
It's and whatever the bits and earnings per share
What's diversification is when you own pretty when you own a lot of shares of different companies and you spread it all around
Why did I do this? Oh, this is the one that I wanted to do. What stock should you buy based on a personality quiz?
Okay, here we go. Do you tend to play it safe? No, there's 30 questions
You're gonna drop viewers. It's been two minutes. Okay. How much do you know about the stock market? I know a lot
How much money do you make? Oh ding-ding how much are you willing to invest it?
Ding-ding is the stock market something you want to invest in for the long term. Nah, fuck it
Just give me something quick and risky. How much money should you would you like to make to the stock market? That's ring-ding
Where do you check your email? I don't use my email. Are you trendy? No, do you like to travel?
No, I'd rather stay home. Would you like to invest in banks?
No, how much of your income would you like to have in stocks?
Yeah, maybe a little are you scared to invest in stock market? Not really. Would you like to educate yourself on the stock market?
No, do you eat a lot of junk food? Yeah
Do you want to do you want to relate to the stock you're investing in?
I don't fucking care is it gonna make me money who gives a shit. How important is it to have known name stock investment?
I read that again. How important is it to have a known name stock investment?
I mean, I guess it's kind of important if you need to know what the fuck you're investing in who will manage your stocks
I will are people you know invested in the stock market. Yeah, sometimes
Why are you investing in the stock market? Because someone told I'd smart
Which would you prefer a high risk? How often do you check on stocks?
Every single day. Are you spontaneous? Of course I am how many shares are willing to buy a ton
Do you save a lot of money? Yeah. Yeah, how much are you willing to lose a lot?
Are you going to invest the loan?
What we're gonna go into like a carpool of sharing the shares no
No, no, no, no, no. No, I'm gonna invest. Oh, of course. I'm gonna invest alone. Oh
Good budgeting not very good. How important is the integrity of the company you want to invest in? Did I make 30%?
It's kind of important do your magic ability to hold on
What season do you plan on investing all of them? You should invest in capital one. No, you shouldn't
Why would you do that? I don't want to invest in a bank
Actually real what click it coward. What? Hold on. Yeah, you took a screenshot of my face. So what?
No, I don't want to invest in capital one. Wait, there's only a few they're all banks
JP Morgan Chase capital one Bank of America. What's going off my face? Why is it was cameras fucked up? What's going on here?
Why is it going like?
What's with the refresh rates fucked up I was doing this put that out why is it doing that it's cuz I'm a hologram
Just turn myself green. It's not talking Star Wars stuff. Hey speaking of Star Wars. Why is it fucking doing this?
How do I fix this? How do I do this? What's going on?
Refresh rate is that 60 Hertz? What the fuck are you doing man? I'm sure camera turn on your lights. It's lights
Oh, I got it. It's gone. But now I'm all like wiggly this camera sucks. I got it. We're good, right?
No more scanlines, right? Oh, we're good. Okay. I don't want I'm not gonna invest in capital one
This is I feel like somebody made this somebody made this because they own like a bunch of shares in all these banks
And they're like, maybe I guess he's fucking people to buy this shit
That what's going on over there? Okay, choose your weapon. Oh
I don't know. It's either gonna be electricity or it's gonna be the lightsaber. It's lightsaber. Obviously, what kind of childhood did you have?
Oh, this is a long one fucking god. Okay. Okay. Okay. All right. Can I just say uh
I'm general grievous. All right, that's the guy. I saw I most relate to next
I'm for do who what Marvel character we we know which Marvel character matches your personality. Oh
Show the image. I forgot. This is a reddit quiz
That's like that's like your annoyed cat. I mean wrong one. That's a wrong image. Oh shit, man
This is this is gross
This is not real
To believe
And I meet it this time that's not a real picture it's not I know it isn't
That's like you open up the door that's like the face that you make this like how you feel and how you look
When the raid ain't going so well has been 12 hours and you still have to first pull
It's like dude, can I please go eat and I do something else? Hey, look at me
It's not even accurate
Holy shit, that's so fucked up. Okay, which Marvel character am I Captain America?
Okay, the Marvel superhero teams are with the music fuck you. Oh
undertale
Alright, can I say I'm gonna say this and I think it's accurate the undertale soundtrack could be
One of the best one of the top probably three
Soundtracks in any video game probably like top five at least somewhere in the top three. It just is well with okay
Whether you like this game. I don't like that. I like the fan base. I don't like them. Whatever
This these songs are objectively like fucking
bang
Minecraft and undertale those. Yeah, you're right. That's pretty high
okay, if I had you just like in a room and you like a blindfold on and you have like you like a thing covering your
Ears and like you didn't you didn't know what this was if I was like, all right, take it off
Take the headphones off take the eye shield off and you heard this. I was like, what do you think you'd be like, right?
I like it. It's good. This is good. And then I'd say hey, you know, that's from right now
What is this from Super Mario 2? No, it's from Earthbound. No, what's it from then? It's from undertale. I
Know it isn't it's not it can't be I can't I can't like it
I just can add in the middle of that song. All right, let's go this
Okay, the Marvel superhero teams are all drafting a new members. Which one do you want to be a part of?
nobody wants to be on the Fantastic Four now because there's only four of you and
If there's a job that has to be done one of those four people has to do it that would suck
I want to be on the X-Men because there's like 40 of us and if somebody has to go do something
Hey, we got we need like three magic users and a guy with a big fist and he like crystal
Explosives it's like okay
That could be like eight different people I can stay home. Oh
okay, like
Gambit and
Cyclops and beast you guys you got that right? I can stay and just play fucking fortnight. Okay
Go for it, man. Like hey, I'll do I'll get the next one like tomorrow. If you're in the Fantastic Four you got to shit every day
Nope X-Men you can't like lounge on the couch. If you're mr. Fantastic
You can't like put that on somebody else
What motivates you?
This is fucking two and a half hours old. I'm gonna need another one. Do I even have did I buy two I did?
I I suppose well, I'm gonna have friends and shit. All right, tonight's the night
You're going on your third date with the most perfect person in the world
What did I tell you all the viewers here? This is I told you what makes though what makes them attractive to you?
Well, hold on. Let's get back over here. Ah
What's it what makes them attractive it's sarcastic and we they have a strong moral compass they got a wicked charm
They're super smart. They're really rich. They're super ripped. They can keep a secret. They just have this dark intensity to them
When it comes to relationship, would you ever date another superhero? Yes. Absolutely. I need someone who understands my lifestyle. No way. It's too dangerous
I'm not really interested. I feel like I feel like the answer is probably yeah
Because like if I levitate
The like the pizza rolls across the living room. They're not gonna be freaked out by that. They're gonna be like, oh, okay
You're a dick. But if I do that in front of someone that doesn't have powers, they're gonna be like
Couldn't you couldn't just get up? No, I couldn't just get up. Why couldn't you just get up?
Look, I've got fucking superpowers. I don't have to get up. You do you would never understand
Okay, if you had it your way you I can have it my way at Burger King
But I wouldn't want to go I wouldn't want to have it my way there
I'd want to go to McDonald's that I'm gonna go through the drive-through and just drive through it and go to the McDonald's next
door, uh
What was your what's your last meal be?
last meal candy
No, something like it was like a was like a steak dinner or something up that fast food
You suspect someone close to you has betrayed you. What do you do?
Trick them into confessing. Please. Give me Loki. Please. Give me Loki. Please. Give me Loki
Please I'm gonna do everything that Loki would do so I get Loki and then I could share it
Hold on
Give them the benefit of the doubt kill them before they do any damage destroy them, of course
Aren't these the same confront them about this terrible rumor find a way to use this to my advantage
I'll just have a few words with them over drinks
Dr. Doom has stolen the powers of the silver surfer and taken over the world. How will you stop him? I mean motherfucker
I'm on the X-Men call somebody else
I'll stay. Oh, yeah, I'll get up. Yeah. Oh you already got up. Hey, oh
Jubilee already got up. All right. Yeah, no, go for it
Don't know is I don't have any fucking powers. I
Lied to my application
Okay, it's dr. Doom stole the powers of the silver too much Sonic the Hedgehog. No, no, halo. No, no battlefield one
No, it's not something good kill zone three. No Mario Odyssey. Oh
My goodness, this is the one I want
Okay, so dr. Doom stole the powers of the silver surfer and taking over the world how he stop him since dr
Doom was bound by honor. I tried to reason with him and he didn't work at peace force
I'd fight him. I'm smarter than him. My ego demands it. Well, that depends the person I love in danger
I'll always try to do the right thing. You know, that means getting my butt handed to me
I'd join the fantastic four and work as a team the situations bigger than me. No, you wouldn't no you wouldn't
We just don't we just discussed this. I would try to reason with dr. Doom first. Oh
You just got caught driving too fast and now you got a speeding ticket. What do you do?
I'd say, thank you officer and pay the fine
Please the police officer would be putty in my hands. I could talk them out of anything
I'd rip the ticket up flip off the cop and be on my merry way
I'd try to make the cop laugh and get out of the ticket
But if that didn't work out accepted and move on I would I would talk I would please
What's your favorite part about being a superhero?
Having the coolest toys and meeting other people like me. I always thought I was alone
These are my powers to help others who can't help themselves
I kind of like the mystery aspect of it. I better not get Superman. That's boring
One of your co-workers is always putting you down. What do you do about it? Okay, is the co-worker also a superhero?
Or is it just like I'm working in the office for it. Is it just as a superhero?
Are we also is it X-Men is it an X character?
I'd pull the person aside and talk to them privately found out what's really going on, you know
I can only take so much before I explode. I'll just walk away. I've got bigger fish to fry
I just write back to them and make them cry
I'd take whatever they say is a compliment and defuse the situation. I turn their insult into a joke and then we would all laugh at them
Nick Fury has asked you to represent shield and go out to dinner with a very important
That turned in a different way. Oh
Nick Fury has asked you to represent shield and go on a very important mission. Oh, actually, this is perfect for me
Me can I do that one?
You only catch the breath is atrocious, ah, can I be the guy that goes at the dinner and it's fine
I don't have to get in harm's way
Okay, their breath is terrible. I'd ignore their breath and pay for the meal. I'd cancel the dinner in order takeout
I can't stand annoying smelly people
I'd politely offer a mint and say this is a rare candy from another dimension that must be enjoyed
It might be that one because then you can laugh you can laugh about that
give them the mint and you both go like
It's an altoid
And you're in and everything's fine and like they're good that would work
I'd end the meal quickly and say sorry, but Nick Fury needs me to save the world
That would be this one. You have a big day planned at work, but wake up with a cold. What do you do?
Hmm roll back up and get some rest. There's no way I'm going to work today suck it up and go to work
No, call my boss and let them sick that I can work remotely going back to bed
What's your relationship to large family gatherings like holidays and family reunions? I think they're great. I like them
Pick one thing from a fairy tale to have with you in everyday life. What is it?
Why would you carry on a poison apple?
Jeannie that grants three wishes of magical singing voice a ton of woodland friends poison apple. Okay
This is the only one that cannot be
Obtained normally you can make a shitload of woodland friends
You could have a bunch of you go to the woods and make like friends with the squirrels and shit
Just bring like seeds and nuts with you
They all like you you can train to be a singer and you can just put poison in an apple
Like this is the only one you cannot get normally I'm getting three wishes
Oh, it's far cry the game that I lied about skip it. Okay, we're at
It's time to get deep at least when it comes to exploration. That's right. We're making you pick deep sea or deep space
Where would you rather explore deep sea man? The deep deep space is just I feel like it's a bunch of nothing
It's just a bunch of like colors and little lights and shit and that's cool
But this creatures we haven't even seen before in the deep sea
It would be so interesting to be under there and just like lie on the ground and look at all of the sharks and stuff
And all of the weird deep sea animals deep space is too much. It's too much to do
I would freak me out. I'd be like, oh cool deep space
I guess it's gonna take me like 30 years to go from here to there
Even if I fly with my superpowers
It's like six million light-years away where I could just go like two miles deep and see a weird fish that one
We promised this question won't make you evaporate when we snap our fingers. Thanks for the fucking spoiler buzzfeed magic quiz
Pick an infinity stone time. I have time. It's time. How would you rate your relative cleanliness?
I can do this again and again and again
Forever why is that minus two time stones the best stone?
You can do whatever you want. You can fucking manipulate anything
I can go back in time and like gain a thousand pounds just fun and then go back and fucking do it again and to
Get skinny I can do whatever I want. I could do whatever the fuck I want
I could go back in time and I could like I could go forward in time and see what happens and just go back
And then fix it and then go forward again, and then it's stuck
How would you rate your relative cleanliness? There's a few things a little bit of clutter
Okay, Avenger didn't pick that by the way while you're just making me an Avenger
I didn't I said X-Men motherfucker if you weren't a superhero, what would your job be?
teacher first responder a spy a truck
It would be a truck driver. I just want it so that's I could just I would just drive on the road
Just be me in the road which animal is your soulmate? What animal do you feel like you most relate to?
dolphin dog rhinoceros monkey grizzly bear hawk
Where's the Clydesdale? I love I love birds. I do words are like one of my favorite animals
I love crows. I love Ravens like hawks. They're really really interesting Falcons and stuff. Ah
Rhinoceros is crazy though. Fuck. How would you describe the art in your home?
I have a pain. I have one picture of Super Mario doing growing and intensity pop art
There's any part of being the president sound appealing to you. No, no all these things suck
But what's the worst thing that could happen to you on a date?
You're not physically attracted to them. All they do is talk about themselves. They complain a lot. They have no manners
They're boring. I can't hold a conversation one of us forgets their wallet. They're into astrology
That's probably this one because that's just fucking awkward because then it makes the other person have to pay for the meal and then it's like
Oh shit
Well, it looks like it's gonna be you
One of these foods. Congratulations. You're now eating only this food for the rest of your life
Hope you choose wisely, but what did you choose?
All right for the rest of my life. Let's break this down steak is just protein. It's just meat. Not enough
I couldn't do it grilled cheese is just dairy. It's just like filling and heavy, you know pizza could work
Tomato sauce is just technically tomato cheese. You get the bread. You got a protein with the cheese. Maybe sushi
I don't know if I want to eat sushi every day though
I feel like it really it would I probably get sick if I ate it too much
That's like that could be like it could be green onions
Thanksgiving turkey does that include the rest of the fixings though? Is that Thanksgiving turkey and
The mayo the cranberry sauce the mashed potatoes the gravy is the Thanksgiving dinner. Is it just Thanksgiving turkey? Just turkey. Okay
Pasta no, I'd you'd get you'd puke
Okay sandwiches is the is the answer here sandwich could be anything you could have a turkey sandwich
You could have a ham sandwich
You're gonna have just put anything between two pieces of bread and you got a sandwich
You can put celery and onions in between bread and it's a sandwich. It could be anything
You could get all your food groups that way. That'd be easy
What social faux pas really greats your gears the most what sends you into a blind rage for no reason?
Okay, I've done this I've done this I don't know about that I've done this I've done this
Not that one people feel the need to play devil's advocate in every situation. I'll be phone addict man. I'll be phone addict
I mean come on put your phone down like we're out doing something together
We're having a good time, but you put the phone down put down the phone. It's be all right, man
I get to be iron man. You are not afraid to just go for it. Whatever it may be. Yes
You're arrogant, but no I'm not but that's only because you've accomplished so many things in life
If life gives you lemons, you'll find a way to revolutionize the entire lemon industry before breakfast
Insanely competitive you're married to your job
And if you did happen to get married to an actual person we're willing to bet they'd have something to do with your job
You can be a prick
But you're willing to sacrifice everything to help other people and that's not insignificant share your results with your friends
I'm not a billionaire though funny because I started playing GTA today. I don't know if that's even accurate what that person just said
Okay, uh kid Icarus uprising
Ironman I'm okay with it
Robo Robo prick. Oh wait. This is another one. This is the same quiz and I just like reduced in brightness
Okay, uh, let's do this one quick. What's trait do you find do what do you most value in people you admire?
Let's see if I can get Tony Stark again. Oh, okay
Create creativity next question. Okay, choose your happy place you find Zen
Uh
At home I do
Here's your solution when problems arise. How do you battle them? It's about the humor
Who's your event? What's your favorite sporting event baseball? It's not even on here
Wrestling who's your potential you you perform at your best when you feel?
Powerful innovative choose your beast if you could shape shift into any animal. What could you shape shift into?
This is just the same exact quiz eagle
Who's your quality what describes you best? Who's your jam? What type of music do you like? Who's your power?
What's your greatest strength?
My dedication my spirit my judgment my ambition my physique
my spirit
my dedication
my ideas
Who's your lair? Where would you like to be secret lair city apartment mansion skyscraper anywhere, but here a secret location
I don't even know where I don't know
Batman
Only stark. Did you guys crash this fucking website too? Okay. It was Tony Stark
Jesus fucking ads your children of what metal gear solid character are you?
Your children are being unruly to get them to behave. Do you?
Their eggs
Am I like a moth
What and are we like a an animal? I didn't a locker
This quiz sucks
Okay, I would
Your children being unruly
Inspire obedience through a rousing speech about children without a nation
This is just each one of these is a character. All right, I'm gonna endure it because they're my kids
Burn their eggs if you were in command of a group of soldiers. What tactics would you use to defeat your enemy?
Burn their eggs
Train my men hard by having them live on an abandoned ocean platform
Hey, that's snake by the way, that's six dad big snake big snake senior. What's his name?
Take over a nuclear decommissioning facility and capture warheads. Oh
Leave the group behind you work. Just burn their eggs
What's your favorite guilty pleasure?
It's talking to myself in the mirror. How was your relationship with your friends? Oh
My friends often end up okay. I need more. I need something else
Oh
Same mattress there's like six of them that are the same fucking foam
Latex foam mattress. There's like seven of them, but you know, they're all good. Okay, all of them are good
there's like purple this Casper there's like a
Lisper whatever it is. There's like four of them. They're all good. They're all fine
Whatever one you get just bad one just get one if you want one if you have a bit want a bit of sleep
Sure buy one of them. All right, here's the next one. Okay. All right, we get we get an encore a double. Oh
Yeah
What? Okay, my friends I burned my friends eggs. What's your favorite animal eggs a chicken?
It's a bird. What did I get?
Wait, isn't this a meme from Metal Gear?
You are not good at cooking eggs. Also Google immature to be turns of terrible things
What Ninja Turtle character are you? Okay. I know which one I am already. Let's just go with this
The best part about these quizzes, especially ones on some of these kids websites is
Some kid will watch Ninja Turtles and they'll be so happy to be able to take a quiz to see who they are and
It may maybe they'll get their favorite character, which is Michelangelo. So these quizzes just give the kid
Every Oh whatever Michelangelo would do they click on it and they just get to be Michelangelo. It's genius
So let's I'm Michelangelo. Let's get it. Okay. What do you do to prepare for a mission?
Man, I relax to grab something to eat man. Pick a hobby
I don't know. I don't have any hobbies, dude
Which of these enemies are you worried about?
Probably. Yeah, I don't know the hip hip no part of it sounds crazy, dude. Pick a quote. That was easy
Oh my gosh, I've always liked cowabunga dude. You have to make the rehearsal. That's a Donny thing to say
Donny that was easy. That's Raphael. Oh my gosh. I don't know cowabunga. That's Michelangelo. Pick a pizza topping
Anything man, how are you feeling today? Okay. I
Were I'm a boy. How old are you? I'm older than 16, man. I'm not under six
Are you feeling today? This is just data. Okay, wait the quiz. Which one of your family members do you find the most annoying?
Okay, who does Michelangelo find the most annoying Leonardo right cuz he has all the rules
Leonardo pick a type of turtle
No, man
What weapon are you gonna use? Totally using the nunchucks, man. How do you describe your personality fast?
I'm a little weird man. Someone tells you the hideout is under attack. What do you do?
That would help them do it. I'm an Avenger. Oh
No, wait, I'm like a leg. Hello. What fortnight skin are you how many more of these left? Okay. Thank God
Okay, you're playing battle royale squad mode and you're flying over the map in the bus
Do you leap up because I have no fear. Just wait a little longer. There's no rush
Stay in the battle bus as I have snacks
Michelangelo you go out to buy a new jumper. What color code do you favor blue?
What's your favorite holiday of the year? What's your favorite film genre comedy? What type of music are you most likely to listen to?
defense
Don't data mine me you're playing fortnight and your teammate comes under attack
What do you do about that do everything you can to help your teammate get into a flap?
I'm too old to know what that is. Erm distract your enemies but pretend to be a big jelly, baby
Okay, that sounds funny. I guess which pet would you like to have the most crow? Oh, yeah
Oh, would you most like to eat? I have no time to eat on the battlefield, but it might have some crisps English
This test is English. I said cake vegetable fingers and baked beans burger, which item of clothing do you prefer to wear?
I don't know hats. You're trapped on a desert island. What one item do you take with you an inflatable house?
Oh, I get to be Ripley
We're not sure why but when we see the sport it's can we want a bowl of jelly?
I should probably would pick that next your answer to these would-you-rather questions will reveal what you were in your past life
We're gonna this one. What's a halo to Diablo which what Diablo though? That's a big that's important
Okay, I'll say on this. All right for your birthday. Would you rather have received cash or gifts?
Would you rather live at the top of a big-city apartment building or at the top of a mountain?
This is so basic and simple. It's just like it's like you were a
big shitty millionaire
In a city, would you rather end hunger or hatred? Oh shit. This is hard
Would you rather be poor or and work at a job you love or rich and work at a job you hate?
Oh, I don't poor and work a job
You don't love of work a job you like would you rather be on a survival reality show or a dating game show this one?
I could make funny. I would I would get okay hear me out
survival reality show is hard and difficult and I have to like go crawl through like mud and shit and like
Limbo under like electrical wires and and eat bugs and stuff
No, this one dating game show I can be like a viral video meme for a few weeks
I could I could like do something weird and be like the weird person that they say no
I'm not you you don't get the rose and I would like do a weird like
Dance or something I get viral for we and that would that doesn't take very much
Would you rather eat pizza or ice cream is the only food for eternity about pizza
would you rather be locked in an amusement park or a library a
library because
There's endless fun here. You have to ride the swing ride every day
You could find something new every day if you wanted to you have to ride the same roller coaster every day library
Would you rather be gossiped about or never talked about at all? I really don't care either way. I'd rather
That's that's fine. I was a musician in my past life
You're calm and laid-back
You love music and how it impacts the people around you
I don't you typically voice out your opinions or send messages through a song
Kind of like our new follower whoo uber muffin. Thank you for the follow. We really appreciate
I won't do it. I definitely was not a musician in my past life. I was a frog what do
Alright, I'm starting to get exhaustion from these quizzes. What's your baby naming personality?
We only have like four more I know this is a good time to go pee
It's bit I'm gonna pee and go get another one of these I'll be right back
Oh, I have to do chubby bunny today, too. Just stay tuned. That's a scared the shit out of me. That's scary music
Okay, I'll be back. I'm just gonna go pee and then get another
Drink that is not to be named because it has a name people. It's like Voldemort. Okay, let's see a minute
Did I even dumb I didn't tweet this stream out?
I'm gonna make a noise right now. Oh
What is this? Oh
That's the Ludwig theme. Oh, no, it's not. I thought it was I didn't look over from a blood-borne
10k and you get the fuck out of here. Come on. Take the BDSM test. No, thank you
I don't think I'm gonna do that on camera. No, thanks. Oh, yeah, we got Ludwig subs here. Ludwig is a good dude
Alright, let's go do it or no balls. Why I'm not gonna take like a what kind of sexual things know
And here's the reveal the phantom of the fucking opera. You see how ugly he is with the light on
Okay, what what kind of baby am I gonna have? What is it fucking Dracula?
Okay, choosing a name for your baby can feel like an overwhelming responsibility. It's likely to be a reflection of your lifestyle
We got a family feud coming up soon here guys
You realize that we've got hive mind that we're gonna play you guys have no idea
How fucking cool this game is was stalling until we get to hive mind and chubby bunny. All right
Okay, what's your baby naming personality take the quiz and find out then get ideas for baby names
What type of films do you like to watch? My kid's name is Greg
next
Anything with a good review whatever the hottest new releases
I don't know things that are reviewed. Well
pretty baby your dream holiday was
lazing on the beach of
beside the hotel pool
Definitely not backpacking definitely not road trip
Definitely lazing around on the beach Greg is a good boy
What what would your dream date involve? No clubs? I can't talk to you
I want to be able to talk to you a moonlight strolled and dancing under the stars. That's to me me hot air balloon
Let's go
No, that's too adventurous. No, it'd be dinner, but I could be both. They could be both
Which maternity outfit best appeals to you?
What do you mean? Like what if I see somebody wearing maternity clothes?
Okay, the
Sun dress I made from myself from organic cotton. I made this dress for this person
I don't know something comfortable
Marvel Ultimate Alliance this thought that was baby shark for a second. No, no, I don't play Rocket League
This is just it's just a regular. This is just a song. I mean, I don't want the VODs gonna get nuked
There we go, Luigi's Mansion. That's good. All right, let's go
What's your favorite pregnancy relaxation activity? Oh
I get it. I get it. This is if I was pregnant
Spot day your favorite cure for morning sickness is
Hypnotism, I don't know. What type of nappies do you plan to use?
Like I'm taking is that like a cute way to say nappy like I'm taking a nap
Disposable nappies. No, this is diapers. This is English to spread another English test
What's what's with all the English tests? Okay, it would be
eco-friendly disposable nappies
Where will your baby sleep in a sturdy?
Okay, I thought it said in a sturdy safe
in a sturdy safe
Classic design sure when your baby arrives, how will you transport them?
I'm in my arms like celebrities do in the same pram my in the same in the same pram me mum used for me
You're finally at 40 weeks, but your baby doesn't seem to be in a hurry to come out
What do you do eat spicy food send vibes to my baby that it's all right to come up sure because what else are you gonna do?
Congratulations, you've completed the quiz now look back at your answers. Oh fucking come on. You don't even have like an algorithm a
a
three a's four a's five a's it's a
Your baby naming person fuck this quiz pretend to be a toddler for a day and will reveal your nostalgic cartoon
personality twin
Okay, it's time to wake up as a toddler. What time do you rise and shine?
Okay, first that was weird ah
Seven thirty or later. I'm a late riser. What's for breakfast ooh? No chocolate chip pancakes
Fruit loops maybe toast no smoothie. It's fruit loops. It's fruit loops
What show are you going to watch Sesame Street done? What toy will you play with?
Toy cars what's for lunch macaroni and cheese definitely who's an outdoor activity swinging sandbox?
Too dirty to get too gritty, and I don't like it cringy
Slide jumping probably slide or jumping
Swinging actually scares the shit out of me anytime, but I see a kid like swinging on a swing and they go up really high
I'm like I have a panic attack every time to dig it at the apex they go like uh don't go don't fall
Fuck uh don't don't get hurt. I don't like swings. I don't like them
Choose a snack round up hooves
Popsicle probably gum it popsicles definitely. What's for dinner chicken?
It's bath time to choose a bath toy
Probably fishies what time do you go to sleep? Probably around 8? I guess I'm Arthur
You're smart loyal and self-proclaimed nerd a baby, okay a
Toddler cannot be a
Smart loyal self-proclaimed nerd you love playing video games and watching superheroes like a toddler
Doesn't have a Twitter account that says that in their bio
Okay, you love playing video games and watching superhero shows in your free time. You would never let anyone hurt your friends and family
Too what am I gonna? Do you never let anyone hurt your friends and family you would?
Stay there like this
Okay, when you're like less than three years old you're essentially a bag of sand
What am I gonna do if somebody's like fighting my friend? Okay, this is dr
Phil's personality test now not now hold on a second
You're gonna take my personality test you're gonna sit down and you're gonna you're gonna enjoy it sit down
now
What time of the day do you feel your best?
Is it in the morning is it in the afternoon or into the early evening or is it late at night?
Well, I don't want to be on your show
When do you feel your best I feel dr. Hey, can I call you doctor can't I'll call you Phil
Phil I
Somewhere into the early afternoon and early evening usually walk do that again. Well, he's got a fucking awesome theme song though
This does really wait a second. This is perfect opportunity for this
There's a show on Netflix and it's called the American Bible study show
It stars Jeff Foxworthy and it's about like you you you get on the show and you've come with a family and you do
Trivia for the Bible and in Christianity and stuff, right? Whatever. That's not important at all. The theme song to this show is
Fucking insane. We have to listen to it because I cannot comprehend why this theme song is the way that it is
It's time to play it American Bible study theme song. Are you ready? No, what's not it? What's it called American Bible Showdown?
Do they even have this? What's it called American? What American Bible challenge? There it is. You're not gonna believe this shit
American Bible challenge did nobody has the theme song the intro or something. It's um, it's crazy American Bible challenge intro
It's Jeff Foxworthy
Okay, I think this is this a whole episode
Fuck I need this. Does anybody can can define this theme song open Netflix. I don't have Netflix on my computer
It's a fake show. No, it's no, it's not you got it
American Bible challenge song
No, this is not it. You got it. Somebody got it. Use the browser
I don't know what my next let's password is. I have no clue what my Netflix password is shit
I need you guys to hear this. No, stop. You're gonna sound like it like slaps and shit
I gotta find a way to do this, please some I need to show this no, not not no not National Bible quiz for seniors
No, you got it. No this one this one this one somebody's gonna find it
I just need the intro
Godzilla fart. I just need the intro to the show American Bible challenge. You're killing me
How is this not here from your own video? No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, please somebody
Please I can't spend all day on this is it
It's not it it's not it it's it's the theme song to the show you got it this it this is it
Everybody calm down everybody relax. Are you ready for this crazy-ass theme song, please play?
Sorry an unexpected error occurred. Give me a fucking break. Why what American Bible challenge? Come on
Sorry an unexpected error occurred Jeremy Jeremy Jeremy. I swear to God this better be real. I gotta move on
It's a broken link. Oh, this is I this is so important to this shit was so important. I gotta move on
I'll find a way to I'll find a way. I'll find a way. I promise I'll fuck
Don't fucking move. I'm gonna go record it on my iPhone. It's here. But I why can't I play it?
That's because I have a VPN on I'm so fucking mad right now
Why can you know use daily motion with a VPN? Why the one day I turn on my fucking VPN sit
Wait, is this is this real? I gotta mute that fucking audio because this could be like a screamer. Hold on
Okay, this is it ladies and gentlemen, we're about to listen to the intro to American Bible challenge. Are you ready?
How fucking terrible was that?
Everybody put your hands up. Everybody just stand up. Everybody put your hands up. Everybody just stand up
Everybody everybody put your hands up. Everybody just stand up
What does this have to do with God and it's Jeff Foxworthy singing the song it has to be right? That's Jeff Foxworthy
The American Bible challenge
That's like the safest song I've ever heard in my life. That's definitely Jeff Foxworthy singing that by the way
I think it might be like a joke. He might be it might be like a big joke. He's like a comedian
It's in one of your videos. Is it really that? Yeah, somebody said it that sounds royalty-free
Everybody just stand up. Everybody put your hands up. Everybody just stand up. Everybody put your hands up
You that's the first part of a chorus like everybody stand up and wave your arms around everybody
Just put your hands up, right? It's not you. You're doing the first part of the chorus. It actually is in the video
Retail media by critician. Are you smarter than God? It's actually in one of my videos by appearing on the world's top intro to this video
Scary, I wouldn't want this guy on this set
Yellow
I just spit over you. I
Didn't even I did not look I did not know this is an intro. I didn't see this one
Hold on a minute. You should be scared every time forget about this
Skip this time that you are outside those walls
This guy's scary. I wouldn't want this
Here come I'm gonna keep his golf guy. I'm Jeff Foxworthy and this is the American Bible challenge
Let's do options first, but I fucking can't even do it anymore good
anyways, yes
It's it's like the first part of a chorus and they just say it like six times and the show starts
I've seen like eight episodes of the show
Everybody just stand up. Okay. All right, put your hands up. Okay, everybody just stand up
Jeff I already am put your hands up Jeff. They're up. Just stand up. I'm standing and my hands are up. What's up?
What should I do now? Should I praise God? No, just stand up. I can't it's fucking crazy. I
Love it though. It's like my favorite theme song
Anyways, dr. Phil's uh, I must have said dr. Phil's community subs like he gave a shitload. All right
You guys stand it up your hands up. Yep. Okay, you usually walk
Fairly fast. I need some music. Let me get some music on for this
I
Just had to hear it again to make sure it was real. Okay. Uh, we had an OST going
I lost it cuz somebody links. Here we go. Okay. OST. We're going back to Mega Man
No dead by daylight spoiler. I never played it. Oh
dr. Dooms battle
Mario Galaxy 2
Way too fucking loud. I'm sorry
Okay, here we go. You usually walk
Fasten we got by the way black cherry. We're gonna try this one
DMCA what if I get DMCA claimed for everybody put your hands up everybody stand up
Pretty weird, right?
That would be strange
Okay, I gotta do this test. You usually walk fairly fast with small steps
Let's fast head down and then a meme about this
No, there's a meme where it's like it's like the virgin right? No, I
walk
Asked with long no small steps when talking to people you stand with your arms folded
Have your hands clasped of one or both of your hands at your hips
Not sure push the person to whom you're talking to play with your ear or hair
That's as great. That's did a kpop dance
It's clasped on your hips push away your hair. Okay, which one?
I usually say I usually kind of like this like no, I don't do that. I definitely touch my hair all the time
Okay, when relaxing you sit with your knees bent with your legs neatly side by side
The legs I usually sit like with what I usually sit with like my legs crossed like this
that
but not like crossed crossed like
Like like the shoe is this way. You know, I mean not like at the knee. I'm talking about like shoe kind of crossed over
Okay, uh when somebody really amuses you you react with a laugh, but not I usually laugh a little bit
No, I don't react that strongly
When you go to a party or a social gathering you
Make a loud entrance so that everyone notices you I don't want to do that
Like a quiet entrance looking around for someone, you know, yeah, I usually kind of be like where the fuck is
Mike that's not Mike and you have like a 30 rack and you're like
Fuck these motherfuckers. I'm gonna drink all my beers. I know it Mike
All right, you're working very hard concentrating hard and you're interrupted you
I welcome the break. It's all right. Which of the following colors do you like the most?
Green and aqua. I like aqua Queen
When you are in a bad when you're in a bed at night in those last few moments before you go to sleep you are
Stretched out on your back stretched out face down on your side curled
Yeah, like I'm on my side curled up and I'm gonna get my I'm out
No, I feel like I would get suffocated
You often dream that you are
Fighting or struggling searching for something flying or floating
Usually that's usually it is like fighting or like searching. It's usually searching. Okay, dr. Phil
Quiz me results of your how do others perceive you quiz from dr. Phil
You scored total of 45 the lively center of attention others see you as fresh lively charming amusing
Practical and always interesting someone who's constantly in the center of attention, but sufficiently well-balanced
Not to be let it go
Like all things should be
They also see you as a kind considerate understanding someone who'll always cheer them up and help them up
Oh, wow, I didn't want to get zero to 20 didn't want to get 60 and up
Yeah, between 30 and 60 is where you want to be and dr. Phil's quiz. I think that's pretty accurate
What's next? What is on here for fun? I just I wanted to put this on here for fun
Are you the imposter just kind of sus? I okay. I
Hate the internet I fucking hate this place. You know I mean
Okay, uh, are you the imposter or you just kind of sus? All right, um
sus
Why now you I have to do this I'm sorry I have to do this I have to be this way
I have to be this way. I have to be this way
Why now you've probably heard of among us a party game
Will you play a little astronaut crew member being hunted by an imposter or you plays the imposter?
It's an incredibly fun and addictive way to lose friends
Anyway, here's a quiz to find out if you're the imposter or not because you've been acting a little sus
Oh, you can see me doing that. I hate that
I hate when I do like a voice and you can see my face fuck off. What all right fine
I'll do it quick
Satisfying. Oh, I don't know that I empty the garbage can where were you? Oh, I was at admin
Who do you think is sus? I think it's why I do
Red oh
You're not the imposter. It was red. I just played among us and won
Okay, moving on what make a milkshake and we'll tell you which among us character you are. Okay, we're gonna do it quick
We're gonna do great. I was start with
I thought this is gonna be a way way funnier for people banana and
Banana and fudge brownie and we're gonna use coconut milk and we're gonna put we're gonna put cookies on it and
We're gonna have a fun straw. I'm purple
I
Don't want to take the fishing quiz. I don't care. Okay picks up everyone's favorite
Okay, this is Luna tunes characters looney tunes looney tunes look wake up wake up wake up wake up wake up looney tunes character
Looney tunes not among us anymore. This is gonna tell me what looney tunes persona. I am this. Oh, yeah
This is the title of the stream. We finally got here pick something for breakfast
Cheers to that don't drink it fast. That's stupid
Scrambled eggs or breakfast sandwiches waffles are too messy and they're too heavy donuts are not good for you
Pancakes are too. It's you can't eat one and then you throw you throw it away. It's not good
French toast sticks
Every time a look those of you that want to talk shit about my pancake preference
How many times have you ever gone to get breakfast talking to you and you eat one pancake and you go?
Oh, that's enough. I'm done. Oh there are hold on. I can like fan through the rest of them
There's like four others here never but then you got like the bacon and you have whatever else the sides
Where you get toast and shit pancakes is too much. I'll take one pancake, please
One pancake this big and I want it as a side. I don't want it as a main course
I wanted as a side not the main thing so breakfast sandwich
I'll pick something for lunch. Am I so am I this boring?
It's just sandwiches every day sandwiches all day probably tacos. I love tacos tacos
Food pick something for dinner, okay
Uh
Pulled pork sandwich. Holy shit. That sounds pretty good right now pick a color green pick an animal pick a random word
Crazy pick a TV show. I like spongebob
Any use infer no Scooby-Doo and rugrats. Yes, these are actually
Okay, if you take out Phineas and Ferb, this is a hard one
Like I can just I could take Phineas and Ferb and just literally just go like that and I don't care
Bob's burgers, I think Bob Bob's burgers will be next in line
For it to me just to be like no and then probably Scooby-Doo. So I've narrowed this down to spongebob Futurama and rugrats
Rugrats I grew up on this show. So of course, I'm gonna love it
Futurama is the best Matt Groaning show. It's not the fucking Simpsons and it's not that new one. Whatever the fuck that one is
Enchantment or whatever not that one. It's this one
So it's probably gonna come down to because this is just nostalgia rose colored nostalgia eyeballs
spongebob in Futurama
No, it's not
It's spongebob. It's fun. Bob pick a cookie. This is gonna another this is another process of elimination dark chocolate. It's gross
Don't like it chocolate chip maybe peanut butter unbelievable
Peanut butter chocolate chip though. No just chocolate chip, but they gotta be soft. No crunchy cookies are all throw up
Like a movie genre, I don't like dark chocolate it's too it's too heavy. It's too much. It tastes almost like bitter and sour
It's I don't like the flavor. I could I would you know, I like dark chocolate shavings on top of whipped cream
That's on like a sundae. I know it's supposed to be I know but look look and some people like to drink
Triple bold black coffee and okay you that's cool. I just want something
I just wanted a little lighter like I like a blonde roast sometimes. Okay movie genre comedy. Take a picture of a bunny
Definitely the funny wide-angle lens one
The day of the week
Okay, most people would say a weekend, but I'm gonna have to give you I'm gonna flip this on here
I'm gonna say Thursday. The reason why Thursday is the best day the week is cuz it Friday. Yes, Friday's great
It's the end of the week and there's like the weekend but Thursday lets you
Anticipate the Friday because you know on Friday, you're gonna feel great. So Thursday is like, alright, here we go
Friday's tomorrow and it prepares your brain like Thursday's best day of the week. Here comes Friday. I'm looking forward to it
He's a jobless streamer. I'm a waiter. What are you talking about? I actually said this yesterday that I would I was Daffy Duck
Daffy Duck and Donald Duck. What's the difference? They both get angry and scream who's smarter?
Okay, I think I'd rather be Donald Duck because Daffy Duck uses firearms
Doesn't he? I want to be Donald Duck. Daffy Duck's like a crazy
But in the episodes where Daffy Duck like shoots Bugs Bunny, Donald never does that
He just kind of freaks out and spins around in a circle and people ignore him. I'm a Donald. I'm a Donald Duck
Donald kills someone in Kingdom Hearts
Okay, if you can get a seven out of eight on this horse facts test you're a horse girl
No, he did it. He did what? It's time for more horse themed quizzes
horse girl German omegalo why
Donald please play hive mind. I'm here for I'm here for a while, man
I'm not leaving anytime soon. All right, so what this is just how much how much I know about horses
What is the average?
Lifespan of a horse. I don't have any goddamn idea at all. I have no idea
You could have told me that fish live longer than horses like a goldfish and I'd be like, I guess that makes sense
They're huge. It's probably this 14 to 19
I would say 14 and 19 years wrong 25 to 30. Okay, which of these gates is the fastest?
Gallop, which of these photos depicts dressage was all this the same picture from different angles
Oh, this is this is caucus bad fur day. I know this one
Okay, what is dressage is this I think I don't know this one
Okay, whatever which of these is not a term for a young horse
Philly
What kind of saddle is pictured here an English saddle or a Western saddle the Western saddle?
What color is this horse? Is this a trick question?
That's white. Oh fuck that Gandalf rode around on that thing. That's white. That's how's that gray
Gray
That's spray paint white which of these horses is wearing a halter
Both of them. What do you call this hair on the horse's forehead?
Withers you got one out of eight, right? You are not a horse girl
I mean someone's got to keep horse girls in check you hold the line. Why is that my why do I have to do that?
He scored better than 3% of quiz takers. Wait, what?
I'm in the bottom 3%
That's kind of that kind of sucks. What do you mean? What's even left? Okay, this is you have 10 questions to prove
You're not stupid. This is so okay. This is so dumb
How many bones are there in the human body two and two or six? Yes
9 plus 8 is 9 10 11 12 3 4 5 6 7
70 during childbirth the baby travels from the uterus through the what before it exits the body for the
Doesn't go through your eerie throw. Oh is the symbol for which element on the periodic table gold motherfucker?
oxygen
During which month gains which month gains a day during a leap year February in which war did the US win its independence?
That would be the Revolutionary War
How many planets are in the solar system?
It's is this pre Pluto being disrespected or post Pluto being disrespected post
Which of these words is spelled correctly?
Which of them is spelled correctly vacuum which of the following is not a continent?
Santa and finally approximately how long has been since the dinosaurs when extinct six point five
hundred million years
All right, I'm like that's seven minutes in the glungus test find out what glungus you are your spirit glungus
so bald
What's your happy place?
Streaming on twitch. This is this somebody linked me this one. This is a discord meme
What's your happy place? Oh
Spending time fishing in a in grilling, baby
Probably war any club warm and cozy what game console speaks to you the most this is discord cringe
It's also the last one. I think
What game console speaks to you the most the 3do? That's not a real console. Whatever's on hand dreamcast console PC
I'll take them all gamer PC for the grimy little keyboard consoles can't talk idiot
I'm gonna pick the dreamcast is the only one on here. That's an actual thing. What's a cool name that you may or may not have
Edo or
Sinsky tear me Sylvester destiny any name. What's a name that you may not have? I don't know
My name is that Sylvester
What's your preferred twitch emote? I've rock on I've really started to really really be into it monkey ass
Have you ever been outside of your home country?
Where do you see yourself in five years?
Dead, um, I don't know. Maybe still doing this. Maybe it depends if I'm still having fun. Maybe yeah, sure, which
fence
Have you ever seen a grown man naked? Okay. Well, haha, whatever you say you are about to find out
What a glungus you are. Are you excited? I what is a glungus the og you are the original glungus
You're a rock solid down-to-earth personality would get you far. Somebody educate me on what this is. What's a galangus? What is it?
It's fucking stupid. It's discord cringe. Okay, but what but what is it a
Glungus is a gold on somebody had it. The glungus is a glove filled with water. So what the type of?
Glander from the glungular region
So it's that's just what it is. But what made that what happened? Why did that become something that people share?
Okay, I'm gonna say okay. What is a glungus?
Lungus
Okay, it's a latex glove filled with water. That's one nice glungus. You have there. Yeah, man. It's my
Five one of the night. I'm hoping to pop. This one is massive. Will you pop it?
Is it okay hold on I could ask this is sex thing. This is not like a sex thing, right?
I might take you know, we all laughing because I'm saying like the sex thing like oh, it's a glungus you like
Yeah, I don't know you like spray it on you. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. Okay. Well, that's it