Let me just change the category and uh oh I need my controller.
You guys play this game with a controller or do you play it with a keyboard mouse?
How the hell would you play this with keyboard and mouse? I think that'd be really really hard to do.
Okay you can't see anything yet you will very soon.
Here we are okay so what's the oh this I've already turned the music off.
We keep the music off. We'll keep it on. Let me just change the title and we can go.
Uh the title's uh gonna get out of prison today um whatever I don't care.
That's fine. This bit's I mean a little bit.
I'm app I'm definitely not gonna come even close by the way to winning a single match.
There's a lot of colors in this game and change it to finally out of prison.
Keep making jokes like you're actually getting out of prison today.
Like wait why are they letting me I've just I'm streaming Fall Guys from prison?
Yes I mean you guys already all know that that's bullshit.
It would be a thing that we do to to the one person that ends up coming and I I'm gonna lose.
Maybe not. Maybe not. There's always somebody worse than you and there's always somebody better than you.
Remember that. It's a very important thing to remember in life.
He's a sage. Sage. I'm a sage. That's pretty sage-like.
If he wins he goes free. What like everyone all the other inmates are playing right now.
Whoever wins this gets the get out of jail free card.
That's really messed up. It's already a series.
Dead Man Wonderland. Is that like a show?
All right I hate the egg one. The egg one's always too hard.
Sorry. You just don't want to come in last and I'm gonna get that gold medal.
I'll get it. Yeah.
Stop. Leave me alone. We only have 11 in here.
Now this is not even that interesting to me because you just see this shit on Easter every
year anyways. A bunch of little kids just fucking going nuts looking for the hidden eggs.
Holy shit. You guys ever do that thing or you guys have your parents do that thing or somebody
it always caused a huge problem for some reason. It just did.
All the little hidden eggs for Easter. Yeah we're gonna do the egg hunt.
And for some reason like one of the participants somebody that came over that day or somebody
that was there or an aunt or an uncle or a friend of the family doesn't matter
put like the like a 20 dollar bill or like a 50 dollar bill in one of them.
Like a 10 dollar bill would be in one of them and it's like dude like don't you come on like
whoever gets that's gonna get like 50 bucks. These are like six-year-olds they don't even
know what money is. Don't don't do that. Put like a lot of pieces in there man. Oh don't
don't put like a 20 dollar bill in there you're gonna start fighting.
And then everyone just says well you know we'll just use uh we'll just use that for something.
Like the kid doesn't even get the money like his parents do.
Oh wow yeah little little little John got a 50 dollar bill in there. Oh good for you sport.
Mommy will hold on to that one. But the parents you just go out to like a nice dinner with you
and like your husband. What somebody said what's wrong with your family. I saw at least a handful
of people say that that was something they remembered. You can't just do any amount of
money is bad because you put a dollar in there even a seven-year-old knows. Oh that's fucking
nothing dude. Like even when you're like eight nine years old it's like oh this one's got money
in it. It's two dollars. Oh this is not this is nothing. A dollar. Why is this even in the egg?
And then like you go you look over like your uncle's like smoking a fucking cigarette like
in the corner like yeah you don't spend it all in one place. It's obviously like it was a way
that like he was making a joke with like one of the other uncles or aunts or something.
I'm winning. I literally cannot even buy candy with a dollar because of taxes.
We literally might be related. I don't know what are the six thousand people here?
What's the percentage that somebody in this chat might be like genetically related to me somehow?
It's probably fairly high. Everyone would be weird. Your mother watches the streams. Yeah but I mean
not somebody that I know is watching. Like I'm sure one or two of you guys in this chat have
shared some old like shoemaker back in like the 1400s or something. Guys don't you understand
there there was like 40 people on earth at one point right there was like there was like
2 000 people that lived in like Connecticut as of like 1442. There weren't that many people.
They're not even gonna score one point. Classic American. Okay somebody's cheating I think. I
think we have a cheater. Is somebody cheating? We might have a cheater. No I think we're just good.
Yeah all that mattered was you had like a little town and there was like 17 houses and like a
hundred people lived in your town and one of you guys sold milk the other one yeah you had corn
and shit and some of you guys were like tough and were like defenders and some of you guys had
you know you one of you guys was a blacksmith we all just like got along we all just spent this
bunch of time together everybody had one job and we all just did it defenders yeah I don't know
they'd be like fights they'd be people would kind of try to steal the corn and we'd have to have
somebody fight it's not gonna be me look at me I would I would be a wizard that's I would be one
of the fucking wizards you know what I mean oh I'm doing that thing again where I combine two
things one in real life and not one in real life all right never mind that's 10 to nothing
holy shit I feel like I'm watching fall guys this is ridiculous 12 to nothing
wait that means I'm on a team with a really good player six people all right if I win this one I
actually earned it I won one game last stream it's the tail one the only game I won last stream is
because the servers went offline and 35 people disconnected this guy's got it thank you what's
your fucking idiot they fell for the scooby-doo trick no no I cut him off come on come on he's
gonna go this way cut cut cut cut cut cut cut cut cut cut cut cut cut cut cut cut cut cut cut him
cut him why did you do that you can't scooby-doo me I'm the original goddamn
fucking scooby-doo you're not gonna be able to do that oh no he saw me he saw me oh
he was running down there I was waiting for him to run down and he saw me at the last second he
instantly turned around he had freaked out and he ripped the other fucking direction
damn it holy shit two crowns bro you got two crowns dude pog two crowns uh yeah the first
one was for free because I played long enough for them to give me one the second one 35 people
disconnected and I outlasted them all with my fiber optic internet that's the first yeah but yes
I did technically it did win one I've come pretty close two or three times maybe a little bit more
than that I've come pretty close maybe five or six times like the final three final five
they really are ruining everything aren't they I'm gonna take the initiative I'm going the other
way I thought I could jump across stop get out of my way I every time I touch somebody I get like
all over I really I'm in trouble wait a bunch of people got dumped okay who is weighing this down
he's in for a life sentence yeah I forgot the prison thing I'll get there I'll get I got it I
got it I got it when are you gonna play jailbreak on tf2 I played a bunch of jailbreak for
counter-strike a very long time ago and I actually probably have three or four videos on the subject
and they're not they're just stupid ass videos it that was so much fun though back when it was
really popular those are my only good videos I disagree but it's because I like free kill a
bunch of people in those videos do you get the stamp of your approval what's your best video in
my in your opinion um I don't think it's I can't really do that I feel like I most videos I made
I really liked for the most part yeah but I mean the live action germa rumble is like just that's
that's like just the complete was the complete package for me it just I had so much fun making
that it was so it was such a fun experience doing that and it was just so grueling to do it but
I think it was so much fun and just like yeah like this just the setup for how that came to
be in the first place was just I had a lot of fun doing it so or the uh the photos are in that was
another one that really liked that one five six all right I'm gonna be in a good position again
as long as we don't lose this in the last 10 seconds we're good choking now we're good we're
fine we're fine we're fine hey when are you gonna beat god hand um I don't know I'm not sure I'm
gonna go back to it I had my fun with it I don't know if I'm gonna do it it's a very hard game and
it makes me very very nervous and scared and anxious when I play it because I might not beat
the game and I've got to try really hard it's very hard it's fun game it's because the casino
isn't it well no grab a tail you know what everyone runs around like crazy trying desperately to grab
somebody's tail in this I'm gonna show you the way that you should play this and that is
don't do anything just hang out and just scope out like the guy in the lower right
he is hiding right now that's the guy I'm gonna keep my eye on because never mind he already lost
it you want to keep your eye on the people that are actually hiding that aren't being seen by
anybody but you this person right here is the target see them on the left that person right
there is the target like a fucking bald eagle we're gonna stalk this person and we're gonna
strike at the very last moment just give me yours he you walked right by me as you see we got the
fucking prey that we wanted I told you I was gonna get that guy I dropped a lot of people
yeah you hunted that child we already talked about this the last time I played this game
everyone says that it's a bunch of children but we're all like 30 plus at least 25 plus
everyone says though oh yeah like I've beaten all these kids and they're all just 27 like just
sitting in their houses find the path oh shit wait who knows the right way somebody move
oh get out of the way out of the way out of the way out of the way out of the way out of
the way out of the way get out of my way you just have to get across the finish line that bastard
shit
you fucking asshole the first time I've ever seen that game that one's fun I okay I want more fun
weird stuff like that unless everybody run the same direction and get squished by the same door
I like stuff like that it's fun like this one this is the one I'm talking about I don't like this one
okay this one would be funny with like five people like 10 people as it stands right now
everyone just smushes everywhere and it doesn't matter it's just someone's gonna walk into one
like if this was 10 people then a bunch of people would really have problem it would be fun funny
because once one person goes through every single person knows the answer but if there was only like
four or five of us someone's gonna make a mistake he hates it
it flew across the map but you mean like actually like flew or fell like flying and
falling are two different actions like guy hacking flying and guy falling off edge got launched
remember we can see your cheat engine and this is important in a minute this is important
hug the right side they all came on the right side yeah we're good oh I just missed that one
just missed just missed just missed just missed just missed just missed
it's okay qualified he's cheating confirmed oh yeah hold on actually this is gonna be hard to do
never mind I was gonna put a full screen video of like this computer glitch noises and words
and scrambled letters and accidentally showed on stream it wasn't worth it avoid the walls and stay
on the platform this is I haven't seen this one either he didn't commit to it well I'm I'm
currently in the middle of a game where I can't really stop so what do we have to do is to fit
through what I get it this person's cheating how do you do that how do you cheat I think you have
to jump on somebody else's head you do you do you do you do you do why do I care about cheating
I could have just won that normally I didn't have to do that the definition of hubris yeah
you gotta get up there before it even starts yeah oh well shit I was doing pretty good on that one
too what happened to one or two rounds I'm still having fun I want to get to the final round again
whatever happens happens somebody fucked that whole thing up I don't know who did but
apparently it ruined everybody you can't just run forward oh no I'm in trouble I'm in trouble I got
can't lose the first round can't lose the first round man can't just lose I fell off it's just
push everybody together and somebody's always gonna get the short end of the stick
first round Andy I was in the last round before that last round Larry this is the worst fall guy
streamer I don't believe that for a second no way no way not a chance you know you know how I know
that because there are like 5 000 people playing this right now that are streaming this there's not
a chance that I'm the worst one someone's always better than you someone's always worse than you
though remember that it's important you are the worst I'm not the worst fall guys but being okay
being the worst fall guys player is just like saying yeah it's like saying you're bad at like
the jumpy house no it's you're not no one's bad at this game no one's good at this game
there is no bad there is no good there is just jumpy house he's coping you let me let me have it
you don't have to come in first place you know it doesn't matter if you come in last place you
got to jump in the jumpy house it's fine did I really not qualify I'm at the fucking finish line
shit maybe I am the worst streamer for this game I really might be the worst fall guy streamer that
I that's sad to think about my ego is getting in the way right now and it sucks like my ego
right now is like no no it's not possible Jerry but you can't be I mean that just that's two in
a row if I make it three then it's possible hey no right at least I got to jump in the jumpy house
it was kind of fun she had got to you no they didn't no don't lock me out don't lock me out
after that you didn't qualify for the next jumpy house it's called a bouncy house hey open up a
thesaurus and tell me what the word next to bouncy is jumpy is not a word jumpy is what do you mean
it's not a word there's so much jumpy oh my god you guys it's called a bouncy castle it's a
jumpy house it doesn't matter is this the hill you want to die on it's actually it's called
bouncy castle not jumpy house that's the fucking bootleg shitty version that's how you know it's
a fake oh that's funny okay I can't do three if I get three in a row then I'm the worst fall guy
streamer on twitch all right I agree with you but that's not gonna happen I'm so scared that
it's going to but it's not going to I can't be the worst fall guys player on twitch what are you
supposed to do why did you do that he knows he knows he's new not the worst fall guys player
on twitch he's screen cheating all right boogers just I just good thing this way I don't have a
camera on thank god in the middle of all this somebody just writes Resident Evil 4 not today
like inception it's just I know it's an inception campaign I'm aware of it now all right let's get
to the final round one that's not good I'll tell you I'm solely responsible for two of our points
I mean after offense and defense like that you're gonna tell me I'm the worst ball guys player on
twitch keep it over here where'd that come from no they why is blue over here is helping them
can we get one I was not the worst player I was responsible for at least three points
where the points go like I'm not the whole team the whole team has to step up and start moving
stuff yeah I'm out of prison I made it made it out an hour ago actually I got an hour and a
half ago a little less than that maybe like 40 minutes all right this is my last one I'm done
after this this is better be a good one needs to get out of jumpy prison yes it's not a bad one
it's not bad unless you are the first person to lose you can if it's 40 people as long as your
number 40 it wasn't a bad round you got in it doesn't matter it only matters when you get down
to the last round you just have to qualify and having good internet qualifies too because if
25 people drop here still counts I don't want to do this one again now how many premium skins do
we have on our team two get in there give me these ones no don't push it back I've just rolled this
dude I just rolled that guy unbelievable I just like necked myself I just like landed on my neck
how did I land how did I just connect I just landed on my neck I'm trying come on we have
an opportunity in 15 seconds here it is dude why the fuck are we always at zero points
if six fucking points I'm not done yellow always loses this is like one of those things where
somebody did the math a decade and a half ago and it was the the alliance had a slight advantage
on the lumber mill battlegrounds map what's it not the lumber what's it called the one with the
capture the flag that's it is it's a very old wow reference not a rathy no war song gulf there it
is yeah I think the alliance had a tiny actually really documented slight advantage on that map
is that yellow in this game for that exact game mode it was hoard what was the actual problem
though what was the issue I was lame and if you play it you probably smell well I guess 13 million
people smell that's probably accurate it's probably way more than that there's probably like 500
million people that smell right now in the world so get what I said oh no I jumped at the wrong
time but it's okay look at all that extra weight this guy knows yeah he knows like I
notice like I turn around he turned around he went right boy he's trying to keep me as the worst
player on twitch mine too can play that game dude see I did that wait it was this guy that wasn't I
can't tell everyone's the same no it's just about being in 40th place and then you just eventually
you get to first place have you guys ever read that book fast rabbit in the slow hair
have you guys ever read that book fast germa and purple alien they talk about that why okay I feel
like a lot of people are having a ton of problems right now why is this one so crappy why are we
just getting fucked with what's going on oh I'm the only one weighing this one down oh
I'm not gonna qualify this guy this guy no I got like grabbed and dumped off the egg
or no I'm not the worst fall guy streamer no it seems fun if you don't win yeah it's because
the going into jumpy house is fun if you it doesn't matter okay if you go in a jumpy house
and you're the first person to go in the jumpy house and the first person to leave the jumpy
house you don't go in and go I won when was the last time you heard somebody open up the doors of
a jumpy house come out and go I won was like a was there a brawl in there like all the other
people in there like unconscious like beat up have a bounce yeah you know what somebody said
bouncy house rumble it should just be a match at like the next live rumble where it's in a
jumpy house and like the shit just gets like popped that's like collapsing out of spoilers
don't worry you had the same idea I did second place lock it in we'll put it in the germ olympics
yeah for those of you that maybe didn't miss uh didn't catch the stream when we talked about this
but we're talking about having a germ olympics where I just get a bunch of like don't mind like
just like you shit-faced friends and we like do like random dumb olympic events
like to balance the egg on your head like okay who's gonna get the gold medal for that one
you like a like shot put floor exercise that was another one we're gonna do floor exercise
synchronized swimming no that's not no that's not an olympic event
bounce egg on your head is not synchronized sleeping synchronized sleeping everyone just
turns off their lights at the same time but well how would you win or isn't the group that sleeps
the longest two people in a sleeping competition they're under the covers and they're just lying
there and there's a timer and what the what the people don't know is that they've both dead
like seven days go by and it's like wow this is the most unbelievable match we've ever seen
and both of them are dead they both died keep cutting back to it like it's been like 12 days
what are you doing I don't know I wasn't even looking I wasn't looking and we're winning
that should tell you something imagine being that guy and being that good probably streaming
the game right now I wouldn't be surprised that's probably a streamer god damn it I got it why do I
have to how many people in here are streamers leave it leave it just defend these ones red's
in trouble no yes I bet you I wonder what your stream is it's probably fucking awesome
no no no over time what do you mean over time get it to double over time no get it dude this
way this way get double over time double over time double over time double over time yellow
just loses every game on that I think like I think actually yellow loses every time
you just stood around wait what am I in this no that's not me I'm not in this if I had to
choose villain red hero blue and piss yellow I'd choose anything but yellow um I'm sorry rage red
blueberry popsicle blue and mustard yellow you got your colors mixed up there point still stands
mustard sucks mustard it does not suck I'm seeing trues here I'm seeing a lot of trues
that bothers me more than it should mustard you guys don't like mustard why what's wrong with it
it's like tangy it's a little sour it's kind of spicy it hits you in the back of the throat
you use just actually like mustard powder like you make like your they make it like a hot mustard
hot mustard is incredible let's do the mustard andy it's great that saying that you like something
makes it your entire identity apparently man I look I'm actually I really like mustard
mustard Martin and you know I got the ps3 the other day ps3 fanboy no I kind of whatever
yeah my my washing machine works pretty well it's a whirlpool whirlpool wall walrus okay oh this one
sucks this is the worst one you cracked the code see those all those streamers can do it very well
not not us we're in the bottom 5000 now oh don't get hit by the next one don't get hit by the next
one wait you gotta wait you gotta wait oh no it's time for bed Jeremy no don't you fucking walrus
andy me I swear to god get off of me get off of me don't touch me don't touch me coward is this it
all right we're gonna be careful we're gonna be careful of coward andy why am I using andy
like oh it's a thing I say oh this one sucks there's not very many people on this one all
right just the deal is just let everybody lose and go you guys must do something crazy not that
nobody knows what to do we made it to the final seven I'm ready come on if it's the tail one I
got it in the bag if it's not the tail one I don't know it's this one oh no okay I'm gonna be quiet
I gotta win my first fall guy hey dick like leave me alone why is everybody such a dick
just cubert this fucking thing damn it I look why did I look at look to chat I don't know why
I was just like what did they say now why that one's so fucking no this game is just a carrot on a
stick nobody wins this like I could just I'm just gonna go to the store and I'm gonna get some
lottery tickets I'm just gonna scratch them I'm not gonna win those either but I'm gonna like
know I'm gonna read on the news about the guy that won 50 grand from the scratch tickets oh
that means I can do it shit I thought like ah it just takes like a lock in concentration and that
I can't do that it's impossible I don't know why I've glanced over with but if you had if
I had a cam on you would have seen like my eyes just fucking glance over you made me waste $20
opening tf2 price what what now are you sure I did that what does that have to do with me
I can't believe I looked uh it takes too much I need to get I need to have three crowns that
I never spend and I just have but I need to I need to get one legitimately one was given for
free one was no get this guy get him get this guy get this guy what am I doing complete it
that guy was waiting at the ledge and pushing people off get him so I'm gonna continue to
scratch scratch tickets this is worse than that this is like getting a scratch ticket and scratching
you don't win any money but one of the spaces that you scratch off says turn this in to get
the next layer of scratch ticket there's an even higher chance that you could win I have to just
keep going back into like the convenience store just trading back and forth until I do that seven
times six times and then this one I might win money but the ticket is free no the ticket was
not free VR lottery tickets that would be what a mess all right I'm locking in I'll see you guys
in a minute it's not a bad idea this guy gets it hey your friend just messed you up bad treadmill
strat stay on it bone shield give me that shit back get out of here hey ah sorry this is a game
that makes me scream and I don't I hate that I'm sorry I'm screaming I need to put a muzzle on
when I play these games you have more viewers now than with Riddick that's all right I mean uh that
does not that surprising to me considering that this game is incredibly popular right now on twitch
and with a bunch of people and has like a million concurrent players and the chronicles of Riddick
Butcher's Bay came out in 2004 and I think four of you played it it doesn't surprise me necessarily
it was still I liked it I thought it was good I thought it was fun it was worth playing I'll put
it that way all right this is the one win or lose win or lose that's it too many people
I did an Aquaman shirt on that was pretty cool I don't know what happened there
what's going on uh I can't keep getting lottery tickets I don't want any more lottery tickets
my car my trunk is full of them they're just crumpled up none of them are winners they all
say great job on them you gotta get the expensive ones this is it this is actually the last one I'm
not doing another one after this I'm leaving I'm done you won't see me until Sunday all right
that's it this is it and I'm gonna win quitting Jerry that doesn't that's not even that doesn't
work that one doesn't work quitting Quincy quitting Quincy quitting Quentin I actually
kind of like quitting Jerry more quitting Quentin Tarantino what quitting when Quentin Tarantino
all right all right I've had enough Quincy Massachusetts yes that is a place oh that's my
big break right there no that thing just fucking came out of nowhere quit Fisto what happened to
the mic what's wrong with it should be fine it should sound good right now what happened
because I'm leaning back in my chair all right maybe if I have like a different voice the whole
time it'll be it'll be better okay how about this ready I'm just gonna keep this on just right here
I'm gonna pretend like it's not on I'm just gonna pitch shift myself like down 20 30 percent
okay here we go mute muted I'm not what I'm not muted I'm gonna prove that I'm not muted
are you ready pee pee poo poo okay told you just say that any of the things that chat will just go
nuts over I'm gonna lose I'm gonna lose I'm gonna rip the ethernet cable up I'm focusing on this one
I'm putting my headphones and I'm putting on fucking I'm putting on like music I'm putting on
some fucking music no not doom it's gotta be something like I'm like Katy Perry firework
is what I'm thinking but I can't play that uh but that same vibe okay is there any royalty free like
Katy Perry like firework music it's a midi version I can't can I actually play a midi version I
haven't heard that in a long time can you do that lawsuit Larry wait can I not play a midi
version of a song can I play wait can I play a lawsuit version of a song oh I midi can I play
a shine the bright just open minds just open minds like the bomb of July
humans can't do that computers can sorry guys I hate to break it to you that was a cover of
Katy Perry firework okay that I'm covering that song am I did it qualify it was too close to the
original I'm gonna get flagged what do you what do you mean too close to the original if you put
that next to the original song I bet you it was so bad that it probably wasn't even like 16 percent
accurate so I don't know if I agree with that like you could run that through the fucking like
lawsuit computer and it'd be like no no then let's hear that the sound what the sound songs like and
what the singer sounds like okay that's what Katy Perry sounds like what does Terminator 5 sound
like oh this is fucking awful this is not even close he might even be singing a different song
he sucks so bad at this no no lawsuit dropped and he what team am I on blue
don't take it from me that's mine at least I got it that's all it matters oh the DMT is kicking in
no not again all right impromptu for impromptu Katy Perry trying to do that note how was that
out of 10 I want I need to know like a four what happens when it's all four
overtime literally four to ten maybe something like that I wasn't paying attention we still want
though all right why is it overtime again why are we getting overtime again if I had some practice
I think I probably could do it if I sat in the mirror for like two weeks and did it I could
probably come really close oh that's that's not this has been on the whole time I sang with this
on didn't I I had this on I sang with that on I had a pitch shift down it was pitched down
it wasn't it had to be it was never on it had the dfx light was on it had to be on all right I need
to pay attention hold on fools you went at the wrong time I couldn't go I was gonna get pushed
off if I had gone if I had gone when the first pass I would have got hit by the thing and knocked
into you guys all want to laugh anyways well I want to hear this don't take it from me that's
this is not the it was pitch shifted down don't take it from me that's firework lawyer version
oh I admit can I play it is picture sit down a tiny bit
that's pretty good that's what people were saying what's wrong with your mic
because it sounded like weird and a little lower and shitty now I get it the fourth of
july part was good but then the firework was like I hit that when you push the horn too hard
and it goes like you don't want to push the horn too hard just enough not over quit don't over
squeeze the horn I can't even see the chat right now now I can shit shit shit shit shit weigh us
down he's ignoring us now I can see you guys guys why did I even jump over I should have just
followed the crowd stop it's been six hours I'm okay don't worry I'm good when I need to stop
I will stop I promise this is probably going to be the last one you keep saying that yeah I know
but this this one really will be the final one if it's the tail one then I'm just gonna leave
I hate this one I I always either do very well or very very poorly on this one focus oh every
single person got hits okay I couldn't even react to that one it's gonna be me 16 17 I made it
b and q you're gonna have to write that another time gonna be made it's gonna be no thought about
it that oh yeah run that back and replay that yeah I went through that that was a blue point
sorry I just almost blew it for you call the umpire and this one right here what
that's right something's wrong with my computer something's wrong with my computer
just go I get I get them good defense yeah something's wrong with my computer
come on one's gonna pop up right here nobody watch that nobody watch I take responsibility
get it just get it dude come on I'll high five you on your way down
didn't get carried that hard uh this is the end right final round or is it one more
yet okay I'm gonna go for it I'm gonna go for it I'm gonna go for the psycho move
everyone's gonna panic in the beginning and not know where to go first I'm just gonna go
no we don't go down what how did he know that
oh you just guessed hacking Henry okay top seven give me I got it all right I need something I need
music or something music's not even fucking good I just like any but what am I gonna do the last
like 10 seconds I'm gonna lose the beach ball at the concert went way too hard way too hard
damn it oh I'm never gonna win one on my own I only won one with internet good I have fiber
all right I'll see you later I'm I can't I gotta go I want to get some lunch I'll see you guys on
Sunday take care guys let's run the credits I really thought I was gonna be able to win one
tonight even though I only played it for like an hour and 20 minutes well we'll see you later
this is not how the music is supposed to be right now I assure you uh what are we gonna do on Sunday
that's you know I gotta that's a good question probably I might I don't know there's a bunch of
GameCube stuff that I want to do I don't know I still have a custom robo is one that I really
wanted to play finish saw super monkey ball that yeah but I'm gonna wait for saw 2 wait for saw 2
custom robo should be a lot of fun Pikmin I want to do that at some point too but I do want to say
thank you to German okay I just freaked out for a second I saw German 995 gave 50 community subs
and I forgot that I did that because we played a completely different game and I said I was about
to say my account may have just got compromised but I remember now that was about that was like
two and a half hours ago three hours ago uh jet snake gave 100 bucks thank you jet snake for the
hundred dollars and then James Morris gave 20 community subs I want to say thanks we also had
a raid come in too Tyler McVicker I missed earlier thanks for the raid appreciate it if you guys
stick around thanks a lot let's see what the credits look like thanks anybody that subs this
channel you are under no obligation but I appreciate it nonetheless and here are all of
you that subs today thanks a lot he's doing the streamer voice yeah I gotta I gotta pull it out
sometimes like Pikmin on Sunday um I don't know if I'm good I don't think I'm gonna play Pikmin on
Sunday I'll tell you why I don't think I'm gonna play Pikmin on Sunday because I don't have Pikmin
on Sunday I don't own it did I buy it before I went on break it was it back here maybe I did
no I don't think I did what about uh Half-Life Alex VR is going to come back once I'm comfortable
here and once I'm really like feeling like I'm ready to go and I feel better and I can comfortably
be in a VR headset for more than three hours or so I want to do Half-Life Alex I want to do
Boneworks I want to do this like 10 new VR games that came out over the last six months and some
stuff that I didn't even do I didn't even finish that I would like to I want to do tilt brush for
a little while that's been I was I did it for like 10 minutes one time I was flipper had an
HDTV there's a lot to do yeah there's a ton of stuff to do so expect VR stuff soon I also want
to bring this up too because this is important I brought this up in pre-stream chat but I want to
kind of make it people aware of it now as of today or last night this work has been started
on a choose your own adventure custom-made game board that we are going to play on stream
completely inspired by sorcery there's going to be a ton of things to do tons of choices trying
to involve people that know kind of about that space and know how to use it and do things like
that there's a couple of really good art that's all folks a couple of really good artists we're
going to be making the artwork for it you know I think you probably know both of them I would
assume you know Ashley is going to be making artwork for it and uh John Silva Star is going
to be the head game essentially maker or the board maker map maker it should be a lot of fun
going to be completely custom-made just a sorcery like choose your own adventure game I'm also
going to hit up some people about it um I want to talk to Arcadium about it because he knows a ton
about this shit get a bunch of input from him because he obviously knows a lot about games
like this so but my point is is that you may hear about people working on this project and I want
you to hear it from the horse's mouth so you might see for instance if Star is talking about it or
if um like John Silva's talking about it then I want you to be like wait oh well hold on what
are you talking about so it's a real thing as of yesterday that's the scariest way to hear anything
general ETA before November that's kind of what we've decided Star is going to be doing a ton of
encounter making and we're going to sit down on a few calls and go over what I really want to
see and obviously he has a bunch of great ideas like everybody else does right but I want it to
be a kind of a blind experience that you guys get to make choices too so imagine sorcery but
it's completely custom-made about around sort of this community and you guys will be able to
participate by voting on what paths we can go down sometimes so before November of this year
is when it's supposed to happen I'll give you more updates when they come it should be a lot
of fun it's official as of yesterday what's on Sunday I'll have to figure that out over the next
few days there are a ton of options so October 31st then well maybe it could be I don't know
I get we can't give a date but Star thinks that this could all be ready at some point
either before November or just barely into November I'll figure it out though but I am
gonna go I'm gonna run I'm gonna run away because I need to eat food I'll see you guys on Sunday
we'll figure out what we're gonna do thanks for watching take care of yourselves have a great
night have a great start to your weekend I'll see you at the end of it and goodbye