Friends, let's make sure we get you in here. If you like the game, the rest of you guys
should be in here.
Um, it's starting. Should we start it? It's starting. Oh, it's already starting.
Alright, so we got about seven people. I think I can still join.
Yeah, but you can still join. So if you go to GTA Free mode and you find our game,
that's where we all are.
Alright, what am I gonna do? First of all, get out of that car. Give me that car!
Alright, nice. Nice. Oh, dude!
I didn't know it was gonna be that long. Alright, everyone's just like
killing each other.
I was expecting like a little more... Oh my god! Chaos!
Alright, somebody get in the car with me.
Alliance. Alright, I absolutely do not want to be in a...
Oh, go on, Bob, get in!
Oh my god, it's total chaos!
Oh my god!
Alright, everybody in, everybody in.
Alright, let's go.
Oh my gosh.
I don't even know who this guy's shooting at, but...
Oh, it's the French guy left.
So, what is it? Everybody versus MLC stealth? Death is happening right now?
Oh my god!
Hey, you guys are my assassins. You gotta take out MLC stealth.
What are you doing?
You just glitched out of the car.
Oh my god, everyone's like glitching.
Alright, hissing gem.
We're gonna do a wraparound here.
Oh no.
Oh, cops. Cops.
Take them out.
Alright, where is everybody?
Oh, this car's stalled.
It's not stalled, it just doesn't have tires.
Alliance, broken.
Alright, let's do...
Alright, you guys wanna...
You guys wanna actually do something?
We should actually do something.
Looks like do something.
Shibby wants to chat.
He sent me one of those, too.
Uh-oh.
Where are...
We're streaming. Can you just...
Oh, you can't alt-tab. We can't alt-tab. Oh no.
We can enter his group chat.
And then tell him we're streaming. Hold on, let me do that.
Yeah, just do that. Tell him we're streaming.
Hello, Shibby. Is it...
Me and Jerma be streaming.
Alright, who's behind me right now?
Who's in this car?
You guys are in both.
Alright, c'mere, c'mere. Let me get in this car.
Let me get in this baby.
Oh, I love how there's no door.
Let me just get in like it's a milk truck.
Who's in the...
I love how Burger Boy's just in an ambulance.
Or what is that? Was it an ambulance or a fire truck?
I don't really remember.
Alright, let's... Hey, let's go get a...
Let's go get a helicopter.
Let's go grab a heli.
Oh my god.
What are you doing?
I'm just gonna sit here.
I don't have to go anywhere.
I can just... Oh my god.
Oh no, he's shooting at me.
That chick killed you.
No, I'm like sitting on top of her with my car.
Oh, she's not having any of that.
Officer, I can't believe what's happening here.
I'll be a good guy.
Hey, officer, c'mere for a second.
Can I like look at your gun? Can I just...
I just saw you wave by.
Oh, you're gonna bring a gun to a point... Oh, c'mon.
You're gonna bring a gun.
Alright, Burger Boy, where are you?
I wanna get in your car.
Who's the pink? Who's the pink blip?
Oh, it's this dude, alright.
He's being chased by police.
Let me get in your whip.
No!
You wanna shoot out? That's what you got.
I'm taking your car, too.
I'm taking this thing to a dealer and I'm selling it.
Oh god, there he is.
Go, go, go, go, go, go, go!
I want everybody...
Everybody to...
MLC City, it's there, it's there.
So everybody come to me on the map.
My car is very destroyed right now.
Everybody come to me on the map.
My car doesn't have any doors on it.
Look at my car.
Nobody kill each other.
Everybody come to where me and MLC City are right now.
The brown blip and the...
What color am I?
I'm orange, I think.
Ah, this cop wants me dead.
I'm gonna let him kill me.
I have no health.
If you guys come to the blip,
I wanna try something.
I wanna see if we can make something weird happen right now.
Will you just kill me or what?
Is that cop shooting at me?
Oh, he is.
What?
Did he just kill me?
Did you just back into me or did that cop shoot me in the face?
He shot you in the face.
Alright, you know what?
Screw this.
Screw this, I don't know.
Look at my statue.
What's it look like?
Is that like a bow?
What the?
Alright, follow me.
We're going to get a helicopter.
Did you just punch me in the face?
I did, but I was accidental.
I didn't mean to.
Alright, let's go.
We gotta get a helicopter.
Hold on.
Look at all these people.
Look at this war going on right here.
Where is Burger Boy in all this?
Let's go get a helicopter.
These cops are doing a horrible job at regulating the laws.
Okay, we gotta spawn.
We got a spawner.
Don't kill us.
Oh yeah, alright.
He's not gonna kill us.
Alright, come with us.
I get so afraid whenever there's a person in front of us.
Please don't shoot us.
Alright, put your parachute on, everyone.
Yeah, make sure you get your parachutes on.
I love how this just...
There is something going on, like a hundred feet away from us.
People are just slaughtering each other.
And I feel like it has something to do with Burger Boy.
Oh, we need a car.
We're all just running with parachutes.
Oh, hey cop.
Ooh, get in this thing.
It only has two seats, I think.
It's alright though.
Oh my gosh, crazy lady.
What just happened to you?
Look, this guy is out of his mind.
I'm outta here.
That guy's out of his mind.
That guy hissing is like just killing people left and right.
I'm running away.
Oh, on our team?
Or not team?
I just saw him like putting out everybody that was in a driver's seat in a car that
was next to us.
I'm going to get a helicopter.
Oh my god, this thing handles like...
Where are you driving?
I...
I have it on my GPS.
I just bought my GPS from Walgreens.
I have cops on me?
No, I don't.
I guess I do.
Alright.
Look at this.
Look at these people just killing each other.
I'm going to get a helicopter and then it's going to be game over.
Again, I'm going way too fast.
This always ends very badly.
Anytime I go this fast, it never ends well.
Ever.
You never like find like a nice safe jump to go off of.
Oh, here we go.
Out of control.
Why did I do that?
There was no reason to do that.
I'm okay.
The cops are still behind me.
Dude, I felt like I was just on a bike.
Alright, I gotta add this guy so we can get in.
Jacob Watson.
Absolutely.
Come on in, man.
Come on in the game.
Oh, my god.
Oh my god.
No!
Get away from me!
Oh.
Oh, Jacob's in.
Is he?
Who is singing right now?
Who is singing?
Wait.
What is that?
How come there's like people talking?
Oh my gosh.
Alright, let's go.
Burger Boy, get in.
Oh, it's Burger Boy.
Quick.
Alright.
Is that cop just shot one of us?
Okay, which way are we going?
We're going to get a helicopter.
Is it off this cliff right here?
Okay.
Alright.
I'll be the navigator.
Go straight.
Go straight until you can't go straight anymore.
Burger Boy, I love how you were in an ambulance just like driving a hundred miles per hour.
One of our tires is blown.
It's going to end very poorly.
Alright.
Don't like drive us into a cliff.
There we go.
Why did you get out?
They're so far away.
Alright, so still.
Ready at the count of three?
I know where we're going.
We're going to...
Oh, you know where we're going.
You're taking us to like the...
What just happened?
I love how I'm in the back.
I'm your chauffeur.
Alright.
Just take...
I'm getting out.
I don't trust you.
No.
What?
I don't trust you.
No, no.
Get in.
I thought you were just going to drive off the edge.
Alright.
Okay.
Go.
I don't even have like my headphones plugged in.
People...
You guys are probably like...
Oh my...
What?
Oh my god.
It's hissing gems.
Get them.
What an intense shootout this is.
No!
That guy is not having a good day today.
He just wants...
Everyone's shooting each other.
I got to plug my headphones in.
Because I think I might be reverbing.
Because I was just too excited to play.
Where are my headphones?
I got to find them.
Everyone just wants everyone dead.
I think about it every night and day.
Bring my wings and fly away.
I believe I can soar.
I see you running through that open door.
Oh god.
Did I crash?
Oh no!
I crashed!
No I didn't.
I'm good.
I'm here.
I thought I crashed.
But I'm good.
Oh I got to get my headphones on.
Alright.
We're good to go.
So everyone's in the airport.
Now it's pretty much just a race to who gets the helicopters.
Sorry.
I'm sorry.
Operation Dodge.
Oh give me this P90.
Oh man.
It is a sad day for anybody coming close to me.
Alright.
I'm safe.
You know what?
I got to get a car.
I got to get a cup.
Hey.
How you doing?
Please don't kill me.
Okay.
He ran by me.
Good.
Hey.
This guy's idea of fun is getting inside the helicopter and shooting all the other helicopters
so nobody else can get in.
Oh you piece of crap.
Alright.
Operation take out the guy in the helicopter.
Operation take out helicopter flyer.
Operation rocket launcher and dispose of.
I got in the helicopter.
I'm going to get over there.
I'm on my way.
I'm en route.
Break that window.
Oh this brings back memories when I smashed my face on that guy.
He's not even moving.
What is that guy doing?
Wait.
What?
Where am I going?
Aren't the helicopters...
Oh they're right there.
They're right there.
Sorry for the...
It's a good tactic man.
That's alright.
Alright.
Who thinks I'm going to make it underneath this plane?
I do.
Woo hoo.
Give me, give me, give me, give me, give me a helicopter.
Please don't die.
I am so addicted to...
Oh my god.
I need to crouch.
How do I crouch?
Oh my god.
What a psycho.
What is he doing?
What are you doing?
My helicopter.
What is happening to it?
Why can't it just stay flying?
What the...
Are you in a helicopter?
Where are you?
Hey dude.
Stop crouching.
Run.
All these helicopters are destroyed.
Oh dear god.
This is bad.
This is so bad.
I'm going to die the second I get into this.
Oh run away.
I'm not even going to go in that dude.
I'm going to die the second I get in there.
Oh my god.
I'm still alive.
It's my chance.
Get in.
Go.
Go you slug.
Oh yeah.
It's time for copter wars.
Oh my god.
No.
Get up.
Oh that was...
I just really had a heart attack.
Those helicopters suck.
Oh my god.
Those helicopters suck for being a helicopter.
Alright I'm good.
This just sucks.
I'm good.
I'm alright.
Yeah what's going on?
I feel like I'm driving a...
Alright let me aim it down to the ground.
Any unsuspecting people I can smash into?
There's cops down there.
Barrage.
Unleash the fury.
Ah.
I'm not killing anybody.
You know what?
I'm going kamikaze.
Oh my god.
Whoever this pink dot is.
You picked a bad day to be a pink dot.
You picked a bad day to be a pink...
Oh I'm going to throw up dude.
Really.
I'm really going to puke.
Did like the controls change or is this lag?
Oh no.
How did I...
But I'm like 4 but flying is...
Well that's how we get out of a helicopter and walk off the front and...
Hey come pick me up.
Alright.
Oh my god.
I think papa got a brand new bag here.
No.
I'm such a bad shot.
I was like landing.
Oh you were trying to pick me up?
Oh I'm sorry.
I thought you were like...
You were shooting missiles at me.
I was scared.
Because you shot a rocket at me.
Alright.
I'm conserving the rest of this ammo.
Let's get out of here.
We're like being shot at to death.
If that killed me I was going to be so angry.
Everyone just spawns and pulls out pistols and you just start shooting each other.
This is so like unorganized.
I'm going to kill this guy.
Oh no.
Get him.
Oh I could have sworn.
Do I blame Tom Brady or anybody for Wes Welker?
No.
I mean the Patriots didn't really have that.
It was a pretty much string of luck that they got into the playoffs to begin with.
Good to see them get that far.
But yeah go Celtics.
That's all I got to say.
Alright where's Burger Boy?
Burger Boy is the number one target for me.
I think he is...
No you're brown.
You're brown.
He's green.
You're orange.
Alright so stream Burger Boy is target number one.
Look at how mad he is.
I want the whole stream.
Let's see if we can make him rage quit.
You guys suck.
For some reason I want to save Cordobomb.
Get in.
Get in Burger Boy.
We're making it out of here alive.
Get in Cordobomb.
Me and Burger Boy are going to escape.
I actually you know Burger Boy.
Oh no.
Oh I got the P90 man.
How is he?
I just unloaded 70 bullets into that guy.
What a champion.
So are we still having a war against Burger Boy?
It doesn't seem like that.
I'm trying to get in a helicopter.
I say we I mean you guys.
Oh my god.
Stay with it.
What was that?
What on earth was that?
That was ridiculous.
Was that a rocket?
Holy crap.
Oh no I want to live.
I want to live.
Get me on like the Italian scooter.
Sick drivings.
Oh here we go.
Get me on this bike.
Burger Boy you want to get in some helicopters?
God ball.
Oh no.
The stream is counting my deaths.
I'm up to 11.
Where'd you go?
Where are you?
Try Burger Boy.
Hey get on this bike.
That's a place I don't want to be at.
Let me get in with you Burger.
Hey wait I would enjoy the fun too.
There's another helicopter.
You can't get in.
I'm trying to hit my head on the blades.
Oh hey let me just get in this helicopter.
Like hit my face on the blades.
Just go go go go go go go go.
Go without me.
We got a boat.
Oh my god.
I'm getting out of this.
Burger Boy that's going to blow up.
That's going to blow up.
What are you doing still driving?
RPG watch out.
That was so perfect.
Oh my god thank god this is being recorded.
Because if I didn't get that on tape I would have been so bad at myself.
Look how destroyed he just got.
He was like trying so hard to stay alive.
And he just died.
You can see like the intensity in his like jump out.
Hold on Burger Boy.
Oh my face.
Hey let me get in that car with you Burger Boy.
Alright Jacob let me get on the back of that scooter.
Oh you bastard.
I was trying to get on the back.
Everybody that got to see that.
That was one of the funniest things I've seen.
Alright let's go.
Oh wait.
Alright get in.
Get in.
Get in the car.
Get in the car quick.
Alright who's...
Oh the cop's on you.
Okay.
Let's go back to the airfield.
Oh man.
Look at this guy.
That guy just got robbed by a cop.
We almost sandwiched that dude.
Let's move.
Alright let's get in this helicopter.
Oh look at that perfect pull up.
I got a feeling this guy might turn into a traitor.
I don't know.
I'm scared.
Oh my god.
Did you just run into the helicopter?
Alright get in.
Oh you flipped it.
You flipped it.
Let me like flip it back.
Can I like get back in?
I'm going the other way.
Go away.
These cops are on me.
Get...
No I'm going to die from the police.
Damn it.
Helicopters.
I was trying to...
Can you like get in and flip it over?
I want to get in the helicopter and I want to just peacefully just fly down, watch some
TV, read a book when I'm parachuting down.
That's all I want.
That's all I care about.
I just want to parachute out of the helicopter.
That's all I want to do.
Let me aim out this window.
Get out of town.
Oh my god.
That guy's a shotgun.
You pulled up in front of the guy with the shotgun.
Oh that's more...
Chaos.
Pure chaos.
All right get us to the airfield quick.
We got people, we got bogeys on us.
What's going on?
He's pulling me out of the car.
He is pulling me out of the car right now.
Gourd bomb, let me in.
I'm leaving you guys.
I'm getting the hell out of here.
Thanks burger boy.
Appreciate that.
All right get in.
Hurry up.
Oh my god.
They are unloading on us.
Geez.
I love how this is just a race.
This is just who can get in the helicopter.
What is that cop doing?
Freak.
He's a bad guy.
He's aiming his gun at us.
Oh man look at this chaos.
We got a fight going on over here boys.
He's got an RPG doesn't he?
I'm getting out of there now.
Oh wait burger boy you're dead?
I'm like sitting in the car with you.
Who killed you?
All right we're at the airfield waiting for a spawn.
Come on.
Spawn a copter.
They're not in the air are they?
Oh man.
Everyone really likes shooting.
Nobody just wants to run cars into each other.
Where are these helicopters?
I'm taking cover behind.
I know someone's going to come and just smash into us.
Oh yeah.
Take the cover.
I'm stuck on the door right now.
Oh man.
Oh no.
No.
All right.
At least I would have died from that explosion.
If I didn't die from that explosion I would have died from the...
You know what?
I'm going this way.
There's police helicopters here.
I got a plan.
You know I have a plan and it's going to work.
Oh it is absolutely going to work.
Maybe it won't.
Probably not.
Run.
I'll take the cop car.
For those of you asking in the stream this is Episodes from Liberty City.
It's the expansion of GTA IV.
We're playing the Ballad of Gay Tony.
And if you want to join...
Did you just see that helicopter crash?
That was...
Who is in this helicopter is the real question.
So if you want to join, my name on here is Jermaw with four A's.
And just join the game I'm in once you send a friend request.
You should be able to.
L-C-P-D.
Oh my goodness.
That is a missile coming at us.
I'm getting out.
Of course I have three stars.
Fantastic.
Alright let's set up shop here.
I'm going to add Zeus.
Where are you Zeus?
Oh my god.
I'm in the middle of inviting somebody to the game and I just hear a crash and you're
next to me.
Okay.
What am I doing?
I'm just like creeping.
Now I'm waiting for a copter.
I'm waiting for a helicopter.
There's no way I'm going to get it.
Oh my god.
Alright I'm getting in.
Look at all these people everywhere.
I'm going to do plan B. Look at the mini map.
Look at how many police are here.
Look at the mini map.
That's ridiculous.
There's a lot of them.
Oh I just barely.
I just barely almost got in there.
Alright new plan.
I'm doing plan B.
I am absolutely.
What was plan B?
Plan B is to go get the helicopter.
Oh here comes the SWAT team.
Good thing they're not coming after me.
How tall.
Somebody's already doing plan B.
What did he say it was?
To go base jump and go float over here.
Who is this?
Is nobody even in here?
I'm taking this.
Give me that.
Give it to me.
Get out of there.
Oh man that was bad.
I'm sorry Mr. Ambulance Driver.
You just try to help people.
I'm such a bad person.
I'm sorry.
Alright turn that off.
That's going to get annoying.
Alright let's see.
I need to go right here.
Why am I flipped over?
I just rammed you.
What?
You're on fire.
Oh my god you're on fire.
No.
Get away from that car.
Give me this one.
No.
Give me this.
Alright.
Did I get him?
No I didn't.
Come here.
This dude's lagging.
I got away.
Alright.
Let's see if the plan works.
Come pick me up.
Turn around.
Alright.
Come here.
I wasn't going to run into you.
I promise.
I'm in the back seat.
Alright.
Driving Miss Daisy.
Driving Miss Stealth.
Hopefully this building is tall enough so we can base jump off of it and fly into the
action.
That's a right hand.
Oh jeez.
Please exit the vehicle and watch your hands and feet.
Thank you for riding in German the worst car driver in the world.
Thank you so much.
No don't shoot me.
Oh you're going to blow it up.
I see.
No I'm shooting all the tires.
Woodadelic this will be on YouTube.
It will.
The whole thing will be on YouTube.
Probably tomorrow.
Alright.
We're going to get a new car.
We need a new car.
Somebody's already doing the parachute.
Where are the cars?
I found a motorcycle.
Oh jeez.
Is this the guy?
Why is he...
Oh get this guy.
Shoot him.
Shoot this guy.
Kill him.
Alright.
I'm right there.
We're right here.
Oh here's the guy that was shooting us.
Let's back into him.
Argh.
I will run you over as many times as I have to.
Hahaha.
Alright.
Let's uh...
I'm getting out of here.
I'm going to do that base jump.
It's going to happen.
Corner.
Here we go.
Oh this is a really small building.
This is going to...
Is there a taxi I can call?
Actually that's not that small.
I don't think they have taxis in...
Aww.
Dude.
Hurry hurry hurry.
Alright.
How high up am I?
Pretty damn high.
Alright.
Where's the action going on?
Over here.
So I've got to jump off this side.
And...
Let's go.
Open.
Alright.
Let's see if I can like...
Float into the madness.
That guy's a helicopter.
Float on the helicopter, boy.
Woohoo.
I'm sure that'll be pretty easy.
Ah.
Look at how relaxing this is.
Just floating around.
Relaxing with my friends.
Oh hey stealth.
I made it.
That was fun.
Woohoo.
Let's go do that again.
Except this time.
I want to get on this.
I want to get on the bike.
I...
I'm trying to...
I just flew.
What?
These are right next to me.
This guy got...
This guy...
He was still in the riding position.
He jumped up and he was like, oh nothing's going on here, I'm just like still riding
the bike.
What the hell was that?
Oh I love how many glitches are in this game.
Oh jeez.
Oh my god.
I can't control it.
Who wants to play baseball?
We've got enough people to play baseball.
We've got like...
There's enough people in here.
Alright, I'm going to be the pitcher.
I'll be the batter.
Let's play grenade baseball.
Do we have any grenades?
I'm the batter.
Alright, ready?
Ready.
So I'm going to throw the ball.
Alright, did you hit it?
Oh I hit it.
Boom.
Oh look at...
Wow.
It went so far.
Look at how far it went.
Around first base.
Go to second.
Oh no.
I got to throw him out.
Oh I didn't get him.
Oh no.
The ball got thrown in.
Oh he's still safe.
Here you are.
You got a triple.
Alright.
Ghost man on third.
Oh okay.
Wait.
No.
You have to leave the car.
Oh.
But it's a ghost man.
Yeah.
But then you have to get in the car and drive to home plate.
So you get over there.
So you get over...
Someone in the stream just wrote, the crowd goes wild.
Alright.
So here we go.
Ready?
I pitched it.
Alright.
Now go run to first base.
Oh.
Missed.
Oh god.
There's another guy here.
We're playing baseball, dude.
Oh it's Zeus.
Oh yeah.
We're playing baseball.
Do you want to play baseball?
Alright.
My runner got home.
I got a single.
Zeus, you're up.
Alright.
Baseball is over.
I win.
Because you didn't get home.
What's my...
What do I win?
I just shot you in the toe.
Alright.
Run home.
To your real home.
What?
Is that a Bad News Bears joke?
Alright.
Hey.
Oh.
Let's get in the tanker.
Please tell me those explode.
Please tell me those.
Please tell me.
No.
Don't shoot it.
Is it connected?
No.
It's not connected.
I don't even think we can connect it.
This is on GTA San Andreas.
They definitely explode though.
For sure.
Oh.
Let's see if I can connect them.
Nah.
You can't connect them.
This is going to be a massive...
You're going to die.
You're going to die in like two seconds.
The fire is gone.
Oh my god.
Look at this.
Burger Boy to save the day.
He did...
Wow.
What a pro.
Let me get in.
No.
I want to get in this.
Dude.
He just flipped.
He just flipped that car.
That's like a five million pound car.
And he just like flipped it over.
I still have my parachute, right?
I hope so.
I love how you just came out of nowhere Burger Boy.
That was like amazing.
I can't believe that thing flipped my anchor.
That's why I laughed so hard.
Oh Burger Boy.
You're going to waste all your ammo.
All right.
Ready?
Here we go.
I am going to jump out of the...
I'm going to parachute.
I'm going to parachute and see how long I can parachute.
So keep coming up.
Shoot.
Oh shoot.
All the people down there.
Wow.
We are up really high.
I think this is as high as we can go.
Thanks Burger Boy.
Woohoo.
Oh yeah.
Thanks Burger Boy.
Woohoo.
So I'm going to watch and see where Burger Boy goes.
So I'll tell you a story while I'm parachuting.
It's like story time.
So one time.
Let's see how long it takes before I can finish this story.
One time I was at Halloween.
I was having a good time as a Ninja Turtles.
And the story is really going nowhere.
I just want to try and talk and see how long it takes for me to land.
Oh more talking.
I love all these people.
I feel the same way.
Whoever was just talking in a different language.
Let's...
Woohoo.
Who is even talking?
I just heard a language I am not familiar with.
Wow.
So who thinks...
Place your bets.
Am I going to die right now?
Am I going to die right now when I land?
We'll find out.
Somebody is now chasing me.
And I have a feeling they are going to take me out.
Oh it's Bert.
It's Bert.
I don't think he died.
I think he's still alive.
I thought you killed him.
Oh, I killed him.
I'm going way too...
Why is this?
Dude, can you imagine if you landed from that high up?
If you landed, like, flat on your stomach?
Dude, your insides would just explode.
Oh, God.
That would be so horrible.
You would not want to be at that crime scene cleaning that up.
What the hell was that?
That guy just...
Okay, I'll take the car.
Fine.
Oh, that guy's got an automatic gun.
Goodbye.
All right.
I'm going to play in cinematic mode for the remainder of the game.
Look at this, like, oh, it's a trailer.
I wonder how long I can survive.
Oh, my God.
I hope everyone in the stream just saw that.
I was trying to, like, hit you.
Dude, on my screen, you just...
How am I still...
I can't play this game for more than an hour, man, and my head starts to hurt from laughing
at, like, the nonsense.
Michael Bay present...
What?
What the...
What is that?
What is this?
What happened to us?
What is going on?
Why...
Is there a hacker in here?
Why am I, like, a teddy bear, like, hippopotamus?
Why...
Why are we, like, a parade float?
Hey, get in.
Get in.
Get in here.
We got to get another person in this car.
Zeus is right above us.
Zeus, get in this car.
Take the other seat in here.
Somebody please get in here so we can have, like, a sodding can parade float.
Zeus is trying to land right now.
Hold on.
All right, let's just try...
Oh, jeez.
He's going out of control.
Let's just try.
When I turn...
When I...
All right.
Before I...
Before I get into uncontrollable laughter.
When I turn, watch the heads go back into the car stalled.
All right, get...
We don't have any weapons.
Hey, guys, it's Paulie the hippopotamus.
Let's play Hungry Hungry.
Let's play Hungry Hungry Hippos.
Ready?
Just hit control.
Come here.
Wait.
So I'm going to stand right here.
You stand opposite me.
And then just keep hitting control over and over again.
Hungry Hungry Hippos.
Ready?
It's Hungry Hungry Hippos.
Hungry Hungry Hippos.
Oh, my God.
Hey, Zeus is right here.
All right, Zeus.
Oh, Zeus is a normal human.
Why is he normal?
He must have died.
Oh, well.
All right.
Get in this new car.
Get in this, like, Camry.
Oh, my God.
It just pulled up.
What is happening?
What is...
How does this happen?
Are you guys in?
Look at our heads.
All right.
Watch the heads when I turn.
This is the funniest damn thing ever.
I've got to get some speed.
Hold on.
Watch the heads.
Here we go.
Ready?
All right.
Come on.
Get out of this mode.
I don't want this mode.
I want, like, the head mode.
I don't want to go too fast because...
Oh, it's the spirit.
Look at...
Ready?
Oh!
How do I keep glitching out?
I want to see, like, the heads tilt.
This is the dumbest thing ever.
How does this happen?
I don't know.
There must be an advent in here.
Look at the heads.
Look.
We look like Barney.
I feel like...
All right.
Look at what this looks like right now.
This looks like America's, like, most wanted videotapes.
And it's like, what kind of criminals are we?
You know what I mean?
Like, look at the criminals driving away in their crazy costumes.
Like, they're trying to hide their identities.
Wait.
What button do you press?
Cinematic.
That's V until you get there.
All right.
Here's the real kicker.
Oh, go on automatic control.
All right.
I'm going to laugh uncontrollably at this.
All right, Zeus.
Get in.
Get in here.
America's most wanted.
Like, the hungry, hungry hippos.
They robbed a liquor store.
It was like a helicopter like...
Oh!
No!
What was...
Did he just kill us all?
Yeah.
Oh, now I don't have my hungry, hungry hippo head.
Oh, no.
That was awesome.
Oh, my goodness gracious.
Give us back our hungry, hungry hippos.
This is so funny.
I'm going to laugh uncontrollably at this.
All right.
Zeus, get in.
Get in here.
America's most wanted.
Like, the hungry, hungry hippos.
They robbed a liquor store.
Oh!
What was...
That was so funny.
All right.
So...
Oh, you should...
Don't shoot at the tires.
That's our only vehicle.
Oh, I think that's a good note to end on, to be honest.
Seriously, that was...
I don't know how that happened.
There was probably an admin in here or something.
I have no idea, but that was absolutely hysterical.
Hippo burgers.
All right.
Let me get on that bike.
Wait, wait.
Here's how we're going to end it.
Oh, my gosh.
Here's how we're going to end it, guys.
Ready?
Everybody.
Everybody get into where we're standing right now.
Boxing match.
And the last man standing wins.
So don't...
Not yet.
No, not yet.
Take the knife.
Put the knife away.
So everyone get to where we're standing.
No knives.
Only boxing.
So if we all...
If we...
Ready?
This is how it's going to end.
Make sure we get everybody here.
So this is how...
Wait.
Not yet.
Burgaboy just puts me in the face.
All right.
Wait.
Burgaboy.
Stop it.
One.
Two.
Boxing fight.
Go.
Jeremy, you just disappeared.
I'm over here punching people.
Oh, I'm going down.
I'm going down.
No, I want to run.
I want to get on top of the car.
Like jumping.
Punch.
People are like running away.
Oh, it's because they're low on health.
I love how nobody's even grunting or talking.
So it's just like silence.
Ready?
Like...
They're just like...
Dude.
Gang up on Burgaboy.
Don't let him win.
Don't let Burgaboy win.
Gang up.
Burgaboy's dead.
Oh, I'm dead.
He has full health.
And I've none.
Oh, did MLC Stealth just win?
No.
Did this guy win?
Oh, and you're a winner.
Hissinggem2788.
Congratulations.
You won the punching round.
And you know what would win?
A knife to the face.
Oh, now they're bringing out guns.
Oh, man.
That was awesome.
That was amazing.
Oh, so if you missed it, if you missed some of it, we've been playing for just about an
hour now.
Oh, if you missed, if you just got here or something, this is all going to be on YouTube
tomorrow.
So...
There were some hysterical things that happened in this.
Like if you just joined us, you're going to want to watch it tomorrow.
What the heck?
All right, it's time for some QWOP.
That's how I pronounce drama.
So what was my final death count?
25?
Oh, God.
Wait, does it say?
No, they've been counting in the stream.
I'm just looking over and glancing over and seeing.
All right, thanks a lot for playing, guys.
If you played, I'll probably do this again.
This was actually pretty damn fun.
So thanks for coming.
If you joined into the game, into the session.
So now we're going to play some QWOP.
And yeah, thanks so much, guys.
Oh, that was a shot in the face.
Pull up.
How do I get out of here?
All right, it's going to be a black screen until I get QWOP loaded.
Q-W-O-P, QWOP, QWOP, QWOP, QWOP.
Hey, yo.
I love Liberty City.
QWOP is a flash game.
It's a flash game where you have to use QW and then OP to run.
And it is incredibly difficult.
So screens, actually screens probably not going to go black.
It's probably going to be just my background.
Just my desktop background.
All right, let me pull up some QWOP.
Let me make sure the stream thing is there.
Oh man, that was funny.
That was so damn funny.
Q-W-O-P, QWOP, QWOP, QWOP.
I'm going to make it so it's just the QWOP screen because that's more fun that way.
Black screen.
Ah!
Screen region.
The QWOP screen.
Hello, ladies and gentlemen.
How are you?
And let's play.
So the goal, let me put myself a goal for this match, this round.
Slug.
I'd say 10 meters.
I'm going to try and slug my way to at least 10 to 30.
Here we go.
Hold on a second.
I've got to get my mixer here.
It's going to be a little too loud.
There we go.
All right, let's move.
Yeah, TF2, I will do a TF2 stream next week, absolutely.
But tonight, I was just running, I had a lot of work I had to do, so I just wanted to unwind
with a little bit of GTA, and that was a lot of fun.
And can I play League of Legends?
That was one of the questions somebody was asking.
Me and Stealth actually have played League of Legends.
For like five minutes.
I'm just not that good, though.
I'm such a noob at that game.
Oh no, god!
No, that didn't count.
That didn't count.
This will, though.
Oh, come on.
Co-op.
I just finished GTA, Mr. ADZY.
If you want to check out my YouTube channel tomorrow, it'll be there, the whole thing.
Go!
I'm actually starting to kind of understand how this works.
Oh my god, how did I still...
Wow.
Okay, I'm good.
And Diablo, I'm going to be...
For those of you guys that are still here, Diablo 3, I'm going to be doing a lot of live
streaming of that game.
A lot of Diablo 3 streams are going to happen.
So be on the lookout for those.
All right, I've got to get to 30.
Come on.
30 meters.
Use your slug powers from the slug god of sluggington.
You know what I want?
I want to go to like a track in real life and see, like just hopefully I'd see one guy just
doing this.
Hey, what are you doing, man?
I'm just training for the Olympics.
Like oh, good.
You'll probably get there.
Keep trying, man.
Like just like slugging, like go, go, go, go, go.
30 meters.
I'm going to make it.
Oh, speaking of grandpa, the grandpa season one premiered tonight.
I'm going to make a tweet about it, but it's on Machinima Respawn.
Go check it out.
It's on Machinima Respawn right now.
Season two, episode one, the montage.
Go check it out.
I got a 10 out of 10.
I got a 10.
Oh, 30 meters.
I did it.
I did my goal.
Now I can...
Whoa.
Now I'm going to try and actually run.
Put it up.
No.
Don't go backwards.
So yeah, that's going to be it, guys.
Thanks for coming.
Thanks for sticking around, for watching GTA.
That was awesome.
And again, if you just came and you were like, oh no, it just ended.
It's going to be there tomorrow on my YouTube channel.
So yeah, I will catch you guys all soon.
One last try.
Come on.
Last try.
I'm going to actually make it.
No, come on.
No, stay with it.
One more.
No, one more after that.
I got in a groove last time.
I don't know how I got in that groove.
I'm like tiptoeing now.
There we go.
I had it.
One more.
You got to pull.
You know, the left leg has to come down.
Oh, that's it.
I can't do it.
So yeah, thanks everybody so much for coming.
Thank you so, so, so, so much.
And I will catch you guys next time.
Actually, stay tuned tonight to my channel because there's going to be a...
There's going to be Minecraft, a new Minecraft video going up tonight.
Because I got a lot of requests for more of that Woosh game theme.
The theme...
What am I talking about?
Woosh.
Why can't I not say this?
I'm like having like a seizure.
Woosh theme park.
That's going to go up tonight.
So thank you so much for watching, guys.
I'll see you guys all next time.
And of course, take care, everybody.
See ya.
Bye.