Hey. Oh, good afternoon. How are you? How have you been? Good. Good. Excellent. It's very good to
hear. Today's a very special day. Today, we're going to be doing bro versus bro with Ludwig.
Yes, I'm very aware of our previous bets that we had. Sure those are going to be addressed on
camera. It'll be a fun day after that, after bro versus bro. You need to do a tweet? I will.
We're going to jump back into Elden Ring. I don't think this is going to take more than
two hours. So right when we say goodbye to Ludwig, we're going to hop into Elden Ring
and go for it. See if I can get to the end. He's addicted. I want to play it.
I got to call Ludwig by the way. Just give him a buzz in a second here.
One sec. Bro versus bro. You know, the competition between two bros.
We each pick a few games that we know that we're pretty good at or activities and we compete.
Whoever wins has to tweet themselves out in a in a mega milk shirt, right?
Oh, let me tell you something. From now on, bets are going to be very, very like benign and boring.
No more like, oh, you're gonna take your shirt off and drink milk upside down while you shit
your pants and tweet it. No, no, no, no, no, no. How about like, I don't know. How about like,
donate to church? How about like, hold a note for five seconds? That's like such a, no,
it can't be like that. It can't be like, that's like Nickelodeon. How long can you hold the note
for? Like, oh wow, you did it for five seconds. That was worth it. Fuck church. I just, I'm not
saying donate to church. I'm just saying like just, I use a random noun, okay? That was the
first noun that popped up in my head. I haven't been to church in probably like fucking 15 years
or something, guys. I don't know. A heretic. Which way do you want it? Religious streamer or
not religious streamer, huh? Let me tell you something. Aliens dropped us off. Aliens dropped
us off in a fucking care package here, okay? Sorry to blow everybody's, blow everybody's mind
here on this. Let's see what Ludwig has to say about that. You good? Heretic. I don't know. Who
knows? Do you don't know? Nobody knows anything. We could be amorphous blobs that evolved or some
alien could have shot a fucking cannon out into the galaxy and we just ended up here. Start your
stream. No, you start your religion. I don't know why I said start your stream. Are you Amish? What
does Amish have to, wait, what are you talking about? What does Amish have to do with that?
Amish people don't believe that aliens shot us out of a cannon. Why are you saying Amish?
He's streaming from rocks and twigs. I am not, actually. You're an alien? I don't know what the
hell we are. Millions of years of cells that have evolved. But why? You know, okay, we're getting
way too into this now. Let's bro versus bro with Ludwig, right? We don't have to ask the why.
We don't start a bro versus bro stream where I start asking questions about humanity and why we're
here. Maybe, well, should we throw Ludwig a curve ball? Right when he answers the phone. Why are we
here? He says. Why are we here? Ludwig. You know Ludwig. He'll be like, oh, play bro versus bro,
of course. And then he'll go and do the intro. God damn, is it a good intro? That's the thing.
A lot of people, you don't understand. A good intro is a huge deal. If you got a catchy intro
on YouTube, huge fucking deal. Guaranteed, guaranteed success. For instance, I'll give you
an example. Hello, everybody. Welcome to Team Fortress 2. My name is, I don't even know,
I can't even do my own intro. What is it? Hello, ladies and, what is it? No, no, no, no, no. I've
heard JermaCraft so many times. Hey, what's going on? Hey, I got it, I got it. Hey, what's going on,
buddy? Jerma here with the Team Fortress 2 gameplay commentary. I would, right? You know what I'm
saying? He never left. He's still got it. It's so weird to think that that was still that long ago.
It's weird because that feels so long ago, but it feels like it was a week ago at the same time.
When I think back to when I was 25, I was like 24, 25. I feel like I'm so, like it's so long ago.
Yeah, Team Fortress 2. All right, I think we are. I didn't even tweet. Fuck, did I? No, I didn't. Hold
on. Let me tweet. I'm going to say, bro versus bro. Bro versus bro. Happening now. Bro versus
should it be bro versus bro versus Ludwig? No, that makes it sound like there's three people.
You're pretending to be young? I don't think so. I think you guys call me out on old
dated shit that I say all the time. I get question marks for references on TV shows that are like
six or seven plus years old. I'm not talking 30 years ago. We're talking like references that
are like five to 10 years ago. That's how I know I'm old. Yeah, I mean, I made an Andy Griffith
reference and nobody got that, which was annoying. That wasn't that long ago. That was like 70 or 80
years ago. All right, bro versus bro against Ludwig. No, that makes it sound like it's a tag team
against Ludwig. How do I say this? With Ludwig. No, that makes it sound like that Ludwig is like
an accessory to that stream. Not like it's not me versus... How do I say this? Featuring.
How about starring? Starring is kind of better, isn't it? Bro versus bro. Starring Ludwig.
That's so... That's so boring. With special... No, I'm the guest today. This is Ludwig's bro versus
bro. I'm a participant. How about bro versus bro? Let's go. That's easy. Okay, that's fine.
And I'm gonna add Ludwig. Yeah, that's fine. And remember, it's on dwitch.tv. Ludwig's currently
trying to set up one of the games that we're gonna play. I'm just gonna chill for a little bit.
Don't worry, today's gonna be a long one. Like I said, after we are done with bro versus bro,
I'm gonna go into Elden Ring. It'll be a long one. I don't know if it's gonna be too long,
but it'll be long enough. Okay, there we go. Yeah, there. That's a good tweet.
How the heck are you, huh? How are you? Yeah, so I think this is gonna work. Like I said,
we both picked three games, right? So we both have three games that we have chosen.
I can tell you my games. And it's depending on if Ludwig can get one to work. We might have to
pivot to something else. One of the neutral games. Should I leak it? Did he leak it? Did he already
talk about it? He didn't. All right. No, no. He didn't? Okay. He did. He already leaked it. He
leaked it? Okay. Well, if he leaked it, then whatever. We can just talk about it. He said
house flipper and battleship. Yeah, we were trying to figure out how to do house flipper competition.
And I was thinking is we both have to pick the same small house and flip it in like 10,
like 15 minutes. And whoever has the cooler house wins. I don't even know how we would
vote on that, though. Do we just do we just look like do a walkthrough of each other's houses and
just be like, Yeah, dude, you won't have it has more sale price. That's true. But the problem with
sale price and house flippers, it feels really random. It feels incredibly random. So it could
be I'm not sure you need a neutral party to come in. We have I wonder if we can we get a neutral
party to look every kind of funny. I have another couple games too. And one of them, by the way.
Oh, I am I'm locked in to be the victor. Like, it's almost guaranteed. I know this because Ludwig
didn't even know what this game was until three days ago. I've got like a decade of experience
in this game. He didn't even know what the game was. 48 hours ago. It's over on that one. Okay,
that's it. I'm just I picked that one to make sure that I could at least win one game among us. Why
would I play? I have no experience in among us. Why would I play among us? And then I got another
one that I have heard. I've heard that he's pretty good at. But I don't know. I don't know
in the scenario that he'll be put in if he'll be a good if he's gonna be all right. I have a lot
of experience with this particular thing too. We need a face cam. Oh, there'll be a face cam today.
Oh, yeah. You betcha. They say you betcha. Let's turn the intro music down. That's better.
So just chilling. Oh, hold on. Hold on. I'm getting a phone call. Hello. Hello,
Jerma. Hi. How are you? Doing quite well. In fact, good. Good. Did you uh, did you do all
you did you get? Is it settled? Settled a while ago. Oh, settled. Okay. Something else come up.
Yeah, I figured that out. Oh, all right. Cool. Cool. Cool. Cool. Cool. All right.
Should be all set. Should be all set to do any house flipping at all.
Oh, so did you leak what we're doing? No, no, I meant that. No, I meant house flipping like
generally like flipping things in your life. Mixing things up. Oh, I leaked. Okay.
Because I think maybe I like I love breadcrumbs, you know, people got there. Yeah. All right. Yeah,
let's leak away. I don't I don't think I've said all the games. You want to leak?
Yeah, no, I haven't. You go ahead and leak. Okay, guys, this is this is the surprise.
We're playing bro versus bro with with several games. Jerma, there's four. There's four. You
know this, right? You know how it works out. There's four. What's the word games that we're
both good at neutral? What are the neutral games? Well, one is one that you I want to say invented.
Really Hasbro's battleship. That's the one I know that one. Amen. Amen. You made that game.
That's always the starter for broke verse bro. I just I try to keep it alive.
And then the other neutral games are rock paper scissors. Oh, shit.
That one. That one gave you the oh shit. I mean, that's I'm I'm actually kind of nervous about
that one. I feel like that either stuff. Okay. Yeah. I guess, you know, you're right. Rock does
beat scissors. That gets stressful. Because it's so it's so easy to lose or win that game.
Yeah, because I mean, you know, but I think you have a good chance at all these.
Next one is connect for neutral game. Okay. Why are you why are you love you? It sounds like
you have a history we can report. No, it's just I I'm glad that these are this simple.
Because I was concerned to be like, oh, yeah, we're gonna hop into a fortnight. It's gonna be
a one v one. Oh, yeah. No items, you know, just absolutely imbalanced and just destroy you and
games you've never played. Yeah. Yeah, I tried to make it balanced because I realized that you
haven't played many games on stream that came out after 1999. That's very true. So So, you know,
and by the way, the last like, whole month, I've only played Elden Ring. It's the only game I play.
Yeah. Well, in the last neutral one is, of course, getting over it by Bennett body.
And how long do you how long each one of these games gonna take? We're doing like 15 to 20
minutes. 30 minutes. What's your time frame? Usually. So it's we just play each game and it
takes like about like Battleship's just the best of one takes about like 20 minutes. Connect four
is like maybe a best of three. It takes like five, 10 minutes. Rock, paper, scissors shoots
like a couple minutes. So it depends on the game and getting over. It's about six to 12 hours.
Yeah. Yeah. Well, the good news is I'm actually a pro speed runner at it and I have a five minute
time. But I think it's neutral. Then you seem like you're talent neutral because you have a great
way of handling anger. And I think that's why this is a good game that you might have a good
chance in. You know what? OK, I don't think that's I don't think that's a neutral experience. Sensing
a little tension. Let's let's pivot. OK, we'll pivot to something more balanced. How about just
reaction speed? That works because I mean, one of the games that I picked is, of course, like speed.
Is that what? Oh, yeah. Yeah. Click speed. OK. How fast you can click your mouse in 10 seconds. I
think I got you on that one. I think I do. Yeah. No, I do. You have history in that, like,
like clicking fast. Oh, yeah. And I know you do, too. A light amount. A light. This is with the
mouse, though, right? This is with a mouse. This is not with a controller. Yeah. Changes it a bit.
That changes it a bit. It does. The dynamic changes when you have to have a hand on your desk.
Wait, is that so I can't lift the mouse? No, you cannot hold the mouse in your hand and cradle it
like a baby and sit there like that. No, it's got to be. You can use two hands.
You can't. The mouse needs to be on your desk. OK, and it's just left clicking, right? Yes. Left
clicking. OK, just clip. OK. All right. All right. Wait, everyone in my chat saying I'm going to get
fucking destroyed. I'm going to get destroyed. Oh, no. I when you told me this game, I was excited
for you because I knew you'd do really well. I mean, I'm I could I'm like about 14 plus 15
clicks a second. Like I'm I'm an absolute maniac at that. Yeah, I'm I'm people say I'm fucked.
Wow. Fifteen. That's really good. That's and that's because it's a lot. It's a lot of clicks in a
second. But it sounds so confident, like way too confident. I think 15 is impressive. I think that
beats most children. And yeah, but you can't hold it in your arms and like it's got to be on the
table. Probably most like teachers would lose to you in this 1v1. All right. All right. I'm ready.
I'm ready. I'm ready to compete. I'm ready to compete. Yeah. Great. Great. And you have a couple
more games. Do you want to reveal them as we go or do you want to just fucking go now? I hope
hopefully the RNG works in my favorite battleship because I ain't going to win any of these.
Well, the good news is it's first to five. So you can't just win off your own games or even like
four games. You got to win five. So we have to win some of the neutrals. OK, that sounds good.
We can reveal the games as we go. Let's just kick off with a bit of battleship. Let's do battleship.
So I do what? Do I have to be online on Steam for this? Oh, yeah, you do. OK, that's easy.
It's actually phenomenal because I just went offline. Yeah, I start every single day and offline.
Wait, why? I don't know. I just like, I just always want to be offline. People give me shit
for this all the time. You know that? I'm never online. I'm never online on Discord. I'm never
online on Battle.net. I'm never online on Steam. Always permanently offline. Permanently. I switch
to being permanently offline in Discord. Really? Well, people would judge me like I'd come to
stream the day after and they'd be like, oh, wow, Ludwig, three hours last night playing Jump King.
You know, I'd be like, oh, yeah, I don't. Yeah, I don't want people to see my like my history of
me playing like five hundred hours of Lost Ark. No, no, don't tell me. That's a meme, right?
It is a meme, but I'm just saying. All right. All right. I'd be concerned for you.
I'm just. Is there a way to leak it to just each other?
What? Your history? Yeah, like can you can you be offline but like show it to friends on Steam?
Maybe. I think so. I don't know. I dude, I I like privated my Steam profile like a half decade ago
and I don't even know how to turn it off. I have no idea how to even turn it back on.
Oh, I have no fucking idea. I almost forgot. We have to we have to figure out what we're playing
for. Yeah. Well, OK, so this is where it gets weird because we had a competition a long time ago
and you won and I had to do a series of things that never happened.
I can't. It was like a cartoon list of things. Yeah, it was. It was like a Bugs Bunny Daffy Duck
cartoon list of weird shit that I had to do. Uh huh. One of them was to take like a picture.
That's like a fucking room with like a Megamilk shirt on with like delivering milk. Yeah, I think
you need to like get milked and then deliver the milk in a milk costume and then also go to like
a casino and wager like five hundred dollars. Dude, it was fifteen. It was fifteen hundred dollars.
It was. Let's just say it was five hundred. That's easy. Yeah, it was a lot. It was a lot.
How do I verify that you can't like videotape in a casino? I couldn't have like how do I verify
you would have to like be there physically to like. Yeah, I think this is this. OK, I look,
I will. I will because that's in a video, right guy. There's evidence of the cartoon list.
I'll just eventually go to you and then bring all the effects and then I can verify it like a like
a Guinness Book of World Records judge. So if you win today, you it's going to be like the
in like those Disney movies where the guy lifts up the parchment and the thing hits the floor
and he's like, so this is what you need to do today. It's got like what are you going to have
to do? What else could you have me possibly do? I think at a certain point, it's just I just go
over to you and I just have a week where I just I get my way. I just want my like string key for
like two days or something. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. We're getting there. We're getting there. You know,
take my string key for one hour. Maybe we keep this one simple then, right? That it's not it
doesn't add to the list. It's just something it's something nice, but like concrete. Yeah,
like like donating to your local church. I already do that so much. You should have seen my face. I
was smiling ear to ear. That was a joke for my chat that they're they all hate me for donating to
your local church. No, because we went back and forth about how I was like, let's make it easy.
Like I don't want to like stand on my head and drink milk with like my ass cheeks showing like
let you say, oh, like donate to something. And I was like, donate to, I don't know,
like church and people like church. What the fuck are you talking about?
Is that what you expect from me? Is it like something that depraved to stand on your head
and then drink like ass drink milk? Well, I mean, it wasn't one of the original things that I was
up to show up in like a sexy maid outfit and deliver milk to your house. Like that. That's a
little different. Now you're conflating the two. You're bloviating. That one's normal. That's like
almost it's like a common request from people these days. I've been asked to do that a lot.
I can't believe you haven't been boofing milk is obviously worse than that. Jesus Christ.
All right. I believe I am on the steam now. Should I join or what are you guys talking about?
This is bro versus bro, man. Just, just bro is being bros. All right. Talking about talking,
talking about maids and milk. Okay. What do you want, man? What are bros supposed to talk
about these days? All right. So join. Do you want to host it or should I host? Yeah. Yeah,
I'll send you. Do you want to play on a fancy board or a simple board? That's up to you. I
usually let the guests decide, but let's do it. Let's cause this is just best of one, right? We're
just playing this. Yes. Just one. Let's do fancy. Let's go fancy. Okay. All right. I'm going to do
hole in the middle. Oh, don't. Yeah. It sounds like you immediately hated that. Cause that's the one
you, you kicked my ass on that one before. Did I? Yeah, it was bad. I think I kicked your ass on
them. I don't mean to be Rudy. I kicked your ass on every single one of them. Well, Ludwig, this
rude. And then there's factual. So, you know, you can go ahead and be factual with you. All right.
Great. Great. Great. Great. Okay. So play with friends. I'm going to join game. I'm not showing
not leaking an old wager. I used to do is that the loser would give the winner a pair of their shoes.
Okay. What's I, what size are you? 11. I'm like 10. It wasn't to wear as more so for like,
that's not like I needed it. I don't know. I had a dream where it's like pink slips and I'd
hang them up on the rafters and it would just be all like the carcasses of the foes I've slain.
I thought it was just like, dude, let me take a look at your like shoe collection and see which
good, what do you got? You got anything cool? And by the way, I don't. Yeah. They're like,
like bands or like slip ons usually, right? You don't. Ludwig, five out of the six pairs
of shoes that I have are house flippers, like house flip slippers. They're house slippers,
house flippers. They're fucking very basic. I don't have shoes, man. I really don't. I have
like one pair of sneakers. I have about eight pairs of Crocs and that's about it. Yeah. That's
right. You do have a lot of Crocs. All right. What's the code? Do you want to? Okay. Now I'm
not going to leak now. Okay. Not leaking. You can show the screen now. Yeah. All right. I think
this is a good setup. Is there a, is there a champ? Do you want to neutral a champ or do you
want to go or separate ways? No, I like this guy. I like this Giuseppe. He's really good. Giuseppe.
Yeah. Oh yeah. Do you mind if I go William Cars like, or do you want me to go Giuseppe too? No,
no. Well, however, I mean, this is a competition, so you can do what you need to do. I'm just asking
questions out here. I'm prepared. Actually really not at all, but how do you get prepared for
battleship? You just do it. Yeah. You just, you believe you just play. Well, I actually open up
to a shot TV and get, you know, just, oh, you come over here and you take a look, just take a peek.
I mean, how do you think I want so much from you last time? Yeah. I know. You know, I think there
needs to be a verifying, uh, oh, by the way, uh, speaking of verifying house flipper, do we have a
neutral third party? Completely neutral party. Absolutely. We do. Cause if we pick a house,
right? Right. Just like, like one of the smaller houses, we got 20, 30 minutes, whatever to flip
it. Have a neutral third party come in. We'll do walkthroughs, a walkthrough, like real estate
style. And they decide who has the better house. Yeah. I think it's some fantastic idea. Okay.
I think, uh, I think I have a couple options we could do. It's a little biased. I was going to say
cutie. Cause she was an interior decorator. I think she, she wouldn't favor me or I could get,
yeah, I could find someone else. Maybe Connor. Yeah. Who would want to do it? Yeah. Uh, yeah,
I like that. It's a good idea. Yeah. That sounds fun. Cause then then it takes us out of it. It
takes Chad out of it. It's not like, oh, we do a poll. We have a third party come in and give us
the real opinion. The facts, nothing but the real HGTV style. All right. I got to place my ships.
I know I'm, I'm like stalling way too much right now. I'm focused. Cause you, you, you, you,
you have somewhere to, uh, you got a cutoff. I have a light cutoff. It's at like 6 37. All right. So
we, we should probably get my time. So I got, I got, I got a bit of time. I got a few hours.
You have experience playing this. I've, I've seen some of the, the experience you have. Oh yeah. I
get a little, I get a little involved. I know you, you never want to do that. I want to do that.
All right. I think this is good. This is terrible placement. This is not, this is not your bro
versus bro. When you do bro versus bro, when you do it, then you can put your play, you can play,
you can put your planes wherever you want. Okay. Amen. Tell them, tell them, Jerma. This is
terrible. I don't know. It can't be terrible at battleship. There's no such thing.
All right. I think I'm thinking this is pretty good. I'm going to go with this one.
This sucks. It's fine. Everyone's, why is everybody giving me so much shit with this?
It's just basic. I'm ready. It's basic. They're all in a row. That doesn't work anymore. It doesn't.
Ah, me to start. Uh huh. Start like I always do. Right. Yeah. Mine's mine. It's the mind meta.
Hmm. Hmm. It's a mind meta. Is there a game you've, uh, always been chastised to play on stream?
Uh, smite or smite because everybody hates it. They think it's funny that they hate it.
So, and they know that I'm going to get like fucking a hundred viewers playing it.
So they just like play it because they just want, I guess they just want me to fail for some reason.
Yeah. I have a similar thing with toon town. Oh, toon town. That's one that I've been looking at.
It's like recently. I like a year ago. Okay. Really only one. I got one in there.
How about the loser has to play that game? The loser of this whole thing has to play toon town.
Well, no, you'd have to play smite. Mine is toon town. Oh, you know. Okay. Just an hour or two.
Yeah. That sounds fun. Omega law. Yikes. That's people consider that to be one of my worst streams
I've ever done by the way. The smite smite one. Yeah. Were you just not feeling it that day or
Oh, did I not intern? Oh shit. No, I, no, it's just like, I just was terrible and I did viewer games
and there were people that played the game so much more than I do. And there's so much more
talented than I am. Um, and I kind of just walked out of spawn and died like 30 or 40 times.
Um, and I made this, I made this big elaborate thing, how much I played it.
Oh, you, you hyped yourself up. People are begging me not to play. They're in the chat right now.
Just freaking out. Oh, that's probably a, it's probably a good pick. I would say toon town is
cool though. No, it was genuinely everyone begged me to play, begged me to play. I boot up toon
town. I was averaging about a hundred viewers. I dropped to 15. I did the thing where I would look
at chat and I would go to read a message, but there were no messages updating a hundred to 15,
15 people, every, it was hundreds begging me to play for weeks. And I look over there's 15
people and the chat's not updating. I'm reading the same message. One guy said, why are you
keep looking over here? There's no new messages. Well, somebody, somebody said that somebody said
that to me in chat. Why are you looking over here, dude? Wow. That person, that's like an
ultimate burn. I was so, so hurtful because he was right. He was so incredibly right.
Yeah, but you have to, the rebuttal to that is what if somebody does, I don't want to miss it.
My rebuttal to that was, oh, you're right, man. And then quietly playing toon town for another
30 minutes before ending stream. I thought you were going to say like, you said,
fuck you. And you banned them. The only guy that's still there. I can't ban my one of 15
viewers. That's like 8%. I don't have, you, you would have, okay. You're talking about looking
over and you know, you don't not seeing anything like you would see the, like you banned that guy
message for a while. If you're playing toon town, right? Yeah. Like it'd be there for probably like
15 minutes and I would just look over and see it. I'd be like, I, you know, I'd prefer to be
chastised and look at nothing. Where are your boats? A bit of a quiet round to start off.
Honest to God, where are these? Does it make any sense? Well, you just scanned three. Somebody
said, how do you miss that much? Just land a shot because when you throw dice in the air,
sometimes you look at when the dice land, it could be anything. Hey man. They don't know about dice.
Oh, devious. Bingo. Come on. No. Oh, there we go. Lock. There we go. I thought it was the T shape.
I'm very happy about that one. All right. So you've got, what, what are your shapes?
Okay. They're on the right there. Yeah. So I mean, it's very, very likely. It's not likely at all.
Apparently I was, I mean, it's how unlikely is that I feel like it's as likely as any of the cardinal
directions, right? You put up a mind, Mandy, you changed bullshit. You asked me already getting
broke. It's pretty early to get that fraudster in a turbo. Ooh, you started off really strong,
but now it looks like I'm climbing. I'm really caught up with that. Ooh. Maybe try East or West.
Yeah. I mean, at this point, whatever it wasn't down. You have a lot of twos. Okay. Maybe if there
were three and you added a mine and you can't have a four shape. So it can't be all in the bottom
three. So it probably has to be on the right. Oopsie. Somebody made it. Oh, come on. Ooh. And
I get the confirmation. He's feeling himself. He's feeling himself. This is the worst case.
So, but that's not, that's not the two because it would have been sunk. So that's gotta be the
fleet. He thinks it's the fleet. I thought I really thought it was the fleet. That was if I'm really
honest with you, whatever, I'm fine. I'm ahead. And this is how I make my comeback. Ultimate
destruction. Oh, it's fucking dumb. Fucking stupid. Fucking game. Fucking game. Yeah. That's
fucking stupid. Yeah. Get the fuck out of here with that fucking stupid bullshit kid.
Your Boston's showing. So, oh, I wonder where he is. So that's, that's three in a row, which means
it has to be your gigantic L. Is it up or down? And by the way, if I get this right, you're taking
a big L here. Oh, that's a loss for all of you at home. What's going on? What have you done? What
is this? I don't, I hate when people do this because I'm too dumb to figure this out. I hate
when people do this. It's just a ship. I don't know. It's three. It's like two or three ships
together. Weirdly large ship. I know it's weirdly large, but it's one big ship. One, two, three.
God damn it. I hate this. I'll have to just, is it this way? No, that doesn't make any sense.
It's either. Okay. I'll come back to it. I'm going to come back to it.
You're just going to come back to it. Oh, yes. Come on. No, wait me. No, wait me. No, wait me. No,
wait me. Oh, sorry. Oh, come on. Do it again. No, I know it's not there. I am very smart.
Who says it like that? I am very smart. Oh shit. He got it. Right. We've tagged four of the five
ships. I don't know why I thought that said ship sucks. Oh, I got, I got to make something
happen here now. Four of the five ships. This one has to go to the left. I've been in a lot of
trouble now. I mean, there's a lot of trouble. You guys ready for smite Thursday? This one's
probably the long one. I'm going to go to the left. I'm going to go to the left. I'm going to go to the
right. This one's probably the long one. Yeah, he's going to go left. Damn it. No, he is not. Son of
a bitch. I got, okay. I got to get like all of your ships right now. And here's the thing though.
I've been holding on to it. I've got a super soaker. You understand? It doesn't sound as
threatening when you say super soaker. And I, I'm going to just pick the place that, you know what
I mean? We're going in the corner. All right. That's fine. All right. That's one of your takes
one down. This one takes one. I got a mind though. You did. Come on. Come on. Sorry. Good. Good. Good.
Good. All right. It's tough. It's tough. And by the way, uh, bingo, I'm doing it again. No. Yeah.
Fuck it. We're going over here. Well, you saved the two. Oh, you, I, you don't think I have a
strategy, a new strategy. I think I'm going right here or yeah. Yep. No. Yes. Yep. Right here. I
don't know. Right here. Right there. Right here. All right. All right. All right. Oh no. Okay.
All right. All right. Okay. Okay. This is not, this just became a video game. Okay. I have to
decide now with my slightly better than average orangutan brain where this is what you're doing
here. I think if I were to be smart about this, it has to be, uh, it has to be, uh, what the fuck
is this? This is, has to be your Tetris piece and your L, but what way is the L going this way?
I am very good at this. I know where you are now. And now I'm going to sink the other one too.
Now you're in deep shit because well, not quite because I, you could be another way here, but I'm
going to say you're over here and you are, and this is where it gets very heated because I know
you have a two right here somewhere. And ladies and gentlemen, we did it. There's no fucking way.
There's no way. There's no way. Oh, that's bad. That's not how you win these games. I don't think
the greatest mine I've ever seen both shots hit. Uh, but you don't know what you don't know where
this is though. I, it's not over. It's not over yet. You don't know where, which way the,
you don't know which way the penis is going. Okay. You don't, you don't, it could be going up.
I lost, didn't I? What the fuck? What happened? The only way you win is if I hit a mine and it hits
both of your remaining ships or my remaining ships, it's definitely just a T like you just made a
normal run of the mill T. It's very normal. You thought that's all I had. You already shot though.
You already shot. You already shot. Oh, I saved my bullets. God wants me in a mega milk shirt.
A lot of people do. He's looking down right now being like, no, no, no, I don't think so. No,
no, no. And he like shoots a fucking lightning beam out and like gives you the power to do that.
I got to see him in that mega milk shirt. He's got to be in that mega milk shirt. Otherwise,
you know, what's the point of me creating? It was all for you in a mega milk shirt.
Well, it is one on my favorite now. I had, I had that in the bag too. Like it's just,
that's just, you know, that's how the cards lay. You know, I think your one mistake was what was
that destroying all my ships, even though you knew where they were. Cause it gave me so many points.
Yeah. Yeah. It's a, whatever though. Hey, it's fine. What Oh, German, where would you like to take me?
Let's do, let's do the click speed. Okay. All right. All right. Damn it. I can't believe I
fucking lost that. Let's do click speed, click speed, click speed. It is. Uh, all right. Let's,
let's do this. Um, so how do you want to do this? You want, you want to do like you go and then I go
What do you want to do at the same time? Well, let's just do you go. I go. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah.
Like one at a time. Okay. And maybe we'll do like a two run, three runs each, three runs each. Seems
fine. Or we could do three. You go, I go. That works too. So you want me to go first because
you're, you want to see what you got working up where, what you're working with here. It's your
game. You picked it. You go first and I'll go and it's best of three. So if you went around one,
et cetera, I'm going to pull up your stream and I'm going to, I'll mute and I'll let you just
be in your own thoughts. Okay. Two, two, two, two, two, two, two, two, one, two, one, two,
one, two, one, two. I got it. I still got it. Mouse is on the desk. All right. All right. All
right. That's 121 clicks in 10 seconds. That's 12.1 clicks per second. 121, 121. That's my number
to beat. Yep. I have to see what you're doing. Yeah. You can pull up the, uh, the old stream
there. It's a little hard to find. Let me get it. She's going to go to youtube.com forward slash
live forward slash streams forward slash now. If you blow this out of the water, I'm going to be
pissed. All right. I'm on your channel. There it is. I'm on your channel. There it is. Okay. Let's
see. Let's see what you got. Okay. Let's see. Let's see what you got on the table. Two hands.
Oh, you can, you can use as many hands as you want, but the mouse has to be on the table.
No shot. That's the three best of three. I just have to learn. I have to learn. I have to learn.
I'm not used to keeping it on the table. He's nerfing me. All right. It's you. It's back to you.
All right. Back to me. Back to me. All right. Here we go. Uh, you could, you, however you want
to do this, that's up to you. I just did. I did one, just one that whole time. Let's make this hard
for you. Here we go. Ah, that was a little lower than last time. I distracted you with noise. I
distracted him. I thought, I thought it'd work. I thought it'd work. That was one 19. Okay. One
19. So I thought, so I had to, I had to get at least one 20. You got to get at least one 20 to
win this one. I wish my mouse wouldn't move. I could just do this. If I could, I would be insane.
I would drop numbers that no one's ever seen before. I gotta go live. There we go. How do you
keep the mouse still? It's out. You don't want me to give you a tactic? Yeah. If you could. It's
no, that's the only game I'm going to win. No, you're not doing your feet. No,
you're not doing your feet, dude. There's nothing in the rules that says a dog can't play basketball.
Why do you look, why do you look huge? What's going on? Why do you look like half your body is
across the rest of the room? You look like you're sitting at the back wall and your feet are going
all the way over here. Why? What's going on with this perspective? This looks weird.
You're distracting me a lot. Do you have a fisheye lens?
What's going on with this camera? I just need to get two feet. All right, I'm ready.
It's not even registering. You look like, you look like you're typing up like a project.
I'm so frustrated. You look so tired from a full day like of like cramming for an exam.
You're just like leaning back like, fuck man, I don't want to. How many words is a 1200 word essay?
God damn it. I'm at 1100 words. I can't do it. I can't do it anymore.
Oh my God. All right. What was your technique? The technique is you brace with whatever your
non-dominant hand is and then you just spam with the other one. What do you, that's not a technique.
Yeah. No, you, I just asked you like how to do a five paragraph essay and you said you just sit
in front of the computer and you write. Yeah. What's the, what's the key? All right. The key is
just get, come on over to my stream. I'll show you. I'm there. Here's the key. Key is you are not
trying to click. You are trying to pulsate. Does that make sense to you? You're one finger,
Freddy. It's one finger, Freddy. And it's pulse like, and you pulse for instance,
let's go ahead and beat that last one. Here we go. All right. 12.3. You should see me with a
controller, man. You should see me with that. That's why I picked this in particular.
It was a demoralizing play. You're demoralizing me. I got to win at least one. All right. All
right. All right. Germa's on the board. Germa's on the board. It is what it is. You put your feet up.
It was like, you were like lounging on a boat. Like that was that. You want to go for one more?
Do you want to try it one more time? No, I really don't. I really don't. I thought that you had a
secret way to hold the mouse and you're using two hands and cause you kept saying as many hands as
you'd like. And so I thought there was a secret hold. Oh, I would outsmart you by using my feet
as the hold. I see. So you thought I was, I was just kind of messing with you like that.
There's a special way to do it. Yeah. Yeah, I did. I did think that I was deceived. Well,
I'll take, I'll take, I'll take one. Let's hope I get another one. Well, it is, it's my game now.
It's my game pick and you know, I, let's travel the world together. Let's play some GeoGuessr.
Sounds good. Oh, GeoGuessr, me and you. GeoGuessr sounds good. I'm actually pretty good at this
just to give you a quick little rundown. Really? Do you have like a history? Like
I've played it a few times on stream. Okay. Sure. I think I know somewhat where I am.
Do you know, is this world? I'm going to like burp in your face. I'm really sorry.
Is this world? It's actually the competitive mode. Oh, how does this work? I'll send you a link
and we duel head to head. We can do best of three. They're pretty fast. Okay. And basically you,
you just got to get it right, right off the bat. Yeah. You'll kind of see as it goes along,
but you get as much time as it takes one person to guess. The moment one person guesses,
the other person has 15 seconds to lock in a guess. You can, you can move around, zoom pan,
whatever. But, but it's 15 seconds after a guess is made and whoever's closest will get more points
and the difference in the points will take down your overall score. So you have like a life bar.
Oh, okay. So are we, are we, are we, am I in here? This is me. This is you, you're Sean.
You didn't say the whole thing. 200. Yeah. Is this, is this like an old name?
I just, before you became nine eight five. Are there other nine eight five names on the way?
Like, did you just end that German? But maybe like it was Sean 200, Jeremy 201,
Freddie 202. I took first names. It just kind of went from there. Right. Great. Yeah. They,
I asked my chat earlier what the nine eight five was and they said, well, this makes sense. Now
it's with a little bit of a tinkering in your brain, it should make sense. Yeah. Yeah. No,
I, I think I get there. It's grams is what it is. It's my, that's how many grams of sugar I put in
my coffee because I don't know. All right. So are you ready to explain how this works? But one,
two, three, four, five, just to look around, look around. Well, I'm not going to guess right away
here, but you look around and you make an educated guess anywhere in the world or is this United
States only anywhere in the world, anywhere. All right. I got it. I got it. And then you just,
when you feel comfortable and confident, you just drop a guess. And I don't want to say anything
because I don't want to give you, you prefer to mute up. You can mute up and kind of talk through
your thought process here. I'll like, but I did a bit for you. Okay. Okay. You already guessed.
Yeah. Well, I thought I thought it expedited for you, you know? Oh, fuck. Okay. Um, well,
I don't know. Seven seconds. I would click somewhere. How did you fucking, how did you do
that? How did you do that? Well, the license plate said blue on each side, which is exclusive
to Italy and Albania. How would you know that? Are you this well traveled? Yeah. You know,
I like to get out every once in a while. You know, I'm fluent in French. Yeah. I have not left
continental North America. You understand? Ever? Ever in my whole life. I thought you played the
game a bit though. You know, maybe. All right. I, I know what this is. I know what this could be
because we've, I, this is very specific. Okay. All right. 10 seconds. You can speak out loud,
speak free. I don't know. Oklahoma, somewhere in Oklahoma. What are you talking about? How would
you know that there was a guy on our lawnmower? How do you know that that's in fucking Austria?
No, I need to explain your thought process on that. A guy was on a fucking rider mower.
That's like John Deere. We're in Oklahoma. How did you figure that out? Uh, I, uh, so sorry. Um,
I figured it out because I drove, I buy a car and it had a European license plates. Uh, and then if
you look around, it's a bit, it's a bit gloomy. So I figured it's a bit South, right? You know,
we're not, we're not so North cause it's, it's still quite, uh, uh, flourishing with wildlife.
I've only been to like, like 12. I've, I play the game a bit and then I just figured it was,
it was middle EU. I got lucky on the hungry. I thought we were in like, okay, it was like
Oklahoma. It had a European license plate. I didn't, I, you, you guessed too quickly.
I couldn't even look at the license plate. I just saw a guy in like a lawnmower and I was like,
all right, this guy's got a big yard. He's got a big, a lot of grass. I don't know where his house
is. I wonder, is there a dual mode with just NA? No, no, we can do Europe. That was a good one.
I'll take Europe. Oh no, I can't, I can't. I'll just change. I'll change it to United States for
round two. I won one. It's now it's around two and it's just us this one. All right. Yeah,
no, we can do whatever. I think you can click on duels and maybe that'll do. Do you need a link
again? Um, do I just go to the menu? I can also do this for you. I think you have like a, oh yep.
Does that work? I think so. Yeah, it should, shouldn't it? It does, doesn't it? Okay.
All right. Just us. Just the United States. Bro, this is Canada. I can tell because there's a
license plate. The Canadian flag is right there in the red on the license plate. You see the lights
are red. The back lights are red and white. All right. It's not fucking around before I
how this one was just to rattle you. I have no idea. It's just a rattle me.
I, this was just, I have zero idea where this is. I won't even be close with my guess.
Texas. I thought somewhere in like New England. I thought New Hampshire. I just picked somewhere.
I couldn't even zoom in fast enough. I just picked the spot like up in New England.
Oh, hurry up. I don't know. I don't know. There's gonna be a sign here.
What the fuck did that say? Oh, who's closer? Me slightly. Did you find one of the highways?
Nah, I just figured it was like somewhere in the middle. I was trying to go to the airport.
You're trying to go to the airport? Yeah, because it'd be like, oh, welcome to beautiful,
like Chicago or something, right? Like at the airport. You must have found something in Utah.
I got stuck in the parking lot. Yeah, me too. I just clicked because I figured you would think
I know what I'm doing, but I didn't. That's actually a pretty good strategy, I think.
Try to get close enough and have the other person panic. Yeah. I just guessed central enough.
Very obviously. I know like where we are. Where are we? No way.
I thought it was like somewhere in like this like Ohio, Pittsburgh. I got lucky. A guy had
a Philadelphia Eagles sticker on his car. Oh shit. All right, this is a healing round. So
you can't lose here. It's all about just getting close and you can recover up to a quarter of the
points for your guess. That's a good strategy. Look for like stickers on cars. Uh huh. Yeah,
people are very, you ever thought about a German 985 bumper sticker? No. I thought I'd start
thinking about it. So I can drive around and find, see if somebody has it and like beep beep,
like beep and be like, hey man. You know, Jeep owners, they do a nod. It's like a thing. If
you have a Jeep, you nod at other Jeep owners. Maybe German sticker havers do like a sign to
each other that only they know. Oh, I see what you're saying. I have a little secret handshake.
Exactly. Where the hell does this want me to go? I don't want to go that way. What's that?
It's that. Oh, you were closer. It was Arkansas. I was thinking like Kansas. Yeah. Yeah. Just throw
an AR on it. You're there. Here we go. This is where it gets real. The 1.5x damage. Yeah,
you could beat me in one fell swoop if you get a good enough guess. Just literally this is every
neighborhood in America. I know. Seriously. I'm lost in cul-de-sacs. This could be anywhere.
Gotta find a main road or you're not. Oh, I thought that was going to be like,
I'm running for a Senator here. I'm just like making noises on your stream.
Sorry. I'm so deep in thought that your noises, it's like a good buffer.
Main road does not help. I feel like that's a guess. That was a bad guess. Oh, it's a great
guess from him. I'm thinking. I think I've seen Indiana. Well, I didn't say Indiana.
This is the big one. This is going to be whoever. This is going to be it.
This could be unless we're both very close. Yeah, this could seal it.
I thought that was a crispy cream. Oh, what the fuck? This place is called big D.
Any guesses on your end? I'm a little lost. He's not going to be close. Sorry. I lost.
I thought you said you were lost. Yeah, I lied.
That's why I was like, oh, I'll just be close. I'll be close enough.
Oh, no, no. I found a sign. I found a sign. Shit.
Uh, two, one, then two, one, then Jerma. Yeah, it's two, one.
Two, one and your pick as well. Okay. Don't be down on yourself. I won my game. It's normal.
I don't know how well you're going to do on this next one because we're playing pick Ross.
Did you have any opportunity to sit down and play pick Ross to even know how the game works?
This is picked up picks, right? It's picked up picks. Not one second.
You have not played even one second of this. Okay. So I mean, this is guaranteed win.
You didn't play one second. I thought I would just naturally beat you out of my gaming skills.
Oh, dude. Oh, I don't know, man. This is like a thing you need to know how to play.
But if you win, this could be a lie too. You could be making this up.
If you beat me without any experience, you have no idea what's going on.
Then I'm hanging up the gloves. Is this a single player?
Oh yeah. Here's what's going to happen. We are going to, I'm going to pick you a puzzle.
We're both going to do the puzzle at the same time, starting at the same time.
And whoever completes the puzzle first wins that round. We'll do best two out of three.
Oh, love that. So let's, uh, let's go ahead. We can be very, uh, democratic about this.
Okay. Okay. Great song by the way. Oh yeah. No, picked up picks is great.
Pick Ross is great too. Um, I hope you, uh, enjoy what you're doing because it's a very,
very much one of the greatest, uh, mind puzzles. Is there a difference?
Do you want me to pick Ross? I probably should give you
at least a small rundown of what's going on. I kind of have to in general,
it doesn't have to be in depth. Don't feel bad for me. You know,
okay. I brought you to GeoGuessr and you clicked on Oklahoma when it was hungry.
That's true. Uh, okay. Let's go ahead and let's, let's, let's do, let's do a tutorial.
I feel like that's fair. Okay. Sure. It's not fair if you do not get into a tutorial.
It's just, that's just a fact. Let me open it up. Okay. So, uh,
do you have access to the ones that are 15 by 15 by the way, or are they all locked in the,
just in classic mode, are they locked? Yeah, I think I can do it. Okay. Oh no,
they're locked. Oh, they are locked. Okay. Absolutely locked. Yeah.
This is going to be tricky. I can only do five by five. Oh, you can only do the five by fives.
What's wrong with that? Is that bad? That means we can't do the same puzzle. Wait,
you can't do the five by fives or you're already done. I've already done those five by fives.
There's a, there's an endless mode. What if we just do that? What is, what is that? Let's see.
I mean, let me try to get this captured. I can't get it captured. Why not?
Game capture. What's going on here, dude? Oh, this is just Voltorb flip. This is what? This
is Voltorb flip. I, I've played this game before. Voltorb flip? Uh huh. Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Hold on. Yeah. And, and Pokemon, they have a game called Voltorb flip and it's very similar to this.
Does Voltorb flip Picross? It is, it, that is exactly what this is. It is Voltorb flip.
Yeah. Slightly less. Um, there's a little more guessing in that game, but yeah.
All right. So here's what we're going to do. We'll do max, uh, with minimum width,
max width, do 15. Wait, wait, minimum width, max width. Yeah. Make it 15 by 15 or 15. Oh,
we can do 10 by 10. How do, how do you know when you're done, by the way, out of curiosity?
It will be, it'll complete. It'll be, you're making a picture. Great. So do 10 by 10 and just
do play. Okay. And let's go over some very basic. I'm so happy by the way that you're playing this.
Okay. Because dude, this is the new meta. I'm telling you, this is the new, another,
this is another, fuck it, fuck Battleship. Which, where do you want me to go for this?
I'll do endless and do 10 by 10. Endless max width, 10 max height, 10.
Now it's probably going to give us, it's probably going to give us different puzzles. I'm going to
assume because yours probably does not look like mine. No, I see your screen. They're different.
They are different. Okay. So, hmm. We may have to pivot. We may have to pivot to
neutral. No, no, no. Click through a couple of times here. Let me see what you're getting into.
Okay. So let's do a tutorial. Oh, this is awesome. Okay. So how Picross works. Hi,
ladies and gentlemen. Welcome. How Picross works, my friend, is this. You have a grid
and you have a series of numbers. This is not, um, Sudoku. So shut up. This is different.
Where you start is you see these numbers I have on the left and numbers I have on top,
versus this one here is six. What this means is this means that six of these squares are going
to be filled in on this row. They will also be filled in horizontally. So this six is part of
this one, two, one, two. Do you understand? What is one, two? Why do they express it? One, two,
one, two. I'm so glad you asked that question. A six. So on the left side, in between each one of
these numbers, there has to be at least one space. But let's say for instance, if the one was right
here, the two would have to be at least here. You cannot, yeah, they cannot be, uh, if there's a
space in between, they cannot be touching. So for instance, we got four, one, one down here. That
means there's going to be four in a row somewhere, a space, a one and a space. That space does not
mean one space. That means any amount of spaces. So that means it could be one, two, three, four,
all these spaces, one space, one. And you have to use logic to deduce exactly where these pieces
need to go. So if you, let's do, let's, let's, let's do a little bit of logic here. So if you've
got 10 spaces here, it has to be some of the middle that have filled in. It has to be, has to be. So
one, two, three, four, five, six. One, two, three, four, five, six. You know, for certain, these two
have to be filled in. They have to be 100% of the time. Following. I'm following. Following. So this
is where it gets hard because you have to figure out where, because you're looking up the top row,
you're looking at the bottom row and there's no way for you to tell. Initially, you have to kind
of work backwards in a way. So let's start here. By the way, there's only 10 spaces. So if you have
an opportunity where it's like four, five, six, seven, eight, you know that eight of these spaces
are filled in. There's only 10. So I mean, it's, it's fun. It's really the top 10 game on,
but we've already did it. What? No, no, no, no. I'm just, I'm working on it a little bit here.
Okay. So that's the concept of the game. Okay. So for, let's, let's see if I can do this. This
one's kind of tricky because that's four, one, one. It has to be the high. Uh, actually, I don't know.
One, four, one, any of these equal 10. I don't think so. Wait, three, four, five, six, seven.
Okay. All right. Perfect example. Perfect example. You see this one right here? Uh-huh.
You see how that's a one, two, three, four, five, six, seven. And there are three spaces,
eight, nine, total 10. Take a look at that. Ladies and gentlemen. Now you've got yourself
a full row and block these out. So you don't fuck it up for yourself later. Interesting.
Out. There's other one, two, three ones. You are, you know, that that's certain that they're going
to be filled in and that gives you information here as well. See these ones up here. Um, excuse
me. If these are all ones, you know, for a fact, there has to be a space between them.
There has to be. So that's blocked off and that's blocked off.
Someone said, stop. This is awful. What? I think this is great. This is great. This is
a good look out. He's pretending. I don't think you're pretending. I'm pretending. What would I
be pretending? Yeah. I know what. All right. So here two, one, two, two, one, two. It's let me, uh,
student Ludwig. Uh huh. Yeah, please. Would you, what would you see? What would you consider
doing here on the, which one? The two, one, two. Yeah. What would you, I mean, do you have
any information that you think you could give me? Right. Right. Two, one, two. Let's take a peek at
this bad boy on the two, one, two over here. Yeah. Yeah. Oh, a lot of information actually.
Now that I'm, I'm like, I'm zooming out a bit. I'm zooming out a bit to be clear. You're talking
about the two, one, two, the left. I'm talking about the left two, one, two here. Right. The
left two, one, two, the information in so interesting. That's when you bring it up.
The middle probably can't have anything around it. Right. That is exactly precisely what's going on.
So probably got to block those guys out. Yes. Shut off the blinds. There is minimum. Now, you know,
you know that this is the two. Oh yeah. Has to go this way or it has to go this way. You
don't have that info, so don't be careful. Don't do it. Don't know yet. Don't know yet. We'll get
there. You might get baby steps. You know, there's another thing. You know that the other two is here
somewhere. You don't know if it's here. It's like Battleship, right? Like, you don't, you're trying
to figure out where that ship is. Where's that too? Where is it going to be sticking this way?
Could it be over here? It's, it's too, it's too early to tell. I'd say it's similar to Battleship.
Yeah. Yeah. But again, take a look down here. What would you do with this? Uh, down four, one,
one, you probably got to do all the four on the left, right? Bottom left. Well, hold on, slow down.
I guess, I guess that's not necessarily the case. What do you absolutely know with this right here?
Uh, this can't be the four because obviously if that was the four, remember it's, it's sequential.
This has to be the first number in, in this row. Right. If this is part of the four,
it would have to be like one, two, three. Let's see. Yeah. If this was the four,
it would have to be one, two, three, four and then space one, space one. But you don't know
that information yet. So this could be the, it could be part of the four. You never just
YOLO guess and rip it. You could, but you got to get it right. Right. You YOLO guess and rip it.
You, the picture will not complete. Makes sense. Makes sense. Is it, so it's always a picture. Is
that the, is that the case? It's always a picture. Interesting. Okay. All right. I think I'm getting
the hang of it. I think I'm slightly. Yeah. I think I'm slightly getting the hang of it. I'm getting
like inch by inch. You know? Yeah. Rome was built today. It's a really fun game. I would
highly recommend it. All right. So let me see if I can figure this one out while we are. You do
that one and let me, let me mull this guy over. Right. Let me just, yeah, mull it over. You're
good. Give it, give it a stab. Yeah. Just mull it over. So I'll start this mulling this one.
This is, this is part of the two, but I don't know where this is part of the two, but I'm not entirely
sure. Two, three, four, five, six, nine. I don't have that info yet. So it's tricky. This one
actually is pretty tricky because it's really a lot of low numbers here. It really could be
anywhere. I mean, okay. It has to be, take a look at this. All right. We know that. I mean,
he's already done. I'm not done. Come on. They're just, they're toying around, right? What are you
talking about? Have you been, wait, this is, is it, are we doing this one for real? What's that? No,
we're just having fun right now. You're getting stressed out. All right. This is, this one's for,
all right. All right. All right. All right. He's, he, I see what you're doing.
I'm gonna be quiet because I can't talk and play this game. It takes way too much of my brain power.
I don't blame you. It's hard. This one's actually really hard. I got a really hard one. What makes
it hard? A lot of low numbers, not having like free ones, like free spaces. The way this game
gets really hard is when you have a lot of low numbers that do not equal close to the maximum
on the grid. So if you have a bunch of ones and twos, it's, it's, you have to really work backwards.
Shit. I've got to make a decision here. I've got to make a decision. I got a terrible one. It's,
okay. So the ones that are endless, I think are random. So I don't know if I can like logically
deduce this one. Okay. So I did my puzzle. I think I got it. Did it finish? Yeah. Yeah. It like popped
up and it said, well done. Oh, you finished it. All right. Okay. All right. So you get it. I think
I get it. All right. You get it. Let's boot it. Let's do a, let's do one for real. All right. You
want to do a big one? Yeah. 15 by 15. Is that the normal 15 by 15? Okay. And endless mode, I suppose.
I guess we'll do endless mode. Okay. All right. And we're going to, I guess we'll mute because
I'm going to be, I need to focus in. Yeah, no, I think that's fair. I think it's fair. You click
on the size multiples of five and square grid checkboxes, right? Um, endless isn't like concrete
pictures. If that's a multiple of five. Yeah. What's that? I don't know what that means.
It was pre-checked. So I guess I'll keep it. Maybe yours was pre-checked. Yeah. Oh yeah. I think
that, okay. Checked and means is, is the, okay. Yeah. I see. Yeah. All right. You ready to do it?
Yeah. Let's boot up. All right. I'm good luck. Good luck. Yeah. Let's go 15 by 15. Let's do it.
Fuck. Yeah. Fuck. Yeah. Pick Ross, baby. All right. 15 shit. This is going to take a long time. I
don't think he's prepared. It's like an hour, five, six, seven, eight, nine, 10, 11, 12, 13, 14.
Shit. It's close though. I got to be a guarantee. Shit. Four, five, six, seven, eight, nine, 10, 11,
12, five, six, seven, eight, nine, 10, 11, 12, 13, 14. Fuck you. Did I count wrong? Five, six,
seven, eight, nine, 10, 11, 12, 13, 14. I don't know. I can't make that deduction. I, I mean,
I can get the nine. Nine, one, two, five, six, seven, eight, nine. We got that. Good start. Good
start. Fuck. Five, six, seven, eight, nine, 10, 11, 12, 13, 14. I'm going to lose in my own fucking
game. 14. It's not enough. I don't, it could either be here and down or here and down, right?
But fuck, there's no way for me to tell. Fuck. I'm going to lose in my own game. I'm going to lose
in my own game that I picked and I was so confident. Six. Okay. One, two, six. Fuck,
that's 14. I'm going to lose in my own game. I can't even go anywhere. I don't know where
to start from this. This is probably the one, but I don't know. It could be anything.
This, I'm going to have to just go for it, but I, there's no way for me to know.
One, two, three, four. One, two, three, four. There has to be one here and then somewhere in
the middle of the three. Why did they pick Picross? The endless mode is random numbers.
I didn't know it was going to be random. I'm fucked. All right. Start over here.
And 11, 12, four, one. No, I can't do it. Four, five, six, seven. There's nowhere to start.
There's nowhere to start. Bro, there's nowhere to start. There's nowhere for me to go from here.
I don't think I can fucking do this one. There's nowhere for me to go. I have to guess.
Or five, six, seven, eight, nine, 10. This is part of the two. I don't fucking know.
Five, six, seven, eight, nine, 10, 11, 12, 13, 14. The thing is I'm, if I get this wrong,
the whole thing is fucked up. Okay. Relax. It has to be one, two, three, four, one. It has to be
this. It has to be. And then the, I don't know where the three is though. One, two, three, four,
five, one, two, three. I don't know. Three, four, five, six, seven, eight, nine, 10, 11, 12, 13, 14,
five, six, seven, eight, nine, 10, 11, 12, 13, 14. One, two, three, four, five. This has to be this.
Two, three, four, five, right? Yeah. It's going to be so embarrassing when he comes over to the
stream. When he comes over and he finishes and he sees this, it's going to be the most embarrassing
moment of my career. It's going to be the most embarrassing moment of my entire career.
He's going to be like, all right, man, that was pretty easy. And he's going to come over
and I'm going to be like, I don't know, I have four spaces filled in. It's so fucking much harder
than the regular ones. Okay. Four, two, I don't fucking know, man. I have to guess in random
directions, I think. I have to guess. I have to guess. Fuck. Okay. It's time to guess because
there's no way for me to logically fucking deduce this random mode. I'm going for it. We're going
for a guess. If it's wrong, the whole thing's fucked anyways. It's wrong. This is definitely
not, this is one of the ones. I got it. It's wrong. That has to go. Yeah. Yep. I got, I deduced
this one with my fucking brain. Check this out. See this? That's definitely one of the ones. The
two is over here somewhere. I've deduced it. Shit. No, I didn't. I don't think I can actually
logically figure this out. But if you guess and it's wrong, the whole thing is over. I've tried
to hit you with a battle ax. He's like fucking swinging at me and I'm dodging. I have to go for
it because how the fuck? And maybe I know that at least because there's no way this is part of the
two. Am I getting a bloody nose from this? No. So this is probably part of the four. It is. This is
probably part of the four. One, two, three, four. So we're going to say it can't be that way.
It's also, it's maybe not though. I don't know that because this could be one, two, three, four,
one, two. Yeah. I don't fucking know that. Bro. This is so hard. If I'm going to at least say
that this is not the two that I'm going to commit to it. If I commit to that, then that means one,
two, three, four, five, one, two, three, four. These can be filled in. I was at the one or part
of the three. Is this the two? There's no, I, there's no way to tell. There's no way to tell.
Ludwig said, please let's do an easier one. Hey, what's up? Oh, hello. Hello. How are you doing?
Um, I'm doing okay. Did you finish a little bit of guessing? No, did you? You didn't? Oh my God,
dude. Look at my stream. You didn't finish. Wait, what do you, you're, you're barely through it.
It's way too hard to 15 by 15 is a bit, it's a bit, it's a lot. It's a, it's a mental task.
Um, I think part of the problem is because it's endless random mode. It might be even harder
because when you completed the last one, did you make a picture? It was like vines. Okay. It was
like over earth. Like I would not have seen it as a picture normally. How are you doing?
I'm doing okay. You know, I, I'm, I'm hanging in there. Would you like to go to a, to a 10 by 10?
I am down to go to a 10 by 10. Yeah. Cause I think this would take me a good 45 minutes. Yeah. And
I know you've got to go at like six or something. So I got at least six, seven. Yeah. Yeah. Okay. Um,
I suppose too hard. So, all right, all right, all right, let's do it. Let's do a 10 by 10.
You have no idea. I thought you were running through it. I thought you were just smoking me.
I'm sitting here panicking. I was like, this is over. Like I picked the game and I can't even do
it. I think it's I'm going fast, but I was so worried that it's like at the end, it's not going
to complete. And I'm going to look back and be like, Oh, cause it's a couple of points. I'm just
like, I'll put the six there. Cause uh, cause it just feels, it feels nice. It feels good to just
click it. But if you're wrong, the whole thing's messed up. Exactly. Yeah. Yeah. So I was, I was
making a lot of risky plays. 10 by 10 will be a lot easier. 10 by 10. I feel great. We are going
to cap this out in 10 minutes each. I imagine. I think so. All right. You ready? All right. Yeah.
Yeah. Good luck. Good luck. Good luck. Much better. Much better. Four, five, six, seven, eight, nine,
anything I need to build eight, five. I can one, two, three, four, five. I don't know that. I can't
do that. I can't fuck you. What are you talking about? The two, let's just assume the two is here.
Let's just assume that's the two. Cause we have to, right? One, there's your one, there's your one.
Let's go ahead. Let's get that one, two. Let's assume the two is here. Just assume it.
Okay. That's part of the one. That's part of this one. Also part of the one. It's part of the three.
This part of the two, one, two, or one, two. The rest of this cannot be filled in. All right. Five.
There's your five. There's your two. There's your two. There's your three. There's your two.
There's your two. Four is up here somewhere. Okay. We've got one, two, three, four, one, two,
three. Let's assume the two is here. Four, there's your one. There's your one.
Go to that. Now we can say with an assumption here, we've got that situated. Go ahead and say
that's one. We've got the one there. There's your two. There's your one. We're here somewhere. Three
and two. Come on. Come on. Come on. Come on. It has to be right. One, two, three, four. It has to
be in the middle here. It has to be. There's your one. Wait, if we're accepting that. Wait,
we're accepting that, then one, two is here. What? Yes, it has to be. There's your two.
There's your one right there. Still looking for a one here. There's your two. There's your one.
That row's done. There's your two. It has to be there. It has to be there. Three, two.
Three. There's your two right there. There's your two. There's your. Where is it? All right,
relax. It's your three. Probably. This is your three. It has to be. Yep, this is your two and
your three. Right? Right. Yep. Oh no, no, no. Go back, go back, go back, back, back, back, back,
back, back, back, back, back, back, back, back before I did that. This is the one. This is the
two. This has to be there. There you go. Get rid of this. This is the two. But what direction?
That way. This is the three. But what direction? I don't know. Here's your three. Two, two. This
is the one. No, it couldn't. It might not be. Yes, it is. Here's your two. One, one. Fuck. No, wrong.
Um, this is the two and then one, two, one, one. Here it is. This is the three then. Yep,
there's three. This is done. Dude, this is the two and there's your one. There's your two. There's
your one. There's your two. What the fuck am I drawing here? There it is. Got it. Bingo.
Uh, I got it. That's a, uh, that's a completed picture. I've no, you were quick. I have no idea
what this is. I want you to know you, you bested me. Uh, cause I, I was still, I was still really
thinking. I was still mulling it over. Uh, this is, this is, it's a hard game. It's very hard. Uh,
which means this, I'm, I'm, I'm sorry. I don't want to stall and finish my painting. I'm just close.
No, no, do it. I mean, I just did it. So yeah, I mean, they're, they're tricky, man. They really
are. Okay. One, one, two. They're really fun though. Got it. Dude, you were, um, you were
literally 30 seconds behind me. So yeah, it took me six minutes, 10 seconds, a little over, a little
over. All right. That's your win though. That's your win. Yeah. So, you know, hey, credit where
credit's due, but that's a good game. Oh, do you want to do best? No, we don't want that. We don't
ask you a serious question. Be, please. I, you know, you and I know each other pretty well now.
Uh huh. Do you hate this? This game? Yeah. No, I actually think this game's fun. Okay. All right.
Cool. I played a game on the, on, on, I think it's Pokemon Platinum, maybe earlier, but there's a
game called Voltorb Flip that is very similar to this, but there is a level of RNG in it.
So it's, it's only, um, it's only five by five, uh, but there are like bad squares. And if you
click the bad squares, you lose. Yeah. There are versions of that. We'll do that too. Right. They,
they add like a minute to your time or something. If you get it wrong. I probably played that game
for maybe eight hours straight. Yeah. Uh, it just like getting upset. I've melted, I've melted
eight to 10 hours just lying in bed, laying the one on the DS. And it's like, it's like 12 o'clock
at night or like one o'clock in the morning. And the sun starts coming up and you're just like,
oh shit. And you just put it down and roll over and go to bed. Yeah. I, I, I can't imagine,
I'm looking at classic mode, right? And it, and it has the, uh, what is it? The, the 40 by 40s.
I can't imagine that. No, that, that's like a 2000 piece jigsaw. That would take me like a,
like a few weeks to chew through. I feel like some of these would be almost impossible to do
with in less than a day or two. Why did you get two crowns? Um, probably just under six minutes,
five minutes, maybe I don't even have access to the 40 by 41. So 40 by 30. Uh, all right,
let's, let's boot up next game. Jerma, are we gone? That's a good game. It is really good.
And you're off time. You boot up like, uh, the pick the one on switch is really good too. Yes.
Are you just zoned out playing that? Just edging on the couch. It's so awesome. Cause you can just
have that like on your lap while you're watching TV or something. And it just something that sits
there. It's awesome. That sounds awesome. So where are we going? Super auto pets. So it's,
it's going to be two, two, two to two. Cause there's no way I win this. I will try. How do we play
together? Are we just trying to get to, we're, we're going against each other. Yeah. Oh, really?
Uh-huh. That's kind of cool. Is that new? Uh, they've had it, but it was a little laggy at the
start. It's, it's a little, we did the tournament this way. Oh, okay. Oh yeah. That's right. Uh,
I'm sending you a code. Do I need like any of the expansions or anything? No. I think I, I think I
have one of the first expansion pet pack. Yeah. That's it. That's the only one there is. Okay.
Cool. It opened. So you, are you still into this, huh? You still into this game? Yeah. I've seen
you playing it. They just released a new pack that has like, there were 80 pets. Originally there's
80 new pets. Um, 80, 80, 80. There's, there's, it's like a whole new game now. Uh, there's a pack
that it carries none of the pets over. So it's, it was, it's foreign to me. So it's like a new
game in a way. Jesus. And I'm, I'm one of the pets. I'm one of the pets. You are. Yeah. Um,
ready? I'll just, I'll do it for you. I can't wait to hear that in the game. Do you know what? It's
obviously a fish. Yeah. A gold. Oh, all right. Yeah. All right. So what versus mode? Uh, it is,
it is versus mode. And then I sent you the code on discord and that's joined private. Okay. Join
private game. Uh huh. And then you're in. We're good. We're good. We're good to go. Yeah. We're
going to go. So now it's, you have 15 lives and you lose a certain amount of lives if you, uh,
all right. So are we going to, are we muting and going to our separate? Oh, we do. So we talk.
Yeah. You don't want it to reveal too much. We can talk during the battle. Okay. Okay. 13
time or the bottom, right? And it's ticking down fast. Okay. I don't know. I don't know. I don't
know. I, I, I honestly forgot how to play that. I forgot everything about the game. Did you get a
full? Oh, you got a full squad off. Okay. I was worried. Yeah. Yep. I kind of forgot everything.
I mean, it's a great start. That is not a bad start. That's all right. I'll take a trade.
How much time is on the clock for you? Oh, it was seven seconds. Great. Great. Great. Excuse me.
Wait, you need to turn that timer up my hair. Excuse me. Did you get to even do your turn?
I just put random shit up here. Oh yeah. That was a random bunch of shit.
Let me, let me double check to see the clock. Hey, I like it. You know what? No, no, let's,
my timer is stuck at 15. I'm going to, I'm going to redo it. I'm going to redo it. All right. All
right. So funny. Turn on fast forward to get more time. I don't know what that means. I'll just give
a 60 seconds per turn. Abandoned game. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Abandoned. Same code though.
Is it available now? It should be. Oh, you are using the pay to win pack. I am. Which is fine.
I think that's fine. Did I turn that off? I can turn it off. Let me know. Let me just also use
it. We can both use it. Okay. All right. Uh, add an S at the end of the code and it should be good.
No. Okay. Actually, no, no. I'm sorry. Don't go in. Uh, add two S's at the end. Two S's. People
saying show your screen. Why do you think I'm not showing the screen between these things?
Okay. I am. All right. Now you can show the screen and we have, yeah, we have about a minute per
turn. All right. Perfect. All right. Good luck, man. Good luck. Good luck. I mean, I'm not supposed
to tell you like a fucking story when I'm, when I went to like the Dunkin Donuts drive through,
because I have no idea what the fuck I'm doing. How about this one? This bird. You buy food one,
one until end of battle. Mosquito. I like that. Hold on. I can, I can roll, right? You can,
how many, how much money, what does it cost three to pick to get people? I know this is good. So
then end turn, give left most friend one attack. I think that sounds fun. I mean, that's, that's an
oxymoron, right? All right. What do you got? Honey. Oh, I went with the little honey play.
Okay. That gets that summons the bug. That's right. All right. Okay. It's just a start. It's
just the first part. That's fine. Early. It's early game. Yeah. I, you don't even see my screen
right now, which is holy shit. The next turn is going to be unbelievable. See in a minute.
I don't know. This is random. So we're hoping it goes to the mosquito. Use the honey. What? How
much does it cost? I thought it was three. Is it, is it one? I know it's three. Yeah. Oh, right in
the back. I see you doing fish strategy. I see. I think I'm still okay. Take that one.
Didn't even respond to me. He's still muted. All right. This is okay. Hold on. Did I, did I
fuck that up? Enter and give five, five to a friend ahead of a head of what that sounds insane.
I want you to know, I didn't ignore you. It was just, it was the longest piss I've ever done in
my life. Oh fuck. Oh fuck. Oh fuck. Oh fuck. I don't know what that does. I think, I think I'm
good. It's like awesome powers. It just kept coming. Oh my God. What a behemoth. You have a
chick. What are you practicing? Hey, I mean, when you tell me that you've got to, we're doing a
bro versus bro, I need to be at least somewhat prepared for it. Got to bring the A game, I guess.
I took a bath last night. Where's the relevance? There is none. I have no place in it. You take
baths a lot. You a bath guy? I am. Are you a bath guy? I love taking baths. Really?
Yes. Yeah. What's your favorite Epsom salt flavor? That's an important question.
I've been going to Himalayan recently. I like the orange too. Yeah, that's fair. That's good.
I pretend I'm an athlete when I, when I use the salts. You doing like a cold bath? No,
it's warm, but I feel like the salt, it's like, oh, my muscles are rejuvenating.
I have an athlete's heart rate. Did you know that? That's pretty sick. What's your resting?
120, whatever it is, a hundred and a hundred, maybe 90. A hundred? I don't, I have no idea.
Mine's 40. You have a 40 resting heart rate. It's 47. Yeah. Oh, you do not. I have a 47
resting heart rate. Yeah. You just keep juicing this guy. I'm not lying to you. I got a 40
resting heart rate. I don't know what you like. Were you actually like an athlete?
You know, I played, I played on soccer teams. I was, I was involved in the action.
That's actually, that's really, really good. I think my resting heart rate score is 70. 75.
Jimmy, I don't think that's great. I'm almost, I'm a neurotic fuck though, dude. Like I'm all over
the place. Wait, wait. In what sense? It's just like my heart rate just, I'm just so, my energy
level just skyrockets and comes down and skyrockets. I'm kind of a mess. I feel that. I feel that.
Are you a daily coffee drinker? Uh, I, yes, I am. I quit recently. Someone quit. Do you
do any other caffeinated beverages or did you just drop every day? Okay. Green or black?
Uh, black tea, black tea, black tea. That's good shit. Oh, this is where we get started.
This is where we get started. Rev it up. Rev it up. Rev it up, baby. Oh, slow it down. Slow the,
turn the engine off. This is the comeback I needed. I like green tea. You want me to prove it?
Like why are you, you want me to prove it? Yeah. Why would I need to prove that too?
Yeah. I don't know. Prove it. Prove that you like green tea to me.
Yeah. I want you to prove to me that you've drank green tea recently. That is so dumb.
I apologize. Pull up my stream and I'll prove it to you right now that I'm a black tea guy.
That you're a black tea drinker? Hold on. I need to, um, I gotta, hold on a second.
Do you want to see where I'm getting down with? Um, what are you getting down with?
You see this? Pull this, pull this bad boy up. I gotta pull the stream. Why didn't it sign me out?
These are my mugs. Are you going to win here? Uh, yes.
Okay. What do you, what do you, I don't want to go over the game though. Let's see what you got.
Oh, you're good. You're good. I got to move it more towards, move it towards your right.
My right. My right. Wait, where are you sitting? I'm sitting. Why do you have, you're drinking
quad mug? I, yeah. Cause I like, so I have one tea, it's English breakfast, but then I
often drink throat goat, which is my other favorite tea. Dude, I thought you would do it.
That's how you were drinking it. Like you were holding it like that and taking sips out.
Yeah. And I like, I, I can just go for, I go for the whole, the big picture. I go around, you know?
Oh my God. I have to play the game. You focus. You've, I'm distracting you back to muting.
Am I doing a homina? Oh, why am I doing that? All right. You got this. You're nervous. You're
anxious. I was so, I want to see your tea. So do you not, do you like green? I like green tea.
It just doesn't have enough caffeine that I can, that I can justify. Yeah. No, I get it.
Still using a two, one bird. You know, this game is so cool. It really is so much fun. Um,
this is food. Okay. I mean, it's, I don't know what the fuck I'm doing. Is the lobster any good?
Lobster's terrible. One of the worst, I would say. You could also hit the fast forward button
during the fight and then you get more time to play. Oh, you do? Yeah. Cause it actually,
for whatever reason, cause the game already knows inherently what happens.
Oh, okay. So you get a little more time. Just starts the timer. It's kind of weird,
but. How'd you get a 19, 24 blowfish? I fed it a lot of pears. That skunk was a great decision.
Yep. That's what I was thinking. I think it's a narrow victory. Narrow.
Unfortunate. If I lose one more, I'm done. It is, it's a quick GG. Yeah, it would be a,
all right. This is where I really, really, where I really get involved here. What? What happened?
Why? Why did I have to think he's supposed to give us power? Wait, who did you pill? Don't
tell me you pulled something. I, I, oh, I sold it. I didn't pill it. Oops. I saw, I thought,
I thought selling did the same thing. I'm noticing this time crunch. I sold the best for you. I sold
the ant. I didn't kill the ant. I thought it was the same thing. Oh, this is bad. Hey, well,
I got pick Ross. You got super awesome. Hey, you know what? Come on. You gotta,
I gotta win one, right? It's my game. All right. All right. All right. All right. Hey,
it was an excellent bout. That was, this, this game's fun though. I like this game a lot.
Three to two German. You actually did inspire me in this game. I did your hedgehog shenanigans.
Oh yeah. You did like the head, the triple hedgehog, right? Uh huh. Yeah. Yeah. So we do
is that this one? Uh, it is say it again. That's a different pack.
Well, no, I would do another one. Oh, no, no, no, no, no. It's a, it's, yeah, it's your turn.
Your pick, your pick of a game. All right. Three to two and you have one game left. I believe
I do have one game left and I feel like it's going to be a bit. So it's the first person to get to
three wins, three, like game wins for five, five. Cause I'm at three right now. It's I'm at three.
You're at two. So house flipper is the last game that I have picked and we're going to need a
third party. Connor eats pants. DM me. Okay. He's ready, able, and willing for the cause.
So we're going to have to set a time limit. I think 15 is 15 too short. Maybe, maybe 30.
I would say at least at least 20 to 25 minutes. Well, let's do, I mean, I'm happy to do 30. I
think that that'd be probably best. It's a night still young. It's only five night is still young.
Congratulations on your super auto pets win. Thank you. Thank you. You know, I thought I'd
speed that up. So we have more time for house flipper. I mean, this is going to be great. I
feel like this is going to be, so have you played house flipper before? I have three hours in the
game. I watched Clint Stevens play it about four years ago and I played it too for about 40 viewers
and, uh, and that, and that's my history of house flipper. What's yours? I mean, this, I, this is
one of my top streamed games ever, ever more than like your numerous, numerous hours in blackjack.
No, I, I, this is one of my favorite games ever made. You've been discussing amount of hours in
blackjack. You know that, right? I have a lot. I would, I discussed things a little, I think a
little harsh, but gross it's like, it's like six to 7,000 hours. That's like this people play
league of legends for like 10,000 hours and not a big deal ripping in hours. All right. So you know
how to, there's not, okay. The competition here is who can make a cooler looking house, right? It's
not like gamer skills or anything. This is just like your design skills. This is like from the
heart. Yeah. Make something beautiful. I have a feeling that you're going to be pretty good on
this. I'm kind of hoping, but we'll see. So we have the third party that we're going to do a walk
through and they're going to pick which house is better, which house is better looking. We're well
designed, right? Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. The better house. So we need to pick a house that's small.
Yeah. We, we, let me see. I'm booting in right now. You got, you got, you, you are up to date here.
You got all your tools and money and everything. Uh, let me, let me double check. I should, right?
Cause I think I went offline mode, which was my one problem. Okay. That's a terrible start. Oh,
I can't believe that worked. It worked. All right. If I hit continue game, what happens?
How much money you got? 280,000. There you go. All right. So, and only my hand. You only have your
hand. Well, here you probably only have your hand. Well, no, if you hold down right click, you should
have pretty much everything. I'm seeing one big old hand. He just got the, he's just got the hand.
I added your files. Yeah. So you should have, should have all the tools here. You don't have
a flamethrower. Say it again. Let me go to the, let me go to the burned house and see if maybe
things are different. Maybe the abandoned house. Let me go to the abandoned house and see what's
going on over there. It might, it might take you a second or two to, you might have to do the
missions though, to unlock the tools, right? No, I know how to do this. I know how to, this
shouldn't take me more than 15 to 20 seconds max. Okay. So we need to pick a house that's small
that we can, it's not going to take us like two hours to do. Yes. What is your recommendation?
Where's your heart lead you? I would say if you go to, when you go to the laptop and you go to browse
like for purchase, we're talking about maybe the many generations house or the, um,
slightly larger. Do you want to go bigger? We can go bigger. No, that's, that's what I mean.
It's slightly larger. I was thinking abandoned or, or the burned house. A home admin legends
could be fine too. I think that's great. I'm down. Let's do the home admin legend. Home admin
legends. Yeah. Okay. Great. Great. Great. Great. Actually that might be too small. Let's do,
maybe the one to move into might be good. And now it's apartment. We're going to find like
one that's got enough that we can really design stuff in. I mean, this is like the breaking bad
house, right? The breaking bad house. Yeah, there's like, it's like a reference to breaking
bad. Um, what about the century old one? Not a contrived one. I think this, okay. This century
house, I think is where we're going to go here. That's big enough. It's got two floors, got a big
living area. I think this is good. I'm coming in hot. I'm coming in hot. This is surely worked.
And you're going to buy that house, the century old house, and then you're going to go there.
I'm not going to touch anything, by the way. Is this a Germanism? My chat just became German.
Wait, you just. Does that happen to you ever? Like you're reading German in your chat? Yeah,
it's everyone's speaking in German. What? I don't know if that's one of those German things. It's
like, ah, it's time to speak German, everybody. Not that I'm aware of. I hope that didn't start
it. Or did you change your language on like the little cog wheel? No, no. It's like it's
auto correcting. Yeah. No, they're just speaking good old fashioned German. Really? Okay. Interesting.
All right. All right. Let's see the house we're going with. By the way, I want to make this really
clear outside and inside. Outside and inside. Outside and inside. Be aware of that because
whoever, you know, Connor walks through, how's your yard look? How's your, how's the front door look?
Many Generations House. I think that's good. Many Generations, I think it's a good house.
Are we running that one? That's the one, yeah. I have not moved. All right. I don't think I
have many tools, but I also don't need many tools. What do you have? Okay. Do you have access to
painting, tiling, demolition, brush cutter? Brush cutter? So I got my hands and a good work ethic.
Wait, wrong house? Wait, there's a Many Generations House. What? Did I do the wrong house?
Oh, maybe I said that and that's not what it was. Oh, Ludwig said the wrong house. Oh. Oh,
I just said the wrong house and you disagreed with me. Oh, century old house. Is that, what did I say?
Uh, it is supposed to be the Many Generations. You need to be able to clean and stuff. Oh, look at
this. The turtle house. If you don't have access to your tools, you're not going to be able to do it.
I can clean everything. I can pick things up. Wait, which house is it?
Unless you have the specific mop, I don't think you can do it. Um, what was this house again?
Century old house. How expensive are we talking? Like a hundred thousand?
You're gonna run me out. Yeah, you might be able to go, I think you can go into your like config file
and give yourself all the tools. Yeah, that's what I was trying to do. Um. Yeah, I gave him my save,
but it won't, if for some reason the tools won't click. Century chat chat. Am I dumb? Is there a
house here? Am I just missing it? Century. Am I stupid? Let me see. Is this DLC? Oh, this might
be a DLC house. Okay. That changes things then. You have a DLC house. I own all the DLC for this
game. All right. So that might, yeah, that is DLC. It is. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Okay. Okay. So let's do,
what, what do you have access to? What's like the biggest house you have access to?
Uh, the biggest house, the absolute largest is the house on the castle or the house on the moon.
Just married. Yeah. But the ones that I think would be good for this would be like the, like
I got a home in car, turtle house, you know, the boring house. That's a fun one because then you
have to spruce it up. One to flip the turtle. The turtle house is small though. But we only have 30
minutes. Is there, I mean. That's true. You're right. We don't have all day. Um, which one is
bigger? Turtle house or the one to flip? I think, do I have the one to flip? Well, yeah,
we'll do turtle. The turtle is very big, very easy. Um, I just, I'm concerned you don't have
access to tools and you won't let me, let me, let me get into it and then see, let me go there and
see. Okay. Yeah. Cause if you don't have access to the painting tool, then I mean, you can't paint
the walls. Yeah. All I can do is lift things and move them around. I'll just readjust where
everything cleaning not available yet. That's absurd. Okay. Okay. Yeah. I had it earlier.
There is, there's missions you can do that unlock all the tools, but it takes like 45 minutes.
That save file I gave you should work, but I don't know why it's not. It's supposed to work
in the sense that it's supposed to give you the tools. You're just supposed to have my save file
essentially. Right. Okay. Let me, hey, let me, let me give it one more. Is there a console here?
Oh, is there really? Okay. How do you enable console commands? Cause I used to do it with like
an INI file. Oh, you don't have the DLC. So the save won't work. Oh, that's what it is. Okay.
That makes sense. All right. Let me buy the DLC then either, either that or there's somebody's
people saying there's console commands that I don't necessarily go into your save game.
Press tilde and enter a press. What the fuck is that? Enter the code IDDQD. Leave the pause
screen. Cheats are now enabled to open console. Just press that like little tilde. Have you tried
this? I have not. I don't know what this is. Is that, is that, you're not like fucking around
with us, right? That actually works. I have to get all the DLCs. I would try the IDD. Let me try.
Let me try this guy. Let me try this guy. Am I just saying something out loud? That was like bad.
Five DLCs. Okay. Press tilde and enter the code in the game. Yeah. So I guess in the game,
do you, can you open up the dev console with the, um, I'm booting in. That's the fucking doom code.
Nevermind. Oh, it's a, it's a bit of a meme here. Yeah. I think, I think you are right that it's
through the system files. I know you can do it through the system files, but it might be a little
too much stumbling for this remainder of this afternoon here. Oh, there is a code though. If
you put in tilde, is there a code that you can, what's a good code? We have a few. No, no, no.
The IDDQ thing isn't fake. That's real. It's real. Why are people saying that was the doom code?
Okay. Google house flipper, unlock all tools command. Okay. I think, I think we're making
progress. Okay. Cool. Very cool. Now what I'm supposed to do is hit, um, she turned out and
able to open the console, press this in game. Oh, be careful. I was going to say be careful
opening the dev console. Oh, what happened? Nothing. You just worried me. Uh, and then
I'm saying, I don't know what, I don't know what it's going to show. Like I would just, I would,
I don't know. Who knows? Right, right, right. If I hit, apparently if I have this code and then I hit
F three, I get all the tools and then if I hit F five, I get all the money. Oh,
Oh, all right. We're in business eight improves all the tools. Oh, that's great.
Are we in business? Oh, we're in business. We are. I have everything now. All right. Awesome.
Perfect. So, um, so let me give you a quick little rundown of house flipper. So you see,
you have a grid. You have, it should be like, uh, it looks like the house is on bricks and a
foundation. It's like a 10 by 10, sometimes 15 by 15, the grid on the foundation. And you'll see
this numbers that correspond to where you need to place your tiling. And if you see on the left
side, there's like a four, a three, and a, and a two, you need, there has to be at least one tile
on the ground. All right, let's just go before I embarrass myself anymore. Um, okay. Yeah.
Understood. Noted. Noted. All right. So timer starts, timer starts now. Or you actually know
how to play it. Cause like, there's like a specific stupid shit that you like need to,
like, you have to clean with the mop. You can't like use your hands. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. No.
Hey, me. I come on talking to Mr. House flipper. I'm excited. I'm really all right. So you need to
make this look as dazzling and beautiful as possible. Connor's coming in. Bingo. You want
to come in and he wants the best house possible. Okay. You let's, let's get it. Let's get to it.
Timer starts now. Good luck. Goodbye. Okay. Here we go. First of all, get rid of this shit.
We're going to cut this grass. He's going to forget about the fucking lawn and mine's going
to look incredible. He is going to completely neglect and completely forget the lawn.
Connor's going to look over and he's going to be like, this is disgustingly ugly.
By the way, Connor, Connor, I hope you're going to be very, very, um, thorough. What was that?
Okay. That looks all right. Make sure nothing around the back. That was a dragon ball.
Why? Yeah. He's going to go in there and look, Ludwig is going to have a 10 minute debacle where
he can't figure out what kind of couch he's picking while his lawn is uncut. Do this first.
I don't give a shit about couch. All an interior really is, is like the accent walls
and a chandelier and you, wow. Wait, I can't, I can't stop talking. Connor might be watching.
Connor can't watch these three. He needs to be completely, he needs to not know anything.
Hey, it looks good. No weeds, right? Right here. Get rid of that. I'm going to plant a couple of
trees. I'm telling you, he's going to, he is going to neglect the fuck out of his front outside
garden. Oh my God. And I'm going to be a streamer in there. Plants. Let's go. Let's go. How about
let's something, um, let's do these. Oh yeah. Let's go. Look at that. Already perfect. Not bad.
Can I extend this out a little bit with some gravel? We need, uh, outside. We need floor.
We need outside shit to go. Floor coverings. I knew I just want, I just want stone. I want,
I want crushed stone. Where is crushed stone? Stone. Where's crushed stone? Where is it? It's
like, where is it? What the fuck? They're not going to fucking, they're not going to tell the
difference. So who cares? Cobblestone. Here it is. Delete that. Delete that. Delete that. Delete
that. Why am I fucking Santa Claus? All right. I just want a little bit more of a bedazzle.
It's all about first impressions. I'm going to put like a nice thing of flowers here,
right there. It's a first impression. Okay. That's all right. Line that with flowers.
I need to like delete this. Let's take care of the outside, the paint on the outside. Hold on.
All right. Maybe something funky, right? Something funky. Somebody said Connor is too dumb to notice
that. Connor is like an incredibly intelligent young man. Okay. Um, excuse me. All right. What's
something that's, that doesn't scream? I'm trying too hard to make the judge like me,
but it's, but it's, but it's pizzazzy enough where it's going to stand out. I'm going to say
the outside of the house is going to be fresh morning. This thing right here, a fresh morning.
How's that look? I don't like it. No, it's all right. It's fine. It's fine. It's fine. Is it
fine? It's fine. That is it. Is that an awful color? I can't tell. What's Connor's favorite
color? Does anybody know? Who here watches Connor's stream regularly? What's his favorite
color? I'm going to say it's probably like blue, right? Just put all of Connor's favorite things
in the house. Like just have them on tables and shit. Is it blue? Okay. Yeah. We're going blue.
We're going fucking like bright blue. Uh, paint. Blue. But isn't that wicked ugly?
Oh, that's right. He does. He loves Sonic the Hedgehog. I'm playing to,
I'm playing to a strength here. He loves Sonic the Hedgehog. I remember, yeah, we took an Uber
together at the streamer awards. I remember he had, um, headphones in like, uh, AirPods
and he was just like sitting there like fucking going like this, like pumping himself up and
just like hanging out. And we were like, oh shit. And all you could hear was like blasting in his
ears. It was like Sonic heroes. I was like, that's a good song. That's based. Oh yeah. That's what
I'm saying. I got to get up higher. This house is fucking ugly. I'm really curious what he is
doing over there. I can't wait to find out. This is what a fun, I, this is a guy like this idea
is he gives up, you give two people like 30 minutes to like 40 minutes to flip a house
and then somebody, a third party has to come in. I love that. This is fun. I like this a lot.
I think we're going to be time efficient here. I know he's going to neglect so much shit.
He's probably like walking around with a flame thrower, like laughing, right? Like he's going to
have to be. That's what I did when I first got the flamethrower. He didn't have the flamethrower
before. No way. And look, you might be thinking I'm wasting time on the exterior. I don't think so.
The interior is easy. It's out here. The first impression that matters the absolute most.
I need to get a scaffolding. This is going to take like, this is going to take the whole time.
How long have we been doing this for? You're wasting time. How long, how long,
how much longer do I have? Nine minutes? What do you mean nine minutes? I have 20. It's okay.
It's been okay. I have 20 minutes. That's plenty of time to get in there. And we'll shit up a
little bit. Get these delete the rocks. I have unlimited money. So who cares? Also huge tip.
I got to get rid of these paint cans and shit because that's an eyesore. That's a big problem.
And I don't think Ludwig's going to do that. All like the debris and shit that you die. Yeah.
I'm not going to leave this crap everywhere. All right. I need scaffolding at this part out of the
way first. I'm going to sell it. Don't worry. I'm not going to be an idiot. Why am I even putting
them around here? It's only the front. Oh my God. Just go. I think I can get up. I can stand up
there. All right. All right. All right. Go, go, go, go, go, go. I need paint cans up there.
What is make house? How do I get rid of that? How do I get, how do I delete this?
Make house? I'm making it. How do I, I can't sell it. Let's do this then. Turkey. Um,
I don't think that fits there, but hold on. Oh shit. Yeah, I think so.
Oh, all right. All right. Keep going. Keep going. All I need is five minutes in the house.
10 minutes in the house. Get up. I got to get rid of these ugly marks here. Sell these. I
can work clean up as I go. It's good. Clean up as you go. Don't fuck around. I got to get rid of
the how you doing. That's so awful. That looks good. Almost ready. All right. We're good.
Exterior is almost done. And as you go, now leave the rocks. It's aesthetic. I need lamps,
lights, lights, lights, lights, lights, quick, quick, quick, quick. Something cool. Um,
outdoor, outdoor lamps, lights that lead in. Cool looking lamps, cool LEDs or something. Strips.
Yep. Okay. LED strip two meters. High intensity. These are going to be, I mean,
he loves something like the hedgehog. Why can't I put it down? These aren't bright.
That doesn't even look that bad. All right. Hold on. I need a little bit more life out here.
Um, I need plants. Wait, no. What are these? What are these? Hold on.
Hold on. I need to put, Oh my God. What are these? Just playing the fiddle. This looks like a
fucking G mod house. Okay. Okay. Okay. I need plants. I need plants, plants, plants, plants,
plants and lights, circus table lamp, whatever. Okay. This is going to be this color. How do I
turn them on? Turn them on. Holy shit. Cool. All right. I need a, I need plants. I got to,
I'll get to put a sauna in the fucking house. All right. Come on. Come on. Come on. Come on.
All right. I got to go inside. Go fuck it. We're doing a sauna. We're going to have a whole sauna
in here. Oh my God. It's so dirty. It's so dirty in here. Get rid of all this fucking bullshit.
I don't want to use the dragon balls to get this out of here. All right. This is the sauna. This
is the sauna. Okay. Here we go. I don't want this thing. Get it out of here. The dragon balls in
here, I guess. I don't know. Okay. Clean, clean, clean, clean, clean, clean, clean, clean, clean,
clean, clean. I would probably like the dragon balls. Yeah, I can display them later. I only
have like 16 minutes. Hey, can we do an extension? Can we do like a 10 minute extension?
Feeling a little stressed over there? I just, there's a lot I want to do.
You know, I'll grant 40 minutes, 40 minutes in. Okay. So we got an extra 10 minutes.
Yeah. 10 minutes. That's good. That's good. That sounds good. Good luck.
I know it's a Christmas tree. I just heard that you're doing a Christmas theme.
He's doing Christmas theme. What a mistake. Christmas in fucking January? What is it?
Christmas in March? Big mistake. I'm just going to see right through that. I know him. All right,
let's go. Let's go. Sauna. The walls of a sauna are wood. This has to be done first. Wood panels.
Here we go. That looks good. Handling. Let's go for it. It's wood on the ground too. I can't
wait to present this. Could there be a toilet in the sauna? Like it's my version of a sauna,
right? Should it be like a toilet? What do you guys think? Maybe? It's possible. There's that.
The floor is already wood, but I want, I want a different wood. I want like a nicer,
more pristine looking wood. Let's go for sauna. This is a sauna plus shower. I need plumbing,
right? Wait, that's not correct. Oh, here we go. Sauna door. You got to build these walls again.
It's already so loud. I'm sorry. Hey, there's the sauna door. Okay. I need a light in here.
Um, like a lamp. Lights. Yeah. Lights. Okay. Something hanging just like a wall lamp.
Ooh, this looks nice. I turn it on. I need a light switch. Elegant light switch. Ooh, nice. Very,
very swanky in here. Very swanky. I like it. Okay. Sauna. Sauna sand timer. Okay. Sauna bench.
Here's the sauna heater. It goes like right here. Yeah. Cause it goes like, shh. Now I need, yeah,
sauna bucket with a ladle. Put that there for now. How do I spell this? Oh my God. How do you spell
sauna? Sauna? Swan? What's going on? What's happening? What happened? Sauna. That's how
I was spelling it the whole time. Okay. Bench. Make it a little bit darker. There. We're going to do,
we're going to have to go across the back wall here. Very nice. Oh, this is so cool. Ludwig
does not have a sauna. Don't fucking leak this by the way. I'd be pissed if you do. I'd be really
mad. He's going to be like sauna. Don't like seriously. I don't even know who this is.
No, I don't want that. Sauna. Okay. Oh my fucking God. Head lift. Okay. There we go.
So I can like lie down at either end. Very nice. Almost done. Corner bench. Sauna sand timer.
Sauna lamp. That's better. Okay. There's your sauna. Sauna's done. Wait, I need a bench. I
need like a stool to put this on. Like right next to it. Like right here. Right there. The
bucket's got to go here. Take a look at that. Why is the lights off? Is your sauna? It's dark in
here. All right. Those lights are actually, I might move them, but they're okay. Wall. Yep. You got it.
You got it. I'm good. I'm good. I'm good. I'm good. Don't worry. Okay. Walls. Walls. Walls. Walls.
Back. Oh, back. Where is it? Oh, there we go. Okay. Walls. Wall panels. Here we go. It's this
one here. Beautiful. Beautiful. Yep. I got to get some kind of decoration in here too, right?
Ceiling's got to be wood. All right. I need, I need a better floor than that. Much better.
Floor panels. Please. Yeah. That's a sauna. That's what they look like. Yeah. That's what it's,
this is a sauna. You get in here, you go shh. Ceiling. Uh, I need to paint the ceiling brown.
Can I even do the ceiling? Coffee. Cocoa. I guess this one. I don't think I can paint the ceiling.
Oh my god, dude. Come on. Dude, I can't paint the fucking ceiling brown. Um, how do I do this?
Why is it so dark in here? I need more lights. What the fuck? What is this? Oh my god. We need
more time. All right. All right. Speed it up. Speed it up. Walls. I need lamps in the corners.
Lamps. Now. Lamps. Uh, all right. This one's, that's enough. It's kind of like an old lady house.
This is very galactic, I think. It's ugly. I don't like it. Maybe one. Oh, it makes too many
shadows everywhere. Looks like there's spider webs all over your house. That thing sucks.
Something else. This is, I like that. This one's good. Brass. No, I hate brass. I don't want brass.
Okay, cool. We're doing, um, ouch. Just go in here. Living room here. We separated by wall.
Uh, and the wall is going to be, the door is going to be here. No, like yeah, here. Right here. It's
three, right? It's a three or four. I think it's three. You only have six minutes.
No way. There's way more than six minutes. There's way more than six minutes. How about, um,
this is fine. I need a little more room. Little section. Okay. We need paint.
This is bedroom. This is bathroom. We're going to keep bathroom where it is.
This is bedroom. This is kitchen and shit. This is not. I need a kitchen. This is bedroom. This is
kitchen. Okay. Kitchen net right there. How much time do I have actually? Truly how much time?
And then it's furniture. Okay. We need a couch. I'm going to go with something really sleek.
Something sleek and thin. Are these all pink? Oh yeah. This right here. Snowman wooden corner.
I need snowman. I'm in pastel. No, no, no, no, no. Snowman. Just regular snowman.
No, man. Wooden standing kitchen set. Here it is. And there's an oven in it. Perfect.
But what kind of color do I want here? Okay. I'm thinking the white. I'm thinking black and white.
Get this out of here. Perfect fit. Is this the wrong way? I got to flip this. It's the wrong way.
You get an order to make this in somebody's house and you build it the fucking wrong direction.
That's got to be flush. Connor is going to be very detailed. Nice. Good. I mean, if a fridge
right here, uh, that's fine. No, uh, make it a white. Hey, I need more light in here. It's so dark.
I need some bright ass lights in here. Okay. This fridge. I need a table,
little table, just a little one. Table. Um, this will brighten it up a little bit with,
yep. This will brighten it up. This looks like an operating room. No, no, no. I only have like
eight minutes. Hmm. I don't, I like, I kind of like that color. Where's the TV going to go?
This is too big. Oh fuck. That's too big. It's a ping pong table. Countess table.
That's a detail that somebody will overlook. That's cutting board. How about like a round table?
Round table auto. Oh my God. Perfect. These are so uncomfortable looking. This is just every chair
that a dark souls NPC sits in that you pick an item up off of. Uh, come on something quick.
These are fine. That's whatever. It doesn't matter. The windows right there. You can get a big fresh
chair out there. I gotta close these. Oh fuck. I need to paint the walls. I need a different
floor. We need carpets and shit. I need bed. How much time is left? Dracula bed. All right. I'm
doing a huge Dracula bed. It's going to be a fucking wow factor. Wait, I can go down. Okay.
The bedroom is downstairs and it's going to be a huge Dracula bed. What the fuck? Bathroom. Fuck.
Should I ask for another extension? What do you think? How's he doing? Does he, does he need an
extension? You think? Oh, we're running out of time. We're running out of time. Quickly, quickly,
quickly, quickly. Bedroom set down here. I get the walls look awful. Bedroom set. Not that thing.
It says what? That's a fucking dog bed. That's fine. Um, TV. I need a huge TV. 85 inch TV.
Okay. How do you get into the, it's, I don't, just wait. I, we have to put stuff down. Carpets.
Hmm. I need carpeting. Floor, floor coverings. Um, my God, hurry the fuck up. It looks so like
dead and lifeless down here. Oh my God. Dude, really? Okay. Cool. Um, TV is on.
Need light. Just like a big, wait, hold on. Clean that up. Time, time check. This is TV room.
Painting, painting, painting. Four minutes. Way too big. Way too big. Like dude, like dude. Yeah.
That's like, oh cool. Wow. Who gives a shit, right? Like another one up here. Um, what's this?
Fuck. Not that. Quick. It's all accent work right now. Sunrise. Oh my God. Fuck you. Small.
Just do two of them and put this one upside down. Actually kind of beautiful. All right. I need
paint, paint, paint, paint, paint, paint, paint, paint, paint. I'm out of time actually. Walls,
paint. Walls, paint, paint. Oh my God. I hate pressure. That's gotta be like this one.
Oh, that's so boring and plain. Something else. Quick. Fuck. Oh no. This is bad.
Fresh carrots. It's a kitchen. This is why we do the exterior first because this is going to look
all right. Hurry. Hurry. Wait. Exit wall. No. Too late. Fuck you. Get over there. All right.
Yeah. Okay. Delete, delete, delete, delete, delete. Don't make it look ugly. Okay. Go, go, go, go,
go, go, go, go, go, go, go. What else is in here? I don't have a bathroom. Where's the fucking
plumbing? Where's the plumbing? Why? Where's the plumbing? Hurry, hurry, hurry, hurry. Go, go, go,
quick. You can take a shower in the sauna. God damn it. I need a shower installation. Shower.
Where's the shower fixture? Time. One minute. Paint, paint, paint, paint, paint, paint, paint,
paint, paint. Calm down. Oh shit. The shower's in the way. That's the accent wall. Okay. Why is
there so much fucking plumbing in here? That's so ugly. What? I don't even know what's supposed
to be in here. TV room? Oh, this is just a lounge room. This is the relax room to get out of the
bedroom. You need a sink? Oh my God. Get this fucking thing out of the way. It's good enough.
Throw the paper. Oh, I got it. We good? Hey, German. Hey. Yeah. I was wondering if you wanted
to wrap up in a bit. How you're feeling? I know it's been stressful. Do you want to wrap maybe
like another, what is it? Two minutes left. 43, 30 is on my clock. Maybe 45, 30. Oh, how are you
doing? Do you think you want an extra two or three minutes? I mean, I've been done for like a little
bit here, but I'm happy. All right. No, we can call it right there. You call it right now? Oh,
yeah. That sounds good. Right now. Yeah. Yeah. We can call it right now. I think that's it.
You know what? Hey, let's just be gentle about this. Let's call it. Let's just call it. So you
want to call it? Build? Oh, yeah. We can say the build is ready. Is your build ready for? Oh,
yeah. Yeah. I think my build is ready to have a peek at it. Oh, he's stalling. Okay. I get it.
No, I'm not stalling. I'm ready to go. I'm ready to go. I'm ready to go. I need to sink. Okay.
I'm here and ready to go. Question. All right. So you got to start from outside the house,
standing where the beach is. Right. And we're going to have Connor, he can open up each one
of our streams and bring him in this call. And we will individually do a nice slow walkthrough
of our property. And from there, Connor can decide who has the better designed house.
I think that sounds excellent to me. And pencils down, by the way.
Right now? Pencils down? Pencils down. What about one plumbing system, though?
Pencils down. Pencils down. Pencils down. Pencils down. I don't need another pencil.
You don't need any more. You don't have to sharpen it. We're good.
All right. All right. All right. All right. Pencils down. I'm outside my house. I'm ready to go.
All right. I'll bring Connor on the call. Do we want to do yours first or mine first?
Let's do a tour of... Let's do mine. I made you go first earlier. We can do mine if you'd like.
Let me open your stream. Okay. I'll Discord screen share if that's easier for you.
Hey, guys. Connor, one second. Just give me one. I need some water. I'm a little anxious. Give me water.
Yeah, I got your stream. I got it. Is he okay? I think he's okay.
He's very nervous, it sounds. I haven't heard him like that in a long time.
What's up, dude? I'm doing good. I'm ready to judge.
I'm just... I'm so ready. I'm actually... I'm kind of nervous too, if I'm honest.
You all right? I don't know.
I'll just go. What's like online?
For this entire contest, if he loses, he has to play Smite on stream. And if I lose,
I have to play ToonTown. Oh.
Oh, okay. Discord stream sharing if you prefer.
Connor, do you know what you're doing here? Yeah, I have to figure out how to turn you up.
I don't know how to work audio. Audio's dumb.
Yeah, basically, Connor is here as our representative who will be judging which house
is the best based off the constraints given, the house we had, and the time given.
Your job is to come in here and just complete independent third party.
We're going to give you a walkthrough of both houses and you are to determine who's is better.
Sounds good. Does two minutes on the
clock for a walkthrough sound fair to you, Jerma? Do I watch a stream or am I able to like do it
and like do I have to boot up my own house? I think a solid three minutes.
Three minutes. Three minutes sounds great. I'm Discord screen sharing, but also my stream,
it's up to you. I imagine Discord screen sharing might be a bit easier.
Yeah, I'll just I'll cover Ludwig's face with my face because your audio is delayed
because I'm watching your stream. And if I can start, can I go or
let me know when you're ready, Connor? OK, I'm ready.
All right, let me let me get my timer set a timer for three minutes.
Connor, welcome our house, which we've called Relax.
As you can see, when you walk in, there's an accent wall, two accent walls, in fact,
because I wanted to I wanted it to be like a like a dream house.
Right. This to make you remember what it was like being young.
You know, oh, so let's let's actually head down walking in.
I don't want to reveal too much. We look to our right.
You can see we have a television, a nice reminds me of my dad couch.
Yeah. Yeah. You might notice the gun.
We just like a little bit of safety, I guess a little bit of safety will turn here.
And we have some nice bonsai trees
just to decompress and and we'll keep moving over.
Here's the kitchen area.
Now, again, turn off the flashlight.
Oh, sorry. Yeah.
Oh, yeah. There's like a big like resident.
My bad. Sorry. I'm so stressed.
Here you go.
This is the kitchen. This is the kitchen.
Very pink themed. Again, very, very relaxed base.
So we have our fridge here. We have our microwave.
Right. This is, you know, but but but also.
Hold on. OK, wait a minute.
Why is the microwave just like on like a children's table?
It's because we actually have a really short
member living in this house.
Also, I don't know why I pointed out that it was on the children's table,
not that there is a pistol sitting on the microwave.
Safety is key.
So we have this as our main kitchenette area.
There's a stove, a sink.
We'll ignore that.
Now, let's move over to the bathroom.
So we have his and hers.
Hey, you're breathtaking.
You stand up here in PTV, of course.
And then hers, it's, you know, it's a little more like that.
It's a good girl toilet.
But it also has safety considerations because I understand this is a turret.
I understand that it's it's it's it's it's scarier.
It's scary.
Women have been asking for that.
They've been like they've been asking for like solutions to the problems, you know.
Where's the wall?
Do you like streaming, Connor?
It's open floor pan.
I think I do.
I enjoy it.
Check this out.
Whoa.
It is the ultimate stream room.
We have everything.
3080 in there.
We got at maximum GPU.
That is a while.
That's like that's like Han Solo's chair.
I'm like, hey, someone ate my sandwich.
Oh, right.
Yeah, you got a clock.
Is that like the like street?
Like did he say that like the stream?
Yeah, yeah.
It's like the streamer thing.
It's famous.
Like someone ate my sandwich.
Yeah.
So he starts the stream like that.
He goes.
Yeah.
Oh, guys, somebody my sandwich.
I think everybody.
Yeah, you get it.
I get it.
And so and that's what are these little orange orbs on the floor?
I've seen them around.
There's like what are those guys?
You didn't clean them up.
Oh, these guys.
No, actually, they're accent orbs.
They're accent accent accent orbs.
Yeah, it's a European thing.
Well, time's up.
Don't ask any more questions.
Anyway, that concludes the tour of our house.
Dragon Balls is what they are.
Excuse me.
They're Dragon Balls.
Yeah, I didn't want to get DMCA's striked, but they're Dragon Balls.
This is like on like an island.
Yeah, yeah, it's it's it's like cats out of the bag.
It's similar to Kamei's house in Dragon Ball.
So.
Oh, oh, OK.
It was a pretty good house.
It was OK.
It was neat.
That was it.
That was that was the Maison de Rsistance.
Pice de Rsistance.
You know, I don't speak that.
You got to you got to like like what does that mean?
It's my house, my house.
Oh, OK.
Yeah, it's your house.
I get it.
Complicated.
Jerma, what's your what?
What do you work with?
I am ready.
All right, you do.
Connor, you do you have my stream?
Oh, I got to put this in.
Yeah, hold on.
I'll pull up the live stream.
One of the old live streaming.
All right.
Not live.
You want to do.
Look, what do you have?
You have a timer.
You can set.
All right.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Hey, Siri, set a timer for two minutes and 58 seconds.
I just I started a little late.
All right.
You're good to go.
OK, here we go.
Connor, hi.
Welcome to the house.
The first I like.
I like the Christmas like price gun.
Exactly.
First of all.
Right.
Points already.
So as you notice, we're on the beach.
We don't have to spend too much time in that.
But as you see, I have a nice cobblestone walkway
leading towards two relics that have been lit up pretty well.
Those are very, very, very, very expensive bronze statues.
How are you doing?
You know, it's such a thing that we ask every time somebody.
It's like it's like welcoming.
Like, you know, you know what it's about.
So we're feeding into him a little bit.
We want people to come in and tell us how they're doing.
Right.
And hopefully we're doing well.
I've got a cool a painting of I don't know.
I don't know who that is.
It just was expensive to come in the front door.
As you see, pretty beautiful plan here.
We've got the the mustard walls got a little bit.
This is smart TV, by the way.
I don't think Ludwig had a smart TV in his house.
I had a curved monitor, which I mean, that's kind of a meme, isn't it?
Yeah, I don't really get the application of those.
Yeah, weird.
Like mine really impartial, not really impartial.
So I just he's right.
I mean, the kitchen, it's a small kitchen.
But, you know, the big coup de grace here is this is a sauna.
Smart TVs cause cancer.
So this is a nice sauna.
You can get in here, sit down, relax.
Turn out if you've ever been to a sauna.
He thought about that, though, because saunas prevent cancer.
So if you go to the smart TV, you can walk in the sauna and then you're fine.
And then you can sweat out all the talking and everything.
Beach.
Yep.
In beach.
You don't need it.
It's really nice.
This door go outside.
That is don't forget about the fact that this is like an apartment door.
I think it's cool.
Number 12 bathrooms in there.
Yeah.
Who the fuck cares about the bathroom?
Bathrooms are dumb.
Anyways, this is just a little.
Let's take a look inside the bathroom.
You can hang your coat over there if you wanted.
Is that the toilet?
What's that blue paint splodger?
It's where that's not.
It was just somebody.
It's it's an accident.
Here's the sink.
That's great.
Yeah, toilet paper.
This is a state of the art.
It's one of those nice toilets.
It is like the wall shower for me and walk in the shower.
Sure.
Yeah, just like some exposed plumbing in some spots.
It's hard to get out of.
But then this, by the way, this door is fucking tiny.
It's like a his and hers shower.
Yeah, it's a it's any wherever.
OK, here we go.
Down here into the this is just a bedroom area.
I got you.
This is also smart TV.
And you get the big big.
Be careful.
Master bedroom.
Really, it's up to you what you want to put in here.
You want to have this house.
You could because there's nothing in there right now.
Yeah.
I mean, you could put it could be like a den down here.
They could be a play area.
Yeah.
Yeah, I feel like it's a fixer upper down there.
But I feel like it reminds me of the movie Room.
Yeah, that's what it reminds me of.
Like Brie Larson.
But I really feel like it's the sauna connected to the kitchen.
I think the design, especially the exterior, the blue,
I think speaks a lot to one of my favorite series.
I might be yours, too.
It's not the hedgehog.
Oh, I love Sonic.
Yeah, one of my favorites.
All right.
Time's up, time's up, time's up, time's up.
Brown housing over, brown housing over.
Tails is cool, too, isn't it?
Because this color is tails.
It's like he's right.
I had pink, which was like.
You were you said it was like Dragon Ball.
It was like it was like Sonic's balls, which are.
They're not pink.
And I was even right.
It's not even correct.
A new picture of them.
There's a lot of picture.
I'm sure you can find many different colors.
Amy, why is pretty spamming Smite Sunday to me right now?
So, Connor, with all that information, where's your head at?
What are you thinking?
Talk to us.
Do I need to give like a number score for each
or just say like which one is better?
You could you could you could.
Yeah, give a number score starting starting with starting with me.
If you could.
What I like about yours, Ludwig was, you know, the it had heart, you know,
like you obviously had like a vision when you went into it.
But I like how like a third of the space was a bathroom or two bathrooms is and hers.
You know, exactly.
Well, so kind of on his story.
But Jerma has a his and her shower, which I thought was kind of a neat addition
where you can say that.
Not him.
I just want to cut inside and cut you off.
No, I never said those words.
Let's be very, very clear.
This is a shower.
You can enter from two different spots.
That doesn't make his interest.
It just makes it a hazard.
I want to be clear about that.
That that glass door opening into a wall is a threat to liability.
All right.
But but yeah, I see where you had that.
Yeah, I like I liked your basement Ludwig because I, you know, I'm a streamer
and I like how it kind of thought of that, you know,
is like if I'm going to live in one of these, I'd probably need that that space.
Yeah, as a streamer, I always feel like I want to ready to go.
Don't you want to do don't you want to decorate your own space?
Yeah, and see, and that's that's what I like about Jerma's.
That was Jerma not only to have a bedroom downstairs with a smart TV,
but he also thought of like, you know,
preventive measures with the smart TV, with the sauna.
And you can say like, you know, the sauna is unnecessary
because it's like they're on the beach.
But it's at the same time that sometimes you don't want to be in the sun
and you want to like feel the heat.
You want to be I don't want to go outside all the time.
Right.
But it's like I'm in the sun.
I don't want to go outside.
Sauna kind of doesn't make any sense in like a summer beach house, does it?
Not really.
But you know, it's kind of like a status symbol, though.
It's like, yeah, I'm rich enough to have a sauna while I live on the beach.
Connected to your kitchen, by the way.
It is connected to the kitchen.
It's very accessible.
Although kind of I'm not going to tell you anything bad about my house.
It's a great house.
So Connor, what would you give my score, final score,
keeping the stream room in consideration, also the protection?
It's hard for you to like give a number score.
But this guy just spoke for the first time I chat.
His name is Minecraft's quickscoper 2007.
And I'm going to have him pick because it's his first.
I'm going to have him give you a number.
Minecraft quickscoper.
What do you think, man?
Is he going to do Jerma's too or?
Yeah.
I mean, maybe whatever he wants.
That's OK.
He gave you a five little.
You got a five out of five or out of 10.
Did he clarify?
I don't know.
He just said five.
OK.
He said Jerma's an eight.
What about you, Connor?
How much watch time does he have on both of our channels?
His account was made today.
This could be like a band account for me.
That's, you know, making their way over to you.
I think I think that's a pretty accurate score, though.
It's a band account on your channel.
Could be, you know.
So so all right.
So you give me a five.
Jerma gets a point.
I will say I will say eight is a little generous for Jerma
only because you did point out the fact that the shower does go into the wall,
which kind of goes against the whole his and hers idea of the bathroom,
because then it's like tough to enter.
So I will say Jerma was a bit more of like a seven instead of instead of an eight.
The glass shattering.
Great.
But I also like Jerma's better because I don't like Dragon Ball.
I don't watch anime.
Only anime watches Pokemon.
Such a deep, deep, deep insight.
I told I told everybody in my chat that's why you clean up the Dragon Balls.
You don't know what series they don't know exactly.
Exactly.
And Ludwig knows that too, which is why I was a little surprised by that.
Like, I can't wait to collect them all and pray for you to leave this.
I would rather collect all the Pokemon is what I would do rather than Dragon Balls.
He literally just has a big old bag of Dragon Balls that he just brought outside of his house.
He only has three of them, though.
You had like a lot of them.
Oh, it's a fucking cat toy.
What are you talking about?
He also just brought it back.
Oh, I have a cat.
You know, it's like you put like a little spins around like the mice kind of move around.
OK, yeah.
Jerma got seven point five.
All right, Connor.
It feels like you made your mind up.
It feels like Jerma won that.
Thank you so much, Connor.
Really, really great insight there.
Really.
No problem, guys.
No problem.
What are you up to later today?
Oh, you booted him.
Oh, that was me.
Shit.
Absolute piece of shit.
But his and hers, his and hers from the get go.
He was on your side, Jerma.
Well, to be fair, we've got to be we've got to be fair.
We can critique each other's work at this point.
I mean, I mean, half your house is bathroom.
I think that I couldn't have a better basement.
I could not have a better basement.
I mean, and there are weapons pointing in every direction of people.
Why are you saying it like it's a bad thing?
I just don't think I would want to have like a weapon like a turret in the house.
OK, I disagree.
I disagree in this.
And I'm I bought it because I was scared the liberals would take it away.
So I just talked up early and often.
OK, but, you know, with to each their own, I guess your OK,
your bedroom was I thought I lost on your bedroom alone.
I just should have started.
Streamer bedroom was like, oh, no.
And it was like beautiful.
You had the big accent wall with the lights.
I was like, this is bad.
I'm like, well, the lights I had a beautiful, beautiful Persian rug.
I was, you know, admittedly my upstairs.
Can you I I do like how you terraformed your house.
Yeah, I exterior was important to me.
Interior, too, because you added the whole wall right across.
You made it two rooms.
And the sauna, you know, that was that was the sauna.
You probably spent a little too much time on that.
I was. Yeah.
Well, German, that does make it three, three now.
OK, three to three, which makes it my turn.
It does, which means I get to pick the game.
What games do I even have left?
So where are we going?
You just take a little squeak over here.
Look. Oh, of course.
I don't like that.
I don't like that realization that you found something good.
Yeah, I'm just going to send you a link, a link.
I don't even get to know what it is.
No, you'll see.
You'll see.
Just just you'll see the link and you'll get to play.
Don't leak the link if you could.
I will not leak the link.
OK. What's wrong?
How much experience do you have with this with with with this game?
With this game in particular, a mild amount of experience.
Occasionally, I have booted up a game once a year.
OK, do I? How do I like make a click on a seat?
Click on a seat and then just type your name in.
What about intended stack?
That's just put a thousand.
OK, he's making me play poker.
It's heads up poker.
That's right.
That is right.
You need the owner to approve of this.
Approved.
OK, approved.
Hold on. Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait.
I don't I don't there's no timer.
There's no timer.
I don't know.
OK, there's no timer.
All right.
There's no time.
You can take your sweet.
Oh, there's a timer at the bottom of this.
So yeah, but there's a timer.
But Texas hold them.
Texas hold them.
That's right.
Oh, because there is a timer and you got a little good time.
When I said there's no timer, I meant that more like metaphorically.
OK.
All right.
So I can see your hand, though.
I just showed it to you.
What?
So like, for example, I can raise right here.
I'll just I'll do a slight raise.
We have a thousand chips total.
Whoever has all the chips at the end wins.
And that can happen.
The river comes out.
Is it Texas hold them?
Yeah, it's Texas hold them.
So the flop will come out.
But you have to call.
There is the flop, you know, and then it's action to you.
And then you can check.
You can raise.
Let's go ahead and bet.
Hey, I don't call it.
I'll call it.
And then you call it.
There's an ace.
Action to you again.
You know, and what you just keep betting, right?
Yeah, you just keep betting.
And whoever gets all that.
And then like you bet like a little bit there.
And then maybe I'd be like I'd be like, you know, what?
What's what's 50?
What's 50 more?
You know what I mean?
Just small.
It's a nominal amount.
What does that mean?
Jerma, you absolute idiot.
Am I stupid?
Because I just won the game.
That's a three of a kind.
You just got shocked.
I just shocked him.
I play poker all the time.
Some of my favorite games.
I play poker every day of my life.
I play it more than Blackjack.
I play it more than Elden Ring.
I just shocked him.
You flopped a set.
I thought he was being stupid.
I thought he was being I don't know what I'm doing.
I thought he was actually stupid.
I'm still in it.
What are we playing to?
I'm still it's whoever gets the most chips.
You have to get all my chips.
It's whoever gets all the chips.
I still I had 50 because I won the first hand.
I had 575.
I'm taking them all.
I chip in a chair.
Let's go.
King. King.
We're going to see another nine and I'm going to win.
King me.
Yes.
It's all right.
We're going to see a nine and I'm going to win.
Give me a nine.
Oh, that's all right.
It's all right.
I took all of your money before.
No, no, no.
This is the comeback.
Oh, this is a fucking amazing hand.
This is an amazing go all in.
Go all in.
You're going to come into 150.
Don't be shy.
I'm just why would I do something like that?
Come on.
Let's see.
How about we just go all in?
You're going all in with 150 chips.
You're sitting next to a billionaire right now.
I call.
It doesn't matter to me.
I'm just trying to bluff them.
I'm taking all these chips right now.
No, no, no.
I can win.
Nine.
No, you cannot.
It's a nine.
Nine.
Oh, my God.
I just I honestly that is fucking crazy.
I can't believe I all into you.
And I just.
Jerma.
Yo, what's up?
It's time to play some Connect Four.
You were playing Connect Four?
Best of five.
Oh, that was that was very humorous.
I will say.
Queen eight.
Queen fucking eight.
He goes all in after I raise it with ace king.
And he bets 50.
Like it's 50.
Like I told I had I knew what was happening there.
Hey, you you had a choice.
Oh, yeah.
What were the choices?
You could have folded.
You son of a bitch.
So what's the what's the score right now?
Four to three.
It's game point for you.
So how many games we have left?
Well, if you win this, it's over.
The only games left are the neutral games.
Oh, shit.
What are the neutral games that we have if this keeps going?
Connect or rock, paper, scissors.
And you get to pick between rock, paper, scissors and react time.
If I win this.
Oh, dude, this is this might come down to rock, paper, scissors.
What a fucking disaster.
OK, all right.
Here you go.
Here you go, Jerma.
Let's see.
Here's your link.
Put in your name.
Connect for best of five.
It's the best of five.
I'm assuming I don't want to show this.
Not playing two in town chat.
I'm not playing two in town.
I'm assuming I don't.
I do not want to show this, right?
I would not show this.
I would keep this private so I can show this.
Yeah.
Timers on the screen.
It's your move.
I haven't played connect for and since I was probably four.
That's got to be a joke.
It wasn't.
What is this?
What are these moves?
Guys, I don't know.
I don't play connect for.
I don't.
I know you just get four in a row.
I don't know.
I panicked.
Whatever.
Fuck.
Who cares?
All right.
Fuck.
Who cares?
There's one.
This is the best of five.
That's the best of five.
That's a lot of game love.
It's a lot.
I just rematch.
Yeah.
Rematch.
He starts again.
Of course.
Hmm.
A mirror match.
Time's up.
Fuck.
I don't know.
I actually don't know.
I'm scared.
Got to make a call.
Got to make a play.
All right, Jerma.
Yeah.
One game away from this being a game nine situation.
Oh, fuck.
I'm not good at this.
Got to make a major comeback.
Yeah, I'm not good at this.
I'm not very good at this thing.
This game.
I'm starting first here.
You have no connect force because I know.
I don't know what I'm doing.
I just know that there's two colors on the screen and I have to.
I don't know how this works.
I mean, I do, but throw a wild card in here.
Oh, you're trying to do this like diagonal shit.
I'm just mulling over option.
I got nothing right now.
It's quite shut down.
Fuck.
I lose.
It's over.
Okay.
Connect four is like tic-tac-toe.
It's like one way to make sure you win every game.
And that's it.
I didn't throw.
I just don't.
I didn't.
I promise I didn't throw.
All right.
How are we going to do this?
Rock, paper, scissors.
Oh, my God.
I can't believe this is going to end with rock, paper, scissors.
We're just going to go full cam for this then, huh?
We can do full cam.
There's also a pretty good website for it.
How do you want to do it?
I'll link it to you.
You take a look at that.
Okay.
Wait.
No, I sent you a bad link.
This link.
Sorry.
All right.
You want to do it through the website?
I think it's pretty hard if you do it with the delay.
I've tried it before.
Yeah, that's true.
That's absolutely true.
Exciting as the throw the fist.
But it's best of five, just so you see.
Oh, it's best of five.
Yeah.
Am I good to show this?
I have a question for you.
Yeah, you can show everything.
Before we jump in, do you happen to watch anime?
I'm not going to answer any of your questions
because I feel like if I give you an anime,
it's going to be tied to one of these items.
Like if I'm like, why would you?
That's a weird paper because it's written down.
It's scissors because they edit it and cut it up.
It's a rock because you got to have a skull of a rock to do it.
I come on.
I don't know.
I feel like that question, I'm going to say like full metal alchemist
and you're going to be like scissors
and you're going to get it.
So I'm not going to say anything.
Weird that you would name an anime though.
I attack on Titan.
Full metal alchemist.
There you go.
There's rock, paper, scissors.
Now you don't know.
You have no idea which one I'm going to do.
Okay.
Well, I got a question for you then.
Yeah, please.
What's your favorite vegetable?
Carrot.
Is it really?
Are you sure it's carrot?
I like carrot.
That means, okay, you must be a fan of orange.
I knew it.
Wait, why would I pick that?
That was your thing.
Because you like anime.
I just picked the orange one.
Everyone who watches anime picks teasers first.
It was subconscious.
Ask me a question.
Okay.
Would you consider yourself
solid, like a stone?
Are you someone that can be relied on?
Are you constantly, constantly
cutting things out of your life
and trying to drop stuff from your life?
Or are you the type of person that would want to
get under the covers and get covered?
I feel like I'll say this honestly.
I feel like I'm more go with the wind.
Are you?
Yeah, I go with the wind.
Got him.
How did you know?
I thought you would think I'm paper.
Exactly.
Because rocks go with the wind.
They do.
Not as paper.
All right.
Let me ask you a question.
If you already selected, you selected rock.
You hesitated.
You hesitated, which meant you're going to pick paper
because that's the safest choice.
It's right in the middle.
I made a decision.
You did.
Yes.
Give me just one moment.
It's not happening.
What's not happening?
I had a whole plan.
It failed.
What was the plan?
My music's been buffering all day.
So I was going to count until it buffered.
But then the music didn't buffer this time.
So I've just been counting rock.
Oh, that was stressful.
That was stressful.
It was my tried and true.
You always go back to your tried and trues.
It hadn't been picked in a while.
Rock had not been picked in a while.
He knew that.
He fucking knew.
I thought you were going to go scissors initially.
That's why I was like, wait.
But that's why you go in scissors.
I was like, wait a minute.
He's going to know that I think he's going scissors.
You booed me.
You booed me today, Jerma.
That's all right.
I still owe you $1,500 at the roulette table.
Yeah, I'll still go to Vegas.
Give you a costume and actually a lot of things.
Look at a bucket list of things to do.
Enjoy Toontown.
I heard it's pretty good.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
I'm looking forward to it.
Oh, that was fun.
That was a blast.
That was a good time.
Thank you very much, Jerma, for gaming.
Absolutely.
Anytime, man.
You know, I've lost almost every single one of these.
Have you really?
I almost exclusively lost these.
It must be cursed.
I think I'm just a bad gamer is what it turns out to be.
That was close.
That was really close.
If I was 30 seconds factor on Picross, I'm going to play that game on the plane.
Yeah, the Picross, I think, is what really did you in.
All right, brother.
Yeah, thanks a lot.
Have fun with whatever you're doing next.
I got a jet.
Are you staying live for a bit?
I'll be live, yeah.
I'll be live for like another couple of free parts.
All right.
Well, have a good one, brother.
Have a good stream.
Yeah, thanks a lot.
It was fun.
Peace.
That was a lot of fun.
That was awesome.
I can't.
I actually won one of these.
I never win one of these.
He has a jet.
I've never won these.
I don't ever win.
I thought he was going to get me in the end here.
Oh, that was fun.
All right.
I'm going to take a quick break.
I'm going to refill my drink.
Am I going to jump into Elden Ring for a few hours?
I'll see you guys in.
Oh, the poker shit.
Yeah.
Oh, man.
That was bad.
Oh, he got so screwed there.
I can't believe you did it.
I can't believe you did that.
All right.
I'll be back in like two, three minutes.
I'm going to go pee and get a drink.
I'll see you guys in a minute.