Hey, what's up everybody. Jerma here with a Team Fortress 2 gameplay commentary. And
tonight, gonna be playing as the Scout with the Default Scattergun, the Criticola, and
the Candy Cane. Yeah, the Candy Cane. And in this gameplay, it's on King of the Hill Harvest.
This is on my new server. The IP of which will be in the description. Go check it out.
Go play on it. There's no reserve slots or no admins really there yet. Except for me,
I think Boo, Stealth, and Burger Boy are the admins at this point right now. But there
will be more. I don't know how I'm gonna do this, guys. I'm trying to figure out a way
to get people reserve slots without giving out a million of them. Because what I don't
want to have happen is this. I don't want to give out 50 reserve slots and have the
same 50 people, the only ones I can play in the server. I don't want that to happen. So
I might not even do reserve slots. I'm still going back and forth in my brain trying to
figure it out. But there will be admins. You can get admin. I don't know how that's
going to work though. I will make that very clear in a future video. So don't worry.
If you're trying to figure that out, do not worry.
So another thing, a really important thing about the server. I want to answer a couple
of frequently asked questions about this server. And I'll start right now right off the bat
while this game plays in the background. So it is a 24-7 server. It is not 8 to 8 in the
morning or something. It is all 24-7 dedicated. It's not like sitting right here in my backyard
It is in New York City. I think it also says New Jersey on it too. I'm not exactly sure
where the town is. But if you live in New York City or around there, you're probably
going to have like two ping. So that's pretty cool. Second thing I get all the time is what
are the custom mods and the plugins you're going to add and all that stuff eventually.
So let me start with my favorite one. Eventually on that server, there is going to be the friendly
fire spawn kill mod. I have no idea what it's called. All I know is I want it. There's something
about just the pure chaos in the setup time of a game. People just destroying each other
in the spawns. I think that will be there at some point. Another thing that's going
to be there at some point is probably something like HL stats or game stats. One of those
stat tracking programs. Because I used to love when I had a favorite server in Team
Fortress, I would always do slash rank, wanted to see where I was compared to everybody else.
And I think that's an innate thing that we all love to do as Team Fortress players. And
even just FPS players in general, you always love to see where you are in regards to other
people. So that will be there soon. Probably HL stats X, only because that's the one I'm
the most familiar with. And when all these things get installed, once I do all these
mods and once I do all these different plugins and stuff like that, we're going to have to
really experiment because I have no idea if they're ever going to work. I might turn the
server on one day, install one of these plugins and it's like, Oh, German, the server exploded.
Whoops. So I don't want that to happen. I want to slowly, gradually get these things
installed to have the least amount of headaches and the least amount of downtime that I could
possibly have. So one of the last things that people asked me and people wanted to make
sure was theirs, there are no random criticals on that server. I turned them off tonight.
Well, tonight, oh my goodness, it's like three in the morning. So earlier tonight, I turned
them off. We tested it. It worked. So there are no more random crits on that server. There
is still damage spread though. I'm not going to turn off damage spread. I'm also not going
to turn off pellet spread. I'm going to keep it all as the defaults, all as out of the
box TF2, except for the no crits. And the reason why I'm doing that is I just feel like new
players when you're in a no crit server and no spread, everything, it's very hard to do
well if you're new. So I just wanted to keep it as default as I can. And I guess you could
say that those are my reasons. So that is the end of the server talk. And one thing
I wanted to bring up before that this video is over is I tried to get a stipulation match
tonight, and I couldn't do it. I think the item servers are down for Team Fortress, or
at least they were for like a good long two or three, four hour period when I was trying
to play. So if those item servers come back, that's probably the next video you're going
to see is a stipulation match. I'm not going to tell you which class and what stipulation
it is, because I know a lot of you guys like to be surprised by that. So I will keep my
lips sealed. I'll keep that a secret. And one last thing before I got forgot this. Oh
my goodness, I forgot Diablo three comes out in like three days. I already have the thing
pre purchased. It's going to own my life. And you're going to see a lot of content on
Diablo three. And my question for this video to you guys, please let me know in the comment
section. What type of videos do you think you would like to watch? If you were to watch
Diablo three? Do you want to see class breakdowns? Do you want to see kind of like more of a let's
play like highlights, boss kills? What do you think you guys would like to see in Diablo
three for videos? That is my question of the video guys. Thank you all so much for watching.
I really do appreciate it. And I'll see you guys all soon. So take care, everybody.