Hello everybody. Hi. Hope you're doing well. Sorry for starting late.
We had some multiplayer issues. We were just sitting here figuring it out. I think we figured
it out. We're good. Thankfully didn't take too long, but we kept on getting disconnected to
each other. Had to try some. Okay. Well, hey, ladies and gentlemen, there he is.
Hello. Hello. Hello. Hello. Hello. Hello. No. No. Hello. All right. Well, let's mute this.
Let's mute them so I can do my intro. That was very loud. Did you just drive by? Was that you?
That was me. All right. Give me a sec. Give me a sec. Gone. But yeah, we're going to play some
motor area. We're just to pick up right where we left off last week. Continuing the training
session. Oh, I didn't mute on his side. Sorry, dude.
All right. Oh, you can, you guys didn't hear what he just said. So I'm like on both ends,
you, I'm talking to you and they don't hear you. And then I was talking to them and you don't hear,
you know what I mean? Like I just ruined that whole thing. Is this your first time?
Um, first time streaming 375th or something like that. I think. Okay. Well, um,
you'll get better. All right. We don't even need an intro. We're already here.
So we're starting late. So let's go. Those of you that don't know what Terraria is. Um, it's a base
building block exploration game where I know and that let's go. It's 2D Minecraft. Your guys ever
played Minecraft? When's the Minecraft stream German? I already did it. Did you? Yeah. Dude,
you're a trending gamer. You know, I did. I've played Minecraft like six times in the last,
like three years. I think you need a new playthrough. I will never do a playthrough of
Minecraft again. I might open it and like fall down into lava once or twice for like a couple
hours and build a dirt house, but I'm not going to do like a full play through it. You know,
it would take a million dollars to beat the ender dragon. I mean, it would take,
if you have a million dollars, I'll do it. Wow. Wow. Okay. So play Terraria. He wants a million.
Okay. Why do you think a man now? I got a nice fat check for Mr. Stir. Hey, I'm going to invite you
to the squad stream. Cause my chat's telling me to do it. How did you start streaming?
It's yeah, it's been on. Don't let this be like last time where you didn't think I was streaming
for like four hours. No, I knew you, I knew you were streaming. I mean, you're just like,
want to squad up apparently. That's what they want. So where we last left off, hey,
we're not in hard mode yet. We haven't killed the wall. We were in the dungeon and um,
but we want to do before we kill the wall. And the last thing we were going to do is get you that
sick new summoner armor step. That's right. Do that. We need to go get some water candles from
the dungeon. Hey, drama left the game. No, I didn't. It said you left. So we can do this rejoin,
uh, thing for like another 20 minutes. Hey, sweet. Everybody watching you all missed it,
but you know how we rejoined and tried to join each other and talked about how dog
shit steam is for like 20 minutes so we can do it all again. All right. Pretty good. Pretty good
stuff. All right. Um, hold on. So you want to try this, uh, because again, yeah. Oh yeah. I
have to invite you. Hello. Who do I watch? Germa or story? You can see both with the squad stream.
Hello. Okay. You're gonna invite. I did this did this last time though. Do you remember this did
this last time it did. And then it was fine. But like you need to be able to rejoin. I hopefully
again and I can, I'm here. So let's hope that that looks, it's just like there's what happens
when you play terraria. Yeah. Okay. It's, it's the first time, first time jitters. The game was
nervous. All right. You ready? I'm ready. Uh, here there's one. Okay. Okay. Okay. Before we go,
while it's nighttime, we're going to end up needing demonite bars. So we're going to have
to kill a boss that drops demonite bars. Demonite bars. Yeah. I think we can just kill the eye.
No, how many bars do we need? Uh, a bit. I think we might have to kill it twice and then we can
walk to the dungeon. Where's it going? And you can remember how to play. I know, I know how to play.
Well, you wanted the refresher. You know, this is just like, Hey, reminder, everyone
welcome back. We're the guys. I'm melting him right now. I'm melting him right now.
I'm hit. I took a hit. I took a few hits. I took like six hits. All right, we're good.
Okay. We're good. How many bars? Uh, it gives it or so. I don't know. Why is it two? I made another
one. We're going to need another one because I, I used all of our demonite bars to make
storage. You get hit. I got hit. He's killing our guy. Why can he go in there? There's a wall.
He doesn't give a shit. Oh, good job. Now he dropped all of his things in there and then
mine and you can have them. That's a dated reference. What did I do for a dated reference?
What did I do? What did I say? I don't know. Uh, but that's probably enough. Do you have enough
bars? Uh, we will, but we have to go to the dungeon and get a water candle. You said can I
has cheeseburger. I did not say that. Take this, take, take, take, take, take that. Don't like deep
fake thought that shit on me. All right. I got it. And that's a charm. So don't call him Jay.
That's my mom's name. What? Oh, that's true. Actually he's Jay nine to five. All right. What
is this a spirit? This is the, uh, the one with the minions, right? Yeah. But what don't I have
like a double jump right now? And don't I need that because of my training wheels? Your own
training wheels. Yes. Uh, so when we come back, I'll make you the full set and then you'll wear
the full set. Oh, like for now double jumps. Right. Pretty good. Double jump is important
for somebody that's on training bills. Oh dude, he's selling a kimono. Oh, I thought that was a B.
What does he got? He's selling a kimono.
You could just call me Jeremy, you know. You're right. Okay. I'm going to store some things and
we're going. You sure? Yeah. I have three bananas. What do you do with these?
You can have them. I hate you. Oh, I see. I think I killed somebody. Oops. That's just,
that's how it is. What is this? Did we, did we make this? Who made this? Yeah, that's my,
I don't want to tell you what that is. Let's go. All right. I'm going. So do you eventually get like
speed increases like times two speed or extra speed or you get boots that let you sprint,
you get wings that let you fly and move faster. You can also, right now you should have the hook,
right? And give you a hook. If you hook the ground, it'll like pull you towards it faster than
your move speed. That's really cool. You technically could lay down wire all the way across the map to
build a teleporter or you can make like mine cart tracks. Wait, wait, am I going the right way?
We're not even the same party. You're going the right way. Okay. Did I miss anything? No.
This is our first time playing together in four years. I didn't think he would talk to me again,
but here we are. Why did you think that? You know, the money. Oh, right. The money handle
the money. It was, you didn't say you've already forgotten about the money.
I never forget. I never forget about the money. Oh, I remember I did that.
Is it one? What happened? No, none. You left again. No, I mean that Mike, that was like a full on,
like the game hard crashed. That wasn't a disconnect. Terraria like hard crashed.
I don't even have it open anymore. That's good news. I just want to play. What the fuck?
I mean, I played with Ashley for like two days straight, maybe three. She never,
she never crashed. Why am I crashing now? Are you sure that we don't have to like update mods or
something? Yes. You're sure? I'm sure. Okay. I mean, I'll just, I'll just run the errand by myself.
Just wait. I'm almost here. It's really like we just have to like grab a candle. It doesn't matter.
Okay. Can't run a sprite based game. I mean, it's tough. Yeah. See, I got like everything all set,
right? What the fuck was up with that? That's weird. Yeah. That was like a, like,
like I didn't, I couldn't move. I couldn't do, like the game just exited.
Maybe it's, maybe it's me. Is it you, you think? And maybe, no, it's a, I'm the problem,
you know? All right. I'll be ready. Whenever you're ready, I'll be ready.
Oh yeah. I'm just, I'm just running an errand. So I can't, you have to invite me. I can't just
join off you. I did invite you. You did invite me. I don't see it. Invite friends. Oh, there it is.
Got it. Okay. He had it already. All right. Joining stir. He had it already. Hopefully my fucking game
doesn't crash. Uh, he had it already. All right. Hey, let's do like strike three. I think last week
someone was saying, well, that wouldn't be a problem either. I'm going to ignore what that
guy said and forget what that guy said. I'm going to repeat it. It's disgusting. Don't tell him.
He won't know it's me. Yeah. Hello. Um, no, but like what, what, what's, what's the problem?
I don't know. I don't know, dude. Pepe face. Yeah. I'm going to go find me and you like backup plan.
You can always just play games made 40 years ago. It's fun to do that though. Yeah. Did you get
the item? What did you get the item? Um, yeah, I'm just grabbing a few more while I'm here.
I'm being productive and I want to come back here. That's like the sec. That's like the third loud
fucking driver. It is. We're getting a lot. And that's what happens when you live in Manhattan.
Are you next to a highway or is it just like, it's just Vegas, Vegas, baby.
DOS is 40 years old. Is it real? What? I had no health. What? I dropped 47 gold.
I'm doing a great job. Um, I should go back there. I'm doing a great job. I'm,
I'm just like a fucking animal in your server. Where are you? What do you like to know? Oh,
you're hanging out on the giant thing. Uh, I want to participate. I don't want to just be
like a squirrel in your game. I got you the things. I got you the things. Did you, you need to get,
you dropped 50 bucks down there. We'll go get it. Hold on. Hold on. I want to be a
Warcraft critter in your fucking server. Just come here to the, come to the forge. My darling,
my darling. Why do I have a triple jump? Did I get that with being by being a squirrel?
You might have a cloud in a bottle. Oh yeah. Okay. So here's, here's the boots. Where are you
darling? I'm the squirrel in the room. Oh, you're the, okay. And here's my hat. So you put all those
on, you get an extra bonus. You'll be able to summon like 30 guys. Nice. Okay. I don't know
what the bonus is. Six defense over these three movement speed throwing damage. That's not bad.
All right. Let's put them on. So I can have max minions. Cool. All right. I'm gonna go get my 47
gold on table. So I can have two extra sons. Killing enemies or continually damaging bosses
generates soul wisps. After generating five wisps, they are instantly consumed to heal
you for 10 health. That's actually pretty great. That's really cool. All right. Nice. Let me go.
How many can I have? You said, let's see. I remember to touch the table. How do I, it's not
sons, it's summons. So your, your bird, I don't remember what you had the dank creeper perhaps.
How do I stop being squirrel? Okay. Thank you. All right. So let's see. No, this doesn't count as a
summon. No, that is a century. Oh, the boys that follow you. Damn it. Okay. What about these? Are
these some? All right. There we go. No, nevermind. You don't have two of those. That's just century
two. I'm century guy, not summon guy. Right? No. What are you doing? The clouds, dude, I'm going to
have to tell you something right now. I threw away the other ones. I don't think I have those
anymore. No, no, no, no, no, no. Wait, wait, wait, wait. They're in here. He's being quiet. He's very
upset. Hold on. There we go. I'm thinking like, do I run back to town? Do I run back to our base and
hit him or do I get the gold? All right. So that's shadow drop staff is one of them. And then you can
only have one type of summon out at any point anyways, right? You can have more than one type.
Okay. So you, your, your pants, your armor and your helmet give a summon and you have one by
default. So you should be able to have four summons. Okay. Cool. And then you touch the
bewitching table and you get five. All right. So I definitely, um, I definitely threw away
some as a dog, dank creeper. Okay. Hold on. That's the good one. Oh, summons a dark or a rain from
the sky. No, no, no. That's not that fire is a story. Okay. That's the creeper. That's the one.
All right. Proud of you. All right. So let me go check it out. Let's see what it does.
It's like I can have three. Okay. That's pretty ridiculous. I can have three of these out at the
same time. Why am I so slow? It should give you five, five. It's not giving me five. It's three,
four with the table. Right. How do I activate it? Right. Click the table. Unless I just didn't read
the helmet. No, you didn't read it right. It's four with the table. Okay. All right. I'm ready to be
guy that just walks around and lets other things do everything for him. Um, well, wait, the owl
might be taking a summon slot. How do I, how do I get the owl to leap? The owl shouldn't be doing
that. It's a pet, which no, no, no, it's a highly doubt it. It's, it, the helmet is, uh, in its
helmets, minion damage, not summon minion. Okay. The two other pieces are extra minion. The helm
is 10% more damage. All right. So what are you, what are you at? Um, I'm grabbing the 47 gold that
I dropped. I'm going to go do that. I'm not paying attention chat. So as I was saying the last time,
last time we were playing, you were talking about how you wanted to like know more about
what you're doing. You said you're going to do some reading. Did you do any reading? Um,
so what would you like to do? I haven't had time. I haven't had time. All right. I would like to do
a boss. Okay. Here's, here's a couple of things that can be done. Um, you can actually change
the server to expert mode and bosses drop more things on expert mode that you can only get in
expert mode. And then we can kill bosses. We've already done. Um, I think there's two more bosses
for the mods that we can do. I have to double check which ones they are. I forget what we haven't
done. And we can do the wall of flesh, which is a big deal because after that, the game goes into
hard mode. Oh, okay. My guys can't get in here. I'm just kind of doing a little bit of exploring.
Okay. So none of those options. No, I just going to do a lot. All right. You pretty much just spoke
a different language for 30 straight seconds. Um, whatever you want to do, whatever you,
whatever you think would be the most interesting and more like most fun. You were talking about
like how you wanted to read up. You wanted to go in order. You wanted to make sure you weren't
doing anything and understand what we were doing. No, I know, I know what we're doing. What are we
doing? We're doing the wall of flesh. It's hard mode. It's like Diablo. You get, you, you, you
level up to a different, different quality. There's a couple of bosses before the wall of flesh that
we'll technically skip. If we do the wall of flesh, we can come back and do them later,
but we're probably never going to do that. So do you want to do those before we do the wall
of flesh? Sure. That sounds like fun. Okay. I need a second to check what we haven't done.
We didn't do the star scouter and we did not do slime. God slime. God is that what's the slime
God? Oh, because we never found the meteorite. I think we have to walk left and find the meteorite
and then we can do the star color thingy. Okay. Um, slime God is, it's just two big slimes at once,
but it drops some, some good stuff. Exploring caves is a lot more fun than just, uh, and more
productive than digging. Oh, okay. So, um, you don't think shaming you? No, they're saying that
don't like dig, go find a cave. Digging is like not productive to go like find stuff.
But what if you want it to dig? I thought you wanted to dig. You must have wanted to dig.
I don't know, but I'm putting a lot of torches down because I'm holding the shift.
That's because I'm holding shift to like do the thing where you can just automatically change to
what the hell was that? Give me these back. All right. There's a present out here. I love presents.
Okay. Uh, so we need to go, we need to go left. Yeah. I'm at the meteor. I'm mining meteorite
right now. That's what I'm doing. I'm just coming over here. You're at the meteor now.
Yeah. Let me touch, let me touch the thing. Oh, I got the little globes around me. I'm gonna get
so confused. Can you buy? Yes. Dynamite before you come here. How much do you want? I don't know.
Like 20. Why don't you just open the present then? All right. You want 20 dynamite. Yeah.
There might even be some in the box. How does one sound?
How do I only have enough money for one? You can search in the box and see if there's gold.
Search for gold. Search for dynamite. Search for bombs. Bombs would be good enough.
Okay. There's no dynamite in here. Bomb. No bombs in here. No, I'm an idiot. I don't want
to filter weapons. Filter all. No dynamite. There are bombs in here though. I'm gonna buy
whatever I can buy with this. You wanted, guys, what's happening right now? 20 silver. Why can
it? Okay. All right. I got 11 dynamite and 12 bombs. Okay. You're going to want to,
you're going to want to come to me now. I'm on the way. And then you can participate. Good.
I love these things. This is so cool. Uh, where exactly did you, why'd you dig over here?
What? Stop asking me dumb questions. What's, what's, what's, what did you do over here?
Did we do this? I don't remember doing this. I can't see you. We're squad streaming. You can
see what I'm doing. You can just look at the squad window. That's why chat was telling you
it's not productive because like that's natural. It's just a hole. They exist. Uh, do you, do you,
how are you doing on Nana? You need like Nana stones? Whatever the hell these things are.
Uh, I think I still need like a few. Cause I have three. Wow. Someone's been holding out.
I like my little flare gun though. Like makes me able to see what I'm doing.
All right, buddy, boy. All right, let's go. This is meteor. This is the meteor. You don't
stand on the meteor because it burns you if you stand on it. Okay. So that's why you're going
to mine. So you just chuck some bombs down there. You want me just to start, just start throwing
dynamite down there and just throw a dynamite, you know, throw some bombs. The goal is to get
the meteorite as dynamite stands up in this game or does it fly? Okay. Some, some games dynamite
stands right up. Wait. Ow. What do you mean it stands up? They just don't like flat. Oh,
like you placed it on the ground. Yeah. I know. I thought you were insane, but I get it. How far,
how far down does this go? Uh, stop. You see like the brown rocks that are flaming. All right.
That's the meteor. I'm going to get it in there. See if I can get it in one. This is kind of like
a pinball game. Well, you see like you could just drop it over here now. Oops. I'm fine.
I'm good. I'm good. I'm good. I'm good. All right. Watch out.
What's a blast rate? I just told you I was throwing one. This is a lot. So what do you,
do you like crap bars with? Yeah, we don't, we don't really need much more. How do we get it?
Also, we need to be, we need meteorite to summon the boss. Oh, okay. That we were going to do.
Do you want more than that? Or is that nothing? This will be enough. Why is that shooting at you?
I don't know. I think it's on drugs. Might be. Okay. So yeah, that's 300 meteorite. We're good.
We're good. Go back. Go back. What do I have? Let me look at my stuff. Sticky bomb. That's cool.
Sticky dynamite. It's combining dynamite with gel. So when you throw those things, that's cool.
All right. I got a goodie bag. Also, I can wait. That hook. Oh, here. Take these. These won't break
if I throw them to you, right? The stars. All right. Oh, muscle talk. Do you want this ancient
shiv? 35 melee damage, 4% crit, very fast attack speed, average knockback material,
enemies release a blue aura cloud on death. No. Sell it. Sell it. Sell it. Who has the most money
in here? They all, they all just give you money. They don't have like a bank. Too much, too much
like fallout. All right. So on the left side for me is like default characters. I know pretty
much what all these do. You added like two expansions to this game and I don't know what
any of this is. Here's the important ones. Faye, the dryad, sells boss summon items generally for
bosses you've already beaten. Okay. So she helps. Cool. Paul. Paul's nobody. All right. Well, let's
summon them. And he doesn't have the things I was looking for. So you want to summon the boss?
Oh, this guy's boss is summons as well. We have to go up to the sky box. Like we can only summon
this boss up in the. Really? The tops. Yeah. I actually don't know how hard this boss is or what
it does. Oh, that's good to know. We're prepared. I know that we need platforms. We're going to need
to build platforms so we can actually move. Do you have enough wood for that or do we need to go get
it? I think it's in the box. All right. Well, I'll be up here. Okay. Hope you're having a good time.
Hope you're having a good day. I'm having a good day. I hope you had a really good drink.
A good drink. Yeah. Well, just like treat it yourself with a beverage. You know what I'm talking
about? Who's this person? Why is there like a lady up here? She had a lot of health.
Hag? Where the hell am I? Yes. You coming? Oh, it's because the gravity changed. Okay. That's cool.
My health. What's wrong with my health? Jerma hasn't activated squad stream. Oh, that's my bad.
I accepted the invite. Okay. I activated it. It's live now. Oh no, I did it. Yeah. Yeah. I'm
saying it's my fault. Did you not hear me? Dude, you got like such a cover because no matter what
happens, if something wrong goes, if something goes wrong, it's you could always be like, well,
Jerma is a stupid idiot. You have, you have like such insurance when you like do anything with me,
it seems. And you know, if I wouldn't have that, if you had a little bit more confidence,
a little bit of self-respect and you can be like, no, you can literally throw a baseball through
your window right now. And it would just be like, Jerma, you fucking left the thing over here. You
left the window unlocked and you were cleaning the window and it dropped and people would believe
you. And it'd be like, what did I do? I didn't do anything. True. I said, how big does this
platform have to be? I'm just doing it. One, one, one, just protect me. Summon your sentry thing.
They're everywhere. No, you're fucking auto shoot sun. Oh, you mean this thing? Yeah. Don't forget
you have a sun. See, this is all your fucking fault. Oh, fuck man. Like I brought my car in to get
repaired and I need a, I need like a new gasket. Jerma, like what the fuck, man? Like you should
have been in the server faster. What happened? I, I stupid man. Usually I just blame Ronnie.
This guy is so like oblivious and selfish that he made me buy like seven different cables to
fix a computer problem. Like I trusted him and he took advantage of me and I ended up buying like
seven cables. Wait, what? Okay. I'm summoning a boss. All right. Where are you going to summon it?
And where I am, you just summon it and then it comes to you. I'm getting my ass kicked. I'm worried.
Do I? This shit shooting us from underneath. Whoa. Okay. I don't know what it does.
What are you doing? What's this? How do I do this? Oh my God. Okay. You're going to jump over that
apparently. Why is he focusing on me? You know, like honestly, you're probably dealing so much
more damage than me. Oh, I'm speaking of dying. If you're, you can use your mirror, go back to town.
I picked up my stupid pickaxe. Where the, oh my God. Where the fuck is our healer? Do we,
oh, she's right there. How do I, how do I respawn? Oh, that didn't go so well. Is it, is he dead?
He might've left. No, wait. Hold on. Oh, respawn time. What's your max health? 160. Yeah. We're
pretty low. We should be a lot higher right now. How much higher do we need to be? Uh, we could be
at 300. Oh, that sounds pretty important. Yeah, it does. Should I wait for you? It still shows
his health bar. So I don't. Is he just hanging out up here? He shouldn't be. Yeah. I don't know.
Let's go find, uh, health. How about that? Is that? No. Uh. Why, why, what's with the,
what's the, why this topaz? Give me that. Uh. So are we just gonna go get health? Yeah. Hold on.
Why is everybody vote kicking me? Didn't you hear what Star said? I was the one doing the damage.
Who's the birthday person? Is this, I'm just breaking this guy's house and taking his stuff.
He doesn't care. What happened? Star. Star. It's boss.
Oh no, he's by chest hurts right now. Seriously. What the fuck?
I'm just going to. Tyler doesn't give a shit. I don't know what I did, but he's raining fire
down. Oh shit. It's the fucking prophecy. He's not going to kill him. He's going to kill everybody.
He just goes killed. No man. Why are you not reacting to this? I feel like you would be
fucking freaking out right now. Are we in the same game? Am I muted? Yes. You've been muted.
I think I was muted. Oh yeah. I, whoops. All right. Calvin has one sliver of health. He's
going to die. Yeah. I was trying to give some advice and some tips and some, some technique.
Maybe. What happened? He, I just was, I was breaking some into somebody's house and he
just spawned on me. Well, let's, that's what's weird is he still has a health bar. All right.
So he's, he's somewhere. All right. Let's go find him. He's just like appears. This is so scary.
It's like, um, I feel like it's fucking Mr. X by the way, did you play the new resident evil
two remake? Uh, I watched a lot of it and played it. That's probably one of the best games of the
year. Oh shit. You mean it's one of the best games of 10 years ago? Well, yeah. Because
Capcom hit a hard spot and couldn't, couldn't make new games anymore. So the new strat is just to
make old stuff again. He's on me. I'm dead. I was going to teleport and I didn't. I'm, I'm,
I'm a ghetto. He's just juggling me right now. I'm dead. Why don't you just kill it,
Jerma? Come on. Fuck dude. You're the strong one. I'm the one doing the armor. You got the
summons. You have the sentry. You have all the good stuff. You take all the fucking good gear.
He just juggled me. He just juggled me. He did. He just juggled me in the air. We're not, hey,
don't even give me this kind of shit. You've got like a guy on training wheels here and where like
a hundred percent less health than we would need to be. And you just, you, all right. Yeah. I don't
know. You just put me in armor. You have better attack damage because you have all the summons.
I've given you everything. You can't, all right. You can't put like a toddler in fucking like gold
armor, give him a sword and say, all right, I gave you all this really cool stuff. You're like,
really? Look at how you look at how shiny that armor is. Why have you not killed the other king
yet? What? But can't you? Toddler screaming. Yeah. In the game, in the game. I still am like,
just like a baby in this game. Okay. Well, the boss is somewhere with like 7% health. Just say
sliver. It's like a cooler, like more like cooler vocabulary. He's, he's one. He's one. He's lit.
Where is he? Is he right there? Is that him? What is that? I'm afraid to do anything right now.
No, it's gold. Only it shows bosses on the map, but he's not. What if he was like all the way over
here? I don't, I don't see him. All right. Can I go back and like open the chest that I was going
to open at this guy's house? All right. It's already open. There's like nothing in it. So yeah, go,
go ahead and do your stupid thing. Does he leave when there's a party going on? No, maybe he doesn't
know. Okay. He's by me, me, me, me, me, me, me, me, me. He hates me. Uh, don't die. Don't die.
Give me like two seconds. I'm trying. Tell me if you're going to die. Oh, it's going to be close.
Oh, it's going to be close. He's dead. Okay. What'd you get? Uh, I got broken star trail healing
potion and broken star trail. It's a weapon, a snake banner, vanquisher metal. That's nothing.
It's broken. So that means it's bad. It's terrible stats. Let me see. Where are you? Here. What was
that? I don't know. What's going on? Oh, I want to see. I want to see. Uh, yes, I drew it. What else did
he drop? Something else too. Where is it? Oh, dude. Graviton surge. Oh, quick sort. Sort of. Yeah,
there we go. Okay. Okay. Well, that was intense. There's a guy that resets the stats on an item.
I don't know if we ever got them. That was fun. It was apparently we don't have enough houses.
Can I, um, my hand's up in the back. I'm like raising my hand up. Yeah. And you call. Okay.
Thank you. Uh, can we get more health so we don't have to, uh, like be, uh, nerfed the whole time
we played again? Um, I would, I would like that. Yeah. Who the fuck is this guy? We just have to
go explore to find the health, right? Yeah. Random parts under the ground. Random parts on the ground.
You got it. I'm going. Uh, if you take our giant tunnel and go down and then go to the right,
because I don't think we explored the right. What? Oh my God. I thought I had an extra, like,
I was going to jump. I was going to do the double jump, but like his platform was here.
I didn't know. I was going to just wait till, you know, jump before you hit the ground. I didn't
know. I, your platform just killed me. Oh, good joke. He wasn't a joke. In fact, destroyed fucking
evidence. Oh, uh, good joke. Okay. Let me, I gotta store some shit before we do anything.
Oh, the Calvin's respawning health. Nice. All right. Let me deposit this stuff.
Okay. Okay. Now what do I want with me? Oh, definitely like 7,000 torches. Hey,
where the fuck did the guy go? Did they leave? Did they get invaded yet? Spoilers. I don't want
to see spoilers. That can't even happen. We're in normal mode. Can't even happen. We're in normal.
Wait, like eight more hours of us playing together. That's actually our first blood moon.
What do you mean? What are we talking about? What? What does the blood moon do? What's that mean?
It means they're going to start attacking. Did I just say we haven't been invaded yet? And then
did I do that? Well, no, being invaded is like dark souls. Oh, that's where like 16 players show
up in your game and gank you. Is that really what happens? No, there is an alien invasion.
I assume is what they meant. Okay. So do we do this to defend the house?
Yeah, if you want to. We, they drop a special item, blood droplets, and we need a few of them
because we've never had a blood moon before, as far as I remember. Honestly, if you just stay in
the house, they all come to the door and your summons stay outside and they'll probably kill
everything. Oh, cool. The door. Ah, the door. They are coming. All right. I got left side,
you get right side. Oh, this makes you feel like a necromancer. I thought that was you. Wow.
Who's got the glasses? So yeah, like, yeah, we still don't have the freaking,
the guy that like we are missing so many NPCs. I do not want to build houses for another hour.
Or like we should go to hell and just make a whole bunch of rooms for all these idiots.
We're going to put these people in hell. That sounds kind of mean. Now go on collection. All
right. What or I'm going to go up the dreaded patchwork patchwork. There's a mini boss on my
side. Oh, honestly, the blood moon. This should have happened to us like
years ago. This is all kind of irrelevant. Sorry, I've been really bad in muting my sneezes,
but I figured I'm going to let me be honest with you. If I muted my stream and sneezed,
it would still show up on your stream. So if I meet, I would have like, I would have fucking
like you need an actual, you know, come on, be a professional. I would have just panicked
and pressed a bunch of buttons and probably like restarted my computer accidentally.
Anything would be better than listening to your bodily fluids like eject from your face.
You disgust me.
No. All right. So we're going to go down and this is the hole underneath the
house eventually or the one that like to the right all the way to the right.
Oh shit. We need a minotaur. So this would be good for you. How can you let stuff in here?
I don't know. I don't know. Did you even like clean this up for you? What?
You let the shit in. Why do you have the door open? You're supposed to be the terraria master.
What? Oh, because these guys are chumps. How long does the blood moon last? All night. All
night. All night. I'm getting lots of money and stuff. I need to find the goblin guy.
I need to make rooms. Germa here, here, here, here's what you're going to have.
What? I knew my save minutes were skulls. Yeah. Yeah. Hold on.
Okay. Everyone get high. Can I see some drama hypes in the chat? I don't want to see it.
Wait, is this? Wait, what? I just picked up so many. There's so much shit out here. What?
I don't know what this stuff even is. I'm just a vacuum cleaner. Severed hand, blood orb. All
right. I've never seen this before. Duh. Okay. Try this item. It's, um, you know that, that
Undertale game? It looks like every character in that game. Undertale. A skull I just dropped down
here. Have you ever played Undertale? No. Unpleasant, strange skull. Yeah. It deals
summon damage, but it looks like an actual spell. Um, you meant to say that's, that's, that's just,
no, no, no. You're talking about one character in Undertale that everybody says that stands,
right? Okay. That's fine. Like the only character. No, no. It's like, yeah. Have you ever played that
game? Did you leave this door open? I did. All right. What the fuck does this do? 45 plus one
summon damage. Summons a ghastly skull to shoot laser beams, which cause damage over time.
And I, yeah, I don't know really what that means. Once this is, uh, you're having a bad time.
Kill death. What? I just got an achievement. What does kill death? Dude, I don't, I don't know.
Ronnie would like to watch your broadcast. A request from steam.
What is that even that, that, that can't actually be you, Ronnie. I want to watch you play on steam,
please. That's funny. Oh my God. You're so needy. I want a higher quality version. I forgive you.
That's a very good joke. That's fine. Cause I talked shit about the cables and then like ignored
chat and you probably said something. They had to like wallow in pity. Okay. Um, I feel like we've
been collecting. So no, we're good. We're good. We're good. Go underground and just look for the
hearts. But let me deposit shit. Also, uh, it might be worth it to use a splunker potion because you
can see the hearts through walls. Like everything lights up. Okay. Yeah. So if you get, don't use
like one potion on this. Do not use more than one potion. I'm going to fucking scream. Don't use
more than one spelunk potion. Spelunker. You ever played spelunky? You know, spelunky two. I have
played spelunky and I was like, yeah, this is, this is fun, but I didn't really do much in it.
All right. What am I doing with spelunk? I can't say the half of that word. Just one. You said,
yeah, it lasts for five minutes. Use it when you go underground. How do I take just one thing out
of the closet box? I don't know. Just take, I don't know. Oh, I got one. Okay. All right. Use,
just use it when we go underground and then look for hearts. Yeah. Just run around. You'll like zoom
out all the way to, don't be a boomer. Put your glasses on. No, I'm not going to do that. Zoom out
and then you'll be able to see the heart. I can't do that. And you can collect them really quickly.
Use the skull. What the hell? Is that better than this? Better than what?
That's, I think it might be better than what I was using before for like my main.
I based like what I like on about, on sounds though. I'm not sure if I don't like that sound.
Oh, you don't like the sound. All right. So you said go down underneath our base and just start
looking for hearts. Yeah. I'm going, I'm going for it. I apologize, but you do not like the sound
though. How far zoomed he is, is unreal genre. He better zoom out. What I can't, what I, I can't see.
I'm not doing it. If you waste the spelunker potion, I'm going to be mad.
Like if you end the spelunker potion and you're like, okay, I got one heart.
I'm not, I'm at 139%. Remember that. Oh, oh gross. I hate it. All right. I'm taking spelunker
potion now. Aren't you the same person who, who is like one of the only people that agrees with me
that path of exile, like makes you vomit because of how close you are to the screen.
Yes. I, I, but that's different. That's top down. How was that different? Top down view
and it's 3d. All right. What, will the hearts just be hearts or is it like in a box or something?
Big red heart crystals. Okay. There is also life ports, which will be like blocks that have hearts
in them. This is cool though. You can do this. Five minutes of this. That's not that much. We
can just tell a funny story. What? Dude, I want to hit you. Get out of here. All right.
I need to go home. Why did you just do the batman? I have one question.
Batman, the beer. I can't hear the original beer. You know, I'm telling you if you only
find one of these, dude, chest, chest, chest, chest, chest, chest, chest. I see it. I swear
fucking good. Let me ask you one question. Superman go. I don't even know. Superman.
Why would Superman be in the same universe? I know, right? Like who even figured that out?
We got cool stuff over here. Okay. So it's chest. I don't see any heart though. What is this thing?
It's like a person's house. Okay. Uh, arcane band, bomb, shuriken,
swift, miss potion, recall potion, and some torches. All right. Very cool. Very cool. And water.
Water. I found one. Shoot him. Dude, you know what we really need right now is a freaking
poon hammer. What the fuck are you talking about? Is that really loud? Did I peek the mic on that?
Oh, if you want to hear a mic being peaked, I got it. Don't fucking do it. Like everybody hates
that. Nobody likes that. All right. I got it. Life crystal. So just take it, right? Yeah. And
it's a 20 HP. Cool. Now this is the part of the game that I was talking about. That's the part
again that I wanted to see. You're like about spawning bosses and going and picking up meteors.
I wanted to go look. You're doing it. It's dude. It's the problem is that I've had to hold your
hand at every step. It's the part of the game you want to see is exploring and fucking go do it.
Every time I go do it, you go, Oh boy, I need a demon, demon, uh, Titan or hold on.
I have been very respectful of you. I've been patient. I haven't. Not at all. Everyone was
like, man, stars, like really like fucking trying to rush him. I don't like it.
And I kept muting last stream going like, I know, what the fuck? I don't know what to do.
Like, what the fuck? No, that's not how that happened. What do we got in here? Have you found
one? I'm not looking. Wait, you're the one with the potion. We don't both have the potion. Why
didn't you take one and do this? There's nothing in this chest. How the fuck is that possible?
So are we splitting these? Just keep using them.
What is it? 180. All right. You have max health right now? Yeah. I might have spunky potion right
now. Can you deliver one? Can I, can I Uber Eats a spunky potion? I don't even need it. I'll find
one. Okay. Not bad. What is that? What is this thing? What was that? A dragon? Hey, I just
killed the dragon down here. He dropped a starfish. Good job. Good job, buddy.
Ooh, what's this? Chest. How can I, how can I have? Did something happen here? Why can only have two
of these? It was three before. Am I missing something here? Does it say they count as two
on the staff? No, no, no, no, no, no. Because your bewitching table probably just wore off.
Cool. Recall potion. I got some recall potions though we can share. You don't share them. You
have the mirror. Oh, I thought that, no, doesn't not wormhole. All right. Sword items. Wait.
I'll figure this out later. I don't really like this thing. It might pick up at bosses,
but it takes like kind of too long and it can't shoot through walls.
Hold on. I'm getting to like the water here. Water. I'm kind of concerned about this.
What is that? What's a giant clam? Giant clam down here.
I found the giant clam star. Come to me. Where is he? What do you want? I was busy
blittling my chat. I got a giant clam here. There's a giant clam boss. Oh, okay. I'm coming.
I don't know where it is. It's here somewhere. Um, we're going to have to go underwater and we like
can't breathe underwater. It's a shitty ball, like easy to kill for us. Yeah. But still we can't
breathe underwater and now I'm wasting my. Oh, it's right here. Yeah. What are you talking about?
Oh shit. He's right here.
Dead. Okay. Yeah. It's like one of the first bosses you're supposed to kill,
but he makes an NPC summon. Oh, okay. Well, that thing was really stupid. All right. Let
me see if I can find another heart. Ami, Amidius, Amidius, the sea king. What does that guy do?
Anything cool? The NPC. Yeah, there's a guy down there now. Yeah, he sells, uh, he sells weapons.
Are they good? They're okay. I think we're a little bit past them now. I just need like another heart.
How many do you need? What's the max health? The max is 300. I need like five of them then.
Have you just been taking them? I have two. All right. That should be fine.
No, we have to get you to 300 because then there's like a,
just, just, we're getting you to 300. Don't, don't give up. Okay. I'm going to run out of
like inventory space. How many do you need? What are you at? I'm at 180.
Yeah, I'm telling you, you've been eating these and like you, you just been eating all the lunch.
You're also not very good at finding them. I've got three already.
I had the Spelunky potion and there was only one over here.
Well, you gotta, you gotta go quickly through the ground, cover the most ground, zoom out.
I'm zoomed out. About 400 is max, by the way. I, I, it was gonna preemptively warn you to not
listen to your chat on this shit, Jerma, but you're falling for it. They think they're smart. They
think they know what they're talking about and they're going to backseat you. They angst me at
the 400, but you need to just like fucking smack them and keep them in line. Tell them you're the
streamer and to trust you. Can you do that? Why would I ever strike somebody in my chair?
That's fucking uncalled for. That's the only way some people learn. What the fuck is a rude
elemental? It's really mean. It's kind of like what I'm doing right now. Is there one above me?
These guys are really distracting. They're like just screaming in my ear, it seems. Hold on,
just despawn them? Yeah, but what if I get attacked and I need them?
Jerma, you don't need anybody. Is there nothing up here? There's nothing. You're a star all on
your own. You don't need these people. Uh, there's another giant clam. Ignore him.
There's a chest here. Um, there's a worm in here too, apparently. What is this?
Cloud in a bottle. Stop. What the fuck? Wait, what? You motherfucker. Really? What are you doing here?
Get away from me. Okay, I've got four hearts for you.
Dude. Okay, this is what we call unfair. He's dead, but I don't want to- that's bullshit.
I'm eating this fucking hamburger. What the fuck else is even else in here?
Giant pearl. I don't have an inventory space. Where are my summons? Summon them. Then
it doesn't want to give them to me anymore. They might be stuck somewhere else so you can
unsummon them by the stat underneath your bar door. Mud blocks. I have like mud.
That's funny to you. It's kind of funny because like I don't want this stuff.
Have you been auto trashing things? No. Get on it. Rope. I don't have any rope. Dangerous potion.
I swear I had a- hold on. I swear I had a shadow key. My god, how do I just delete an item?
How do you just delete an item? You drag it to the bottom right of your inventory. What the fuck?
Oh my god. There was a door in there. Okay, Jerma, I don't know what you're on about,
but here you can have- The trash in the lower right,
you said. I'm putting it and it just like takes up the space. What? Why? Oh my god. No,
it doesn't. Why does it just not just disappear? It's the last thing you delete it in case you
want to take it out. Oh god damn it. I was saying- The one to the left of that is auto
delete and everything you put on that list the moment you pick it up at auto trash.
Because I'm sitting there going like why is this like taking up an inventory space now?
Hello. Here's four life crystals. Don't delete them. Also, here's an item that you will enjoy.
You know, try that that hasty necromancer's heart out a little bit.
Just laughing. Just laughing. Just laugh it up. Don't drown in your bath tonight. Get some water
wings. It was like two feet of water. I know. That's why I thought it was safe. Look, there's
a lot going on there, okay? What did I just- I have a full inventory. Get rid of this. Everybody,
we're real worried about you. I'm fine. Relax. You didn't tell me that I had to do that.
I did. It was one of the very first things I explained. And that was also a week and a half
ago. I thought that you would have a memory of a week. Oh yeah? Well, how come you didn't know how
to turn the server on correctly this week? What was it? I distinctly remember you saying,
I forgot how we did this last week. That's a distinct thing that I heard last week. Is that
not true? I don't think that happened. Hey, is the server working? You ain't gonna fucking fool me.
All right, slowly. Let me- 20 minutes. That's way better than this. All right, so the cloud in a
bottle. Yeah. So there's like different versions of that cloud. Fleeting cloud. Intrepid cloud.
When it says that, that's the stat associated with it. Or it'll be like plus three move speed
or something random on it. And you can re-roll that stat. Do you want this one that has- But
we don't have that melee speed? No. So should I just dump it somewhere? You can probably just
sell it. All right, well what is this? What am I doing? Release bees, win damage. That's good.
After taking damage, let me deal damage to all nearby nodes. That's all right. This one's not
that great though. Yeah, that one's not that- I mean, you take a lot of damage. Can you go over
max mana? Yes. Items will go over max mana. Okay. Yeah, just I'm making sure. So max mana is just
how many stars you can use. And then there's some items later on that'll give you like a hundred
plus max mana. Right. Okay, that's cool. Should I pick up anything else? Let me see this. Fashions
mana powered armor. So that I'm assuming this, I can take hits with my mana bar instead of my health
bar. I'm assuming. Yeah. Dwyane's effect. That's actually really good. Sometimes I don't know if
you're asking me a question, your chat a question, or yourself. All at the same time. Because I feel
like- I feel like I'm falling for a trap if I answer you. No. Like he's going to figure this
out himself in like two seconds, right? But it's rude to ignore you. No, I'm just talking. I just-
What? You don't like talk out loud? Only works if you have no armor or vanity armor equipped. Well,
that's kind of- Oh, that item is not good. Yeah, I was gonna say that was gonna be some.
Necromancer's Heart. Max number of centuries by one. Decreases your life regen. Oh, shit.
It's worth it. Oh, but okay. What is this? A helmet? It's an accessory. Oh, shit. Okay.
Okay. It's a necromancer's heart. Do I put this on my head?
Stick it on. Is this a hat? I don't know if it's like a chest piece. You know how games are.
Yeah. That rune of bleeding. I know how games are. I'm gonna switch out the rune of bleeding.
Because I like this one. I like the double jump. What is making that loud ass noise over here?
That's a little bit of a rumor. All right. So, what do you want to know? That we have some health?
You need to get to 300 health. I need to have 300. Okay. You are not allowed to do anything
else until you get there. Okay. I'm not allowed to do anything else. Okay. I'm running
an associated errand. Okay. I'm gonna go- Do you care if I take another Spelunky potion?
Or will you be mad at me for that? You know, I'll accept it. I accept
that this is the way things are just gonna have to be. And then when we kill Plantera
and we don't have any freaking Spelunky potions, I'll just know who to blame.
Okay. So, don't take one. Is that what you're saying?
No. Go ahead. Just do whatever you want. It's what you normally do anyway.
There's none even in here. Oh, yeah. I took them.
Oh. Was that your insurance policy to make sure I could have taken them?
Oh, no. Because I used one to help you find them. And I got you four.
And you got one. I was just, you know, just trying to help.
I'm gonna bring the bombs down with me. I'm gonna start blowing stuff up down there.
I don't- All right. It's time to go on an explosion spree.
Three, four. All right. And I can have one, two. That's insane. That's awesome. Cool.
All right. I'm gonna go down. Just pick a spot and just go down.
I might even pass you. I would say hello on the way down.
No. No, kid. Your aeon's behind me. You're like a roach to me.
All right. I don't think I'm gonna go down this far. I'm gonna go over here.
I mean, as long as there's an easy path to just run along quickly is all you need.
I guess I'm just gonna go right now. Also, if you went to the jungle,
there is usually a lot in the jungle and the jungle is pretty open.
The jungle? I probably already used the potion, so it's-
I did not use any potion. I don't have any potions. You took them all.
I'm gonna go up. Don't go as far down as, like, the water?
Here. Do this. Go back up to the surface and then keep walking left until you get to the jungle.
It'll be the area that's jungly and green and muddy.
And you should pretty easily be able to find some in there. If not, some chests and other stuff
because we haven't been in the dungeon at all or in the jungle at all.
On my way. Look at this guy. I don't think I'm gonna get a lot of use out of that.
All right. There's a way we can- This looks kind of jungly, doesn't it?
This is not the jungle? I guess not.
Jerm's gonna hate the jungle, I feel. Why do you feel that?
This is desert. I think I'm getting close. Did you open this chest already?
I mean, I'm at the meteor. There's nothing even down over here.
Meteor head and keep going left.
Past the meteor. Past the meteor.
Okay. Ouch! I was prepared for that jump.
Ouch! I see what you're doing there.
All right. Then up this hill, there's the giant hole.
And just keep going down the giant hole.
And this does look like a jungle.
All right. I am at a hole that's in the ground. Is that the one you're talking about?
This big one that's down here? Yep.
All right. Yep.
Let's go get some hearts.
Stand back. I'm gonna throw bombs everywhere.
These are not as strong as I thought they were gonna be.
They're actually very weak, but it's okay. I have a lot of them.
Okay. Nothing yet. Is that gonna hit me?
No. Yes. Watch out.
It's not gonna hit me. All right. Spot.
Let's take a look. Oops. Oops.
Oopsies. No. Even better.
All right. I think there's something right here.
Pretty cool. Found a little cave system.
All right. Keeps going down.
There's no internet in the jungle.
All right. Hold on a minute here.
I ain't gonna fucking screw around.
All right. It's safe.
Moon glow? Just bomb it.
Did you say you were gonna teleport to me?
Soon. I'm trying to get you the thing that you need to have after you've
finished getting life crystals.
Ooh. Yellow slug. Okay. This is something down here.
All right. I got one.
I'm planning for your future.
I found one. Life crystal.
And spiked anklet of the wind.
10% increased movement speed and plus 2% damage.
That seems pretty great.
And it combines with something else, I think, to make like lightning boots or something.
Damn. Artery potion. Recall potion.
And a honey dispenser.
Oh, nice. Okay.
What about this thing? Green torch.
I want that.
Oh, all right. I need...
I need one more heart.
So don't even use the potion.
There's no reason to do that.
Okay. I mean, I'm gonna...
I just need one more.
Okay. No, I'm not gonna drown in here.
Oh. I'm gonna make sure of that.
What? What's wrong?
What? Nothing.
It's fine. Everything's fine.
It was almost bad, but it's fine.
I want to get in there.
I feel like I'm...
I feel like I'll drown in there.
I think I really might.
Club tornado?
Tornado.
All right. No, I'm gonna go this way.
I feel like that's underwater. I don't like that.
Dude, just bomb everything.
That's what I'm doing.
Nice.
Didn't I have more bombs than that?
I thought I had more bombs than that.
I guess I used them all.
Time to dig.
You did use a bit.
Get the fish. Fish. Fish.
Do I? No, I don't.
I don't have to get the fish.
All right. This...
Hold on a minute here.
It's safe.
Ooh. I can go that way.
What's this way?
So much to learn.
You killed a hellbat.
Good for you.
I don't think there's anything up there.
I'll go down here.
Mud block, right?
The mud block is gonna be auto-deleted
when it's in that right slot, right?
Yeah.
Left slot.
The left slot.
The left slot is your list of...
Enable auto-trash.
I mean, it's on the right
but the left one on the right.
How do I put something in there?
Enable auto-trash to automatically trash items.
Is it not enabled?
How do I enable it?
The top button, I think, enables it.
One of them does.
There's like side buttons on it.
Oh, okay. There we go.
This is kind of blending in.
What's down here?
Pee-pee-poo-poo is down there.
Nice.
Nice, dude.
Yeah.
Epic.
Hello.
It pulls out a pee-pee-poo-poo.
I love pee-pee-poo-poo.
You're really gonna pull out a pee-pee-poo-poo?
Yeah.
Unbelievable.
Oh, come on. Where's one?
I need one more.
How many life quarts has he walked by?
Zero.
I've been getting my eyes open.
You've been getting life quarts when you see it.
It's the...
I know what it looks like.
Life? What do you mean, life?
Yeah, he has no clue.
What do you mean, life? Cool.
You don't have to tell me something.
It's different than the heart crystal.
It's a block.
It's heart blocks.
And when you combine 10, you get a life crystal.
Oh, okay.
Cool.
That's really good to know.
I'm glad that you told me this.
I did earlier.
Hey, it doesn't matter.
What did you say?
That you're like...
It doesn't matter.
I'm done.
I'm good.
Okay.
Holy fucking God.
That would have been so embarrassing.
That would have been an actually, horribly embarrassing thing.
I would have had to delete my Twitch account
if I just fell there and died because it was dark.
All right, let me just get up there with the rope.
You move in a mixer?
It's a really easy, funny joke to make, you know?
I mean, you really don't have to be funny on Twitch.
You just have to stay current with whatever the current thing everyone is saying.
And then you'll be like, accepted into the fold.
I have 300.
You're trying too hard with your carnivals and your fucking movie nights.
Just like, come on.
Cut his mic quick.
What the fuck?
Okay.
I think I just would have died, but I landed on health.
Yeah, just throw your cat.
Get your dog in there.
Get Otto in there and chuck him.
I would never do that to a fucking dog.
You are fucked.
Hey, I got another one.
Does Otto ever do malicious poops?
Like, what's with dogs and malicious poops?
Why are you saying it like that?
Well, where it's like they poop somewhere they know they're not supposed to
because they're like, they're trying to get back at you.
Like me and Ashley left the house the other day for a while together
and she like, hates when people leave like all dogs do.
But she's like, such a baby.
I come back and there's two poops like hidden in my bathroom behind the toilet.
Malicious poops.
All right, I'm coming back.
I have 300 health.
Are you ready to move on?
I got 300 HP.
Oh, I'm ready to move on.
Are you?
Oh, yeah, I have 300 health.
Wasn't that the whole point, me to get 300 health?
All right, this really good ring.
Do you like want this?
I don't even know what the hell it is.
What ring?
This, no, this anklet, sorry.
10% increased storage speed.
All right, let me make sure I have everything I want.
Torch.
I want that one.
I'm almost out of apples.
Severed hand.
Auto trash.
Is it just throw away?
Okay.
You're going to pick up a lot of them.
Anyone buy these off you?
Not worried.
I had mud blocks in auto trash.
Oh, what the hell's going on here?
I'm zoom.
I need to zoom in.
You know, you can auto trash more than one thing.
Right?
I think you're getting that, right?
Like, how do I add another slot?
Every time you put something in the auto trash slot, it is auto trashed.
Even if you'll never pick it up again.
So every, even if you stack it on top of it.
Yeah.
And then if you, oh, okay.
And then if you, how do you do it?
I can use the middle button.
If you click the middle button, it shows you everything that's in there.
And then you can remove things later.
That's good to know.
Okay.
All right.
I believe I'm ready to do whatever you want to know.
Okay.
Um, 139.
I know I'm compromising.
Give me like, give me like, I'm coming.
I'm coming.
Okay.
Come here.
Take these blazing hearts for you.
Now use those.
Those are the new life crystal.
Wow.
I couldn't find many more of them though.
That's fine.
We'll be fine.
I'm sorry.
You didn't use the last crystal.
I, it couldn't.
I, I couldn't.
It's, it's stored.
There's a life crystal just in there.
Can you do anything with them after you reach max HP?
I don't think so.
There might be some recipes with them so I'd keep it.
But I forget.
Just in the stash.
There's a fucking fireplace in here.
This guy's crazy.
Okay.
All right.
Very cool.
I need some more torches.
Are we going somewhere dark?
Um, I don't know yet.
Torches are wood and what was it?
Wood and gel or something.
And gel.
We don't have any wood.
Gonna have to cut down some trees.
Do you have any wood?
Nope.
Do we have any trees left to cut down?
Or just buy?
Uh, yeah, there's trees all over the map.
Left or right?
Uh, I think I might've damned him.
Oh, he's here.
Yeah.
This guy, the old guy with the beard.
I think I might've damned him.
Yeah.
I think he might be gone for all eternity.
Let's do 100.
All right.
Where to now that we have good HP?
What's the plan?
Um, slime god.
Slime god.
All right.
Let's go kick his ass.
Hey, baby.
Next time that I see you in the game, I can kick your ass.
Uh, we need one little ingredient.
You guys seriously don't remember that Reggie quote?
And so I'm glad that one person got that.
I actually forgot too.
Who's Reggie?
It's from the Nintendo World Championships 2014.
See, I didn't know that part, but you did.
And that's good.
As somebody myself who's sick of companies and corporations and people selling out,
I for one love Reggie Fils-A-Mate for selling me Nintendo games.
He made it fun.
You can't.
I'm sorry.
There are some things that you just you cannot like talk shit about Reggie.
You can't like that.
I there's some things that I would tolerate.
He worked his way into my heart through a very calculated marketing plan that he himself
didn't even come up.
I fucking love that guy.
I mean, I'm just I'm not I'm not gonna I can't stand for that like at all.
You know what?
Maybe like maybe like one guy in either of our chats really thought about it for a second.
I was like, you know what?
Stir is a salty ball sack, but he might be right.
Okay, I can't agree with his lifestyle, but cut his bike.
I'm about to he's going to get his mic cut quick.
All right.
Uh, I'm ready.
I got my bacon cheeseburger.
I'm ready.
No, just sell this.
Actually, we still have potion merchant.
All right.
That's pretty fucking good.
Actually, I'm going to eat it.
All right.
I got I just clicked the thing.
So we moving.
Uh, I'm grabbing a thing real quick and then we're going to fight the slime god.
Yeah, okay.
I wonder how many times and I know it's like completely necessary,
but I wonder how many times has been said during these two sessions of
I'm just going to go grab this thing real quick.
And he's just gone.
I would have to give you a whole quest to go on to like distract you.
And I really just need I need 25 of a specific block right now.
Do you want to walk over here with me and get this block with me, bro?
Well, you're like 3,500 feet away.
Exactly.
You don't want to come do this.
I'm just going to go get this thing real quick.
I need a couple of these real quick.
Oh, I defeated my 200 zombie.
Cool.
I'm going to need you over here really fast.
I need help collecting these ebstone blocks.
Oh, wait.
I already have 500.
Uh, never mind.
So what's this?
What's the slime gods?
Move set.
Hold on.
Do I dodge left or dodge right?
You have to dodge both.
That's the crazy thing.
This deadly boss mod is going to tell me what to do.
And we got like a cricket sound effect.
I'm dealing with a lot in my life.
Okay.
You show no respect.
I give you a lot of space.
No, I'm talking about like no.
Wow.
Okay.
That's you had something to say.
I'm talking about like I'm I'm outside right now and it's like it's quiet.
Oh, boy.
That was like that was a loaded cannon.
Just ready to blow.
I'm sorry.
You don't even know.
Okay, German.
This is going to be a hard fight.
Deep issues.
All right.
Hard fight.
If you if you do have any potions or like a buff.
I just took my bacon buff.
A potion I threw to you increases mana regen.
Yeah.
Take seven minute duration.
All right.
I took it.
Is it going to be tough you said?
Yeah.
If you run too far away from you, they like run at you really fast and like slam you hard.
So you got to focus more on dodging rather than running dodging slime blobs that are
going to bounce at you and try and jump on you.
Right.
While one like slime orb comes after you.
So dodging is more important.
It's just a lot of shit on the screen.
We need to kill the big blobs as quickly as we can.
Big blob as quick as possible.
Okay, I'm ready to give it a try.
Where do they spy?
Usually we you like, oh, let's build like a platform to fight them.
Or just now most bosses we're just doing right here.
Okay.
So focus on dodging.
Dodging is more important than.
Hey, hey, hey, hey.
Wow, that's so weird.
Don't do that.
I know.
I was just curious.
Wait, what?
Because you did it second.
Now we have I don't understand why it's like overriding our centuries.
So you have to do that.
Just leave them here then.
Just don't even spawn another one.
Right.
I need to touch the table.
Make sure you use your apple.
I have a burger.
I've got bacon already.
I'm ready.
Where's he at?
Okay, so you have to dodge that one.
Don't worry about destroying that one.
The brain.
Oh, yeah.
And it confuses you and shit.
It's really annoying.
So don't get hit by the brain as you've called it.
Ouch.
Oh, my God.
I'm not I'm so slow.
I'm going to fucking.
Let me climb the rope.
Don't die.
Don't just run.
Just run.
Oh, God damn it.
I'm very slow.
Yeah, we both are.
It's kind of a problem.
Because we've never found boots.
And even though I've gotten like every single NPC in the goddamn game,
we still never got the cobbler.
Yeah, I feel like I'm on slash walk right now.
Yeah, it's kind of you can't you really can't dodge those things
unless you can move faster.
I'm assuming there's this.
I mean, there's the thing I just got that like 10 percent movement speed thing.
There is also the if you kill the eye of Cthulhu on expert,
it gives you a dash you can use.
That's a pain in the ass.
And I do it accidentally more often than I do it intentionally.
Should we just stack movement speed to do this
and forget about any other buff things?
No, I think there was I thought there was a person in here.
I'm like, why is there a guy in here?
Where's the one that I got?
Not equipment.
Yeah, there's 10 percent movement speed.
I think it's going to wear it.
What would I replace this with?
The bees thing isn't a lot.
I mean, it's better than nothing.
Use the grappling hook to move quickly.
Yeah, but even then we really need like boots or something.
I'm going to build rooms and see if the guy shows up.
When did I pick up a thousand torches?
Well, I had these for a while or this is this minion damage increase by one.
It's really not a big deal at all, right?
Not really.
I'm just going to wear the anklet then.
I mean, that's a when the fuck did you like?
I guess it really is not that big of a difference.
It kind of is.
You can craft Hermes boots with calamity mod using 10 silk.
Now, when you talk to Hermes boots,
is that like an you talking about an item to make or drop or find?
Oh, yeah, you can.
Well, it's like a 10 step program, too, because we have to make a loom.
Loom?
I forgot how to do all.
You know, I need like a cheater mod.
I need wood.
Can you just go collect wood?
Can you go knock down some trees?
Yeah.
Yeah, I can.
Go chop wood, son, please.
How much do you want?
Just so much.
So wait, I need my axe.
I don't even have an axe.
Come on, please.
Wait, is it piggy bank over?
You can use bombs.
People tell us to replant the trees.
And why did you do this?
Am I making it harder for me to get in my own house?
Uh, is there even an axe in here?
Did we throw away all of our axes?
Maybe.
I think we may have.
Doesn't this guy sell them?
I'm going to buy a copper axe.
OK.
Copper axe.
People are telling me to talk to the guy with the quest.
Fighting the heat.
We're in Egypt when he told me about this artifact and it was very hot there.
Some kind of ice crystal.
Some kind of ice crystal that can cool things.
I thought it would be awesome if I could cool down by using it when it's too hot outside.
I only know that the different ice creatures contain this crystal inside them.
Can you please find it?
OK.
Find the ice crystal.
But first, my most important mission is go collect wood for dad.
That's more important.
God damn it.
Jeremy, you're supposed to chop wood.
And you didn't.
Me and your mother need one moment alone.
So do you want like a thousand wood?
500 would be like art.
OK.
I'll just get a thousand.
And then we're replanting these trees.
OK.
I've got us the max storage space.
We've got we've got a lot of space.
We're doing good on space.
How do you replant a tree?
Just kind of acorn the acorn and you like eat it and you poop it or something.
Father makes son get a thousand logs.
And that is it.
That is at least the second or third like peepee poo poo joke.
From do you know how old I am?
I do actually.
All right.
You want more than 500.
Dude, you I am I doing this wrong?
I'm OK.
I'm just looking through our storage and
I'm finding a lot of things I didn't know we had that are really good things
that I should have known we had.
Yeah.
Every once in a while.
Like there was a bat hook, which is just a better version of the hook you already have.
Oh, cool.
There was like a 56 damage sword.
Nice.
Yeah.
Anything else like I should know about in here?
I told you about the weapon in there and you went.
Did I?
Yeah, I said, hey, this is this weapon here.
It's like cool.
And you were like, no, not worth it.
Does that mean trees going to be growing over here?
Oh, and there's also working.
You should have a minotaur skull because, you know, there's someone
that's on the helmet, right?
OK, yeah, it's not.
Is it too close?
You need three blocks in between them.
OK, just plant trees out here.
Can I imitate a bop it, please?
I think I did that like two years ago to get high trees.
You need three blocks in between the seeds.
All right.
I'll just put them every so often, you know.
I'm going to have like a thousand wood here soon.
I currently have 571.
No, no, no, no, you don't.
I plan to torch.
That's not what I wanted to do.
Germa terraria, germa terraria, germa terraria with a bunch of pogchamps.
Pog, pog, pog, pog, pog, pog.
What's the hardest thing in the whole game?
All right.
Well, what's the thing in the game that is so difficult that you have to play perfectly
and there's still a random chance that you're going to lose no matter what you do?
The final calamity boss, which I can't call me this or something.
Cal Midas.
It's something like that.
Supreme Calamity Calamity.
Yeah, that's the one.
Have you ever beat it?
My game actually bugged at a certain point in Calamity, so I never got to the end.
One of the bosses would appear and then run away from me.
So I just kind of stopped playing.
Time to operate.
I forgot about that.
Sorry, we're just talking about like funny jokes in the stream.
You know what I mean?
Oh, yeah, I understand.
Funny jokes.
It was like a storm wraith worm that you absolutely 100% need to continue progression.
Just would run away.
For a second.
I thought that was said.
Germa has cut down his 50th tree or something.
I was like, well, did 50th slime.
I feel like I've killed way more than 50 slimes.
They just accidentally get in the way and you just chop through them.
How long does it take for a tree to grow?
I do.
I don't know.
Just just sit there forever.
Okay.
That's what chat wants you to do.
That's been like telling you to plant trees since we started this playthrough.
So you're going to sit there and you're going to wait until those trees grow.
Why haven't you planted any trees?
Because it's a waste of time.
What?
What do you mean it's a waste of time?
Why am I doing this thing?
If you just walked it to your right, there's more trees.
There's some more trees over there.
Okay.
Well, I'm coming back with 833 wood.
Is that enough for you?
That is more than enough.
We'll probably never get through that.
So all the trees you planted kind of pointless.
Just throwing it out there.
Well, it was good to know.
Yeah.
I mean, it was, you know, learned.
You learned next week.
I'll remind you.
Here you go.
Dickhead.
Go get it.
I'm sorry.
I'll get it.
I'll go get that.
I'm sorry.
That was my fault.
Wow.
Germa uncensored.
Ha ha.
Oh God.
You want this or not?
I do.
I forget why I want it.
Why did we need it?
I don't know.
You just maybe go do that.
You said when I need 500, we'll do it.
500.
We'll do it.
Was that a punishment?
Like father, son, you go chop wood.
And I don't remember why I wanted it.
Was that just you just punishing me?
No, I like actually needed it, but I don't know why.
Oh my God.
The loom for the loom.
The loom.
Are you building a loom right now or have you DCed?
Loom for the boots.
He muted.
Germa uncensored.
Ha ha.
Oh God.
Look, it was like a different time back in 2012.
Titles, I didn't even like, nobody even knew what to do.
Nobody.
Your titles in like 2011, 2012 were not like cool, like ironic, funny titles.
You can just forget about that.
Come over here.
Can you talk to Popo while I talk to Popo?
Is that a thing?
Yes.
So he sells potions.
He's our guy.
Before we fight a boss, he's our freaking guy.
Okay, so vanilla potions gives you an extra summon, health regeneration, extra defense.
He is our guy.
There's actually one button, I forget what it is.
Someone probably knows.
You press one button, it drinks all the unique potions you have in your whole inventory.
Really?
B.
Yeah, so don't accidentally press B.
Don't press B.
Until you need to press B.
Let's you move swiftly in liquid.
Okay.
Oh, also take, here, take this.
I'm giving you a skull.
I'm currently trying to process.
Well, it's a very important item that I got.
I got it for you.
You just, I'm like, I just turned 21 and you brought me into the fucking bar.
And you're like, hey, what do you want?
It's like, I, what even is rum?
What the fuck does vodka taste like?
I don't know.
Hold on a second.
Iron skin.
Oh, you get iron skin.
I'm trying.
Increases D.
That's a lot.
Yeah.
Do I not have any money?
Where's all my money?
What did you say?
Okay.
Fleeting Minotaur skull.
Here's some money.
Increases your max number of minions by one.
Decreases non-minion damage by 10%.
Is this a helmet?
It's an accessory.
Yes, but this is, this is a skull.
No drama.
No, that's a skull.
We had the same conversation.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
A heart is like as big as your fist.
A Minotaur skull is like a huge fucking skull hollowed out.
We've had this conversation before.
No, no, no.
I'm not going to have it again with you.
I refuse to accept that one.
So what do I replace then?
This one's 20 mana.
That's pretty good.
A Minotaur skull would like, it would be too big.
Yeah, real life Minotaur.
Hello.
Get rid of the B, but it's plus four defense.
That's a lot.
Is plus four D.
That's a lot of defense, right?
It's okay.
So I wouldn't want to replace that.
What about the 20, maybe the 20 mana?
What is 20?
Yeah, get that out of here.
It's not, I mean, slowly generate life, but that's another minion.
And I can't just put it on.
Yeah.
Now I can have like five of these fucking things.
Get rid of the crappy anklet.
I remember why we needed wood, but I think it's good.
Okay.
Crappy anklet.
This is good.
Well, this is, okay, you, there's a,
why do I have candy cane blocks here?
Isn't that what you wanted?
Do we need any blood drop, green slime?
But I'm just saying literally everything I have.
Just dump it.
This person's name.
I just got five community subs from somebody named Jerma sucks.
It's like capital J and capital S, just Jerma sucks.
S-U-C-K-S.
My man.
Well, thank you, by the way.
How do I make a loom?
A sawmill?
37 gold.
What am I doing?
All right.
You wanted me to buy.
Okay.
I'm going to buy man of a generation potion.
Right?
I already did it, so you can't tell me no.
Iron skin.
Should I buy like a few of each of these?
Yeah, because you're going to keep using them.
Iron chain.
That's right.
That's the stupid random thing that you need to make the one time.
It makes, oh, let's make 10 chains.
Like I'm not destroying the environment by doing this.
I only need one, but I'll buy 10.
Thanks for selling it in a pack.
Obsidian skin potion.
Light regen.
Yeah.
And then shine.
Marmo light in the abyss.
What's that mean?
Ah, don't worry about that.
Oh, spelunker.
These are expensive.
Do we need these anymore?
We don't need spelunkers anymore, do we?
We will always need them.
Well, this seems insanely important.
I'm going to get like 10 of these.
Max number of minions.
Top row is up there.
Okay, that looks like a sawmill.
Am I spending all of our money?
You're spending a lot of it.
It's fine.
We had like 40 gold when it's gone.
I mean, just go through all my expenses.
What's the big deal?
It's all gone.
I used 40 gold.
This is why you have to like get it.
You have to like get a different box from me.
You just make, all right.
Listen, let me tell you something.
Let me get, this is a strategy we're going to use.
Make me a separate box for me to put my stuff in.
And then you can just go in there.
Too many of them might crash or cause problems in multiplayer.
Oh, all right, never mind.
So I'd rather just have it all in one spot.
And even then, I think it was making too many slots
might be a problem, but I don't know.
Okay.
Well, I'm going to, I don't want to press B on some of these.
Yeah, you have cobweb.
You must have like a million cobweb.
I probably have put like hundreds of it in here.
Is it in your ammo?
Sometimes it goes there.
Uh, no, I have snow, I have 12 snowballs.
I swear to God, I had cobweb.
Did you already take it out of here?
Yeah.
Upgrade your copper axe.
No, I just, all right.
I want this, whatever it is.
What is this?
Because that is, I want like the fucking popsicle.
Is it, can you get, is there one that exists in this game
that has blue as well?
You know, like the rocket popsicles.
What are you talking about?
What?
Damn.
Oh my God, I forgot about auto houses.
My God.
Kind of irrelevant now.
Why are there two Minotaur skulls in here?
Because I had more than one.
Uh, I think later on you can combine them with some stuff.
Let me see how many of these I can have.
Oh man, that's insane.
Five of these things just flying around.
Five of these things in two of these centuries.
So you, can you stack the skulls?
I don't think so.
Are you sure?
Can you?
I mean, I don't see why not.
Um, huh, well.
I've never thought about that.
No, you can't.
No, they're unique.
Oh well.
All right, so I'm going to, I've got,
I'm pretty much ready to do whatever you want to do.
I just need to go get one thing real quick.
Sure you do.
I'm sure you do.
If we want to fight the slime god again,
and I personally, that's what I want to do.
You want to fight slime god again?
Okay.
We need more blighted gel.
Hey Jeremy, can you give a shout out to my cat by going pss pss pss?
Yeah.
Pss pss pss pss.
All right, so I'm going to go get that.
All right, you're going to go get something real quick?
Yep.
I'm going to go get something to eat.
Combine, wait, there was a, there was a,
there was an advice Jupiter.
Combine the minotaur skull with your necromancer's heart.
Um, no, I think you also need a soul stone.
Hold on, wait, what do you mean?
You might also need a soul stone to make what he's doing.
I talked to a craft guy.
It's Jeffrey, right?
Remember, am I muted or am I talking to you?
His name's Jeffrey, right?
I don't remember.
Ah, sorry.
Wait, I put the minotaur skull on the crafting thing.
Okay, I need a soul stone.
What is that?
10% increase minion damage, increase your mach number of minions,
increase your mach number of sentries.
Taking fatal damage will instead return you to 20 life every five minutes.
Where do we get a soul stone?
Uh, we need a mana bauble and blood.
I think we might have one of those.
Uh, search for mana bauble.
Mana bauble?
Yeah.
Oh, mana bauble you could just make with 15 arcane dust.
But the thing we don't have is the goblin to combine trinkets,
so we can't actually do that yet.
What?
We have to find the goblin guy.
Sometimes he's in the dungeon, like, bound,
or he's underground, like, tied up, and you need to rescue him.
And he's really important.
Just make the mana bauble?
Yeah, you could.
You might as well do that now.
So what does it take to do to make a mana bauble?
What does it have to put in there?
15 arcane dust, which is you can make from fallen stars.
Oh, okay.
I have 10 fallen stars on me right now,
so I can basically make it when I come back.
I don't think we have any fallen stars.
Hey, I have 10 fallen stars on me right now,
so I can make it when I come back.
Yeah, but I wanted to do something because I'm useless.
I'm just like the guy standing.
I'm like an NPC in your house.
Well, do some research.
You gotta let me fly.
Try and find the goblin guy.
Get some cobwebs.
I'm gonna go cobweb hunting.
Let's kill spiders, I'm assuming, right?
I already forget why I needed the silk in the first place.
Tori is like, that's like, okay, I need a loom.
I should do this.
I need to get, I need a sawmill.
Okay, now I've got this.
I need cobweb to make...
Why do I need silk for?
Oh, for boots to make boots.
Okay.
You need to cut a hundred, a thousand wood.
I need to cut a thousand trees down to summon the goblin.
Sure.
Son, go get some cobweb.
All right. Cobweb comes with spiders.
Spiders come from underground.
We can fight the god again.
All right.
Or do you want to get the boots first?
Um, let's, let's try it again.
Let's fight.
Let's win.
I've got extra minions.
Wait, this is cobweb.
Barry the cob, the cobbler!
Cobbler!
There he is, right?
Where is he?
He's, I don't know, find him.
The kick your ass.
Is he in there?
Is he in there to kick your ass?
Oh, he's on the roof.
Is that him?
Yeah, that's him.
I don't think he sells the specific thing we need, though.
But he does have boots that help you run.
Whoa.
What is this stuff?
Okay, hold on.
Too bad I spent all, we don't have any money.
Healthy boots.
Oh, no, he does sell Hermes boots.
I think he spent all our money.
Five gold for Hermes boots,
or we can just like gather cobweb.
I am gathering nothing.
Find a pig.
We have 28 gold in the story.
American runs super fast.
Damaging drops from below your boots.
So Hermes boots are just,
you just put them on and never take them off.
You'll take them off eventually, but.
And also I'm pretty sure we have the stuff
to combine with Hermes boots to make lightning boots.
Let me check on that.
Dun, dun, dun, dun, dun, dun, dun.
Oh, we need the fucking goblin.
Everything, everything.
We need rocket boots and the goblin sells rocket boots.
And yeah, and we couldn't combine without the tinker anyway.
God damn it, dude.
All right, well, let's just kill this guy.
We have like our soup.
Press B before we go.
Let's kill.
We have upgraded our health.
Last time we fought this guy,
didn't we only have like 200 health?
Or would that, am I making that up?
You're making that up.
But we didn't have potions.
We can beat them with potions.
You ready?
All right, hold on.
Am I about to press B?
You take everything, right?
Yeah.
All right, I'm gonna, I'm gonna put,
you know, put your sentry down first.
Did you put one down?
Yeah.
Okay.
Pressing B for potions now.
Holy fuck, that's a lot.
And I gotta eat a hamburger.
All right, I'm ready.
I don't have the thing.
Oh!
Piggy!
We only have four minutes of these potions.
What did you do?
I need ebstone blocks.
What?
What is it?
Ebstone block.
What do you mean?
Do I have any?
I've got boots.
I'll be quick.
Gonna do something real quick.
Oh, by the way, that was probably like,
that was probably like nine gold.
I'm gonna get killed, kill Piggy.
They, it lasts for like seven minutes.
I'll be back.
No, it doesn't. It lasts for four.
I'll be, dude, it's gonna take like two seconds.
Like I'm already done.
Like I already have it.
I'm killing the pig.
Okay, you're putting it to use.
Good thing I took all these potions to get 500 of them.
Yeah, and I turned them all into blocks.
I need ebstone brick, like the raw form of it.
I forgot why I went and got them, I think.
Oh wait, no.
It's the whole thing.
You know what? Just, just forget about me.
Forget about me.
You'd be happier if you didn't even know me.
At least the sentries are still up there.
Forget about me.
Okay, I'm ready.
Did we take enough potions again?
No.
No, they last four minutes.
Okay.
Oh my god, I have a gravity potion.
It ate my fucking gravity potion.
Why am I floating around?
Because you probably also had a featherfall potion like I did.
No, I don't think I did.
Stop bouncing around on me.
God damn it.
Ow.
Ow, they're everywhere.
I'm gonna die.
Talk to the nurse if you need to.
I'm dead.
I got juggled.
Oh, gravity potion wore off.
Okay, this is so much harder when I'm not running.
Oh god.
Just don't die, just don't die, just don't die.
It's kind of impossible.
It's impossible.
It's impossible for me to not die.
I'm dead.
Oh my god.
I'm just trying to talk to...
I can't move.
No, it's still here.
It's still here.
We're like this late in the game and I still don't have a weapon I want to use.
Is it still here?
No.
Germany gets all the fucking good items.
There's something dropped over here though.
Immunity...
What is a nazar?
Ayaya.
Climb the rope?
It's harder when you get like hit and you just get juggled.
What is this thing?
I have some casualties.
Make more platforms?
Yeah, we kind of only have this one platform.
Should we make like two or three other platforms to fall down to and jump to?
Fall down and jump up and...
Because we're really only like one one plane.
Yeah.
Okay, do it.
Was that was all that wood that I bought?
Yeah, I put it in the storage.
I'm gonna go get a thing real quick.
Do we just have platforms?
The wood just turns into platforms.
It just does, right?
How much should I have?
Like a couple hundred?
Yeah, so then we can kind of like jump and fall from plan to plan.
I think Jerma last stream said building these platforms was cheating.
Did I say that?
You did.
I don't remember that.
Okay, so theoretically...
How did you make the...
How did you do like the little...
It has to be connected to a wall, doesn't it?
In it?
Yeah, how did you do this though?
How did you make like the little staircase?
How did you like place the stairs?
I have no idea what you're talking about.
Oh, there we go.
All right, so you gotta be like enough to...
Let's see, like that we can jump.
Like right here.
Because if I go like this, right there.
I can clean that up.
Okay, yeah, it seems like you can like jump up.
Like jump up over here and then up.
There's more...
Because you just can't get away.
There's just too many things to like have to dodge.
They take up the whole space.
Ralph is here.
Who's Ralph?
Okay, I'm gonna like do...
I'm gonna make like a...
Hold on.
I'm gonna do a bigger arena.
You go get...
You do a good thing real quick.
I'm gonna make like some space.
I got the soul thing for you.
So when we finally get Goblin Man.
I need more of these.
All I do is give.
All I freaking do is give.
And what does Jerma do?
Take, take, take.
All right, this should be good.
Let's see if he'll laugh.
That's all I can do.
I mean, yeah, because like what are you even talking about?
I'm doing stuff here.
All right, I'm thinking...
Let's do another one.
We're making an old NES game.
We're making...
What's that game?
That like Burger Town game?
Burger Time.
What?
A goblin army is approaching from the east.
We're being invaded.
Oh.
Goblin army.
No.
Is this like bad?
Do I have to get over there?
No.
It's like the blood moon.
They just keep coming until you kill enough of them.
And this is...
We needed this, right?
Didn't you say we needed this stuff?
No.
Okay.
It's so funny that I can look over there and see.
Like exactly...
You're not even writing the emote.
Jerma, give me your minotaur skull and your other thing.
Minotaur skull and the...
Okay, buddy.
Give them to me.
All right, hold on.
Geez, I'm kidding.
Give them.
What an idiot.
Get robbed.
I'm a summoner now.
Oh yeah, that's right.
You are the summoner now.
All right, we have a pretty interesting platform now
to like escape stuff and like drop down and escape that and jump here and...
All right, I'm gonna pee, okay?
While the goblins invade, he's gonna pee.
No, fine.
I won't.
I thought you said this wasn't a big deal.
Yeah, but you have to like actually do this one.
Blood moon just kind of ends.
This one has like a percentage.
Oh.
Is there a boss again?
I would appreciate your help.
Because all I do is give.
Just pee my pants.
Just what?
I said I have...
Somebody said just pee.
Just like pee your pants.
Just go to the bathroom.
Yeah, good.
The thing is, I could do that and no one would know I actually did that.
I mean, you'd probably tell everyone.
Where's Jerma?
Jerma, I need you.
I'm right here.
Jerma, take this.
It's the thing.
Oh my god, this is the best birthday ever.
Thank you.
Hey, no problem.
All I do is give.
Well, to be fair, you did just take that from me before an invasion.
Sorry?
Don't...
Stop comparing this game to Minecraft.
It's way different.
Nobody wrote any of that.
I just...
I'm trying just to cause constant conflict in the chat.
That's usually what I'm doing.
You need some help?
I can do a better job.
No, I do not need your help in that.
Oh, because I'm too good?
No, I...
We don't...
We do not need like a...
Like here comes like a hot take from Star.
I have some pretty good takes.
No, I don't want any of those takes.
I don't want to hear any of those.
All right, I guess that's fair.
I think so too.
It's pretty fair.
So this is this you would?
Oh, yeah.
You don't have to chop it.
They just drop it.
It's really helpful that way.
It's very helpful.
Or you could plant trees.
Goblin army has been defeated.
Good job.
So now what does that do?
Should hopefully aid in finding this goblin asshole.
All right, I have to go pee.
I'll be right back.
All right, I'm going to go spelunking.
Everyone on the squad stream,
click over to Star's stream now
because that guy's just going to stand still
and type in my chat.
Like what happened to Hillary's emails?
What about them?
Hey, don't worry.
We'll be back.
We can all have like an intelligent discussion
now that he's gone.
I am absolutely...
By the way, I'm absolutely...
I'm gonna cut you.
I'm like...
He's...
No, it is...
I'm not going to...
I'm not going to walk away.
You think I'm going to walk away?
No.
All right, I'll see you later.
I'll be back in like two minutes.
Okay.
I am...
I'm back.
Hey, how's it going?
How are you?
Okay, let's go.
What do you say?
What do we do now?
I am looking for the goblin tinker.
Cool.
That's 100% the priority.
I have popped a hunter potion to see enemies,
which apparently, according to my...
I'm going to continue to build our boss chat room.
If you want to actually build an insane boss arena...
That's what I'm going to do.
You can make an arena out of minecart tracks.
And then at the end of a minecart track,
you can change it so you turn and change directions,
and you can actually make an in-the-air diamond-shaped minecart
that just drives you around in circles.
Pretty dope.
All right, I'm going to do one more of these.
If you like having like four,
and then also just in case you fall,
you know, we need some one down here too.
This is more for me than it is for you.
Okay.
People are telling me to get the boots.
Get the boots, get the boots, get the boots.
Should I get the Hermes boots?
Should I just get them?
Yeah.
Especially if you don't even know what they do,
so you need to like experience what they're doing for you.
I will after I do this.
Watch out, bug.
Or maybe you could wait.
Actually, I don't know.
He spawned flat ground just off screen.
There we go.
And then I'm going to do this.
Just in case, you know, a little spot.
This is fun.
Enjoying building, you know,
a nice little simple build stream, no pressure.
This is, yeah, let's just-
Flip that house.
Make sure you build a roof.
And-
A roof?
Why would I-
We need a roof on-
Here it is.
I found the guy.
And then you're going to want to get some heart statues,
you know, set up the red wire,
and you're like to have the hearts that you shoot out hearts for you.
All right, that's good.
Dude, it's Chuboy.
Someone said don't have the arena that close to the NPCs.
Yeah, I'll move.
Like, I'm going to have like another section over here.
Oh, somebody gives 10 community subs.
Who was it?
It wasn't me.
It's a great Canadian FK club.
Thanks for the 10 subs.
Thank you.
Sick.
That's a lot of subs.
No, thank you so much.
What mods are being used?
Uh, times 5,000 damage.
We die instantly, one hit kill.
And permadeath.
Mean streamer gives sarcastic answer live on Twitch.
Never trust him again.
I've actually, I really don't, I don't even really know.
He's the mod guy.
He's like, hey, just join my server.
And it was like exclamation point mod.
And not Jermis chat.
It's still mildly inaccurate.
Silly physics.
Yeah, we have a silly physics mod.
I didn't buy the table.
Yeah.
He's going to like, I don't know.
How long does he spend down here?
He's already up.
No, he's not.
I don't have any god dang recall potions.
My life is misery.
Okay.
Oh, now I'm going to do that.
What?
Stop that.
So now you can just be like, oh, there he's coming down this way.
All right.
They're all up here.
Down.
All right.
Up we go this way.
They came, they dropped down up.
Okay.
Jerma, it'll be good.
I don't think I have enough gold.
Not enough gold?
What do you mean?
You need money?
All right.
That's enough.
Where do you go to get your swell on?
What?
Like, what's your what are your hobbies?
You have any outdoor activities?
You going outside in Vegas?
There's a lot of beautiful places in Vegas.
There's a lot of like mountains and trails and yeah, there's a lot of cool stuff.
But do you go to them?
Yeah, a couple of times when you have the opportunity.
I'm worried about you.
I mean, used to be like so in shape and so buff.
I could feel it.
Press B to run.
Nope, that's not going to work.
Okay, he's going to mute Mike again.
Why am I going to mute Mike?
I don't know.
You just don't like talking to me, I guess.
I want some like, I think I want some more coffee.
This late?
Yeah, never mind.
You're right.
This is too late.
Get some vodka.
I got too much shit to do.
And yet you're here playing Terraria.
What does this like hourglass looking dropper you've made?
It's just like a design.
Oh, so you're like splicing up our lives out here?
I mean, yeah, it's just like it's an easy aesthetically pleasing structure.
Oh, all right.
This is good, right?
We have a lot of places to go.
I'm going to do one more down here, but not actually down here.
Okay, because then it's like, oh, no, I fell off right here.
It's all right.
All right, now I'm going to go get the boots and put them on.
Do I have enough money?
Let's find out.
I'm a boot master.
I do have enough money.
Harpoon.
Is this any good?
Not really.
All right.
Spike bomb.
Cool.
This you would I'm just gonna put.
All right.
This is like four jumps.
Hey, this, this Nazar.
What is this?
It's like equipable immunity to curse.
Like, is this just a material that I'm going to need at some point later?
I don't remember what curse is.
So I don't know.
I think it's like good for a specific boss, but I forget which status is cursed.
Dude, look at this thing.
Look at this thing.
So what do I replace this with?
Well, you know, I know.
Okay.
So how many minions can I have now?
Count them up.
Max entries, max minions.
I have another room for another accessory, too.
Is there anything else I should be putting on?
What's the one that I have the mana one on already?
20 mana.
Boots.
One of the boots of boots, though, aren't they?
Or boots.
The boots are new boots.
They're not an accessory, right?
You can buy the Hermes boots and buy the rocket boots off the tinker and combine them to make
runny, jumpy boots.
Spectre boots.
Yeah.
But can I put this on?
Oh, this is where it gets tricky for me.
The boots are an accessory, they're not actual boots.
Well, I'm going to go get them.
Is that guy still on the roof or did you lock him in something?
A cobbler?
He should be in one of these rooms.
He's on the final room.
Oh, I don't have the Bank of fucking America mod.
I don't know.
I'm having Deja vu.
What is that?
I want to go find ice skates.
Do we have one?
All right.
Hermes boots.
I own them.
Wow.
Those are fun.
Oh shit, you can.
How do I get out of here?
Wow.
You are stuck.
Please rebuild that wall, though, because that'll stop being a house.
It'll stop being a house.
Yeah.
It's just standard wood to do that, right?
The wood that you just destroyed, you just picked up because you destroyed it.
So you have it.
I didn't know how that worked.
I didn't know if it fell.
All right.
Cool.
Nice hook.
So now I have the boots.
I have that cool new item.
Let me see what I got now for, you know, stuff.
Get the rocket boots, rocket boots, rocket boots.
I think the tinker is still in the cave.
Yeah, I would just wait for him to appear, which will just be a while.
I think we might have to like leave this area and come back.
Okay.
Well, this is just a healing potion, 100 life versus 50 life.
How do I make it so does it do the better ones first when you press H?
I think so.
Oh, requires an ice machine.
Okay.
I knew it was something.
Get, get the sans head from the chest.
Hold on.
Let me like just go over what I need to like.
I just got this new item and shit.
So now I have one, two, three, four, five, six, seven, eight.
No, no, no.
Holy shit.
I'm an idiot.
I was like, no way.
I was like, wow, keep going.
They just keep spawning.
You'll get that many later though.
Two centuries and five of these.
All right.
So now this, what is this?
This thing, 28 magic damage.
Storm cloud.
I feel like I'm not using this at all.
19 magic damage.
It looks cool, but I'm not using it.
What about us we have?
Do I just drop those?
Do we?
I think I have to use the fucking sans head.
Would that be so bad?
No, I mean, I just don't like using it.
This is the day.
Why don't you like it?
I've given you everything, Jerma.
What's wrong?
Get the, do you think I was literally born yesterday?
I'm going to set you.
Oh yeah.
What's that?
Okay.
I think I have my gear that I want.
Got my stuff.
I'm going to be able to have another one of these.
Minions, mana regen, life regen, defense, and movement speed.
Is what happens when I press B.
So that means I can have a sixth minion.
We have our arena over here that is being, it's not just one plane.
You can run around.
Should I put torches around every, up here?
I'd put campfires.
Campfires.
I don't know how to even make them.
Which is wood and torches.
Oh, okay.
I guess campfires give health regeneration.
How many should I just put them everywhere?
I guess.
Just fucking just have campfires everywhere.
Yeah, sure.
All right.
For 10 or 15 spaces.
Wow.
That's not specific at all.
Oh yeah.
We have a star fury.
Hold on.
We need those.
But we basically can make it.
God damn it.
I'd like the last time I played Terraria, I did a run with this weapon
and I don't want to do the same thing again, but it's such a good weapon.
Am I not picking those up?
No, wait.
Okay.
That was a yawn voice.
It was.
Last time I played this game, I used this weapon and I literally wanted to do it again.
I'm sorry that I'm boring you.
Do that again.
No, don't do it that fast.
Do it like every, like, do it like every one or do it every like two or three seconds.
Good.
Keep going.
Okay.
That's that's great.
That's just wow.
That's great.
All right.
There's a lot of fires up here.
I love these.
Okay.
Here's what we're going to do.
Yep.
We're going to fight this thing one more time.
Okay.
Hold on.
Let me just do.
Oh, stop hitting me.
There's a rope here.
Should I do like a Donkey Kong tropical breeze?
Whatever the name of that game is and have like vines to like climb on?
Probably not.
If they like hit you while you're on a vine, you get released.
Unless we can.
I think you can craft cobalt shields in this.
That would actually be really helpful.
I don't know how to do it.
They're saying hang heart lanterns.
Yeah, just because you like get like, you know what I'm saying?
Jump, jump, jump like from vine to vine.
You're going to try and do that during the fight and you think you want it, but you don't.
But what if, but just what if there's a reason?
What if it happens?
What if you just fight?
What if, what if you just have a scenario where that works?
You think you want it.
All right.
So I think we have a decent area here.
But you don't.
Here, take this.
I don't want it.
Glass.
I don't want to make glass, dude.
But I like need to really bad.
So, um, chat is, you wouldn't, you're making fun of me for like doing,
like picking up shitty stuff.
But somebody said they were watching the other stream
and they're saying that you, your inventory looks fucking stupid right now.
Like it's being spammed.
What?
You're like, oh, you pick it up like dumb shit, like stuff we don't need.
And there's somebody saying that you're in your inventory.
You have like a bunch of trash.
Is this true?
I mean, like one or two things.
What is it?
It's not a big deal.
What do you have in your inventory?
That's like, so there's such a problem.
Throwing knives, jester arrows.
Why do you have jester arrows?
Because I picked them up.
Want to fight about it?
I forgot what I was looking for here.
Wait, does he have like auto trash?
Nobody said that drama making shit up constant conflict.
I was taking stuff out of the, I was taking stuff out of our bank and throwing it at you.
And I think I might've just deleted a bunch of stuff because you have it on auto delete.
What?
I've been throwing shit at you while you were staring at like nothing.
Oh yeah.
Then I was probably just fucking deleting it.
If you're throwing like really stupid shit at me.
Like, what did you throw at me?
I don't remember.
It might've been, there was a magnum.
You threw magnum rounds at me?
Like, I know you don't need them.
Flaming arrows.
Like, okay, let's fight this fucking boss.
Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait.
Get ready for it.
Wait, I need, I need those.
I gave you something.
I need them back.
What do you need?
I don't know.
The thing that shoots the bee.
The bee gun.
I gave you like ammo.
Wooden arrows.
You gave me 500 wooden arrows.
Here you go.
Here's your trash bag.
Thank you.
Okay.
All right.
Touch this.
Hold on.
I need to get this.
So we're doing the same thing.
I'm just touch the thing.
I'm going to spawn all my friends.
Just let me know when you are ready to do this.
Do that thing.
Okay.
I'm ready.
Okay, let's go.
I mean, is this kind of cheating if you just build platforms?
Is this like cheating?
Stop.
I'm concentrating.
But it's cheating though, right?
Stop it.
Can we do it?
Shell.
Oh, what was that?
That was huge.
That was all the-
Slime god.
Oh, yeah.
Gives you this stupid item.
It's going to give you a place in your inventory
that like permanently makes you slippery.
Oh, yeah.
I hate this.
How do I get rid of this?
You just delete it.
Get rid of that.
But what does it-
He gives purified gel, which is a crafting thing.
Some stuff.
But should we-
Does this have any purpose at all?
No.
None.
Don't even put this in the-
Just throw it away.
No.
Because are you ever going to want to slide around?
I mean, can I slide around and do like a thousand damage a second?
No.
All right, I threw it away.
You're going to slide into my DMs though.
What?
A frog leg.
All right, what are-
Okay, a long time ago, you told me about this weapon, this Arcalis.
Yeah.
And oh, you can turn it into something eventually.
Yes.
We need to be in hard mode to finish it.
Okay.
It is a really, really, really good weapon though.
But we would just need to kill wall of flesh
and then we could basically build it.
Okay.
He put the slime god shit in the chest.
What shit?
What did you do?
Well, what a bunch of fucking tattletales.
Really?
Am I being pranked right now?
No, I just-
I put the slime god thing in the box to save it in case-
just in case we wanted it.
And everybody ran-
No, it's not.
What if we want to use it?
He put it in the box.
This is why we shouldn't be squad streaming right now.
You know what? Communication is key.
Eventually it all comes out.
Somebody said get carnage.
Carnage?
Carnage is a sword that I have.
Oh, you have it.
Why? Does it make something?
Get carnage from storage.
No, I have it.
Why do you need it?
I don't know.
Somebody just wrote in all caps like, get it.
Okay, well ignore that guy.
I don't know.
I'm just- people have thrown out ideas.
He reads the one guy that says carnage,
but not the spam for the rocket boots.
I can't even make the rocket boots
because the goblin isn't up here.
Is he?
Oh, he's up here now.
He's this blue guy in a-
So I can do it now.
I couldn't do it before.
I would have to go-
There was a reason why I've been waiting.
It's a reforge, right?
No, reforge is to reforge the random stat.
What you're doing is shopping.
Because he has rocket boots.
Allows flight.
And then I combine the rocket boots
and the Hermes boots.
This table right here is the combining table
that you're standing in front of right now.
You can combine rocket boots
and Hermes boots to make specter boots.
And then I think you can combine
specter boots and Zephyr,
which I will give you even though I was using it.
And then you can make lightning boots.
The warican runs super fast.
So I've got Hermes boots, rocket boots,
specter boots, and then specter boots
and whatever you just threw to me
makes another one.
Makes lightning boots.
Okay, lightning boots.
Allows flight, the warican run incredibly fast.
Wow, this is cool.
All right, let's go.
And then the next thing that I did, I-
What? You need to also get some shit
to make frostbark boots.
It just keeps going.
Is this monster hunter or is this terraria?
A bit of both.
Holy shit.
I could, how much?
They're like little bunny slippers.
That's the takeaway.
They're bunny slippers.
Oh, this is like, this is great.
Oh, are you talking about carnage ray?
The like staff?
We could probably make that.
I think we have most of this.
I'm too lazy.
That's, yeah, this is not that fast though.
I mean, it has to, it queues up
and you go, you have to be running
for a while for this to work.
Yeah, if you use your grappling hook,
you instantly get to run speed.
Oh, really?
Okay.
I didn't know that.
Let me test that.
Perfectly on the ground.
All right, so we're walking,
we're walking, we're walking.
Oh dude, this is actually probably what
you should be making.
This would be very good.
I see.
Okay.
You gotta release the hook first, too.
All right, I get it.
Oh, goo bow.
So, ah, these are cool.
Hey, why'd you even kill that boar?
There was no reason to kill that boar.
Here we go.
Oh, that's so fun.
I wasn't making a joke.
I was just wanting to say, here we go.
All right, what do you want to do?
One second, I'm reading something.
Oh, and we kind of need hell stone,
but also we can kind of just honestly
skip a lot of this if we just kill
the wall of flesh.
What else can this be turned into?
Frost spark boots, lightning boots,
and ice skates.
Okay, allows flight super fast running
and extra mobility on ice,
seven percent increase movement speed.
What do you get the ice gate?
You can make ice skates out of leather
and ice blocks.
Leather and ice blocks.
Okay, without these on,
I don't think I would play the game.
I'm just realizing how slow that is.
Yeah, that's pretty bad.
Wow, it doesn't feel like an immediate,
it is.
That's huge.
You can never go back now.
There's a couple things we can do.
Like, because we killed that boss,
we have a material that can make
a bunch of stuff and a lot of it's good.
Yeah, my internet's not not up.
That was weird.
No, my internet's like not my internet's fine.
That wasn't like my internet.
That was weird.
Was it?
It's Twitch.
Oh, not my Twitch.
It was Twitch's fault.
Oh, maybe the server like ingest servers.
Not my Twitch.
Twitch took manual control.
All right, well, you guys.
I didn't try.
I didn't leave the game, right?
Like my internet.
I was still in the game.
I don't think you did.
But usually, I mean, it takes a while
if you're going to drop.
I just assumed you're like basically gone.
But I think you're still here.
I guess it was just a weird like
server issue or something.
But we're here.
What do you want to do?
I really want to make a bow.
I need some hellstone.
You can help me mine hellstone
and then we can kill the wall of flesh.
OK.
I don't know if that sounds like a plan.
Hellstone is a huge pain in the ass to mine.
Hellstone, I'm remembering.
And I didn't get an obsidian potion.
You should buy an obsidian potion.
Buy an obsidian potion.
Yeah, which is what I should have done.
But I can't return because I don't have a fucking mirror.
Do we have any?
We might.
But I mean, the potion seller will sell them.
Oh, potion seller?
Give me your finest potion.
I wasn't going to do it.
Oh, my God.
Oh, man.
Yeah.
How many do you want?
Bring me one.
So bring like two or four.
I can afford three obsidian skin potion, right?
Yep.
Just make sure I got the right thing.
All right.
Do we have any of those wormhole potions?
I don't think I have any.
You can buy some from that guy as well.
Oh, OK.
I'll get some.
Let me buy a couple of those.
Wormhole.
There they are.
All right.
I am going to teleport to you in just a few seconds.
Just a few moments.
I'm bracing myself.
I'm standing over lava.
In a moment.
OK.
So get some.
We're safe.
I'm safe.
You were safe?
Yes.
OK.
Where the fuck are you?
Oh, here we go.
I have brought.
Excuse me.
Hey.
I have brought you.
I'm going to drink one of these, right?
OK.
And then you can do that.
Here you go.
Oh, fuck.
How do I throw it?
Right click.
OK.
So Hellstone is these rocks down here.
If you stand on them, even with obsidian potion,
you'll still take damage.
And it won't make any noise.
Your character won't scream.
You'll just slowly die.
And it's one of the worst things.
OK.
So the deal is, what are we trying to mine?
These ones?
I don't know.
I just don't know.
What are we mining?
I don't know.
No, but I mean, what's the goal?
What are we trying to get, if you said?
The Hellstone.
We're mining the Hellstone.
And it'll hurt you if you stand on the Hellstone.
So that shit's Hellstone.
You drown in lava?
No.
You drown in lava.
Should I try to get some of that shit over there?
Is that going to burn me?
You can stand in lava for seven seconds with the obsidian potion.
Just make sure you don't actually stand on the Hellstone,
because it will still hurt you.
OK.
How much this do we need?
The poor guy occasionally blacks out during conversation.
We're worried about you.
You have any hobbies?
You get out there?
You get enough exercise?
No, there's just a lot going on,
but my second time ever playing Terraria.
Come on.
You have like 6,000 hours in this game.
This is the second time I've ever played it.
Nothing to do with how much Terraria you play.
Yes, it is.
It's how much you listen to people when they talk to you.
It's a lot of information to process.
He was busy reminiscing about the 50s.
At least someone's honest.
Can you delete lava?
Is this like a Minecraft way to block it?
No.
I mean, if you just like build around it.
Also, yeah, Hellstone creates lava when you mine it.
It's a thing that's happening.
All right.
I think if this function is going to run out here in a second,
I have 55 seconds.
I have a minute.
Oh, what was I doing?
How much do I have?
17, 40 seconds.
Also, we need a platform that goes from left to right.
Very far distance down here,
but we can fight the wall with flesh.
I have like 20.
I'm not like going to risk going down there anymore.
What's that?
Some in there.
I'm not opening that up.
I'll just drown.
Work on operation left and right platform.
Okay.
Like towards where you are now?
Either direction works, honestly.
I don't think I don't have any like wood with me.
Can I not fly down here?
Or do I have to be running to fly?
You should be able to fly.
Old face?
What the fuck?
Yeah, I was holding it.
That was weird.
I have to hit it a third time.
Okay.
All right.
How safe is it over to you right now?
I can't really tell.
It's safe.
I've got platforms starting to go this way.
I'm afraid I need this lava and shit.
Oh, no.
Not the lava.
Okay.
I am coming over there.
I'm assuming you already got all these chests, right?
No, we can't open those.
We can't open these unless you have a shadow key.
I remembered getting a shadow key, but I like don't have a character.
We don't have one in our stash.
But you need a shadow key to open these.
I swear we got one, though.
I'm swearing it so hard.
I'm swearing it.
All right.
Obsidian door.
Oh, my God.
What have I done?
It's okay.
There was like lava.
There was lava like in the room.
Did you like pull a little lava in here?
The lava slimes.
You give me all the health you got?
Yes, I will.
Here you go.
I'm assuming we're going to fight something down here.
If I were betting on it.
Yeah.
So do not.
Last time I opened one of these chests, our game's froze.
So we cannot.
There's no way to open them.
We need like special keys or something, right?
We need a key.
Did you say you're going to give me a platform?
Yeah, come here.
We want it to be at one level, not like multiple levels.
So just like going in a straight line.
Okay.
Do you want me to go the other way?
Do you want me to just keep going with you this way?
Like, do you want me to like?
Let's just both go the same direction.
The same direction.
Did you get me to play?
You did, you did.
You would platform this.
Ay, ya, ya.
So, all right, you can just let it drop here.
Walk across.
There is a thing that will come at you and it will move towards you forever.
And you can't go behind it.
So you need a lot of like backing up space.
Okay.
There's like a flame wall or something that comes over here.
A flesh wall.
It's the wall of flesh.
It's the actual wall of flesh.
Yeah, it's not just nicknames.
That's its real name.
That's what it is.
That's not like what they call me when I go to the gym or anything.
I'm going to make sure I have my summons.
Guys, I'm frickin' ready.
Can you like do something?
I thought, well, I was waiting to see what...
I don't know, I've never done this before.
I don't know how far we need to go.
Very far.
I thought we were working together, you know?
Hey, I didn't do that.
That was you who did.
Okay, so just keep going.
Let's just keep on.
We should actually go the other direction.
Because this is where we come down.
Up, up, up, up, up, up, up, up, up, up.
That's way easier.
Yep.
Somebody gave $50 to you.
They said, hey, stirrer, thanks for the stream.
It's been hilarious.
This German guy's kind of a psycho.
LOL.
That was from Shining Path.
Nice.
Yeah, I mean, thank you, Shining Path.
For the $50, by the way.
That's a lot of fucking money.
Thank you.
To star.
Thank you to star.
Yeah, no problem.
I mean, like, I'm the highlight of the stream.
You know, I'm like, I'm like woke.
Oh, come on.
Really? You knocked it over.
Oh, my God.
Is this truly the legendary blade?
Like, I have such shit weapons this whole game.
I'm going to probably going to need something better.
This thing ain't good.
No, it's not.
Did they kill the wall of flesh yet?
That's a...
That's a question.
I'm almost out of...
I'm out of, um, platform.
I got no more.
Here.
Take.
Thanks.
Keep going.
I'll defend you.
I'll put that to good use.
I should make a funny trap so when he comes over here one time,
he'll fall in when we fight the boss.
So, um, this is activating hard mode, essentially, after this.
It's like the final thing you do before it becomes hard mode.
You don't even know what that means.
I don't.
I mean, I know it just means the game is hard or no.
Don't do it.
What are you talking about?
What is going on?
Uh, don't touch...
That ground will hurt you.
So just be sure you don't stand on it.
Yeah.
Uh, you keep doing what you're doing.
I'll be back.
I'm gonna try and make this bow before we fight it
because my weapons have been garbage this whole game.
And, you know, I'm just kind of sick of it.
I feel like I deserve happiness as much as anyone else.
How come I keep putting myself before other people?
Is this lava ever gonna go away?
I'm trying to, like, drop it.
Hey, look at that.
This feels so odd doing this.
I'm out of platforms again.
Oh, well...
I've gone all the way over here.
It's also better if you do it with, uh, just, like, bricks.
So if you have any random bricks, like dirt or something.
I mean, I have, like...
I have obsidian brick.
Yeah.
Just go for it.
Go wild.
Just do it with a brick?
Will it be, like, on the same plane?
I guess so.
I didn't know if it, like, caught the top of the, um...
The lip of the wood, like, the platforms.
What?
Can I just make obsidian platforms right now?
Oh, fuck.
Yeah, you can.
Just go.
Oh, just go, just go.
Just go!
I'm do- I'm going.
What are you waiting around for?
I'm not.
I just touched.
Ow.
Somebody just threw, like, a fucking boomerang at me.
Kill this guy!
Not you.
My- my minions!
They're just hanging out in here.
What are you guys doing?
They've- they've trapped themselves.
All right, I need to...
Oh, you idiots.
I'm on new minions now.
You guys blew it.
Uh, once we go into hard mode,
we can actually get you, like, an absurdly overpowered...
Minion.
Really?
Yeah.
It- it will, like, autopilot the rest of the game for you
for, like, a long time.
If you- you're into that sort of thing.
It tracks minions through walls,
like, very slightly off your screen.
It just kills everything.
Really?
It's nuts, yeah.
I feel like that's- would that be fun, though?
I used to use it.
It was kind of fun.
I mean, it's, like, fun to not be annoyed.
Oh, there's a new one.
What is it?
Um, what's the matter?
Nothing.
Nothing's the matter.
You're doing great, honey.
Thanks.
I need to fight a boss.
What's the matter, actually?
Any more demonite?
I'm almost out of, I think, ways to make platforms.
Frog.
Uh, star.
I'm- I'm almost out of, uh, platforms.
I'm fucking busy.
Okay.
That's what I got.
I do have- I have, uh, ash blocks?
Can I make, like...
Yeah, that works.
That works, too?
They're not gonna fall?
Mm-mm.
It's, like, silt and sand, that fall.
Oh, my God.
These guys are throwing the fucking boomerangs.
Where are my friends?
I thought I could trust you guys.
Why didn't they come here?
Oh, fucking idiot.
Oh, you guys are dunking into the water.
The very hot water.
To kill the worm.
I get it now.
Eater of worlds has awoken.
Star?
Yeah?
Uh, boss.
We already fought this boss.
I just need more resource.
From which side?
Just comes up and swallows me.
Like the big fish in Mario.
Is there- why is it-
Is there a reason why this says 8 a.m.?
8 a.m., no.
I am officially out of materials.
Besides, like, uh, yeah.
I have no more, like, materials to keep this going.
Okay.
Back to town.
It might be enough.
I think we're pretty- I'm pretty buff.
Normally you can kill wall of flesh if you just walk backwards and throw dynamite on the ground.
Which, dynamite falls through platforms, so we can't really do that in all the spots.
I'm just testing my work to make sure we can go right through it.
We just need to walk- run backwards, right?
Yeah.
Because I'm just making sure that there's plenty of space, there's no holes.
You know, I'm just checking my work.
It's pretty good.
She seems like there's- wait, there's a hole right there!
Aha!
This is why you check your work!
The, um, sometimes the lava slimes will create lava when you kill them,
and they'll, like, rip a hole in the platform.
This is why you check your work.
Okay.
I think, uh, I'm- so I'm just gonna come back to you.
That sounds- that sounds great.
Hello.
What do we got?
Hey.
I need those potions.
A lot of apples.
Fuck, I sold that.
Oh, come on.
Is it raining presents?
Okay, I don't need it.
It's raining presents from the sky.
Yeah, it's raining, um, slimes that are dying and turning into presents.
What?
That's awesome!
Sometimes during this, uh, slime king appearance.
Oh, does he?
That's cool.
Uh, can I have that bee bow?
Yes.
Yes, you can have the bee bow.
Don't you just love beemo?
I- I don't know.
What is that?
Uh, bee bow.
You need the bee arrows.
No.
Okay.
Even more people have shown up.
God damn it.
Oh, what a pain in the ass this is becoming.
I got- okay, go back to the corruption.
Christmas hats?
All right, um, potions.
I want to bring out my life regen speed ones.
You already have the materials.
Yeah?
Get some of that bacon out here.
I think I'm good, right?
I got life regen, summoning ability, defense, movement speed, oh, and mana regen.
Um, fuck, dude.
If you could figure out how to make a kiln, that would really help.
What?
What's with this, like, social network website spam?
Say that again, sorry, people are going insane.
I said if you found out how to make a kiln, that would really help.
A kiln?
Yeah, it's like, I think it uses lead and I don't know what else.
Kiln?
Anybody understand?
Looking for how to make a kiln.
Um, it is 18 iron bars and eight torches.
I don't know if we have enough iron.
Let's see.
I have seven, it's lead for us.
Oh, lead.
Uh, there's no lead in the box.
God damn it.
King Slime?
Is he?
Oh, King Slime.
Yeah.
He's in, oh no, he's inside.
He's inside, he's killing, people are dead.
He's killing people, people are gonna die.
All right, well, like, what kind of panicking asshole am I?
I'm just standing outside watching him kill everybody.
Uh, he's killing people, he's, he's, he's killing people inside.
I'm witnessing a murder.
I mean, he's murdering people.
I feel like I've got something I should do.
All right, he's dead.
Oh, you should be able to get that rideable slime that I had that you were jealous of,
but you're not jealous of anymore because you have a frog.
Yeah, let's see what I got.
I'm on the phone with you.
Slime just teleported inside and I'm out here right now, man, and it is wild.
They look just like people.
So what happens if he, okay, what happens if somebody in here dies?
Then they're dead and they respawn after like a day or two.
You get like a new guy with a new name that does the same job.
Oh, solidifier.
You know, you're all replaceable.
You think slime hook.
We need you.
You know how many people want this passion job you're done for.
I got a slime hook now.
Oh, I think that one is like a triple gooper.
Is it?
Yeah, like it attaches multiple times.
I think so.
It doesn't look like it's doing anything different.
While you're attached, trying to shoot it again.
Whoa, whoa, Spider-Man.
Oh, our merchant fucking died, didn't he?
I need like for the first time ever, I needed him.
Oh, no, nobody died.
Who died?
The merchant used to be right there.
What do you mean the merchant?
They got a guy with a beard.
Oh, he's over here now.
Ralph.
He died a while ago.
All right.
These guys are fucking annoying.
Not even him.
Who sells like good arrows?
Odd Michael over here.
Is that for real?
Odd Michael.
All right.
I got technique hidden blade.
Throwing class.
I'm irrelevant to you.
Okay, ninja hood.
Relevant, right?
Yeah.
A bottle of water.
Whatever this is.
Blue slime banner.
Shinobi slicer.
Just putting it in.
Ruby hook.
Going in.
Mining potion.
I don't want that.
Do you think I am auto-trashing?
No, it's just Jester.
Like shouldn't someone be selling Jester out?
Jester.
I feel like that's really familiar.
Or hellfire or something like just something better than wood.
Or do I craft with wood arrows?
All right.
Let me see what I can do here.
I got six presents.
Is anything actually good come out of these presents or never?
Is it just like a thing for fun for Christmas time?
I think it actually has seasonal events and something like there's Halloween items.
But no, they're not really good.
I know if during Halloween there's like costumes I can give you.
Yeah, I mean I got like the Santa Claus outfit.
All right.
Are we going to attempt the wall?
Let me make some arrows.
We're going for a wall attempt.
Possibly.
No, my computer.
That was almost an F.
It was.
Almost.
Oh, money.
This is just lava down here.
Did a lava slime die down here?
Is that what this is?
What are you up to?
Buying arrows.
No, it's honey.
Stand in it.
So what's the basic rundown?
Blood moon is rising.
Well, now we're stuck here.
Just ignore it.
You don't have to stay here.
Oh, fuck, dude.
Dude, the streamer looks really cute.
Hey.
Hey, cool.
Thank you.
Oh, he thought it was for him.
Well, it should be.
It's in my chat room.
I thought it was that each chat is for the other person.
That's why, like, you get the $50 for me.
Oh, right.
We both don't have face cams.
No.
No, we do not.
A lot of stuff out here.
I can't just leave without picking up this stuff.
Even if it's worthless.
Nice.
I need more hellstone.
God damn it.
Wait, no.
I shouldn't.
I need obsidian.
That's what I need to make hellstone.
I want to do that.
How much do I have to pay?
No.
Are we winning?
Get in there.
We've paid 700 times already.
You just missed it.
Free stuff on the roof.
He's in there crafting.
Crafting.
He's down there crafting.
All right.
Are we doing this now?
Are we actually doing this?
I need like two seconds to grab obsidian.
Can you give me like two seconds?
Or you can help me get obsidian.
Like contribute.
I don't know, dude.
I don't know, man.
I'm currently fighting blood.
It's not like I'm having fun getting obsidian down here.
That's kind of cool.
That's kind of good.
Wait a minute.
So that's five defense.
All right.
I'm just going to come down to you.
Okay.
I guess we can fight this.
Are we going to try this?
Be able to do it.
Go into the stash before you come down
because I don't have a return way yet.
Because I don't have a glass kiln.
So you would like me to remove what from the stash?
Voodoo doll.
We have a guide voodoo doll and a clothier voodoo doll.
Guide is what we need.
Just want one.
Just one.
Okay.
Anything else?
That is it.
Oh, obsidian potions.
And obsidian potions.
I'll make sure not to drink two of them.
I'm just going to buy them.
Do I have money?
I know I keep putting money in here.
So what do you think?
Four obsidian potions?
Just two.
We either die or we don't right now.
Okay.
Either die or we don't.
You got it.
Make sure you touch the summoning thing.
Yeah, I am.
And have a weapon that can attack at range.
That's kind of all I have.
Can you actually grab me the summon that skull
that you were using before that you didn't like?
The minotaur skull?
I can't- the weapon that shot the laser.
Weapon that shot the- oh no, I'm using that.
Oh, you are?
Yeah, I am using that.
I thought you said you didn't like it.
I don't like it, but it's doing more damage than what I have, so.
Okay.
Well, then yeah, you can come down here.
I'm coming.
Oh, it's a- why did I save her?
Shit.
I didn't know who it was and I clicked on her
and then I should have known.
So is there a certain thing we do to summon this thing?
Yes.
Cool.
Let me break it down like this.
Break it down.
Which button do I have to press?
Nine, one, one.
Let me show off what I'm like.
You are down here.
Come all the way to the right.
Yes.
Coming.
That sounds like you're stepping in snow.
I like this sound.
Ow.
Dude, this is actually so good.
Who the fuck is this?
No, that's yo-yo, never mind.
What'd you just drop?
Vanquisher medal?
Ignore it.
Oh, okay.
So, um.
I think this might need to be longer.
Longer?
Yeah.
I'm concerned.
All right.
Grats on 150 health bat kills.
Thank you.
You're still not at 400 health, are you?
No.
350.
I didn't bring any building materials or anything.
This is still not long enough?
How long does this gotta be?
It might be, but I want to be sure.
Because if you reach the end and the boss isn't dead yet,
then you're like in a panic jumping over lava pits and stuff.
And like trying to work your way through houses while it kills you.
Well, I'm just gonna start grabbing material then.
Either it's long enough or it isn't.
Yeah.
And I'd rather it be long enough, you know?
I'm probably just gonna dynamite it, actually.
We're normal and we should be fine.
All right, so...
Once we get to the other side of this building, we'll do it.
Okay.
This is relaxing.
I'm going for it.
I'm building the thing up.
No, we're good.
We're good.
Just come here.
Wait, we're done doing it?
We're good?
Yeah, yeah, just come here, come here.
All right.
Uh, hand to me gently the voodoo doll.
And the obsidian potion.
Okay, gently hand you the voodoo doll.
There it is.
Okay, gently.
Why, is it gonna break?
Gently.
Okay, and how do I split the potions in half to give you one?
I'm just gonna drink it.
Can you right-click it a second time over your inventory or something?
Or you hold right-click when you pick it?
Something like that.
It's just right-click.
Okay, um, I have a potion here for you.
Here it comes.
Okay.
Okay, Jerma, did you get it?
So, um, drinking it.
Uh, are we, are we, are we doing this now?
Should I press B and drink everything?
We're doing this.
Okay.
Summon up your, uh...
Why am I on fire?
Do things.
Why am I burning?
Let's just get the fuck out of me.
Okay.
You ready?
That was insane.
Okay, I'm, uh, I'm ready.
I've got my thing summoned.
Kill that boy.
What you have to do is throw the voodoo doll into the...
Oh.
Here it goes.
And then we just attack.
Thing.
Then we attack and walk backwards.
Okay, start walking backwards.
I'm dropping dynamite, so...
Keep going.
Oh, yeah.
I said it wasn't long enough.
I didn't think I was gonna actually...
What? He's dead?
Yeah.
The last second, I was like, you know what?
We went...
We did so much.
We needed, like, 35 feet.
Yeah, we were a little over-prepared.
Wow.
That's funny.
We needed, like, a couple of hallways.
We made...
Oh my fucking god, dude.
Are you serious?
I'm sorry!
That was, like, the last 40 minutes of this stream.
No, I did a lot of other things.
I built a lot of items.
We needed from here to here.
Holy shit, you were not confident at all.
That's so funny.
That's what you call overkill.
Yeah. Hey, well, look.
It's over.
We win.
You should have got a couple items
and everything that he drops is good.
Okay, wall of flesh.
Prepare to face the terrors that lurk
in the light and dark parts of this world.
Place in your inventory to gain increased item grab range.
Yeah, I trashed mine.
Unfortunately for them, they were twisted
by their inner demons until they were beyond saving.
The underworld.
Wild cleric emblem.
12% increased radiant damage.
Healing spells will heal an additional one life.
That's a Beerus healer, okay.
Shadow diamond.
Arcane summoner emblem.
Now that's some good shit.
15% increased summon damage in plus 20 mana.
What do I replace?
I cloud.
I don't even need cloud in a bottle anymore, do I?
Because I can fly.
It's tech right.
I don't need cloud anymore.
You probably don't need it now.
No, I'm just going to put that on.
I'm going to update it.
Oh, fuck, fuck.
This is the tax collector.
That's awesome.
Well, I don't have purification powder.
Replace the bees.
Oh, I like the defense on the bees still.
It still looks seems pretty good.
You can start showing the goblin your accessories
so you can try and roll like plus four defense on every accessory you have.
Oh, that's cool.
So if there's one that like, oh, this one doesn't have the defense,
you can just try and roll it depending on what it costs.
Cool.
Is there a certain stat that a caster or summoner should be looking for?
Like plus one to more monsters or something?
Defense is like the best one.
Just defense.
Look for defense every time.
All right, so the goblin is back at the town, right?
Yep.
Well, that's cool.
Um, so now there's a lot of things going on.
I'm staying down here for like one second
to get a couple of essences for a super OP weapon.
And this game is really fun.
I'm like, I like, don't know what I'm doing still,
like kind of learning a little.
But like, this is, this is like really cool.
There's like so many things.
There are a lot of things.
All right, let me, uh, let's talk about the goblin you said, right?
So you're talking about reforge?
Yeah.
Is this going to do it automatically or do I get to look at it?
Uh, it's a random roll.
Oh.
And it's, it's going to roll like the thing that's green, right?
Yeah.
Does it, what does it cost?
It'll tell you when you put the item in.
Depends on item.
Three gold, that's it?
Yeah, the melee speed.
I'm not, that, that, that sucks on here.
So I'm looking for anything else really.
Did it work?
Am I missing something?
I don't have enough gold.
Right.
Okay.
Come here, come here, come here.
Hmm.
3% movement speed.
A schmelve.
Why is this stacking burn?
Okay.
That's not bad.
This one already has four defense.
I feel like the 4% movement speed on this is, does, is dumb.
Yeah.
It's, it's not enough.
I mean, it's nice because movement speed is like not dying in Toraria, but
eh, you're really going to have to stack it.
All right.
I'm going to, that, that fleeting cloud in the bottle is just trash.
Now I can just sell it, right?
Um, don't sell it.
Don't sell it.
Okay.
We need it to keep like, that's why I'm so afraid to sell anything.
Cause I feel like it might be needed later.
I explained this a long time ago.
And that's why I'm saying it.
Listen.
When you look at an item, if on the item it says material, then you might need it.
Right.
If it doesn't say material and you don't need it, you'll never need it.
Everything says material on it.
There's like one thing that doesn't.
Angry, okay.
Angry ball and chain.
Can I just sell that?
Uh, doesn't say material.
Hold on a minute.
No, this thing increases defense by eight.
It slows you, I think.
That's pretty good.
I can fly.
Oh, yeah.
I think we needed this whole walkway.
Huh?
Yeah.
This walkway could be longer is all I'm saying.
I need to get like two more essences of chaos.
I'm going to make like, I'm going to be making a mistake here.
Someone's going to scream at me because they're going to see
that I'm like selling something I'm not supposed to be.
Honestly, I'm not afraid.
Mandible bow.
Not after that last bite.
It's not, none of these are materials though.
Like harpoon.
Oh, the guide is still dead.
Mandible bow.
Like this stuff sucks.
Does it just sell?
Yeah.
Just sell it.
What about this ancient shiv?
Not material.
Mandible claws.
Like these things are dumb, right?
Yeah.
Yeah, you're getting it.
You're getting it.
I'm not understanding.
Severed hands.
Get rid of them.
Auto trash those severed hands.
I told you.
It's going to be slicer.
Get rid of them.
Who needs them?
Nobody.
All right.
Let's see how that gets me.
Demonic carnage.
What is this doing in here?
63 melee damage.
Fast speed 15.
What the fuck is this in here?
Oh, I was using that.
I'm not using it anymore.
What?
It's pretty okay, but you need to build really high defense
and like melee stats.
Otherwise, you're going to take so much damage trying to use that weapon.
The harpoon, do anything cool, it's a material.
I don't think so.
You can check with the guide, but I don't think it does.
It's not like it sells for 26 silver.
Wait, what's going on?
Why is everybody losing their mind?
Oh, this is one of those stupid melee damage weapons that aren't melee.
Now let me try to reroll this again.
Why does the price come down every time I do it?
It was three gold last time, now it's 275.
That's not good.
Two percent, I went down.
Two percent melee speed instead of four.
I only have three gold.
Yeah, there's a, wait, I have more than that.
I got way more gold than that.
This weapon's really good.
Okay, get up here, turtle.
Oh yeah, we need to go get you the crazy summon.
Pig's not going to get hit by the lava?
Don't kill the pig.
All right, I just looked over at Chad and I almost died.
This pig was easy.
That's because the air is blowing fast.
The air is fast, dude.
The wind is going nuts right now.
One more.
I feel like I'm in need of a new staff.
There is an insanely good one that we can get you pretty soon.
I do, I like this one, but I need to do more damage.
So one of the first things you do within hard mode is you have to fight
basically the same bosses you fought before but harder that are mechanical bosses.
So like the worm we fought is like the mechanical worm.
And I think it's them that drop hollowed bars and the hollowed staff is actually
really, really, really, really, really good.
Really?
Really.
The wind is too strong.
I can't get back in that house.
Use your hook.
Oh, right.
Also, if you hook a closed door and open it, you go whoosh.
Oh, come on.
All right, all right.
Got it.
Plus three defense and plus 0.75% damage reduction.
Nice.
Oh yeah, that's also the only thing you can get is damage reduction.
So the extra movement speed on the quick lightning boots.
Why even have that?
Why not just roll something else?
They're already quick.
They're at 14 gold, never mind.
There's a good reason.
That's a pretty good reason.
All right, I'm going to put this other stuff in here.
I've got like wild cleric emblem, the underworld.
I'll keep the wall of flesh in the inventory, right?
If you want.
If you care about that kind of bonus.
I mean, it's kind of a good thing.
Shadow diamonds.
I'm just telling you what I picked up because I want to be able.
Oh, well, she told me about the shadow diamonds.
No, no.
No, never mind.
Buy a piggy bank.
You can put those in the storage, though.
Does it do you get like a return on investment?
Do you get like a percentage increase?
Piggy bank is kind of annoying to use, but it's really good.
You put items inside of it and you can place it on the ground.
So it's like a second storage.
Oh, oh, that's all right.
So like if at any point you're like, oh, shit, my inventory is full.
You place that you can put shit in the piggy bank.
And yeah, I don't like dealing with it myself.
But it's worth it.
Well, maybe eventually.
OK, I am ready.
I'm just trying to farm minions so I can get a thing.
If you go to the snow biome and you just start killing shit,
there's this one like flying around enemy
that you're going to need to kill a couple of.
And that's what drops the summon and is the super good summon.
So you're telling me snow biome, I don't have to go up.
Press M and I look for snow.
Yeah, the snow up in the cloud or is that a cloud?
That's a cloud.
OK, I do see the snow.
The snow is at the top of the corruption to the right.
Yeah, I see.
So it's going to be a little annoying because it combines two enemies types.
But yeah, also, now that it's in hard mode, there's like the regular enemies will hurt you.
So be careful.
All right, I will go kill the things down there.
Also, collect snow blocks because then you can make the upgrade to your boots
and leather if you find any.
Aye, aye.
Aye, aye, aye.
I just tried to double tap D to run fast.
DD.
Like, didn't.
But why though?
Oh, stop getting so close.
Hello?
Hey, hello, right?
Oh, yeah.
Yeah, right.
You think you're funny.
Hello?
Let me drop in.
That guy took a lot of hits.
You're still not at 400 health, are you?
No.
That's what I like about you.
Hey, thanks.
You're like not afraid.
I've made it to the snow.
Is this snow?
This is like ice, right?
This is ice.
Carnivore tail.
Oh, what's that?
Can't look at it.
I just that hurts a lot.
You weren't kidding when you said that this there, but much, much harder.
No.
Also, if you see something spawn in the eye and the air after you kill something,
that's like a crown and it like doesn't move.
Like it's stuck in the air and doesn't drop to the floor.
Pick those up.
Essences like essence of sunlight, essence of ice.
Maybe I don't remember what it's called.
Do I have it?
I don't even like that.
Well, that's not good.
Bad.
I don't have any fucking.
Hey, I found some torches.
Good thing.
Like idiot me was able to like save this run.
See me in the past knew about me in the future.
In fact, let's just go ahead and like take them all.
I am about to roll.
There's a lot of fucking people over there.
These things are not doing very much damage at all.
What things?
My summons.
Yeah, they're a little outdated at this point.
So you're saying snow area.
Snow ice block, right?
Not snow block.
I think it's snow block.
Is it snow?
Because I can get snow right now.
Yeah, it's no block.
How many do we need?
I mean, describe once you need 20 to make the ice skates,
which is really what you're in it for, you know?
Yeah, that's true.
I feel really bad.
I spent this much time like crafting this fucking bow.
It sucks.
I immediately got this throwing weapon that I think is better.
It's hard to tell.
And then what was the enemy that I was looking for down here?
I don't know how to describe it.
Usually it's above ground.
I'm not entirely sure if it shows up above the ground.
But you know, in the corruption, the flying eyes with the tusks?
Yeah, it's like that, but it's semi-transparent and icy.
Okay.
See, I just saw it.
I just died.
Okay, you're going to need to kill it.
Like it's not 100% drop chance.
And the item I'm looking for is the thing to summon them.
Rotten chunk?
Don't care.
Jerm is not going to read my message.
Laughing my ass off.
Got you.
Got him.
He's gonna get you.
To see you in the funny papers.
That's your go-to, isn't it?
Is it?
I think I have like 300 snow blocks.
Okay.
Yeah, you're good.
I kind of just kept going.
All right, let's do this.
Oh, nice.
These are good.
All right, looking for the rotten chunk carnivore tail.
Not down here.
He said they usually hang out above ground.
Oh, I'm pretty sure.
Come on, right here.
And it didn't look like you dropped it.
And I'm just a rotten chunk.
I have no idea what the chance is, but I've never like intentionally farmed them.
But every time I've gotten that, I've been a very happy boy.
Got him.
I'm gonna fucking die.
What happened?
It's your fault, dude.
Hello?
Dude.
It's all your fault, dude.
Come on, dude.
I can put some of this shit away, finally.
Dude.
Is it one of those things where I'll know when I see it?
Is it shiny or something?
I don't remember.
Like, it might be a staff.
I mean, you'll check it if you see a random thing drop.
I didn't say hello to the soundboard.
I will if it happens again.
Hello?
Hey.
That wasn't even me.
That's a whole new person.
You're not going to say hello?
Hello?
Goodbye.
Now, how many hellos do you have?
Eight or nine.
No.
And one no.
I think I got it.
Is it a glacial crystal?
I don't know.
It's a quest item.
Wait, no.
I got it.
I got the quest item.
I see shard.
My armor gives three defense.
It's a staff.
God damn it, dude.
I hope I'm killing the right things.
I believe I am.
I see shard.
No.
What does it all do?
What's this?
Glacial crystal.
You can't pick up more than one of these.
The monster spawns in the underground ice biome.
This is not it here, what I'm attacking up.
Oh, I know they spawn there, but underground ice biome might be better.
Which is probably underneath where you are.
So just go underneath.
Yeah, it is.
There should be some down there.
All right.
Well, hold on a minute here.
Be careful.
Because I'm scared of this.
Where's my rope?
I don't know.
I need the guide.
I hate when the guide dies and then you get a whole new item.
What does this do?
And the guide's still dead because you went to hard mode
and you're like, come on, guide.
You know what I'm saying?
Yeah.
What?
Yeah, whatever.
Found him.
No, that's not an ice corrupter.
Hey, remember these ebb and stone blocks?
I have them now.
That's cool.
Remember like two hours ago when you were looking for these?
Got them now.
And I had to go get something real quick.
It's called an ice clasper.
Okay.
It is.
He's correct.
This is an actual statement just made.
My fingers feel like wet cat food.
What does it mean when you feel like wet cat food?
Are you all right?
No.
No, I'm not all right.
Okay.
Icy shard.
We're just going down.
I wish I brought bombs.
Can I get a better pickaxe?
I feel like it's been ages since I've got a new one.
How do I stop biting my fingernails?
Which one are you using?
Dip your fingers in vinegar.
Come on.
None of this water fucking count.
Uh, uh.
The purple ice block.
Cool.
Purple ice school.
I feel like I know what this tastes like.
I want to like crunch into this purple ice.
It's going to have that like a good fruit juicy grape kind of taste.
Okay, bro.
Come on, bro.
Ice block.
Maybe I should get some of this too.
All right.
Well, there's frost worm.
I didn't drop anything.
Did I upgrade my boots?
Yes, I did.
I'm trying to figure out like the best.
Should I just keep going down into the ice?
Just keep going?
I mean, this is clearly like we're getting down to like ice now.
Oh, I'm muted.
There's a lot of mobs that you kill in hard mode that drop really good things.
So you're like not wasting time.
Yeah.
I mean, I've picked up at least a handful of really cool looking things.
Have you gotten any essences?
I have gotten like a, I've gotten a dragon essence.
No, I'm sorry.
Dragon scale.
Okay.
Yeah, that's useful for something.
But if you find like sunlight essence, I think elum essence might be the cold one.
I need those.
Okay.
Oh, also very important for the progression of Terraria.
If you'd understand what's going on right now.
Sure.
When you get into hard mode, the first thing you should do, one of the first things,
it's actually it's going to be annoying.
You get the poon hammer.
It's literally called poon hammer from the wall of flesh.
It's guaranteed drop and the demon alters that are in the corruption zone.
You smash them with the poon hammer and then it adds new resources to the world
because he pooned them.
Of course.
Okay.
I just want to make sure we're on the same page with like the poon hammer.
Yeah.
I don't know who that was.
That could have been anybody.
Yep.
Snow.
Come on, anymore snow.
Maybe like find a cave or something.
Also, if you see lead, surprisingly, we still need it.
Actually, there's usually a planet that has it.
If you find a gravity potion.
Actually, I can buy one.
I'm on operation lead.
I'm going to take a brief detour from all the important freaking work I'm doing.
Get some lead.
What's the sunbat?
Sin bed sunbat.
Why is the sunbat down here?
Good question.
Is that like, is he got, is he worth something?
That is really good.
Oh, angry dog.
What?
Fight the angry dog.
Did he drop anything?
Cursed flame.
Well, there's a spot to go down here.
Still in the ice biome.
That's good.
What are they still shooting at?
All right, you guys can stop now.
Oh, wait, the sunbat.
But he could sneak up on me.
That's not going to be good here.
What's this?
Essence of something.
There's a big cave down here.
This should be good.
Pick it up.
I didn't pick it up.
I thought I, no, I thought I did pick it up.
This, there was two then.
Essence of sunlight.
And did I, I didn't pick it up that first time when it popped up on the screen.
Thank God.
You guys just said that because I, I thought I had, I thought it went in me.
All right, let's keep going.
Amethyst.
I'm running out of torches though.
Not good.
No, when it popped up on the screen, I, I saw, I mean, I would,
I said the name of the thing.
I said essence of, and then I kept going.
I thought I just picked it up.
Okay.
I want people to make it fun of me.
That's fine.
It's down here.
Anything.
The generation potion.
Sick.
Give me that staff.
I want it.
Let me do this.
Let me have my fun.
I have, how many ice blocks do I have?
Absolute shit load.
All right.
I'm going to have to like come back.
Kind of running out of materials and space.
Go up here.
Essence.
Ice slimer.
Where am I?
Oh, there it is.
Ice clasper.
Did I get it?
Essence of Ilium.
Oh yeah, that's it.
Did I pick it up?
Essence of Ilium.
That's what I'm looking for.
Yep.
That's one of the things.
Somebody said it's not what I'm actually looking for though.
It's, it's, it's a thing that you're looking for.
Okay.
It's part of the puzzle.
And there's another one.
So those things also drop a staff.
And that's what I really want, right?
I'm just going to hang out here then if they just, if they spawn in here.
Dude, you can like go get a drink and just let your summons kill them.
They come near you.
And it's just AFK farm this game.
We don't, we don't give a shit about the heart crystals anymore, right?
We do for some reason.
We do.
Okay.
Got Jacob's here.
I don't want to drown.
That would be bad.
That started to be because my name is Jacob.
That's why I didn't die as an ancient ice chunk.
Ah, what's that?
Uh, crafting material for something.
This ice shouldn't break.
Um, summons an ice clasper to fight for you.
Are you kidding me?
This is it.
There it is.
I got it.
I'm excited now.
All right.
So I have like a cool, powerful thing now.
Oh, you just got it.
I just got it.
Wow.
You did it.
Well, yeah, now you, uh, now you win.
I did.
Now I win.
You know, I've been getting some upgrades.
I got a lot of them.
Branding material.
Making some power plays, making, making some power moves.
You know what I'm saying?
Something else over here.
What's this?
Topaz crawler?
Use it.
Not yet.
I don't want to use it yet.
All right.
I think that's, uh, I'm good, right?
I'll just get off.
Dude, you are so good.
So are you telling me I can have like seven of those?
Six of those?
I have however many you can have.
Oh, wow.
I don't, I'm not keeping track of your damage.
Yeah, they're, they're insane.
It will stay good for a long time just because how actively they seek out targets.
10, but from 10 damage to 50.
That's a huge difference because really all my damage has been coming from the,
the sphere stuff thing that's been doing all the damage.
Nice.
Um, stay there for one second.
Stay here.
I'm going to teleport to you.
Actually, there's something you can help me with.
I have no torches, so hopefully you bring light.
Uh, I have 2000 torches.
Would you like some?
Yeah, it'd probably be nice.
There's a chilled turtle down here.
Uh, here.
I'm dropping them.
You ready?
Um, hold on.
There's like 500 torches right there.
I think they fit perfectly in this hole.
They did.
I don't think I can even pick them up.
I'm out of space.
Glow stick.
Um, fuck.
What do I have?
What dumb thing do I have?
I have some lead ore.
Not very many.
This lens.
Do I have dirt?
Oh, I do have dirt.
You're right.
Do I have dirt?
Snow block.
No.
All right.
I got to get out of here.
Use the heart.
I can't.
You need to come up here to me.
You need to come up to the surface.
There's a boss.
That will probably kick our ass.
Be gone, evil.
Uh, you just killed it.
Uh, no.
It's still going to be on the surface.
You need to come up.
I'm coming up now.
Uh, I need to put my, uh, anything on.
There's going to be ghosts.
Uh, don't die, dude.
I don't even know what's going on down here.
I'm trying to get out.
Fuck.
Dude, don't, don't get ghosted.
I'm trying just to get the fuck out of the hole.
All right.
I'm on the surface.
Uh, is there an ice golem?
Is there a blizzard?
Like, is it storming up?
Uh, yes.
It's very blizzardy out here.
Okay.
Walk left and right and try and see if you can find the ice golem.
Maybe it was underground.
So, because I went up the one way.
I'm fucking confused.
Why?
Why is this not?
Is this a summon?
I got my shit.
All right.
He's here.
Help bar showed up again.
Okay.
I'm coming up.
He's somewhere.
I don't know where exactly.
Be careful because he's going to hurt.
I don't know if we're ready for him.
Oh, he's on me.
On me.
He's down this hole.
Your things are attacking him.
Good.
He's almost dead because the summons are nuts.
Melt him.
And also he's in a hole.
Wait, does it corrupt her?
Okay.
Keep going up.
Keep climbing out of the hole.
Climb out of the hole.
Go to the surface.
Uh, oh, oh, go, go, go, go.
Where the hell is this thing?
Um, it was in the hole.
Oh, it's on me.
I mean, this thing jumping around.
It's going to, they hurt a lot, dude.
Well, they drop really good items.
Uh, it should be dead.
This is like pure fucking.
Mimics drop.
Wait, where did they die?
What the fuck?
The dart rifle.
Why is there another one?
Let's kill.
They, they just spawn in blizzards.
He's over here underneath this house.
Holy shit.
They are destroying him.
Yeah.
Those summons are ridiculous.
What?
Oh my God.
I can't pick up anything.
I have no room.
There's another one.
There's another mimic.
They just kind of wiggle towards you.
And then they go up in the air and try and slam on top.
So if you see it go up, just move a little bit to the left.
You should be fine.
I'm stuck.
I'm stuck next to the house.
Open the door.
Dig out the right.
It's like a horror movie.
Okay.
I made it.
I can't tell what's happening.
I don't even know where we are.
He's on you.
Oh, it hurts.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
No, no.
Hide.
I'm hiding.
Keep away from me.
I'm dead.
No, it's all right.
Kill it.
Are you gonna buy a wormhole?
All right.
I think I have one already.
Is there another one spawning?
I killed him.
Dude, I got to like just I got a ton of shit.
I just gotta deposit and come back.
All right.
Is it done or is there more?
It's, it's, it's dead.
Okay.
I still need to destroy some altars with the poon hammer.
Alright, I...
And would appreciate all of your summons nearby.
Let me make this staff.
Right?
Okay.
Wait, this what?
What are you making?
Can I make something?
Can you?
Yeah, I thought I got two different materials for something.
I don't know what you got.
Wasn't I looking for the essence?
That can't make anything yet.
No, okay.
Where's the dude?
They just make a lot of things.
And you need multiple.
Where's the...
The guide might be dead still.
I think he's dead.
Oh no, he came back. He's all the way on the left.
He's the second on the left.
Oh, I got something for you.
I don't know what this is.
Cosmic Immaterializer.
Oh, this is a different summon.
Sun Gods, this is like...
This takes...
There's nothing I can do with that right now.
What?
Summons a Cosmic Energy Spiral to fight for you.
Does 4,439 damage.
Wait, what?
The thing that I can turn this staff into does 40, like 500 damage.
Oh, yeah, that would take a long time to do that, though.
What about the essence?
Let me see what that...
What can I do with that?
Did you pick up all the stuff that was there?
I'm still getting it.
Oh, dude, this sword is awesome.
I'm so hyped.
Starlight Wings?
Dude, everyone, get hype and chat.
Reduces damage.
Wings of the Nightingale.
Horizontal Speed.
7.5.
Acceleration Multiplier.
Average Vertical Speed.
These are stats I have not seen before.
Blood Orange?
Permanently increases maximum life by 25.
Prismaline?
It's like a knife core of Ilium.
Cryo Key.
Summons Cryogen.
Dimensional Soul Artifact.
Boosts all damage by 25%, but at what cost?
Ooh, this is what we get. Cool.
Arc of the Ancients.
That's the super sword that I can pretty much make.
Yeah, you kind of can, can't you?
Yeah.
It's ridiculous.
It does melee damage,
but it makes stars shoot from the sky
and missiles shoot from your weapon
and just clutters the screen with nonsense.
But it's melee.
What about the Archilis stuff?
How do you do that?
I mean, the Archilis sword,
the thing that you would like,
oh, hold on to that.
Isn't that one of the components?
What are you talking about?
Is that one of the components for this?
Yeah, yeah.
To make Arch of the Ancients.
Excalibur is really easy to get you.
And then we have the other sword.
We would just need the essences, which we have.
We have three Elum and three Chaos already.
This one.
Slow moving ball of flash freezing magma.
Nano round.
The butcher.
All right.
Well, let me just deposit this shit
because I'm not going to be,
you're going to be using that, not me.
Silver ore.
Even stone block.
This is still working really well.
I don't think I'm going to have this on the bar anymore.
I don't, yeah, I don't think I'm going to be,
let me see what that can turn into though.
What can I turn this into?
Can I turn it into anything?
No.
I think it's time to sell this.
Yeah.
How long were you out there looking for the ice clasp?
Like in that mess of bullshit we fought, I got one.
Not that long.
This thing's cool, but it's time to sell it.
It's going away.
Say goodbye.
This is just too good.
All right.
Now those, I can make the boots, right?
Ice skates.
What does it take?
You need leather.
I think there's some in there.
There's seven leathers.
Show the crafting guy the leather
and the boots will be on there.
And then see what else you need.
I don't think there's enough leather
and I don't even know what drops that.
You just kind of get it.
Okay.
I'm looking for the ice skates.
Ice skates require 20 ice blocks,
five leather and five, any iron bar.
Any iron bar.
We don't have iron bars, do we?
Lead is the same thing.
It is.
Do we have any lead bars?
A few.
We need five.
What's the best place to find any iron bar?
Iron or lead?
What's the best place to find it?
Underground.
Not too deep.
Just somewhere.
There's honestly going to be a lot of it.
We just kind of ignored it.
Desert fossil?
We need desert fossil for anything?
Hold on.
First of all.
Okay.
Unholy arrow.
I'm just looking for iron.
Oh, you gave me 5,000 torches
and I put them all in the trash.
And by trash I mean the deposit.
What the hell is making that noise?
Is that lead right here?
Hardened sandstone.
There we go.
Lead.
Tin.
This tin doesn't count as iron, right?
I don't think so.
Lead right here?
I think I have enough.
Lead.
How much lead ore makes a bar too?
Something like that.
Three.
Okay.
I should have enough after this.
Some more right here.
Hey, hey Jemba.
Hey, what's up?
I got a blazing heart for you.
Ooh.
That's not, that's not like emotional.
That's like I actually have it.
Do you now?
Well, I appreciate it.
Three, six, nine, 12, 15.
I need five.
It's just lead ore in the box, right?
Like three or four.
I need five, right?
I think I just put some in actually.
Yeah.
Here is the blazing heart.
Woohoo.
You can also craft blazing hearts to get your health to 400,
but you need hellstone.
So if you like spend the time to do it.
All right.
I'm going to make those boots.
Lead bar.
I'm going to go try and kill a harpy.
I think.
Do you say that there was lead ore in here?
I think so.
Yes, there is.
Oh wait, I was crafting the freaking dummy thing.
Okay.
So easy to forget what you're doing in Terraria.
Yeah, it is.
Especially at a point in a game like this where you're instantly thrown this many new items.
Yeah, it's really overwhelming, but it's a lot of fun.
All right.
So I have everything I need.
Ice skates.
Pass them?
Oh, I have to do it over here.
Where's the loom?
Oh, it has to be in the inventory.
Yeah.
What am I missing in my inventory?
Ice, lead, leather, and then like what am I missing?
What the fuck am I missing?
What are you trying to do?
You might be at the wrong crafting station.
Ice skates?
Ice skates.
You have to stand near this thing over here.
The ice creator.
Oh, there's an ice creator.
Okay.
Yeah.
I got annoyed at the same thing.
All right.
So I got the ice skates and now I'm going to make the super duper super boots.
Okay, chat.
Like what the fuck was I doing with the purified shards?
Do I have to go to a different table for this one too?
Is there another table?
I have to take the boots off.
Okay.
Am I losing my mind right now?
Or the tinker table?
Which one of these is the tinker table?
Tinker table on the left.
Far right.
On the far right.
Okay, there it is.
Oh, I keep muting.
Here, try this accessory.
I don't know if you're going to actually use it.
But here.
I'm just going to look at the louse flight super fast running extra mobility on ice.
Seven percent degrees movement speed.
So this is just, we just keep going.
So it's super fast.
Faster than incredibly fast.
One can only assume.
I mean, they'll sound pretty, pretty good.
Okay.
Now what can I do with this?
I can do more than this?
No, no.
It's just that it's not.
It's not.
You can't.
This is the end.
Oh my God.
Angel treads.
Extreme speed.
Water and lava walking and temporary immunity to lava.
Enhanced ability to walk on water, ice, fire blocks and lava allows flight as the
wearer can run incredibly fast.
These seem like better, right?
That's a lot of bars.
But whatever.
I mean, let's how fast is fast?
Super fast.
Let's just run.
I mean, that's that's pretty fast.
Can I fly for longer too?
Not really.
Hey, you want to want to assist me?
Yeah, I just was looking at the thing I just made.
Yeah.
Okay.
You gave me.
Did you check the accessory I gave you?
Fear monger.
5% reduced damage taken.
Enemies are less likely to target you.
Um, it's not that good.
But no, what can it turn into?
You combine it with some healer item I don't have to get.
And then it like reduces damage to the allies around you.
Oh, that's cool.
5% reduced damage taken versus 4 defense and 1% damage reduction.
What turns out to be more damage mitigation?
I'm saying 5% less damage or 1% less damage and 4 defense.
Anybody know?
5%.
I had to guess.
Well, we'll get it on there then.
No more bees.
What can I do with bees?
Honey balloon.
That's cool.
All right.
Assist.
Plague hive.
I mean, there's a lot of stuff.
This is what I was saying.
This is like going to the bakery and the chocolate factory at the same time.
And they just say, hey, by the way, Jeremy, everything is free today.
But you can only have 10 things.
You can have anything you want, but you can only pick 10.
It's more like you can have whatever you want.
You can have whatever you want, but you need to learn and understand what all the ingredients are first.
No.
As long as you can prove to us that you know the recipe, we'll give it to you for free.
I mean, that looks really good, but how do they possibly get all the pastry in there?
How do you get the chocolate sprinkles on there to stick?
Sorry, motherfucker.
I know how to make the meringue.
It's eggs and lemon.
Okay.
What else?
A wormhole to me.
We're about to get fucking crazy.
What?
Hold on.
I don't have anything.
Do I have?
Let me deposit my...
Hold on.
You need me now.
Wait.
Hold on.
Seriously.
Do you want to fight a boss or no?
I do, but there are too many fucking ingredients on the table.
I mean, you're going to have more after this boss.
Oh my god.
Okay.
I guess I'm coming to you.
Quick, before this blizzard ends.
I don't even know where the fuck you are.
Wormhole potion.
I'm on the map right now and I don't even see you.
To the right.
Wormhole potion.
I'm doing a...
I'm here.
You have all your stuff summoned?
I've got all my stuff.
Is this going to be hard?
I don't know.
Dude, I don't know.
Honestly, it's hard to gauge
because I fought a lot of these things a little bit late
the last time I played.
So I was already too strong.
But also you have seven ice claspers
or whatever you have.
Also, I have one.
So it's just...
It's just...
It's murder, dude.
We're going to do another one.
I might have done two.
I don't know if the second one's full.
Oh no.
I tried the strategy and it didn't work
because I'm stupid.
I'm fucking dying like a dumbass.
Drops a lot of health.
Go pick it up.
Go pick them up.
I'm going to be real with you.
I just can't even tell if there's anything on the screen.
Everything is so...
It's so dark.
The blizzard is rough.
You're dying, man.
Do you have healing potions?
Yeah, I'm good.
The thing that mine dropped was pretty shitty.
I don't know what you got.
Ice golem.
Another ice golem.
Also, actually, for a summon boy,
if you go up in the sky,
you can fight the wind elemental
and then you get an accessory item
that just like...
Really?
Where you constantly have a wind elemental
that follows you.
What did he drop?
Anything good?
I think he dropped a lot of it down the hole
and not really.
Blizzard.
We're still kind of hanging out
waiting for another one to spawn.
He dropped an essence.
He dropped a frost...
Barner?
Frost Barney?
Frost Barrier.
Ooh, nice.
Lucky shackle.
Oh, God.
I don't even know what my summons are.
They're just running around aimlessly.
I'm trying to summon another boss
and it's not happening.
Amarok?
Let me go.
Here he is.
This music is so loud.
Is it just me?
It's just like louder music than every other boss.
My music's turned down.
What's that?
Dangerous glacier.
It's not very good.
Yeah, I don't know what this boss's drop pool is,
but I'm not impressed.
I've got to stand still.
I've got to read you.
I want to make sure they're all still alive.
How many fucking torches did you put on this house?
What?
What are you talking about?
I don't know.
Nothing.
Where?
Nowhere.
Show me.
The house over to the right.
The random generated house.
I don't know.
There's a torch on every tile in front of it.
Like, no space between them.
I don't know.
Sometimes I get scared, man.
Pirates are approaching from the west.
Fuck.
Go back to the base.
Tell me when you're there, because I need to wormhole on you.
I'm here.
I'm at the base.
Okay, they'll be here soon.
They're kind of annoying.
There's no doors.
They're just like every other invasion.
Pirate captains kind of hurt.
They drop a absolute shit ton of gold.
Really?
So we want to be here to kill them.
It is.
I'm just going to have to deposit it.
I will have to look at it later.
I'm going to have to look at it later.
It's all in there.
I don't know.
I'll check it out later.
The pirates have arrived.
Honestly, you're probably going to auto kill a lot of them.
Especially if they walk this way, because I have the lava ground,
and they don't give a shit about lava.
Yeah, they really don't.
What about the other side?
If you stay on this side, then they probably won't spawn on the other side.
They're coming in here.
This door is open.
If we shut the door, they shouldn't be able to get in that door.
Nothing despawns in Terraria, right?
It just stays there.
It's like money.
Or should we go collect it from time to time?
I actually don't know.
I think it's a lot different between multiplayer and single player.
Well, I got some.
There are more than 4,000 items on the ground.
It starts to despawn.
Well, now there's 3,415.
That's a lot of stuff.
There's like a...
Oh my God, there's so much stuff.
You can drop like golden toilets and stuff as well.
You're going to want to sell that.
Oh, man.
We might have to destroy a pirate ship.
I'm surprised we haven't seen it yet.
That would be the pirate...
Whoa!
What?
It just crashed into the side.
Here we come!
Somebody's just like...
Somebody didn't know how to break.
Full speed ahead.
There it is.
Okay.
Oh, look at all that stuff.
Oh, no, it's not the pirate ship.
Boom!
Oh, where'd it go?
The flying Dutchman.
Here she comes.
Come on, fire.
Why isn't there fire?
Get in there.
Be brave, you pile of shit.
Be brave, fuckers.
Be brave, all horses, asses.
You bitches.
We done died today.
That game.
What a game.
We should probably make sure we have everything.
I did get a tuba.
You're right.
What does a tuba do in this game?
That's one gold 57...
Holy shit.
There's a whole bard class that attacks with music and buffs allies around them.
Well, that was insane.
That's a lot of stuff.
Did we get everything?
I think so.
I'm just checking.
I don't want to leave one piece of silver on the ground.
How come a golden toilet is two gold and a golden piano is 60 copper?
Let's see what we got.
Golden bathtub.
You can sell this to anybody, right?
Does it matter who you sell it to?
No, right?
Two gold.
Nearby players get a bonus against pirate corsair.
24-carat tuba.
50 symphonic damage.
Four crit.
Launches an explosive burst of sound.
Damage empowers players with bonus.
Damage reduction 11.
Holy shit.
Golden clock.
Guarding gold ring.
Increases coin pickup range.
Two defense and almost 0.5% damage reduction.
Golden door.
Can we have a golden door?
What?
Golden door?
I didn't get one.
I got one.
Do you want to put it there?
Do you?
No.
Okay.
Flying Dutchman trophy.
Holy shit.
Zealous hand cannon.
82 range damage.
Almost 10% crit chance.
Is that that stupid KO fist?
No, it's a big cannon.
Can I see it?
Where are you?
Oh yeah.
Golden charge.
Golden table.
Golden platform.
Garo's breath.
Oh, I think it uses the grenade shells or magnum rounds or whatever.
Okay.
It's a golden toilet.
And then a golden chair.
Don't shoot it in the house.
I mean, I wasn't planning on it.
Give the rounds.
Do you want the seating charge?
I have a lot of those here too.
Oh no.
Do you still use that honeycomb?
I have it.
Do you want it?
Yeah.
I'm curious if this ever makes anything good eventually.
I just gave it to you.
All right.
I want to just play with the tuba for a second.
I just want to know what it does.
Yeah.
That's what it does.
So it just shoots up with a little bit of grenades.
They don't go very far.
All right.
Well, that's cool.
I can turn it into anything?
No.
I'm just selling it.
Unless you want it for anything.
It's not a material or anything.
No.
I don't.
Stone.
What about this captain's foie gras?
Thrower class?
Sell them?
The what?
The captain's, like, the thrower?
Give it to me.
I'm doing throwing weapons now.
Damn, that's a lot.
That is a lot.
They're pretty good too.
Flying Dutchman trophy, I'm assuming he's not.
OK, this guardian gold ring, I think, is pretty rare.
What can you do with it?
Coin ring.
Really?
It increases coin pickup range, and hitting enemies will sometimes drop extra coins.
I mean, rare doesn't usually mean always good.
Well, let's put him onto it.
Where's Popo?
Hey, put this door on.
No, potion.
Put that golden door somewhere.
Why can't you?
I don't understand.
Where the fuck is Popo?
I could have just turned around and just placed it, but I don't know.
I don't know why it was.
You know, it's your server.
I feel like it's a golden door.
You get the honors to, like, put the golden door up, I think, somewhere in my brain.
Yeah, I deserved the honor.
He doesn't know how.
Yes, I do.
See?
OK, I know how to put a door up.
I needed to prove that right away.
Why am I on fire?
Am I burning?
I think those are your shoes that you're wearing, that you're just not used to, that you light on fire when you run.
What?
No.
You just look cool.
No, this is happening when I get home in the house.
Oh, that's...
I built...
Where is it?
Where the hell did I put it?
I need a staff.
I want a staff.
I think you're standing in front of it.
It makes us run faster.
It's the torch that's there.
This thing is, like, fun.
This summons the spheres.
This summons the ice chunks.
This summons the skulls that shoot after a second.
I want a staff.
Then we're going to have to start doing the mechanical boss.
Annoying glacial sting.
Do you want this?
Oh, well, that's annoying.
Why would anybody want this?
Yeah, you're being very annoying right now.
That means, like, it sucks, right?
I mean, you can reforge it.
Oh.
How do you do that again?
What's a good thing to make for a pickaxe right now?
I'm actually forgetting what our next pickaxe progression is.
I think we're supposed to get cobalt, but I never can find cobalt.
Maybe it's because cobalt is something different on servers, like lead and iron.
Right.
But, oh, hell, that's why I was confused.
Okay, so I need to go smash more of those alters.
And then we can start getting better stuff.
Coming with you.
Oh, didn't you say to go, like, up in the sky?
I wanted to find the potion seller for gravity potions,
and then I was going to do sky stuff, but he wasn't there.
No.
I don't know if he's dead or what.
Trixie the party girl has arrived.
Yeah, she can go live in a dumpster for all I care.
Trixie the party girl?
Yeah, don't talk to her, Jerma.
Okay.
You're too good for her.
Oh, I'm Trixie. I like partying.
It's my whole identity.
All right.
You know, your parents are paying to go to college.
This is really respectful of you.
Whenever I go off on, like, a random tangent,
you start doing the...
He's not saying...
I'm just blocking it out.
I'm blocking out your, like, nonsense.
I already forgot. Where were we going?
I don't know. I'm following you.
Why were we going this way?
I don't know. You said I'm going to jump real quick.
Alters. Smash the altars.
I'm blocking out the crazy things you're saying.
The world has been blessed.
Did you bless the world?
Yeah, that's me destroying altars.
It adds new wars.
Wait a minute. Did I just pick up, like, fucking 50 gold?
Maybe.
Wait a minute.
I just saw gold.
What are you up to down there?
I'm coming to find out.
I love that when you show up near me,
it just means, like, 30 guys are going to go beat up somebody near me.
Oh, here's Jerma.
It's pretty great.
There's, like, a fucking sword over here.
Lazy Blitzzard?
This is a huge weapon over there.
I thought you said you collected everything.
That item's worth using for you
just because right-clicking makes you go fast.
If you hold down right-click with it,
you'll keep dashing.
Molten Pick?
God damn it.
Yeah, we haven't upgraded our pickaxe in, like, ever.
I'll be right back.
What? This is awesome.
Wait, no. Can you recall the base?
I'm going to be the base way quicker than you think.
Who needs a recall?
I mean...
Okay, bro.
Well, it's free, so fine.
What do you need?
I need to make a Molten Pickaxe so we can get the new pickaxe.
I need the Molten Ore.
This thing is pretty awesome.
Let me deposit this shit.
Desert, also, sandstone,
seed,
ock, blood droplet,
lens.
I need this pickaxe so I can get that pickaxe.
Mom?
Mom, everyone has the new pickaxe.
We forge it. Lazy is back.
Magma is wrong?
Molten is five hundred stones.
Okay, I need the other pickaxe, Mom.
You bought me the wrong one.
Minus five hundred percent speed?
Are they sure?
I need money.
Reforge.
Alright, we're good.
Superior.
I don't think that
debuff was working.
Maybe it was.
I need new armor.
So, can I upgrade this stuff?
Like the spirit trappers
stuff.
This thing looked like it was swinging really fast
when I did it last time.
No, it was swinging this fast before.
Jerma.
What's up?
It's fucking mission time. Mission time, alright.
I need your help in
locating the underground
granite subsystem.
Alright.
I understand. I think I can help you here.
You want the underground
granite subsystem.
Yeah, that's the subsystem.
What's your favorite pizza?
What's going on with all these people down here?
Did you put these people down here?
Yeah.
You're a fucking monster.
They're banished.
They're not even good enough for the prison.
At least let them
walk around down here.
No.
Why is it free wood in here?
What do you want down here?
Are you looking for the granite land?
It's like a purple looking area.
It's an area.
And we need it.
Purple looking area.
Yeah, it's fucking purple.
Alright, okay.
I don't know where it is.
So we kind of just have to explore.
How many torches do you have?
Did you use all the...
I gave you like 500.
Well, you did, but
let's see what's happening is
I have deposit all and I'm not all clicking them
and I deposit them all back in.
Okay, because you just deposit all.
That's all you ever do.
No, that's not true.
I do look at a lot of things.
I do go over lots of things.
But if you come to me
I have 1400 in hand.
Well, that's good.
There's a big fish down there.
Yeah, honey?
Look, a fish!
Alright, give me that shit.
Ah, dude, you know who I fucking need?
Here, you stay here.
God, I still don't have a fucking mirror.
Sorry, I'm having a meltdown.
Why don't you just take mine and then come back to me?
I can do that.
You better get this back.
Okay.
Why is it doing that?
Do you have an alt selected?
Oh, well, that would be a thing now, wouldn't it?
You're never getting this back.
Hey, it's Popo.
Glow sticks, cool.
That's one of my torches that you promised.
Do you want to find something specific?
You keep on going...
Uh...
Don't tell me what you're doing.
I forgot what I was doing.
We're doing a psychotic amulet.
Glow sticks are amazing.
They work in water. Nice.
Nice.
No, that's like, nice.
Oh, what's this?
I can't get this. This is too good of a material.
What is this?
That's why we're on this mission.
We need to find... I added the new resources to the world,
but we can't mine them yet.
So we need to find the
granite area.
Because there are...
There's a way to get a pickaxe from that.
Wait a minute. Hold on.
Purple.
Oh, shit. I know what I'm doing and I can't do it.
I can't fucking mine this either.
There's something over here too.
Where? In here?
Where's the heart?
There it is. A life crystal.
So,
we're trying to find the material to be able to get
new axes to be able to
mine the shit that's down here.
Use heart.
What? I can't.
Why does everybody keep telling me to do that?
Like, how...
Silt. Stone.
Stone. Stone.
Mine the tote pouch. Yes.
Yes, yes, yes.
Yes.
Don't mine the tote pouch. Don't listen to your chat.
You have one thing that you need to do.
And you have yet to
describe what that thing is.
The granite. It's a purple biome. You cannot miss it.
It is like a dark purple area.
It's somewhere underground.
Last time you tried to explain it, you went, uh...
That was like, I don't... What?
No.
You found it? It's... Oh, you did find it, you fuck.
Dirty fuck.
You are absolutely
filthy.
What are you guys talking about? Am I underwater?
Yes, I am.
Hey!
To your left, and that's a boss that spawned in it.
It should be really weak for
how strong we are right now.
This is a boss?
Do you listen to me?
I was saying, this is a boss?
Like, as in, it's not,
shouldn't be. It's like a standard enemy. Not, hey, is this a boss?
It's
from before hard mode.
I was mocking it.
Like, this is a boss?
No. You're covering for yourself.
I am not. I appreciate that you'd go to those lengths
to me. Listen to that clip, and you'll hear that it was like,
this is a boss?
Rannet block. Yeah.
This is a block?
Rannet? See, I'm not hearing it.
Energy core. Wound stone.
Ooh. Ooh.
There's a guy down here. There he is. Mr. Wizard.
Oh, he found him.
Where'd he go? Found the wizard.
Hey, friend, this bondage was starting to chafe.
Crystal ball.
Ice rod. Ooh.
Oh. Here. Take your stupid ice mirror.
29 damage.
Someone's a block of ice?
Is this any good?
Uh, I think his stuff is dated.
I'm not sure.
Crystal ball. Functions as a demon altar.
Guard thing.
Oh, dude, crystal ball. That's actually, I'm getting one.
Do you have 10 gold on you?
I have three.
Ah!
Isn't, what, aren't you gonna, like,
trap this guy somewhere?
Uh, I'm, yeah, he auto moves into
one of the trap houses.
He auto, hold on a minute.
He auto moves into one of the
trap houses. Yeah. Yeah.
He gets caught in the trap. How do you move in,
how do you move into a house that traps you?
Most of rap is
about this exact situation.
Here, will you take?
There's silver bars in here.
Oh, sick. We found a way to summon one of the
skeleton bot, uh, mechanical bots.
So we can do that.
And then you can use hollow bars to make a pickaxe,
right, chat, right?
Or does hollow bars not have a pickaxe?
Anybody know? Yes. Correct.
Yes. Everyone's saying yes.
Okay.
Hollow bars have a pickaxe. You also need the boss souls.
So yeah, we're gonna have to do all
the mechanical bosses then.
Hooray. Which is a pain.
But that's one down.
Uh, because
in the granite area,
I'm trying to remember,
like, no enemies are spawning
and this place sucks.
One of the golems drops
the, like, geode
clump or something.
And the geodes allow you
to make a pickaxe. But there's
no enemies here.
And I'm kind of pissed.
If I had a six,
if I had a clone,
if I had a tiny clone of star, would I torture it?
He wouldn't, he does.
You mean like a
doll, like a voodoo doll or something?
Uh, no.
No, I wouldn't. I'm just gonna keep going this way.
Drop it in the lava.
I'm not gonna use
a voodoo doll on somebody.
If anything, I would, like, have a voodoo doll
of somebody and, like,
cook bacon around it.
So it would be like, hmm, what's that
bacon smell? I would put, like,
Money on its hands and shit.
I would light incense
and have, like, aromatherapy around it. So you just, like,
felt better? That's not how it works.
I know it's not how it works.
Alright, Yerma! Yerma! Yerma! Yerma!
Yes?
It's a back to town. I'm getting
areolite ore.
That's more important. No one cares.
You just wanna skip everything.
I'm gonna drown.
Don't fucking drown! Holy shit, that was lucky.
Alright, back to town.
back to town all right for what uh we need to oh shit it's daytime we need to beat mechanical bosses
okay uh we need the myth round for mechanical bosses this part of the game is so annoying
what feels like to upgrade to your next pickaxe the things you need to do are so specific too hard
like i meow thrower i kind of want to play with the meow thrower might be fun let me see what else
i picked up some stuff that i want to look at i got the good boots i have the fear monger
five percent damage reduction yeah that's good that's good these are all really good so it's
gonna take a lot for me to replace this what about armor i can't i feel like i need new armor soon
the psycho amulet boost rogue and range damage in critical strike chance by five percent grants a
massive boost to these stats if you aren't moving does that count for my summons it does not
well what about you star what about me do you want the psychotic amulet what does it do
boosts rogue and range damage and crit strike by five percent oh yeah i do grants a massive boost
to these if you stand still if you are not moving yeah i do okay here you go yeah i do
what does massive mean then how much more than massive man oh i did oops oh yeah
oh dude you're right i'm right what did i do no chat guy was right he knew exactly the thing
i needed he knew just how to top blade just right you caught out like three times but
well i'm glad congratulations i'm glad you're happy i'm very happy i just think we might have
to kill the slime god again okay um does somebody sell we do better healing potions than lesser
healing potions or do you have to deal with i just put some potions in the storage but
oh no potion guy doesn't material you can you just craft them how do you craft them okay healing
potion so i need glowing mushroom and in lesser healing potion it's a it's a huge pain in the
ass is it a pain in the ass to get these uh you yeah we also don't know where our mushroom biome
is so you're gonna have to find that uh i need your help to kill slime boy
then things are gonna get a rolling did you say you wanted cobwebs i don't care about them anymore
oh sorry i like three hours later slime god has awoken uh did you give me that throwing thing
that you mentioned throwing things yeah you said throwing damage you had a thing i said yeah i
wanted it and i don't think you ever gave it to me like two minutes ago yeah just yeah the thing
that we were just talking about the damage thing yeah yeah i get it did you repick it up
no i have it where is uh give me the purified gel that you drop purified gel
i mean you've been um say please for this please germa that's all it took here take this too
and take that too and i guess you can have you can have that too i don't care you already have
one of those what about this book eldritch tomb material cast eldritch tentacles to spear your
enemies does it now whoa how much damage does that do 56 and 33 it's kind of look at this is
shit quality what i think this is shit quality though
augur of the elements cast a burst of elemental tentacles to spear your enemies
uh it's night time so let's we're gonna fight one of the next bosses i'm gonna look up how to
make the others really fast all right okay let me get some of those potions out here
is this guy gonna is his heart is this like a don't fuck around
pretty strong right now oh shit you know i'm granted pickaxe isn't good enough
where's the fucking bacon bro all right oh did you just throw this back to me did i
all right wait wait what that is that what you're looking for the ghoul banner no the the the foie
the the point y'all no i just threw those on the ground no actually i'm gonna put this down
we got it we gotta go we gotta go daylight's burning i mean midnight a midnight oil okay
are we fighting it right here shit where did i put it skeleton prime whoa there he goes
he's got a lot of health yeah it's kind of a he's kind of a mean guy he is kind of a mean guy
like we're the only reason he exists you know yeah i didn't even drink my potions i don't think i'm
going to though why because he's chasing me because of not too much danger
skeleton prime oh now we're chunking them uh some oh summon your things again your
sentries i got oh are they all in the same spot i'm just like i spawned them when he moved a little
bit where's he going what are you doing he's kind of just running back and forth here
arms are all gone
oh that hurt so is there a skeleton like a super skeleton prime uh it's the skeleton twin eyes
this guy and mechanical worm and then after you beat all of those you're gonna fight
plantera sounds cheeky get some better mana potions yeah these these ones to kind of suck
huh they feel like only like two with like three lobes i don't mind me just picking up my
my gel knives that are everywhere sorry mom armor pen do you need armor pen uh we both get that
well we both get this yep those are guaranteed first time you kill a boss
so what about the the mechanical bosses is this just lore stuff what the other one what the other
item that he drops once useful tools turned into savage beasts when their ai's went rogue a mistake
that draiden failed to rectify in time i see that you have awakened that is old toy that is mod added
lore okay it's the most pointless thing you could be reading i didn't know if it was like a material
or something or like a boss thing or lore i think i deposited my other one of these
ah shit we need souls of night you don't have those by chance do you souls of night hold on
i actually like deposited what is it what was that thing called no i did it again
fucking god damn it i was just trying to go over here
what the hell is this thing called again sort by name sort by id what are those boss soul things
called what a soul of fright is what he dropped that's not what we need
either way we need a mithril anvil oh this part's annoying didn't have another one that was more
item range i forget what it was called thanks bunny duck my foot hurts a lot sorry to hear that
oh yeah yeah oh wait i have the pickaxe shake it out a little gel all right oh there's a goodie
bag in here vampire did you get vampire mask vampire pants why is everybody freaking out in
here everyone's like what what what's going on what nothing's going on no no something like
something major is going on what are you talking about something what something something what
somebody was streaming that's what you sound like something something what that's what you sound like
apparently somebody was like in the top of just chatting streaming porn
oh actually someone was saying that in my chat nice how many people it had 20 000 viewers
why did it take an hour to put that down what i don't know it's late on the west coast i guess
it's not that late it's like not even 10 o'clock i mean it's not like i don't know if they have like
24 hour moderators on every single channel just to make sure someone doesn't do something wrong
no but did you hear how many people were there yeah but they're historically very slow at these
things and very inconsistent in their moderation so i'm not surprised i guess is what i'm getting
at it's like yeah that sucks but i'm not surprised i mean it's just kind of bizarre
we need to make sure it's really hard is this something we want i got to check with my supervisor
are we doing porn now 20 000 people there that's that's fucking insane all right um so what's next
by the way what uh what's your what's your like time frame here how you doing uh i don't want to
go much longer i've i've been a good sleep schedule boy yes um is it as midnight for you i'd like to
go a little oh yeah i'd like to go a little bit longer just so i can get this pickaxe thing out
of the way yeah so that the path is clear when we next start so what i'm doing is i got a gel
pickaxe so that i can mine one of the new ores and get you a pickaxe and then we can mine the
other ores and have a good old mine fest mine now i can get palladium then i can make a palladium
pickaxe and then we can start making a mithral anvil and that kind of stuff actually maybe now
is like a decent spot to stop is it yeah it's kind of like the uh the true start to uh the hard
mode okay because we haven't even gotten a single ore yet we only did one mechanical box it's been
six hours it's been we've played for a while yeah time flies when you tararia yeah it kind of
it was five hours before i looked at the clock it was really fun though it's all right how much
more like okay percentage wise like how much more is there left to do that's reasonable to do
not like oh i want to beat the last boss that has five trillion hp and i need every item in the game
of the normal terraria game it's these three new ores gearing up whatever you want to get then you
fight uh plantera isn't a big boss and golem is done pretty quickly after that then i'm pretty
sure right after golem you've got cultist then you have the lunar pillars and then you have
the moon lord which is the classic final finish and then calamity has a bunch of
shit after that and thorium has one boss after that so like even if we didn't do the super
late game calamity stuff i'd say we're at most halfway through but probably less than halfway
i mean i'll i'll finish it i'll like at least get to the end of like the actual game
do it again yeah getting to the end of calamity is a little bit
but like some of the late game calamity stuff just gets so obnoxious to craft and the amount of stuff
you have to keep track of is like not actually fun anymore for me i don't know i mean that's
that would be something i would want to do like on my own time i think yeah but uh actually there's
very easily another stream we wouldn't be done yeah i don't think unless we like really rushed
it and i don't think we're gonna do that yeah well see you hey see you next week for uh terraria
are these things quacking terraria episode three episode three actually well we would have done
this this would have been episode let's see six hours we did how long was the last week's stream
like six oh you're doing in like actual episode well because it would be a youtube episode each
episode would be about 10 to 15 minutes all right we'll say 20 no way more than a longer game you
do 20 because then you 20 i don't know you can get two ads in it you can get the mid roll
uh-huh okay so two four that's three episodes an hour three four six three three six nine
12 15 18 so we're we're like episode like 37 of terraria right now yeah so tune in next week
next week for episode 37 yeah yeah well go get some sleep okay i'm hungry too i think that yeah
that's a probably a good place to call we're just under six hours yep yep yep yep maybe if you
didn't start so late start so late let's start at like five p.m it was like it was like three
o'clock when i talked to you five for me yeah well i mean i i wait hold on i specifically
asked you like yesterday when you wanted to start and you were like it doesn't matter just hit me up
and i was like i usually start around three or four and you're like yeah that's fine i was being
polite like i was judging you the whole time but why didn't you say like hey can we start like at
like one or two i would have been like all right i i asked you like twice i was i'm just messing
why are you doing our stream is like six hours longer than your usual one so we're good um you
haven't been paying very much attention my average stream time is like seven to eight hours now
is it it's like six to eight hours yeah i don't even believe you you don't even pay attention
anymore oh my god like you pay attention to me i do
yeah i think 90 percent of the streams i do at least in the last like six months have been at
least six hours sometimes they're a little shorter but sometimes they also go like 11 to 12 hours too
did he leave him or am i still no no no i i i muted for like one second now you do not go for
11 hours i went for almost 13 hours at one time okay hold on hold on hold on hold up
oh are you gonna no no no do it are you gonna like go to like my like twitch stats or something
and find out what everybody doesn't know this but if you actually check a streamer's videos section
you can see what games they play when they play yeah oh my god i hear myself fuck no so go go
go to my my pods and go look and tell me what the stream times are i'm looking because
i'm i'm both surprised and like truly impressed that you can last at your age and at your health
for seven hours i'm i'm as healthy as a goddamn ox all right no that's good i remember the good
old days of uh you know germa two three times a week if you're lucky of three hour streams
yeah but i was still it takes a lot to get used to transitioning from editing down like a seven
minute video no like i never used to do it i didn't do i didn't do anything
so when you when you make like videos like a 10 minute video one day like anyone hey it's
somebody just mentioned this yeah i used to stream once every four or five months so i think we've
evolved well no you're like your first like i'm gonna be streaming video was like i'm gonna be
streaming at least two or three times a week no that i did they were only like three four hours
long that's what i mean it's like you did like hey i'm not i'm not sure how much you know this
but do you know that most people on twitch do not stream for more than like four or five hours at
a time did you know that like that's like nobody streams for like more than six to eight hours
a ton of people only stream for like three or four hours did you know that i don't i mean a lot of
people do but i don't know if i'd go like a ton like not streaming is the twitch meta i'm telling
you calls out the entire platform no i but what that's not calling anybody out that's saying like
that most but they also they also stream more days you understand well a lot of people that like oh
like kim the tat man streams like four hours but he does it twice a day it's a lot i think you're
just trying to i'm trying to downplay no no i'm telling you twitch streamers because you think
you're better than them now but it's just like oh i got it i'm playing a clam he can talk he can
have his little talk and he everybody knows it's just bullshit it's just noise oh why did
you just killed everybody i please tell me that you
i didn't do this you killed everybody oh because he's oh my god i i'm leaving i'm out here
i had nothing to do i'm fighting it oh my god dude he's
slaughtering everyone oh is this gonna be okay for next week no no wow like really you're the
last person i would count on as a superhero the same thing before when people were dying oh my
god they're dying what the fuck do you want me to do dude what do you want me to do i want you to
fight the clam i have all my shit spawn you summon the motherfucker in here he killed
everybody what do you want me to do i can't even spawn there's clams in my spawn you threw a if
you rolled a grenade into my house and i got shit exploded and you were like dude hey come why
didn't you do anything about that why weren't you prepared what am i supposed to do i'm just
saying i'm not seeing you helping everybody is dead everybody is dead
all the time it took you you know this is justice this is justice for all the people that you like
locked in here every single fucking person is gone you deserved this for having such a terrible
fucking house dude they're all dead oh my god that's fucking funny the pig lived
yeah i was i can't believe i can't believe you're not fighting back i i just like
i was like asleep in my bed and you like stood over my bed with a frying pan and hit me right in the
fucking face and i ding hey dude what you get up and fight come on do something that was fucking
ridiculous so i just looked you like hey where's the fucking guide i was trying like i i've never
fought clam after hard mode and they they give him a lot of shit i don't know if he drops better
stuff that's the second time tonight that a spherical like hey arnold shaped head object
came crashing down instantly from the sky on me and scared the shit out of me that happened at
least two or three times oh my god the first was the ufo thing and then that all right well
how do we do we have to clean this up or is this can we like can you roll the surface back no this
is how it is we just got griefed man you have to like roll it back we got griefed that's fine
they'll come back and what you do is you put in like a wanted ad in craigslist and a bunch of
fucking hopefuls show up oh spacious room big base oh we got extra tiles for our room they
don't realize it's all vertical space oh like a thousand square foot apartment for everyone and
it's all vertical yeah dude wow what this is really interesting hold on it's that's a really
good price for a 1400 square foot apartment yeah yeah but you don't realize it's like three feet
wide and fucking like a hundred feet straight up close knit community yeah they're packed in
that's anyway yeah now that everyone's dead i guess definitely a great place to stop
yeah well now we have to now there's no you know all these these tombstones we've never died in it
this game's easy so the people that like you know they were oh yeah that's it see you later see
next week we would really like winding down there and people that were like involved with
this and like really paying attention to what we were doing they're going to be like what the
fuck happened because then you know i already left yeah they're going to think that we like
we're fucking around with each other and like throwing grenades you know each other's like
houses you don't do that that's the one thing you don't do is destroy houses you know i'm saying
people thought oh they're doing like a dynamite joke and they killed everybody nope like they
were throwing dynamite at each other from across the way all right i'm gonna leave and the nurse
came back the same we already got we already got one sucker someone's back well that's good it's
only gonna take like four hours of game time for everybody to come back right uh good okay i'm gonna
check one more thing before i'm done as if there's like a wyvern up god and they you you killed these
people why me like i was i was very i was very vocal about i didn't like this they were here
and you're like no no it's fine wasn't it though all right i'm gonna i'm gonna take off okay thanks
for playing star i'll see you next time on next week wow next week when hopefully everybody
respawns by then yeah i'm gonna stay in a little bit longer so we get some people to respond
but bye to you well bye to you bye to your stream bye to your chat bye guys always a pleasure
have a great rest of your night get some food get some sleep tata and there we go that was
a nice little exit there the game leave exit all right so that was some more terraria it's fun
it's fun it's just a it's a game you know it's a video game it's been a while since i've
actually played like a multiplayer video game with somebody and saw it to the end
so that should be fun at least i want to see just to get to the end it's fun to make new
stuff look into items kind of overwhelming but it's still a lot of fun but um to give you guys
some info here i am not going to be back until at least wednesday or thursday as of this stream
i'm going to be across the country we're doing a facility walkthrough with all the people involved
in the carnival stream so i'm gonna be spending time working on that we're gonna get that all
hammered out so i'm gonna try to stream on wednesday i'm gonna try to i should be back by then i'm
hoping i am so it shouldn't be more than one two three days maybe three and a half four days
at the very latest you will see me back on thursday is there a set date for the carnival yes
there is september 21st mark it on your calendar that's the date i was warning you a few hours go
to put your arena away from your npcs well no that's what i said to him that's why we wanted to
build it out to the left more that was on him that was his house it's his server his house install
calamity music for next time yeah people a lot of people saying that calamity do we both have to
do we both have to have that though because isn't it like if i don't have the same mods as him
tell him but we're gonna do the bits and the subs and then i've got to get ready to go do this
i will have a shitload more details on exactly how this stream is going to be done
when i get back wish me luck i am equal parts excited and a little nervous right because
obviously anytime you try to do something like this even like the germa rumble video any like
big stream or big video is always like all right i want to make sure this is done right
i'm looking forward to it though i can't wait so six hours ago a while back now we had
10 bucks from fuss row force row boto thanks for a thousand bits thank you they say hey i think i
actually said the same thing last stream but would what would you recommend for someone playing dark
souls one oh weapon wise i think we yeah we talked about uh you can really use anything in
dark souls one it's whatever you feel like playing with except um what's it what's a weapon you
wouldn't use in dark souls one that's been a while since i played it the last time i played it it was
like a joke stream so don't use the broken sword yeah the thing that you spawn with don't use that
the whip and the fists yeah the whip sucks the whip sucks in every game does the whip have any
purpose at all besides it's like okay in some pvp scenarios right some of the impression of rp right
thank you too thank you to dad thank you to daddy for the 15 dollars here thank you dad they say
they say germa uncensored haha oh god thank you the 15 dollars thank you thank you dad
appreciate that that's it that's all they say uh thank you to uh k white for the 250 hey germa
uh mr pig and i just want to say i grew up watching your videos and now i have your sense
of humor and because of that no friends thanks what are you talking about who's mr pig who's
mr pig you can't it's a contradiction right there
germa sense of humor equals no humor at all all right well i mean how long you
john cena john cena says that if you're gonna dish it i'm gonna dish it back come on you you
want to dish i get a dish i got i'll serve it up hot only reads the worst messages confirmed
no i read i read a ton of good messages today like come on sometimes sometimes i've got a hot
steamy spaghetti here that i just i'm ready to serve sometimes dodging like mean comments like
all right what's that person how about this one no i know you're fucking around i'm just kidding
but thank you for 250 though appreciate also thank you too uh devakitty for the 250 here's
some streamer pop quiz what's the name of the 1986 action comedy film starring
paul hogan as a weathered bushman from the australian outback uh is that crocodile dundee
i got it yeah what do i get okay uh all right well that was elaborate thank you uh thank you too
thank you to daydream 88 for the 10 bucks thousand bits thank you daydream hey germa i know
you get these types of messages a lot i just want to say you sincerely for all the years of
i want to thank you sincerely for all the years of laughs and smiles i've been watching since the tf
two days back when i was in middle school and now i'm going to japan in two weeks for a whole year
of study since i won't be able to catch your streams as much i'll have to keep up with the
bauds especially september 21st it's been amazing to grow up with you japan it's really weird to
think that i've been doing this for over eight years and some people may have been like in high
school or even like younger and like now they're fucking like grown-ups like oh yeah i started
watching you when i was uh like in college and now i'm 30 like holy shit and that's me too like
that's me as well so it'll be interesting when i when i actually crossed the 10 year mark
it's gonna be an interesting milestone but it's coming quicker than any of us think but daydream
thank you so much good luck in japan thanks for sticking around for that long a lobotomized
teddy bear thanks to the 250 germa i'm in boston for a few days right now and i've never been
what would you recommend i should do or try or see thanks and keep being a funny man
first uh somebody asked us a few months ago we had some good ideas the museum of science is awesome
if you get a chance i would say to anybody that was coming from anywhere else that boston has
probably the best museum of science i've probably ever been to there's tons of awesome shit there
if you have if you're traveling with like family and there's younger kids the the children's museum
is awesome too that whole area is just really good go to faneuil hall there's tons of great
like shopping and restaurants and stuff
there's a lot of interesting stuff restaurant restaurants uh there are so many restaurants
in boston it's like it's hard to even tell you to go to one but i would definitely say museum of
science if you have like young siblings or cousins or something that you're with uh children's museum
then uh faneuil hall i'd say that's probably let me check out like you check out you know um like fenway
fenway is awesome too if you can get in the you like baseball even just being around fenway it's
like right in there so you got plenty of opportunities to kind of be part of the scene
it's pretty good i i i wouldn't recommend the duck boats i don't think that's kind of i would
i don't know if i would recommend somebody to do that there's nothing wrong with the duck boats
but the duck boats really is a kind of i'm out of town guy in a hawaiian shirt with the kind of
sunscreen all over his nose and glasses around his neck kind of thing to do you know what i'm
saying it's a very like touristy thing to do i don't know if it's you just kind of float around
and drive around and they if you really really want to do something insanely touristy
uh boston has a pretty famous duck boats but if you if you're into that then absolutely do it
it is a subterranean vehicle it goes on the ground and then goes underground well no you don't like
it just it floats it's a boat it's a boat it's a car boat that drives around and you float you don't
submerge but uh have fun it's a very very very interesting city it's got a lot of history
got a lot of history it's a historical place in the united states but uh fraudium weapon thank
you for the 250 fraudium happy terraria saturday germa hart love this game but love watching you
and stir play it even more i also wanted to wish you safe travels in the coming weeks prepping for
the carnival stream good luck be safe and have fun uh one more germa yeah it's it's a pretty easy
trip i'm not like spending like a week there not yet this is going to be a fairly quick
turnaround i think it's not going to be a situation where i have to be out there for a long time
it should be fun thank you i really appreciate it and terraria is a lot of fun that's why i am
going to see it to it's at least base game completion uh fooey thank you fooey for the host
and i thought you gave subs here too but thank you fooey for the host i did i i might as well
just say thanks i thought it was subs under there but sometimes my brain is wrong but i do
appreciate thinking hey croacher thanks for the five subs there you are croacher that was a while
ago and i think i missed it i was i was really tunnel vision tonight is it actually over the
stream what was the length uh six hours and 15 minutes here i was too late uh phylactery lich
thanks for the 5000 bits i said it i caught it but we were in the middle of a of a gaming argument
but thanks for the 50 bucks phylactery local streamer called out on past stream set schedule
defend self he's come a long way yeah all right this is what i what i was trying to say before
he look he opened up my past streaming schedule shit and he was like oh all right hold on i was
wrong here going from making a video that is seven to eight minutes and not having to be live in
front of people for more than you know i didn't really do it that often you like kind of build
up your comfort level to do it and i'm not gonna lie two years ago three years ago it was a
difference it was it's a lot different it was a big change to hey instead of sitting here and
like playing a game and trying to do like funny weird interesting things and in dark souls and
you're not even getting out of the tutorial room for two or three hours it was hey i'm gonna be
here and these people gonna be here there's no use nobody used to be in the room you know like
nobody is in the room now but it was just me and transitioning from it's just me to there
might be thousands of people here you need to kind of build up like a stamina to be able to
oh it's been an hour or two okay um i think i'm done it's been three hours uh yeah that's uh
bye nobody to yell that the joke you just said sucked yeah that's yeah like you know what i mean
it's like different it's a different beast i could say something stupid and then put it in a youtube
video and not know if people thought it was funny until like potentially a week later
i get instant feedback now so yeah and now i can stream for six seven eight hours at a time and
it's fine never it didn't use to be the case though instant conflict yeah but yeah that's
that's 50 bucks from phylactery thank you and then finally here tingy can we make it official
and call these weekly streams sterarius saturdays no yeah i i've come to the decision and realization
that you cannot name anything a day of the week ever again because oh it's scare saturdays it's
terraria saturdays what if we can't do it on saturday oh shit we have to do it on saturday now
there has to be a scare saturdays on saturday instead of just being just do it when you can
you know what if we do a terraria on friday it's like oh shit man time to rebrand everything
so i'm against naming days of the week in a title stop scare saturdays because you're a coward
yeah i don't know fine say it but i also ran out of like kind of scary games to play for a little
while but scary games suck they're really fucking stressful and i'll tell you i'm not going to
bullshit you it got to a point where it would be like thursday night and i would know i was
going to record something for saturday or like friday night or even even on saturday afternoon
and i'd be like fuck man i don't i don't want to play scary game right now fuck it's going to
scare me i'm gonna get like stressed out and
it you're gonna have to make yourself want to do it in a way jump scares and all that yeah
vr horror games are a blast to watch you play i had to have lost at least a few years of my life
there was at least two or three parts of that game that would just
it was such a jump in such a scary scenario that it my like i definitely took at least like
three years of blood pumping capability away from my heart like at the end of my life
unless i'm a super high strong neurotic kind of person anyways so you add in terrifying jump
scares just dials it up to a thousand but let's uh get the credits on here these are all the subs
from the last six hours or so here they come just a second i promise you they'll be here
i'm telling you they're gonna come in just a second any minute
there they come there they are but i will see you guys uh next week i'm gonna try to stream
on wednesday but if for some reason it's i'm not done with whatever i'm doing then it by the
absolute latest i'll be back on thursday and i will bring news with me thank you uh wing for
the five dollars what's the best dark souls one weapon thanks for the five dollars though i don't
know i don't know um the katana the drake sword there you go the drake sword the drake sword the
thing where you cut the tail off of the dragon i use that for like the rest of the game until
like you have you fight well i'm just gonna save that now i'm just gonna say it's the break
sword this weander is good yeah most of the two-handed weapons the two-handed swords are
good right black knight sword black knight halberd black knight great sword it's a it's vey hander
not this we hander meh that's all right i could be either one well there you go you got like
there's at least 12 weapons that have been put into chat hopefully you find one
oh the speed hander uh black knight halberd is a speed runner weapon so it's probably good
yeah don't they stack it up with something too they put a ring on and get to like one health
um red tear stone ring yeah he said he said the line oh
but anyways i'll see you guys next week have a great rest of your weekend i know i mentioned
this before but i want to make sure because i know there's some people that are wondering if i am
going to be there i probably will not be at evo tomorrow i knew i was thinking maybe i could get
there for an hour or two or something but i'm not going to be there i don't think so if you oh he
said he may be there on sunday i'm no longer planning on doing it but take care of yourselves
see you next week much love guys see you soon