Hey, what is going on, everybody? Jerma here with a new Little Gems.
Now, this has been a long time since the last Little Gems, and I do apologize for that.
But, I finally got the hardware necessary to be able to record off my iPad.
If you followed this series, you'll know I had a lot of problems with trying to get games off the iPad, off the iPhone, and Android.
It was a real journey, we'll just say that.
And if you're wondering what I'm using, what capture device I'm using, I'm using a Game Capture HD.
It's from Elgato. Very easy to set up, very easy to use, and it works like a charm.
As you're seeing on the screen, you can actually see this iPad footage, and the sound is included, so two big thumbs up to Elgato.
And with that, we are going to move on here and talk about Spellsword.
So what Spellsword is, it is an action adventure platforming RPG death arena game.
That is a mouthful, but let me just compare this to a game that already exists.
Super Crate Box. If you like Super Crate Box, you will absolutely love this game.
Now, replace the gun mechanic in Super Crate Box and use these card mechanics and a sword in Spellsword.
So the game breaks down like this. There are four maps to choose from.
Each one of these maps is going to have 20 levels to play on, and an endless mode.
Now, obviously, you cannot complete endless mode. Endless mode is just for you to play on and last as long as you can,
defending yourself from waves and waves and waves of these enemies.
And you get money as well, but we'll talk about money later.
But when you load up a regular level, 1 through 20, it's going to give you a certain specific task.
Whether that be kill a certain amount of enemies to complete the zone, or collect a certain amount of these cards,
or last a certain amount of seconds, anything like that is going to be your objective.
When you load up one of these missions. So how do you kill enemies? What do you do? What's the actual point?
Why is the game called Spellsword? Well, let's get into the card mechanics.
In each level, there's going to be random spawns of these cards. All you have as a weapon is just a sword.
You can slash enemies, it does damage, but the real way to kill these enemies and the real way to progress in the missions
is to collect these cards and to upgrade these cards.
There's no activation button, you just simply touch them and they will do their ability.
And the abilities range from ice shields and ice lances, to fireballs that cover the whole screen,
to invisibility and invulnerability, there's a lot here.
And it just happens to randomly pop up on the screen.
You cannot decipher what card is going to come up, it just is going to come up and you have to grab it.
Now this makes for some really, really good chaotic gameplay, where you are constantly jumping around,
double jumping, grabbing this card, grabbing that card, oh fire bomb, oh my god, poison cloud.
It gets really, really hectic, which is the best part about the game.
It's just so much fun in its little chaotic atmosphere.
And on top of all of this, there is an entire upgrade system and item system in this game.
There are hats in this game, you heard it here, there are hats in this game.
So that should be enough for you to go download it.
Anyways, there is an entire upgrade tree, where you spend money that you get from doing missions,
from killing enemies, they're little rupees they land on the ground, you've probably seen them in the video.
And you use that money to buy upgrades to your various things, and it's so addicting.
I have spent a lot of time in this game so far, and I still, there's a lot of things I have not upgraded.
It takes a lot of money in the later levels to upgrade some of these cards to their fullest.
But you are going to need it though, if you plan on doing any endless mode stuff,
there are three different difficulties on the endless mode, it's easy, normal, and hard.
And if you want to do hard, and you want to last a long time, you're going to want these upgrades.
It's going to help you immensely.
But now let's talk about the price point of this game, and is it worth it, should you go download it right now?
The answer is yes, because just recently, this game went free to play.
This game is a free download right now for iPad and iPhone, it's on the iTunes store right now, and it is an absolute steal.
I highly recommend this game, if you like these quirky little action RPG type games,
where you kill a lot of things, you upgrade a lot of stuff, then this is the game for you.
Also, because the game just recently went free to play, they introduced a monetized system,
so there's now an in-game store where you can buy rupees, you can buy these things called dragon coins.
They added a lot of stuff in this 1.1 update they did not too long ago.
But that's going to wrap up the video guys, thank you so much for watching, I really do appreciate it.
And go have fun with this game, it's free baby!
And I'll see you guys all next time, and of course, take care everybody.