Ladies and gentlemen, please welcome the chairman and the sole proprietor of the
German Wrestling Federation, German 985. Here to do the opening ceremonies for
our first ever Germania. Just want to say welcome everybody to Germania 2014.
That's right, that's right. Let me hear you scream. Pump it up baby. So we got a
lot of cool shit planned for you guys tonight. We got a lot of awesome matches
and I just want to be real clear with you all about something tonight. If any of
you think I'm gonna lose the championship match against Captain Crunch,
then you got something coming. If you think I'm that bad to lose against a
serial character... And here we go. Ladies and gentlemen, if you don't know that
music, you should because it's none other than Glooman. After what happened last
time at Germa Rumble 2, I'm sure he has something to say to Germa. What the fuck are
you doing here, Glooman? This is my night. Jeez. Yes, it is just always about you, isn't it, Germa?
Well, I've got a surprise for you. Surprise? I mean, I wasn't aware of a
surprise. It's me you'll be facing in the championship match. What? What? That's
impossible. Where's Captain Crunch? Captain Crunch and Germa both won the
Germa Rumbles. They're the ones that are eligible for the championship. This is a
revelation indeed. What is going to happen next? Welcome back, ladies and
gentlemen, to Germania 2014. We're gonna get the first match underway, and it's
going to be starring none other than Gabe Newell, who you all know and love.
Gabe Newell is gonna be facing a couple of different opponents here. He's going...
Gabe Newell gets attacked from behind by Sonic the Hedgehog with a chair! Sonic
the Hedgehog and Pac-Man behind him! These are his two opponents, by the way.
No introductions have gone down. It's just Gabe Newell coming down by himself,
and he gets absolutely ambushed by these two disgraceful wrestlers, can I just
say right now, when Gabe Newell gonna take a chair shot right in his face, and
the match hasn't even started. This is just even more ridiculous when you
consider the match you're about to see is a 2v1 handicap tornado tag match.
Gabe Newell versus Sonic and Pac-Man in the ring at the same time, and you're
gonna see Gabe Newell flustered right now. He's trying to keep his composure, but
how can you, after something so disgraceful like that, and there's the
bell, ladies and gentlemen, first match of Germania 2014! What a way to start it,
and right off the bat, Gabe Newell takes a double DDT on top of all the
punishment he has seen so far, and I'm not exactly sure why there's a referee
in the ring. Can we very, very clearly state this? The referee serves no
purpose because there are no rules in the German arena. There is no set rules.
Anything can happen as to why what we just saw was totally legal, and what a
spinning, almost a neck break type move on the top rope, pulling him down, and
Gabe Newell spins and slams his face on Sonic's face into the ground while
Pac-Man sort of just sits there watching, and you might be wondering why this? Why
does Gabe Newell have to go against these two fighters at the same time? Well, it
was a challenge that Sonic gave to Gabe Newell after he was humiliated in the
first German rumble with the powerbomb over the top turnbuckle that Gabe Newell
did to him, and his choice was Pac-Man. I'm not exactly sure why you'd pick
Pac-Man is going after the referee. Pac-Man just tried to punch the referee in
the face. I think he might be a little confused as to who the opponents are, but
that's Pac-Man. He kind of just does his own thing, and you can't really corral
them, but I'm assuming it's because they have a lot of history. They're both very
old characters, probably friends from 20, 30 years ago, and what a DDT. Double DDT
by Gabe Newell, and the crowd is getting really riled up right now. What's
happening? Someone's coming down to the arena. That's Gordon Freeman. Gordon
Freeman was watching backstage. No doubt got sick and tired of watching this
2v1. Sonic and Pac-Man beating up on his boss. He's going to come at him even the
odds for sure here, and he slides in the ring looking for some blood, and it looks
like no, no, no! He punches Gabe Newell in the face. He punched Gabe Newell right in
the face, and here comes the Spy sprinting down to the arena. He's not going to waste
any time. He sees his boss in dire need. It's his favorite class, the Spy. Gordon
Freeman gets out and goes right for him, and it seems like the Spy just picked up
a sledgehammer from underneath the ring. The Spy took a sledgehammer from underneath
and is smashing Gordon Freeman with it. This is getting insane. I can't believe
what I'm seeing right here, and all the while, Gabe Newell with a fantastic
double DDT. Wow. Okay, maybe take a little bit of a breather after that one. No time
for a breather. There's no time for a breather. Look at this crossface. Sonic
is in a crossface right now while Pac-Man is face down on the mat. Gabe Newell
could get a submission here. He's taking any second here. Oh, Pac-Man with a nice
breakup elbow drop on Gabe Newell, who could have easily just walked away right
there with a victory. Had he not broken it up, but this has become an intense,
insanely intense first match here in Germania 2004. What the fuck is Pac-Man
doing? Okay, he just like flipped himself over the ropes. That was a little odd.
He got a chair. That's what he was doing. He knew exactly what he was doing. Picking
up a chair from under the ring. There are no rules. Remember, guys, nobody can be
disqualified for any of this behavior that you're seeing right here, and Gabe
Newell's being held back by Sonic, and Pac-Man's not doing anything. Pac-Man is
staring at him with the chair. Okay, I think Gabe Newell is kind of confused as
well, and he gets a Bulldog for his trouble. Pac-Man, I think, blew a casket
in his brain and is just standing there with the chair in his hand. I think when
he went from point A to point B, picking chair up and putting chair in hand may
have just ruined his whole brain. I'm not sure, but we're going to talk about
what's actually happening. Gabe Newell and Sonic the Hedgehog seem to be in a
1v1 situation at this point, and you got the Spy and Gordon Freeman on your left,
so remember they're still there, and you got to figure that Gabe is going to try
to take the fullest advantage of this situation. Looks like he has a chance
right here. Going to set Sonic up in a powerbomb, just like the first Jerma
Rumble. Can he capitalize? He brings him straight down with a Razor's Edge. This
could be it. Pac-Man is still catatonic. Can he get the one count? He gets one. He
gets two. Can he get the third one? He got the third one, and Pac-Man just
drunkenly falls over with the chair. What was he doing that whole time?
Nobody will ever know the answer to that question, but Gabe Newell
goes against all odds at a 3v1 at one point before the Spy came in and sealed
himself the victory. So, Gabe Newell, congratulations on the first match win,
and apparently we're going to go backstage right now. A fight has broken
out in the garage area. I'm not entirely sure what's happening, though those are
Biaz. Those are the four Biaz that are supposed to be in the cage match for the
third match of Germania. Hopefully they don't waste all their energy by
preemptively getting started, and if you want my personal opinion on this,
you can't put a bunch of Biaz in the same dressing room and only have one
McDonald's Happy Meal in there. That's how this shit gets started. But whatever,
we've got a match to get to. Second match of Germania coming up right now.
Here it is. The introductions have already been started. This match is going
to be a very, very interesting one. We've got a gauntlet match lined up here.
If you don't know what a gauntlet match is, it's when one person has to
consecutively go against multiple other opponents, and in this case it's going
to be Grandpa versus all the shitty characters. And this is a request from
Grandpa. He said, fuck the shitty characters. I'm sick of seeing them. I
want to put a stop to it once and for all. So he's going to get that opportunity
starting with the 30s Milkman, who is, in my opinion, the worst character
that's ever been made. I've said this before. I've brought up a lot of the
different shitty characters that have been made. I think Milkman is the worst
one because, I mean, he's just like a guy with, like, white pants and white
shirt and hat on. Like, the guy sucks. But that's the bell, so that means we're
going to get started here. If Grandpa pins the Milkman, that means that
somebody else, one of the other shitty characters, is going to come down. It's
going to be one after the other, after the other, after the other, and the only
way this can be stopped is if Grandpa goes through all of them or if somebody
ends up pinning Grandpa. So it's going to get pretty interesting. Hopefully, I
mean, the Milkman could just win right now, and that would be a pretty awful
match. So I'm assuming Grandpa has it in him to at least get through one person
or two people. I mean, as kind of sloppy and shitty that Grandpa is, Grandpa
himself is kind of a shitty character. But, you know, we won't say that too
loudly so he doesn't hear us while he sets up a neck breaker, and Milkman's
legs almost got caught on the ropes there. While Grandpa is going to go for a
pin one, he gets the one count. And typically, when you see a one count, it
means that the other person is almost totally fine. There is really no damage
being done by Grandpa. Or, what the hell was that? That was like a toddler picking
up an adult and putting him on his face. Like, that was, oh, what a reversal by
Grandpa. He's favoring the drop kicks for some reason. Grandpa really
likes those drop kicks, and he's going to go for a knee smash here into the
ground. No, that probably hurts. That probably does hurt. Going to go for
another pin, gets the one, one count again. So very clearly, this is quite a
stalemate between two weak-ass people. And Grandpa, I don't know what he's
expecting here. If he can't even go through the 30s Milkman while he gets
spun around and slammed on his back, if Grandpa cannot even go through the 30s
Milkman, how does he expect to go through six more people after this? I'm
looking at my notes here. I'm pretty sure it is six people. So, good luck to
you, Grandpa. While he lines up some type of maneuver here, really got to get his
footing there, knee smash right in the face, jumping almost on the throat there
on Milkman. Going to go for a pin, one, two, finally gets the two count on the
Milkman. So, progress is being made. As awful progress as it is, while he throws
him into the ropes there, it's still progress. And, as much as Grandpa...
You want to check the fuck up over here? You want to check the fuck up?
What the fuck are you doing? I can hear every single word you're saying.
Dude, just don't destroy the desk. Oh, no.
What the fuck are you looking at, asshole?
Fuck you, old man. Fuck you.
I just want to come see a wrestling show. I'm out of here.
See, that's what happens. You can't do that, Grandpa. He gets picked up by
Milkman. Milkman had kind of floated his way out here, somehow. But now
they're over here. No, Grandpa, no, no, no.
You think I'm a shitty character? No, this is not the time to be doing this.
You think I'm a shitty character?
This is our commentary table.
Oh, okay. All right, all right.
Yay! Go away. Thank you very much.
Milkman. Milkman, are you all right? He's not responding.
The referee has rung the bell, which means the next combatant has to go in.
He can't perform anymore. So, it's going to be the chicken.
And someone's coming from the Raptors.
Somebody just splashed off of the Titan-tron.
That's the turkey. That's the turkey. That's the chicken's long-lost rival.
I am shocked that he is able to get up and walk around after a 50-plus foot
jump right there. And there's Martin Van Buren from behind.
They're not even coming out in the right order.
This is supposed to be a gauntlet match.
It's supposed to be one after the other. What are they doing?
What triggered this? I seriously don't...
And Santa Claus is under the ring?
Santa Claus has been under that ring for probably like three hours, by the way.
Meanwhile, Grandpa, not paying any attention to who's behind him.
That's Batboy with a clothesline.
He's supposed to be dead.
Batboy is supposed to be dead right now.
But for some reason, he just snuck up behind him.
Is he even supposed to be in this?
He's not. Everybody that is supposed to be a combatant in this gauntlet
is over on the left side fighting right now.
And Batboy is in the ring.
Does this even qualify as a match anymore?
I'm not sure, but what a spinning kick.
Just laying Grandpa out, who must be pretty annoyed right now.
He went through Milkman and then was supposed to go after the chicken.
The turkey showed up. Van Buren showed up.
All these people showed up when they weren't really supposed to.
And there's just chaos going on on the left side.
I'm not sure if we can cut to that for a second.
I want you to see what's going on.
Milkman has gotten up and he is just taunting Santa Claus.
I'm not sure why, but Santa Claus and the Milkman are both going to go out of here.
No, we've got the turkey. Van Buren trying to keep the peace.
Santa Claus is going to go for a punch.
Santa Claus punches him in the face and the Milkman is not happy.
He's not happy jumping across and hitting him.
I think I saw the egg there as well.
So I don't know what's happening.
I think when you bring the term shitty character in, and this is my personal opinion,
I think this is what happened.
Everybody here, it was called a shitty character.
And I think that they are all pissed about that and trying to prove to each other
that they are not the shitty character.
But we got Grandpa with a one, a two.
Could it be? Oh, he didn't get the three count.
He just barely did not get the three count.
That was centimeters away from the three count.
And now we've got a good old fashioned slobber-docker in the middle of the ring.
Grandpa doing some right hands.
And here comes Van Buren to break it up.
I'm assuming he's on the side of Batboy, but you really never know what's going on.
Now he's getting stomped.
And here comes everybody else.
This ring is going to get flooded with people right now.
Could be a huge standoff between all these characters.
Grandpa in the corner just barely getting himself up.
And oh no.
Grandpa, you are in a world of shit right now.
But he still has at least a little bit of life left in him.
Can he take on all of these shitty characters?
Doesn't look like it. He's getting overwhelmed at this point.
Ring the bell. Ring the bell. This is over.
I've seen enough. I don't want to see any more of this.
Please just get this ring clear.
Everybody's disqualified.
We're going to move on to the next match.
We'll see you all in a few moments.
Poor Grandpa.
But you agree with me though, right?
No, I do agree with you.
I think if we can't get a hold of Captain Crunch,
no one's heard of him in like six weeks.
And the egg went to dinner with his wife.
And it's going to have to be you in the latter match.
And it's going to have to be you in the latter match. It is.
You're just telling me when to go. I'm ready.
I'll be here. I'll be in the backstage. I'll be ready whenever you need me.
You little bunch of bullshit.
This is still going on.
This is still going on backstage.
They're still beating the shit out of each other.
He's going to split his head in a car.
He just slammed his head in a car door.
Why is he pinning him?
There's no pins right now.
I think they are just all so fucking drunk
that they have no idea that they're not even in a match right now.
They might think they've been in the match the entire time.
But they're supposed to be in a cage match right now.
And they're not...
Okay, we're going to let them just fight.
This is the third match.
Okay, they're obviously not listening.
So we're going to just get right into this here.
This is a four-way backstage battle.
And the last man standing wins.
That's what I've been told by my producers.
And that's what we're going to do.
So it seems like Lumberjack Beer and King Beer
are fighting each other.
I don't know why he's calling himself King Beer.
They don't like being associated with numbers anymore, apparently.
But that's something I was told before the show started.
That it's no longer Beer No. 25.
Beer No. 300.
King Beer, by the way, looked like he was down for the count there.
But he gets back up.
And it seems like Sexy Beer
and Big Boy Beer.
That's the other two, by the way, if you're wondering.
If you're keeping track.
But who really is? They're all beers.
It doesn't really matter.
But yeah, last man standing, we've got a suplex, a tiger suplex
onto the concrete.
Remember, this is concrete.
There is no soft area for you to land on.
They're just throwing each other into stuff.
Just like that, right into the wall
goes Sexy Beer, by Lumberjack Beer.
And if I were to guess,
if I were to take a wild guess,
I'm going to say King Beer is going to win this.
Because he's the King Beer.
No, King Beer is down.
King Beer is down for the count. He's not getting up.
So is Sexy Beer. We're down to two already.
I guess I'll give them a little bit of credit where it's due.
They have been going at it for
the entire evening so far.
This is not totally unexpected
that two of them would go down.
I'm surprised any of them are standing at this point.
What a slam! He slammed his head
on the side of that wall.
That is a solid wall.
How are these two still alive?
A better question is, are the two on the ground
even still alive?
I'm not even entirely certain.
What I am certain of is
these guys are going to owe us a lot of money.
Because they told us they were going to do a cage match.
We bought the cage. It cost like
seven and a half thousand dollars to get that cage here.
And they're not even using it.
So somebody owes us a lot of money.
And I don't know who's...they have like a beer fund.
But they better pay up.
Groin kick by Big Boy Beer
to Lumberjack Beer. But he receives a couple of punches
for his trouble. And he gets...
Lumberjack Beer gets an elbow in the face which kind of
distracted him for a second. And there he goes!
Down his head! Hit the ground! That's it!
The Beer Battle Royale is going to
go to Beer 419
or Big Boy Beer
as he likes to be called.
Doing a lot of trash talking and
making his way out of the arena. And look out!
Watch out!
Who was that?
Who would do that?
I'm the only beer that matters.
Fuck all those pieces of...
We're back ladies and gentlemen with the
final match of the evening.
This is the main event
of Germania 2014
as we learned not that long ago.
This is going to be a ladder
match between Glooman
and Germa for the World
Championship of Germa
Wrestling Federation. It should be a good
one. My blood is boiling.
Let's get to the contestants.
Coming down to the arena first is going to be
Germa who does not really need
an introduction. I don't need to tell you who this guy is.
A lot of you already know and if you're just finding
this video somehow and you don't know who I am
or who this guy is, well then
hi. Welcome to Germa985.
I hope you enjoy your stay. Anywho, we're going to get to the next
contestant. The next contestant is Glooman
who is kind of
on a mission here. Glooman is
well aware that he was created as
a shitty character. Glooman is well
aware that he's just been ridiculed
and everyone thinks he's a joke. And he
is out for blood tonight. He's out to prove
everybody wrong. That not
only can you rise up from the bottom
but you can stay at the top as well.
And here's to hoping we get to see a very
good match between these two very skilled
two very skilled opponents to
each other. And we're going to get the ladders involved as well.
So ladies and gentlemen, welcome to the
main event. There is
the bell everybody. Hope you have
your popcorn ready because this one is going
to be a doozy indeed.
A lot of history here.
A lot of aggression. And a lot
of things that need to be dealt with. A lot of
problems that have to be sorted out between
these two. And this is a perfect place to do it at the
main event of Germania. The coveted
world championship of Germa
Wrestling Federation is on the line
here. This is it. This is
the one. There is no other title. There are
no other titles besides the
world championship. Unlike other wrestling
venues, there is only one.
And it is this one. What a belly
to back suplex. He back flips him.
That'll take the wind out of your sails real
quickly. He follows it up with a couple of punches
to Glue Man's face. And I
would like to address this really
really shortly. If Glue Man is made
out of glue, right? Because that's like what he's
supposed to be. He's supposed to be a man made out of glue.
How do you feel pain?
Does he feel pain? Does he break
bones? Does he have any bones?
That is a question for a scientist.
And not a question for
me. But we're going to get back to the action
here. I wanted to talk about the ladders.
Because if you're unaware, if you don't know
how a ladder match works in a
wrestling federation, essentially
it's somebody has to pull that ladder into
the ring. And the championship
briefcase is floating above
on the catwalk. So what you have to do is
you have to put the ladder down. Beautiful DDT
by the way. You have to put a ladder
down, climb up, and
grab the briefcase and rip it down.
That's the only way to win this match.
You cannot pin. There is
no giving up. It's only
climbing up that ladder. And
there are a couple of them surrounding the
ring. So their options here
are pretty varied.
They can go from either side of the ring, which looks like
Jerma might be doing it. Might be picking up the ladder for the first
time. He's got a ladder throwing it into the ring.
This is where it gets interesting.
No, they're going to stay outside.
Usually once the ladder gets put into play,
that's when you see. Oh, what a cheap
shot. What a cheap shot by
Jerma. That was disgraceful. That was
unbelievable. You don't pull that in a championship
match. Well, I guess
you do if you want to win, which Jerma
will do anything to win apparently.
Belly to belly suplex.
Glueman almost into the stairs there.
And now the Glueman is incapacitated.
It seems like Jerma is going to set the ladder up here for the
first time. Maybe he's going to hit him with the ladder.
He doesn't hit him. He gets reversed.
He blocks the ladder and pulls it out of his hands
and hits him with it. And Jerma goes down.
And this is where the ladder gets set up. What super
human strength by Glueman.
And this could be the end, ladies and gentlemen. There's the briefcase.
He's got a hold of it. Jerma's got to do
something real quick here. Grabs him
right by the coattails and pulls him down.
That was very, very close.
And something is happening. Oh, no, no,
no. No, don't even tell me this.
Are you fucking serious right now?
Captain Crunch is in the crowd
dancing and singing.
What is he doing? And what is going on with that
microphone? What kind of fucking sorcery
is going on in the crowd right now?
You have not answered any of our phone calls.
You're just going to show up in the middle of the last
match? That's unbelievable.
And all the while, we've got something climbing up on top.
Jerma and Glueman are both on top. Thank God the
cameraman got here in time. This could be the end.
Who's going to go down? Jerma with a power
bomb off of the ladder. My goodness.
Glueman is now bleeding off of his
forehead while Captain Crunch is still dancing.
He's going to hop over that little barricade
there. Are we going to see a three-way
triple threat ladder match right now?
Is Captain Crunch going to get in the ring?
We have no idea. Looks like
he is. He's grabbing another ladder.
Here we go, ladies and gentlemen. This is what
you live for. This is what you watch
for. This is a triple threat match
now between Captain Crunch, Glueman,
and Jerma. And as we see, Jerma is going to slowly
climb up here. Everybody seems
to be distracted. Jerma is very tired
going for that briefcase. Nobody is paying any
attention to him. He gets knocked over
hanging by the briefcase, and he gets picked up
by Captain Crunch and slammed on his back.
What calamity. What insanity.
And Captain Crunch, while Glueman is
lying down, Captain Crunch might be
setting up for Crunch attires me. Captain,
that's what it is. There it is, ladies and
gentlemen. That's his signature move.
He perfected that for many years.
And I just got to say this. I want to stake this
very clearly while we have a second here.
Bill, how have you not said
one single word during this
entire broadcast?
How the fuck is that even possible?
I kind of just like to watch.
Alright, well, whatever.
Back to the action now. It seems like all three
competitors are standing on their feet,
which is a pretty rare occurrence in a
ladder match. And this could be a good
opportunity here. Yup, that's a great idea.
Double teaming on Captain Crunch.
He's a fresh competitor. He has
not been running around. He's been just in the crowd
hanging out. Good idea to take
him down. And what is Jerma doing?
Why did he throw down that ladder into
the turnbuckle? That doesn't seem like it makes very much
sense at all. And Captain Crunch just gets a
triple beating. Punches in his face.
And Jerma with a nice fireman's carry
throws him over. And here comes
the ladder again. Setting it up this time
was maybe thinking about doing something in that corner
but did not capitalize while
Glooman picks up a ladder. Jerma's just going to go up.
Jerma's just going to go. What is he doing?
Why would you do that? He just
tried to climb the ladder in front of Captain Crunch
and speaking of Captain Crunch, he's in Glooman's signature
move, the tombstone. Captain Crunch
reverses it. Does the tombstone to
Glooman. This is it.
Get the ladder. Get the ladder and climb up. No.
He's signaling for his finishing move.
The captain's kick. There it is.
Captain's kick. This is going to be
the end right here. He's picking him up. Why are you picking him up?
Put him back down and climb the ladder.
He just got way too cocky right there
and it could be his downfall while
Glooman goes over to pick up the other ladder.
Where is he setting this up? What's he doing?
Captain Crunch runs into it and blocks it.
What are they doing? He's going to go for a swing.
They're both running into each other. This is it.
Captain Crunch with a beautiful double-handed swing
and pay attention to
Jerma, guys. He has been sitting down like
that for the last minute or so.
He has not gotten up and Glooman
also on the ground. Captain Crunch has
an opportunity. Got both of his hands
on it. Is this going to be the end? That's the end.
That is the end, ladies and gentlemen.
Captain Crunch is the
Jerma Wrestling Federation
Champion. What an absolutely
absurd,
insane ending to a
crazy night. I had no
idea that Captain Crunch was going to be showing up to the
arena. What's in that briefcase? Nobody
will ever know. It's probably like 30
bucks. So it was definitely worth it.
All this trouble for Captain Crunch
to come down here and win that briefcase.
So thank you all so much for
watching. It's been an absolute pleasure
bringing you Germania 2014.
And we'll see you next time.
Take care, everybody, and have a wonderful
night.