This is not fair. Here's what I'm playing with. Floppy disk, ash cheeks, Illidan from Warcraft.
He's apparently really good at this. Oh, is that you across the way? No. Oh, come on. Bot Chris.
You hit- God, you hit me. Oh, that's you. Come play, baby. Dude, that's bot Steve. Come play.
There we go. There we go. No! Is that you? Okay, listen, don't get fancy. You got a kill.
Okay, I'm actually quite happy. Damn it. Damn it. I was almost at a three piece. I know you do. I know you do.
Okay, I'm coming over.
God, how did he come over?
What's up, dudes?
Hey, get out of here. Does this guy already have a pistol? No, he didn't.
Already has a pistol. You're starting with pistols, right? Bot Bill. Good thing it's Bot Bill.
Oh my God, I just missed a bot. Oh, it's up there. Wow. Turn off your game genie. Turn it off.
Game genie? Yeah, you got like game genie up there.
Oh, what are you doing? How many times have I touched you in the face like fucking five times?
Oh my God. Can't believe you died right there. But it's okay, dude. You gotta keep trying, you know.
You just gotta hang in there. Are you behind? That wasn't me, was it? No. I'm only in third place.
I'm getting destroyed by these guys. There we go. Let's clean it up here. Let's clean it up here.
Bot Tom with a life... Jesus. Bot Tom going hard.
I'm afraid to go over there, man. I feel like he's gonna shoot me in the face.
Or that'll happen. I'll just drop down like Spider-Man and get myself killed.
Oh God, where am I? Where am I going? No! What are you doing in the spawn? What are you doing in the spawn, Jeremy?
I'm spawning. What else do you do in spawn? Yeah, I thought you were spawn camping, dude.
What are you doing in spawn is the real question. I was chasing... I was looking for you guys.
Wow. You were nowhere. That was just BS right there. I don't believe it. I called BS with that one.
Oh, I'm doing great. Oh God. Floppy disk.
Thanks for standing still, Bot Bill. Give me the free headshot.
You're getting free kills off of the bots? Come on, dude. You don't want to be that guy. Oh! No, no, no, no.
Total commit... Floppy disk, I swear. Thanks, Bot Bill.
How many free kills are you getting off Bot Bill right now? I got at least two free kills off Bot Bill.
So not fair. Are you kidding me? Get out of here. Wait, is this our spawn? Yeah, I think this is... Wow, I'm in the wrong spawn.
Did they switch? They might switch. No, I don't think... This is not called duty, dude. No, they don't switch, no.
Who's that? Okay, Wretch with a big booty. That's the picture. Yeah. That's a nice booty you got there, Wretch.
Oh, come on. No, no, no, no. No, no, no. What? I just got hit in the face. God, with that aim.
Is it a bot or no? No, that was you. Oh. Oh. Feel it. That was you with the... Hold on, let me trash talk for a bit.
Oh, get on my level. Oh. Are you mad? Are you mad? Hey, Bot Bill, stand still again so I can get some kills.
Oh, somebody just saved me. It may have been Bot Bill. Bot Bill, is that you? God, I'm getting...
I'm on the pistols right now and I'm getting screwed on. Oh. Is that you? Yeah. Good aim, dude.
Yeah, I was aiming. I hate these guns, these LMGs. Bot Bill, Bot Bill's mine. Oh, wait, it's on my team, never mind.
Whoa. That big booty of Wretch's is getting all kinds of kills on me. Make it stop. Where do you come from?
I came from behind. I don't know, I think I jumped down or I either spawned down there. Behind. Yeah, you're looking good from behind, Jerma.
Looking real good. You look beautiful. Beautiful. I can't believe it. I can't believe I didn't get that guy in the face.
No, I wish that was you. I wish that was you so bad. But no. No, but too many people. Too many people.
I'm stuck on a little like dipshit pistol. You're probably caught up with me, dude. Look at all these...
You got your whole team is over here. Don't shoot me, Jerma. No, fall damage. Are you kidding me? Well, that's embarrassing.
I've got to reset a level. Oh, mediocre, you... Suck on it. Suck on the justice.
I would have had so much joy from that. That is what we call the justice, Pinai. Get on it.
All right, all right, time to take over. This guy Rio, AD and like a pro. It's gonna be fun. Man, oh man.
I just have to wait and then strike. Get out of here. Oh, no. Wow. That was you, huh? Trying to go for the knife kill on me.
That wasn't me. No. Second and third, though, man. Ain't too bad for the first game. Let's go to the monastery.
I don't care. Here we go. Let's do it. Time to be fancy. Going up right. It's going up two o'clock. Two o'clock.
The starting route in the game. Yeah. Watch my videos for tips and tricks.
How? What the hell was that? It's almost like I was shooting a time crisis machine that wasn't calibrated.
My shots were going like five feet to the right. Somebody at the arcade didn't calibrate the goddamn light gun.
That's what it looks like. Oh, I'm getting some kills. Not gonna lie. Doing solid. Camping their spawns like a boss.
Get that guy. Yeah. Camping their spawns like a boss. Like a B.O.
I'm scared. Oh, I just came from their spawn. I just shot you.
Because I was scared. I don't know. I thought you were like an enemy. You're like trigger happy.
There we go. I'm doing some damage. Not gonna lie. Bot Chris. Playing like a badass. No.
That's like my first death in like ever. Yeah. In ever. Well, not forever, but in this game.
How did you kill that guy? And I didn't. Hey, dude. Don't be mad. Get even.
I, what? This is possible. I love playing CSGO with you, dude. Thanks.
Not gonna lie. That actually startled me. I actually got startled by what just happened. Oh, God. This guy.
What is he doing? I just stole another kill.
Dude, I'm still a level three. I should be at least at like level six.
Oh, finally. I get like a shot on somebody. Come on, Chris. There we go. Come on, Chris.
Come on, Chris. Where they at? Oh, behind. Behind. Behind.
Chasing down my bot. Ooh. Hello. I'll take you down. Where is everybody? I wanna play the game.
I'm killing them, dude. Yeah, I got him. I'm on an 18 streak. I'm doing pretty solid.
Ooh. Lucky me. That guy was just getting lit up.
I love when there's like four dudes shooting at the same guy. I know. Like, yeah, I think I'm gonna die.
Oh. Oh, no. Apparently, he has phantom bullets that were going through you and hitting me in the face.
But I think I died, so. Phantom of the Opera bullets.
Oh, bot, Chris. Get lit up. Oh, that's a lot of BS right there.
I tried. I jumped on and got the jump on him. It didn't even matter.
What happened? What the hell is this guy doing? This guy is just sitting.
Oh, no, no, no. Like, heaven forbid, I steal one of yours.
Heaven forbid. Heaven forbid you steal, like, a dozen of mine.
Dude, you stole, like, a Crayola crayon box set worth of kills from me.
There was at least 12 in that box. I want my orange and I want my blue and purple back.
Oh, well, then I'm gonna scream.
Yeah, living room set, baby. Who wants it? 799? 799? 799?
Holy crap, no!
I think somebody's on knife.
Yeah, it's almost the end of the game. You almost got me.
No! I could have gone that knife.
I'm terrified right now. I'm terrified.
Where is he? Yes!
Did you get him? On the AFK.
I had to get it. There we go.
Well, I want to thank my parents for raising me properly.
I want to thank Jerma for being a good sport while I stole all his kills.
And Gigi, that's pretty much it.
That's pretty much it.
GG.