Hey, what's happening guys? Germa here with a live commentary.
Want to talk about a couple of things. This is really, really late at night.
So, I apologize if this server has bots in it, because it probably does.
I'm not sure. Most cases are pointing to yes.
So what I want to talk about is I want to talk about a new Q&A video that I want to do.
Because a lot of people are asking about it. I got a lot of people saying,
I want to ask you more questions. Are you going to do another Q&A video?
Or what's the deal with that?
So the answer to that is yes. In the comment section in this video,
I would like you to ask a question.
Oh god, here to this century.
Oh wow, he's still there. Oh, I got it.
So I want you to ask a question in the comment section.
Anything, could be anything. Just as long as, like I said before, when I did this before,
don't do any questions like, hey, are you dumb?
Well, because you already know, yes I am. Pretty dumb.
No. You get the idea, though. Ask a real question.
Something that I can actually answer that's not ridiculous.
Something like, oh, are you excited about Skyrim?
Which, not really, to be honest with you.
Oh, we got to get rid of that century. Got it. I got it.
But yeah, I'm going to start doing this on a probably bi-weekly basis.
Maybe once every couple weeks I will do a Q&A video.
Because I know a lot of you guys have a lot of questions,
and it's fun to answer them sometimes, so I'm definitely going to do that.
Okay, what's left down there?
What? Oh, boy. Oh, boy. Scout.
Oh, I would have had him, too. Would have had him.
I could have, the sniper killed me. Oh, damn.
What do we got here?
Because I can't sleep. I have problems sleeping, guys.
A lot of my commentaries, well, they're not recorded this late,
but a lot of my commentaries are recorded during the day,
and then when I can't sleep at night, sometimes I'll just do it, and goodbye.
Ooh. By the way, if you didn't know, this is kind of a, not really a tip,
but sort of a check this out type thing.
If you hold down your, oh, let me get, oh, my God.
Oh, that would have been epic. That would have been epic.
If you hold down the left mouse button, look in the lower right,
see how I'm charging the shot?
It goes really, really far the longer you hold it.
So just something, if you didn't know, if you weren't, oh, damn.
If you, that's a great screenshot right there.
Yeah, a lot of demo men don't know that,
that you can hold down the mouse button and launch it.
Let's see how far it goes. I'm pretty sure it goes really far.
So here's the maximum.
Yeah, pretty much almost all the way to the base of that rock.
Let's try it again.
And yeah, look at that. See how far away that was?
Leaves you pretty vulnerable, because I think if you hold it down too long,
if it goes the whole way, I think it just screws you up.
Let's see.
Oh, I guess it's a little, it's long.
It goes longer when you hold it a little less, I believe, though.
All right, let's win this. Eat that sandwich.
That guy's name is KillMe.
Oh, I got him. Come on, one more.
Ah, how did that not hit?
Oh, my goodness.
You know what? There is a sentry right here, isn't there?
That guy's me. You're me, dude.
Something over here. Yep. Got it.
There we go.
Wow, the sentry was still there.
That's pretty unbelievable.
So speaking of games and questions and stuff like that,
because it's so late, because I've got nothing better to do,
I'll just ask, do you guys want to see
Grandpa play Battlefield or Modern Warfare 3?
Because he said it's like his favorite game.
And he's really excited for Modern Warfare 3.
Grandpa was freaking out when he heard
that Modern Warfare 3 was coming out.
So I don't know, if you guys want to see Grandpa
give you tutorials on how to play Modern Warfare,
let me know, because I'll definitely just be like,
hey, Grandpa, what are you doing today?
He'll be like, all right, nothing.
Why don't you make some Modern Warfare videos?
Where am I going?
Oh, I'm going the right way.
He'll probably tell me to shut up and to grow a set of balls,
because he hates me.
No, I'm just kidding.
And for those of you, I'm going to spoil the fun.
For those of you that do not know,
that is a character.
That is not real.
My grandpa, that is not real.
That's not my real grandfather.
It is, in fact, me doing a voice for fun.
It's a character I sort of created,
and I'm going to keep him.
So don't think like he's never coming back,
and it's like, I'll let the imagination...
Oh, look at all these snipers.
Oh, my God.
That was insane.
Dude, there are so many snipers.
Oh, man.
So right here, I have an HL2EXE crash.
So let's move on to later in the gameplay.
Here we go.
Oh, what's going to happen?
Am I going to get headshot by a sniper?
They're all up there.
Ooh, that was pretty dirty.
Oh, boy.
Let's do a roll here in like two minutes.
I'm going for three lives.
I should probably start.
That would be actually a pretty cool series
if you gave yourself a certain amount of lives per gameplay.
Because you guys know how I do the one-life gameplays.
But what if I did a three-life gameplay
where I start at the beginning of a round,
and I say, hey, I only get two lives,
and then I have to stop
and see what happens, whatever happens, happens.
We are rolling here.
Holy crap.
My word.
Oh, a spy.
Spy.
Where is he?
Did he get killed?
No, he's right there.
Oh, my God.
Wow, do not miss him again.
Thank goodness.
People still on the...
Oh, boy.
Nope.
Oh, there's a sentry.
There's a sentry.
Need a medic.
Need a medic sentry over there.
Still alive.
Let's see if I can't do this.
Oh, God.
Oh, well.
Two more lives.
And then I'll end it.
I'll end it.
I can definitely take that out.
I can get that sentry, no problem.
I just have to not be a freak.
You are not one of us, are you?
Yeah, you are.
All right, I'll get it.
I'll get it right here.
Maybe not.
Oh, God, the crit came over here.
Oh, crap.
I can't even go over there.
There's one.
There's two.
Oh, smart engineer is smart.
And there's another one up there.
Ah.
Bastard.
I would have had it.
Because I would have been able to kill it
when he was working on it.
All right, this is my last life.
Last life.
Here we go.
Got to get up there quick.
Bouncing around like a ping pong ball there.
That one doesn't count.
That doesn't count.
That was Bolshevik.
All right, so this is the last life.
Make it a teleporter, too.
Damn it.
Damn it, damn it, damn it.
There we go.
Okay.
Don't get shot by a sniper.
All right.
Let's see what I can do here.
Oh, I just have to get...
Ugh.
You.
No, get these away.
Ugh.
I need a medic.
This is just not possible without a medic.
We don't have a medic, do we?
Nope.
Whoa.
Oh, get him.
He's done.
Oh, thank you Mini-Sentry for saving my life right there.
All right, what do they got up there?
Nothing.
I got that.
Okay, that's gone.
That's a major, major problem.
So that's okay.
That's good.
There's definitely a sentry right here.
Yep.
Gone.
Goodbye.
Spencer.
What is another one right there?
I know it.
There's definitely another sentry right there.
Let's see if I can't make something happen right there.
Let's actually...
You know what?
Forget this.
I'm going to kill like five people.
Or two.
That works.
All right.
I can get that.
I can get that sentry.
Let's see if I can't be a little freak show here.
Goodbye, sentry.
Get on the cot.
Oh, all right.
This last life was a good one.
No.
Blow up.
Oh, boy.
We need a medic so bad.
Oh, that's the last life.
Let's see if we cap it.
Just see if we cap it.
But in the meantime, answer your questions.
Ask your questions down below.
I will start that probably in the next couple days.
I'll do a video answering some of the questions that I pick from the comments.
And you can also ask it on my Facebook and my Twitter, which are in the description.
So here it is, the final life.
Let's see if I can do something freaky.
Here we go.
Demoman away!
And we're going to cap it, right?
All right, at least we capped it.
All right.
Thanks, everybody, so much for watching.
I really do appreciate it.
And I'll see you guys all next time.
Take care, everybody.