It's not a funny Thanksgiving special. Miku Picross.
It's not a funny Thanksgiving, it's just a Thanksgiving whine downstream.
I'm gonna talk very, very lightly, very slowly.
Write ones in chat, if you just kind of got the notification that I was live.
And you're on the couch.
And you got the phone in one hand and one of your eyes are open looking at it.
And you're just kind of on the couch, just, oh shit, he's live.
I'm just gonna chill today.
I'm not gonna talk loud. I'm gonna do some Miku Picross.
What do you mean two? What do you mean two? Where are you?
ASMR Andy.
We're gonna play, alright, so let's go over this.
I know a lot of people are like, what are you doing?
I saw that Miku Picross came out two days ago. Three days ago.
I was like, oh, I remember I played that Miku game and everyone was like, oh, everyone loved it.
I love Picross.
Of course, I'm gonna play the Miku Picross game that comes out.
And I don't want to hear it from people in chat that this game came out a year ago on the Switch.
I am a PC CD-ROM player.
But yeah, let's just chill.
We're gonna do a relaxing Thanksgiving whine down.
Maybe the stream will, I don't know, maybe a couple hours, two, three hours, just to relax.
I don't need to do anything crazy today, just to chill.
Hope you had a good Thanksgiving.
In offline chat, people were saying that I should do the Thanksgiving tier list.
I already did it.
But if you just need a quick refresh.
Hold on, I don't want to like burp on you.
Okay, so Thanksgiving tier list, I believe.
Stuffing and mashed potatoes.
Stuffing is S tier. It's the highest thing.
Mashed potatoes are also somewhere around early S, maybe A.
Maybe mid A, mid S.
And there's a lot of new viewers, so let's go over this.
And I told you we were gonna relax today, but I'm gonna get a little angry right now.
Because people are gonna get mad at me and I'm gonna get angry back.
This is the only time we're gonna get an elevated vocal range here, okay?
So I think that canned cranberry sauce is 100 times better than real cranberry sauce.
The stuff that's in the can, that comes out and it's shaped like a can when it comes out.
Like a cartoon.
And when that, listen, when you turn that sideways so it's the shape of the can cranberry sauce.
It's more like a cranberry jelly.
Exactly.
You turn it sideways and you slice hockey pucks.
A little bit thinner than a hockey puck.
But hockey puck, hockey puck, hockey puck, hockey puck.
Spatula that up, get it on your plate.
You now have the opportunity to take cranberry jelly, cranberry sauce whenever you want.
It's not gonna get all over everything.
Sometimes you don't want cranberry sauce all over your mashed potatoes and the turkey and the potato, you know what I'm saying?
It gives you the opportunity to take a sliver of that cranberry puck and put the cream cheese spread it onto the turkey.
It's, I'm telling you, that's S+.
Hockey, like hockey puck size, not hockey puck texture or flavor.
It had to be, okay.
It had to be hovered right over the end stream button and I pressed space accidentally.
Well, all right.
I'm live, I'm here.
What a bad stream.
Can you imagine?
I just go live for two minutes to talk about how much I like hockey puck cranberry sauce and leave.
That actually is kind of funny and I could have just stuck with that.
I apologize for those of you that, let's get, should I explain this again for everyone that just came back?
I need to explain this because people are gonna be like, what the fuck happened?
Wait for people to refresh.
You have 20 more seconds.
Okay.
All right.
So I'm imagining people have refreshed.
Let's just go over really quickly what just happened.
So I hit the, I hit the go live button on my OBS over here and didn't move the mouse.
I just press go live and now here I am.
And I'm talking to you, right?
Like after a minute or so, I didn't move the mouse.
So I accidentally in a rage talking about the cranberry sauce, hit space bar, which is confirm.
And it was hovering over the end stream button because I never moved the mouse.
There you go.
So now I don't, I don't have to explain it again.
I wish we should probably wait another few minutes and I'll explain it again for people to refresh another five minutes or so.
All right.
So today it's going to be a chill Miku Picross stream.
I don't have no idea what's in this game.
All I know is that I love Picross and I mean, I've played the Miku game.
Why not?
These are two things that are real.
I'm, I've played them.
Yeah.
We're only going to be live for maybe a couple of hours.
I just want, I don't know.
I want to do this thing.
I want to start doing more of this.
I kind of had this like epiphany and this is, I'm like not joking around.
I'm like, I mean this completely and fully.
I kind of like the idea of every so often just going live and it's, we just kind of chill and hang out maybe for a couple hours or something.
Just randomly.
I like that idea a lot.
A little bit more low energy stream sometimes because I feel like I'm so high energy all the time.
And that's like the only thing you ever see.
Right.
Like I'm always like so high energy, but like it's like, it's like five, six o'clock in the afternoon, evening.
I think we maybe I could maybe we get a couple of chill streams every now and again.
Right.
I know.
And look, you can have a chill stream and scream sometimes.
I know that sounds weird, but it happens.
But I know I'm going to just chill out.
I know that I'm going to get the question wrong and I'm going to scream, but it's all right.
We're still chilling out.
We're just hanging out.
Right.
You need to hit the bong.
No, no.
But I'll tell you, that's where opportunities like me strong playthrough.
Right.
Bring back the comb streams.
Yeah.
That's what I mean.
We could have, you know, this high energy streams and there's low energy streams.
I think it's a nice experiment to see how this works.
But I'm ready.
How do you have a low energy stream when like Miku is just banging like just blaring in the background?
Like when Miku is just like, what's the song?
No, that was wrong.
I did the wrong song.
That was Nyan Cat.
Everybody chill out.
This is supposed to be a relaxing night.
That was Nyan Cat.
All right.
I'm sorry.
I've got it wrong.
Isn't there?
No, no.
I had it right.
I did have it right.
That's a Miku song.
I'm telling everybody.
This is a real Thanksgiving relax stream.
True Miku fan.
That's right.
So when that's just blaring in the background, it's going to be hard to relax.
All right.
Everybody relax.
We need to collectively just hang out.
Okay.
All right.
I'm pressing the button.
You guys hear it?
I can't hear it.
When is the chill going to happen?
We're chilling as of exact.
Hey, look, I'm early too.
The stream hasn't even started yet.
You can play Fall Guys.
I'm not going to ever play Fall Guys ever again.
I'm just telling you, that's a fact.
I don't have anything against the game.
I'm just never playing that game ever, ever again.
It's a fun, cute game.
It's like a fun experience.
I'm just never going to play it ever again.
That's it.
Face reveal.
All right.
So here we go.
Picross is fun.
If you've never played it before, you're about to see how it works.
I know I'm not going to.
Okay.
Last time I played Picross, I explained how the Picross worked every 30 seconds.
So I'm not going to do that tonight.
We're just going to chill and play it.
What happened to your face?
I haven't shaved in like a week.
That's what happened.
Okay.
So normal puzzles, special puzzles, music, gallery, settings.
I already did the settings a little bit.
Listen to music and unlock new songs.
How do I do that?
I need money.
Well, you guys have to tell me which one you think is good.
Oh, we can unlock music.
Why does your chin have cell shading?
I don't know.
All right.
Let's play.
Happy Thanksgiving, everybody.
Hope you had a good one.
Hope you had a lot of turkey, a lot of and all that good stuff.
All right.
So here we go.
So these are going to be really easy.
It's going to be like, it's going to be impossible for me to lose these.
Let's go.
Level one.
Here we go.
Wait, I can move the camera.
Actually, that's not a bad place for it.
This is fine over here.
Is there a timer?
There is.
All right.
So how Picross works?
I'm not doing that.
Stop.
OK, there's five.
I didn't mean to press that.
It just went over there.
I'm restarting.
OK.
That's that row of five.
All five.
There's five.
Do I have to explain this?
All right.
So hold on.
Paint.
What does check?
Because X is mark.
B is check.
Oh, OK.
I like doing it like that.
I'm not doing a hint.
So let's just go over this real quick.
Explain.
All right.
I'll explain.
OK.
Shit, I have to explain.
This is a relaxing stream.
OK.
So Picross is a video puzzle.
But you can do it on paper, too.
But so the first...
My chin is real, I swear.
OK.
So how you play Picross is...
You see the numbers on the...
I'm getting trolled.
OK.
So there's the two.
There it is.
So what do we make?
How does this game work?
Let's go type in, like, how does pic...
Oh, I unlocked some artwork.
Oh, my God.
There's a lot of stuff here.
Wait a minute.
Can't I already see it?
Cool.
There's a lot of levels.
All right.
I'm down.
OK.
I'm...
People are not going to stop saying it, so I'm going to explain it very quickly.
OK.
Let's do it very quickly.
In under 30 seconds.
If I go over 30 seconds, I'll turn the screen off.
The left and right are numbers, which indicate how many cubes need to be filled in in that
row or column.
For instance, there has to be five filled in long ways here because the five at the
top is how much needs to be there.
So we know it has to be all five because there's only five spaces.
By the way, if you see a space between the numbers, there has to be at least one cube
of free space between these two numbers.
So for instance, I'm not going to do it, but here and here, right?
There has to be at least one space between these two numbers going down.
Here's your explanation.
If you don't understand it, read a fucking book.
It wasn't 35 seconds.
We're relaxing today.
Was it 30 seconds?
Which book?
I don't know.
What was the last book you guys read?
Well, we know it can't be...
And by the way, this is very important.
Two can't be over here.
It has to be sequential.
So this is the one.
There has to be a space, which is here.
So therefore, there needs to...
The two is here.
That's how it works.
You read the Bible the last book is you read.
Okay.
All right.
New artwork.
What is it?
I don't know.
What are these pictures?
I'm not even looking at the pictures.
Okay.
What's your favorite book?
I actually haven't read a book in a long time.
Bad.
Although I don't know.
I've...
I have read...
I think the world has completely changed in a way.
What I mean by that is...
So there's a lot of information you can read online.
There's a ton of articles and news programs.
And there's a lot of reading that you do on a regular basis.
That's not out of a book.
So you are still reading.
You're not necessarily...
I mean, I don't necessarily read novels anymore, right?
I don't really...
Not that I can remember.
But I do a lot of reading.
Yeah, the five by fives are always very easy.
When can I unlock new songs?
Reddit doesn't count.
No, I'm not...
Look.
I'm just saying that you do read a lot on a daily basis.
It's not necessarily a novel, but you are reading a lot.
Okay.
How many...
Oh, there's a whole...
Oh, level one.
Level two.
What else is here in level...
All right.
So we're going to...
I'll get through these quick.
Can you lower the sound effects?
Are they loud?
Sounds too loud?
Turn the music up and the sound down?
Is that what you want?
Because I can do that.
Music's a little loud.
Is that a little better?
Music's too loud?
Is that better?
I think we're in a good spot, right?
There's special puzzles, too.
All right.
Let me get some money so we can make some...
Unlock some stuff.
All right.
Let's see.
So remember, this is where it gets interesting because obviously one, two, three, it could be there.
It could also be one, two, three.
Therefore, what have we deduced, everybody?
If it has to be three going this way and there's only five spaces, what have we deduced?
Exactly.
Nice work.
And again, what...
Guys, what can we deduce from this row?
It has to be a space in the middle.
How can we deduce it?
What do you think?
I mean, what do I have to deduce this from?
One, space, then three.
You get it now.
You guys get it.
By the way, Picross is probably one of the most relaxing fun games I've ever played.
There are a hundred million versions of what you are seeing on the screen.
It's on every app store.
It's on every single device.
You can find it.
It's a lot.
So if you like this, you go, oh, well, this is cool.
I wish I had like a hundred billion puzzles to do.
They exist.
All right.
So what have we deduced here?
Here's what we've deduced here.
I actually want to do that because this is physically not possible.
If we know these two are here and this is a three in this in this down and up and down.
It cannot possibly be here.
You guys get it.
You understand?
No one's too dumb.
No one's dumb enough to not know this.
Okay.
That was pretty good deduction right there.
All right. So this is three.
And there it is.
What the deuce?
Why did you just say that?
You guys want me to look at every picture that comes up?
Or should we just wait and just go through the gallery later?
Please.
God.
No.
I think you're the only person that said that.
There were.
It's okay.
This chat moves pretty fast, right?
It's hard sometimes to pick up what everybody's saying.
But that was I think three nos and every single other person said yes.
I kind of feel bad for the people that said no.
It's like shit.
There's like 96 percent majority that said they want to see this.
Okay, cool.
I feel bad for them having no taste.
Well, I mean, come on.
This is going to be a quick one.
That's a world record.
I think that puzzle that might be the world record because I might be one of them.
I don't know how many people played that level and went that fast.
I probably in the top 20.
I love these mini cans.
What is it?
Pog Pog Pog.
You guys like this character?
The little cans are great because so the bit I don't like drinking an entire huge soda
unless I don't know why this is the way this is.
But let's go over this.
Oh, it just got absolutely real.
By the way, this is now real.
Those were little warm up rounds.
But now is where you have to really start to pay attention.
Some of these hit cross games can get to be 25 20 by 20 50 by 50 sometimes.
They get they get kind of crazy.
But anyway, so look at this.
Look at how difficult this is.
So there's a two down here.
But where where the heck would that be?
A little bit of deduction.
How many was it?
What is it?
10 by 10.
So this is 10 by 10.
So take a look at this.
This is very interesting.
This dream is so funny.
It's like you're showing your grant.
What are you saying?
Like you're showing your grandkids anime that you don't understand.
Reduce this.
Wait, I'm showing my grandkids anime that I don't understand.
What does that mean?
I understand half of this because it's Picross.
So I can tell you about the Picross part.
I can't tell you about all the Miku characters, dude.
Okay, my grandmother one time.
My grandmother.
She she bought a hat one time and she bought this hat and she wore this hat all the time.
It was kind of one of those hats as a flip hat where it's got all the way around.
It was like not a beanie, but has like a brim on it.
So she wore this hat all the time and she didn't know what was on it.
She didn't know what was on the hat and what was on the front as a graphic.
A bucket hat, yeah.
So on the front of this hat was a graphic of the four South Park kids.
She had no idea what they were.
She thought they were just four cute young cute boys.
Like she just thought it was like kids.
She did not know that they were the South Park kids.
So that was kind of endearing.
And I feel like I'm am I doing that right now?
And it'd be like, oh grandma, you know, that's from a TV show.
Oh, the TV show with the four young cute young boys.
Yes, of course. I know that one.
Yeah, it was and she wore it all the time.
Did you deduce that? You should have.
Like she saw them as like little grandkids, not as kind of crass television.
OK, so here's what happened. Let's deduce it.
So what we've done here, you're probably wondering.
Jerma, I mean, you're so smart and everything you say so intelligent.
Help me. I'm having trouble.
So we filled in almost the whole bottom row.
What can we do now?
We now that this see the two and the seven at the top.
This is guaranteed to be these seven.
So all we have to do this. I love when this happens.
It's so much fun. One, two, three, four, five, six, seven.
And look what we've done over here.
We have deduced so much. Stop explaining.
I beg you. Your brain, your monkey brain takes too long.
That's not you're not chilling out, man.
Shut up. Shut up. You're an idiot.
This is not I don't see anybody chilling here.
I see people being rude.
It's supposed to be a chilling out time.
All right, so let's go.
Remember that? OK, no more explaining.
Actually, that sound kind of is annoying, isn't it?
Yes, that's the hat.
Somebody in sub streams put it up.
That's the hat. It's in sub stream right now.
That is the exact hat that my grandmother wore for years.
Yeah. OK, I'm going to turn this sound.
I'm going to turn the sound off. I don't like it after this one.
All right. So let's get going.
Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Two.
Cool that it fills that in automatically.
A lot of these games don't do that.
Perfect chill time. I actually don't.
Please explain to us.
Why are you treating why are you treating this like Citizen Kane?
I'm trying to figure out what that what that person means.
I'm treating this.
Somebody said I'm treating this little Sudoku puzzle like Citizen Kane.
What does that mean?
I just don't I just don't understand.
Here's the tricky part.
So this is going to go this way that way.
Oh, that goes to part of the five.
That's the one playing pick across alongside you.
Oh, let's see.
One, two, face one, two, three, four, five.
So what is this picture?
A dove. Oh, we got some artwork.
I didn't even talk about the little cans.
OK, so the little cans are the perfect size because how many ounces is it?
Let's see. Seven and a half ounces.
So it's almost eight ounces.
You get a big thing ice and you can just keep pouring this
in and pretend like you're drinking a full can.
So it's easy to hold.
I like it small.
I think I'll be able to clear this whole first and second page in the next like 20 minutes.
All right. This time, I'm not going to say anything.
It's up to you to deduce this because I'm just going to do it without your help.
I might need it eventually, but whatever.
I think I can get this. I think I can get it.
OK, let's just assume this is the first one, which it is because it's telling me.
So that's one.
Let's say it's the other one is right here next to it.
That means I think this is what that means.
And that is exactly what it means.
OK, that's the is this the second?
So this is the second one.
That means this has to be here.
The other one is right here.
Take what else is that helping with one or one?
That's one.
And then it's three.
So this game actually helps a lot because what's you know, it's what's happening.
A lot of the a lot of pick cross games don't do this.
It won't see on the left here next down here.
See down here.
That one being grayed out is telling me this is that one.
A lot of them don't do that.
So this actually is a lot easier than a lot of typical pick cross games.
So that's it's cool.
So I know that this is the first one.
That means that these nothing else can be over here.
So now I want to know.
I don't know if this is part of the two part of the four.
I don't know that yet.
My cousin could beat your ass.
All right.
Well, that's that's fine.
Don't be true.
So this is the one.
So that's really that's really good to know comfy.
Yeah, good guys.
Wicked handsome.
Okay, I'm being distracted.
So this is three.
This is the one and there's two three, four, five, six.
That's two.
Very nice.
Almost there.
Nice.
Wait, what'd you say?
Somebody said something here.
This is important.
Would you say something you asked?
We talked about this.
What the hell is you just right?
It was about how you okay, I asked an NPC in a dream for an invention idea
and she said something to me, but I forgot telling you.
You have to be make sure you get up and write it down.
Something about your dream.
We let's go over it one more time very briefly.
If you are in a dream.
Have you ever noticed that when you're in a dream?
Oh Christmas tree when you're in a dream people if you if you ask certain people
in your dreams about stuff, it will give you such unbelievable.
Oh my God.
I completely forgot about this.
Let me read this.
Okay, so I was a little high.
This is that this is out of absolutely nowhere, but I'm going to read this.
So I was kind of high and I wrote something that I think is unbelievably profound.
I remember just being like high sitting on the couch and going I have to write this now.
So I wrote this down.
This is I was a little bit high and I wrote this and I think it's incredibly profound.
So let me read it to you.
And this you might think this is coming out of nowhere, but it's it just kind of popped
in my head like oh like when you don't ever watch like for instance,
like some of the old videos that I have, you know back in like the TF2 era or back in whatever era,
you know, if you see like an old picture of you or something you like wow, look at that person.
Here it is.
This is about the preservation of audio and video preservation of audio and video.
Okay, and photos.
I haven't read this in a while.
So it's been like it's been like a week or so.
So I don't know how fucking stupid this might be, but I'm just going to go for it.
I feel like I'm going to give like a class presentation.
I think the Miku sound out of my ear.
Okay, preserving video and audio is slightly uncomfortable
because it's like time traveling to confront or combat your past self.
Needing to revisit almost a different person who no longer exists.
You aren't the you from before and you can feel it.
Your memories almost clash into each other when you think or see back,
almost like two different people's feelings agreeing and disagreeing at the same time.
You are the same, but that person doesn't exist.
It only exists because it lives in your brain.
That person will never exist again.
It's only a fleeting part of your mind.
And your accounts are all you have.
Memories turn into well-acted plays that you yourself start becoming the audience for.
What about that?
Did I read all the live tweeting of Poopy Halloween I did?
Vsauce made that video already?
Oh, whatever.
All right.
Let me see.
Oh, this, I also wrote this really high and this is wicked funny.
All right, ready?
I wrote this high.
I always try to keep track of things I'm saying.
So when I was high, this is like a few weeks ago.
I had another, I had a million-dollar idea and you guys are going to laugh,
but I don't, maybe you don't.
Million-dollar idea.
Fruit sweatshirts slash hoodies slash merch line with solid colors
and matching fruit patch of same color.
Banana slash bright yellow, strawberry slash bright red.
Like, wow, that sounds fucking actually pretty sick.
Okay, what else we got?
There's all the Hubby Halloween stuff.
Okay, so yeah, let me go over this.
I watched Hubby Halloween, the Adam Sandler movie.
And let me go over it.
I live tweeted the whole thing, but I never, I never tweeted it.
Do you want me to do the whole thing?
You want me to do the whole thing?
It's like, it's like two pages.
Okay, let's start.
So, let's start.
So this is the entire Hubby Halloween movie from start to finish.
I wrote just my thoughts on it as the movie went on.
Mute the music.
I'm watching Hubby Halloween.
I don't know what this movie is about or who the fuck this guy is.
It's been 40 minutes.
Why is he walking around a high school dance?
Why is this guy in the movie?
Why are they all so fucking mean to this guy?
Ha ha ha ha ha ha.
He has a magic superhero thermos.
He can throw it like Captain America's shield.
It can turn into anything.
Literally any object he needs in that current scene.
Is he a superhero?
It just made him food.
I think that's what was implied.
He poured a bunch of food into it and it made a smoothie.
Okay.
And then that's when I stopped doing draft tweets and I went to my notes.
Okay, and then it goes here.
Okay, here we go.
Wait, why are they on a scary road now?
Someone just threw a trash can at him while he was on his bike.
They are trying to kill him.
People are trying to fucking kill this guy.
This is major spoilers, by the way.
Why do we care that Walter is a werewolf?
Who is Walter?
Who is this other guy?
There are missing kids?
Wait, where was Hubby last seen?
I don't remember.
Were these kids with him?
He's not related to these people and he's shitting in their house.
He didn't wipe his ass and he waddled off the toilet.
A dog just ate his own shit on camera.
I'm serious.
That's what I just watched.
The dog is evil or was that the Walter guy?
What was the grenade?
He doesn't know he's in a haunted house and macing people.
Who is Paul Blart's character a parody of?
It seems like they want to tell you so bad.
It's really heavy-handed and I don't know.
They are pissing their clothes and they got caught.
The werewolf?
And the other guy, they're peeing their pants on a bench.
The world's going crazy now.
People are throwing rocks at him.
Shaq is now the narrator of the movie, but it's someone dubbing Shaq's voice.
Shaq is now a major character in the movie.
His wife's voice is dubbed too.
The police are doing a sting operation with Hubby.
They're trying to catch his high school crush?
The school crush is a demon?
They loved each other all along?
The killer is in the house.
Spoilers by the way, I'm serious.
Mom is the killer?
Are they all outside?
They're all, no one is dead.
She's pouring gasoline on them.
Just take the gas can away.
What the fuck, she's like 90.
It's, just get it.
He's contemplating letting them burn.
They were apparently bullies?
This whole scene was on TV?
Everyone just laughed and said there is no reason at all to dislike him.
They're laughing about it.
The whole cast is saying sorry.
And what about the werewolf?
Why were they trying to hurt him?
Like trying to hurt him, it was just no reason.
Mom is explaining how to be nicer to people and disappeared into the woods?
All these guys watch is Hubby.
Is this a joke?
She's acting like it's a prank.
He makes gadgets, like I don't get it.
He had super powers from Salem?
It is now a screaming compilation at the end.
Ha ha ha ha dude, I'm dying.
It's like I'm watching a YouTube compilation of Sandler screaming.
That's all I wrote.
The movie was crazy.
That movie was out of control.
I remember as I was watching it, I was like, I don't, I was also a little high.
I think you're noticing a theme here.
Honestly, if you watch Hubby Halloween, you're going to sit there and be like,
what is going on here?
What is happening right now?
You were not a little high.
The movie is just, it's just crazy.
It's just crazy stuff happening.
The sound effects volume, I'm sorry.
Imagine if the TV was turned off.
No, no, I'm telling you, if you go back and watch Hubby Halloween,
you're just simply going to go, wait, all the stuff he said like happens in this movie.
There's a part, I'm not kidding, there's a part where a dog is just eating his own shit.
And it's like, what's going on?
Why is this dog doing this?
It was just like, what's happening?
It was all right.
I did watch it.
I wasn't high.
Everybody relax.
Turn the sound effects down.
Was it a dream journal?
No, I just, I was kind of high and I was,
like it was like Halloween time.
I'm like, I'll only put it on.
Is that better?
Just having no sound?
Let's see.
It might be better.
Is that your zonked journal?
Yeah, it kind of is.
There you go.
There's like the last few times I've been a little high
and I just write stuff down and I just wrote down like a whole Vsauce video.
Well, I thought I was being so profound.
I remember sitting there looking at that and just being like,
this is like potentially like Nobel Prize winning shit.
Turned out it was just a Vsauce video.
Okay, this one's going to be hard.
What should I do first here?
3, 4, 4, 5, 6, 7, 8.
I don't know.
5, 6, 7, 8.
What can I start with?
Maybe the 5.
Let's see.
3, 4, 5, space, 1, 2.
Really, what can I deduce here?
4, 5, 6, 7, 8.
3, 4, 5, 6, 7, 8, 9.
Because if, let's see, if it was like this,
it was like boom, boom.
Boom, boom, boom, boom.
That would mean that this would have to be 1, 2, 3, 4.
1, 2, 3, 4.
So it has to be here, one of these.
3, 4.
So by deduction, it has to be these two and it is.
That doesn't help though.
Chest level gameplay.
We're just chilling out today.
I read you some more drafts.
There, aren't you happy?
Let me see.
I'm going to, I'm going to go for it.
It was wrong.
Reset it.
Okay.
It's okay.
I got it now.
This does help a lot because now this is the 1.
This is 5.
So right, if we give a count of 1, 2, 3, 4, 5.
Boink.
1, 2, 3, 4, 5.
Cheated.
That's not cheating.
That's just deducing by failure.
I learned from my failure.
Can't hide the fact that you tore your pants like a barbarian
because you were too lazy to stand up.
No, I didn't want to stand up because I, I know.
There's no reason for me to tell you why.
I just didn't stand up because I felt like it.
That's it.
Okay, 3.
Well, it can't be here.
Oh, look what I just did.
Now it opens up.
It's that.
All right.
This is probably, I think this is all ones though.
It's annoying.
1, 2, 3, 4, space 1.
Let's just assume.
We can't assume.
Maybe we can.
1, 2, 3, 4.
1, 2, 3.
No, we can.
So that means that it has to be 1, 2.
It has to be here and here.
So we can do that.
That's correct.
This is also a 1.
That's the first one.
So there you go.
And there's another one here.
Okay, so that's 4.
That's 1, 2, 3, 4.
1, 2, 3, 4.
We don't know.
We can't decide that.
Is everyone relaxing?
Somebody said this game sucks.
I want them banned for at least one full minute.
It's always hard when you have very small numbers
with large gaps.
Because this is the 1.
At some point from here to here is another 1.
And it's just hard to know where it is.
I'll get it though.
All right, so I think I can do this though now.
So this is 2.
1, 2, 3, space 1.
Got it.
Very cool.
This is the part of the 3.
1, 2, 3.
Can't be here.
This is 1.
That's very helpful.
This is part of the 4.
1, 2, 3, 4.
Very nice.
You're never going to win this game.
I guarantee you I do.
I would bet.
I bet you I complete this level.
I bet you $100 trillion that I will compete.
I will beat this level.
There's no time limit.
I will just this level will this level right here
that you're seeing on the screen right now.
I will finish it.
It'll do the thing and it'll give us whatever the thing that
I'm going to finish it.
But don't worry.
It's literally impossible for me to not finish this exact
level right here.
Nobody's going to nobody's going to like, you know,
monkey paw me, right?
It's like this is what I'm telling you.
I'm telling it's a hundred trillion dollars that I will
beat this exact screen right here.
I will beat this this level right now level 1-008 and
there's no time limit.
This is part of the 3.
This is also might be the 3.
I think that's the 4 right here.
It's not over.
No, it's not.
What do you mean?
It's not no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
Stop that.
No, you didn't.
I didn't say I couldn't make any mistakes.
I just said I was going to complete this level.
I didn't say it.
And by the way, there were no mistakes allowed.
When did I say that?
That was not but don't curl that monkey paw.
It's not happening ever.
This is chill stream.
I never said it by the way.
I'm not allowed to make a single purple X.
No, I just said I'm going to complete the level you get.
You can talk all the shit you want.
That's not the case.
I like the music chill.
I don't have anything in this role, but it can't be here.
That's beer all starts coming together now.
What are you smoking?
I'm not smoking anything.
I'm drinking a can of Sprite.
Big hand.
Why can't I just drink like a normal person?
Sprite.
I like Sprite.
Sprite's very simple.
It's very just it's just like a sweet bubbly drink.
This whole stream is going to be claimed.
I think like this whole stream is going to be muted.
So I'm glad you're here chilling out on Thanksgiving Day
wind down.
This entire stream is going to get muted.
Just to let you know.
Hey, but the thing is though you might not even need sound
because if you just watch me play the game you see kind of
my what my deductions and stuff.
You can still enjoy it.
Just put on your own soundtrack.
I do like 7up.
I like 7up more than Sprite in the flavor department,
but Sprite is a little lighter, right?
7up I think is better tasting than Sprite,
but Sprite is lighter.
So if you want a lighter drink, you know, that's what I choose.
That one was simple.
Now this is going to be really really good for us.
Very nice.
Always great when you get this fill in here.
That's so good.
You can you do a tier list about this already?
But Miku?
I don't I only know like four songs three songs from Miku.
All right, so let's go.
It's easy.
This is eight.
Yeah, this one.
Wow, this one was easy.
It's got to get one.
Everything is just connected.
Everything's connected.
This one was very easy.
Yeah, necktie.
We have to check out every single picture.
That's what was voted on.
So did tier list.
I did every one of those already.
So what a tier list, please.
I already I did it already.
You guys want you guys want reruns?
You want me to do reruns?
But maybe my tastes have changed.
It's true.
Unlock some songs.
All right.
Where do I go for that?
So set your favorite characters.
Oh, wait a minute.
Who is the characters?
What character should I have?
Maybe everyone was talking.
Everyone was saying this character Luca.
Okay.
Puzzles on keyboard.
How to play credits sound.
All right.
How do I unlock songs?
Special music.
All right, unlock new songs.
How much money do I have?
I have 26 cents.
How much is this?
How much does it cost to unlock?
What song should I unlock?
I don't know what songs are.
Do you see anything you like?
Where's uh, where's that?
Is it here?
It's called peep.
Oh people.
Is it here?
That one.
I mean, I it's like a five second delay.
Which one?
I'm just gonna I'm just gonna do this one.
All right.
How about 393 150?
Shuffle.
Okay, this one sounds pretty good.
The butterfly on your shoulder.
Now it's the chair.
How about this one?
I was already laughing.
I need more stars.
All right.
We have it on shuffle.
We got it on shuffle.
This is I like this.
This is relaxed.
You're 42.
Not no, I'm not close, but I'm not getting there.
Wait, why is this playing?
What?
Reset it.
It's eight.
Oh, it's eight.
Eight.
I'm an idiot.
I went too far down.
What a fly on your shoulder is the song name.
Oh, well, I looked over and I see this.
I was like that.
What is that?
Oh, I really genuinely thought you meant that.
This one should be another easy one.
I think so.
Yeah, it will be.
Look at this.
Love it.
Perfect.
I mean, I want to say it's right here.
Kind of has to be.
Okay, so four.
Very cool.
Two.
Nice.
Four.
One.
Nice.
Three.
Done.
This is also a one.
So it has to be here.
It's also one.
It has to be here.
This is the six.
So I mean, even if it's one, two, three, four, five, six, it has to be there.
And it has to be here.
Oh, I didn't mean to do that.
I pressed the button a little too much.
But actually that's fine.
Okay.
Nice.
Jeremy, can you cover yourself in oil?
Just like all of, what do you...
Time that person out.
Time that person out for like five minutes.
That person needs to be timed out for like five minutes at least.
When he can.
I have to go to the settings.
All right.
We'll do it or no.
How you guys doing?
You guys have a good, uh, I'm gonna say Halloween.
You guys have a good Thanksgiving?
This is a chill stream.
Yeah, it is.
Oh, all right.
So it's in here.
Oh, okay.
Background music settings.
Just haven't been anything, right?
It's gonna shuffle then.
Oh, I have to set it.
Will it just shuffle?
Is it the only one through that I have?
I was gonna pick this one.
I don't celebrate.
Well, if you do, then you do.
Get at the bottom.
How do I, um, make it so it will?
I don't know how to do it.
I just picked one.
Let's see what it is.
Is it different?
Oh, okay.
Ooh, this is cool.
I didn't mean to do that.
I can't use the analog anymore.
Six.
This one's five.
Oh, this is juicy.
Look at this.
This is juicy.
That's, look at how juicy that was.
Not even done either.
Oh my God.
That was juicy.
Can't be there.
Gotta be here.
There.
Wait, what?
What?
What happened?
Oh, I'm an idiot.
I went too fast.
I should have known because that was, that was the two.
Well, I went too fast.
That was juicy.
It was juicy.
What?
Stop saying that.
Why not?
What do you mean stop?
Stop saying juicy.
What's wrong with everybody today?
I can't say this was a juicy one.
Why?
You have 18,000 people watching you play Picross.
I don't know.
Dude, come on.
I feel like that's like insulting to me.
Like what?
Is that for you?
Was that an insult?
What was that?
Is that gonna insult?
Oh, you think I'm funny?
What?
I'm funny to you?
Well, funny how like how?
Funny when I amuse you?
Funny like a clown?
No, tell me.
I want to know what you fucking mean by that.
I should say you say funny things.
I say funny things, huh?
Well, like I amuse you.
That is one of the best scenes.
Like that scene is crazy.
Not a big deal.
That's classic.
That's a classic one.
Hey, I think there's people here because it's in the title.
How many people have eaten their Thanksgiving turkey?
And they're on the couch just sitting there with their phone going like this.
I didn't press the button.
Here's a quick tip for you.
If you want to know about Picross, if it's one large number,
just count the amount it takes to get to whatever the fold of the cap here is,
which is 10.
And that's what's left on both sides.
So let's say it's seven.
You're going to leave three on both sides because seven plus three is ten.
So therefore the middle four will be filled in.
That's an easy way to do it.
And for all of you that are going to be playing it later this afternoon.
How is it?
Whatever.
Yeah, thanks for the tip.
Play Professor Layton?
No, I can't play that game.
That game pisses me off.
I actually get angry when I play that.
It's just like all the all the so many of those puzzles in Layton just get so
my brain just can't do it.
I'd rather just play Picross.
Okay, so can I do anything with six?
Six, I can.
Again, leave four on both sides because that has to be the middle ones and therefore
look what we just did.
Layton is pretty tough.
It is.
And that's it's fun.
I just I get to a point in Layton where I get to the first ten puzzles and then they
get too hard where I go.
I don't really care anymore.
It was fun while it lasted.
Oh, this is eight one.
Okay, that would be part of the five.
One, two, can't be there, can't be there, can't be there.
So then this is interesting.
One, two, three, four, five.
Can't quite put something here because I don't know but I could actually.
Yeah, I could.
Is it two?
He's in music.
Jerma, you are fucked up.
What did I do?
I want you to explain to me what I did in the last 10 to 25 seconds.
In the last 30 seconds, I did something so fucked up that you wrote that.
But what did I do?
All I've been saying is okay, so that's one, two, three, four, five.
Okay, there it is.
And there's two.
What did I do that was that screwed up right there?
I want to know.
Tell me.
Oh, dude, you are so fucked up.
And what's your language by the way?
That's the middle two.
So can I go this?
I can but I don't know that yet.
This is obviously the two but it could be either one of these spots.
I don't know.
Turn the music down.
You understand that there are like at least a half dozen Miku fans in here that
it can be very mad at me if I turn the music down.
At least a half dozen.
You're like I'm missing something that I can do right now.
Five?
Yeah.
Okay.
Well, the one is here.
All right, that helps.
Two, three, four, five, six.
Three, four, five, six.
Oh, there we go.
Nice.
That has to be over here.
This is a one so it could be here.
This is also a two so it could be here as well.
Yeah, two in the top row is done.
That's true.
Then this five, one, two, three, four, five.
There it is.
Okay, so that's not available.
This is available.
This is not four.
This is four.
And now this is part of the two.
I think it's here, but I don't know that for sure yet.
So I'm not going to do it.
One, two, three, four, five, five, six.
One, two, three, four, five, six.
What?
How?
What did I do wrong?
Wait, what happened?
Two, one.
Uh-oh.
Oh, I mean I marked it wrong.
Shit.
Oh, that's what happens when you deduce wrong.
Sorry, I'm good.
You scared Luca.
What do you mean I scared Luca?
Oh.
A headset.
That's okay.
That's cool.
Dude, this guy deduces.
Sorry, I have a full plate of spaghetti over here.
So I changed it.
What should I put the music to then?
Because I have to set it for the puzzle background music.
You guys have to pick one.
Which one of these should be puzzle background music?
These are instrumental.
That's why.
Okay.
What about this one?
These are all instrumental.
Third one.
May I?
Okay, one, two.
Yeah, we'll do this one.
I don't know.
You're the Miku expert.
I'm not a Miku expert.
Guys, I thought Miku was somebody actually singing until a year and a half ago.
I don't know.
I didn't know very much.
I thought it was a gorilla's scenario.
That just shows how much I knew.
Somebody said it's not.
No, it's not.
It's a...
It's a robot.
She's a...
What do they call him?
Vocaloid?
Yeah, she's a Vocaloid.
Yeah.
It's that Vocaloid technology.
You happy with this one?
She's more real than you.
All right.
She's real to me, but sad.
We're crying.
I...
Be mean?
I'm not being mean?
I didn't do anything.
Miku is a wonderful character.
When did I say anything bad about Miku?
Ever.
Are you serious?
Three, four, five, six, seven, eight, nine, ten.
Apology with tears.
I didn't say anything.
Hey, go make an open-faced turkey sandwich.
You just made 18,000 people cry.
I'm playing my game.
Everybody chill out.
It's Thanksgiving.
One, two, three.
Can't be any of these.
I love when it does this.
So this is...
All right.
So here we go.
So that means one, two, three, four, five, six.
Has to be in here.
Is it that?
Do I have it already?
That's pretty close.
Is this the three or the two?
This has to be the three, right?
Why are you so mean?
If I get this, then it's good to go.
I didn't say you say sorry to Miku.
I'm sorry, Miku.
There you go.
Now tell me if I'm right.
I think it's the...
It's the three.
Yeah.
The two?
Where would the...
No.
Oh my God.
All right.
So this is obviously part of the three.
So this is...
I can do a lot of deduction here.
One, two, three, face one.
One, two, three, four.
I don't know if that's correct or not.
This is...
Probably the six.
I wanted to press the other button.
Can you please do an ASMR stream?
Yeah, sure.
Let me just get a little bit more of my spaghetti.
I wanted to press the other button.
Why is it so wet?
I have to put extra sauce on it.
My spaghetti sits in at least two or three inches of sauce.
And then when I'm done, I tip it up like this and I drink it.
Do you really think I do that?
Be honest with yourself.
Sit here and think.
What does your eyes have to do?
You say...
Does a person actually do that?
No.
No, but no way.
Glad we could figure this out together.
Four, five, six, seven, eight.
No.
Oh, I think I got it.
This has to be there.
That helps a lot.
Cool.
What are you talking about?
I've got three X's.
I'm trying to go too fast.
Somebody said, what is that?
Copypasta?
I'm not going to read it.
What about smelling me or something?
Whatever.
All right.
So this is the...
Two is right here.
All right.
We got it now.
One, one, four, three.
There it is.
All right.
I got a lot of X's.
Don't read it.
I think I can get a new song.
I mean, the mods are just sniping it.
So I really probably shouldn't read it.
I'm not going to read it.
It's not going to read it because it's like as weird.
I need a new song.
I need some help.
I think I have enough.
Is particle miracle any good?
You're a weird guy.
Read it.
You could be kind of a weird guy and not be kind of a gross guy.
Is this one good?
What about coloring?
I'll do this one.
I already own this.
What?
I already have this one already.
What about by your side?
Oh, why was that locked?
I already have it.
I actually like this one.
It'd be a puzzle background.
I think this one's kind of cool.
I'll do this one.
Yeah, I'll keep this one.
These songs are really obscure.
What a special complete one large artwork.
Well, let's clear this whole thing first.
They're very obscure.
Really?
Whoops.
I went with the garbage one.
There are another nine.
Seven are here.
Any other big ones?
The six.
Another six.
Remember that it has to be here because just of absolute standard deduction.
Any more big ones?
Five, six, seven, eight, nine.
Now I can get that in a minute.
All right.
Let's go for it.
But what did I do wrong?
I got it right.
Stop.
Stop what?
This is pretty good popcorn scream.
That's pretty cool.
You made a fresh thing of popcorn?
Cool.
Fresh popcorn is the best.
And nothing beats.
You know what?
I really do love just sort of carnival food.
Popcorn.
Fresh pop.
It's not much that's better.
The stuff in the microwave is good.
It's fine.
But when you're at a fair and that machine is just bacon.
You wash the little pan bubble over and it fills up.
They get the big scooper.
It's hot.
That's like you have a clown diet.
I don't eat good.
It's fun.
It's good.
I just don't eat it every day.
I actually prefer bear slash carnival popcorn over movie theater popcorn.
Movie theater popcorn is a little way down for me.
It's a little too oily and too much greasy in a way.
It's like too much.
The pop stuff at the carnival is light.
It's nice and salty and hot.
It's not as way down as movie theater butter tastes.
That's not to say I don't like movie theater popcorn.
I do.
I love it, but I never eat it all.
I always try to get a small and you just kind of like blah.
Like just eating like a pad of butter.
I don't like sweet popcorn.
Not really.
There are some things that I just do not like to be sweet popcorn is one of them.
And I know that there's a lot of you know, it could be both right?
There's a lot of things like that, but I don't I'm not into it.
I've had obviously caramel popcorn before and it's good, but I would not put it anywhere even close to regular popcorn.
This is the one of the two.
This is probably the one I'm going for it.
I was wrong.
That's a stupid move.
Actually kind of helped.
What is it?
Choker.
Gallery.
What about kettle corn?
Um, I don't think I've had like, I don't know.
The real kettle corn is just sugary, right?
It's just sweet sugary.
A little salty too.
It's like both.
Yeah.
Are we going to probably move in?
Are these 15?
All right.
There's a lot of 10 by 10s.
When's the, when do you get to?
All right.
Actually, I might be able to do most of these.
I don't have a time limit for the stream, but I just was going to hang out for three hours.
Whenever I'm just kind of done.
I don't know.
I like this idea of just kind of a strip.
I don't, I don't know.
I want to try this thing where streams don't have to be like six, seven hours long.
Like five, six, seven hours long.
I can just do them whenever.
Just maybe they're shorter, but just do them whenever.
No, I'm not leaving yet.
Four, five, six, seven, eight, nine.
Okay.
So I can do this.
It's very good.
You made her sad.
Apologize.
Okay.
This is four.
It can only be here.
I'm going so fast.
Look at how, look at how happy she is.
Maybe one or two.
That was pretty flawless.
My mom loves Jerma.
Um, if your mom doesn't think I'm bad or anything.
I didn't stay on this for very long.
My mom is a fan of you.
Really?
My mom hates you.
I have a feeling.
I don't know what the moms love him.
Well, I will say this.
If you have a relationship with your parents or your mother where you can
both enjoy the same thing, potentially enjoy the same media.
That's actually pretty, that's pretty awesome.
That's really, really nice.
That's sweet.
It is.
So that makes me kind of happy that you can kind of enjoy things
as you know, together.
That's pretty cool.
All right.
Seven, eight, nine.
So six, seven, we can do a lot here.
I don't want to get it wrong.
Two, three, four.
One, two, three, four.
Well, here's your five.
Five.
Here's your two.
Here's your four.
Here comes your three.
This is your six.
Here's your four.
This is part of your three, obviously.
This is part of your four.
Here's your three.
Here's your two.
They're your reptile eyes.
I'm a human.
Dude, when you just get in the zone on some of them, it's awesome.
Feels so good.
I don't know that yet.
Can you please do a Bernie Sanders impression?
Uh, no, it's a chill day.
Chillin' out.
No human likes Picross this much.
Can I ask you a question?
On the Sunday paper, when you pick it up and you do the crossword
every weekend, does that make you a weirdo?
Hundreds of millions of people that do crossword every week.
Hold on a minute.
Let me, let me get this, let me get this for your generation.
When you open up Wordle every day, still human?
You still human?
Hmm.
I don't play Wordle nearly as much as you do.
I got Picross that I play every, you know, every few weeks.
Maybe I'll jump on and do a game.
You do Wordle every day.
Still human?
People play, what is it, people play it all the time.
Well, okay.
Everybody was giving me shit earlier for not reading.
But this is very clearly a game of logic and reasoning and deduction
and making your brain work.
How, why is this a bad thing?
Well, I'm not, I'm not playing Call of Duty today.
I'm not playing, I'm not playing the FPS Call of Duty game.
Therefore what?
No, we're deduced, we're deducting today.
All right, let me restart because somebody called me a red-filled
Redditor and I don't even like, what is that even supposed to mean?
All right, we can do this.
I don't know why that's doing it.
That's just like making me laugh.
I don't know why.
Red-filled Redditor.
That sounds like such a shitty superhero name.
Happy Turkey Day.
Yeah, YouTube.
With this X being here, I think I can do the left side, but I just,
my brain's too small to do it.
This is definitely the two.
Can you stand up?
No.
No, no, I'm not going to stand up.
No, why?
I'm not, I'm not doing that.
No, I've had this nightmare like five times.
I'm not doing it.
I've had this nightmare five times.
I keep having this dream.
I'm not doing it.
I'm not standing up.
What's your opinion on Dr.
Pepper flavored baked beans?
That's weird.
I don't have an opinion on it, but my first initial reaction is
that's a little strange.
Probably all I have for you though.
Is he actually naked or is this hinting at it?
No, I do.
Okay, I'll stand off.
Whatever.
I have pain.
I'm just, I don't know if I've had this nightmare.
I'm letting the nightmares happening.
What if the nightmare happens?
What if the nightmare actually happens?
Hold on.
I'm turning the camera off.
No, this is like, this is a nightmare.
All right, standing up.
Standing up.
Come up.
I'm, I stood up.
You're short.
I didn't stand up all the way.
Throw your pants.
No, you don't need to see my pants.
You just need to know that they exist.
You, I'm burning time here.
I could have done this in three minutes.
Nice pit stains.
Shut up.
What's going on?
I told you I just burned fuel.
And I don't know.
I just do.
I feel like there's like two or three just little people in my
body shoveling coal into a furnace.
And that's like how I, that's how I function.
There's just three little like, like people just shoveling fucking
coal into a furnace and that's how I like, I operate.
My body is like an old train from like the sift 1700s.
Right here, but it might not be.
It is right there.
What was this one?
Do you heat your house up?
I, it just gets so hot in here because this computer over here,
obviously when you're streaming.
So when this computer is live and I'm live to the internet, like
I am right now, this thing has to, it's encoding every frame that
you're seeing and putting it out essentially like uploading it to
the server and coding a shitload of data.
So this computer is just sitting here, just calculating and pumping
out hot air and I could like, yeah, I could get, I have like
air conditioning and everything, but, and I'm telling you right
now, I'm not going to open a window.
You just open the window.
I have my windows just wide open while I'm sitting here talking
about like, oh yeah, I'm a red pill redditor and oh yeah, spaghetti.
I, that would not go, I don't want that just broadcasted out to
like the fucking neighbors.
Be serious.
No, these windows stay closed.
These windows stay very tightly closed.
This is a whole house.
You're broadcasting to 20,000 people.
Yeah.
Those 20,000 people have chosen to be here.
If a random neighbor in like, I don't know, like an apartment
complex or a house or a neighborhood, they didn't sign up to
hear you talk about how you shit your pants today.
They did not sign up for that.
So I don't want my, all my windows to be up well.
I'm just like, oh, what the fuck is that guy doing?
What is that guy doing?
Why is Boise like this?
That's why you, it's a chill stream.
It is, it is a chill stream.
17,000 people already seeing you do that.
I know, but you are here because you chose to be here.
You clicked on my stream.
You're not reading a book.
You're not reading a book in, in your, in your like place.
Just being like, oh yeah, this is a really relaxing day.
I'm going to keep, I'm going to put the window open today.
That's nice out.
No, no, no, no, I don't want to show my dick on camera.
I don't want to show my dick on camera.
What is that person doing?
Why is windows open?
Why is he screening this stuff?
These windows are open.
He's yelling these random things.
What could he possibly, what could you possibly be doing?
Oh yeah.
No, no, yeah.
Cause let me open up all my windows and just start, you know.
How many baseballs can I fit in my ass?
Oh, time that person out, ban that person.
Ban that person for a day.
No, not happening.
It's a chill stream, everybody.
Same reason if I feel like I'm singing.
If I ever sing in the car, let's say I have music playing a little bit
or I'm like, just sitting there like singing.
If I was singing this song, those windows are up.
There is no way I'm going to pull to a red light and be like,
whoa, that guy's singing.
That guy's singing.
How is it any different?
Can you tell me how that's different?
I know for a fact, a ton of people that do that, that all of a sudden,
oh no, I'm going to pull up to the red light.
It's like,
I'm slowing down to the red light.
The screen.
And now we go back to what we were doing.
Come on.
You can't give me shit for this one.
Don't even start with that.
This guy's only filled in four squares in three minutes.
Hey, how was your Thanksgiving?
All right.
Now I'm going to focus and I'm going to get it done.
Just relax.
What can I fill in?
Three, four, five, six, seven.
Oh, I can do this.
Probably wait.
All right.
I'm focused now.
What's a lot of low numbers.
But I just, what am I doing?
Right bumper did that one space.
I don't want to guess.
One, two, three, four, one, two, three, four.
So this and okay.
This is the three.
Yeah.
So here one, two, three.
All right.
So now that I know this, this is one, two, three, four, five, six, seven.
One, two, three, four, five, six, seven.
Oh, this is the one.
Nice.
You that's free.
This is an animal crossing song.
What is, hold on.
What did you say?
What is this animal crossing ass song?
It's this is Miku.
I was like, all right, ban him for a minute.
Ban him for a minute.
Time.
I'm up for five minutes.
I am really giggly today.
You're right.
Shit.
I have to stop.
It's tough.
I keep fucking up.
I just imagine somebody coming to the stream and just they've never
heard anything like this before.
Like what would you, what would you honestly think?
Like I've never heard a Miku song.
I have played animal crossing.
That's what I know.
That's what I have up here.
What is it?
Like what is the song that I'm listening to?
All right.
I got to get, I got to get it together here.
Miku and Animal Crossing fans are the same.
They probably share a pretty big audience.
They're both fun.
Both cool.
I don't know yet.
All right, that helps.
All right.
So nothing else here.
So this is it has to be there.
What is it?
Paper tags.
New song.
All right.
This is a fun game.
I'm going to do particle miracle.
I regret my purchase.
Hold on.
Nevermind.
This is going on the puzzle part.
I thought, okay.
People like what am I and what the fuck?
What do you mean?
I thought it was an instrumental and I didn't want to buy an instrumental.
Song is fine.
Song is good.
I just thought it was an instrumental.
How do I feel about, how do I feel about visual novels?
I don't think I've ever done one.
What, what, what constitutes a visual novel?
Have I done one before?
Ace Attorney.
I told you I can't play Ace Attorney.
I physically cannot play it again.
I can't.
Why, why not?
All right.
We're going to explain this to some of the newer audience.
So every, I want to say every like every like 10 seconds to one minute.
The screen goes and flashes a white flash in your face.
Does this every 10 to 15 seconds.
And it's just like.
And here's my head and you can't turn it off.
It's not true.
It is true.
You know how I know it's true because I bought the entire Ace Attorney
remake when it came out because everyone was telling me I should be
playing it and I was so excited about it and I went in and it just
did the, it still was doing it.
All right.
I can get this here.
I can do this one too, I think.
Play romance games, please.
Remember you're balding more on your right side than your left.
That's not true.
What's happening with your, with your being, when you're experiencing,
I'll tell you, here's what you are experiencing.
You're experiencing my hair.
My hairline is here, right?
Like I'm, I just pulled it over.
My hairline is right here, but my hairstyle is kind of, I have wavy hair.
So my actual hairline is that, right?
What you're just, what you're seeing is you're seeing how it falls on one side.
So therefore you think I'm balding on one side, but not the other, but just
my hair is wavy and goes like that.
I also need a haircut.
So like this mad scientist shit back here is, should be like that.
And this should be a little shorter.
Also, I've been fucking banned for one day.
Oh, that does that.
Ooh, this is, I like this part.
There's a lot of the three two threes.
Just realized that.
It's great.
Six.
Again.
You should grow it out.
No.
Ow.
I like it like this.
If it stays like this, it's fine.
Having the, let's say medium length hair.
It's I need to, I got to clean it up though.
It's a little sloppy.
I don't know why I said haircuts.
Oh, you can sort it by character.
Can you?
Please go back to the Hillary Clinton hair.
That's never happening ever again.
All right.
What should I buy now?
What's this one?
I need more.
I think I have most of them on shuffle, but I don't think it matters.
I think the shuffle mode stuff, I think that's just in this menu.
If I press play on this, it's going to shuffle in this menu, not in the game.
How come you try to specifically like 10 seconds behind?
I don't know.
Maybe it's your connection to me.
I think that's how it works.
Right.
Like I'm West coast United States.
So maybe if you're, I don't know if you're connecting from putting it out,
broadcasting to you in Europe or something, maybe it's a little behind.
I don't know.
Please.
Popeye is in the list and the music done.
I, uh, I can we get a, um, make it a poll.
Should I turn the music down another notch?
Turn the music down one more notch.
Yes or no.
What a pull up.
Well, I forget this up.
Somebody said Popeye is in the, is it in the menu?
Where is it?
Somebody said it's in the menu.
No, it's not.
Okay.
I'm just being lied to being lied to switch to me.
Cool.
Let me, I'm going to change character.
Yeah.
I'm going to play the other character.
Please.
Uh, I tell, I tell, how do you say it?
I'm going to puke.
You're not going to just drop the volume of the stream a little.
I'm too.
I'm at a very good volume.
Yeah.
You just, please.
I'm going to puke.
I don't think you're good.
I think you're going to be okay.
Just turn it down.
Why are you blasting it?
Wonder if it's this one or this one.
314 is a given line, isn't it?
Let's see.
I think you're right.
You are correct.
Yes, you are.
I'm not paying attention to the bottom.
Well, I know that's that.
Bye, Germo.
Bye.
See you later.
Thanks for coming.
Hope you had a good Thanksgiving.
Music down.
No.
Okay.
I wonder if I can do the ones.
Is this the four?
Yes, it is.
Three, two, three, two.
Cool.
Two, two.
I think that's going to be it here.
Yeah.
Can you please play the music on your violin?
I owned a violin.
Do you have enough stars to?
You need to talk louder.
No.
I need a new song.
How about this one?
What?
How do I not have stars?
I got it.
Okay.
I'm going to bang out some levels really quickly here.
No more chill.
We want aggressive.
That's that's just not going to happen right now.
Let's try this one.
Zero doesn't really matter because I'm going to get all the
info.
I need her right here.
Okay.
Well, that was easy.
What was it?
One, two, three, four.
We can also put our own soundtrack on.
How do you know the four and the and five are on their
respective sides?
That's actually a good question.
I'm going to answer it.
So on the left-hand side of the screen, say the four, it's
four space five.
What that means is the four has to be on the left side.
They have to be spaced that way.
So if it's four space five, the four has to be first.
It can't be five and then four.
It has to you read it left to right.
So left to right.
You have to put the squares in in sequence.
So see two, one, one.
It's not just like, oh, two, one, one's going to be randomly
in here.
The two has to be first, then a one and then a final one.
You can see how that looks.
It's two here.
There's a lot of space.
The space doesn't matter.
It could be one space or it could be ten spaces.
It just has to be one square in the middle.
It has to be kind of stuck.
No, I'm not.
One, two, three, four, five.
All right, reducing.
Well, I know what that is now.
Deduced.
Still have no idea how this game works.
Well, should we should I explain it?
What are you going to slurp?
You want me to do my spaghetti?
You want to have my spaghetti?
Is somebody coming to say when's the next slurp?
Is that what you said?
I need to do one more and I have enough stars.
This is a chunky one.
Can't say, you know what I mean?
Can we do a poll for Satori Landy?
I feel like you're just going to say yes to deliberately piss
off the people that don't want to hear me explain the game
for like the 12th time in the last two years.
And you're going to deliberately just try to annoy them
because I'm going to sit here for five minutes and explain
the whole game again.
That's what I know what you're doing because I would vote for
that if I'm in the chat right now and I'm watching this
streamer.
I'm going to be like, yeah, let's get him to explain the
game.
So all these people get fucking annoyed and leave.
I understand your I understand your comedic effort.
I get it.
That's why I'm shutting it down.
Three, four, five, six, three, three, four, five, six.
Okay, four, three.
Very nice.
Be over here.
Eight complete.
Three, four, three, two, three.
Is it a heart?
Playing the game and annoy people.
Well, I just said I wasn't going to do it.
This vote is a this vote doesn't mean anything to me.
What did you eat today?
I have one single cup of yogurt and a Sprite.
I had what?
Somebody said what?
It's like that is so shocking to hear that.
What?
Oh, yeah, guys are cranberries.
S tier for me mashed potatoes.
Great.
Oh man.
Oh, you know, God, we got this little butterball turkey.
Oh, it's so good.
What do you do?
Well, I had to go yogurt today.
That's it.
Nice spaghetti.
Liar.
Shit.
Do I only get one star for these?
But I was getting less stars.
Oh, clear the puzzle.
No misses.
No hints.
I'm getting two.
I could get up to three.
All right.
I got to get why lie viewers when you're eating spaghetti.
Because there's no actually spaghetti over here.
I think I can get this whole thing one.
So let me mark it.
It's one one, two, three, four, five, one, two, three, four, five.
Nope.
All right.
It's getting a little weird here.
One.
We did that seven now.
Reset it.
I don't care.
Reset.
I didn't mean to go that far.
Why would you lie about having spaghetti?
I don't know because I thought it was funny.
You're a cheater.
I'm not cheating.
Oh, that's a big raid.
Box box coming in with a monster raid.
What's going on?
Thanks for the raid box box.
Hope you're doing well.
Hope everybody had a good Thanksgiving coming over.
Celebrate it.
You as well box box.
Welcome.
We're playing pit cross.
We're just doing a chill night stream for two, three hours.
So hanging out.
Welcome.
Thanks a lot.
We're discussing our favorite Thanksgiving dinner items.
And what I said, I said that my favorite Thanksgiving item was
cranberry sauce in the can that you have to actually get like
and it splies out and hits the thing.
People thought that it was kind of weird, but that is one of
my favorite items.
But yeah, welcome.
Hope you had a good holiday.
Again, if you celebrate it.
I think I can do this.
It's one.
Oh, by the way, box box.
You got it.
You got to check out.
You got to check out pit cross.
All right.
It's like one of the most fun games ever cranberry sauce is
underrated.
He was eating yogurt spaghetti.
Don't lie.
Can I do this?
Let's see.
One, two, three, four, five, six, seven.
Yeah, that's the whole line.
Now the whole thing opens up.
Oh, yeah.
Mm-hmm.
I did it.
Satellite.
All right.
This is Miku pick Ross, which what that means is this is a
you've unlocked pictures and music from Miku.
If you're a Miku fan, I'm just a pick Ross fan.
I mean, I mean, it doesn't doesn't like Miku, right?
All right.
I thank you.
Do I have enough for another song?
All right.
I need one more level and I got it.
Dude, it's annoying.
All you do is eat spaghetti and lie a weird trait to have.
I don't know.
I feel like that's I don't know for some reason.
I feel like that's like a like a relationship thing.
Like you like we're like breaking up.
All you do is eat spaghetti and lie like what the fuck I feel
like what what is what is this?
This is part of the I don't want to go that actually I can
because it's a two there.
I might be going a little quick some people saying hey,
he's going really fast.
It's hard to keep up.
You you'll start to pick it up.
Once you get it, you get it.
There's only okay.
This is like a actual two out of three chance that I get this
right over here.
There's a 50-50 chance that it's either here or here.
I'm going to flip the coin heads.
It's okay.
Just don't make another mistake.
I need the stars.
So then it has to be down here.
I've reduced it to three, four, five, six, one, two, three,
four, five, six.
I can get this latest high.
I mean, yeah, I feel like it would be very difficult.
It's a five one.
This seven's done.
So it has to be here.
Very nice.
Wow.
Build it all in in one second.
You like it would be annoying high.
Yeah, but I would rather here's another thing too.
I made this.
I've talked about this before.
I don't want like, you know, doing drugs to be something
that's like, oh, I'm going to do that in stream.
Like isn't that funny?
Isn't that cool?
No, I thought about like stuff like that before, but it's
just I'd rather not.
I'm completely honest.
That's not to say like, oh, it would be like maybe be kind
of fun.
I just don't want I don't know.
I feel like I'd rather just not do that.
Liar.
You talk about it like every stream.
I definitely do not.
That is it.
That isn't an embellishment and don't get me wrong.
Like recreational marijuana, if it's legal where you are
and you, you know, safely doing it and you know, privacy
of your own home or among, you know, friends in a place
where it's safe and you're going to be, you know, safe
about it by all means, right?
But I don't know if I want to make it like content piece.
I think that's going another step forward because I mean,
so I mean, we all know that the famous clock fiasco, right?
The big clock scandal where I had been, you know, doing
marijuana because well, one of the main reasons why I
started taking in any amount of THC in the first place
was because the pain problem that I have.
So I wasn't like I was I mean, I didn't start really.
Oh, I'm going to just get high every single day.
That wasn't any ever what I want to do and that's not
what I do either.
But that like you can't I just can't do that anymore.
It was very clear that I can't read a clock and people
are going to know there's no way people are going to I'm
going to be able to hide that like I take a little bit
of THC and like relax and stream and I can't read an
analog clock and people go what time is it?
I'm like, I don't I don't know.
Like, what do you mean?
You don't know.
How is it possible?
How is it possible that you don't know that?
It's like, I don't know and then it's embarrassing
because I can't you said you lied lied about what being
high that day.
Did I say that was I actually high that day?
I thought I was I don't remember.
Did I make that up?
No, I don't think so.
Maybe I told you I made it up.
So you didn't think I was a moron.
I don't know.
There's something else going on there.
He's high right now.
He has dementia find the clip of me talking about it.
I'm actually curious.
I forget what the lie was.
What did um, there's a famous famous person.
What do they say?
They said as long as you have it's like tell the truth
always so you never have to remember anything who said
that like Mark Twain or something is like always tell
the truth.
So you never have to remember anything not Winston
Churchill.
I think it was Mark Twain Lady Gaga.
No, I think it was Mark Twain.
Fuck how deep does that lie go?
I wonder here's another problem.
I have real I have like kind of bad memory problems
anyways.
So I actually don't even remember if I was come on.
I don't remember if I was just fucking around or not.
Like when I said that that time that I told you I was
lying about it.
I might have just making it up.
I don't remember.
I actually don't remember it was Peewee Herman.
Is it this is just what this is a clip.
Why are you clipping this?
The left and right are numbers which indicate how many
cubes need to be filled in in that row or column for
instance, there has to be why did you just link this
to me?
This is just me explaining the game.
I think you said you were not I then later came clean
that you were I can't keep track of what the fuck
this guy ever says you lied about being high in the
concrete level not the clock.
I think that's correct.
That's what it was.
Yep.
I think we're mixing it up a little bit.
So let me let me clear the air.
Let me get a clear picture of what happened.
So during the hitman 3 streams, I was walking around
on one of the levels where it's like I think it's
like the club or something, right?
It's a big concrete level and I did not know where
I was going and it was so frustrating and I was
getting so pissed off and so agitated by it and I
look I remember looking over at the chat and being
like people were saying this can't be for real.
He has to be under the influence.
There's no way a person could be like this.
I'm concerned about him.
I remember reading people saying I'm concerned
about this.
I'm very concerned about him and I was like fuck
I can't be this stupid.
I was like, oh, I guess the yeah, I guess the
edible started kicking in.
Yeah.
I remember I lied about that.
Yep.
Oh hundred percent.
That's what it was.
So I made it up that I oh, yeah guys.
I took a little bit before the stream.
It's like kicking in and everyone's like, oh, okay.
All right.
Now it makes sense.
All right, dude, do you you're good.
I'm sitting there going like fucking thank God
clock one was real.
It was I actually remember people writing in the
chat.
It was so just like man, I he's not pretending and
it's not even funny.
It's just like concerning that he doesn't know
where he is.
That's so funny in a way though.
I made up that I was high to make so you didn't
think I was like having like some type of problem.
Like I didn't want to never think I was stupid.
Yeah.
And then all right restart and then I can't I
came out later like months later.
That was like guys.
I made that up, right?
Okay.
So we are we're I we clear the air on this.
I gotta be careful because whoa, stop doing that.
I don't these are not guarantees.
This is a guarantee.
No, it's not.
How did I just get that?
Are there any lies you told on stream you haven't
come clean about?
I I don't I don't think so.
I mean, I kind of just I mess around a lot like
we all do here.
I mean this this plenty of opportunities where I
just kind of say just stuff just to make up a
scenario for fun.
Fuck.
No, I'm not going back.
I think it's clear when I do that though.
I think it's pretty set in stone that that's me
just messing around spaghetti and meatballs.
Yeah.
I mean, but did you honestly believe that was
real?
Come on.
When yes, it's like almost the whole screen
filled in.
What is this a chair?
Why would you lie about it?
No, because it's fun just to like make up fun
scenarios that just I don't know why why not?
It's fun.
Oh, I didn't even click on it.
Let you in here.
I did by the first song.
I've seen that a lot.
I'll do that.
What is the first song?
Which one of these is the first song?
Hey guys, did you know spaghetti and meatballs?
But you forgot about the laugh track right after
that.
That's just kind of funny what you said.
All right.
Where's the first song?
How was your Thanksgiving?
It was great.
That guy spammed spaghetti and meatballs dozens
of times.
No, did I just catch the spammer and I thought
it was with the way I said it about you?
Whatever.
All right.
What's the name of the song that you want me
to unlock?
I don't was it this one?
That's hard.
I can't it's hard for me to translate that which
one the one you were on the previous one the
previous one this one.
I'm trying to I can't read it this one chat
read it wrong.
I'll put it on and blast it.
Well, I'm not going to blast it, but I'll play
it.
Is it instrumental?
No, it's just one of the one I bought has
vocals, right?
Please don't blast it.
I have a headache.
No, I'm not gonna see how it is.
I think that's all I can do down here now.
So I can do this.
There we go.
This one this one's got this was this one's
top rows again.
You're up to one.
One down here is a two somewhere.
All right.
Hold on to do.
That's a one.
Okay, he's actually pretty good at Picross.
Oh when I'm just when I focus I've been playing
Picross for years for 10 years.
I remember the first Picross game that I ever
played I think was on the original DS the original
Nintendo DS.
So it's fun.
Now.
All right.
This is very beginner to intermediate stuff.
There's once you get into the 20 by 20 like 50
by 50 it gets really you have to pay a lot
attention to everything going on.
I don't know why my voice just did that but my
eyes were very confused by it.
Yeah, see 10 by 10.
This is all 10 by 10.
Then when I go over here 20 by 20, this is
obviously level 3 20 by 20 is pretty I'd say 15
by 15 is pretty standard 20 by 20 gets pretty
hard.
You were 20 by 20.
I'll I'll try 20 by 20.
Let's see if I can handle it and see everything
right.
All right.
So this is 20 by 20.
So therefore 15 16 17 18 so if teens that means
five has to be on each side.
There's this they get they get pretty wacky and
I tried 17 18.
Let me think if there's a 10 50 by 20 that means
that as long as there is and see can't do anything
in the middle really because there's no way to
know where it sits.
Really there's more I could get from here.
Can I let me tell you what 1 2 3 13 14 15 16
17 18 this 20 here.
1 2 3 4 5 15 16 17 18 9 is 19.
I think I got it though.
That's one.
There's only one slot that's not filled in here
and I don't know where it could be.
Let's be two in the middle.
1 2 3 4 7 8 9 10 1 2 3 4 5 6 7 8 9 10 I don't
think I can reliably fill these in but I guess
so because that means 1 2 3 4 5 6 7 8 9 they both
could do that.
Although this is not something you would actually
know.
Are there any 20s like a whole row?
I need us.
I need an edge for 15.
I need an edge at least some kind of edge to
start yet.
Sorry restart part of the 10 this is part of the
9.
We said I just did the exact same thing.
Fill in the 7 10 3 4 5 6 7 space 1 2 3 4 5 6 7 8 9 10.
I mean it could be so what like two out from each
side.
I don't know where the space though is but it has
to be like this and it has to be at least these
ones up here because I don't know where the space
is.
I am so annoyed whatever I'm going to leave it
because I don't know where the space is going to
be because it could be whatever I got it.
That's enough info to help you to have an oatmeal
brain.
I can't actually that's a lot of info though.
This is a good start.
Perfect.
Now.
I don't know anything about that.
Okay, what about the top row 3 4 5 6 7 8 9 10?
Although I can fill in some of this though because
it's definitely in this row here.
I just don't know if it's this way.
It's definitely here.
That means the two has to be here then.
Yeah.
What do you mean the two is not there?
How is that possible?
What?
Oh shit.
When they get big like this, it's all right.
I just can't get three strikes.
I mean it has to be at least one 1 2 3 4 5 6 7.
Any more info?
Good 10 9 and 1.
Okay, this is part of a 2.
Well, here's the 12.
Can I do anything with 12?
Say 1 2 5 6 7 8 9 10 11 12.
Before 1 2 3 4 5 6 7 8 9 10 11 12.
Okay, so it has to be like this.
One more, right?
Why are we yelling at each other?
Why are people screaming at each other?
Turn off the music.
I have to admit it has been a little distracting.
So if it's a little distracting for me, the person streaming,
then some of you guys must must be unbearable for some of you.
I can't turn it off from here.
I don't want to give up.
Turn it up.
No, I'm not going to turn it up.
I'm getting closer.
So not much longer.
I love Miku.
I do Miku's great.
But I think we're going to put on a different song.
Can we streamer's choice?
I don't know why I wanted to listen to this for one second.
This is worse because it's probably really copywritten.
That's not the one.
Never mind.
Where's Miku?
Austin Powers.
We did that already.
Oh, I could just play Miku songs that I like.
Holy shit.
That's actually true.
Okay, is this the right version?
Is there more than one version?
I guess it was the one.
Probably here, but I'm afraid to get three strikes.
Nice.
That was risky, but it was worth it.
2 3 4 5 6 7.
Part of the 10.
You need to sing it.
All right, this is 11.
All right.
So that was fun.
What else should I do?
Are both songs playing right now?
I don't think so.
I turned it.
I should.
I turned it on.
People saying play triple, triple baka, triple baka.
Okay.
Yes.
Have I ever heard this?
Seven.
Where's the two go?
Okay, this one a half.
This is one, two.
Oh, it has to be this way.
All these need to be filled in.
Is the, yeah, this is nine.
This is no, this is not five.
Right?
One, eight, nine, one, two, three, four, five, one, two, three,
four, five, people, people, people, people, people.
That's this is definitely part of the seven.
Right?
Yeah.
Well, I would imagine this is probably the four, but I can't deduce
that, but I'm going to go for it.
It's three strikes.
I got too comfortable that I'm going to finish it.
I'll finish it.
Shit.
I'm not going to get any points with this.
One, two, three, four, five, six, seven, eight, nine, ten.
Still don't know what side it's on.
Do I?
I do.
What happened?
What'd I do?
What'd I do wrong?
Where's the one?
What?
Hold on.
It's here.
Oh no.
That's bad.
I can't reset.
No, I can't.
I've been doing it for too long.
That's why it these 20 by 20 is it just they take a lot of you
just have to remember you just can't just go fast.
That's all right.
Any more requests?
I'll take any requests by the way.
It doesn't just have to be Miku long as it's not going to get the
channel turned off.
Like the world is mine made like 15 mistakes.
All right.
What was it?
Somebody said I have a request.
This one rolling girl, is it right?
How come these aren't in this game?
I don't want to miss you know, I don't want to misrepresent this
game.
This is these are not in the game.
I'm playing them on YouTube.
I wonder why would they wouldn't be in game probably licensing
problem.
I made this game.
Isn't it Sega doesn't Sega own this stuff who made this Sega
not make this?
Probably not.
That was fun.
I'm going to go back to some easier ones.
I want to least clear this second row here the second one.
Okay, how's the volume good?
I love when this happens, you know, it can't be anywhere over
here.
It helps free up a lot of space.
Usually 234 23.
All right.
Well, I mean, I know it's here and I know it's like here.
Like magnet.
I feel like I can get this.
Yeah.
Oh interesting one.
Huh?
Oh, I thought that was part of the
I just wasn't looking down shit.
Come on.
I can't make those kind of mistakes.
That's the rookie mistake.
This is different.
Oh, I already heard this one.
L polka polka was it live and polka.
Oh, it's this one.
I know this one.
This is this is a classic song after I feel this wrong and
see what the special puzzle is.
Seven eight nine.
This I could do these two.
It's yes.
One two, three, four, five, six, seven, eight.
Yo, what?
Yo.
So this is part of the three.
Then we know one, two, three.
It cannot be down here.
I mean, maybe it does a little because it's either it's either
one, two, three, four or it's here.
So I just go for it.
I just go for it over here.
It's on it's either over here or it's right here.
I'm going for it.
You can call me a cheater if you want, but I got one.
I mean, what is this?
What the hell is that?
This is different.
This is a different artist.
Play it.
Turn it off.
This is called Kikuo.
Kikuo love me.
Love me.
This is a different artist.
This actually helps because now it's one.
Don't tell him.
Play time machine.
Time machine.
I said fuck you.
What?
What the fuck?
That was a bonus track.
We weren't supposed to even hear that one.
How do you do Donald Duck?
Something like that, right?
You go like I'm stumped.
It's definitely this row.
This row or this one has the most info.
One, two, three, four.
This is a one.
That's a one.
All right.
This is two after this.
Why is everyone so angry?
You're cringe.
You skipped a good song.
I didn't skip it.
We listened to half of it.
Go back, liar.
I think this actually helps here.
It does.
Okay, so I can do that.
One, two, three, four, five.
That's all I can do.
But this is three.
That's cool.
Helps a little.
I'm going to unfollow.
Why?
Because I skipped a song.
Here, I'll put a streamer's choice on.
There.
I'll put a streamer's choice on for a bit.
Somebody said, bro, relax.
I'm going for it.
Yes.
This is the never video.
This actually goes.
It does, yeah.
This way, I'm going to, we'll keep this on for a little bit.
Those of you that have not heard this before, it's a great soundtrack.
It's by Terry Scott Taylor.
Pretty good.
Really nostalgic.
Nostalgic.
Can't even say it.
Now we turn this up, of course.
Oh, you don't think we're going to turn this up all the way?
This is not Miku.
Yeah, I'm playing.
Oh, yeah, it's Hatsune Miku.
The game where you do Picross.
Of course, the soundtrack is going to be very important.
This is incredibly important.
Let me see.
What should I put on?
Oh, yeah, this one.
Let's go.
This way.
Dude, this guy fucking loves the saxophone.
It's great.
This whole game has a vibe.
This one's tricky.
I feel like it kind of has to wait.
I don't know.
I really don't know.
I know that.
Yeah.
Hey, why don't you fucking take it?
Sit down for this one.
This one goes super hard.
This dude loves...
I do.
All right.
I like the saxophone.
It's a fucking...
It's an unbelievable instrument.
And plus it's like...
What do you mean?
It's an oboe.
This is an oboe.
Oh, now it's just cascades.
All right.
Now we bring everything together.
Here we go.
This goes hard.
Of course it does.
This whole soundtrack is...
This is the best soundtrack of any video game that is ever released.
I genuinely mean that.
I really believe that.
See how you guys feel about this one.
This one's a great one.
You guys are going to love this one.
This one's pretty topical today.
What is this?
This is the Neverhood soundtrack.
The OST for the Neverhood.
By Terry Scott Tello.
This is the shit that would play when you were doing a puzzle.
They just added to the whole thing.
Are you going to...
Yeah.
Is this what you play when you play your iPad games?
Oh, this one's good too.
This one's really good.
What?
Oh, fuck.
This chill Thanksgiving vibes.
Come on.
That's the three, right?
No, it's the four.
Oh, I'm such an idiot.
What else we got?
Do I have to play the...
Come on.
I do this like every like a year or two.
In the sequel to the Neverhood, there was a...
It was a bonus room.
It was called Skullmonkeys.
So there was a bonus room in the sequel to the Neverhood where you go in it and they sing you a song.
And this is the song that plays when you're in the bonus room.
It's been the inspiration for a lot of music in the video game world.
If you didn't know, look it up.
Here it is.
You don't.
And a little like your mom.
There are no monsters here.
Hey, wait, look over there.
I was just kidding.
Be scared.
And when you turn this game off in the real world once again, you won't have to play Make Me Leave, but try to pretend.
Because I'll be right there when you open your...
Is this too loud?
Oh shit, I'm sorry.
Because I'm your little invisible musical friend.
So show me to your pets or show me to your pals.
You really will impress every nifty guy and gal.
Show them you're individual.
Show them you are bold.
Besides, I get residuals for every game that's sold.
I'm your little invisible musical friend.
Somebody said when Jerma gets the aux cord.
So that plays when you're in a bonus and it was funny and it was like weird and people thought it was like, what the fuck is happening?
It was like a secret room.
There you go.
All right, we're doing streamers choice again.
What should I play for streamers choice?
I got one.
This is a good one.
I don't think people are going to be upset about this one.
All right, I got to pay attention now.
So three could be here.
It's probably there and it is.
Now the real question is there is a two and a one hanging out here.
There's also a three.
Ah, I took a guess.
I just wanted to get it done.
If I had put the marker there, I wouldn't know it wasn't there.
That's three strikes.
Shit.
This is Superstar Saga the battle music or the Game Boy Advance, I believe.
One, two, yoko Shimomura.
Yep, I think Yoko Shimomura might be probably one of the best.
I think the best that ever was.
I think so many soundtracks by Yoko Shimomura were, I mean, they're just unbeatable.
I don't understand how it's possible to have that many 10 out of 10
soundtracks in a row every time.
I don't understand because it's not just one or two.
It's all of them.
Every single one of them.
Being that talented and being that connected to music and stuff.
It's just, it's just unbelievable.
It really is.
Redditor music taste?
I don't know.
I could, all right.
That's bait.
That's bait I was about to take.
I was about to just eat the onion there.
I was about to eat the onion.
All right.
Nevermind.
Chat's choice.
What do you want?
Will Miku?
All right.
Well, give me a Miku song.
Magnet.
That was one.
Yeah, I remember seeing that earlier.
Magnet.
Is this correct?
All right.
What's some other music that I want to show you?
Hmm.
Do more Neverhood.
I was going to play the Avengers theme because I wanted to have the mods.
I was going to say in private to count how many bad chest there were.
People already started doing it, but my joke is ruined.
What should I play?
I guess we're doing this.
I feel like it's right here.
Yeah.
One, two, three.
My favorite gorilla song.
Um, it used to be Stylo.
Stylo is...
I just like the beat.
Stylo slaps.
Yeah.
I'll put it on after this.
You guys get mad if I put it on now.
This stream is definitely not going to be up anymore.
It's going to get dropped in a second.
Bye.
Happy Thanksgiving.
Thanks for coming.
Thanks for chilling.
And again, like I said before, I want to start doing more of these
streams that we just kind of chilled.
Put on some music.
Do something just simple.
Hang out for a little bit.
I like these a lot.
Does this help?
Good.
Talk about spaghetti.
I love spaghetti.
Okay, good.
This is also six.
Hold on.
That's okay.
One, two, three, four.
Two.
One, two, four.
One, two, three, four.
Six.
Is this six here?
Yep.
Sweet.
All right.
No mistakes.
Good.
That's what I like to see.
All right.
What's it going to do?
Oh, yes.
Stylo.
It's almost over.
I won't stop it.
Here we go.
This is one of my favorite songs on the album.
This thing is, this is sick.
No, I was typing.
Do you hear how fast I was typing?
What just happened?
I typed three words.
Why did that take so long?
Oh, we keep this one on too, by the way.
But if you guys like these, you know, start streaming around like
six or seven p.m.
Pacific.
Stream for a few hours.
Do it every so often.
A little bit lower energy.
Hang out.
I actually like it a lot.
Now, there were some high-energy moments today, but that's just the way it is.
I can't stop that.
What's the ultimate Miku song to play right now?
The Miku song?
Intense voice.
Okay.
I already did this one.
Today?
I don't think so.
What's the one where, uh...
What's the one that...
I forget what it was.
Play...
Ma...
I'll play that one now.
We'll do two more.
Don't worry, we're queuing it up.
I got, we got time for two more.
One, two, three, okay.
Then nine, ten.
What's the other one that's like this?
It's like
Yeah, it's like
All right, this one's a little...
This one's crazy.
Wrench in, wrench in now.
All right.
Oh my God.
Okay.
This is the one?
That one's, uh...
That one's a little much.
That one's crazy.
Um...
I just wanted to hear the beginning.
Just wanted to hear the very beginning. That's all I wanted to hear. All right. We need we need one to go out on
I got one to go out on. How about this one? What do you think? Should we play it again?
Give me just something random. Give me something random. There's something that's just completely out of left field peaches
Wow, holy smokes. Wow that you just brought back me
You just brought me back like 15 years really Wow. I
Completely forgot about this song and this band
Alright, let's get out of with this one
Then it goes look out
I'm moving to the country. I'm going to eat a lot of peaches
Moving to the country. I'm going to eat a lot of peaches
Something's done here
Can't be here
Is that millions of peaches peaches for free
That
This was a D song back in the day they're like fighting in this music video. Well, this is why I don't know
We're not doing this one. I don't know about this one. Cool. All right. I'm already doing it
So I'm already doing it. So what we knew one more. All right. Let me play the one that everyone's been requesting
It's what's it called. It's called like my Marta. What is it? It's going too fast Mar
Matt
Mart you're okay this one. All right this one is this correct?
Yes. Yeah. All right. All right. We'll go out on this one. I'll try to get this puzzle on quick
Eight
Fourteen nine ten
two three four five six seven eight nine ten
Seven one two, three, four five six seven. So then one is part in three. So one
Bingo increase the volume. No, it's a little too loud
fourteen
two
one two, three four
Come on Gwen, I can do it. Come on Gwen. We're gonna need another one after this. It's getting faster
It is getting faster. Any more special requests? We got room for maybe one or two more
Maybe just a Kaizen opening. We can start doing anime openings now
All right. Here we go. What's your favorite anime opening? Let's play them all
Streams are gonna get turned off bad chest. Oh wait, this is uh, uh, hold on. I'm sorry. I paused it. This is
Salmon tuna. I this is where this is from. This is what that's from, isn't it?
Oh my god, I know this. Yep. Oh, yeah, I've seen it. All right, let's go back
We're getting stuck
Got it. All right, what are the what are the anime intros do you guys want to hear?
Any more anime intros? What else you got? I got one for you. My it's dreamy's choice. There you go
Oh
That's part
You're punching me and you're doing bad chest I
Got I get one anime a year. I actually think I've watched any this year
I watched I watched one anime a year. Is there anything that I should watch chainsaw, man, but I like chainsaw, man
Yeah, I mean, I don't yeah animes are right. Like I don't hate it
I don't watch that much of it. That's why I have my I have my one anime that I watch a year
Well, I somehow I love some animes mob psycho is good
All right, if you were to pick between mob psycho and chainsaw, man
We get a poll in the chat, please Bob psycho or chainsaw, man, what would you watch Bob psycho 100% really? Okay
You would probably like mob psycho better. All right, this is getting weird here. So I'm one two three three
Are you no, I'm not high chainsaw man is I missed what you said mob psycho is a masterpiece
I don't okay. You need to close the poll. We don't need to have it open anymore
Almost that's a very very strong decision. All right, I'm almost done with this. So where are we?
How do I not have all ten of these one two five six seven eight nine
I don't want to guess but I know that's there but I mean that there's 80%
Okay, I got a shave bad. All right one final song to take us out a one final
Anime intro. What do you want do the mob psycho intro? No, I don't want to walk
okay, I don't want to watch the mob psycho intro right now because I want to watch it when I'm sitting on the couch and
You know it gets to that part
Your favorite part where like something cool is happening a really beautifully animated sequence and it hits that drop of the song and you
Just like you feel like warm and you're just like here it comes. Yes. There it is
That's what I like and then you rewind the YouTube video of the intro
Okay, let me ask you a question and I want everyone to be real be real with me. Don't lie. Don't make it up
I want I want to know if you do this. Are you ready? I'm just I don't have to say anything
I'm just gonna do it and I want you to just observe
Let's take the one punch man intro for an example
Oh
Am I a weirdo am I a weirdo
All right, you get it you get the idea you get the idea you get the idea you get the idea
Alright so what's the last song for real because I'm about to finish the puzzle it's almost over Pokemon Colosseum music, okay
I don't know why I muted it. I like this
Why is it muting? Stop muting
Okay. All right. This is good shit. All right. What is this? Oh
I think you make a huge picture with all this. That's cool
That's I like that. All right, one more. All right people seem to do this one. This is called Anamanaguchi
Let's take a look at all the artwork a sea of people asking for bloody stream and kickback
And he picks the one dude who wanted the Pokemon salsa song. I thought it was interesting
I wanted to play it. That's pretty cool. You guys have fun. That was chill. I very much enjoyed this dream
I hope you did too and again, happy Thanksgiving. Those either celebrate it. Hope you had a good one. I
Will see you guys the next stream. I I got some sponsored stuff to do on
Saturday we're going to be playing
Darktide I've seen a lot about it. It looks really fun
Vermintide was really cool. So actually excited really excited to play it. I'm gonna play Darktide. I'm gonna try to get some
Friends some friendos to play it. So I think it's a four-player co-op. I heard it at Darktide rocks
I heard it's really good. Yeah, I'm very interested in playing it and it's gonna be sponsors. That's cool
But I'm gonna try to find a group. I'm already talking to some people should be fun
That's on Saturday the 26th and then I don't know Sunday Monday
We'll figure the rest out but I will see you guys on Saturday. Take care of yourselves again. Happy Thanksgiving
That was Miku Picross actually really good Picross. It's a little bit more beginner-friendly
I think which is a good thing if you never played it before and if you like Miku then I mean obviously it's there
Appreciate it for hanging out. I'll see you guys soon. So Saturday stream will start probably around
230 Pacific I want to say around between 2 and 230
I'd say 230 Pacific is probably a safe place to put it. Is the VOD ever gonna get uploaded?
Ah, that's a great question. I would just check in like 10 minutes. See if it's even there expect more of these though
Where we just kind of hang out I open up something a little more chill and we just play it and just do whatever
See you guys Saturday. Yeah, Breath of the Wild is like that too
It is although I I can get a little high energy on those streams just because not very good
It's still fun and I'm gonna go when I'm gonna go probably take a bath tonight. Maybe we think take a bath
I think I'm out. Happy Thanksgiving. See you later. Good night everybody call your mother