Uh, Telix. Telix, me and you are the same exact character.
Well, we can't do this.
We are the exact same character.
Why? Why? Why are you me?
Why do we all have berets on?
Who is shooting at me? I-
Me and you are twin brothers.
Why do all three of us have berets?
We're like triplets.
Oh, hey, so how-
Why is he shooting at me?
Oh, I have a star.
My apologies.
Oh, I was diced.
I can't believe we're the same character.
Alright, get in this cop. This cop's gonna get the-
Quick, get in.
It's alright, it's Alex.
I don't think the cops want you.
This cop's gonna pull me out of the car.
What's with that rag, though?
You guys have to beat the cop.
Oh, no.
Let me in.
What?
Confirm this.
Are you wanted by the policeman?
Uh, no.
Okay, good.
Oh, my god.
I was trying to sandwich Alex right there.
Fortunately, it didn't work.
You're darn right it didn't work.
Are you throwing grenades?
No.
You made a grenade throwing motion.
Yes, you are. Those are grenades.
You are throwing grenades.
How did Blue die?
Get me out, get me out of the-
I got ran over by a cop.
I am innocent.
Explosions everywhere.
Get me out of the-
I splattered and killed you.
I made it out.
I have three stars now.
I made it out alive.
Wow, dude, you psycho.
What are you doing?
I'm going to get you.
Get away from me.
No.
What are you talking about?
That was the scariest thing ever.
I jumped down here. I'm down here.
I'm trying to find you.
I'm going to over the top rope land on you.
What?
Raymond Stereo from the Top Turnbuckle.
Right into Big Show's arms.
Get in the-
What the hell was that?
What's going on?
No, I don't want to get in the vaccine now.
Why is the car exploding?
Italics, are you shooting us from afar
with an explosive sniper rifle?
Who, me?
You son of a-
Explosions are italics.
Hey, I didn't kill you.
He's like posted up behind cover.
This is what I think of your cover.
Oh shit.
Oh.
I got to turn around.
We got to go around the way.
I got to try not to crash into a whole bunch of-
It looks like we went through a tunnel
and our arms broke in the tunnel.
Oh no.
What are you doing?
Asshole.
Let's do it in the cop car. That's more interesting.
Let's get everybody in the car.
I'm coming.
Hold off your trigger fingers.
I'm going to get killed first so I can take away my stars.
Oh, what the hell? Why do we have three stars?
What happened?
Oh, I did just get in the back of the car.
I have three stars right now.
We didn't do anything.
Okay, honest to God,
I really want to watch this back and see what the hell
we even did wrong.
I just shot a cop in the head like twice.
Alright, well let's turn this around.
All of us maybe
die and lose our stars.
I can't get in.
You don't have a wheel.
Wait for me.
This car is so screwed up.
We're not getting any speed.
We're going so slow.
We're actually turning around and going the opposite direction.
There are only cop cars in the city.
This is like drive on PlayStation 1.
Here we go.
Yay.
Oh, that sucked.
My head hurts.
Parachute.
He came over the ramp.
You did it.
Look at this drain. Look at this. What's going on here?
Are you getting sucked into a whirlpool?
Is that you?
Dude, we are sucked into this
whirlpool vortex right now.
Oh, it's like this terrain is
impossible to drive a motorcycle on.
Why is this happening?
There's lots of dead cops stuck outside the drain.
Look towards the dots
on your minimap. Here we go.
We're coming. We're about to fly to the drain.
Yeah, me and Boo are inside this
piece of jello.
Oh, wow.
I almost landed on one of the boats.
That's a pretty sick
jump. Alright, where's this drain?
Me and Boo are stuck in this
drain jello pudding.
I can't aim. My sensitivity is too high.
You can shoot?
Yeah, I'm still in this piece of crap.
Oh, what is this whirlpool?
It's a trampoline whirlpool.
What is this?
I was just standing on the bottom of the ocean
right there.
You can use your gun too.
Oh, man. This is...
I can't hit anybody.
Look at this guy. Look at this cop.
Oh, this is ridiculous.
You guys are in jello. What's going on?
I can't aim. My sensitivity is too high.
I've got an idea, guys.
I want to see if I can jump into that from the top.
I'm trying to get out. I got out.
Stay down there where it's safe.
This is a helicopter.
I've got an idea. I'm sending down a life raft.
Oh, my God.
What are you jumping in?
Jumping in with a cop car is a life raft?
You know, it would really suck
if you'd land on top of my bonnet
and I would have drowned.
Obviously, I would have been hurt
from the collision of you landing on me with a car.
Oh, the helicopter is shooting me.
I have no stars. Get away.
No, no.
They shot my raft.
Oh, my God.
Why did he do that?
A cop just jumped over the railing
and died in the water.
He dove in the water.
Why?
Why did he do that?
Did we lose our Jolo Whirlpool?
I think we did. Oh, my God.
What?
Dude.
Listen. Listen.
I tried to open the door of that car
and the guy was on, like, drugs.
He hit his arms.
His arms.
He's shooting me.
The cops are underwater.
I can't even explain
what just happened.
The guy was, like, shit-faced.
And then you plowed into me. He wouldn't get out of the car.
He would not get out of the car.
He was looking at me like
he was like...
Oh.
Oh, I found a helicopter over here.