Okay, so I had the- something's wrong. My ethernet port's fucked up, but whatever. All right, we're good. We're here.
Okay, let me ask you a question. Do you- all right, do you think- and by the way, I'm not even late.
I'm not even- it's supposed to be between 10 and 11 a.m. And I was early. Good thing I was fucking early, huh?
Because the stream was supposed to start between 10 and 11. Oh boy, good thing I turned it on at like 9 40.
Ugh. Ooh.
Not happy. Not happy. All right, technically not late.
Yeah, we're gonna play this game. I- I- in the process, I was getting ready.
I've wanted to play this since it kind of came up.
All guys back up. I'm not playing it. No.
No, I'm- I'm over it. I'm over it. We're playing barn finders.
I'm over it. I'm playing barn finders instead. And plus, I- I have the Twitter open. I can see that the servers are still done. No.
I'm back. Let's see. I'm gonna check to see if the-
Good thing I started fucking early.
Good thing the stream started like 30 minutes early.
What does it say?
We're aware of issues affecting matchmaking right now. We're working on a fix. It's not- it's not ready.
We're gonna play barn finders until it is.
And I don't even need to do an intro. I don't want- let's go. We're gonna play barn finders.
Are you ready?
No, Drew? No, I couldn't do it. I was gonna- oh, I- I would- I couldn't do it.
I was about to open it. I double clicked it and I was like, I don't want to fucking play this game.
I don't want to do this.
Now, who do I want to be? I promise this game's gonna be interesting. You're gonna love this one. I promise.
Okay, let me-
see if this works.
Hello? All right. I don't want to- I want to be-
I think there's a- there's a picture of me online that looks like this.
That's like every face I make in every photo. All right, what about- okay. Yeah, absolutely. One of these too.
I think this one.
Character's name?
Um, I don't know. How about, uh,
beer?
That's too easy though.
What's the title of this stream? I have like rage made that- what is it? What is it? Hunting for treasure trusts.
Okay, that's fucking-
It's gonna stay. I don't even care.
All right, let's go. Fine, it'll- it could be beer.
All right, that's good.
Barn finders. Profile represents your save file. All right, let's go.
New game.
Wait, hold on a minute.
FOV, make sure that's over 90 degrees.
FPS limiter, excuse me.
Oh, sensitivity way down.
All right, let's accept those settings.
Are you sure to start a new game? I- I hope so.
Who's the audio? How do I- how do I reduce audio?
All right, let's go.
So this is a game where you have to buy and sell shit that you find in barns. You're gonna do this in an auction system.
It was on the recommended in the discord. You can- you this mounts?
Like, did I run over that chicken? What was it?
Ah, the life of a GTA 5 NPC during the Trevor campaign.
Uncle Billy?
What game is- what are we playing?
This is- no, this is not Duck Dynasty. This is-
It's auctions and buying and stuff.
You have to find like hidden treasures in-
What's the name of that game where they yell at each other and they buy storage units?
And like they go through like old dirty diapers and somebody finds an old ring that's worth like 60 dollars.
What's- what's that called? What's the show called?
Did Wars? Storage Wars. Yes, that's what we're playing.
Okay, somewhere in America.
Uncle Billy, wake up. Young and our generator's down.
Get a battery for my truck and fix it. Let's work awful hard. Our vacation waits.
Take a battery from your truck. Place it in the generator. Hold on. This is like Skyrim. I just pick up everything?
What? It's got money? I got three dollars for taking that? What was it?
Press and hold to throw item. Turn the game up, please.
Okay, I got you. I got you.
Okay, now that was way too loud. Why is there a really loud bugawk sound?
Okay, is that better?
No, do I have to do it? Can I sell my coffee pots?
Recycle.
Six dollars. It gives valuable item, usable object. What's in here? Recycle everything.
Do I not eat the food? I just recycle the food. I don't eat it.
Recycling.
Can I recycle my bed? Can I recycle my toilet?
What's in here?
Can I crouch?
Yeah. All right. Well, recycle this.
I got 30 bucks. All right. So now what do I do with the 30 dollars?
Recycle this.
Welcome to Barn Finders. Get car battery from the car's trunk. Put it into the generator and use your computer
to find jobs and travel all over America. The server's a backup. I'm playing Barn Finders for at least half an hour.
All right. Can I sell this to somebody?
All right. Where's the truck? Why all sounds low, but the chickens sound. Come on. Wait, can I play basketball?
Okay, I think I've seen that on Vine.
Like 30 times.
That's every popular video on trending that was on Vine. All right. I got it. Nice. Wait, wait, wait. I'm supposed to get
Wait, wait, wait. Where's my truck? This is my truck. All right, get in the truck.
Holy shit, this guy scared the hell out of me. Okay, battery. Get the battery from the truck.
Weapons? All right, battery. All right, then we take the battery. Put it in the generator.
No, this is it right there. Gunshot.
All right, cool. Check your computer for a job. I got it. Now my computer turns on.
Oh god, okay. I'm afraid to open these.
A naughty stag for a friend.
Hello barn finders. Can you help an old friend?
So I heard there's a still a naughty stag at the old red barn. Maybe you could find it there for you.
There's money in it if you do.
Find the old stag at the red barn. All right, let's go to barn hub.
Travel bike. Wait, you drive cars in this game? It's automatic plus one liter grade.
Need to go to the red barn. Oh, I don't know. I only have 30 bucks.
Travel to red barn. Can I pick up the brick? I can't pick up a fucking brick. Are you kidding me?
I would have given this game like a full letter grid. All right, let's go. So how do I get there?
Michelle, wait, you open your shop?
Spam emails are cool. Check them out. All right. How do I drive the car? How did you get over here?
What? How did he get over there?
All right, store items. Store quest items. All right, I gotta go to red barn. What's it? But do I have a map?
How am I supposed to find red barn?
Just go to the only red barn in town? I have to go to the computer. I didn't have enough money.
Item cap. Barn hub. Here, red barn. Travel one gas.
How do I get gas? Can I buy gas? Gas, gas, gas, gas. Auto parts?
This looks incredibly elaborate. Gas, gas, gas, gas, gas, gas, gas.
Call mom. Where do you get gas? Antiques, play, death ray, tv.
Buy gas on the computer. No, you don't.
Where's the gas? Gas is on the map? Yeah, I don't know. I don't have any gas.
This is probably a stray gas can. Is this it? I just need to sell. I need a can of gas.
Recycle all your trash and buy gas. Wait a minute. Ah, look at that. I got one gas. Nice. Okay, cool.
Now we can go. All right, I'm ready. Remove motion blur? It shouldn't be on. I don't think there's
an option to remove it. Resolution, full screen. Yeah, texture quality. GPU memory. 700 million,
whatever it is. Oh, motion blur. Okay, grain. Get that off too. Uh, everything else is okay.
All right, let's go. All right, red barn. We got one gas. It's just a cut scene to drive the car.
That's hard. You gotta give me control of the car. Use resources to fix broken items. Turn off v-sync?
You would die on the way to the red barn if they let you drive.
Okay, maybe. All right, tutorial. As a barn finder, your job is to find requested items.
Look for other valuable items. You can sell them in your shop. Search for additional items
and secrets. All right, let's find a secret. Definitely one right here,
but it's probably stuff under things, right? Crash. Oh, that famous red barn. Let's explore. Oh,
open it up. Do I have a flashlight? Cigarettes. That's worth at least 10 bucks.
Oh, I actually kind of like this game. You just make money by recycling stuff and clean up a house.
Look at chat. You're blind. What? What? What? What? What? Sorry for interrupting your plans,
Jermis. Oh, now I feel like a dick. I feel like an asshole now. Oh, no. No. Was I like a whiny
streamer? Shit. No, I wasn't. No, I wasn't. You didn't hear it. I was off camera when I was gone.
That's a fake account. That's a not even a real account. No, I wasn't on camera.
You didn't hear anything. Oh, this is worth $70. Oh, 70 bucks. Well, the zoom in and zoom out.
All right, let's mark that for transport. Wait, study it. Why do I study it? Transport it. Press
T to transport. Transport it. Pick up in three, two. Oh, okay. He just takes it. Can I transport
this stuff? You baited by people. No, it's real. I don't have a key. Wait, it is. Let's go. Let's
go. Let's go. Right. Let's go. Back up. Is it working? No. No, don't do that. No, it's for real.
Has to be. Looking for a game to capture. Okay, here we go. Was it right? Come on. I'm just going.
I'm going. Let's go. Let's go. This is it. Let's go. Let's go. It's real. It's real. It's real. It's
real. Wait, hold on. What happened? That is real though, isn't it? You're so gullible.
But wait, hold on. Hold on a minute. You fucking really just got me with this shit? This person
didn't tweet that. You linked me a fake account of this person. That's supposed to be... That's not
okay. I was so ready. I was like, this is the... Okay. And I... Oh my God. And you even did like
the little... Oh, like, hey, at German 985. Sorry about that. Like, hoot. Oh, come on, man.
That's just my ego getting in the way. Like, oh, the Fall Guys guy hit me up. He must have seen
my stream. One of the top streams for Fall Guys. He must have came in and said, hey, man.
Oh, fucking dammit. You guys, seriously, what the fuck? All right, we're playing AI. I just... I
was in the middle of doing that. I was in the middle of doing something else. This is a fake
person. Wait, is it? No, it's a real person. How did you even do... Wait, Fall Guys owl.
What's the real person's name? This is... That's not all right. I'm playing AI dungeon. God damn it.
Why did I... I got absolutely... I got absolutely baited there. That's the worst one in a long time.
I was in the middle of playing something else. Oh, boy. Oh, boy. Okay. Here we go. AI dungeon
is what we're doing for now. I... What am I... Wait, I fucked it all up. Sending me like... All
right. Like, you may as well say that, like, if I send you to Bitcoin, you'll send me four.
Like, seriously, like, I just... I thought that was real. I clicked on it. I'm like, oh, this guy's
real. I trusted. I prepared myself for this shit. I'm so fucking sad.
All right. What we got? What should I pick? It's not even a real person. Stop tweeting at me,
this guy. This is a fake account. He's probably gonna get his account removed. Yeah. LOL. Sorry.
All right. Well, have fun with, like, your account. What do you want me to know?
He apologized. It's a real account. It's not a real account. I can't fucking believe it. I cannot
believe it. I am so... Words cannot even describe how just upset I am right now. I can't even tell
you. I didn't even save that last game, too. And now I'm going to be so turned off on that one.
All right. Let's do fantasy. Select a character. What's it going to do? What is it going to get
warmed up? All right. I want to be a wizard. Now I need, like, music, too, for this. I wasn't
ready for this shit. Fantasy music. Your character's name. Garfield. No, Garfield.
All right. Here we go. Didn't you guys say that? Is it text to speech?
Only for premium. Oh.
Why are you laughing? Why is the rat laughing? Why is... Why are they laughing?
Why are you laughing? Do I need to put it in quotes? Don't ask questions. Ask why are you
laughing, right? Say why are you laughing, right? Do I need that in quotes? Oh, you can't see.
You say, oh, that's new. Okay. So that works, right? You say, why are you laughing?
Man suddenly turns around and blasts you with a bolt of pure energy. You fall to the ground in
pain and see the book on the other side of the room. Okay. Do. What do you do? Grab at my pearls.
I don't know why. I don't know what that means. You grab at your pearls. You can't find your pearl
necklace and you feel something sharp prick your finger. It's your necklace. And the pearls are
back to normal that they must have been deleted from. Okay. Attack. Attack the rat. Attack the
rat man. You attack the rat man. You grab a rock from the ground and hurl it at the man. The rock
flies straight at the man who was too stunned to move out of the way. Throw another rock at his
head. You throw another rock at his head. The man turns around just in time to avoid the rock.
He sees another rock on the ground and picks it up preparing to throw it. You grab another rock
and throw it at the man. Dodge the rock. This guy has spells. Why does he need to do this yet?
Dodge the rock. You dodge the rock. The rock lands next to the rat man. Suddenly the rat man leaps
at you and bites your throat. You fall to the ground gasping for air. Grab rock and smash
his head. You grab a rock and smash his head. You grab a rock and hurl it at the rat man. The rock
lands on his head. Okay. Wasn't he on top of me? You grab a rock and hurl at the man. The rock
lands on his head. Your head starts to throb. Suddenly you fall down on the ground and fall
unconscious. Say, is there anyone out here who can help me? You throw it in the air and it fell
back on his head. You say, is there anyone out here who can help me? Your mouth tastes horrible.
Your mouth tastes horrible. You're lying on the ground. You look up and see a human standing above
you. He grabs your hand. Say, thank you. No, I'm, I'm in bad shape. I'm in bad shape. Slap his hand
away. I'm in bad shape. Don't worry. We'll get your help. Suddenly you feel the worst pain of
your life in your stomach. You fall on the ground and start to lose consciousness. Say, I ate raw
eggs earlier. Can you bring me to someone who can help? You're having organ failure. I ate raw
eggs earlier. Can you bring me to someone who can help me? He starts dragging you on the ground
towards the nearest village. You look up at him and see that his eyes are completely black. The man
is not a man. He is a monster. What kind of monster are you? I'm a man. What kind of monster are you?
You continue to get dragged on the ground. Suddenly you fall asleep. Your eyes flutter open and you
see the sun. Wait, so I just completely totally like misjudged this guy? Is he, am I, am I
hallucinating? What's going on here? All right. You flutter your eyes up and you see the sun. Okay.
Stare into the sun. You stare into the sun. You suddenly feel much better. You are in so much pain.
You just want to lay down and die. You look up at the sky and see a beautiful girl in a red dress.
Stare at sun until it hurts. No, until stare at sun and continue staring directly into sun.
I spell that right? You continue staring directly into the sun. The beautiful girl reaches her hand.
Suddenly you feel a blast of heat on your face. You scream in pain. Wait, is this from looking at
the sun? You start screaming in pain and fall to the ground. How many times? I'm just on the ground.
All right. Get up. You look around and see the man dragging you. You ask him what he is doing,
but he just ignores you. You feel like you're going to die. What do you do? I stand up. You stand up.
The man continues dragging you towards the village. Suddenly you notice a hole in your stomach.
You fall down and pass out. You face, your face becomes increasingly numb as you lose consciousness.
Do you have any water? No, do you? No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no. Excuse me. Do you have any
Gatorade? How do you spell Gatorade? Like that, right? Do you have any Gatorade? He stops dragging
you and looks at you. I don't have time for your foolishness. Say, do you have any water about
Powerade? He walks over to a nearby tap and takes a drink from it. And I have some water.
He pauses and thinks for a moment. I'll ask my wife if she has any. Where is your wife? Oh shit.
Oh no. Where is your wife? He starts dragging you again. Suddenly you feel a sharp pain in your back.
You continue screaming as the man drags you into the village. I'm getting my fucking ass kicked.
Give me water. Scum. You say, give me water, scum. He looks over his shoulder at you. Shut up,
or I'll give you something to really scream about. He continues dragging you. You finally
reach the edge of the village. What do you do? Cry. Start crying. You start crying. You're not
sure what is happening, but you're dying and all your dreams are gone. The man stops dragging you
and shouts something in another language. Suddenly a woman appears out of the crowd.
Please help me. I am dying. You say, please help me. I'm dying. She turns and leaves.
You're left there to die. In the end. How do I spell? Resurrect as a phoenix. You resurrect
as a phoenix. You become a phoenix and spread your glorious ashes to the wind. Who dares not? Who
dares not? How do you talk like in fucking old tongue? Who dares not give aid to thou in need?
You say, who dares not? Hold on. Let me get this. Hey, I got this now. I might as well use it.
Who dares not give aid to thou in need? There is no answer. You feel a great sense of loss.
You've lost all of your powers as well as your ability to fly. You are now immortal again,
although with a lot less pain. Oh man, that's not good. Okay. Uh, ask where? Say, where am I?
I want to know what the village is. You say, where am I? You stand on a beach. There's no
one in sight. Suddenly you feel a cold wind blowing. You look up to see a storm storm.
Go surfing. Go surfing. You walk out into the waves. They are gentle at first, but soon they
become much bigger than you could have imagined. Suddenly a large wave smashes you into the sand.
Grab my board and ride the waves. Next quest. Find a magical spell book called the Book of
Essence. You grab your board and ride the waves. You stand up and ride the next wave. You ride it
all the way to the shore. It was one of the best rides ever. Now see, go to the nearby
tourist trap themed bar. You go to the nearby tourist trap themed bar. You walk into the bar
and see that is filled with tourists. Right. You order a drink and you notice there's no bartender.
There are several round tables in the bar, each with its own bartender. Okay. Walk to bartender
and present annoying coupon. You walk up to the bartender and present an annoying coupon.
The bartender looks at you like you're an idiot. You explain that the drink is on the house.
He says that only happens if you buy a round of drinks for the entire table.
Buy a round of drinks for the entire table. Now I'm going to get my free drink.
You walk up to the bartender and give him your drink coupon. Okay. Buy a round for everybody.
Wait, no. No, that's my free drink. What do I want? Oh, okay. Let's be really annoying. Say,
I want a vodka drink, but don't feel like vodka. Do you have anything fruity without gin? You say,
I want a vodka drink, but I don't really feel like vodka. Do you have anything fruity that doesn't
have any gin in it? Bartender pours you a drink and says, here's your drink. But don't you dare
tell anyone that this is on the house. You sit down at a table. Yell out. Yell. I got this drink.
Say, scream. I got this drink for free. Scream. Free drink. Free drink. I got this drink for free.
You say, free drink, free drink. I got this drink for free. The bartender grabs you and says,
you can't just give this away for free. Where do you come from? I come from, I don't know,
New York City, Boston. Like a large tourist group. I come from, it's got to be from the city,
like Los Angeles. You know what I mean? You say, I come from Los Angeles. He shakes his head and
he walks away. You get a tap on the shoulder and turn around. It's the bartender. Okay, hold on.
Look behind me. Nothing personal. You look behind you. There's a big guy behind you. He looks angry.
He walks towards you and grabs you by the shirt collar and stares into your eyes.
Where the hell did you get this drink from for free? From the bartender. Smash drink on his head.
No, no, no, no, no, no. We're going to befriend this guy. Put all the blame on the bartender.
I got it from the bartender for free. I got it from the bartender. I got it from the bartender.
He stares at you and doesn't reply. He keeps on walking. You feel very scared and start trembling.
He continues walking towards the exit. Say, don't let the door hit you. He turns around,
looks at you and laughs. He begins to let go of the door, but then it slams into you and throws
you on the ground. Ow, my shoulder. Wait, was I behind him? Was I walking out with him? Did that
thing just happen where somebody holds the door for you and it's a heavy door and you don't realize
it and they let go right when you get kind of too close and the door fucking crutches you and you're
like, oh, fuck. That happens all the time to me. It almost breaks your hand and you try to pretend
like it doesn't hurt. You're like, oh, ow. Oh, thanks, man. Oh, ow, my shoulder. Okay, how about
it throws you into the ground? Say, be more careful. You say, be more careful. The door
closes and the angry man disappears. You stand up and see that you're in a kitchen.
You walk around and notice that there are several exit doors all leading into other rooms in the
house. Find the bartender. Find the bartender. Shit. You find the bartender. You walk into a
room with a big man in it. You try to speak, but he grabs you by the shirt collar. Who the hell are
you? I'm the boss. Get your hands off me. He doesn't respond. He just continues to stare at you. You
notice there are several people watching you from the corners of your eyes. Let me go. You're hurting
me. All right, fuck it. Grab him by the shirt like he's doing to me. You grab him by the shirt. You
pull him closer to you and he pushes you away and runs away. You don't chase him. You turn around to
the kitchen. Chase him. No, I ain't going to get like beat up four times. You chase him. You look
behind the kitchen and see that he's gone. You walk back to the living room. You continue looking
for him, but he's gone. Suddenly you feel your phone vibrating in your pocket. All right, answer
the phone or add some story in where I see him hiding behind the couch. Tell him to answer the
phone. Hand the phone to the man and have him answer it. Hand the phone to the man. Have
him answer it. He's gone. Find the man and have him answer the phone. You find the man and have
him answer the phone. You look for the man, but you don't see him. Suddenly your phone stops
vibrating. You wonder where he is. Then you get a notification. Someone just messaged you.
Look at the message. You look at the message. The message from a girl. She says that she saw
your video. She also says that the video went viral and you have over 300,000 views in one hour.
It replied. Reply to the girl. Let's see what it does. Block her. You send a message back to
the girl. You receive another message. Hey, do you know who this is? You reply to the message and
ask who it is. You say new phone. Who is this? You get a message back. Hey, it's me, Kate. Oh,
hey, Kate. I remember you from last year. Remember? That's how you know you don't remember this person
from last year. Okay. You get it. Hey, it's me, Kate. Oh, hey, Kate. Say, do you remember last year?
Yeah, it's me. I remember you too. All right. So who's going to crack to have both of us know we
both don't know who either one of us is. Remember me from last year? Yeah, I remember you too from
last year. Hey, it's me, Kate. Hey, it's me, Jeremy. Yeah, I know you. I know you too. When are we
going to get specific and find out who the liar is? Okay. How do you know me? I saw you when you
were coming out of the bank last year. You ran into me and broke my iPhone 5. Oh yes, I remember
now. That's how we're friends. Coming out of the bank, I bump into you and you drop your iPhone
in the shadows on the ground. Oh, sorry. Hey, you want to be friends? Say, it was a blessing.
The iPhone 5 sucks. I hope you got a new phone since then. You say it was a blessing. The iPhone
5 sucks. I hope you got a new phone. No, I still have the same phone. You stop talking. There's no
response for a while. Are you still there? Yeah, I'm here. Okay. So here's what happened. So I
didn't reply because all right, I'm kind of done with this conversation. I don't really care that
much about this. And I got the, are you still there? How much time passed? Like, shit, if I don't say
yes, I'm still here, then I'm an asshole, right? I'm that like, I want a dick. You're not going to
reply. Um, yeah, I'm here. And now I've committed to the conversation. How are your 15 kids? I don't
know. Like, what do you even talk about? You say, how are you 15 kids? They're fine. You? Oh, it's
the hardest job I've ever had. Right. You don't respond for a while. So do you know what the
nearest hospital is? Who is saying that though? Am I saying that to her or is she saying that to me?
I think that's her saying that to me. Is this the 16th kid? Is this for the 16th kid?
You say, is this for the 16th kid? Ha, yeah. There's a long pause and you can hear her
breathing. I need to go. I love you. You don't respond. Oh my goodness. Oh, wait a second. Wait
a second. Whoa, whoa, whoa. Hold on folks. From last year, we, what do you mean from? Wait, wait,
wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait. Hold on. You've your phone rings and I, I stopped. I didn't
answer it. I wanted somebody else to answer the phone for me. You look at a message and it was,
it's from a girl says, I saw your video. You remember me? Yeah. I remember you. I think from
last year. Yeah. Do you remember last year? Yeah. I remember. Oh boy. I, this is not good. Um,
what the fuck? This is, it's my kid. How you don't, we don't know that. You say, am I the father?
There's another long pause before she responds. Yeah. You're the father. I can't be with you.
There's a third pause before you respond. I, I'm not just going to hang up. That's fucked up.
Their names be Gary? No. Can their name be fruit snacks?
Can their name be fruit snacks? What? Their name can be fruit snacks. I don't know if that's allowed.
Fine. This is not fine. Uh, I can't wait to see little fruit snacks.
You say, I can't wait to see little fruit snacks. I love you. There's a pause.
I, you send the message and put your phone down. A few minutes later, you get a message. It's from
her. Hello. You say, hello, I'm pregnant. You don't respond. It's with twins. We need to meet up.
You don't respond. And the other one would be named fruit snacks too. There's a pause. Fine.
You stand up and walk out the door. The woman walks in as you're getting in your car.
Thanks for doing that. It means a lot. Okay. Go meet, go meet, go meet her or go meet,
go meet my pregnant girlfriend. What, what should I write? Go meet Kate. You go meet Kate. You walk
into the cafe. Hey, you're here. I was waiting for you. Yeah. I got your message. What's this about?
I press enter, right? You need help? Yeah. It's a pretty big deal. It involves you and some of your
friends. Where are the kids? I'm a wizard. Say, where are the kids? They're over there. You nod
your head and head to your friends. You walk into the cafe and see a group of kids sitting in a
corner. They look alike, but you can tell they're different people. Wait, what do you mean they look?
Wait, what? Wait, these kids are my friends? Wait, I don't understand what's happening.
What do you mean they all, they look alike, different people? What? Hi kids. What's going on?
You say, hi kids. They turn to look at you. Hey, we're waiting for Kate.
No, I didn't wait for Kate to arrive. You're the one that took my picture, right? But who,
who's saying, who's telling me this? Say, no, I, I know I, I did not take up any, no, I didn't.
Just no. I didn't take a picture of Kate. They know. Yeah, I am. I'm going to help you,
but I need you to do something for me. What? Never talk to or contact me ever again. Can you
do that? Yeah, of course. Good. Now say hi to the kids. Wait, hold on. All 15, 16 of these kids,
my kids, and they're my friends. Oh, um, okay. Never talk to me. Can I do that? Yeah. Okay. Go
say hi to the kids. Go to the kids. Go over to the kids and what? Say hello. You walk over to the
kids and give a little wave. Hi kids. Hi. Make sure you, I don't know. What, what should I say?
Make sure you try to do good in school and do good in school. I don't know. This is making me like
sad. One more thing. Make sure you do good in school. Okay. One more thing. Don't tell your
parents about any of this. If you do, I can't help you. Oh, great. That's all. Don't tell,
it's me. Don't tell your parents that you're going to do good in school. Go back to Kate.
You walk over to Kate who's already sitting down. So, oh, there she is. The man gets up and the two
of you head out the door. Who is this? You say, who is this? She's a good friend. Just don't expect
her to be your typical escort. Wait, you shake your head and continue walking. How much is it
going to cost? Wait, just fucking sprint out of the bar. You sprint out of the bar and run down
the street. Settle down there. You skid to a halt and find yourself in front of the police station.
Sit on the sidewalk. You slump against the building and fall into the sidewalk. You sit and think
about what to do. Suddenly your phone rings. You pull it out of your pocket and see that it's
Claire's number. Oh no. Answer the phone. Hey, it's me. Claire, is everything okay? Did something
happen? Man, everything's fine. I just want to see how you are. I'm fine, thanks. I'm just having
lunch with some friends. It looks like I might be here a while. Are you doing? You say, how are you
doing? I'm fine. Just wanted to see how you're doing. Do you want me to meet up later? That'd
be good. Okay. Yeah, I have magical powers. Eat the phone. Eat the phone. You eat the phone. You
put the phone back in your pocket and go eat your food. Okay, go to Claire's. Am I just in like these
big magician rogues with a magician's hat on? Like a wizard hat? Weren't we supposed to be in like
medieval times? What's going on? You go to Claire's. You get in your car and you drive over to Claire's
house. You pull into the driveway and kill the engine. You sit there in the silence for a moment
before grabbing the package of cigarettes and pulling one out. Smoke all the cigarettes.
Smoke all of them at one time. Smoke all of them at once. You pull out your lighter and light the
cigarette. As you take your first drag, you notice a man watching you. He's average height and weight
and he's wearing a dark blue shirt. Roll down the window. You roll down the window. You stick
your head out the window and motion the man to come over. He nods and walks over.
What can I do for you, sir? I'm looking for Claire. I'm here to see her. Who are you? I'm her boyfriend.
Well, you can't just show up at my house like this. Can I see some identification?
Okay, show him my Chuck E. Cheese membership card. Show him my Chuck E. Cheese Platinum
membership card. You show him your Chuck E. Cheese Platinum membership card. He looks at you and
turns it over. I see you're a member of Platinum, but I don't see that you have any other special
privileges. I have the only card. Show him my Dave and Buster's membership card. You show him
your Dave and Buster's membership card. He looks at it and turns it over. I see that you're a
member of Dave and Buster's, but I don't see that you have any other special privileges. Show him
my VIP. My VIP Costco card. My VIP Costco card. My VIP Blockbuster card.
No, no, no, no, no. Show him my... Yeah. You show him your VIP Blockbuster card. I see you're a
member of the VIP Blockbuster card, but I don't see that you have any other special privileges.
They don't matter. Show him my American Express Metal Millionaire card. Let me see. I see that
you're a member of the American Express Metal Millionaire. I don't see that you have any other
special privilege. Show him my voting license. I see you're a member of the voting license,
but I know you're not. This doesn't matter to me. God damn it, man. Okay. I see you're a member of
the 3% back rewards, but I don't see that you have any other special privileges.
I didn't even say that. Show him my special privileges. No, show him my skeleton key.
I see you're a member of the Access card, but I don't see that you have any other special...
I'm just gonna write... I'm gonna write on a piece of paper, special privileges,
and then hand it to him. There. You hand him a handmade ripped note stating special privileges.
He looks at the ripped note and then back at you. Hmm. I see. Well, I suppose I can see you
if you're willing to wait around for a bit. Follow me. Thank you. Jesus. The man leads you
through a foyer into a living room. There's a leather chair and a table in the middle of
the room with a beautiful vase on the table. Turned vase upside down. Or... Wait. You turn the vase
upside down. The vase shatters to pieces as you hear a click from the end table next to the
leather chair. You see a pistol with a silencer on it. What? Grab the gun. I found the secret
hidden like gun compartment. You grab the gun, hold it in your hand, and point it at the man.
Who the hell are you? What the hell are you doing? My name is Lewis. I'm a cop. This is my apartment
and these are some of my firearms. Put the gun down. Okay. Put the gun down. Why do you have a
gun? People I work for are very organized. They're great at getting what they want and they always
get it. Why do I have to ask? What, am I in school? Can I use the bathroom? Sure. It's just down the
hall and to the left. You walk into the hallway and look at your reflection in the mirror. You
are a skinny kid with no facial hair or muscle tone. Wait, why am I a skinny kid? Oh, fuck,
this still says I'm playing the other game, doesn't it? Shit. Hold on. Wait, hunting for
treasure chests. That's real. I can stay. Okay. You flex in the mirror. You flex your bicep. You
notice the gun in your hands. We need to talk about what the gun is talking to me. Put it down.
You put it down. It's sort of private. I'm sure it is, but the more people who know what's going
on, the safer it is. It's not that big of a deal. Why is the gun talking to me?
Shoot the mirror. You fire the gun and the mirror shatters. You stare at your reflection
and then go into the bathroom. You stare at yourself in the mirror for a while. What are you
doing in there? What the heck? What are you doing in there? Shoot in the toilet.
You put the gun under the toilet and pull the trigger. What? Like in the toilet bowl in the
water? What was that? It was nothing. You don't seem very convincing. Well, I'm not. You wash
your face with the toilet water and flush it. Don't do that. Why not? Because some of us can
still use a mirror. Are you crazy? What else? This has got to be more after that. You're not
going to give me anything? It's just easier. I don't care if it's easy. I like looking at
myself in the mirror. Well, you're not my type anyways. Leave. Leave. Leave. Leave. Exit. Okay.
All right. Okay. All right. All right. All right. All right. All right. All right. All right. All
right. All right. All right. All right. All right. All right. All right. All right. All right. All
right. Okay. Um, I have, we've moved on. I'm in another segment in different scenario. Okay.
You leave. Get the, you raise your voice as loud as you can. What the hell is going on? We're
robbing the bank. How much do we have? About $7,000. I don't see any masks or guns. We don't need
them. Oh, why not? Because the tellers are too busy panicking to notice anything. Do we have a get out
of jail free card? No. And what the hell is the point? Because this really isn't that serious.
When you got nothing but time, I'm sure you'll explain it all. Take all the money and give it
to everyone in the store. Spending on candy. Take all the money and give it to everyone in the store.
That's a really stupid idea. Why? Because the robbers will get caught and we'll get fired.
Ask him if the joker put them up to it. Where's the joker? I've been missing a lot by not using
the dragon AI model. Is that in this website? Where's the joker? What happened? We had a small
disagreement and he left. Who is this guy? Do dragon AI. You have to pay premium for it. Oh,
the dragon model tells better stories. Cost money. Click the gear. I'll do that probably
another time. I'll buy it and we'll do it. It's worth it. We'll do it again. Is fall guys ready
to play yet? Don't tell me. Yes, it is. If it's not, there's a week free trial. Click, click,
hold on. I don't want to fucking boot apologize for this poor service stability. Rest assured
everything will be up and running very soon. In the meantime, here's a sneak peek at the new rat.
This is fake. This is not real. It's not real. It's not ready. Check other streamers fake news.
Oh, I know it's ready.