Oh, yeah. Whoa, whoa, whoa. Wait a second. Wait. What is this? That was the most shocking
thing ever. Why am I shooting a machine gun at people? What happened to the cut scene
I was just watching? I was seriously going to start saying stuff. I have no, I don't
even know what to say. All I know is this. This was heavily requested that I... What
the fuck is going on? Look at this stupid controls. Stop giving me control if you're
just going to take it away. What the hell? What the hell's going on? Why did the bike
explode? What? No, don't even tell me. Don't even tell me his bike's going to explode.
Why? No. Oh, no. Oh, let's punch him and kick him. And I wonder what's going to happen
to his bike. Get the fuck out of here. Go blow up somewhere, dickhead. How did that
not take them off their bikes? And this guy with like his fucking lawnmower, like is this
guy driving a lawnmower? What is that thing? Seriously, get off like you have John Deere
and fight like a man. Oh, here comes like another guy. I've been driving in a straight
line for like at least a few minutes. How much further is it up down the road? Up down
the road. Yeah. Is that Scooby Doo? Hold on a second. Hold on. I need to go see Scooby
Doo and the gang. Get on the bike. I have Scooby Doo to track down. There it is. There
it is. Go back. Go back. Oh my goodness. All right. Let's slow down a little bit. I need
to see if okay. Okay. Alrighty, then. I can't move. Okay, I can move. I got it. How do you
Okay, you can block by holding space. And that's a punch. Oh, sick combos. Oh, look
out additional thugs. Just so you just punch them in the face. So this game is equal parts
terrible racing equal parts awful beat him up with a camera that doesn't even know where
it wants to go. Can I grab him or something? Oh, are we are we only throwing punches that
like drunk teenagers punch like throw? Oh, yeah, I did like a quick time event on you.
Hey, don't don't talk to my girlfriend like that. Don't talk to my girlfriend. She's my
girlfriend. No, you are slept alert. I can't believe you. Yay. It's fine. It's like fireworks,
honey. Don't worry. Yeah, I've come to the conclusion. This is probably the worst game
I've ever played in at least this generation. I mean, like something like big rigs over the road
racing like you saw the last video in this in this kind of series. That game came out a long time
ago. It had like a this game doesn't have any excuses. This is a next gen game. Why is it this
bad? Why is this game this dumb? This is like a next gen game for like, I don't know. I have no
answers. If somebody can give me the answer that I would love to hear it. What did his audio clip
just cut off? Okay, you know Batman Arkham Asylum and like Arkham City and stuff. It's almost like
they saw that game. And they said that's a really good fighting mechanic. Let's like put that in our
game too. But the reason why that was so much fun in the Batman games is because you're fighting
like a dozen people at the same time. And it's not just the same animation over and over again. It's
like completely like the countering system in Batman Arkham. This is like turning into like a
Batman Arkham Asylum is a fun game video, which it is. I mean, that's who can deny that Batman
Arkham City Arkham Asylum. Arkham Origins I'm sure is going to be good. Let's give me talk about
something good and not something bad like that. Who is this? Is this Macho Man Randy Savage?
Or is that Mr. T? Yeah, this aiming system is honest to God. I think it's trying to make me.
I think it's trying to auto aim for me. But there's no option to turn it off. Look at this.
When I go when I graze by an enemy, watch what happens. It's like goes out of control
right by him. Come on. You know, you want you don't want to aim at the ground. You want to
aim at me. I'm up in the window. Can you see me? Yeah, I'm up in the window. There you go.
No, no, no, not to the up in the window. Oh, you got me. Oh, I bet you $1,000.
They don't kill me. I bet you $1,000. I can walk right up to these crates and be completely fine.
Let's see. Yeah, I'm almost at the crates. They're getting a little more accurate.
I made it to the crates. And I'm completely on. Oh, you're you just got scared. Sure. Sure thing.
Sure thing. Yeah. Good. Good. Good. Good. Go back to the kick technique. Why am I missing him? What
the fuck am I missing him for? How am I missing him with a wrench? I'm hitting these guys with
a wrench and it's not even touching them. I'm done. If somebody you know owns this game,
go to their house, get them a cup of coffee, brew them some tea, get them a nice warm blanket,
wrap it around them and tell them you're sorry. Say, man, I know you spent like 20 bucks on that
game. I'm really sorry. Here's some tea and here's a blanket to keep yourself warm because you're
you're probably cold on the inside from playing this game. Thank you all so much for watching and
really do appreciate it. See you all next time. Take care, everybody.