Yeah, we'll do Dread X. Alright, what are some must-play games in the Dread X Collection 1?
What is the must-play from Dread X 1? Oh my god, I can't even... Can I not even launch this game?
Okay, I think I have to go... This is weird. Alright, never mind. Weird. That was weird.
Everyone fears losing their mind.
Let me just make sure this is not too loud. Alright, so which one should we do?
There is Don't Go Out, Hand of Doom. We did that one a little bit.
Summer Night Outsiders, Rotgut, Pony Factory, Shatter. We did this one. I wasn't fair to this
one. I was annoyed at the internet. Do Rotgut, Pony Factory, Summer Night, Rotgut, Pony Factory.
Alright, we'll do Pony Factory. Let's go. Does it matter? I should do... Okay, that's fine.
That should be fine. I remember these old... No, it's not. I remember these. It used to be... Wait,
what happened? Anytime that popped up, it was always like, alright, we're in for a real one.
Wait, what? What? Really? Oh, shit. Alright, let's go. Duskdev made this. Oh, shit. Alright,
let's do it. Let's do it. Alright, so this is Lights Out, Begin Game. I'll turn the lights off.
Lights are going off. Sure. It's because of Mambians. Here we go. Winston arrived at a solution
to the moral decay of his town. He called out to Hel in a secret candlelit room one evening,
and Hel answered him. The human body could, Hel promised, be twisted, stretched, and broken into
a kinder, more... a queen shape? The human heart molded into something less human. Winston's town,
now filled with the cruel and the ignorant, could instead be filled with magic ponies,
if he could provide a factory in which to make them. Winston thought they could be beautiful,
gentle, and good. Yeah, Hel had other plans. I don't think so. No, no, no, no. Okay. WASD.
There's no sprint. Pick up. What is this? Oh, God. You actually have to shoot stuff? Locked.
Look for the unlocked door to complete each area. This is unlocked. Okay. Hold left mouse to fire
the bolt gun. Hard reload. Keep on the lookout for ammo pickups. I'm telling you, I'm the guy that
distracts people at the door. I distract people at the door. I'm the, you know, I'm the guy with
the glasses. The actor, you know, doesn't zoom in. It says the actor. And it's like a quick few cuts
of me doing things and like distracting people and doing like a magic trick behind them and stuff.
I'm not the person that comes in and does this. That was, those are very loud. The amount of
question marks. I don't think a lot of you guys were here earlier. I hear something running. I'm
at almost an ammo, man. What did that say? The game's loud. Um, hold on. Let me help you there.
I helped. Can you not see? What the fuck are you talking about? I just reloaded my gun.
That you were not in the hallway before. I have no ammo. I'm dead in one hit. That thing was not
here. See? Oh my God. I'm dead. Just kill me. Kill me. Kill me. Kill me. Whatever. I got him with
every shot. Holy fuck. Okay. I need health right now. Oh my God. There's another enemy type
what is it doing? I think I'm in trouble here. One. Why are you guys saying one? One. Why is
every saying one? All right. I'm in a much better position than I was last time. I have 15 shots,
70 health. Here he comes. Okay. Thank God. Is that ammo? That's a lot of ammo, isn't it?
No, it's just tape. It's tape. Oh my God. Oh my God. I'm dead. Oh fuck. I'm dead. What do I do?
I have no way. I don't have enough ammo. I don't have enough ammo. I have 19 bullets.
I can't kill all these people. Oh fuck. All right. That was that was actually pretty scary.
That was fucked up. I can't beat it though. I saw you need to you need to be really in there
and you got to get in there and get use your eyes. Okay. That was terrifying. Let's do another one.
Which one? Summer night. People saying to play rock out. Some people said summer night too.
Somebody else said steam is back up. Let's do. Yeah, let's do rock up and then I'll
we'll do a few more of those steam games too. It's bright. Oh my goodness. This
looks like the old starting soon screen. Have you seen the trailer for the Morbius game?
Yeah, it looks fucking cool. You'll see a rock at the curve of Gano street when you do walk into
the woods. I was pissed when they said they were making it a card game though. What's going on?
It's like you you get other cards and you use those cards to level up the other cards.
I don't know. I'm not into it. And how are they going to have anybody actually give a shit about
that game? I mean, it's just all different versions of Morbius. There's no other Marvel
characters in it. It's like Morbius in a suit. Morbius in a tuxedo. Morbius in his beast form
and stuff. It's just like, why the way? I don't care. There's no other Marvel characters in the
game. I don't know if they think that it can sell on its own, but I don't think it can.
All right, I need to find Gano street. Is this I mean, this looks like woods to me.
Are these the woods? Big bank. Okay. It's like an underground dance party. This guy is really high.
This guy is high as a kite. If that's the only move you're doing. Okay, so what's the deal?
Yeah, like I was sweaty. Really sweaty. Just keep going. It's just it's the freaking peanuts.
All the different Charlie Brown dances. Okay, what am I looking for? Look behind you. Nobody's
following me. Rock got rock got who said that? Did I say that that I said that this guy doesn't
is not very scared. Look behind you. It's a chair. Where's the light coming from? What? I'm here.
What is this for? Green mold cake time? Are these? Okay, these are not these are not butterflies.
These are asses. Okay, right. Those are asses. Of course, let's get this shit out of me. Why
would you ever come down here? Like, why would you ever do this? Would you ever come down here?
Okay, I would come down here. If all right, if we if there was like 50 of us, and 10 of them were
20 of them were professional bodybuilders, then yeah, I'm only coming down here with 50 people.
No, 100. You're a chicken. No, I'm only doing this if there's and I'm 10 people's too little,
10 people's too little 20 people's too little to for me to be comfortable being down here.
There needs to be three, four, five rows of people all walking down this way. Because I mean,
if there is a rot gut, he's a kind of a big scary guy, or like a monster or something.
You understand that if he starts grabbing and attacking somebody, 10 people are going to get
on top of him and like one of the bodybuilders is going to wrap around and like start choking him
out. Like grabbing him behind like this and fucking holding him like this. Like somebody
going to grab him and choke him. What the fuck was that? Was that the sus guy? What was that?
What the hell was that? Was that the sus fucking face? What was that? What I did, I like just caught
the end of that. What the fuck just happened? I just saw the sus face. And that was really weird
because I was like pretending to go like this and like, and I let go and I just started seeing
things. I'm like, wait, I didn't do that. It was it was some woman. Okay. But you know what I mean?
And we're all going to have various weapons, right? Like, like pipes, like tire iron,
regular clothes iron, and you're coming down here with 50 people. And and one person is going to be
the electronic specialist. They're going to have a backpack with like 10 cell phones with SIM cards
in them and shit. Like like a traveling like communications guy. We're going to we're going
to have this guy have a backpack with like 15 SIM cards in it to make sure we have a cell phone
signal. And that guy's right in the middle. We keep that guy directly in the middle. So no matter
what our electronic specialist can like reach the surface. I don't care if this guy's to walk around
with a huge antenna behind him going up almost touching the ceiling. I'm almost at the end.
It's gonna be horrible. I just scared myself. What is it? What is it? What is it? What's rotgut?
It's gonna blow up. You went the wrong way. No, I didn't. It's gonna be like,
what the fuck is happening? It's gonna scream. I'm just warning everybody. It's probably gonna
scream in your face. It's getting closer. It is. Oh shit. Get the fuck out of here. What about what's
going on? I'm getting outside. What the hell is going on? What was that? Game crashed. Rotgut.
What happened? What happened? My mouse? I can't look. My mouse is not even on the screen. I can't.
I have to like force quit the game. I can't get out of here. You just psyched yourself up.
I beat it. Okay. That's kind of cool. What else is on here? Oh, right. I was going to do the some
more of the steam stuff. All right. We'll do the one that everybody wanted me to play. That's
what is it called? The one I had just downloaded. Do Summer Night. Okay. We'll do Summer Night.
Absolutely nothing scary happens in this game. For best results, play in a dark room and wear
headphones. Use Alt F4 to leave. Well, that's full of shit. What? What's going on with the moon?
20 points. Yeah, I'm not smoking anything. What's this one called? This is called Summer Night.
The Dread X Collection number one. There's like five or six of these. I imagine eventually you'll
play them all. Or at least some of them. Or most of them. Whatever. Lovely night. Watch out. Watch
out for that guy. Watch out. Watch out. Don't touch the poop. Can I move it? Get out of the way. So
what? Just some weird guy comes and like shits on your lawn? Monkey business. Get out of the way.
Get out of the way. They're blocking the way. Warm breeze. This thing is going to scream in my
face. I'm telling you. I already know. I know it's gonna scream in my face. It's gonna be like
I'm waiting for it to scream. See? It just did. I got it. I got it. Funny fungus. Hey, stop. Don't
even. That is something. I heard a sound. What was that? Can you hear that? Meet me in the park. Can
you guys hear it? Is it too low? I can't turn it up. I don't think. It's like a turn it up. Can't. I
can't hold on. Next transition. I'll do it. It's gonna hopefully it's not too loud. Don't stop
hitting me. If I if I try to get if I alt-tab it's gonna close the whole thing out. All right. Let
me try. Come on. Come on. Come on. Can you see? I got it. Nice. It said time flies. You're gonna.
Okay. Yeah. Here's the thing. Didn't work. Didn't fucking work. You know why? Because there's no
door over there. Now if that came from over here I would go. Yeah. What's going on with the moon?
Come on. What is that thing? I'm telling you. I'm only doing things with like 50 people. You know
what I mean? I'm like anytime I go anywhere it's gonna be a hundred people. We're all gonna like be
ready. That's not scary. There's just like a rat in the attic. Nice try. Is there on my webcam?
Ah. That's. I didn't even. I've been holding right here this whole time. The battery is going.
My itchy face. The battery's gonna go to zero and some hands gonna come over and grab and pull and
it's gonna scream at me. Error. Okay. I don't know what it is but like I feel like a lot of older
people jumpscares like don't work. I'm gonna pretend to be like a fucking 70 year old.
Whoa. What was that? Holy smokes. Oh he's an ugly one. I tried to punch. I'm trying to put.
Somebody's breathing. How am I supposed to go over there? Why would you punch? I'm telling you. I'm
doing. I'm doing a triple crowhop. Like crowhop. Crowhop. Crowhop. Punch as fucking hard as I can.
Directly square here. As hard as I possibly can and try to take that fucking head off.
We're talking crowhop. Crowhop. Crowhop. Fucking wham. You know what I mean? No not the game.
Like the monster. Not the game. What the fuck? Are you kidding me? I knew it was gonna be something
weird. Dude how come there ain't 50 people in this house? Huh? Give me the batteries. I did it.
Those batteries were huge. That was creepy. That was creepy. That was a good one. By the way,
monster is in my house. I don't fucking. I don't care. I mean that fridge is coming down.
I mean like monster in my room. Oh my god. I'm in like the kitchen. Monster's right there.
I'm grabbing the fridge and I'm gonna fucking he-man that thing and just like rip it out of the
fucking wall and just toss it down and smash it down and shit. I'm grabbing every kitchen knife
like. I'm grabbing the frying pan. That's over there. You over there. You're getting a fucking
boom. You monster. You fucking big scary motherfucker. You're getting a frying pan here.
Stop dude. That was your. You made this joke already. You made this joke already. It's not
a monster. It's somebody that like lives in the house. It's like your mom. No dude. Mom's like
coming out for a fucking midnight snack. I ripped the fridge out of the wall. Dude,
that's just a pizza guy. I'm telling you. TV is coming off the stand. I'm going to Tom and Jerry.
Cartoon style. Crush this into this person's. Into this whatever. This is monster's head.
The vacuum cleaner. Oh my god. I'm holding the vacuum cleaner the other way.
Like a joke weapon from fucking Dead Rising. And this is. I'm baseball swinging the vacuum
into their head. I'm telling you what would happen. I'm telling you what would happen.
Monsters. Oh. Turns out it's like. Okay. By the way. It's. It's on its back and it's
crabbing backwards at you. All right. That's a really bad position to be in. I'm going to.
I'm fucking macho man. Randy Savage. Elbow dropping you right in the fucking stomach.
I'm running up and I'm going to fucking just right in the middle. What a terrible position
for you to be in. They're getting the people's elbow. Or vacuum cleaner. Just get it ready.
Up. Down. You would get eaten. There's no way I'm getting eaten. What happened to my webcam?
No. There's no way I'm getting eaten. Oh you think I'm going to get eaten?
Into the freezer. All the frozen food is coming out. And I'm taking it out of the
package and throwing it out. I'm going in the fridge. All the raw meat is just like
getting thrown out in front. Every piece of food that I have. It's going to be like meat.
It's going to go for it. And that's when you go fucking. Right. Oh my God. That was probably
so loud. How sweaty I am. Was that loud? Okay. Okay. Thank God. Dude. Just keep like big boots up
in your bedroom. You hear like. I've come to get your soul. Whatever. Right. Oh. Oh. Those
boots are going on. And I'm running out there. I don't care if I'm fucking naked. I don't care
if I'm naked. I'm going to be in huge boots. And I'm just going to fucking. I'm going to get my soul.
I'm going to get my. You're going to be trying to eat me. And by the way they're going to be
two sizes too big. Two sizes too big. What am I talking about? I'm talking about if a monster
were to. Horror movie style be in my house. Normal shoes. What if it was a dinosaur?
What are you talking about? A dinosaur is an old animal. Why would it be a. If it's a dinosaur
then. Okay. Then that's a. I guess I'm dead. Oh no. No. I would. No. What I would do.
Excuse me. I would take the standing lamp that's in the living room. I would take.
Unscrew the light out of the standing lamp. Take the lampshade off and have a javelin and just throw
it. Like right into the fucking dinosaur's heart. You know what I mean? Like. Do you really think
you are special enough for a monster to come after you? I don't know. He's going off the record.
What do you mean off the record? No. If a dinosaur came to the house. I would just go out. I would
just go. I would. I would meet the dinosaur outside. And I would go like this. Be huge. I'm
much. I'm huge. I'm much bigger than you. Like this. My arms would be in the air. And I'd be
going like this. Go away. Go away. Go away. Go away. It would work. Imagine what. I'm just
seeing like a clip from a movie in my head. I'm out there like go away. Go away. Go away. And it's
just. I'm the first to die in the movie. I the first to go. That's the opening scene of the movie.
All right. Anyways.