Hey, what's going on everybody? It's Dr. Jermick here, at my desk using my mouse and my keyboard going to put some patient files into the directory.
Let's see here. Anyways, I'm a doctor now. As you know, I have my doctorate in surgery.
Oh, let me just get this telephone here for a second. Hello? I don't care. I'm a goddamn doctor now. Get this phone off the desk.
Oh, everything must go.
We are going to do an ambulance mission. Now what this is, you will see very shortly.
In addition to the original game, you can do stuff in ambulances, and I've never done it before, and it's incredibly difficult and crazy.
So here we go. Gonna do the transplant, heart transplant, in the ambulance. Here we go, baby.
Get this off. Thank you. So far so good. How am I gonna do this here?
I should probably...
Hey, like, watch the potholes, asshole guy driving the car.
Okay, the back of the door just opened. Are you serious?
Come on. What are we doing? Are we on like a roller coaster right now or a road?
No, I'm gonna lose my tools. Hold on. Where's the...
Wait, there it is.
Come here. Come here.
Come here.
Pick it up.
Okay, here we go.
Nice and easy. Nice and easy.
Get me into that rib cage.
Hey, can you, like, stop at a Taco Bell while you're at it? I'm, like, kind of hungry.
Jesus Christ.
I'm gonna kill this guy.
I'm legitimately going to kill this guy.
I almost got the rib cage done.
Get this out of here.
Get this glass tube off the guy. Come on.
Hold on, I gotta... I gotta start to move some of this stuff.
Do not lose this. Put it down right there.
Here, we'll, like, throw this at an oncoming car.
Well, the doors don't even open anymore.
Okay, good, good, good. So far, so good.
No, no, no, no, no, no.
No, no. I still need to open this.
Come here.
And everyone thinks I'm on drugs.
The whole point of this game is... Oh, great, there's a saw in his body.
The whole point of this game is you're supposed to be, like, a guy on drugs.
Like, that's the joke.
Where's the guy driving the car? How many beers did this guy have?
Come on.
No, I'm gonna lose this guy already.
Here we go, here we go. That's what I want.
That's what I want.
Just shut up for a second, car.
Get that toaster out of the way.
Where's the heart?
Where's his heart?
Where's the heart that I was supposed to transplant?
Did it go out the back door?
Oh, it's already over.
He's losing a lot of blood. It's necessary, though.
It's completely necessary.
No, hold on to it still.
Don't I have... Where's my syringe?
I need to, like, feed this guy drugs so he doesn't die.
Almost, almost.
No, come on.
All right, where's the syringe?
There it is, there it is. Come here.
Come here. Come on, stick him in his face.
Yes. Yes.
We're good. We are good.
Just need to cool it here.
Don't want to lose the hearts right here.
Oh, no. God, that heart's gonna fly out the back.
Protect the heart. Protect the heart for the time being.
Okay, the doors are closed.
God damn.
Get out of the way.
I still gotta get those two pieces of ribs out of there.
I gotta get those, like, riblets from chilies out of there.
All right, so far so good.
So far so good. So far so good.
No, I need to cut those. I still need to cut those.
No, don't put that...
No, come here.
This thing's gotta go.
This is gonna fly into his face and kill him.
Come over here. Where's the scalpel?
I just need a scalpel.
Gotcha. Gotcha. Gotcha. Gotcha. Gotcha.
No.
No, I just got hit with the drugs.
This is gonna be ten times more difficult now
because I am on, like,
whatever the hell it is, morphine.
No, dude.
Are you serious? I was so close.
I don't even know what I'm cutting into right now.
Hopefully his heart.
This is gonna make me die.
I'm gonna throw up looking at this.
Is the heart free? I can't even see.
Is the heart free? I have no idea.
Let's see if I can pull it out.
Nope. Easy.
I just gotta cut into the...
This is gonna be really bad, guys.
Where is a scalpel?
Can I please find a scalpel
in this mess of an ambulance?
I got a tool.
Got a tool. Here we go.
Slice these ventricles. Slice these ventricles.
No.
I gotta cut one more. Cut one more.
Get out of the way!
No!
Good, good. Open that up. Throw all these up.
Out. Out. Out with you.
Out with you. Out with you. Out with you. Out with you.
I don't think I have enough blood.
He's gonna lose too much blood right here when I try to cut him.
There it is.
One more precise cut. Right there.
Right there. Right there.
Cut it! Now we just need to cut the ventricles.
I'm, like, leaning into the
computer right now, guys. This is, like, so intense.
There's one. Right? No?
Give me that cut.
Give me that cut. There it is.
I gotta get this last one. I got it.
Got it. Got it. Wait, no, did I?
There's one more. That red one.
Holy jeez! Where's the heart?
Where's this other heart? Come here!
Oh, pop it in the air.
No! No!
No, get in! Get in his
chest. Get in there.
Get in. Yes!
Wow, that was ridiculous.
That was intense. I can't even imagine doing, like, the brain
surgery. There's brain surgery, there's
kidney transplants, and heart transplants.
I have no idea how the hell you'd be
able to do that with a brain transplant one.
But anyways, guys, that's Surgeon Simulator 2013!
And, uh, it's on Steam right now.
I believe it is ten
bucks? I could be wrong. I believe it's ten dollars
on Steam. And I'll see you guys all next time.
Thank you so much for watching. Take care,
everybody.