Oh, you're in big trouble. You're in big trouble. Wow.
The sea is still this morning. The fresh pine scent fills the air, and the shining sun beats down on
the newly crafted pyro shark nest. She will need to be careful though, for predators lurk around
every corner. The winter months are always the most difficult for pyro sharks, so the summer sun
gives them plenty of time for the necessary hunt. The food is scarce, and the coming months will be
grueling, but the incredibly strong will and sheer cunning of this young female might just help this
endangered beast to another spring. Our first journey begins in Lakeside. This small, quaint
pool houses quite a large surprise. Weighing in at over 12,000 pounds, the pool room pyro
shark is a wonder to behold. The graceful swimming technique known as unguntu has been passed down
from generation to generation. Now, as one could probably imagine, this particular breed likes to
be alone and does not take kindly to would-be encroaches. This pool is not big enough to house
more than one pyro shark, unless of course, he happens to be mating. Unfortunately, most
pool room pyro sharks do not make it out of this pool because of their own laziness. Frequent sniper
and spy attacks kill most of them. Hopefully, the others will survive. Welcome to the shock tank.
Oh, you didn't think that there was a shock tank in Lakeside? Well,
I mean, there is now. Here we go. I think I see some prey. You're just drowning. Get out of here,
sharks. These are sharkless waters. Got him. Got him. Swarmed him. These are sharkless waters.
I need the help. Oh, there's a lot. There's a bunch of people. There's a bunch of people.
Come on. Somebody jump in here. No, no. I'm getting shot at. Jerma, Jerma, Jerma. No, don't die. No.
You're my shark brother. So, how is our lovely two-foot swamp pyro shark doing, you ask?
As happy as can be. It is a lovely day and the forecast calls for clear skies and calm water.
Striking with ferocity and quickness is all in the pyro shark's repertoire. And their favorite
food source is the scoot. The scoot is so full of tender meat and morsels dripping with bone marrow,
it is the pyro shark's favorite. Next to, of course, probably his fin. The two-foot
swamp shark only lives to be about four years old. Time is of the essence. Spy checking,
food gathering, and territorial guarding need to be done quickly. They will spend most of their
few days in these sewers, so they need to spend them wisely. And what's this? A wild skilt showing
himself to our young little friend? This could mean more rations during the winter. Be careful,
young shark. The skilt is known to be a fast runner and could lead you into a trap. This skilt
seems to want to lead our little friend out of the water, which is very, very dangerous indeed.
Pyro sharks have trouble breathing outside the swamp, so another time, another day. Now,
this is a treat indeed. It's not often we get to see the sawmill pyro shark. We caught this one
during its bathing hour, drinking up the cool, crisp water, cleansing his sun-battered skin.
Sawmill sharks are a quiet breed, although highly aggressive. Their main source of food
is the solly bird. Solly birds fly from peak to peak in search of their favorite health pack snack.
The sawmill shark knows this and uses deceit and cunning to lay a goo-covered sticky trap in place
of the bird's favorite meal. Once the bird is consumed, it's back to the bath. And to spend
the rest of the day in relaxation. And before we go, do you remember that little skilt that
was giving our two-foot pyro sharks some trouble? Well, if there's one thing you need to know about
the pyro shark, it's very simple. They always get their kill. Always. So it seems this pyro shark
will continue on through the spring and pass her lineage down another generation. Take care,
everybody. Good night.