That was really bad. Do it louder. No! All right, so what uh, what do we want to do?
I got a few options here. Let's see. I could do... I could play Isaac. Oh, what about um...
What about Chop Goblins? This has been on the list for a long time. This is, I think this is pretty
short. Isn't this only like an hour or two? This is like less than an hour, isn't it? Yeah, let's do
that. That sounds fun. Yeah, I'm gonna give it a try. Give me one sec. You should see it momentarily.
Keep the title. Keep the title. Yeah, I think, let me see. I love how this is a Chop Goblins
game of the week edition. Cool. All right, now I'm gonna get it. Yeah, it's a little uh, it's an FPS
made by... what's the dusk dev there? What's his name? Uh, the stream is probably gonna lag
for a minute because I'm downloading a game. So I might f for a minute or so here. All right,
here we go. Let's give it a shot. That was quick. All right, I already love it. I already love this
game. I do need to change my capturing though. Will it capture it? Hey, there it is. I already
love it. All right, look sensitivity is going down. Let's try that. Kids mode. What is kids mode? Oh,
listen to this. Wow. Whoa. The music is... Oh, oops, I didn't mean to do that. All right, let's do it.
Okay, select difficulty. What levels with no enemies or UI? You're new to PC shooters or just
want a chill experience. Kind of chill. This is a chill stream. The intended balance for a first
playthrough or goblin mode. Uh, I'll do this one. The year is 1984. On a whim one evening you decide
to break into the local museum's basement and see what sort of treasures it might hold. One dusty
wooden chest catches your eye. You open it and a mob of strange creatures leaps out. This particular
chest was secretly a prison for the malevolent chop goblins lured inside by the promise of
delicious cheese and trapped for untold eons. They're now loose to wreak havoc on the world
once more. You know what must be done. Grabbing an antique dagger from a pile of dusty artifacts
you give chase. Antique dagger you grab from a nearby crate. Not the best weapon. It's better
than nothing. And a skilled welder might be able to deflect thrown projectiles with it. You can also
do a quick dagger attack at any time regardless of what weapon you have out by pressing the use
button. Whoa. I gotta turn sensitivity down. Uh, okay let's try it. Uh, it's gotta go even lower.
It's too low. I'm sorry it's too low. I'm gonna say 40. All right that's this is close enough.
I can't get it to where I want it. That's fine. All right Goldilocks. Sensitivity is probably the
most important thing in PC gaming. I don't care if you have a GTX 3090 or an RTX 4080.
Six monitors and like a fucking i-10 like 55 million. If your sensitivity is wrong you're
gonna do dog shit in games. Ass too. It's very fast. I gotta turn it down just a little bit though.
Okay so chop coin. Oh shit. Is there how do I parry? Wasn't there like there was like a
parry button right? Am I making that up? Get some ammo. Scared the shit out of me.
Tremor what are you playing? This is chop goblins. Oh speed runs this game up probably crazy.
Okay fire can I take that was really stupid. That was a really dumb thing to do.
Anymore? Do I have a map or anything? There's a gun right there. All right you know if you know
if the dusk dev is working on this and there's a there's a weapon like this in the game it's
gonna be clean. I'm just saying. Yep. How do I take out the other weapon? Wait I want to I
didn't check the other thing down here. There's another door. Where was it? Oh no just wrapped
around. Zoro? Oh my god the tannins. I forgot about my tea. Why did nobody remind me? I gotta
take these bags out. One the other one's like all the way at the bottom. Hold on I think I can get it.
Burn the shit out of my hand. I just reached into the tea. I just burnt my finger. All right
I'll live. Oh boy. Yeah this thing's full of tannins. All right get them next time. Test.
No we're good. Did I get a soda? There's no jump interestingly enough. Hey good thing I was playing
Resident Evil right before this because I feel like I'm doing very well. All right where's um
oh it's E when you have a different weapon. I don't think I can switch between the two.
Very good. Oh right click does it too. Right click is way better than E.
I think I can reflect those. What do the chop coins do? Oh that's a good question.
Oh can I get one of these? I get plenty of ammo which is good. Okay I think I got everything.
Let's go out. Are you naked right now? Um no I'm actually kind of pretty sweaty right now. Does
anybody know if any of those you know those desk air conditioners. Are those things real? I kind
of like need one. All right I need a key. They suck. I figured it was kind of meh. Why would I
do that? I tried to pick it up with E and I stabbed it. Fan. They're not fans they're these weird
chilling machines. They have to vent outside of a window. Hmm don't hit that. Oh my goodness
there's a lot in here. I should have just lowered them all down. Whoa big coin. This is a really
British stream. Oh wait I didn't get all the things. The Chop Goblins have escaped the museum
and are running amok on the streets of your city. Sounds of wanton destruction greet you as you
exit the front doors. You catch a glimpse of several Chop Goblins disappearing into an alley.
With shock you realize they are carrying the crown jewel of the museum's collection.
The ancient Aztec time manipulation tablet. With that precious artifact they could wreak havoc not
just on your city not just on the world but on time itself. You know what you must do. The Chop
Goblins. The Chop Goblin does are sort of like Smurfette except huge angry steeped in 1950s
stereotypes and there's way more than one of them. Goblin does don't need cleavers to do damage.
They attack with cutting words alone. Keep some cover handy. Blinch them if they start winding up
and whatever you do don't insult their hairstyle. Oh my goodness. Oh no they chopped down the
building. They're chopping down the buildings. We gotta go stop them. Wear one of these. It's a
baseball hat with a fan in the brim with a hole in it that's pointing down at your head.
That's actually like I kind of want to like try it. I kind of want one of those. Is that weird?
My goodness okay that hurts. Actual skill issue here. I'm almost dead. Okay I gotta heal. I'm
almost dead. Is this still the Resident Evil 4 remake? What am I doing? Oh new weapon. Yes.
Streets a shotgun. Oh shit. Okay all right not bad. Bathroom. You're gonna play stalker too
when it comes out? Um I think the stalker games my brain is not big enough for them.
Whoa how do I get in there? Although I did play the those old stalker games. What was it on like
master difficulty or something? I played it on some difficulty that was really really oh no like
realism. It was like realistic mode or something. What was it called? It was a different mode.
People said no I'll play on that one because that's like the best one to play on.
Something like that. It was master. It is the recommended way to play even if you're not good.
I want all that. Yeah I just didn't really get into them. I tried playing what was it?
There was an extensive this is years ago. This is like four or five years ago now right?
There was an extensive argument and well debate is probably better to say than argument on what
game I actually should have been playing. Is this like two or three in the original series right?
Jesus oh my god well that was a little ridiculous. Go use the key. Did I get one? I didn't even pay
attention. You have the key. Oh well let's go do it. What about ultra kill? I'll play the new ultra
kill patch. I'd like to wait a little bit longer though. I'd rather wait till at least a couple more
chapters are there to play. How much is even left of the game? Is there one or two chapters left?
Maybe three chapters left? I want to get up there. Hmm how do I get up there? This game jams. Yeah
this is nice. There's no jump button. I like games that have little secrets like this. So there is a
combo meter up there. They've locked the fence. What? How do you bolt cutters? You missed a lot of
secrets. Oh man I love when games have secrets. Oh man I really love when a game has secrets.
Like I could go that way. I could go over there. I could look that way. How do I get up there? Is
there a jump button? I just don't know what it is. Found a wand charge. Is it alt space control? No.
Cool. Uh oh. There's a new enemy. I don't even know what they yell and if you're in line of sight
it hurts you. What are they saying? We want some cheese. Yeah that's what they're saying. They're
going where's the cheese? It's the lore. Oh start again. Come here. Here's some cheese. Yeah where's
the cheese? I like the chop goblin. Oh boy. Holy shit. What just happened? Oh bolt cutters. Let's
go. There's a gamer slo-mo. Nice. I think that's a gamer slo-mo. You can switch weapons. I mean I
I like the shotgun. All right I got the bolt cutters. Let's go. You're related to these
goblins. Hey yeah. Hey back off. Hey back off. How's that sound? What did that button do?
There was an extra button. What is it? What is it? What are those? Where was the fence?
Not back here. It was way back. Goblin. Calm down bro. Hey here's an idea and just like kind of
put this around your brain for a second. Back off. Jesus. Time portal. Let's go.
Why is he so pissed? Hey back off. A whirl of colors passes by and you emerge from the time
portal gasping for breath. After a moment you survey your surroundings and it doesn't take
long for you to comprehend the chop goblin's plans. You're in the castle of Count Dracula.
They must mean to wake him from his eternal slumber to aid them in their evil rampage.
A strange weapon lies in front of you seemingly fashioned to hurl wooden stakes left here by a
doomed vampire hunter no doubt. They'll probably come in handy for the battle that's about to take
place. The Nosperatus are Dracula's fearsome feline pets created through dark vampire magic.
Now they've joined forces with the chop goblins. Keep your distance and watch out for their lunge
attack. Oh hell yeah. MK Impaler. Clean. This, I like this zone. This sound is cool. There's one
more. Remember did you ever have a goth phase? No I did not. A goth phase. You should start now.
I don't think I want to start goth phase at 40. I don't know if I want to do that. Why not?
Because I don't think I can pull that shit off at 40. I can't pull that off right now.
Yes you can. I don't think I can pull it off. Not with that attitude. Can I get in there?
Goth is ageless. Being goth is ageless. Yeah I'm just telling you I don't think I could
pull it off right now. Goth is a lifestyle. Yeah one day should I just turn on the webcam
and just have just like straight straight black hair like do like put like powder all over my
face or something and have like dar like put like bags into my eyes wear like a cloak put
be like Count Dracula for a day. Okay hold on this is like a puzzle I need to figure this out.
Oh my goodness these things are kind of scary. Just do it on Halloween. Okay I might.
I might. I don't know. I can't. This is not a Roblox birthday party promise.
Wait what am I doing? I need to touch that. A door somewhere has opened. I kind of already have done
this in a way with the whole like oh like Lucius Malfoy. Didn't I? Kind of. That does not count.
I don't think Bugleberry. No Bugleberry is not goth. I don't I don't know about that. All right
what door opened? Bugleberry to me is like are you afraid of the dark Nickelodeon. That's like
whatever that is. Like campy horror. I don't know what you would call it. Does he tell you to say
that? No I'm just it's an observation. Yeah he's like a Goosebumps villain. Yeah yeah like are you
afraid of the dark Goosebumps. I have been told that that is the intent the intent of that uh that
is what I have been told. That that's what they were going with but he's been going for.
Who told you that? Hey hey back off. I wonder what he's up to. True yeah I wonder what he's doing.
That looks like something I should put up there. Wait this thing's take a lot of damage. What the
hell is that? No honestly what the hell is that? Bam. Dude come on man. I'm gonna show this but
like what the fuck are people doing? This is on Redbubble? Oh my god. Why? Hold on a second.
This is apparently like a like a throw blanket on Redbubble. Okay. No I uh uh I don't I don't
want to do it. I don't want to do it. I'm not doing it. This is a fucking picture where I got
like the sun in my face from like at like TwitchCon like 2017 or something. I don't even know when
this is. Oh my goodness. All right. Wait people actually own this thing? What? No. I okay I'm gonna
stop giving this attention. All right let's go let's keep playing this game if we have a plan.
Vampire. Oh my goodness gracious. Okay. It's better that you don't know. Bro. All right.
How many masks do I need? Am I going backwards? Yes I am. You know I one of the reasons why
Bugleberry is like I would say one of my uh he's like one of my favorite characters.
I love Bugleberry. I just love that old kind of Vincent Price horror kind of campy
jokey but not really a lot of inspiration from that sector there. Oh my god that scared me.
What do you mean character? I mean he's a character. He's a character right? You know
people describe people like that. He's a character. Um where is this thing with the masks? I haven't
been paying that much attention. All right where am I going from here? I'm kind of lost.
Was it down? I think I'm just walking in circles. Oh okay hold on. This is new. All right that's a
third mask. This is mobile game ad level of gameplay. What do you mean from me? I mean I
was reading chat and talking. Yeah here it is. We're good. I know where I am. We're right here.
Oh preparing me for something.
All right he's dead. What was he even saying? That was adorable. Again you emerge from the time
portal. Dracula's foul baritone echoing in your ears. Define yourself in ancient Greece.
Dracula's defeat was a heavy blow to the chop goblins and you guessed that they now seek the
staff of the Corinthians. A powerful magic weapon from the anals of myth and legend. Did I say that
wrong? I think I did. Whatever. They cannot be allowed to wield such a weapon. You must first,
you must find it first. The mods are uh having a grand old time over here with various images
and where they are put. Various blankets and um and wardrobe and uh having a having a grand old
time. All right they can't be allowed. You must find it first and use it against them. The big
choppers are the ultimate chop goblin warriors. You weapons slow them down and they can destroy
your health in seconds. Be careful. Any new weapons? Oh I like this area. It's anals. Anals. I know.
I figured that out the tenth of a second after the words came out of my mouth.
Pistol for a little bit. A little slow. I can't believe they made this in row. Oh that's still the
title. Ah I love this. I want one of these. You know what I mean? I'm never I'm never gonna have
one of these but if I if you told me to just okay dream dream house. I just want like a nice clear
cool just little pool not a big one. Everybody I don't like big pools. I just want a little place
for me to go sink and just like soak down to my chest and just like ah just for a little bit.
A shallow little pool like a little no like like a yeah like a hot tub. A hot tub that's not just
hot water. I just want to sit in a little just like this and I want it to be like a plant right
here. I want it to be like oxygen producing from like cactuses plants and shit all over here. You
know what I'm saying? I want this exact lighting too. You want a bathtub. This is way bigger than
a bathtub. Let's use the chop goblin as sort of a scale here. This is big enough for like five
people to sit in. I and I want it for me. I don't want anybody else sitting in this. This is for me
not for anybody else. This is not a case where like oh yeah come over here come over here and piss in
my pool. No no no no this is for me to sit in here and decompress. Holly could use it too. Yeah no
yeah that's no no I'm just talking no outside other outside people could use it. I wouldn't
even tell anybody I had it because you know the first second somebody would be oh my god
the second that somebody finds out you have one of those oh sick oh cool yeah and they
stood there taking their shirt off. He's like no we're not uh yeah we could but uh oh dude really
you got a little a little pool like that let's go I'm getting in. No no no no no don't go in that.
I don't know probably a weirdo if you want. It's all right man just dump a bunch of shock in it.
I'm sorry I puked in your nice pristine pool. No just don't shock in here it'll be fine. No what?
No I want a clean pool. I don't want to even fucking puke in my pool. I don't want to piss in my pool.
Sorry man I accidentally I peed and shit in your pool but it's all right just that white powder
that you sprinkle in that like with chemicals just dump it in there and it'll get rid of the puke.
Oh dude you're never coming over again.
Dude you got weird friends. Why are people doing this in your pool?
Nobody ever says that. Nobody ever says they're doing that but they do and you know what?
Shame on you. Shame on you. I wonder I wonder I wonder like you know oh like pissing yeah
shame on you and you can't here's the thing about a pool there is no verifying anything in a pool
a lot of times there is absolutely no verification so somebody could just be in there pissing and
it's just like I have no idea and nobody else does and no one will ever know there's no verification
when somebody goes in a pool oh that hurts oh they weren't kidding that actually hurt a lot
I got a huge raid slime cycle thanks to the raid welcome everybody we're just chilling out playing
some chop goblins we played resident evil 4 earlier resident 4 remake mercenaries it was fun
but thanks hope you had a good stream we're currently talking about um nothing in particular
just uh I want a little personal pool but I'm never gonna have it but it's like one of the
things I would really like to have
all right I'm gonna die I don't even know this is a save point I think you just have to beat the
level all right can I not get in here yeah we're just chilling appreciate it though
I love that if somebody were to ask me what is your favorite thing in the world
and it's we're not talking about like any what's your favorite thing like
what's your favorite food is different like obviously like in the world I know but like
this right here this is how this looks is one of my top 50 favorite things in the world
just like bright blue clean clear water in a box is really high up there I know a lot of you get
it any type of large square or circle container with nice pristine blue water in it what about
an aquarium yeah secret door maybe it's this one really I like that sound too it kind of like
bubbling water even just saying bubbling water there it is it's my favorite thing in the world
right here all right I need to stop because I'm dead get out of my pool that's my pool
he's gonna go piss in that pool in front of me oh shit okay I actually I have to be a gamer now
he died in the pool okay you know those shows where they um they kind of redo your whole house
and after a week you come back and they you have like a blindfold on and you take it off in the
living room and it's like oh my goodness look at all this it doesn't matter what my house or
what my apartment whatever it looked like before just in the middle of the living room just make
a nice pristine blue square chest high pool and I'm gonna cry I'm gonna do this I'm gonna be like
I can't even look what they put in they put the pool they did what I liked I would cry
and they could be rotten wood all over here and I wouldn't matter as long as I was there
all right this game just got this game just got a little harder good I don't have any ammo I need
to get ammo with this gun equipped thank you those guys hurt a lot I should probably parry
can I parry those are they too big maybe I actually did it thank goodness yeah it but the
water has to be faintly lit with like a light blue like kind of slightly teal light and the
twinsons odyssey soundtrack has to play in the background all right just pull them in here why
look it up look up that soundtrack and you tell me why I should play that game on stream nice
you should play every game of existence on steam I don't think uh
twinsons odyssey is on steam is it it's the sequel to little big adventure a little big
venture 2 it's on steam what how did I not know that that's like in my top that's probably my
top 20 favorite games ever made it's on steam buddy ooh okay add that to the list hello trinch
how great is mr twinson I have I done this I feel like I've played this on no maybe not maybe not
those of you that know you know about that game but I don't know maybe not maybe I thought about
wanting to do it years ago and I just never did it there's a remaster of the two games coming up
and lba3 has been announced you're gonna make me cry do not put the lba2 soundtrack on in my pool
and tell me that there is a sequel coming out while I soak in this did I think so I don't know
who did the voice acting in that game but it is unironically and I mean this I mean this 100
truthfully that game has some of the best voice acting of any game I've ever played get those
coins um I will it's no I think it's less than a few people even doing the voice work and they do
dozens of characters and they're so good there's so much life and so much energy and so much
passion in that voice work it just trust me when I tell you it's phenomenal the characters that
people do oh the elephant voices oh my goodness you're gonna make me cry all right I didn't get
the coins why are you walking in circles uh oh right should we should we tell all right let's
tell them when I get on a topic uh I will just walk in a circle and just forget that I'm playing
a video game and just it's probably annoying I'm sorry I've been doing this for like 12 years
I'm sorry has there ever been a time when I played a game and didn't just like absent-mindedly go on
autopilot in a circle while I was talking no it's never happened oh nice you don't have a
multitasking talent you know I can carry a lot of things at the same time I don't know if that
counts but you bet your ass I'm getting the entire grocery run in one go does that count
that's multitasking you got one on your pinky hanging one on your thumb one sort of wrapped
around your left hand one gripped you have it bunched up tight you take the two ends and you
bunch it up tight you got like 10 bags in your hand that's just a that's not a multitask oh can
you sing while you do it too okay back off what's the point of this room it's the build the wall
break the wall rebuild the wall in Minecraft as you've called it before yeah
is there anything I missed in here oh no several doors have opened apparently
wait here we go oh I think I just like natural shit remember I told you one of my favorite things
is the sticky kind of gooey lava where it's charcoal looking and then they hit it with that
little stick and it opens up and it's like lava I want a room like this too in my house it's like
jello it's a weird thick jello lava dude wants a lava pit in his room yeah that like rolling thick
sludge it's really thick I should have been like a scientist like a viola I don't know I should
have gone into something to do with that it's still time it's still time I hope this doesn't
kill me instantly I'm afraid my god oh my god how do I get up should be a geologist
a lot of cool things to do I mean I could always just wear a like a fisherman's cap and have
sunscreen all over my nose I have like a bowling shirt on with a camera around my neck and a
fanny pack and have my wrists both of them planted on my back walking around and following the other
scientists going like wow what you wow look at that oh wow oh can I get a picture of that
I can just be like it's going like vacation all right I can just go on like vacation just
don't have to like bro's talking about his 40th birthday that's what I'm saying yeah
just be a geologist orbiter oh this is actually bad hold on I gotta pay attention here
shit okay that was hard just checking in how's your health going it's going all right it's going
good I would tell you if it was any major changes or anything I think another big part of this year
too my right and I told you guys about I'm slowing down a little bit there's a lot that goes into
that so the wand is stored in this temple the correct symbols must be nearby symbols are nearby
shit nearby was anybody paying attention to symbols because I wasn't one doesn't kill me
oh okay triangle um it's a circle with two legs uh what's his name cubert and then m this way e
that way w the other way oh yeah let's see that looks like what I need how's Joel doing
oh jill's doing good okay well I just used one of 10 I just used 10% of this thing's power
which was a stupid idea because I probably have to all right don't use it again
where to my neighbor got a new car today and he's been standing outside staring at it while eating
chips 15 minutes oh I get that I get that well it's pretty good again you find yourself in a
whirlwind of colors the last thing you heard was the familiar sound the az tech time manipulation
tablet activating this must be their final dreadful bid for victory you emerge in a desolate
wasteland a future that is not what could be they've transported you to an alternate timeline
a grimy sci-fi dystopia where the chop goblins already won you stand in their vile capital city
chopping grad surrounded by the ruins of human civilization in front of a strange industrial
structure must be their hq you grip the staff of the corinthians with rage a world overrun by
chop goblins just means more chop goblins to shoot it's time for the final battle the hack
goblinators are part goblin part machine they have transcended the bounds of flesh
and are faster and more cunning than the other chop goblins relentlessly flanking their foes
and attacking with deadly laser cleavers final level I think so I only have six more shots with
this I don't think I'm going to use it till the very end this is my resident evil rocket launcher
whoa okay they're already I gotta learn the reflect is so powerful probably I can't I love
this music play lifeline again no no way that I think I'm just sealed that's getting sealed
it's permanently didn't I beat it I beat that game already didn't I or did I just pretend that I did
in my brain so I don't ever play it again yeah I beat it the game was hell that old ps2
mic was so bad yeah I remember the very end the blast battle was that huge robotic monster thing
right I can't believe I actually beat that game um where do I go oh that's cool a motherboard
building didn't miss something where's the where's game progress the lever I didn't pull why did I
do that you beat it I don't think I did it's to your left did you play seaman again no you guys
have to understand the reason why the oh the re hold on the reason why those games were some
of the longest streams I've ever done is because I didn't want to turn those games on ever again
because I know if I turned the dreamcast off that game would never be opened again
so I had to stick with it because that was the only time you were ever going to see that
so it had to be like a 13 hour 14 hour stream same thing with the lord of the rings games
those old lord of the rings games were so hard and just so crazy it's so frustrating
there's no way I was gonna open it again and you know that if I didn't beat those games in one day
you guys would a week would go by hey dude no that lord of the rings stream was really really fun
and really funny like that you are you gonna ever finish it yeah yeah I don't know maybe like in a
maybe some point soon then a year will go by and it's never it's never happened
I need ammo I reflect it wait where's this dead what about pajama sam
I mean there's a lot of games to play just do I really want to play them for more than a few
hours goodness that's good there is somebody behind me I knew it I'm dead I need health
right now nice I guess I could use this I'm gonna use it whatever it's a tough room
oh sad sad all right well now I know where to go hey there's a difficulty after this too
for all you gamers out there you washed your hands um like two hours ago will you at least
go back to yakuza ever again I know I think yakuza actually could probably see a pretty major return
especially with more streams like this it's kind of pick something just
jumping it play it I don't even think about it let me make sure I'm at full health I don't
top it off there we go play it tonight I really thought this is roblox maybe we should change the
title now this is by the uh dusk dusk dev David what's uh I wonder how you pronounce David's
last name I just lost 40 health iron lung I loved iron lung all right he's a great dev he makes
great stuff can you please play roblox we've been chatting on your world I don't have a world
how do I have world I don't even know it okay well that's what you have to do you got to use
that wand because everybody is deadly in here they get them all oh okay give me something good in
here another big guy cool oh man first person shooter roblox or leave well you're talking about
you not me is it even what the fuck what what do you mean what the fuck these they're evil
robot chop goblins they're destroying earth if I get points for this guy then you guys are wrong
I did they're just trying to work uh detonating bombs and explosive electrical
destruction rays across earth that yes that's what they're doing at their job right should I
let them continue they were actively dropping like emp electricity bombs all across the world
all right this room sucks hey everybody I think I got everybody hey jerma ligma what's that
what is that
hmm where should I go did I go this way yeah I did I already went this way this is like way back
what about breath of the wild uh I'll go back to that oh okay I can go up here this didn't keep
going today I'll play more breath of the wild at some point um on your birthday or something
now I'm kidding I'll play it like probably like a week how do I turn this off it has to be in
this room right destroy the computer there's no switch in here it has to be so switch in here
to turn that off when you're gonna play my game what's your game breath of the wild you didn't
make breath of the wild I'm gonna get the ammo down here but I don't know where to go yeah I
made breath of the wild this is kind of like a server room but there's nothing in here
I'm looking this is a switch somewhere I just haven't found it hey okay there it is there we
go shit um what do I do now there's no jump and I can't get back up here up the ledge can I I don't
think I can yeah there's no jump maybe if I run fast enough I'll make it can I walk on the edge
oh thank god this is a tricky jump with no jump button all right here we go don't die out here
look at all this all right I'm I'm this is gonna be jeez yep whoa big guy
anymore all right I don't want to use all this shit I need to save for the big guys like you
okay nice he alive oh my goodness
wait this is the star wars lightning oliver again oh I like this this is cool looking
zordon destroy the cyber goblin to set things right you emerge gasping from the time portal
back in the museum basement your own time just as you'd left it but what of the chop goblins you
glance frantically out the window the city streets are miraculously undestroyed and unchopped
the nightmare is over then your eye catches something in the corner the dusty old chest
that had imprisoned the chop goblins is still there and still open the chop goblins are still
out there somehow waiting for the opportunity to chop again oh come on vinny you beat me by
fucking 2000 points that's funny loser pov it's like once again mode to start a new game with the
same weapons oh okay once again very cool vinny beat you because he played dmc5 I'll have to be
a good gamer and check it out oh I'm curious I just want to see how hard it is on the hardest
difficulty like how much harder is it is it really okay seems like it is they're a lot faster I feel
like all right tell me the truth and I devil may cry I've never played it not even for one second
I've only seen trailer gameplay footage from like Nintendo directs and e3s I all I've seen is
announcement footage of devil may cry is it sad secret would I actually like that game and I know
people are going to go yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah there are like five or six of them I have the
same issue with god of war it's like oh god of war one god of war two god of war three god of war
new god of war god of war new god of war two god of war no don't play god of war two play god of
war three play two and then skip five and I just I don't know wait what do I start what should I
what should I actually do just do one two three four and five no do one three four and five skip
two and skip the reboot is what I'm being told I feel like a fake fan if I skip games though
well I'm not even a fan anyways so who cares I guess that's true cheat true fans actually skipped
two all right okay I hear you two is unbelievably bad what happened why and if two was so unbelievably
bad then how did they pull it together so well to have three be so good but what happened it's
complicated okay yeah that was fun that was really fun game I like the chopped goblins how much even
is this on steam right now I think this is like a this is like a couple of dollars or something
isn't it five bucks this is five dollars worth it is great and you can get the soundtrack if you
get the chopped goblins game of the week bundle for five dollars and 93 cents that was awesome
I had this on the list and I'm just like I gotta find a day where I could because I knew it was
only gonna be like an hour and a half or so hour two hours end of the stream um hmm maybe we'll do
that as one run of Isaac sound I think that sounds good we'll do an Isaac run
uh let me just go pee one more time I'll be right back