Oh, look who it is. It's Twitch chat. Hi guys. Uh, hold on. I gotta move my mic. Wait, wait, wait.
Hey, thank you for waiting. Your patience is unmatched, everybody.
Will I be watching green screen edits? No. I want to make sure I make this very clear, very,
very clear. Uh, green screen edits are going to be only designated for the green screen movie
night. They might be more than two. They might be even more than that. I might have to do more
than three, but, uh, we're not going to watch them on stream. We're not going to watch them
after the stream. It's, we're going to get a good, clean, dedicated movie night. Not even
one, not even one. Oh, we got it. We got to hold onto them. That's the specific reason
why we did it in the first place is to have like a big movie night. So this is a
little too loud, ain't it? Mr. Like Birdman is a little loud. Am I sick? I was a little stuffy
this morning, but I'm good. It should clear out here in a minute or so. What do I think of
Fallout 76? I haven't played Fallout 76. I heard it's not good though. I've heard it
is very, very, very much a broken video game. I don't really have any intention to play it.
Not really. That's an understatement. Yeah, I just don't, I didn't even attempt to play it.
But the thing that we're going to attempt to play tonight is something that we've been
talking about for a couple of weeks now. And I knew at some point I wanted to play it. So
we're going to do it tonight. And I know that this schedule has been so odd.
I've been streaming a lot more frequently, but it's probably going to stay like this.
I have not yet decided on how the hell I'm going to, what the new schedule will be.
I don't know. I mean, maybe we'll never stop streaming like Monday to Monday.
I'm kidding. That's not going to happen. Yeah. If you don't, if I played Undertale on stream
long time ago and I thought it was fun. I hope if you want to stick around and watch this,
this is just kind of an extra stream that I knew I wanted to do. So if you don't want to know,
if it's spoilers and all that shit and you don't care, then see you soon. Thanks for stopping by.
So let's get it on the screen. It's kind of odd to capture because it just like starts.
It's just, it just starts. So I got to turn this off and we're going to go.
It's a three hour game. Well, I don't even know. Is it? Here comes a three hour stream.
No, don't worry. I'm going to like really, I'm going to really drag this out.
Every opportunity that I can stop and make like a 30 minute conversation. I'm kidding.
Okay. It's got a weird name too. Like your computer thinks it's a virus, right? This is
not a virus, right? Is this, is this his way to make everybody, to make a big joke out of
this? All right, here it comes. It should, it should show up on the screen very shortly here.
Uh, any second now. There it is. Hey, are you there?
Welcome to Undertale 2. Are we connected? I remember that. That's the heart. Excellent.
Truly excellent. This is, this is 18 years in the making, by the way. He started this when
he was one. He started coding this when he was like, I think four and a half months old.
We may begin. First, you must create a vessel. Select the head that you prefer.
No, but this is more like me, right? Is that more like me? I've got like a long,
skinny chin and the hair that comes down. That's like hair going up, going down. That's
like a long chin. Select the torso that you prefer. Can you also, can you also customize kill
streaks? Well, I don't understand. All right. Well, I'm just making Charlie Brown.
Select the legs that you prefer. This is the same thing. What's the difference? A fat left
leg or a fat right leg? I'm just going to go with this one. This is your body. Do you
accept it? Sure. Excellent. You have created a wonderful form. Now let us shape its mind
as your own. Where the hell is Sans, man? I don't even like this. What is its favorite food?
Sweet, soft, sour, salty. Sans, where's Sans? Pain. Cold. No, my favorite food. I'm doing
this as if it's me. Okay. And whatever one is the closest to Sans is the one I'm going
to pick. I don't, I think I'm a salt kind of person. Salty. Sansy. You know, your favorite
blood type. Uh, D is not a blood type. That's like the funny answer. Or is that O? Is that
O? I don't even know what my blood type is. What is my blood type? There's no blood type
C. That's D, but that's not an O. Look at the O's up there. Look up under, see blood?
I think I'm a, I think I'm a, I think I'm a dual blood citizen. What color does it like most? Red,
blue, blue or green? Oh, right. Like that's a tough one. This is actually hard because these
are my two favorite colors. Am I determining how much HP I have by doing this and how many
intellect and like mystic points I get or something? It's going to be, it's going to
be, uh, I painted my office screen. It has to be green. It's going to, it's blue. I,
can I go back? Please give it a gift. Kindness, mind, ambition, bravery, voice.
Because you know, I got that one. How do you feel about your creation? It will not hear.
Well, I've got to tell you, I think it has a little bit of hope from that first game.
Remember that one? Determination. Where's that one? Where's Sans? Where's Sans? How do I feel
about your creation? I'm kind of afraid of it. I don't know if it could like much jump
at the screen. Have you answered honestly? Uh, yes. Yes, I have. Nice Peter Griffin voice.
Oh, Lois. Lois. You acknowledge the possibility of pain and seizure. What?
No, I have to acknowledge the fact that it's going to make it pain and seizure.
Is this, is this telling me that it's going to be flashy? No. Understood. Name your vessel.
Uh, me. Whoops. It's me. Who made it? No, no, no, no, no. I did. I made this. Excellent.
All right. Truly excellent. Thank you. I did this. Me. I. Your answers. Your wonderful
creation. Uh-oh. Will now be discarded. No one can choose who they are in this world.
Your name is Chris Sans. Uh, what's, how do I? Chris. Chris, if you do not wake up,
we'll be late for school, Chris. Oh, that's uh, that's Abigail. I will wait outside for
you. All right. Okay. I got my Legend of Zelda. The drawer is mostly empty except for a school
cross-country cert with a tear in it, a tear. Okay. So am I like in high school or something?
Closed draw. It's a beautiful day outside. There are CDs under the bed. Classical jazz,
religious scuff. There's also a game console. It is one normal controller and one knockoff
one. Stay, just stay. Definitely takes place in the nineties. It's a computer desk. There
are many boxes under it filled with old books. Okay. What about the bird? It's a red rag wagon
with a rusty bird cage in it. Looks like it's seen quite a few crashes. Why do you have a
bird cage? Ragged. There's a ragged in here. A cactus. There's not much to say about it.
There are crayons in the drawer. Their labels have long faded and there's no green.
Oh, just like the nineties. It's only you.
The door is locked. Okay. Bookshelf. There are many books. Tales of snails. A storybook.
Snails do not have tails. A scientific reputation. Can snails help your garden? Not
really. And a signed copy of the history of humans and monsters by Gerson Boom. That new
character that everyone's going to fall in love with. Wait, what about? That's it.
You looked inside the sink cupboard. There's a can of Icy's Cool Boys body spray. Spray
for the boys. Flamin' hot pizza flavor. It seems to be almost entirely full.
That's good. Yeah, Toby, you already got me. It's a toilet. Flush it. You flush the toilet.
Chris, is everything all right in there? Yeah. Yeah. I'm going to be the first person that finds
the secret with the toilet. Sans is going to come out of there. Chris, what are you doing
in there? You did not put a bath bomb in the toilet again, did you? I can't wait until Sans
comes out here and he goes. Can't wait until he does that. On the shower ledge, there's a
small container of apple scented shampoo and a gallon size container of pet shampoo.
All right, can I leave the bathroom? Wait, what if I say no? It's good to conserve water. Oh,
whoops. There's a photo on the fridge. It's of you, your mother, and your brother.
Okay, so I have brother. Is my brother going to be the guy from the first game?
Oh, by the way, I think this is a sequel to Undertale. I don't know. It might be.
It's emitting a pleasant floral scent. Cookie cutters for gingerbread monsters and gingerbread
humans. Cinnamony batter caked up. There's a cinnamony batter caked on the stove top.
There's some white fur stuck in the drain. You got to look at everything.
It's a landline phone, but you already have a cell phone. It's a chariol, the beloved living
room chair. All right, TV. All right, this hopefully this is like GTA. GTA. And there's
like a shitload of TV channels. It's the TV doesn't seem to even be plugged in anymore.
Chris, there you are. We might still be able to make it. Here comes the first song. It's
a beautiful day today, is it not? I hope it stays this way when we when Asriel visits next
week. But I wonder after the excitement of university, will we still enjoy coming home to
this little town of Undertale? I remember those cats. I remember that girl from the Muppets
in the electric blue balloon band, whatever it's called. No, Dr. T in the electric mayhem.
We're going to school. I'm late. So does everyone have a...
Oh, Chris, we thought you weren't coming today. We're doing... No, this is... I know this
person. We're doing group projects this month. Oh, so walk around and find a partner. Okay.
The snake. Chris, you know, Jockington and Caddy are always partners. We're the ultimate
academic duo ever since our first gym class. It was hula hoop day and they ran in a hoops
for us. So she used me instead. That's our origin story. But I hardly know her.
Hahaha. What do you think of that one? Funny, right? No? Well, I got news for you, pal. I
already got a partner. Oh, I'm not doing this one. No, I'm not doing it. Black and white
hard-boiled egg. Sadly seems like it already has a partner. What about Falco? Chris lit again,
I see. Oh, you need a partner. Sorry, I'm already partners with the second smartest student.
Oh, wait. Chris, now that I think about it, your unique skill set might help a lot on this
assignment. What? I actually wanted to get an A. All right, easy. Settle down here, daffy duck.
Hey, Chris, what's up? Did you lose your pencil again? Here, you want the candy cane
one or the one with the lights on it? Huh? You want to be partners? Birdly already asked me,
but I could ask his Alphys if we could make a group of three. I'll ask if you're sure. Not
yet. I'm going to be the third partner here. What about cat sip from final fantasy seven?
I'll click, click, tap, tap, take. I can't. I have to. Okay, I have to let go. Ask her
for this. What? Whoa, whoa, whoa. What am I watching on my phone? It's schoolwork, of
course. Animated schoolwork. And hey, Chris, have you chosen a partner yet? I want to be partners
with the snake. This is kind of not fair. If you can't get anyone, maybe your mom will be your
partner again. Okay, where is haymaker? No, no, let's be partners. Okay, I'll ask. Miss Alphys,
is it okay if we have a group of three? No, I don't want to approve of this. Abort.
Well, but Chris doesn't have a... Noelle, what were you saying? She was saying we're five-y alone.
I just wanted to know if... Noelle, can you please speak up? Uh-oh. Hi, five-five-y.
Five-oo-five-y. Am I late? Oh, no, no, you're fine. We were just choosing partners for the
next group project. And five-ee-five-y, you're with Chris. Great. Now that everyone's here,
I'll write the assignment down. Has anyone seen the chalk? This is the third time it's gone missing,
and you all know I can't start class without some chalk. How about this? If no one speaks up,
everyone gets in trouble. Anyone, please? This teacher sucks. Hey, there might be a box in
the supply closet. Miss Alphys, why don't you just, uh, sell... Oh, five-oo-five-y and I.
Good idea, Noelle. Since you came in last, five-oo-five-y, why don't you go and get it
for me? You can't keep this up, I know. And Chris, can you go with her and make sure she
actually gets it and stays out of trouble? Thanks, Chris. See you later. Eating the chalk?
What are you doing? Whose footprints are these? Chris. Didn't see you there. Hey.
You didn't see anything just now, did you? Huh. You can't even say. Chris.
I can't get in there. I have to go around my pop filter. Let me tell you a secret. Oh!
Quiet people piss me off. Just because you don't say anything,
I can't tell exactly what you're thinking. It's over! I caught five-ee-five-ee eating all the
chalk. This was her last chance. Now she'll finally be expelled.
Come on, Chris. Don't act shocked. You know it's true. Everyone's waiting for it. Everyone wants
to see this happen. Why am I pulling these back? Why? So, congrats, Chris. You got me.
I'm done for. Let me say, one little thing seems like a waste to get expelled just for having
a snack. So, Chris, if I know you're going to pull the trigger, I'm going to just get
expelled with some real carnage. Chris, how do you feel about losing your face? Chris,
you got a good mother. It would be a shame to make her bury her child. What the
fuck is happening? All right, let's get this over with. We'll get more chalk,
mosey back to class, and then, Chris, you'll do our project. How's that sound?
What happened? What? Don't bother answering. If you haven't gotten it by now,
your choices don't matter. Let's go, freak. At least you're honest. The locker is covered in
Jockington Memorabilia. Locked. Locked. Locker's lock is locked. The lock's locker is
locked. The lockers lock's locker is locked. All right, are you ready for the Sadie Hawkins
Hawkman's Sadie Hawkman's dance? At this dance, all chaperones will wear giant hawkheads
and screech at any students that make contact. God, can you walk any slower or what?
Nah, I get it. Not used to walking around without someone holding your hand.
Come on, freak. This is like bad. Well, here's the closet. Too bad. We were just
starting to have fun. What the hell is happening? Hey, Chris, is it me or
is it really dark in there? Hold up, Chris. Are you going to go in or what?
Come on, if you're going to be a wimp, then I'll. We'll both go in at the same time.
See, why are you so scared? There's nothing in here but old papers.
Let's try to find a light switch. Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait.
That's weird. I can't find a switch. This is further in.
Uh, kind of big for a closet, huh? You think we'd have reached the end by now?
Is this a surprise birthday party? Hey, Chris, I think this closet's broken.
There aren't any walls. Well, we've worked hard enough.
If Alfie wants chalk so bad, she can get it herself. Let's split.
What the? Hey, this isn't funny. Let us out. Let us. Here he comes.
The floor, it's. Did I not play Undertale? I play. Yeah, I played through Undertale like
fucking five times. Wait, what happened? Am I a different, am I the same character?
At times you see it flickering, the light only you can see.
By second nature, you reach out and save the game. I made this.
I found the run button. Yeah, I did. Cool. You're not going to move? Yes, you are.
It's really interesting tidbit about this game. Toby made the whole thing in Game Boy camera,
which is like just, I don't even know how you did that. It's too dark to see anything.
I thought you, I mean, I, I, I mean, I did. You thought I made, yeah, well, I mean,
I saw a figure. A blob that seems to be able to move. It's too dark to see anything.
One of these is going to have some kind of item in it, right? Has to. It's too
dark to see anything. All right, that's creepy. Right? Like, come on. This is weird.
It's too dark to see anything. Let's go down. Uh, item. There's something glowing inside.
Take it. Yes. You got the glow shard. Can I see what it is? No, don't toss it.
I have a cell phone. Glow shard. A shimmering shard. Its use is unknown.
Equip wood blade. Nothing, nothing. No weapons. Power. Level one human.
Body contains a human soul. Spells. Guts. Magic defense. Config file. I think this is
full on full screen. Hold on a second here. All right. That's pretty good, actually,
because now I can do this. I was running into a window this whole time because there's no way
to. Oh, is this going to work? There we go. That looks so much better. Cool. Nice. All
right. So now we are actually in full screen. You press alt enter. I didn't really think about
it. All right, let's go. That's, that's a lot better. Now I can actually see everything.
All right, so there's a figure going this way. We're going to go this way.
That one's red. It's going to shoot a laser beam. Yep. Come on. I've got Platinum
God and Binding of Isaac. You really think I'm going to get hit by that?
What are you talking about? You bathe your body in the light. Power shines within you,
breaking through the darkness. Any pain you may have had melted away. HP fully restored.
And a safe one. In this land, only eyes blinded by darkness can see the way.
Okay. So we've got, uh, that's the two. And hold on. We got to, they all have to be dark.
So that's it. Eyes blind. Darkness is the way, right?
2000 hours in Binding of Isaac. I've stepped on the cubes that you need to step on to open the
door in a certain order. Come here. Come on, man. Should I talk to these guys? Oh, they just
explode. I'm really, I'm actually pretty good at this because I mean, I like, I have about
two, 3000 hours in Binding of Isaac. And when you, I always check all the poops for coins
and everything. You know what I mean? So, Hey, back off. Come any closer and I'll Chris.
Phew. Hey, don't scare me like that. Dumb ass. Unless you want to get clocked in the face.
Anyway, enough screwing around. We got to find a way out of here.
Uh, where is here? Anyway, it doesn't matter. You got us into this mess. You get us out of
here. Lead the way, Chris. Are there party members? This is fairly new and that fairly,
I mean, it is new because I'm like, God, nevermind. You walk way too slow. I was just
sprinting. What? I was just going as fast as I could warm up. Okay.
Hey Chris, there's someone up there waving at us. Any idea what they want?
Here he is. He's going to be here. I can't believe it. Run. Talking about a guy. Oh,
wow. Like mega Satan, huh? I have plenty of training. I beat mega Satan with fucking
lost. I didn't get hit one time. Down here quick. I didn't even know what it wanted me to do.
I didn't even get to see the tutorial. All right. If I can hit one fucking time,
I'm going to go in the dryer and have somebody turn it on. Oh my God. He's so weird.
I wonder if there's any in that building up there. Weird flex. What?
Let me check and open these doors. It looks like a shop, but the door's locked
and no one's inside. I'm so weird and quirky. It's locked. I hate that word. That word is
worse than mayonnaise. In front of you. Yeah. Castle looms beneath the empty town. A black
geyser emerges from it, piercing endlessly into the sky. Power of this place shines within you.
Yeah, I'll say, but I guess we're going straight in a castle. Why the hell is there
a castle inside a supply closet? Welcome. Do not be alarmed. I am not your enemy.
Please come forward. Both of you at the same time. Welcome. I am the Prince of this kingdom,
the kingdom of darkness. Chris Susie. Oh, sorry. Five oh five. There's a legend in this land,
a legend that Monday two heroes of light will arrive and fulfill the ancient prophecy foretold
by time and space. Please hear us. Listen to my tale. Very well. Once upon a time,
a legend was whispered among shadows. It was a legend of hope. It was a legend of dreams.
It was a legend of light and darkness. This is the legend of Delta Rune. For millennia,
light and dark have lived in balance, bringing peace to the world. But if this
harmony were to shatter, a terrible calamity would occur on this world.
The sky will run black with the terror and the land will crack with fear.
Then, a heart pounding, the earth will draw her final breath. Only then shining with hope,
three heroes appear at world's edge. Sans, Papyrus, and you, a human, a monster,
and a prince from the dark, me, Sans. Only they can see of the fountains. Thank you for
playing the Delta Rune demo and banish the angels' heaven. Only then will balance be
restored and the world saved from destruction. Today, the fountain of darkness, the geyser that
gives this land form, stands tall at the center of the kingdom. But recently, another
fountain has appeared on the horizon. It's over there. And with it, the balance of light and
dark begins to shift. So, Chris, five of us, thank you for listening to my long tale.
I deeply believe you two are the heroes of the legend. That despite whatever
enemies you may face, you two have the courage to save the world. Delta warriors,
please, won't you accept your destiny? Uh, no. Wait, what? Me, some kind of hero or something?
No way, not me. You've got the wrong person. But, but, but, without you, the world is...
So what, if the world is destroyed, I don't care. It's none of my damn business.
Might even be kind of fun. Anyway, Chris, if you want to play pretend with this weirdo,
stick around. I'm going to find a way out of here. Oh, no, five will find me, wait.
Oh, wait. The heroes are already running away. And they didn't even know I was here. My dad's
gonna make me son of the month. Who the hell are you? I'm the bad guy. You clowns want
to seal our dark fountain, huh? I'm still picturing you guys as clowns. Save the world
from eternal darkness, huh? Hey, don't try and deny it. We both know you'll go east.
It's your only way home. But I, Lancer, won't let you go there. And I've got a flawless two-step
plan to ensure it. Step one, I thrash you. Step two, you lose. Nice playing, kid. Really?
Actually, it's a pretty good plan. Mind if we use it on you instead? Actual full-on RPG.
Oh, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa. Wait, wait, whoa, whoa. What was that? Interesting. Okay. So you
have to time, it's time hits. Okay, cool. And then when you, all right, this is cool.
This is like just, that's really, that's actually pretty cool. I'm gonna do it. Check.
Warning. You tell Lancer to watch out for Suzy's attack. He readies himself.
So what are you guys gonna do? What are you guys doing after this? Lancer's motorcycle is
actually just a bike that's on fire. That was a compliment. You tell Lancer you can't
tell the difference between his clothes and his body. He seems flattered. His attack power
went down. Oh, you make my feelings do wheelies. Sweet wheelies. Oh, I'm getting hit.
Wait, wait, wait, wait a second. My bike's running out of fuel. All right, you
punkaroos. You had the luck of the draw this time. Next time the losers will be you.
What does that say? I don't know what that means. Bye losers. I gotta get home before dinner.
39 D money. Oh, it's a dryer run. Oh shit. I gotta go in there. Are you two okay?
Um, allow me to introduce myself more properly. I am. Take off the hood.
I can barely hear you. Oh, all right.
Well, I don't even like, I didn't even, I don't care if Sans is in the game.
I don't give a shit. Why am I pretending to care about that? I got like, I pretended to care
about it like an hour ago. And me, I like believed my own pretending. I was actually
waiting for it. Hello everyone. I'm Rousey. Chris, Susie, it's ever so wonderful to meet
you. I'm certain we're going to become great friends and this way to leave is east, right?
Yes, that's where I wheel. Got it. See you at school, Chris. Um, I suppose it's just the two of
us then. Chris, I'm a prince, but I currently don't have any subjects. I've been waiting
alone here my whole life for you two to arrive. So I'm really happy to meet you.
Hope we can be good friends, Chris. Let's try to find Susie. She must be to the southeast.
You can lead the way, Chris. Hey Chris, I really think we should go catch up with Susie. We can
come back here after our adventure is over and then I can bake you a yummy cake. Hey, thanks.
Rousey the lonely prince is now your ally. Our fluffy boys shines within you.
Oh, Chris, it's the training dummy I made. Now seems like a great chance to prepare for
the enemy. Would you like me to teach you how to fight? Yeah, I just, I want to know. I know
how to do it, but I just want to be told because I want to know what the deal is. See that heart
there, Chris? Yep. That's your soul, the combination of your being within it holds your
well, your compassion and the fate of the world. If it gets hit, you and your friends
will die. If everyone's HP reaches zero, then Jerma has to get into a dryer and we'll lose.
So please take care not to get hit. Don't get hit by the enemy stacks. Ready? Let's try
dodging. What? Natural. Anyhow, after the enemy attacks, it's our turn, Chris. First,
I'll teach you how to fight. The fighting is unnecessary in this world. There's no harm in a
thorough lesson. Is there anything I can do besides this? Right, that's it, right?
Wow, Chris, that was an amazing attack. Have you done this before or something?
Okay, now let's try defending. Simply defend and the enemy's attack will hurt you less.
Not only that, but you'll also gather TP. Watch the orange big bar on the left and we'll explain
it next. Great, now that we've gathered TP, how about spending that TP on one of my spells?
Because you hit the enemy enough, it got tired. Stop, I used my pacify spell on it.
It'll fall asleep and we'll win peacefully. Magic pacify on the tired dummy. Great,
you could have won the battle by now. Now I have just a little more to teach you.
Acting through this, even though the even the most violent enemies can be defeated through
various acts of kindness. Chris, though, is just a dummy. Why not give it a hug?
You know, I can hug the prince. Oh, that's great, Chris. Each enemy has different acts
that satisfy them. When an enemy is satisfied, its name turns yellow. When that happens, you
can defeat it by sparing it. If we spare all the enemies we meet, we'll never have to fight.
So is it yellow? Not quite. You can hug Rousey. Chris, I don't think this is what you're supposed
to be doing. Hug. Hug the dummy. That's great, Chris. Just one hug is enough, though.
Oh, I don't know how to do anything else. So that is yellow. Great job. That'd be the end
of the real battle. I'm really happy I had the chance to teach you, Chris. That's zero
xp in two delays. That was fun. You're a wonderful student, Chris. And in case you ever need a
refresher eye, here I wrote a manual for you. You see, open the menu, use it on your items.
It's just a dummy. What a JoJo reference? What does that mean? Oh my, the great door is open!
No wonder Lancer was able to come through. Chris, once we pass through this door, our
adventure will really begin. A journey foretold exactly by the prophecy, but Chris, I believe
your choices are important, too. This world is full of all kinds of people, Chris. In the end,
how we treat them makes all the difference. So let's try our best to kill everyone, every
person you come across, and get the bad ending. If we can manage to do that, then chat will
be very upset, and I believe this tale may have a very bad ending and a lot of unsubscriptions
to your channel. Otherwise, I fear that you may get the good ending and people will be happy.
Oh, I'm sorry. Is that too much? I knew you were here the moment I saw it. Let's try our best.
Thank you for playing! The Mario demo screen is going to turn off, the thing that used to be
in GameStop. Now I gotta let the person behind me play. Reset the Super Nintendo on me.
With the door closed behind you, your adventure will truly begin. Our adventure
shines within you. 46 minutes. Oh yeah. Oh yeah. Let's take the scenery in first. I mean,
why am I rushing through this? This demo is only like three hours long. I might as well
just look at everything. The field of hopes and dreams. Enemies ahead, you're gonna die.
Signed Lancer.
Okay, Rudin Drewneer. He won. I didn't have an option. Did I just kill him?
I didn't have an option. I didn't kill him. I scared him.
Bad ending. If you're reading this, I guess you're dead. Signed Lancer.
I didn't act. I will... I... Get away from me with the sword! Don't come up to me with the sword.
Idiot. Hey, don't read the sign. It's a work in progress. Signed Lancer.
Ho ho ho, but isn't my two favorite people. Sike, you guys aren't even in my top five.
Lancer, where's Susie? You mean that purple girl? Ho ho ho, you fools! You're too late to
stop me. What did you do? It was so simple. She beat me up, so I ran away.
Hence a bit anti-climactic. Am I dead? Sorry, you're just going to stand there.
Thought you would at least run to the right. Why? The purple girl's over there. Well,
all right. Put him up down. These types of trees don't contain an item that can heal you.
Whatever you do, don't check the tree and use C to open your menu. Got it? Signed Lancer.
There are two objects hanging from the tree. Take one. You got the dark candy. What about
the other one? Take, yeah. You got the, this, okay, this is two. There's nothing hanging low
enough to take. All right, see you later, weirdo. Hey, if you head that way, my troops will
trash you. Is that a threat? I prefer to think of it as an invitation. All right, I'm gonna
be, I'm gonna be nice. A necklace of Rudens blocks your path. All right, Ruden up top. Let's see,
check. Let's, let's lecture. A necklace of Rudens blocks your path. I can only act with, um,
Chris. You lecture the enemies on the importance of kindness. The enemies became tired.
What? Okay, long live the guy who pays us.
Yes, long live the guy who pays us. Ruden is starting to fall asleep. Can I, they're not yellow yet.
Convince. You told Ruden to quit fighting. It was utterly swayed. Yeah, I guess it makes sense.
Face my diamond cutter. Hitbox is fairly large, but I guess that's the, all right, spare.
Ruden is starting to fall asleep. Let's, uh, spare. I can only spare the top one. Chris,
spared Ruden. Name wasn't yellow. Face my diamond cutter so you can pacify.
Does pacify just make them more susceptible to, ow. Not yet. All right, let's convince.
Pacify just ends the fight. Wait, did I just hit him? I think I hit him. Good. He missed.
All right, starting to fall asleep. There you go. I get, the only thing that's confusing me
is from the first game just having the one menu and having more than one party member is
trying to get used to that. See, I spared them. They're fine. I thought that was him.
Damn. But thank you, uh, thank you Alpine's B for the hundred dollars.
A hundred bucks from Alpine. Thank you. Hi, Jeremy. I'm donating on behalf of my friend
Michael who passed away recently. We've been following since the TF2 days and you've given
us so much joy. Thank you for everything. Alpine, I'm very sorry to hear about that.
Thank you so much for the hundred bucks. You too have been apparently following since, well,
all the way back then. I'm really sorry to hear about that. Hopefully you give yourself
the time necessary to grieve and and much love and much respect to obviously Michael's
family as well. So take care of yourself and thanks for, uh, thanks for being around.
Nothing can take away the memories that you two have. That's true.
That is very true. Why is everyone's messages getting deleted? They shouldn't be.
Let's go here. Uh, I'm Top Chef. My latest cake worked me to exhaustion. Top Chef.
Message deleted. What's going on? Oh, now you guys are just joking with me here.
Mama Miba, I'm Top Chef. My latest cake worked me to exhaustion.
So I took a little nap, but Mama Miba, a scary noise woke me up. The beast was
hunched on the table, eating the cake like an animal. I spritzed it with water and
hissed and ran off. But my wonderful cake is... Oh Chris, that sounds like Susie. We must be
going the right way. Let's try to keep her out of any more trouble. I got, hold on,
this is important. I got something else to say. Um, I just want to make this, uh, very
clear that anytime I hear about something like this, right? Uh, I'm, I'm so just,
if you have this channel and you and your friends and or you and your family members or
whatever and you guys hang out here and you like this shit and you hang and it's like,
it means a lot to you. It means a lot to me. So just knowing that people have fun here
and we're, I think about it a lot. So just want to make sure you guys are very clear on
that. Thanks a lot. All right, let's go back into it. Uh, here's the cake. Why is the cake
like a flying saucer? Take a piece of cake. Yeah, sure. The broken cake was added to your
key items. Is that bad? Should I not be doing that? What if I talk to him again with the,
can I give him the piece of cake? Mama meba mama mama sheba. You know that beast,
please don't come back. All right. No, no, no. No Hathi blocked the way.
All right. Rudin needs to be lectured and how much magic I don't have any magic. So
defend first. The enemies became tired. What? Okay. What is that? Why is it just like a
Wii U drawing? Oh shit. Okay. Hathi's beat slows. Not yet. Now let's convince and then pacify
on Hathi. You told Rudin to quit fighting. It was utterly swayed. Rousy cast pacify.
I guess that makes sense. Uh, pardon us. Uh, fall asleep. You don't do anything.
Oh, we just had a bunch of community subs. Novi gave five community subs. Thanks a lot.
Thank you so much Novi and congratulations to the people that are getting these community subs.
Thank you. Puzzle time. We got a puzzle here. Check it out. Check the clock. In order to
solve this puzzle, you'll have to hurry. They've got so much time in The Legend of
Zelda. I beat Star Tropic's first try blind without taking any damage. Behold the maze of
death. Prepare to get lost clowns. Signed, Lancer. Uh-oh. Failing lost yet? You must be utterly helpless
among these twists and turns. Your sense of direction will save you now. What's that?
It's some sort of enemy. Looks like they got clobbered. Oh, I see. Well, I'm assuming
I have to follow the signs, but I kind of want to see what's over here. Well, wait a
minute. Even if you're my enemy, I've got to warn you. A purple beast is roaming clobbering
anyone who dares block her way. We don't even like fighting. The king left us no choice.
Oh, Chris, we need to stop Susie quick. Hey, wait, where am I? Help. Somebody help me. I'm lost.
Oh, and there are coins. You open the treasure chest. Inside was a white
ribbon. You put white ribbon in your armor. That ribbon is armor, Chris.
It increases defense. Why don't you try wearing it in the equipment menu? Yeah, I will. I think
it'd look great on you. Okay, so this is Chris. And we got white ribbon is
crinkly hair ribbon that slightly increases your defense and cuteness. What the fuck does
that mean? I've higher cuteness. Oh, no. Well, Rousey apparently is cuter now. Chris,
you're giving it to me? Well, does it look pretty? I better get that back. That's a loan,
man. I want three ribbons back with interest. Hey, don't look. This sign's private. I already did.
Oh, it's just this way. There is. Oh, somehow you survived the babies, but don't count on
your blessings before they hatch. Let's see if you're against this team. My triple frogs.
Three Hatties blocked the way. So we can go to act. Let's do flatter. Let's flatter.
And let's get some defense here. You told the Hattie it has cool tentacles. It began to think
about this. That was that one up top is. Is that like a Grinch meter? I don't understand
the Grinch meter. Hey, why aren't you guys thrashed? You're totally outnumbered.
You made a team purely of support enemies. Their bullet patterns aren't balanced at all.
It's like a dinner made out of three glasses of milk. And that's how unusual somehow.
Why don't we talk about this after the battle? Okay. Let me pacify.
Pacify, but the enemy wasn't tired. Okay. Well, one of the middle's angry,
but it doesn't matter. These things until I figure it out. Flatter. And began to think
about this. Now it's very happy that I said that. Hattie's body beats audibly.
X-flatter. You order Raazi to flatter all the enemies. Oh, you can do... I get it. You don't need
experience just encountering your smile is rewarding enough. Why does somebody just say...
All right, spare them both. There, spare, spare. Great job, Hurst. We earned zero XP and $88.
Sweet! How much do I get? You lost. You don't get anything. Oh, can I have some of yours?
No. Fine. Later, losers. I'm still just standing here. Sup? I thought you were running away.
Yeah, I finished.
All right, that's... That's fine. That was funny. Come on, that was cute. My cuteness
was up, but that's why. No, get over that. That's scripted. That's scripted, guys. Excuse me.
That's scripted. He can't solve it. I physically can't solve it.
Come on, man. Open your door, you stupid door. Oh, great. It's you guys. Susie, we were ever so
worried about you. How'd you get past those spikes before? Walk through them. But this door
sucks. Oh, don't worry, Susie. A little bit after we solved the puzzle over there. Nice.
Tell me when you finish it. Susie, we need you to finish it. Sometimes proceeding
will take all three of us. Furthermore, only Chris can seal the dark fountain.
So if you don't accompany us, you won't make it home. So you're saying I have to stick with you,
Rune? Yep. Let's just get this over with. Yahoo! Susie's... Yeah!
Susie's back on the team. Cue the fanfare. Susie joined the party. That was long. Susie
follows at a distance such that no one can tell she's associated. Not anymore.
All right, here we go. Three, two, one, action! Action! Did it! Step on it!
Hey, Chris, if you need help with the puzzle, feel free to ask me. No. And if you need help
from me, you're screwed. Just wait. Let me... how... it's got to be like this.
Yeah! I can't do it. I'm just gonna scream Yahoo! But I would have like peaked the microphone so
loudly. Let's go, dog! Oh, Chris just realized Susie missed the tutorial.
Next battle, we should show her how to act. I think she might really enjoy that. C-Round
attacked violently. You recall Rousey's advice to include Susie in an act. Okay, act. No, no,
don't hurt. C-Round. Compliment. You recall, uh, Rousey, you're just going to defend.
You ordered Susie to flatter the enemy. What? Why the hell would I do that? It attacked us!
Let's smash it before it moves! Oh, look, Susie, it seems harmless. If you act nice,
we might win without hurting it. Okay, hey, little guy, I really like the axe on your face.
Oh, am I gonna get the bad ending because of that? The bad ending. Hehehe, I sneaked
by and made a sign. Weirdo. Wow, look at that guy over there. Susie, listen. As heroes,
we have the power to make a peaceful future. So, from now on, let's try avoiding fighting.
Uh, what if you just took it easy on me? If you weaken an enemy, I can use my pacify spell,
which can put exhausted people to sleep. Yawn, yeah, you talking is already doing that.
Well, um, just think about it. You might have to warn enemies about her.
The violent tormentor is now your ally. The power of mean girls shines within you.
Hey. Hey, kid. You wanna buy a tutorial? It's only 50 dark dollars. Really? You're
really gonna buy it? Right this way, gentlemen. Uh, we're sorry, we're normally puzzle guys, but
we've been forced to do tutorials just to make ends meet. When the king got power,
he fired everyone and replaced all puzzle makers with him. Rooks will scar the lord of the
puzzles. Be careful. I'm TP master. Ask me about TP. Secret. TP only lasts inside a fight.
Once you win, it's out of sight. Having extra feels unbearable. No point in saving. It's
straight up terrible. The leftover TP turns into extra money at the end of a battle.
You mean I only should have been using one square? I'm Ralsei master. Ask me about Ralsei's
fact. Ralsei loves when you give us money. He will hug you and call you honey. Hey,
that's not true. You don't need money to get me to do that. I'm Susie master. Ask me anything
about Susie. Uh, fact. Susie loves when you give us money. She will. Nope, don't care.
Did I say something funny? I don't have any hats. I'm Chris master. Ask me anything about
Chris. Fact. It's a good idea to give us bucks. It'll make you happy and fill you
with lucks. Over there is our donation hole. We had a box, but it got stole.
Hole goals. $1 monthly tutorial weekly. $10 weekly tutorial monthly. $100 stop making tutorials.
Donation hole. If you like our tutorials, please throw your money into a hole. You put
a dollar in the hole. The hole became full. The hole is filled to the brim with cash.
I put a dollar in. The king didn't even give us severance pay. His son just gave us all
beanies. Itchy beanies. That was a fake. That was just a large cartoon dollar.
You guys know fun fact. That's not even true. Never mind. It's a lie.
Never mind. Hihi, welcome travelers. Whatever you got. A star shaped candy that heals 40 HP.
Mysterious hamburger heals 70 HP. Defensive charm that a spooky sword.
I feel like this is probably important. Do I have 200 bucks? I already have two candies.
You get a burger. That's a lot of money though. $70 for a hamburger? That's kind of insane.
Burger. I'm gonna buy one of these cards too. What about yourself? The name's Sheem, pronounced
Sean. And this is my little sheep. It's haha. Over the years I've collected odds and ends.
Of course I have no attachment to any of it. It's just a hobby of mine.
Around here you learn to find ways to pass the time or go mad like everyone else.
Long ago the darkners lived in harmony with the lightners. They were like gods to us. Our
protectors, our creators, those who gave us purpose. And one day we were all locked away in
this prison and the lightners never returned. Embittered, the king took up arms and aims to
take revenge upon the lightners that left us behind. Of course even among his troops
some still distantly hope the lightners will return. You're legendary, ha ha ha. So you
are the heroes who are going to seal our fountain. Ha good luck, it makes no difference
to me. Neither light nor dark hold a future for a dark nerd in my condition. Historically this land
was ruled by the four kings from Card Castle to the east but recently a strange knight
appeared and three of the kings were locked away. The remaining king put him and his strange son
into power. This land has seen this much chaos since. Laughing about it just a little
bit. Well you don't need to know about that. Let's give it a save. Power of mean girls.
Chaos chaos chaos. What do you mean chaos? We're sorry we're normally puzzle guys but yeah
just want to make sure I didn't miss anything. Gaining TP. You get TP when you defend
then you can cast spells. Yeah that's what I figured. Look for the heart outline when you
get close to bullets. Oh wait hold on because it's important. So when you barely get hit by
something it gives you defense points. Say that again. You get TP when you defend protect yourself
and cast spells. You also get TP by getting close to bullets. Look for the heart outline.
Okay so I wasn't getting actually I wasn't getting hit by anything. Okay okay so as long
as I get close enough from the door. It's a lone door frame but for some reason you can't
see through it. Well flip my flapjacks. The clowns are back in town. Well bad news since you last
saw me several minutes ago. I've created a brand new fighting team ready to stop me.
Not even the purple girl can stop me now. Oh what are you ready for me?
Stop talking. Ho ho ho. What is that? Why are you saying that? Ho ho ho. It's my evil laugh.
Scary right? Sound like baby santa claus. Oh you mean like in a badass way?
Shut up. Really think you know how to be scary? Well I uh wrong.
Maybe tough guys like you really piss me off. They said you wouldn't know scary.
They picked you up and bit your face off. Why why does she want to eat people? That's not
true. Really? Then why don't you prove it? Eat this person? Well start with the part
where your face gets bit off. Oh okay I get it. Thank you purple girl. What?
Thanks it was kind of you to teach me how to be scary with an evil laugh.
Hey I wasn't and now you're going to be thrashed. Ah ah Merry Christmas.
I guess that's kind of an improvement. A board of jigsaws walked away. I'm gonna
probably warn. Warn the jigsaw? You and Rousey warned the enemies about Susie. Everyone went
on guard. Fighting? I love fighting. I have a rent payment to make. How? Trying to calculate
this month's rent. So they've been warned. Now let's be friends. I'm gonna just defend here.
Barely lift the finger and well look we have to be friends. Good. I always want to be friends
just like you. We're friends now. I do want to get barely hit. Uh jigsaw is pretending to
march. They're all good to go. Oh wait uh oh uh oh uh oh uh oh thank god. We're friends
now. Voila. Jigsaw is wishing it could quit its job. Double spare. You won. You got 73 dollars.
All right now where's Papyrus 2? Oh no not one of these. Oh look Chris another puzzle.
Oh no. Let's read the instructions. Oh the instructions are vandalized. It says
thou fools thou will never figure out how to do it. Now ruining instructions does
definitely against the rules. Then it says ps I make my own rules. RK. Well that explains that.
Why don't we just climb over this spiked fence? Not because then we'd get impaled and die.
Cool I'll work on that and you do the puzzle. Try your best. Why can't you just stand over
there? Great job Chris. I think you're on to something. I know I'm on to something.
Give up whenever you feel like it. So I'll go what's with this angel and devil bullshit?
You did it Chris. Great job. Damn didn't get to impale myself. Jesus. Good job Chris.
Galaxy brain. Always check the top. Always check around. From the bottom the order of our rooms
in card castle. Of course if you haven't been there you won't know it. Okay uh really emphasizing
that it's impossible if you haven't been there. So I have to see where all the rooms are.
Is it impossible though? I'm killing this guy. No I'm not. What would Sans do?
Warn the enemies about Susie. Matthew has a little secret. Okay let's. Is it lecture or
convince? I just convinced. You told Rudin to quit fighting. He was utterly swayed.
Yeah I guess that makes sense. Long live the guy who paid this. Shit. Okay so I can spare
Rudin and then. Spare Rudin and then. Are they are they warned right now?
Yeah they're warned. I could always pacify. No one's tired. Just kill them. That defeats.
Look I played the first game and I know that.
Spoilers for the first game. Why would you be watching this if you don't know about the
first game? Uh if you. Whatever. You know what I'm about to say. Wow Undertale spoilers.
Well don't act like you never played it. All right let's do extreme flatter.
You don't need XP just encountering your smile is rewarding enough.
Now let's my face my diamond cutter. Yeah yeah yeah. All right so spare. Spare.
Congratulations you win the game. Wait Undertale's a game? Uh it's an app.
That's the proper way to say it. So I mean it's an app man. Uh all right let me.
I guess we're just gonna go this way. Sign. When you step into the light you'll return to
where you were before. I don't think I want to do that though. All right so we gotta go.
We gotta wait till we get an opportunity right now. Okay more of that. More of this.
Uh oh. Hon man drew near. All right we got hon man lullaby or let's do warning.
Oh I wasn't ready for that one. Hypnotize by your idle animation. All right so we can do uh
let's lullaby. Let's lullaby. Saying a soft and entrancing lullaby. Hon man fell asleep.
Suzy fell asleep and we just became tired. Okay well that's good. Can't keep its eyes open
and I can pacify. Now she won't attack. That's good. Though she kind of has low HP.
You kind of got low HP. Now we got another flash here. Back and forth. One two one two one two.
Sure thing. There's Santa. So you've begun to cross the great board.
The halfway point to our castle. Impressive. So it's a shame you won't make it a step further
because my guys are about to smash you into blood. Lots of blood. Splooshing blood. Very gross and
bad. Hey purple girl was that scarier? You're asking me because you're really cool at being
terrifying. I want to be as scary as you. You want to be like me? Yeah. Well that's stupid.
But um the new laugh isn't as awful. Saying you'd turn us into blood is uh cool.
What's up with the bucket though? It's to put the blood in. Oh yeah I'm not uh not supposed
to make a mess. Anyway thanks for your feedback. I'm really feeling scary. No problem I
guess. That's that. I write that. That's I do haha. So are you guys gonna attack us or uh oh
yeah oh yeah I was so excited I forgot to bring any guys but next time it'll be the end for
Hey I've just been calling you guys clowns. Does your team have an official name or something?
Oh Chris we should come up with a name. No we shouldn't.
Then it's decided everyone puts a name in the bucket.
All right everyone's put in their entry. Blue person you can choose since you look like you
don't care. Uh crumpled paper neat paper or lancer labeled paper. Definitely this one.
You take the paper what lancer have written on the outside. You open it up. On the inside it
also says lancer. Wow who did that one it's really good. Wait why did you get to choose
the name? Yeah he didn't. Chris did. Yeah it doesn't matter who may have written it. Regardless
lancer is going to meet absolute doom. This name feels weird actually.
I know let's call it the lancer fan club for short. See you later me. The power of the lancer
fan club shines within you. It sure does. Watch out. Oh oh let me watch it. So three two.
So it's safe up there. It's safe up in the in the corner there. So just stand here. So
then it's safe in the middle. No it's not. It's safe in the. I mean it is. It is now.
Oh same. I'm getting like electrocuted. Stop it. Stop it. Stop it. Stop it. Stop it. Stop it.
Stop it. Stop it. Stop it. This streamer man. What? You gotta say something. Say it to my
face. If you're gonna say something say it to my face. That's uh doing rounds he warned
the enemies about Susie. Yeah. Yeah. Yep. Yep. Yep. Yep. Yep. Show us your face then.
Uh I gave italics my weapon. I was gonna turn it on.
It's not here. Uh vomit listens politely despite having no ears.
Now he can act but he's asleep. Susie fell asleep. They're all tired and can't keep
his eyes open. Good. You're out. Good. Uh you're out. Nice joker reference.
Stop. I got hit. I shouldn't have gotten hit by that. Pawn man can't keep his eyes open.
Let's. I'm gonna put you back to sleep again. See ya. I need to heal uh Susie. Susie's hurt.
Why was that thing? Great board two. It's fireman. Look at this dude.
Oh they're horsey. Pawn men are scary but all in all they're doing is following the king.
Us on the board used to have our own boss. Those were the peaceful times but now even
the boss has been reduced to the king's peon. My name? Mr. Elegance. Haha and these these are
my nostrils not my eyes. Can still see out of them though. Interesting. Fear not we unlike
the simple pawn man possess full faculty over our actions. I Mr. Society am far too intelligent
to ever bow down to such a tyrant unless he asks me. He's very scary you see. What? You
think you possess the power to topple that brute? Yes yes yes. I'm sure everyone will
support you. Go for it. Just as long as I don't have to participate. Okay thanks. Oh
well step on my boots. If it isn't the Lancer fan club you boys or girls had better
turn back while you can. Lancer what is it this time? Oh I'm simply warning you.
Something extremely dangerous is lying ahead. Oh it's actually really inconvenient.
I can't go home at all because I'm so scared. What is it? We already fought this dog. Hey
it's the little guy. That's what you're afraid of. Wow purple girl you aren't scared?
Why would I be? What's it gonna do? Well normally it crushes people to death I think.
Here it comes. K-round. Deep bow warning. Let's let's give it let's do a warning.
You explain to K-round about the importance of dodging Suzy's attacks but it didn't seem
to understand. Well oh god okay it just jumps. Well let's bow. You and Rousey bowed. K-round
bowed back. Its crown loosened. That's it Chris. If we can get its crown off it should
turn back into a little guy. Suzy help us bow at it. Now its crown will come off when I smash
the guy to the ground. Well I'm gonna have to put you to sleep. Can I? I don't have like a lullaby
because we can do deep bow. The crown is 20% loose. Is there anything I can do to make you?
I guess I can. Here I'll do this. I'm gonna bow. Pacify. Can I pacify? I figured maybe I
could um pacify Suzy. All right bow and then heal prayer. I can't heal. Heal ally.
Well looks like we're doing the super bow. Bowed back. Its crown loosened.
Ah felt stressed out and attacked. K-round practiced self-care. What was that? Was that
like almond milk? K-round's HP and attack went up. Suzy stop attacking it you're making
it stronger. Let it think I'm afraid? No way. The crown is 40% loose. Just into the deep bow.
K-round bowed back. The crown loosened again. Whoa. Oof. Oof. Oof. Oof. No no. Um don't bow
and then I'm gonna heal because you just won't listen. Heal prayer. You just won't listen.
Oh my god why was I not paying attention? I just think I was staring. Crown is 75% loose.
Uh deep bow should do it right? Well then I'll be at 95. Well I think we're fine. Deep bow.
K-round bowed back. Its crown loosened one more time. Time to get in the dryer now.
I can't imagine doing that. This is probably some fucking guy on YouTube that was like
you've been going into me bill crazy and today I'm getting in a fucking dryer.
That's right. I'm sure it exists. And we're gonna turn it normally we're gonna turn the dryer on.
We're gonna put it on high heat and high speed. I'm gonna bow this deep bow again.
I'm not doing this bullshit. I ain't going on like the permanent press. I think I won.
Have I made this joke before about getting in the dryer if I lost?
You clowns really are heroes. You saved the next 20 minutes of my life.
We? What do you mean we? We? What do they say we?
Yeah Bill I'm making a reference to Bill crazy again because he's gonna be in the rumble
next weekend. Like I have to I have to bring some of these characters that you haven't heard
of in a while back so you know when you see them in the rumble that like it's like oh
there he is. Oh yeah if you weren't at the green screen stream this next weekend here is
Germany in 2018. That's like 600 characters. That's a lie. I'm lying a lot tonight.
I gotta stop lying to you.
Uh Suzy enough downplay your contributions but you uh you didn't actually help at all.
You only made everything worse by attacking. If you had just acted nice to it in the
first place you could have avoided that entire battle.
Are you for real? That thing was bloodthirsty. The only thing keeping it at bay was my axe.
And earlier you terrorized those troops. Those guys were enemies therefore terrorizing.
Yeah she's right. And before that you ate an innocent person's cake.
Cakes are also my enemy.
Suzy whether you like it or not you're a hero. One with the power to bring peace to the future.
Could you please start acting like one?
Yeah when you lay it out like that I've been a pretty bad hero haven't I?
Alright you got it. I'll change my ways. From now on I won't be such a rotten hero anymore.
I'll just be one of the bad guys instead.
Really? You're going to be on my team?
Yeah sounds way easier honestly. Suzy you can't just...
Quiet toothpaste boy. Suzy is my comrade now. Hey yeah toothpaste boy.
We're going to have monogrammed track jackets.
Yeah at sleepovers where we tell each other the secrets.
Um yeah anyway uh see you guys never if you can even last that long.
Perhaps I shouldn't have been so hard on her.
But I just worry that if Suzy is too eager to fight then well let's just be kind to her
okay. I'm sure Suzy will come around soon.
Well blocking foliage grows thick above your head. The power of the forest shines within you.
101 minutes and 37 hours. It's not that bad.
Hey kid we met us to fix up this old thing of a jig for you.
It's some kind of door. It can take you anywhere you want in the world.
As long as that's one of the two locations.
Anywho we'll keep working on it. Anything to help you out kid.
Oh there horsey. Mr. Society and the puzzle guy fixed that door.
Since it was just the three of us it should work without any issues.
Anyhow I hope it helps you deal with the king.
Now don't tell anyone Mr. Society helped. He doesn't want none of that.
I'm watching you now with my nostrils.
It's a door. Where will you go?
Field forest. Uh field. The door open.
Okay so this okay this is the door to go back.
All right. Ah! Uh oh.
Rabbic slithered in the way.
Uh breathe all? Press zebra peel to blow air.
Freshing boy. How does that mean?
Looking for a couch to get stuck under.
All right. No no no no! Okay I did it.
Press the button too many times.
I did attack and I thought I was gonna punch the person.
All right.
Suzy! Lancer!
Hey hey hey.
Well if it isn't the so-called heroes.
Are you finally ready to see what happens?
When you try to act soft against a team that crushes anyone in their way.
Dark Jack Lancer.
Violent Axe Suzy.
Together we are the Dark Lancer fan club.
So what's your evil plan?
Huh?
Dude we just formed our team.
We haven't done anything past our intro yet.
Have a little patience please.
Oh I'm sorry.
We're uh looking forward to the rest.
You won't have to look forward to it for long.
Starting now we're going to work ceaselessly.
I couldn't say that.
Unstoppably to make an evil plan to thrash you clowns.
Watch your backs and your fronts.
Unstoppably what?
Did I say it wrong?
Franch?
What are you talking about?
What do you mean crunch?
What did I say?
I say something.
What?
What happened?
What is going on here?
All right.
I'm gonna breathe all zee zee zee zee zee zee zee zee zee zee zee zee zee zee zee.
Ambiently damage the spoil.
I can't even.
I can't even man.
You won.
Got zero xp at 77 dollars.
Is Jerma okay?
I'm fine.
it's a stump with some kind of dinner hole in it how's the evil scheming going
huh oh that uh we uh got bored so we're having a snack i see come on all i ate for breakfast was
chalk and i didn't eat anything sorry what are you two having exactly just a daily treasure i
hid in this stump's orifice and that is feast for yourself my main man chris do you want to
try it oh uh there's a honey pot inside it's full of salsa bingo you sweet little pumpkin
it's my secret stash a little snack-a-roo from me to you yummy it's delicious come on you're
just pretending to eat it oh yeah that's what i do too my power is lowered by my hunger right
now but once i eat something you really shouldn't have pissed me off man it shouldn't have
silence you sweet basket of eggs our dark energy bends the rules of grammar
yeah egg boy it's a stump with some kind of dinner hole well has everybody had enough
constantly that's what i do too pretend to eat it oh watch out wearing bowser's cape
the hell is that that guy is like a coat hanger it's a coat hanger and wi-fi kirby who do i talk
to first let's talk to wi-fi kirby i'm just a little ball i don't want to discuss anything
okay you folks look like heroes take the scarf from this chest and defeat the king
besides it's old ragged and doesn't fit me anymore that's what chests are for it's
kind of hand me down situation in here i used to work at the castle until the king fired all the
staff what was my job oh i was a royal colt rat cool story but you open the cheshire
terrest inside was a ragger you put the ragger in your weapons i don't even know why red
scarf 10 2 what do i have on wood blade i guess it's yours amber card that gets you to
no bill oh i know you already have the weapon you've written on so that's just plus one defense
i mean i forgot to put this on oh fine all right we got power of one prickly prince deals
damage with his rugged scarf okay anything else any more dialogue from you no what about wi-fi
kirby no watch out oh calm down it's fine oh wait a minute enter the password
due to everyone forgetting the password it's written at the top
okay i need the there we go see that's not gonna hey we need this oh wait i need to i need to
remember the password it's not the password well different way all right uh blocks are
assembled rearrange press c to choose one head what c to choose one head two body
oh you mixed me all up nice did i though i think i just put them in the right okay
radiates the spirit of joy we won got 48 dollars let me check down here all right so we need to
get diamond come on there's nothing else oh diamond club diamond club got spade diamond club
spade so this needs to be like this so this has to be on it first
first
oh my god somebody just gave 10 community subs uh and ferrick thank you so much for
the 10 community subs shitload of fucking money shitload of people thank you
10 thank you so much man a lot of subs all right so it was now any diamond and then club
so that means i have to go like this i did it backwards spade fuck shit
okay uh dog but no seriously thank you and fair i'm not gonna open this yet
bow bow break the box for a bracelet bow bow it will boost your defense
yeah the king wants to eliminate lightners but we didn't agree with that we escaped but the
oh there's were oh rested don't worry about talking to my associate here whenever bow bow talks
she always goes on and on and on and on and on and on and on uh bracelets are my
be favorite uh pin man one two three came in with 10 community subs
thank you pin man 10 10 20 community subs now in the last two minutes from pin man and
and ferrick thank you both you guys congrats to the sub getters and thank you for your
generosity you guys for real thank you you opened the treasure chest inside was dice
race you put dice brace in your armor just as empty well except for some bowels
okay we need to go
dice brace is better
card yeah amber card that sucks i'm gonna sell it
oh there are two armor slots okay i didn't do really all right let's pretty simple
all right see we need to go ahead chest pants be happy
oh you mixed me on nothing nice okay kill don't fight active spare in the same term i guess
that's yeah that's true so that you can keep it up all right two armor slots i'm gonna give
it to you we should have a magic user that can heal be able to live the longest that's what i
would say okay hole oh rk came by what a hunk he vandalized the puzzle to stop the lighteners
but we know the answers oh you want to get through of course we'll tell you uh the first
symbol is a heart ah just like love does that help heart make me a oh symbol puzzle all the
symbols were different i think you can uh still see the colors they were too all right can't be
any more help all right so that so the one on the left so it's a heart so it's heart
something uh heart something diamond heart uh let's just try this oops oops
oops nope so it's heart spade diamond hey it's my birthday today and you didn't even say hello
that's fine actually what yes i did stop and say hi folks shut up they don't deserve us hey
calm down you two let's celebrate my birthday yeah get ready to hurt oh i'm sorry about this
clover grew close okay we got talk boys talk sports talk birthday talk birthday
what would you like for your birthday let's just have a nice chat idiot ask for a gift
just discuss our likes uh let's just have a nice chat seems like you should talk about
something else it's my birthday what no it's my birthday we're triplets okay uh so let's talk
about let's talk about boys um what kind of boys do you like cute ones nice ones uh i mean
all boys seems like over enjoy talking about that glasses are cute i think fluffy glasses
uh sure never hums like an out of tune choir talk sports talk animals talk trees talk uh talk
sports no talk trees let's talk sports do you like uh sports i want to eat a football sports
my favorite food oh i love you too i've been talking about that spaghetti and tennis balls
that's genius we really agree on it seems tired of discussing so much not yet i guess i could
just pacify oh i don't have enough so could i wait and all i could defend with him
there we go spaghetti and tennis balls oop save it part of the woods bake sale stands quietly
the power of reoccurring bake sales shines with it yes it does interested in a
choco diamond all proceeds go to ruden relief funds i guess it's only 40 gold thanks i guess
the chocolate diamond was added to your items hathie offers a hearts donut proceeds go to
hathie's health that costs 40 gold hathie seemed happy the hearts donut was added to your
items greetings gentle clowns may we interest you in a lancer cookie all proceeds go to
kicking grass it's a mere 40 gold sure thanks the lancer cookie was added to your items
for getting cheated by us now we may fund our illicit plans i don't understand this cardboard
stand is actually just a fake cardboard stand of a cardboard stand is it not oh they've bought
food all right so how should we split this jelly donut i'll take the blood and you take
the skin that's such a disgusting way to talk about a donut all real plans allocate for
delicious treats sounds like you need to go to plan school doctor toothpaste oh yes earn a
second doctorate smart genius am i being made fun of but interestingly enough that's diamond
heart uh spade so maybe i'll need it in a second diamond heart spade let's look at
where will you go uh we're gonna stay at the bake sale amazingly you are already there
diamond heart spade uh you don't look like it i'm in a heart or a spade door well well i'm
the smith malius i can fix anything weapon armor i can even fix you well well what'll it be
fix us your body is a weapon too you must take care of it from time to time
ha ha let's feel my technique somehow everyone's hp was restored well don't you feel better after
a nice massage ha ha you can fix anything weapon armor can fix you fix item that cake
is seething with energy you must let me fix it let's feel my technique the broken cake was
fixed beyond recognition the broken cake became the top cake this is truly a tremendous cake
use its power wisely this cake will make your taste buds spin heals 160 hp to the team
hearts donut it's filled with uh this is a clotty red jam plus a certain amount of hp
a cookie shaped like lancer's face it's maybe not even a cookie heals five hp maybe
it's quite small but some people really like it plus random hp dom has just said something
else dark burger a mysterious black burger made of hey this is just burnt
70 hp a red and black star that tastes like marshmallows blow shard so i got the cake
uh let me uh let me take this opportunity to let me take a quick break i want to grab some
water and use the urinal i will be right back i'll leave the music on because i know
that everybody loves this music see in two minutes okay hello um second whoops okay
turn this down just a little because it is the sub sound is getting a little loud
what was that a loud windows noise now that was me that was me that was me
uh but so let's go back to where we were back up here delta ruin okay all right uh so
i really should play this with my like a controller or something i probably can
something about like the uh arrow keys and zxc is kind of cramping up my hands a little
old fucking man that's pretty much all there is to it all right let's go
do i need joy do i need joy to keep he's a boomer i mean i got my i got like my hands lock up
all right so we got like a diamond heart spade exercise yeah i've been i've been doing exercise
hands does it have hold on wait wait wait wait wait just like i've got a loud windows
noise just make sure you're aware of this was a good game i mean doom was a good game
what are you talking about right there all right oh yeah i like look and listen listen to
this you can hear you can really nice okay that's better i've been doing that for like
two and two plus hours with my hands on arrow keys nice all right i'm ready look at
how much better i'm gonna play watch this i tried it's all right all right we got uh two
blockers we're gonna act rearrange and you defend does it have to be uh in any particular order
does it have to be the same one every time you think oh uh that's not working why are
none of these working oh that's because it's why planet xbox one by the way oh i'm gonna knock
your block off the tetris okay thinking about trains uh actually we're gonna go
rearrange and then i'm gonna spare you head a little thanks for mixing me up you're welcome
buddy uh i was i don't know i was reading chat
i need to pay attention to that i can't just i'm just looking over here whatever
that is getting fucking drier worm guy before the king kangalan i used to eat the leaves
from this tree now i still do that such as the way of the worm all right can i eat leaves
eat leaves i guess i can't steal the dryer what the fuck why was i allowed to go through here
it's a kind of weird shortcut uh okay 40 dark dollars somebody's secret stash was over here
all right we got dancers just have to join the uh join the line here so let's try down down
to the left i see a chest over there i kind of want it inside it was revivement you put
revivement in your items probably bringing somebody back to life i would assume is it
just made his germacene pissed off today pissed off today what why what what happened
but i'm pissed off i picked the worst one to go in can i go down from here look at
how angry he is what what i'm fine i'm i'm doing good i'm i'm like happy this
it's a good day today what did i do okay let me try there's a secret path down
jesus christ you're listening to one guy yeah i don't know i don't see a path
guys i'm fine i'm fine all right i'm fucking fine okay i'm not angry what are you guys talking
about i'm fine oh whoa whoa it's me rose and rose of woes and woes if only a hero would help
is everything all right oh i'm not lancer i'm just a sweet little boy
why does a sweet little boy have a mustache as a disguise
so what kind of help do you need see i have this evil plan that i need to make
and why does a sweet boy need an evil plan to impress his cool friend suzy first if it's for
friendship well then we'll gladly help what shall we do it's all on the paper you delicious
little apple just fill it with the most evil thing you can imagine oh let the clown generated
content begin i've been doing clown generated content on this channel for years now it hasn't
been it's ain't seen nothing yet by the way create a machine to thrash your own ass
presented by lancer industries which was just made up right now head laser sword
lay an enchanting gun with an air of mysticism okay hold on elegant lively cute hot cool and
guns i have to make it garbage you're going to lose points i don't want to do the duck
everybody probably picks the duck i want to do hot and cute okay body plane streamlined chassis
for an elegant thrashing a fast chassis for a tomboyish thrashing chassis for gun lovers
the cannon is highly kissable duck just looking at this is making you lose points
i mean that guy i gotta like how that looks though and shoes sporty shoes for the athletic
thrashing machine attractive wheels leading the way and weaponized treads for raising
sophisticated dinner parties for duck you're gonna lose points i kind of like the yoshi shoes
and we get cute points wait i need the head color let me get it hey i gotta do my colors
all right i like it nobody ever picks duck actually wait is this one of those
self-fulfilling prophecies where everybody that plays this game thinks that everyone's
picking duck so they don't pick it at all it has to be right but just that's only duck
everyone picks duck i why i'll be the first one no fucking way i i refuse to believe that
that i'm the first person that is streamed undertale whatever the sequel to it whatever
it's called down undertale takes place in australia i'm the only person that's ever
done duck is that what you're telling me no i want to do what i had before i liked what
i had before i want to flame the duck body can stay all right i'm doing it is this your machine
yes and it's really cute it's really hot oh it looks nasty are you sure you weren't evil
all right now i suppose we just have a knack for it ha ha tricked you idiot never do
something someone else can do for you for free never do something you could do for free for
free do for money it almost looks kind of cute anyway great job lancer they were sitting
ducks never do something you're good at no it's if you're good at something never do it for free
another reference he's bringing out the old material tonight guys ha ha yes and it's all
thanks to our enemies thank you very much thrash you later okay it's nice as he finally
found a place she fits in she's getting along with lancer too uh hey oh fuck i'm
gonna die wait where's my safe point don't die you can do it i'm gonna die i'm gonna die
um i kind of need to eat candy 40 hp no i don't think getting a dryer i didn't die
revolve around the center and look carefully the darker it gets the more you can see
revolve around the center and look carefully well let me check up whoa easy now just want
to go all the way around just take a look that is to go around the center so like here
the darker it gets it easier it is to see so the lights are turning off
hey it's getting that's coming up here okay it's like a weird bird person
wait they're right here though hard to see there was a switch in the tree
i thought that was just i thought it was big bird anything else that will answer cookie
am i gonna need these for anything though go back and forth what am i doing go back and
forth between this room and the last why am i getting spoilers i don't want to be spoiled
no i'm even reading chat i'm gonna go i shouldn't be doing that it's not really a spoiler it's
something you probably never find on your own yeah but i might go back and peruse around you
know go to the right all right well they're lying on two band-aids i don't know why that
is all right so are ready to be a good guy again now i gotta say being a bad guy is pretty
sweet not only is it way more fun than being good but my teammate's proud of what i do
you earlier suzy ate a pine cone off the floor it gave her a terrible stomachache
it was very brave and cool see finally some respect somehow prince lancer has made real
friends with a lightener so somebody should tell the king immediately it's definitely not
going to be me whoever breaks the news is going to get wrecked uh how's the thrash
machine we designed going uh the what machine the machine we had a whole sequence about it
oh that yeah we'll make it at the last minute you two should really start working on it earlier
what's with the lecture i didn't come here for a second dad hey yeah you tell them oh why does
the king make us take care of his son he's not a bad kid but he's so weird and it's so
obligatory it's no wonder nobody really likes him damn no by the way beware yourselves of the
forest maze you'll probably get completely lost without someone who knows the way through that is
yeah i know the forest like the back of my head oh there's a and and even even on even
undertale is talking about geno and i okay where is he where is he yeah this is this
is a super mario rpg reference right here this is what they're doing so which way are we
going next we were following you oh why i have no idea where i'm going first let's just go
wherever lancer doesn't go or should i maybe maybe i should do it eventually here
nope nope nope nope no slither the way you're gonna blow breathe all press z z
easy let's spare them i do like the sort of uh left and right side of the screen
fucking god damn it
find the secret no hey losers wait a sec where's the lancer well he wasn't going the right way so
you let him wander off by himself you know he's bad at mazes right he's probably lost and
confused right now i've lost and confused sorry susie we didn't mean to make you worry
about him oh look i'm not uh worried about him bad guys got to look out for each other
there's all anyway get out of my way i'm gonna find him see if she doesn't know the right way
either well they go go the way that they're not going what what was the hitbox on that come on man
ah go back can i go back uh whatever i keep forgetting because i could have just done uh
spare instead of uh sitting here like this in defense mode sorry germa for asking if you're
pissed off and causing a wave of people telling you to calm down we all love you can't wait for
germania no i'm just kidding around i didn't i don't remember where they even went well i was
wrong damn i was sure he went this way no way he could save his own damn self i went the wrong
fucking way too oh no oh shit okay i could do the whole thing again right up the middle
and then on the right i don't want to fight you and then oh shit where are they go to the left
right at the middle i got it got it bad because mad bad is mad mad because bad
oh look it's our toy with the toy we made isn't that the machine we designed all right
this will be tough but let's try our best oh that's uh it's not good actually oh you
think that's bad just wait and see what happens when it starts the design sucked so we blew it up
oh i see so now what's your plan going to be turns out we didn't need a plan just a rule
anyone that gets in our way gets crushed into dust that's a pretty good rule but suzy you
need us to return home doesn't crushing us seem a little counterproductive nah so that's where
you're wrong you see i know i can't get back without you guys but being a good guy really
isn't my style so i thought of a little way we can just settle this if you can beat me i'll go
back to being a good guy but if you lose you guys will have to become bad guys with us
and do whatever we say oh our wish is your command so what do you say
um okay we were just gonna thrash you anyways see ya two bad guys blocked away
i've got suzy and we have lancer lancer probably easier to deal with x anything anything anything
i'm told ralcy to compliment the enemies you two look like a really great team i'm proud
lancer started to become a little convinced oh it's working on me flattery won't work
uh suzy and lancer are making fun of you uh let's try suzy sing let's try to sing
ralcy saying a soft and entrancing lullaby doesn't she go to sleep suzy fell asleep
oh what a beautiful song smells like teamwork all right uh so suzy's asleep
so now lancer can i you told the logically best lancer and suzy you too if we don't stop fighting
then someone might get hurt lancer became more convinced it's working really that's bad ow
having an evil laugh contest well she's asleep same thing do again you told her to offer his
you told ralcy to offer his services to the enemies you too if we stop fighting then i could
uh i could braid your hair lancer became almost fully convinced wow i'll look amazing i'm awake
did i miss anything all right let's do the same thing sing suzy to sleep good night what a beautiful
song whoa why for some reason thought it was a dumb an idiot let's convince lancer told
ralcy to come deal a final blow of kindness i in summary i'd like you to and i think we
should all just get along uh oh what's wrong dude i accidentally started liking the enemies
now seeing them just makes me feel round and soft bad atmosphere for battle though
well if you don't want to fight there's no point i guess battles over well you didn't
beat us because you uh kind of cheated by ganging up on lancer with uh kindness but if
i have to i guess i'll go back to your side but don't expect me to do anything but fight
well we're happy to have you back suzy yeah yeah let's just hurry up and go home
i know what about him um suzy does this mean that we aren't a team anymore
uh i mean uh of course we're still a team you can uh be part of the lancer fan club
wow me in the lancer fan club wait if i hang out with the good guys then
can we still have monogram track jackets yeah ralcy will make them huh oh okay sure
lancer joins the team lancer joined the party this is a huge party wait why is he not he's not
following you can follow behind us you know oh okay chad it's a lone door frame but for some reason
you can't see through it wow this is cool i've never been on such a big team before
don't you have a legion of various guys yeah but my dad forced them to listen to me
so they don't actually like me very much yeah well you don't need those clowns anymore
just chill with us aye aye he's doing the chad walk he's doing the chad thing oh no he's dot
man i'm still hungry it's like nothing i eat here matters
should have stolen more money for the bake sale i guess i was thinking of baking a cake later
what's the catch you have to stop making fun of me for one pass i can't stop thinking
about the chad thing uh look suzy a candy tree hell yeah
this that has to be by design right it has to be there's no way that he didn't do that on
purpose damn the last piece is too high to reach worry not suzy i have a special
transformation for times like this really watch and learn look stool form all you did was put
your hands on the ground hey don't act so jealous hey got it oh tell me what it tastes like
oh you haven't had it before oh i mean i've always wondered what it's like
but i'm not allowed to pick it for myself well you tell me what it tastes like you're giving
it to me i thought you were hungry it's her first act of real kindness i changed my mind
oh candy joins the team all right already stop so what's it taste like
yum yum yum it tastes like friendship what's that taste like
like my teeth are disintegrating that's that's actually uh yeah but thank you for sharing
you're a good friend well uh you too i guess just walking along with you guys feels nice
like i'm doing something important because you're alongside the lighteners lancer our purpose
darkner's purpose is to assist them it's the only way we can truly feel fulfilled really
but my dad hates lighteners he wants to does your dad seem happy i'm not sure chad walk
yeah let's ditch the weird purpose talk you're probably just glad you ate a weird berry
yeah i'm still boost from the juice i mean look i'm not from here and hanging out like this
i also feel kind of uh you know happy how long is it gonna go on maybe look everyone
we can see the castle yes that's where i live me and uh my my dad what's that black thing
emerging from the top that's the fountain suzy if we can get there you and chris will
finally be able to go home jeez took long enough chris lancer let's go uh are you sure there uh is
it another way home fountain is being guarded right now if you try to go there uh you you
might get hurt and but come on lancer no one's gonna beat a team like us if anyone gets in
our way all we gotta do is crush them what if you had to fight everybody bleeds right
don't worry about it whoever it is they'll be called on the ground before you can blink
ababa suzy uh what yeah i think uh i think i need to go huh when you when you're coming back
never hey hey wait a second why are you acting so weird uh oh uh oh uh oh hey the lighteners
are approaching the castle get them i mean that's that's just what 700 days played
in answer no you can't come in what are you doing we've cornered them wait ow that's not good
you poor lighteners we were told to keep you in prison for eternity too bad would have loved to
see you guys punished ow define how do you do isn't it chris prison for eternity that sounds
like it might take a while and suzy where's suzy we have to find her we have to find her
chris before she gets hurt or um hurt someone else maybe there's something we can escape with
in here the shackles seem oddly fashionable take them iron shackle was put in your armor
life cannot exist without consuming even the moss drinks water
yeah perpetuate the cycle of existence you ate the moss tastes mossy your hp was mossed out
there's a crack in the wall what could be inside it's more wall well so what did you mind
what's all that green stuff around your mouth two minutes in jail and you've already resorted
to eating moss uh you're a real go-getter chris so you couldn't find anything well chris
let's not give up hope just yet but um if we don't make it out for some reason
and i just wanted to say um i'm glad i was able to meet hey idiots can you shut up i'm trying to
concentrate where is suzy i don't know prison seriously though i'm out of my cell i sweet
talked the warden into giving me the keys how i uh invited him to visit the trash can
anyway now there's a puzzle in the way okay solve it suzy i uh i don't i don't do puzzles
hey how about we just sit tight and wait for lancer he lives in the castle he's bound to
come save us why don't chris and i just help you solve the puzzle i don't need your help
but uh if you said what to do out loud you know i wouldn't stop you
you tell suzy what to do oh god okay so i i need to swap okay add spade swap
add no no add spade add diamond swap add spade add diamond swap add spade
yes we did it great now come free us all right all right all right
thanks for helping her chris she appreciates it chris are you worried about suzy kind of
probably i mean probably seems like she's very she's very influenceable she joined the bad guys
because she wanted to be a bad guy i know i'm a little concerned well regardless of how you feel
i don't think it would hurt to take a moment close your eyes and think about what she's doing
now uh-oh another puzzle out of the cell where to next oh fuck and there's a scary monster over
there oh chris did you say something back there i can't hear them anymore i'll just go this way
well that's a dead end that's lancer's voice damn not another one of these maybe i should
go back and ask chris and make sure they lancer i'll just do it myself come on one more you did
it understand they have to stay in their cells the lighteners can't be allowed to escape
especially the purple one lancer oh suzy what are you doing here
uh lancer chris and rousey are still locked up i i know i i was the one who told my troops to
put you down here to keep you down here forever lancer you you wanted to get rid of us
i thought we were a team i can explain suzy nah it's fine it's fine actually it's fine
he doesn't have to say anything i get it you know why would anyone really want to be
my friend anyway i said shut up but shut up shut up we're gonna see like a fucking death on
camera here get out of my way did you hear me get out of my fucking way no did you not hear
me man i tried to warn you i'm gonna eat your face right don't expect me to feel guilty
when they have to clean you off the floor hey want to see what happens to traders
uh they get crushed i'm killing this person right now i can't do anything about it should
i get hurt i'm gonna let them kill me if you don't get out of the way i'll kill you
no i have to die it's me i'm just avoiding me oh come on you missed idiot
ha ha i can't do it it won't let me wait why aren't you fighting back hey you think i
care if you just want to lie down and die you're just making it easier for me all right that's
enough if you want to die so much then die miss suzy you missed i don't want to kill you man
just move please but if i let you guys go then then you and my dad will fight
and you'll kill each other a lot of dot dot dots i've noticed in this game
at least if you stay here neither of you will get hurt well that's a real
creepy serial killer way to look at it if i just lock you in my basement forever then
like you'll never be hurt and i can take care of you then i i i won't kill him promise
me and him will just uh talk it out peaceful style you know i don't think my dad would like
that hey lancer come on we're a team right nothing can stop us fighting or not all right
dot dot yeah yeah you're right we might as well try i can help too i'll go talk to my dad
ripen him up you know we're getting somewhere i'll head over right now suzy are are we still
friends of course i mean if you want to be whoo see you how am i going to get past his
dad like that come on i'll figure something out so that's why okay chris you found your
way over here apparently hey hey suzy you came to save us i knew you had the heart of a
hero suzy yeah yeah don't push your luck chris and rousey joined the party chad lancer wins by
not moving a muscle so what was even over here anything that i can look at i mean there's this
guy yeah even i got arrested and i'm just a pair of eyes what's the world coming to
save point card castle prison you go up is this open i guess so wait i want to look at the
other way this lift should take us out of here oh now it might take a while so
let's chat get comfy everyone hey rousy you know lancer's dad the king uh when we meet him
you think we'll have to hurt him i mean i could easily smash him but you guys i know
that's not really your thing you're more about uh groveling like total losers classic
rpg elevator scene that's right and i was thinking maybe i could do that too
suzy you mean you want to try acting uh well suzy we'd be happy if you acted with us and
don't worry we'll be there to help you you won't have to figure it out by yourself
sure okay she's gonna die i already all right i mean i made this you know what i mean
like she's dead like she's like she's gonna add i know the whole story at this point
hey rousy uh suzy are you still gonna make those cakes
no i made this well will you stop making fun of me
well if i have to i guess and i'll bake you as many as you like all right like you can make
that many dude well this is our stop i just went to school that's the only thing i did
this morning right hey chris wait a sec you know i'm starting to realize right now
that i am a fraggle rock character took me a long time for about three hours to figure that
out but i am one of the main characters from fraggle rock it'll be easier for us to get
out of here if we all uh get along a little more so next time we fight an enemy
if you tell me what to do i'll listen to you well but you know don't tell me anything stupid
or i'll go back to smashing heads all right chris i'm counting on you dude suzy join the
party for real there's like real creepy clown music here
so lonely lonely i mean what low three visitors standing inside who are you few
nice to meet you i'm rousy this is chris and so what the hell are you doing in there
i'm innocent innocent i just wanted to play a game game but the boring kings found such
fun to be troubled as punishment they crave to imprison my body but i'm fast fast and clever
very clever they lost the chase and locked up their entire race building a prison around the
whole world now i'm the only free one free but you're clearly the one behind bars
things don't seem such from here lighteners sounds like you don't need any help then
that is also i grow lonely in my little freedom so shall you play a game with me me
me i'll show you what it means to be free find the key and i'll let you be free free
the key is hidden from the eyes the old shopkeeper knows a secret tear them from his
skull he is hidden from the eyes the old shopkeeper knows a secret shopkeeper he knows
a secret let's go talk to the shopkeeper where the fuck was that guy all right floor
first floor but this is hold on no no no no no no no no no prison b1 so let me just get out of
here eyes how do i get out how do i leave thanks for inviting me this trash can is really great
so i wasn't progressing when i was going to the first floor exit through the prison
let me just go to the prison and get out there's multiple exits i wanted to go this
way though oh god us animals used to be alone in these cages now everyone's here
so many new people wish we could go back to the good old days when it was just us in these
filthy cages since i didn't want to fight you guys i got locked up how can i you guys seem way
nicer than the king i was arrested for making a puzzle without a license i'll never make
another word search i promise whoa whoa whoa are the three former kings we are the three
former kings we beg you free us once all four of us ruled together but when the night arrived
everything changed oh my diamonds my jewels you must tell me if they're all right oh oh
so first floor go to the shopkeeper where's the shopkeeper am i going right way okay i'm
in the front i'm right at the front door there we go all right it's a door where will
you go uh where was is it wasn't the bake sale it was with the bake sale there it is okay
so you got a secret start talking strange prisoner uh what are you talking about a
prisoner with an odd manner no you couldn't possibly be talking about him i see after all
the trouble i went through to lock him up you want to release him uh now that you mentioned
it it could be troublesome if he was left alone yes perhaps it's better if you heroes
dealt with him now after all it's not as if whatever happens will matter in the end
perhaps a little chaos might be fun so then take this broken key a was added to your key items
if you're so driven find the other two pieces and get someone to fix them
i'll even give you a hint walk where the stars don't shine if you succeed come back
here and i'll and tell me good luck and call this luck no it's more like a curse
but the star okay it mattered to me but here's a walk where the stars don't shine
where the stars don't shine i mean that's he's talking about darkness like is this the way
that it was oh you dickhead just kill him no don't don't don't kill like no i can't
i can't get any bad stuff i want to do the good playthrough i'm already on the bad
playthrough what are you talking about how am i on the how oh my god tap it your choices don't
matter well i guess that's true that is true all right somebody somebody is really badly wants
me to do this and it's probably a spoiler but you know what am i gonna do item use uh
okay doesn't seem to be working what the hell is that all right where here's the hint where
the sun don't shine or something right nice dial-up check up what are you talking about
what uh this way i mean this is the oh shit check ass rival what does that mean
let me show you my salt and pepper shakers watch out now rearrange rearrange rearrange spare
so i could get two broken keys all right here we go i see where the stars don't shine so where
are those stars not shining i mean it looks like over here what is in there there's probably a
broken key in there where the stars don't shine let's do a breathe all and you can spare
any of them it doesn't really matter who a sweet and fresh girl a soft and clean boy
no no you spared the wrong one dude 115 dollars that's a lot of money all right broken key it's
definitely right here you open the treasure chest inside was broken key b you put broken
key b in your item inventory all right i need another clue how do i get another hint
talk to him again z why does this game not have a run button um it does see this is not
running this is running oh he means a run from combat did uh did undertale have a run from combat
i think it did yeah flee all right let's talk to the shopkeeper like i said there are no
random encounters so that makes sense they took the kind of chrono trigger mario rpg aspect
of encounters where you actually have to touch them so so now let's go all right tell me
where the other thing is talk from opening door uh well it doesn't matter walk with the stars
don't shine uh does he not have another hint for me take your time ain't like it's better spent
he doesn't have another hint can i examine the keys okay it's the top part of a key a smith
could fix all three parts it's the middle part of a key a smith could fix all three parts
all right i do have the cake this song is good uh this is just here
no fucking idea check ass oh wait wait wait wait wait order of rooms in the card castle
um no wait a minute oh shit how the fuck card castle oh there it is it's definitely right
there i have to go to the card castle so look at this only 24 different possible outcomes
everyone's just writing the solution oh man oh what the heck everyone's writing the solution
what the i i i saw it i have already seen it i can't go back i've already seen it
well shit i mean what was it again i saw it already here is i'm gonna put it in there
i am i don't know whatever okay oops i really wish i didn't see that uh that's i'm so not fun
and like somebody wrote it and i saw it and now what was i supposed to do be like no you know
i definitely don't see the wave of the solution i mean what did that person say check ass oh
wow it in between that was 10 messages saying the solution and below that was 10 messages
check his ass what am i gonna pretend like i'm not seeing it all right now we have to go
where the blacksmith the guy that can fix stuff i think he's is he around here
where is that guy i think it's the big sail because he was up right yes all right fix this
fix item that key is something with energy you must let me fix it let's feel my technique
twitch plays delta room that's the only one i looked at this key has terrible energy coming
out of it please understand that i only fixed it so that you will never have to use it
okay all right so do i need to go back to the shopkeeper or is he going to be like
i'm gonna go back to the shopkeeper i'm gonna get like gnomed all right shopkeeper are you
anything to say talk trouble opening door so you got burgers i got so much money
you're carrying too much i'm gonna sell sell armor all right no i got home wait and sell weapons
red scarf sell items i got the glow shard man what do we do with this thing
return the cake i'll return the guy where's where's mr cake man he's like over here right
those are the puzzle power ranges don't return cake eat cake give cake put cake up s
what else should i do return cake eat cake don't eat cake don't return cake eat the
red no i'm keeping the cake i want it who can who can wield the spooky sword i'll be fine
i'm gonna be fine don't worry castle let's go let's open up the door let the guy out
uh compliment and no don't spare yet defend told suzy to compliment the enemy
uh are you serious what good can i say about someone trying to kill us
oh suzy if you're stuck why not try saying something you wish somebody say to you
you are unbanned from free ham sandwich day has said that to me before long live the king
it smells like crystals i can't really do anything here perish lighteners
unbanned from germa's discord nice you guys look like you're gonna kill me
unbanned all right here we go wait i'll save it here where will you go down here
let's go talk to the clown again hey i'm back oh the key the key a marvelous fun is about to
break free won't you let yourself outside sure you put the door key in front of the door
the door key created a door okay there's mr clown
visitors visitors now we can play then after you i can play with everyone else too
so what are we playing exactly oh it's just a simple numbers game
when your hp drops to zero you lose so that's the kind of game you want to play
then i gotta warn you you're dealing with a couple of sharks
oh shark to shark i wouldn't have it any other way now now let the games begin
all right uh jevil uh check hypnosis pure aware i think i'm gonna let's check and i'm gonna
defend i mean i want some points here there is no strategy to beat the enemy good luck
okay chaos chaos catch me if you can
smells like chaos it sure does all right we got here away deep end first spun around
jevil got slightly more tired and people felt at ease jevil's defense dropped
shall we play the ring around oh my lord oh all right well uh can i look at the manual
revive mint okay i'm back my hearts go all out to all you sinners i gotta spend these i gotta do some
healing here act hypnosis so as he spun something around jevil's next attack weakened
jevil became more tired let's make the devil's night oh my goodness the world is spinning
we got another person dead good for items nice armor i didn't i didn't know that i was
gonna fight like the secret boss back here um i want to see his what it's nothing but a useless
bird flip flip let's ride the carousel i can do anything okay uh give me a burger and then
what do you get from magic pacify he's not tired enough heal player
damn it i just gotta not get hit are you having fun join the club fuck i need 50
no he needs to be tired heal player can i bring suzy back slightly more tired everyone's hp got
jumbled up oh shit hearts diamonds i can do anything jevil's laughing incomprehensibly okay
still not tired enough rude buster laughing incomprehensibly just loving more tired and
upcoming move got powered up who keeps spinning the world around there's like a whirlwind
but trying to fucking hit him dark burger for suzy if i give this to rousey will she won't be
revived though right oh shit okay nice all right everyone's alive okay no hit got it get
fucking out of here hypnosis jevil's next attack we can jump became more tired you kids are
really keeping up holy shit this is fucking insane okay feels like a whirlwind we're still
all up do it again jevil's next tech weekend he became more tired i never had such fun
how you doing okay i need to heal dark burger on rousey on suzy not rousey cake will the cake
heal everybody okay spare doesn't work yet no i'm not gonna use yet i still i still but i still
burgers i'm gonna give this to chris no i need this to rousey and i'm gonna use i'm gonna
defend and then i'm going to heal suzy yes i'm ready beauty is enjoying in my heart
the air crackles with freedom fuck i need i need hearts donut chocolate i don't have
anything else i got candy okay let's do defend defend and um let's make sure everybody stays
alive for the next one even devil's knife is smiling here we go i get this one
not it's fucking me up oh boy this is bad bad very bad need the cake holy shit do it more tired
it's so exciting i can't take it okay oh i need no i need i'm gonna defend now i'm gonna do
her away now that's 20 no no no i'm gonna defend i'm gonna heal suzy or i'm gonna
suzy okay cookie for suzy chaos bomb was prepared for you what the fuck does that mean
okay suzy is going to healing berries defend and then defend and then i got i and then that's
i'm good i'm ready let's go let's go let's go this is it boys and girls okay man you're
done you're done it's over became more tired enough you kids tired me up don't lose it here
don't lose it don't lose it don't lose it don't lose it don't lose it it's over it's over it's
over it's over it's over it's over it's over i have to just pacify him he okay hearts donut
i don't even know what these four items i'm gonna just take a chocolate diamond
who needs it the most probably suzy magic this is making me anxious i don't this is making me
anxious he doesn't if i peer away here and then defend and then pacify it's over right
he's not tired look at him he's really tired oh i feel like i'm gonna fuck this up with my
save state okay i'm just gonna heal i'm gonna heal chris i'm gonna defend and i'm gonna heal
suzy no oh but i don't know heal suzy i'm going for it i fucked it up i fucked it up
all right we're okay i'm kidding here's my final chaos oh did i do it did i do it did i do it
okay okay okay okay i don't know i'm like i'm locked up right now i'm fucking locked up he's
pulling out all the stops act hypnotize hypnotize and then pacify no no wait no no no no
hypnotize hypnotize get to win i can pacify him now right nope let's defend let me i'm going
just i got a heart donut i'm gonna give it to i'm gonna give to rousy
and then i'm gonna do i have any other healing i don't have anything else
rude buster i don't know what the fuck that does defend and then magic pacify jevil he's gonna
blow it he would wait who did i just heal i'm gonna heal chris heal i'm gonna defend and then
i'm gonna heal myself rousy no oh my life no my life no i can do it i can do it i can do it i
can do it i can get the fuck out of here did i crash the game what happened what fun i'm exhausted
you kids tired me up now i will sleep for the other 100 years unfortunately you kids cannot
have such a pleasant dream from now a nightmare will awaken in your hearts
in the shadow of the night's hand lighteners can you stop it
either way of mischief yeah i'm like on i think i stroke my lightning right there
that was stressful either way a mischief mischief a chaos chaos lighteners from inside
your little self take this and do your strongest a jevil stale was added to your armor
i got i got it i did it pocket falling coming in with five community subs thank you pocket
falling it's too easy that was that was crazy well there it is i did it let's take a look at
but pocket falling five community subs yeah that wasn't easy so it is who it is a
defense item all right we got iron sickle jevil stale a j-shaped tail that gives you
devil energy oh damn plus three magic that should go on yeah that should go on rousy
oh shit where it is the defense oh give iron shackle to you
you need something you can't wear that can you you can wear this and you can wear that
now everybody's got something on
okay and i only have eleven hundred dollars save it oh my god oh my god kairatobi kairatobi
coming in with 20 20 community subs holy shit oh my god oh wait very generous of you thank
you a ton of subs are coming in here thank you guys fucking awesome thank you
topac you guys are fucking amazing you beat jevil first you deserve it
that was i don't know man that i i that was really close at the very end that was i thought
it was over i got so lucky that that was the last time i'm not sure i could have gone one
more round there really don't think so so now i need to go to the first floor
and continue going beats jevil first try loses to pinwood he's insane i beat pin whatever
i didn't that's you stop with this people are starting to believe that you know look let me
tell you something i've gone to like reddit threads before i talked have i talked about
this i probably have but i need to make it i'd reiterate it again people will go on like somebody
they'll be like a reddit post or oh look there's a clip of something that jerma said or did oh
okay whatever and like then halfway down with like 25 uploads is oh it's like kind of
unfortunate because this guy like died to fucking pinwheel and like people that don't even know
this stream will reply and be like are you fucking serious this guy sucks like holy shit
you know there's no way and then you keep up the act no dude it was embarrassing he got
really mad and like that's why i don't watch him and it's just like what the fuck i can't even
like defend myself how am i supposed to like defend that but you did die i did not die to
pinwheel i will we will sit here and watch that unedited entire body uh this is ruden's
room yes that's a door jewels coins almost everyday riches acquired from a legitimate
looks like a family photograph
we sold all of our beds to replace him with treasure my back hurts but life has never been
better hey you're that chump that beat me up earlier there's no way i'll forgive you so
scram we're so sorry we made a mistake earlier we promise we won't do it again
you're apologizing i guess i'll forgive you then your violence against a single
was forgiven all right i can talk to the shopkeeper we'll go uh he did say to come back
what am i doing i'm already on this floor you're there um so here's i have a question
because this is not the whole game right this is kind of like part one or something
i'm not is this is am i like participating in the beta or do i get to keep my fucking
jevil item for like when the next part comes out or am i gonna get like a thank you for
participating in like the beta your characters are wiped okay okay good good i'm just making
sure because i don't know if i can do that again nobody knows oh god uh where am i going
over here let's see the lore talk about we won all right we won you defeated him you really
defeated him i see perhaps you three may truly be heroes after all jevil was just a taste
of what you'll face from now on one day soon you too will begin to realize the futility of
your actions ha ha ha at that time feel free to come back here i'll make you tea
and we can toast to the end of the world he was a funny little man once the court jester
i the court magician a friend could i consider him a friend perhaps perhaps not but he was
the only one who matched me in the games we used to play one day he met a strange
someone and since then he began to change started saying bizarre things that didn't
completely make sense but didn't completely not make sense either soon he began to see
the world as a game and everyone as its participants as the court major and his
only companion i was forced to lock him away or rather lock us all away in his own words
since that time the strange words he said have stuck inside my cotton and my view of
this world has become darker yet darker reflecting on these old memories i think perhaps
i miss playing games with him and i wonder if i hadn't been asked to lock him up would i
have found a little more purpose in my life greetings from japan hope everyone's doing
well hey how are you greetings i need to buy some stuff because i ran out why did i buy a
candle toby admitted that this demo is all he had but he has storyboards ready
well i mean it's free all right the game's free so
he just wrote the story uh well whatever however long it takes i know i've got my
court jester item just remind me not to delete this
all right i need to go back to the castle
okay check ass i gotta stop reading those all right uh let's go up into the game boy room
that's blocked off what's this so the worms have decided to crawl out and play who's there
yeah it's jevil i am ruse card the greatest adversary
thou may have clawed his past all of our otherest penundrums but vows were created
by utter weaklings now prepare thou self for the strongest puzzle of thou's life
toil worms if i stand as she i don't understand if i stand as she pushes
isn't that where that worked joke joke joke god damn it
god damn it and that's it god damn it is this door open though it is hold on let's see what's
down here you opened the treasure chest inside was club sandwich you put club sandwich in your
items look at too many burgers club sandwich a sandwich that can be split into three he has
30 hp to the team okay castle bathroom royal flush currently occupied that's cute throw the
manual away from war room but what if i need to know how to press a uh let's go left first
head hathie blocked away quietly times three all right we got uh flirt order suzy to flirt
with the enemy and hell no oh suzy it's okay if you don't know how what shut up that's not the
problem sure all right look wise guy i'll show you watch this so uh come here often
and hathie felt awkward and left hey get back here and let me flirt with you
it smells like a lonely kiss what the hell does that mean let's do it again
he won't it's easy to flirt with the enemy come on let's see razi do it
i suppose it can't be helped i think your beauty is just transcending your hair is like a
waterfall of like you have hair or i haven't felt awkward enough oh dear oh wait not so
easy oh whoa i didn't know you moved okay that's annoying head hathie's mind is an enigma
all right we're gonna do a double flirt oh my god chris i can't do it yourself
you said some sweet lines the enemies were deeply enamored oh that's all it took
stared him now that you beat jevil you are entitled to never get hurt from now on oh that's
not gonna happen i'm gonna get hit by the easiest thing in the game just don't get it
stuck its tongue out at me what if i do them all okay yep okay that's a pretty good
nickelodeon sound effect oh come on oh all right fine i'll play along did i get them all
because all the tongues are out i mean there you are yeah those guys really think it was all i
had wronged it's time for you to feel my real power behold my ultimate puzzle
have at you face the true strongest puzzle worms this time the difficulty art
magnitudes grander see thou in 100 years ah ha ha ha gullible worms that wasn't real
my ultimate puzzle i have a way better one right here can we see it no inside was a
revive mint that you were carrying too many items yeah throw it away you drop the
manual on the floor with a resounding thud hey chris what are you doing oh no is that the
manual well i wasn't supposed to do that looks like you accidentally dropped it here you go
chris you don't want to lose that you got the manual again so am i what is in the manual
handmade book full of various tips and tricks you tried to read the manual but it was so
dense it made your head spin he tossed the manual hard its pages scattered the wind
uh that's okay chris i can always i'll just make a better one next time just smash it into the
ground i don't want i i don't need that i need the revive mint okay we got two we got a shop
this is also buried in the ground here oh this is the this is lancer's room you found 20
by rupees in the hole unfortunately that's not a useful currency here
it's a hole made of recreation it's a hole made recreationally it's a hole presumably dug for fun
it's some kind of digging implement and it's a music player listen to the contents of the
music player yeah it's full of cartoon splat noises okay a bicycle is lovingly tucked into
bed okay go to the shop welcome to my shop you ungrateful worms uh what is thine interest
i am the duke of puzzles rules card my hobbies include calligraphy law keeping bug keeping
okay i already like them bug keeping cages and long walks in the dungeon
artest thou one of my admirers worm why are you selling to us so i might amasseth funds worms
an army of funds so that i may crushes thou like fermented grapes into a most delicious
and adult beverage vengeance oh how i amuse myself our lord king art a cruel and terrifying
monarch however he is also brilliant for he decided this death to appoint me as duke of
puzzles after pretty mucheth everyone else was furthest or placed inside a cage truly a benevolent
ruler and his son on the other hand is more troublesome than a fistful of fleas he always
asks me the worst queries and calleth me his lesser dad our relation is none you little water
beetle i placate you for your father's sake i do not wisheth to hear your mp3s i would
rather listen to the sweet song of death how is he anyhow all right well what do we got
uh that's brave axe rules rule item fragrant sauce who's even doesn't even have this on
i don't think i need anything i have a lot of healing it's worse than the burger anyways
no i'm good i'm good i think i'm ready to go what item what does this do though
i don't know what this shard does the revivement is 200 bucks brave axe i wonder if i should
just get him a new weapon but he's i'm not gonna i'm trying to do the uh act stuff
healing up yeah see you in the dungeon let me take a look here because you have the
the jevil item it's an oh it's a weapon i thought it was okay well nobody else can even
use this shit so this thing a rugged scarf that cuts enemies like a dagger a basic
scarf made of lightning okay i'm gonna sell both of these he is decked out he's got the
best stuff on all right so i'm gonna sell the red scarf and the rag you also need some more armor
and get this piece of wood i don't want a wooden blade take it off get the axe
and another amber card well i have to take this off i'm gonna sell the stuff i just took
off what oh right okay that wasn't for you that was not for you okay well that's fine
buffiness up sell the stuff and then let's go sell weapons uh i want to sell the axe the
rag the scarf and i am ready to go it's not really as if you need the weapons but if the
need ever arises i would like to have it you know here's the elevator enough worms here comes my
hardest puzzle yet you've cheated through nine puzzles but in combat thou shall be scattered
above from caves prepare for battle with whatever this is uh it's the enemy from earlier
this crown looks different it looks the same yes with my control crown i may control any
disc-shaped life form oh no it looks like it's in pain it looks the same yes the control
crown is painful but i'm certain this creature will feel it relief but it sees how much more
pain thou will be in are we gonna make him bob his head down uh suzy's idea suzy you
want to act uh what's your idea well how do i say this i kind of need you for this one
that's fine i'll help do you want to apologize to it for earlier no i just need you to stay still
first we got to get that crown off its head help me throw rousy at it press c to determine
the angle wait back it up how do i hit back no i didn't i thought i was gonna get
i thought i was gonna get a whatever i'm gonna go higher bro i'm gonna go up got it
crown greatly loosened do it again knock it off the crown greatly loosened maybe one or two more
times i assume just like that one two three no yeah got it nice super bario sound effects
only two dollars though unfortunately why brilliant just brilliant i knew you could
just do it thou great heroes thou seeth that was merely a friendly test of thine abilities
but thou hast won and now nothing blocks thy path i personally could not be less of an obstruction
good luck be with you heroes i hate this guy this guy's side this guy sucks
but i think because of that i think i like him i think i like him because of that it's weird
like that that makes him sort of like the best character in delta runes so far i think because
i don't like them riches they shine with avarice riches they shine with avarice wall banners they
seem to be seem to have been through some kind of struggle okay there was a struggle
anything else we got thrown here make sure i save that one my god make sure i save my items
it's a throne it seems to have been damaged in a struggle well okay there was a fight
oh there's lancer hey there's lancer that's what i said father lancer my son have you
dispatched the likeners as i commanded no but i did even better it turns out we don't actually
have to fight them they said they could just talk to you and they're alive yes and i think
you'll like them a lot there's suzy she's very purple and strong and where are they now
oh all right the thing in the back distracted me because that's like a huge monster mouth
um are you talking to my son chad jr he's gonna take the k-pop and he's gonna do the same
stance hey it's nice to meet you lancer lancer my son yes father chad chad c h d a d
do you remember what i told you don't get too attached you have failed they have poisoned you
with their sentiment their niceness free yourself lancer they care not for you their only goal is
to destroy our glorious fountain they are scum no they aren't what did you just say let him go
uh you want me to let him go very poor choice of words i'll drop him off the edge and let him
splatter unless you all kneel and learn your place what will it be lighteners don't listen
to him suzy heal heal heal i didn't do that i didn't press the button now watch lancer
see what happens when you befriend lighteners what no you traitor come back here
all right enough already who the hell do you think you are oh my people i am a hero to you
i'm the bad guy king block the way it really is a chat all right king talk talk talk talk
let's talk and let's defend suzy tried to reason with the king all right listen up
lancer is my friend uh so if we can get by without hurting you then um
by perish so be it show my son the monster you really are all right you want to see what i can
do huh suzy's will is changing talk became red buster how dare you come here lighteners
king's mouths babble indecipherably red buster i do the talk again then
rousey tried to reason with the king you might not realize it but this is a world where you
don't have to fight i know if we try we can all find another way such simple minded prostitutes
shame you will not live to realize your naivety now perish with the pathetic lighteners you
worship sorry my friends and i aren't going anywhere rousey's will is changing talk became
dual healed you that left us in the shadows stripped of meaning whoa
what are you doing to me here all right that's that's the sound it makes when you win
at like the ball throwing machine of the arcade that's just like spitting out
14 tickets it's not even worth it it's 100 tickets to get a fucking tootsie roll so
um i guess i could just talk again the battlefield is rumbling magic rude fight no
i don't need to defend here magic heal prayer pacify it's gonna let it play out you tried
to reason with the king silence lightbringer your very existence goes against our own by
the knight's will i shall shatter your heart and do a million pieces your will is changing
talk became courage you dare return to torment us once again oh okay interesting interesting
the battlefield is rumbling all right we got red buster dual heal courage it's a damage
courage what's your courage rude buster is a is a bunch of damn not gonna
magic prayer pacify heal prayer i guess i can just heal myself you encourage the party the
party defense raised for this turn rousy cast heal prayer be gone we have found fresh purpose
just gonna stay inside the cube all right uh check courage dual heal heals everybody
courage again it's not really tired you encourage the party party defense raises for
this turn for the knight has appeared moving faster now oops check courage red buster should
i just do it how many tickets was that like 12 not yet i don't think i need to
party defense raised the knight that pulls the fountains from the earth
now he's getting pissed okay well the king's mouth gave a berserk smile
why did i have to lean over and read what why did i have to read that holy fountains
whose shadows are creating a new world what the fuck i'm breaking my concentration hey let's dual
heal on it doesn't matter let's do it your soul shined its power on rousy rousy cast dual
heal we're all good do you see now our new purpose i mean i don't you have to tell it to me
oh the battlefield is rumbling check abandoned by the lightners his heart became cracked with
hatred he cannot be reasoned with but don't give up suit this world should be blanketed
in darkness and darkness shall rule it that was gonna make like a luigi doesn't do anything
it wins isn't there like five like different videos of that and they're like a courage
dual heal there's more like 500 well you know what i mean all right dual heal
then you may see what it is like to live in despair
hit here hey courage dual heal again why not let's just defend now enough talk all before
the chain of justice oh i see what you're doing here oh i see what you're doing here it's
kind of freaking me up we're good courage defend party's defense raised with this turn
you're quite strong aren't you i mean if you say so i like to think i'm pretty strong
the king's mouth give a berserk smile check dual heal defend oh auto not right now if
i keep fighting you like this then autos like let me out the king's mouth hold on
see what about give me two one second go downstairs so uh we're gonna do act of courage
then i feel like we're getting to the end here defense has been raised it seems that
what is next it seems what it seems what what does it seem tell me my knight i shall not fail
you enough is enough i see i say that i cannot defeat you i have grown exhausted from our
long battle lighteners i perhaps i have been too cruel the truth is i was not always this way
there once was a time where darkners and lighteners lived in harmony the time where
darkners could fulfill their purpose and peace it would be a lie it would be a lie uh-oh
to say that i too do not yearn for those days perhaps perhaps you young ones are right
please let us put away our weapons there must be a peaceful solution to all this
come now sissy i'm glad you're starting to realize mr king none of us really want to
fight if you can just tell us about your worries i'm sure we can all be friends mr king
yes yes friends that sounds lovely
my apologies i i'm not i'm not used to fighting like that my body is getting weak
oh don't say another word hey you should be all healed up how do you feel let's see
dick
never better you did i say you could get up chris oh spare me the heroics you
you're the leader aren't you so what's your plan to laugh as you cast us all back into
obscurity you can't even say young one let me tell you a secret quiet people piss me off
he's doing a vain impression stop it hey get away from my friend
or what you'll kill me nah so what you plan then to talk me to death you stupid stupid
lightener you honestly think you have any way to convince me not to kill you nah but they
lantern everyone what is the meaning of this sorry dad you're being overthrown
when i told everyone you were fighting the lighteners everyone remembered how kind they were
this is not a let me change it they decided they'd rather have a king that accepts them
me now i'm the dad you really get some lighteners on your enemies fools i'll kill you i'll
kill all of you yeah that yikes that's what that's gonna be oh i think someone needs a time out
go to your room dad no you all right dude chris susie oh you're all right it'll take more
than that to take us down hey uh i'm sorry because i healed the king we almost uh susie you
were right i was foolish to think we could act so soft to everyone this is in a world
where kindness always wins is it did i do the whole did i do it wrong is this one of those
scenarios where like now i did it wrong because i did the other way i did it wrong this time
it's complicated yeah sometimes there's people you just got to fight but if you never let
your guard down then you might just hurt someone you care about oh susie you're beginning
to sound like a real hero yeah don't get used to it that i suppose you chris should
return home now yeah i guess that's uh that's it well uh daya chris you wanna you wanna go
say goodbye to everyone don't you well if you're gonna make me i guess we can go back
hey susie you came back uh well uh we just want to say bye you know oh actually everyone
here wanted to say goodbye too please let me know when you leave all right yeah okay
are we really gonna do the thing where you go to a family get together
and you part of you just sit in there going uh i kind of like go around in a giant circle
and like say bye to everybody and say hi to everybody and i don't want to miss somebody
because then i feel like they would be slighted and sometimes i i forget that i may have already
said bye and shaken the hands of like some uncle and i go and i do it again and in their mind i
say like what the fuck is he doing you said bye to me like four minutes ago uh way to go kids
now we can go back to making the puzzles we love and thanks to your donation i could buy a
new hat and some shaving cream isn't that nice best you're the best honestly we owe you
you're absolutely amazing great work i'm gonna have to get out thank you i can go back to being a
coat hanger now by the way i asked shaum to come here but there wasn't any interest
no wi-fi kirby even a little ball can say something like thank you thanks darn horsey
you've done and done us a big help now all of us pieces can live in pieces my nostrils
can't thank you enough you did it you ousted that rotten tyrant i'll happily accept a bounty of
credit for my contributions unless the king reappears in which case why did nothing and
the best for last wonderful work my amigos thou has toppled the tyrant freedest of our creeds
truly if history shall not forget the tale of rules card and the three heroes
uh did you hear that laugh i just did what was that that was
everybody's here look i knew you could do it that was your enemy i was cheering for you
that's how much i disliked my job the future looks sweet like a pile of bees puke which
is honey i think the kingdom with so much hope hope you didn't screw it up that means thank
you come to our next birthday too we'll have one soon if that's possible happy looked at
you proudly kiss what's going on i slept through everything wait what about these people
oh i can give him his cake i can give him the cake mom i mean but what a celebration
this calls for a cake and this time i'll make it out of metal so animals can't eat it
oh i ate the cake that's right us animals decided it's okay if the kings stay in the
cages as well now they'll have to put on animal ears and noses why do we not let them
out what oh what about us aren't we going to be restored as kings oh my treasure is unharmed carry
on them i'll be honest at first we weren't sure who make our new king i mean lancer has always
been a bit of a pain but after seeing how nice he treats you guys i think he'll be fine
suzy blue person whose name i neglected to learn all along i thought you were going home
we were but chris wanted to say bye you know oh really that's funny i thought you wanted
to say bye because we're friends i mean i didn't not want to so you're the king now huh yes and
i'm changing some big rules first lighteners are now legal second prison is now only for dads
sounds like some pretty good changing hey dad was protecting the fountain right
is it gonna be okay if we mess with it i have no idea but it's you guys so i trust you
if something bad happens we'll fix it up yeah i guess we'll just see i guess
well see you later come back soon there's always room in town for a couple of clowns
and you because you rescued it it grew to respect you well actually maybe it shrunk to
respect you that's pretty good that was pretty good all right bye everybody that was fun that
was a blast that was really suzy chris are you going to leave i i just wanted to say i
i really enjoyed meeting you two and stop mumbling into your hat for a second
i can barely hear you dude oh i'm sorry uh chris suzy i hope i can see you again soon
is that um is that what is that is this supposed to be a big reveal
that's why did we go back in time next time i'll make you lots of yummy cakes all right
yeah sure dude let's go yeah it wouldn't is that that's we went back in time that's
as real so now what happens he's reading chat i mean i'm trying to keep up to date but uh
is this the fountain don't know how but it feels like we stumbled into
something really important didn't we well there's no time to think about that now
right now it's time to go home right chris as you stood in front of the fountain
you felt something strange it was as if your very soul was glowing
like did i die was it giving my soul to the fountain what happened i can't see anything
hey watch it uh-huh the unused classroom how did we get here it was all just they were just
playing chess and they would did they just they went into the staff room and they did all the
drugs that were in the teacher's staff closet hey chris what just happened that wasn't a dream
or anything was it anyway as i was saying uh let's just tell alphys we couldn't find any chalk
what is this it's a worn down stuffed animal we just did like the teachers crack in the
back and we just had a playing card spill out of a deck in the closet man the sun's already
setting everyone else must have gone home by now i guess alphys will know better than to
ask us next time huh what's with all the bird and animal noises well guess we should go see you
later i guess um i'm saying i had a lot of fun doing a bunch of drugs with you
maybe we should do that again tomorrow let's go back there tomorrow
are
okay sure the door is locked door is locked are you ready for the saty hawkman's dance at this dance
all the chaperones were giant hawk heads and screech at any students that make contact
the lock is locked nobody in the classroom what about on the computer the computer is
turned off everything felt peaceful for a moment looks like motivational quotes from
various literature try your best astral wolf even in your darkest hour that one seems to be
from a video game you ran the water fountain it's lukewarm i didn't go in this classroom
it's a computer it's desktop wallpaper is you and your brother dressed up for halloween eight
years ago well okay you and your brother it's a cool uh minecraft house some kind of
primitive sculpture who knows what it represents the throne of the gods ring ring
chris whatever have you been doing i sat in the car waiting for you after school for half an
hour i called and called but you never picked up you had your poor mother worried sick chris
i'm afraid i'm going to have to punish you huh a friend you were spending time with a friend
chris i will make an exception this time you can continue your adventures a little longer
but when you return home you're going to have to go to bed early see you soon honey click i just
like to just leave school the game the game's not over i have to like walk around town i have
to walk around like springfield and the simpsons there's the library oh look at all my friends
chris what's up caddy's working so i'm starting on our project i've already copied a bunch of
pictures it's the same picture of a soccer ball 73 times gotta go to colleague so ted was stubby
hard she's reading a comic full of hot demon guides so what the what i love reading books
especially the books upstairs you should really read them can we get out of the way chris you
survived suzy i was getting worried now you can finally pay off your family debt how to
draw dragons is 200 000 2583 days overdue however chris i'm a benevolent volunteer assistant
if you turn it in this week i'll reduce your fine to a mere 64 dollars and 23 cents consider
it chris you look through the window to the computer lab there seems to be a dog inside
working at a computer it seems like it's making a game it seems like you shouldn't
interrupt it seems like when the game is finished you can go in you just have to
trust the dog there's an anime review read it no no no no yes teens corner of monthly
tune review mew mew kissy cutie too this reviewer had mew mew too as her first exposure
to the series and let her tell you it makes mew mew one look like a dumpster with sparkly
cat ears with a darker storyline and more mature themes the second one treats the viewer
like a real adult instead of like an animal that will die if it goes 10 seconds without
seeing a beach ball not to mention mew mew's character in the first one is more stale than the
ramen i eat at home by myself with the lights off teens and olders teens and
olders should check out this dark masterpiece signed the anonymous yellow lizard
he says you're in the first game hey punk get out of the road you're blocking traffic
oh wait it's just asgore's kid sorry i'm a little uh worked up lately his job is so boring
nothing ever happens in this town and i just wish something would shake things up
oh you got something to report dark world what is a dark world inside the school
uh sure kid there's no law against dark worlds anyway that's a job for the school board
alphys alphys who's alphys no idea who you're talking about why did they do something illegal
gotcha if i see alphys i'll tackle it foo foo foo foo foo foo foo they're as good as dead
help you uh you want to help me sure punk get someone to rob the bank so i can suplex
them wait do we even have a bank hey get someone to build a bank what's going on over
here how am i supposed to get past this blue lady i'm stuck i guess i should just run away
police chief undyne is supposed to be directing traffic what all she's doing is standing in the
middle of the street yelling get out of my way she's the best huh i feel really directed
let's go in the hospital holy shit it's one of those sliding bead toys that naturally spawns
inside of doctor's offices the beads march grimly along their set path it's an obligatory
hospital piano shrunk to fit in the corner as a result it's missing most of the good keys
plank whom you usually play the piano a bit more beautifully is everything okay you do seem
a little sick oh dad i just i can't just say that to her oh my god i die i'd literally
die oh well sweetheart first time i laid eyes on your mother i walked right up and told her
she was a hot piece of work really yeah she slapped me so hard i blacked out
dad that doesn't help at all anyhow i was dragging in blazers three beat it yet no i'm
still at the ice palace i've been kind of kind of waiting to finish it with you dad
oh well maybe uh you shouldn't wait dad you should bring it here i'm bored as hell
har har har fine you win i'll bring it next time oh it's getting late guess i better go i've got
homework oh that's the group project voice bird guy again what's his name nerdly it's uh
birdly he's not that bad dad i'll kick his ass dad you're not even supposed to get up
bring him by the window i'll throw something at him goodbye dad bye honey oh hi chris
oh so you're just here to use the sink huh come on chris be a little friendlier i'm just here to
use the sink well jingle my gosh darn bells looks like christmas came early all right chris
just give me the straight shot why are you here did your mom make you come here really you've
grown up a lot chris i'm proud of you it wasn't too long ago you were just the creepy kid next
door now you're the creepy kid right in front of me okay all right i seriously you want to
chat or something certified dad uh so why am i in here well they found some crap so it's just some
tests it's no big deal nothing a holiday can't handle i'll be out of here in a jiffy and then
i can go back to uh i don't know yelling at you for getting tangled in our light display
hey chris you want to chat or something don't worry there's no way you can bore me right now
uh okay chris even if we're grown apart we still love your family after all me and
asgore were college pals right oh hey now that asriel's off to college
you think he's doing any crazy parties like me and your dad i'm just pulling you like your dad
was no party animal your mother on the other hand she'd always fuss about going but once
the party started yikes man once she hit me clear across the room with a key lime pie
i got smashed into the snack table and toppled everything tasty pie though couldn't complain
she's a sweetheart isn't she chris smart kind sweet couldn't ask for a better daughter
i wish she wasn't so defenseless scary movies bugs santa claus everything scared her
and when it happened she freezes like a deer in headlights remember she used to even be
afraid of humans under the bed chris it was not nice of you to hide under there by the
way anyway that's what's tough about being in here chris not what's going on with me
just that in the meantime i can't be there to protect her keep an eye out for her okay
i will you forget my name or something patient name rudolph rudy holiday
amazing what's being done with our taxpayer office there's a bunch of roses in a glass
container hey i'm happy your dad brought me flowers but roses what is this beauty and the
beast that ain't gonna work man we're both beasts what's over here it's a regular sink
this castle's white wizards relegated me to this healing chamber but my blood is boiling for
battle what you looked inside the cupboard a very small obligatory piano is hiding inside
at zero pain he's happy at 10 pain he's happy and sweating well okay that was the
hospital you can go into the police station nothing else police tape is blocking the way the
tape simply reads yeah yeah you knock on the door to the police station someone's coming up to
the window they just closed the blinds seems like the police aren't really feeling it right
now qc's diner ice's pizza what is going on here why what is happening oh god someone's
actually here ice ease pizza your number one spot for a piping hot piece of pizza
hey wait a second i recognize you little buddy it's me want to chat for a minute before i
lose my mind you know when as he's coming home you can't tell him this but i really
missed the guy it'd be sweet to cruise around town like old times picking up for example
chicks which has a matter of course may not have ever actually happened but one time undyne made
eye contact with me she was writing me a speeding ticket hey little buddy what's up job
make no mistake little buddy icy's pizza is hell i can't slack off for seconds without
hearing be a team player there's no eye in pizza yes there is you just took it out
but it's okay little buddy i've been saving up to go to college where as he is then i'll
get a theater degree become a famous actor and let the fan girls roll in little buddy
ah yes little buddy good idea meet the rogue's gallery blue ears soft serve obsessed no concept
of personal space keeps accidentally pouring slushies on me and giggling the warrior
thankfully absent due to pizza related injuries constantly terrorizing customers
with war chants purple guy man that guy you gotta actually does that guy even work here
uh my co-workers where would i be without a happy place little buddy a much happier
place would you be interested in trying some of our many 24 pizza flavors we've got normal
cheese ice gravy double ice peeperonis and more stop on that icy's pizza ice me up ice
me up boss what does it say the entrance is locked no one's inside seems like all of
the employees are outside in costume now the diner that's the best character in the whole
game i mean that that's the best character in the entire game why wasn't that a party member
i'm dead serious why the fuck is this guy not a party member this should have been
the other character i want to hear this guy's entire life story looking at my rugged body
you must wonder what kind of secrets i hold my secret is i put all my leftover pancakes
in this giant hat i mean that's hysterical hysterical i and one at some point in the
during the movie he could take the hat off and eat it we never say that and there's
be pancakes under there absolutely fucking remarkable view i sure love pancake ice
wolf does not like ice and drink ice wolf likes ice to be drank to be drink what so
for you two girls that'll be the crepes a cinnamon latte two bunny parfaits and a
piece of firewood i like the vibe of the waitress here maybe i should sign up too
nah serving drinks wouldn't really suit a fire elemental if i got nervous i just melt all the
ice i wish i had more to say hey there i haven't seen you in a while i remember back
on sundays after service you and your family would come in and order the special of course
things happened and then y'all stopped coming together but every sunday you and your brother
come in you'd order you a hot chocolate and you two'd sit down at that table in the corner
drawing shapes in the window with your breath you must really miss him huh how about this
chris got the hot chocolate on the house huh uh we'll take the special and do you have any
edible glitter the youngest one won't eat anything if it doesn't look like treasure
you're alive nice i'm working all right goodbye i can't go over there yes hey look who's walking
around all right all right good hey hey who the hell are you good to see you again
oh what's up you're my friend right
hey we just moved here so i hardly know anyone well yeah got anyone i should know better me
hold your tiger oh you can't just jump straight into friendship it takes time all right that's
enough time take this call it whenever you feel like it you got santa's phone number
i'm okay hey what's up uh what's in the store behind me yeah that's the grocery store
unfortunately it's closed what a pain i really wanted to buy some milk uh someone had a
complainer the guy that runs it hey bud uh you busy tomorrow i need some help with uh something
fred it'd be great if you could come over fred uh and bring dino too i live just next door you
know yes wow you were delivered in there for a while gee what's wrong don't want to hang out
with a stranger well guess i shouldn't complain what are we going to be doing oh i'm not
going to be there that'd be weird it's just going to be you and my little brother oh he needs
friends thanks for hanging out with him see you what's up uh friends we just moved here so i
hardly know why uh got anyone i should be friends with uh my mom your mother huh too
late i already befriended your mom last night she's great came to the store to buy chocolate
kisses she said she's got a locker door to stop you from eating them you sound like a fun kid
hey fred who else you should be friends with uh my teacher elfies yeah i know about her came
into the store with a suitcase and sunglasses thought she was part of uh the mob she opened
the cases stuffed it full of instant noodles paid his small bills then slunk out of the
place pajamas trailing on the floor anyway our relationship is uh purely business
so uh i guess i'll let her do her thing i'm such a big fan behind me yeah that's the
score she's okay all right so i'm gonna i can't wait to hang out with you tomorrow we're gonna
be best friends okay bye hello you've reached the hotline for idiot babies please press one
for idiots two for babies three for idiot babies and four for none why did you call the hotline
for idiot babies if you aren't an idiot baby not sans's number the phone kept ringing infinitely
what no no response but the distant trussle of bones can be heard in the distance oh you got
something better to do okay i'll be standing here doing nothing knock knock oh are you the
human that lives at the top of town wow my mommy told me about you does it hurt to be
blood knock knock knock huh that sounds like the knock of a beginner come back when you've
gotten better at knocking this bird there's a bird whoo you're lucky chris you got to miss
class with alphys it's not fair if i skipped class my dad had never let me hear the end of
it that's actually not even remotely funny i mean it was a little yo chris you survived
suzy i mean i never saw her beat anyone up but uh i'd be careful like one time me snowy
and jonkington were playing handball and she just kept creepily watching us from the corner
then when the ball rolled over to her she just froze solid and kicked the ball as hard
as she could right into the officer undyne's car then undyne came out smiling cracked her
knuckles and totally wiped us at handball anyway suzy sucks chris
holy snowy what did i tell you about knocking the door so hard don't do it it's really
gonna hurt your face we don't have arms you know what are you doing in the trash
oh chris chris you're you're okay i was really worried when you didn't come back
where did you go did you skip class well don't worry about it i'm the cool teacher you know
you're not in trouble well let me know if you need anything it's a dirty trash can
it's a dirty trash can it's a trash can full of well-kept flowers it's a saucer of milk
oh chris uh did you want to talk about something chalk chris even though you never got the chalk
you deserve an award for trying so hard to find it so in return i can let you borrow um
my homemade dvd collection of the simpsons you know the sitcom of the middle-class monster
family it's got every episode in all 28 seasons it's the funniest most quotable show ever
but make sure you don't watch past the second season since they just rebut why
they started diving their own but here and fighting giant uh digga demons the main uh lost
the focus of family there early when their vehicles were shaped like animals and they were
friends with the animal vehicles and then let's not get into symptoms gap enforcement
symptoms discovered on the other side of the board and they dig gravitational field just okay
you don't want to watch it that's okay uh chris hey thanks enjoy your life back here
i didn't i just got spoiled for the whole season oh look it's the cats
there's so much here wait wait wait wait it's your dad's truck the floor of the front seat is
littered with old papers and country cds i'm afraid no one's home right now darling now why
don't you prance on home prissy like long time no see what's up did you want to talk
about something neighbor that chick next door drives me nuts i keep seeing her everywhere i go
she's a total copycat like why though doesn't she realize she'll never be me it really is
the girl from the muppets honestly her whole family is like so trashy that's the um from
doc dr t the electric mayhem that's not i'm not doing trump what oh honestly her whole
family is like so trashy once her sister served me a coffee and i swear it was half
cat it really is um that is what i'm doing but that's i'm trying to do the voice that they
like get a haircut girl for like your whole body it's a bootleg zoo lander hey neighbor
uh when's your brother doug gonna come by uh and uh my girls love to see him he's a sweet
little man very little but he's sweet he's just got one problem just a little small problem
not a big problem he doesn't like my website doesn't like my wife's cooking not really at all
that's wrong you don't like frozen cat food the whole neighborhood is trump tarantino
uh that really was tarantino let me tell you all right let's get that out no more dumb voices
no more voices i'm jerry bro i do voices he's out there getting a big brain in the big school
hope when he comes big shot he remembers this little guy's down street eating oranges and getting
our stomachs pumped what the fuck a little chrissy like what's up give aunt caddy a hug
i'm not even actually your aunt oh my god can i talk to you about something
actually like anything though your choice uh asriel oh my god as we were like what a
cutie pie do you really remember when it wouldn't remember when me and him went to the dance
that was like the best night ever even though i spilled the entire punch bowl all over him
and danced inappropriately in front of your mom and got arrested in the parking lot for making
a scene that was so much fun tell him i said hi oh chris like if you want to come in our
cat flap is like always open well should i know nobody harsh but fair well then i'm not
done exploring oh hi chris did you need help with your homework again i know you were having
trouble last time so uh i actually got a few things ready for you in case uh wait sorry i
can't right now i forgot my house key again and sorry chris i'll help you later if that's okay
see you at school chris uh chris did you uh want to talk about something
suzy that's right you were with suzy when you didn't come back to class i was worried
but everything turned out okay i think uh chris can i ask you something if that's okay
suzy i'm kind of curious what she's like you know i mean who doesn't wonder about her she
never talks to anyone so chris could you tell me about her if that's okay she what she smashed
you against the lockers gosh chris i'm really sorry that's just awful i thought i thought
she she was good just maybe it would take someone special to find her good side
but she really is terrible isn't she chris i'm so sorry you have to go through with this
in fact i wonder if do you think i wonder if alphys would let us switch partners i mean
you know so you wouldn't have to be the one who um gets to be slammed into lockers
and stuff anymore wait i don't think i phrased that correctly have i done everything
dad oh it's someone there just a moment i have almost finished watering these flowers
here we are oh howdy how can i oh i'm sorry i forgot if you don't like hugs like that
well now make yourself at home chris you can help yourself to anything you like
i don't understand is this supposed to be like before like this this is like the before
flowey or chad whatever his name was what's the what's the character from first game chas chad
say chris i was thinking perhaps when asriel comes home we can all go to the diner just like
old times my treat doesn't that sound yummy uh-oh dad dad get rid of this one dad smash this
one smash this one it's a golden flower protected in a container it's a yellow flower protected in
a container it's an orange flower protected in a container it's a green flower protected in a
container it's a purple flower protected in a container it's a blue flower protected in a
container it's a cyan flower protected in a container it's a note it says no rent received
again stop giving away flowers start selling them we have one month see various bags of soil and
it's a dirty watering can there is some dirty fur stuck in the drain it's a rusty fridge
with some photos on it oh if you're hungry help yourself to anything you want to do or open
the fridge all that's inside is a jar with a single pickle in it you decide to pass
it's a small tv on top or some superhero comics it's a door it's locked this is sad well bye dad
oh chris before you go come here you have an interview for your mother take this our secret
you got the bouquet of flowers every day chris bye it's your mom's van
easy easy easy i was gonna go down look i found squidward chris what a pleasant surprise to see
you here and on a school day there must be a reason that you came here at such a time
i father alvin implore you if you have anything weighing on your mind please speak
fruit juice chris if you want some of our sick fruit juice you should come to our service
our choir sounds a bit thinner since your brother went away chris it would be wonderful
if you would sing with us or even participated to any extent instead of just trying to drink the
fruit juice gerson renowned historian author and teacher crystal a snowy gemstone for a
proud mother uh mutler a big bone for the leader of the pack she ra a karaoke microphone
for a brave singer shira gerson boom memorial bench throughout my career some of my best ideas
came from dreams take a rest here if anyone asks your writing that's really nice that's really
nice town hall hey short stuff why would you possibly need to talk to the mayor
your allowance too low ate too much candies lost your frisbee in the wash hey short stuff that's
what the cops are for fuck you dick you dick can we get the bear from the muppets
oh the bear charisma is about to zero no it's negative but she works hard and has a good track
record so you know she runs on a pulse that's politics really you know i'm sorry i'm sorry
the bear is busy right now we need to see her please try causing some terrible crisis
no that's the bear that's that's the big bear from the muppets going down not fuzzy
bear the big guy that the big bear that wears the suit muppets from space the hell is this
it's locked let's go up i'm gonna bang a right let's see what's over here here we go nothing
better than hanging at the lake with my best bro watching the waves go by true what's this
here for this obviously is here for something well it's you i remember you hey there notice
you were uh here it's me you know me right of course you do i'm real popular i just don't
have any friends but it's okay you're here because you're you're here will you be my friend
of course oh oh i'm so happy you're here i'm just so happy i don't know what to do i don't
remember being this happy before what's your name friend hippopotamus hip hip hip hop hippopotamus
that's you big name but it's worth it oh excuse me i forgot to introduce myself actually
since no one talks to me i forgot my own name
hippopotamus can you give me a name onion hmm it's perfect i don't know what it means but
it's perfect hmm feels like it's shaped like me feels like it smells like me wait what was
the name um yum yeah it's perfect um yeah that's my name thank you for giving me a name
i'll cherish it you hear uh if uh hi for potato mask that's your name right i want to tell you
something tomorrow something i can only tell a friend come back soon here well it's kind of
creepy okay you want to see him you want to see a dead body welcome home honey did you have
fun with your friend today by the way i just finished baking a pie if you go to bed it
will be cool when you wake but do not eat it all this time all right chris what is it honey
here oh chris flowers for your mother how sweet these are from him are they not
well worry not chris i will find some place for them it's a butterscotch cinnamon pie
it's still cool it's a small container of apple scented shampoo yep yep it's time to go
to bed are these doors still locked if you go to bed this chapter of your adventure will end
will you go to bed you decided to go to bed you're all right what are we doing why is this
the intro to thriller uh i think i need that sword okay
fancy well there's a light inside your soul that's still shining in the cold with the truth
the promise in our heart i'm with you in the dark to be continued in chapter two so i ripped
out the heart interesting well that's that's so okay um you could move around the cage i was so i
was the heart well i mean that's that's all right that was delta rune uh let me try i take
care of this so here's uh the folder it's in i just want to make sure that nothing was in
here because if you want to install the game you can fuck it up so okay it's in here the
jevil item oh fuck you're right the only thing stopping me from making this joke is the jevil
item i was about to do it and then i realized that the jevil item well let's back it up a
little bit here i don't want to lose that i don't want to lose that never mind i'm not
making this stupid joke anyways you don't keep it what do you mean i don't keep it
but yeah that was delta rune i'll give you what i think about it um i i think it was an interesting
start it's free there really is if you are a fan of undertale if you liked undertale i mean
like what where's the harm in playing it it's it's just free i is it is the whole thing
going to be free no maybe not probably not there's no no there's yeah there's no way to
um i thought i thought it was cute i thought it was interesting but without the whole experience
it's hard to be like well you know there's my problem with what i think about the story
like i don't how am i supposed to give you an opinion on that did i play the first game on
stream i did very long time ago that was probably like it was one of the first games
i ever streamed in its entirety on twitch wasn't it chapter two is the rest of the game
and it's stated to be not free and scheduled for a 2025 release 2025 is that you are you
are you opening up folders to pretend to uninstall on me here or what okay so okay i
get it but anyways um so here's the deal uh over the next couple of days i'm not going to
stream i have some stuff that i need to get done over the next couple of days so nothing
tomorrow nothing on tuesday and then we're going to start up on wednesday i might stream on tuesday
depends if i can get everything that i want to get done done so nothing tomorrow tentative for
tuesday but you'll definitely see me again on wednesday whenever the second part comes out
i will absolutely play it i mean i'm already invested in it so why not and uh the germa the
new germa rumble germania 2018 is probably gonna happen exactly one week from today i'm
gonna try to do it by sunday got a lot of characters to make so i've already been
preliminarily getting it ready so and that is going to conclude tonight's stream so let's get
to the bits thanks for sticking around if you're heading out i will see you at the very least
on wednesday have a great rest of your night see you soon and for the rest of you here
thank you to uh jess homeboy for the one dollar missed you big time this is the first dream i've
caught since you moved as i haven't had internet for six weeks feels good to see you i know what
that's like i know exactly what that is like but thank you so much man check heart lactose
cowl thanks for the five dollars undertale is my favorite game ever in delta ruins is not
disappointed i'm excited to watch you experience it yeah i i want to i want to do the whole thing
so i'm gonna put that in the back of my brain here and i'm looking forward to whenever it's
finished thank you lactose cowl thank you zolder zolder ryan for the one dollar please
cosplay as sans uh that would just be naked with a blue blazer on i don't i don't think
i can do that thank you though thank you elots me for the five dollars lol thank you five bucks
actually it was lol owl thank you swiggity swanky for the ten dollars swiggity swanky
ten bucks i think i did a double take once i saw you playing this have you really run out
of game ideas what this is new what i got like hitman i got red dead i got the dreamcast
i've got playstation 2 i've got germa rumble coming up like what this is what did you think
i was playing undertale this is the new game man this came out like what this came out like
a week ago right two weeks ago he's just being a dick i don't know he's just kidding around
he's just kidding around it's all right don't worry two and a half weeks no new ideas
no hold on to hold on to that one because i'll see you in i'll see you in a few weeks
thank you okay ice cream for the one dollar i love you well thank you okay ice cream thank
decomposer thanks for the one dollar decomposer papa jeremy is streaming undertale 2 along my
own birthday blessed very blessed thank you decompose see you in a few weeks when we play
fortnight i'm never gonna play fortnight fortnight could knock on my front door
with a check for a million dollars if i streamed fortnight for six hours and i would take it and i
would just go absolutely absolutely because that's the easiest thing i would ever do in my life
so why the fuck would i not do that thank you mr sneak man for the one dollar hey germy
your streams and videos always help me get through life's challenges recently i've been
kind of feeling the sophomore year slump but your recent streams have made it a lot easier
on a much more serious note sneak man for next week's rumble or absolute riot we'll see
he won't play fortnight but will gladly embarrass himself doing the dances on stream
yeah but that's like that's like a a phenomenon right now it's not like fortnight has
6 000 active players that's like 600 million active players in that game
is a is a cultural phenomenon phenomenon phenomenon but uh thank you thank you uh
to zolder ryan zolder ryan for the five dollars here uh i really want fortnight no you
fort i'm not playing fortnight right now i'll delete your essay that you worked on for
four weeks no you're not gonna delete your essay why would you do something like that
you worked you worked so hard on that don't delete that because i won't play fortnight
you you just go play for just you go play fortnight right now and like here watch
you like just clip this like you can like just record fortnight just go open up get like
fraps or like shadow play or something and just record the screen while you're playing
fortnight and then just put this over that and then export it and watch it
yeah i think he's at the cube oh watch out watch out he's building they're all the way up
there man hold on what's he always get the john wick uh costume one okay ah i missed him let me
build hold on let me let me let me span a bunch of fucking structures all around everywhere in
every direction okay fun let me get up there oh okay i'm on top now i jumped down and i shot
him he's dead i got him now i'm gonna do dance look at that one oh i like that dance
hey he's got that was a ton of fun i should do that again sometime but anyways mr sneak man
um thank you so much i'm glad that you get some joy here and you can uh kind of relax here
and zolder ryan thanks for the five dollars jerma recently i've been getting into streaming
a lot and i wanted you to know that you're my main inspiration not only that but you're
also my number one source for laughs whenever i'm feeling down or having a bad day
thanks so much for all the laughs stay awesome good luck with streaming have fun with it and
be get to the get to number one in fortnight why am i on this fortnight thing right now i
don't know why because somebody said the word fortnight but i wish you luck zolder uh thank
you so much for the five dollars and absolutely i'm happy to have you what was the game that
i've voice acted in i've i've been in like three or four different games as minor characters
i had like a one role where it was i had like 30 or 40 lines 30 lines maybe
mr big time no i mean like i was the horse lord in apotheon i go like and i die or something
crypt arc yeah crypt arc was a lot of fun to do go read your wikipedia page
sure it's got lots of stuff on it he was the slim jim guy thank you uh thank you again to
alpines alpine sb for the hundred bucks thank you so much dude take care of yourself much love
to you i just got a what sir storyline germa 95 faces incredible challenges as a place through
a plethora of video games with occasional help and rivalry from his friend star trials are
faced dark secrets are revealed and dark souls will be beat on stream as jeremy attempts to
prove to all that he is in fact good at video games written by joel that's my imdb page
what the fuck uh thank you decomposer for the four dollars they say uh pride pride pride pride
and then they say my toes are wet i don't i don't know why that would i don't know
what's going on there but thank you decomposer four doubles uh novi gave five
community subs thank you so much div usp thanks for two dollars here uh devote kitty thanks for
the one dollar germa i'm regret regrettably not able to watch tonight because i'm playing
through undertale and i don't want to spoil delta runes so i just wanted to thank you for
the green screen stream friday was an awful day uh because my appointment to get hormone
replacement therapy got delayed uh till the 6th of december all the way to march 25th
so thank you for putting a smile on my face at my absolute lowest absolutely devil and
that's a big delay that's a long time uh but undertale is a great game i'm sure you are going
to love it because i'm so i'm surprised you didn't get spoiled that's like what undertale is
one of the hardest games to not get spoiled on like it really it really is that's actually
pretty remarkable but i'm sorry to hear about uh your your woes here with um having your
appointment delayed i spoiled it i spoiled myself before i played it and i regret it yeah it's
it's definitely worth doing it the first time when you go through it's it's an interesting
experience but take care of the other kitty much love to you did i spoil it by watching
this stream um maybe no no maybe yeah maybe no i don't know yeah you probably maybe
that's tough because like like the whole not no no no just play undertale and just play it
like you just play the game you know what i mean uh thank you dog funeral for the
ten dollars dog funeral hey germa i've only been following your stream since earlier this
year but you've been endless sorts of entertainment and laughs for me watching you play delta roommate
for a cozy sunday night thank you for keeping me and countless others inspired you truly a
great guy cheers hey cheers to you dog thank you yeah i figured tonight was gonna be
more of a just chill relax and enjoy a game you know what i mean but thank you so much for
the ten dollars i did feel like cozy people maybe maybe i came off as angry tonight because
i was cozy you know i'm like talking like this i'm just kind of walking around like having fun
did i said do i sound angry i mean it was one guy but someday you'll be the one guy
i felt pretty comfy uh ampharic and pinman gave a shitload of subs community subs here
back about four hours ago thank you guys so much that's so many and then uh kairatobi
keeps 20 you guys are so generous pocket pauling gave five thank you we also had a dollar from
doubled 11 is there an estimate of how many characters there are going to be in the next
year mania i typically when i do one of these i like to make at least 15 ish to 20 new
characters and then 10 plus old ones and then ones that i determined to be kind of not that
relevant anymore get pushed out so it's essentially like the last year of streams and what characters
did i like what what things i did i think were funny and then stuff from like two or three
years ago that's just not going to be there anymore it's kind of just not in the same
relevancy as something that happened like two or three months ago i'm not i mean well i'm not
going to do any character reveals here i already did one but uh thank you thank you uh march k's
march k's for the ten dollars i keep it ten dollars hey germo i don't have much to give
you for all the help in these trying years i fear that this might be the last stream for
me and i appreciate so much for the good moments in your stream especially when i was
at the hospital you're a man of joy and kind i hope you keep at it again thanks so much
uh i this might be my last stream what's uh what do you mean i'm not sure if it's still
here or not but uh hopefully if if you have going through an illness or something
i'm really sorry to hear about that i would potentially like to know more you know but if
uh let me see if it's still here let me see let me see yes it says they're still here
no i just uh but i mean whatever uh whatever you mean by this man hopefully that um hopefully
you can either i mean it's hard to without a lot of context you know i'm just i'm really
fucking sorry to hear about that whatever it is take care of yourself if uh if you're
around and you can still chat in the discord i'm sure people would love to hear your story
you know what i mean yeah it was march k's march k's q u e s this community can be really
great sometimes even though we act like clowns yeah i mean i i feel like there's a lot of
really interesting fun people here you know what i mean well hopefully um you know it's it's
like it's it's tough to it's tough to even say anything you know what i mean like that's that's a
a very very heavy statement i feel fucking terrible you know hopefully just like feel bad
i wish you the best i wish you all the love in the world take care um whiskey whiskey when
am i gonna get some more whiskey um i don't have any here yeah best of luck you know
whatever it is you're going through man you have a whole community of people here that
support anybody that's here so replied in chat already let me see i don't really like talking
about it okay yeah now then they will leave it at that but much love to you dude for real we
won't like pry you know there's no i don't i don't want to turn that into like something
like that so take care march if you need somebody to talk to by all means hop into
that discord i i hop in there too it's a really chill environment so link the discord uh somebody
can link it right here there it is right there yeah i'll be in there over the next probably a
couple of days just popping in yeah stay strong dude who are the discord moderators
uh it's pretty much all the mods on the channel are in the discord as uh they have
the ability to change things and do things oh yeah luke is uh like the overlord of the whole
thing so i'm a mod you are not a mod yeah i just played delta root but um thank you to
smacklesmore for the one dollar steal the dryer the dryer is not stealable you wouldn't
be able to steal a dryer especially if it was like a gas dryer what are you gonna do run
up to the gala like oh no i'm just gonna rip it out of the wall yeah those things are like
500 pounds can't steal something that you live inside i don't live in a dryer
not yet what do you mean not yet but you could you could live anywhere like that doesn't
mean that it's like you could like live anywhere get in that dryer i'm not going
in the dryer but thank you smacklesmore thank you the long egg for the one dollar
germa sorry uh for asking if you're pissed off and causing a wave of well we talked about it
don't worry everything's fine i'm just i'm just chilling here we're just hanging out
i was not upset about it don't worry you're good don't worry uh e cookie thanks to the
one dollar germa don't be so pissed off uh suedo lane thanks for the one dollar dream
please calm down hobo toaster thanks for five dollars if i pay you will you please be my
dad i asked nicely and i gave you money um i i not i'm not taking on any new sons or daughters
uh that's thank you though for the five dollars super seal thanks for the one dollar
the resemblance is uncanny yeah i mean like that's that's pretty accurate thank you plank
v2 for the ten dollars thanks for cheering me up on not uh so great of a day thank you
plank whatever it is you're going through hopefully you get through it take care much
love to you much love to all of you no you know what uh no no no if i pay you to be my day
you know i today only today only taking on sons and daughters here we go who's
come on how we got we got one we have one two three four five six seven eight one two
seven 1920 one two three four five six thirty four five 50 60 children 80 children
245 children 500 children okay all right that's it that's it that's it that's it no more
i've got 568 new children okay you missed a chance i mean i told you one said one minute only
i for one welcome my new lesser dad
dad you gotta pay for my college dad now disown them all and that's it that was wonderful
being your dad i have disowned all 567 people and i left one i i wonder who it is and that
one too gone uh anyways thank you to fender mcbender for the two dollars is this the streamer
that beat jevil first try it is welcome to the stream thank you i did uh thank you sagori saguri
for the one dollar seems good thank you uh thank you thank you darkon for the one dollar
real dark souls gamer thank you kind of sly 161 thanks for the two bucks you beat jevil on
your first try what the fuck i just had to lock in and sometimes you lock in and do things
i tried and that was very stressful i got it we did it we did it we did it hey we did it
thank you sly though thank you genie boy for the one dollar when in doubt check ass
i feel like that's the new thing now uh modus pones thanks for the one dollar epic
gamer moment that's all right communist seal thanks for the one dollar truly a god gamer
thank you vroom zero thank you vroom zero for the five dollars nice work jex thank you vroom
zero for your five dollars super seal thanks for the one dollar i will never question your
gamer skills ever again you fucking beat jevil on your first try most people couldn't do it
i tell you sometimes you go you you get get out of the microscope of jeremy elbertson you go
and you scroll through and you look at the slide sometimes there's something there
i couldn't make the noise because i've been talking a lot so like i couldn't make like the
you know the noise i couldn't do it it's just like air coming out of an old bike horn
but thank you lactose cow thank you again for five dollars lactose cow i just need to
give you more money after that jevil and what the fuck was that how how did you dodge that
carousel at the end just fucking activated jex man that's sometimes sometimes i can just like
lock in jex it's hard it's like it's like a i have to it comes from within somewhere
i don't know where but thank you hey clueless sniper thanks for the one dollar your gamer
license just got auto renewed thank you uh and dox and thanks for the one dollar literally
how did you beat jevel jex is stored in the balls i typically wouldn't read that out loud
but that was like that was come on that was pretty good that's pretty good thank you though
thank you to the long egg for a dollar you always cheer me up and helping keep my mind
off post-surgery issues it's tmi but my knee is swollen like a basketball that sounds
fucking painful and hope you recover very very swiftly relax take it easy
hope you recover very very soon uh cheesy uh thank you uh chinese for the ten dollars
i don't know why i said cheesy my brain is like slow right now thank you uh ten dollars
i thank you for ten dollars i actually can't believe you beat jevil first try i take like
all the shit i've ever talked about your gamer skills you get a different dialogue and item for
beating him through combat and it's a lot harder might want to try it off stream it's fun weird
gamer brain thank you so much that was very i can't imagine what it's like if you actually
have to fight him head-on that's probably like it wasn't this when sans the sans fight wasn't
that the incredibly difficult nearly impossible encounter i never even attempted that that
one looked even harder i don't know if that that would look even worse than that one
but thank you so much for the ten dollars really appreciate thank you so much
sans is like three times harder and longer it's gonna be so hard uh flying rapid
unicorn pig thank you for the one dollar still can't believe you did that holy fuck neither
can i neither can i egg johnson thanks for the one dollar egg johnson hey germy the other
night i had a dream where i was working in a restaurant i saw you in the corner by yourself
with an entire pie you looked down at it angrily picked it up and chucked it at the
wall with your full strength and stood there silently while everyone looked in shock
then i woke up why did you do that didn't get my fucking order right like i wanted a
pecan pie and i got a chocolate cream and that was the third time they screwed the order up so
you came into the dream when i was already in the restaurant for 25 minutes you don't have
that context you don't have all you have is that little clip there of you waking up in
in that reality there i was there for about 30 minutes waiting for different pies
and the manager was very rude to me do you know who i am uh thank you platin platin
pla to dunius for the ten dollars thank you platter platter platy i'm gonna call you platy
thanks for ten dollars platy i felt the need to drop some cash for how well you did on
that boss this was even better than watching smash summit thanks that means a lot thank you
everyone calls me plat actually that works all right yeah that's good i'll call you flat uh thank
you s kink for the two dollars germa i love you that's a very very thank thank you i love
all i love all of my children that i just disowned you know what i mean hey valuki
thanks for looking for the one dollar hey germa i don't feel like removing periods and commas to
tell you an extremely short summary of what happened in our castle griffinstein arc
so please read this on stream it was the most fun i've had in our campaign yet it was
wonderful thanks for being such a creative and talented person we love you almost as much
as carl let's see see the party slayed al goro and gave trogg a burial they encountered
the rabbit people and purchased everything from the shop malice the goliath fired the ray
gun and blew the hole blew a hole in the shop's wall they were soon chased out and
encountered the horde of zombies coming face to face with al gulu i threw a single stone and
killed the demon in one hit upon reaching the final room the wizard offered the party an answer
to any question that they would ask under the condition that it was one question asking what
happened to carl instead of asking about the two people we came to the castle to save the
shotgun picked up by malice was pulled from his hand and blew a hole into the wizard's chest
reality began to distort around him as the party found themselves floating on a single
platform in a red cosmic void staring down at carl himself cursed by a powerful ring
carl attacked the party driven by greed to find more chips i pulled the ring from carl's finger
and carl dissolved into smoke before the entire dungeon began to warp and collapse into itself
running out the party narrowly escaped and returned to town to inform the barbarians of
trogg's defeat then the barbarians got absolutely pissed absolutely pissed for disturbing
the ritual of the warrior's harvest with that we completed the castle griffin's deed
all in all carl became a corrupt god driven by greed for chips and was soon dealt with after
being found we love you germa that sounds like a pretty fitting end why didn't you ask if the
wizard eats ass i'm glad you had fun on your campaign sounds like a good time say good night
good night fox good night see see the one guy i eat that there you go good night fox
have a great rest of your night but thank you valuki sounds like an interesting time
hey genie boy thanks for the one dollar hey jeremy i'm a few minutes behind on this one
but thanks for granting us such a breathtaking performance in your first and also last battle
against jevil it was without exaggeration one of the most epic moments i've witnessed on twitch
germa jex times two cheers to that cheers guys uh eat the burger thanks for the two dollars here
uh they say top 10 meme streams that uh what should i be happy about that or should i be
very very disappointed uh they all say oh gerbert it's been like eight months since i
watched a stream live why are you playing undertale part four thank you thank you
darkstar 700 000 games for the one dollar best sans voice i've heard thank you also to garfield
the monday killer gar found lost undertale footage give your funniest commentary chat will
never forgive me for this one watching over there hey bro check this guy out it's my
favorite streamer germa 985 the germa 985 the top 1000 streamer the the one who
beat dark souls on stream yeah dude the germa 985 who made rant movie if i get gnomed
uh i'm making the minimum bits five dollars
hey so griffin stayed dude i was like laughing about that one a little bit
like you mean the germa 985 who had his house invested by wasps so like when a wasp went in
his room he was like you know going on diet it's not that big of a wait wait hold on wait
till he lands wait till he lands then he snaps his finger the wasp blows up his house blows up
and then he goes up in smoke whoa wait the virus the virus i just had like the weirdest
thought right now what if garfield set up a camera in our house they say in our house
it's undyed's house was the only background i could get but but but what what garfield like
put a camera in our house it was like spying on us so sans if what i'm hearing is correct
you're saying like he's recording us and just because we're talking about germa he's got i'm
waiting for a gnome so like put it in one of his garpographs and then he's going to send it
to him at the end of the delta rune stream yeah that's exactly what i'm saying well that's
kind of lame like like we're just standing here talking about germa and like that constitutes
putting us in a video and then wasting germa's time on stream to watch this this garbage
yeah dude something's gotta happen to make it a little bit more fun you know yeah bro
something has to happen dude oh no sats i i don't feel so good hey papyrus you all right dude
i don't i don't know i don't know i don't know what's happening i you guys can't even see this
i don't want to go i don't want to go mr sands please please i don't want to go i don't
want to go out i'm sorry you just disappeared oh gosh papyrus just died live on stream i
think garfield the monday killer just snapped his fingers and inadvertently murdered papyrus live
on germa 985 stream oh no gnome where's everyone safe no dude i've
i watched the whole thing because i was waiting for the gnome there's the video
it's not a gnome uh well it's okay it's okay thank you garfield for the voice work was
actually pretty good garfield sure does know a lot of actors apparently hey extra cheesy thanks
for the five dollars extra cheesy germa i had to drive a car for a long time and miss the
stream you've got to say something funny or i'll have a top tier comedy withdrawal
that was 42 minutes ago i think i may have said something funny bring it back let's see top
tier comedy thank you extra cheesy for the five dollars welcome back hey cobra cat thanks
for the four dollars have a good monday jeremy you too you as well hope you have a great monday
uh iron gunner thanks for the one dollar hey germa that was a really great stream thank you
thank you for being there and thank you for the monetary contribution that's a dollar from
you iron thank you so much uh crow ski thank you crow ski for the one dollar hey germa love
your streams and have recently been subbed for a bit by the way if you didn't notice
delta room is just undertale spelled backwards thanks again inner no it's not that's not it
it's not i'm just saying that it's an anagram
oh wow no thanks hey gondor lane thanks for the one dollar i'm still waiting on a bookworm
adventures germa stream that game and i'll be forever happy give it your famous quote i'll
look into it and look into it when you probably don't look into it but now you say you will
because i said this but you still won't look into it but we'll just say okay now i'll look
into it but probably still won't and now you'll feel guilty for just play it soon
i'll look into that i'll take a look at it thank you thank you the meme police for the
five dollars germa i'm so happy to catch your stream today love this game things have been
horrible recently for me but your streams and videos have made my days better going back to
the old tf2 days thank you thank you meme police for the five dollars sorry to hear about your
recent troubles but being around from the old tf2 days that's a long time ago thanks for sticking
with me much love to you for real i say that often but for real guys is sans gonna be in
the next germa rumble yeah sure fine i wasn't playing i guess anyways thank you gondolin
thank you the meme police and thank you kobecat for the one dollar forgot to give the rest of the
bits have a good monday again thank you thank you kobecat mostly lost thanks for the one
dollar tens of thousands of bits later and you still can't pronounce dib's name right germa
disgust is div usp man he's he's div div div usp div us it's not abbreviated it's not usp
it's div it's divus p divus p i don't want to correct you because i don't want to come off
rude no don't and don't i just i see it and i read it div usp so is it divus p or is it
divus p like uh i or it divus div us okay so i got div i got the div correct but thank you
thank you divus divus p for your correction i will make sure i say it wrong again
definitely gonna say it wrong again but thank you mostly lost for the correction actually
ivy cats ivy caz thank you for the one dollar they say capo thank you it's time for slime
thanks for the one dollar stop playing new games so i can watch your streams again
uh we're almost done with the new games there's not much left i might return to red dead or hitman
so because i still want to do some of the other missions i felt like i was at that was
a lot of fun we'll see hey banana slamma thanks for the one dollar sands for germa
rumble already been confirmed zero two thanks for the one dollar great stream tonight thanks
for being here glad you had fun uh burnt muffins thanks for the three dollars uh
tomorrow i'm going to be going to basic training for the air force even though i'll be sad to miss
your green screen stream and 2k19 germa rumble it will it'll be worth something to look forward
to when i get back when i get to tech school wish me luck good luck to you good luck in the
air force uh when you will when you get to tech school hopefully we see you again good luck
to you well i'll be rooting for you thank you burnt muffins hopefully we see you soon
chubby funster thanks for the one dollar hey germ boy thanks for the great stream was really fun i'm
really bad at wording how much of an amazing person you are to me and how much you put good
effect on my life so i guess this will have to do for now also if glue man is not in the new
germania i'm gonna find you and give you a smooch he'll be there in some fashion he'll be
like an announcer he's too old now he's why he is not he just can't wrestle he got old
uh that's i'm kidding he's he'll be he'll be there he'll be there uh chubby funster thank you
again for the one dollar also shout out to this community all of you are fucking great
lovely and funny and i couldn't ask for a better bunch of people i'm not drunk i promise
i agree i agree there's a lot of really great people here so i i am lucky to have such a
fun and interesting group of people thank you uh thank you sin the panda bot
for the 98 cents and yeah whoops a daisy it's all right though hey germa have you heard about
this uh happening in the u.s right now it's about the strange uh extinction have been happening
to bird species i'm sending this bit donation to raise awareness i don't mean to damper the
mood i'm going to damper them what is what do you mean well everybody said about the bird
it's 98 cents too and that like i let i let it slip through wasn't even a dollar it was 98
cents thank you jess homeboy for the one dollar giving you my last bit to let you know i'm
painting something inspired from your landing in vegas and i'm telling you now so i have to
commit myself to finishing it haven't you better finish it thank you jess minimum donation
is now 50 no way i would never do something like that uh brand the man thanks for the one
dollar hey germa i need a new voicemail could you make one up for me my name is brandon yeah
sure hey what's up you've reached uh brandon just want to let you know i'm not available
to get to the phone right now but if you could please leave your name a number and a detailed
message i would love to get back to you and by the way no let's redo it hey what's going
on you've reached brandon uh the brandowski here just want to let you know i'm away from
the phone right now please leave your name your email your brief message your address
uh all of your children's names all of your your father your mother all their names too
just in case they need to know for any particular reason i'll leave them all there and i'll get
back to you i mean my phone's always dead so i'll probably not i'll probably text you later
but i might not have your number though so if i don't like know who you are then i'm not
going to know who you are from texting so i'm going to ask you like hey who is this on the
text but anyways uh thanks for calling i'll get back to you soon leave your message everybody's
heard about that bird you never did the vegas voicemail i never did right i did not do that
i did that whole thing and it was supposed to be like a because people were asking wait you're
moving to vegas what the fuck it was going to be something you could do and whatever uh
there you go brandon hopefully it works it was plus two until the bird then it was minus four
oh well hey zoot thank you zoot for the one dollar what does no mean can i have
a bus fare home now that the stream's over dad yeah here you go here you go son
take a quarter that'll get you i'll get you down 50 feet down the street hey voice boy thanks
to the one dollar hey jeremy just want to let you know that i used audio from your green screen
stream as part of my film class project this week and i got an a for it i basically made a
cyberpunk trailer was you as the narrator it all got spun from you talking about the virtual world
well i'm glad you got an a thanks a lot voice boy keep at it hey chubby funster thanks for
the one dollar please gross please gross out your beard you look really good with it
grow out gross out i can't grow a beard after about a week it turns to absolute dog shit i
look terrible i can't do it i look so bad ivy kaz tv thanks for the two bucks you made the
long night's well worth from my time in s e r t during my time for relief support down
to the coast during the hurricane i'm happy to be here and thinking of what's going on
here instead of what i saw there uh always know you are great thank you uh thank you
hi because and and thank you for for that that's tough that's really fucking tough i
have nothing but respect for people that help others so much love to you for real
32 year old child can't grow beard i can't but you're always welcome in this community
everybody is anyone is thank you mu means mu thanks for the one dollar love you dad
even if you no longer acknowledge me as your son you still hold a special place in my heart
it's all right it's all right just like grow a beard and come back to me we'll talk thank you
guessing too for the eleven dollars can't catch streams anymore because of a new job here's an
hour of my time and return for all of yours thank you guessing too congratulations on the new
job i hope you make some money thank you for being here where's the job well not like
where but like what like not like wait wait wait where do you work where where's it like what
jeremy don't be a such a boy what thank you glitch bird for the one dollar i only started
watching your stuff in early 2017 during some shitty times in my life which is also when i
started to get into tf2 uh stuck around because your content is genuinely some of the
best i know you probably never go back to tf2 but that doesn't matter because you're able
to make fucking cardboard hilarious uh debatable but and that says a lot also i'm still in shock
over jevil that was amazing thank you uh team fortress two started me down this road
and sometimes i kind of look back in the rear view and see how it's doing thanks for being
around for this long because we're talking about 2017 2018 like two years three years
i'm i'm shocked and surprised and humbled and thankful that there are people that have
opened up this stream and opened up these videos for a year two years three years four
years and you're still here thank you all those people probably that probably knew you from the
server
thank you glitch bird and then finally here at the end we've got moo means moo for a dollar
and chubby funster for a dollar and moo says also just want to say that even though work
and life stuff keeps me busy uh to catch most of the streams these days i owe a lot of these
streams and to this community watching these streams and getting the chance to be mod
for the swell community got me through some not fun times and now that things have leveled
out just want to say thanks for everything jerma heart thank you moo you've been around
for a long time you got a lot of creative funny energy up there man glad to have you thank you
glad that things have started to level up for you and finally chubby funster jerma i meant
grow not gross but my words are not so good me not so good me not like fire
uh what is this what the fuck is this bit message uh thank you uh extra cheesy thanks for a dollar
hi it's me again okay i guess you did say something funny i take it all back i'm sorry
apology accepted and here come the oh my god how many subs were there you guys uh fucking
every day the jevil fight resulted in like 20 plus subs i think it was more than that
i think it was like 40 there are a lot of fucking people subscribe to this channel a lot
and there's a lot of new viewers too i've noticed that too thank you for taking the ride
hopefully you stay on it's crazy because i see i see a lot of um familiar faces in the chat
and uh and uh subs too and equally new faces new subs and new people been watching
youtube videos for years but i finally jumped into your twitch streams welcome i'm gonna i'm
gonna keep doing it i'm gonna just keep doing what we do as long as i'm continuing to have fun
as long as you guys are having fun then let's keep going fuck it you know what i mean
i want to try and do as much as i can i want to try to do the best job that i possibly
can and that's something that i really truly mean so let's go fucking get the gas in the
container you know what i mean let's step on that gas top 1000 uh i'll see you on the goddamn
moon we're gonna get to at least top 780 that's right thank you all of you i know i don't read
subs anymore but it doesn't mean that i don't appreciate it because all of you guys that watch
and sub and pay money to this stream you are the blood that runs through the veins of the channel
i'm blood now blood is incredibly important because without blood you just got a skeleton
that's it you all you're just blood and skeleton and a little bit of skin and right
at the end here before we go i'll see you guys probably on wednesday if i see you on
tuesday then we'll we'll see where we are i don't have another i don't have a schedule
yet see what that ends up being but condo breaker thanks for the one dollar
uh hey german just want to say that i've been watching you since the beggars bazooka sneeze
video which i didn't watch for like two years because it sounded more like coughing
than it did sneezing and that pissed me off to the point of almost deciding to never watch
you again i'm glad i actually decided to watch you also please play pyre airbud with a
mustache is there uh thank you elizabeth for the one dollar is a clip is uh is vinnie okay here
we are this is the teleporter we will use to enter the alien base quite a realistic looking
cave what the fuck am i playing we are why do you link time follow me what what i don't get
i mean vinny's a really a really funny really great dude but what what what's the context here
i mean this is the clip hey thank you also to ivy cast tv again for a dollar thank you for
your kind words my friend i love you and everyone else here thank you for everything
everyone especially you you do wonders goes both ways thank you and then little light of mine
thank you thank you and that's gonna end the stream see you guys soon delta room was fun
that was comfy mostly lost thanks for the 99 cents shouldn't even be reading this while i
thank you thank you for the 99 cents thank you good night everybody see you soon probably
tuesday or wednesday give chat a good night kiss says moo means moo good night chat
that was me turning that was me turning the light off in the room good night good night
family