Hey, what's going on everybody?
Jerma here. I apologize I'm currently eating some Halloween candy because it's Halloween.
And what better way to celebrate Halloween than to play, you know, Typing of the Dead Overkill just came out on Steam.
So a couple things you-
What's up, motherfucker?
They met as adversaries.
Who the fuck was that for?
A monster made them allies.
So the Typing of the Dead, as you can see, is a game about writing on your keyboard.
You can only kill monsters if you type. You can't- there is no, like, shooty gun thing.
There is no weapons.
It's only your keyboard. What the fuck is that?
GOOTORARIO? I don't even know what that is.
I'm such a bad typer too, guys. I apologize. I have to, like, look at my keyboard. I suck so bad.
But yeah, this game came out a long time ago.
And they just re-imagined it.
God, I'm so bad. God, I'm terrible at typing.
Hey, you know what? Let's make a Typing of the Dead video on a guy who can't type for shit.
That sounds like a good idea.
In the difficulty, you can make it much harder than this.
I can't believe I have to look down every single time at my keys. That is so bad.
I'm such a terrible, terrible typer.
Flabwagon.
So I think there's gonna be co-op eventually on this game.
But it's good to see they actually brought this series back.
Cut them down.
Phew. OK, we got through the first room. Can I reload?
I don't think reloading really matters. OK, I gotta get ready. There's gonna be a couple.
There's gonna be a few coming through the store.
God.
I'm sorry I'm not, like, talking.
This takes all of my brain power to be able to do this.
What? What happened to the words that were just already there?
But if you are looking for something to help...
I can't talk.
If you're looking for...
OK, can I have a two second break?
If you're looking for some way to help your typing out, this is probably the game to do it,
because you get to kill zombies in the same time, right?
The best back rubs.
This is actually helping me.
This is helping my typing, guys.
I'm becoming a type master because of typing of the dead.
Oh, shit.
Shit! Fuck you!
I love how I thought this was a great idea to make a video on this
when I can't even pay attention to even talking.
I'm such a brain dead fuck.
I have to, like, pay complete attention to my keyboard and, like, nothing else.
Oh, am I making a video right now or am I trying to use my 100% of my brain to play this video game?
I'm not sure.
Big Berza!
Well, those are for extra points. I get it, I get it, I get it.
Uh-oh.
Oh, boy. Hot diggity dog.
I like how it gives you the...
If you make an incorrect keystroke, it's not just going to, like, make...
Hold your fire.
Mutilate.
Civilian rescued.
5,000 points, dude. Are you kidding me?
Rack it up. Rack up the points.
Whose head is that?
I am such an old person.
I am, like, 75 years old right now.
All right, type C-A-Y-N-I-D.
Some of you guys can probably blow through this, and I give you a lot of props
because typing has never been my forte.
I've never been able to really do it that well.
I have a legitimate headache.
These guys ain't human.
Never seen this kind of crazy shit before.
All right, so what is this? What is this acting?
Boss fight. Oh, I have to hit I.
Shit. Oh, my. I'm getting owned.
This guy is owning me.
I've gotten hit by every single thing.
No. No, Z.
There we go. There we go.
About to rage quit this game.
I'm about to put my hand through my monitor.
I'm about to seriously...
There's going to be some serious rage in a second
because of how awful and how stupid I am
and how... Give me a chance.
That's so... Just give me the gun.
I'll take the gun.
What's going on?
I think they just made it way easier for me
because the game could tell I was having a ton of trouble.
Look, look at how easy these words are now.
We could tell that you, like, sucked ass.
We're going to give you, like, some wicked easy words, like am and okay.
Hopefully that trend keeps up. Look, oh, Sam.
Hog. Tap.
And I still missed it.
I still missed it.
Oh, we're back to being difficult now.
That's so funny.
What was it? C? B? Homework?
D. You missed me.
I wish I could do some better commentary, guys,
but it is mildly pathetic that my brain can't do two things at once.
I'm going to lose again. I'm going to fucking lose again.
Can I have the wicked simple easy words again?
Give me, like, two fro fought easy words.
Come on, man. Bye. Done. I did it.
I beat the first boss in the typing of the dead.