Oh hello. How are you? How's it going? Do you have peanut butter voice? Yeah, a little.
Better? Yeah, I'm a little early. I'm a day early. But I just felt like turning it on.
That's what we're doing. Day five of wisdom teeth recovery. Oh shit. It usually takes a while.
Usually like a week or two, right? He's obsessed with being early. Cozy eye strain? What? Yeah,
today we're going to play. It's been on the list for a little while called travelers rest.
So it reminds me of. Oh, there's an eye strain tag. There's an eye strain tag.
Why would you want to look that up as a tag? Oh yeah, I'm going to search for some streams
that I think are. Yeah, I'm on I'm on Twitch. Let me look for some streams.
Uh, I strain that seems like a like a tag you wouldn't want to go look for.
It's for warnings. Oh, because because right now it says English and I strain.
Those are the only two tags. That's funny. To be honest, that's how I found you.
Do I take game suggestions? Yes, there's a recommended channel in the discord channel
is just open to the public. So if you have a game that that I have not already played,
then by all means put it up there. Definitely make sure to search in that channel. Make sure
that it's not the same thing that's been posted a few times, but I do. I go in there frequently.
I mean, by frequently, I mean at least at least a couple of times a month. I'll just kind of open
it. It's funny. I use the recommended channel in my discord more than any other channel in the
discord. It's like one of the only uses that I have for that discord for me personally is.
What's in the recommended? Let's go look for a little bit. At least once a year, yeah.
But what I usually do is I just kind of start from the most recent one and just go up.
Just take a look. See, I usually go up as long as it's been since I was there last time.
From what I remember, at least. Rude streamer doesn't engage with his audience.
OK, yeah, true, true, true. Insane streamer puts boundaries on how he feels. Yeah.
I think that's important, though. I think that's very important.
Ah, he's strained. How am I doing? I'm doing good. I'm doing good.
It's been kind of a wild few days. Very exciting stuff. Kind of overwhelming and in a lot of ways.
But it's been, it's been, it's been great. I also, no tannins? No, no, no tannins tonight.
It's not that I have heard. Yeah, I, there is another little thing I want to talk about
with Battle Beasts. There's no, I promised no PowerPoint presentation tonight.
So, but like the four or five sentences that I want to say. No, no PowerPoint. Sorry. I know.
When is Breath of the Wild? I know. I don't know. I don't know. I need to like, I just have to play
it. Like, I don't know. I want to play this. There's like all the stuff I just want to play.
You know what's weird about Breath of the Wild? I'm going to be honest. Let's, let's, OK,
I'm going to completely just give you the total transparency. This happens to me a lot. It
probably happens to a lot of people here. A lot of times I will get 30, 40, 50, 60 percent of the
way through a game and then not play it for a little while. And then going back is almost like
shit. It's almost like I walked out of the theater in the middle of the movie
and going back to watch that whole movie again at some point, right? Oh yeah. OK,
I'm going to go back and I'm going to watch. OK, I'm going to watch Infinity War. I walked out in
the middle of that movie, but I mean, I'm going to give it a chance. And you kind of sit through
the beginning again. You're like, I don't know. Who is this guy? Who is this? It's been like a
year since I looked at it. I cared about this. Who is that? This Thor? Oh yeah. I fuck. I don't
think maybe I just won't even watch this movie. So that happens. That does happen to me all the time.
So I can't tell you that it's not that I don't want to. It's not that I don't want to play
Breath of the Wild. It's I kind of walked out of the theater halfway through, got really busy.
I think that was during the period, too, where I was didn't stream very much, right?
But yeah, I will probably finish it. I will. I just need to find the reason to kind of
put the DVD back in. So don't worry. Don't worry. Probably. Can you talk about Brado Beast's
digital version? That's one of the things I want to talk about today.
I want to make sure I don't say anything incorrect, but.
Uh oh. Hold on a second, everybody. Hold on a second, everybody. I don't want everyone
to freak out right now because I just said the word digital. This is not turning into
an NFT project. This is not going to be like, just hold on a second. Let me just talk.
Let me talk. The movie just started. The movie just started. You can't. I'm sorry,
we're going to use the movie analogy here. I'm sorry. Thanos just appeared on screen
and he has like the reality stone in his hands and none of the first fucking 10 minutes of
Infinity War. Isn't he just like, oh, I need to collect six more of these and go my minions.
But if in the first five minutes of that movie, you're screaming at the screen going,
I can't. Why did you? No, you're going to, you're going to kill Thor with that thing.
You're going to, you're going to kill Thor with that. And it's like, bro, the movie's still going.
Like we don't even know. Stop, sit down. Relax. He's got the reality stone. He's going to kill
Thor. It's like, no, dude. Hey, just, hey, shut up, man. I'm trying to watch. And then you get
halfway through the movie and whatever, you know, it's the, I don't want to give infinity
war spoilers is I don't know why that's the one movie that I've refused to fucking spoil.
Why? Why? Forever. And this has been for years, for years,
since the first green screen stream back in like what? 2019, 2018. Oh, I don't want to,
I don't want to spoil infinity war. Why is that the movie that I don't want to spoil?
That that's the one. And even now, like five, four, five, six years later. Well,
I don't want to talk about infinity war because I don't want to like spoil it for anybody. It's like,
dude, it's all right, man. I think it's going to be OK. But anyways, I want to meaningfully talk
about this. And I think there's enough people here now that I don't know. There's nothing to announce,
but so for the game grotto beast, the game grotto beast, because at the very beginning,
the very beginning of this project, this project was community merch and it was like, wait,
we can build a game on top of it. That's kind of cool. We can have there be rarities. That's
kind of cool. But I want to make sure that people understand that we are actively exploring other
stuff to make it so people can participate, because we're not obviously it's not like,
oh, yeah. Can I get every single card, every single grotto beast card? I don't I don't know.
Right. And I think the idea is people that really want to just play the game,
the game portion of this merch, because that's what it is. The actual card game,
we want to make sure that there is a version that people can just play. And whatever that means,
we're exploring it right now. But the one thing that we're trying to figure out and one thing
that we know is probably not going to be in the game or whatever version of whatever this is.
And when I say game, like the game portion of what we're trying to digitize, is this a mod
of an existing platform? Is this a standalone app that you just get or buy whatever? I don't know.
But it's it was absolutely not nothing in these discussions have been a digital digital card
packs. No, this would be something that we can just make sure that everybody has access to play
it if they wanted to. But that's not what's happening. This is not a case of we're just
taking the physical thing and making it digital to like sell digital card packs.
That's not what this is. That's not what I'm telling you. So it would be the version,
the thing that we have right now, these 200 cards would just be the thing that you have.
And whether that's a mod or whether that's a small kind of small digital version that we can make,
that's what we want to do. No, with no in app purchases. This wouldn't be an app
purchase wouldn't be anything like that. But also to we want to just we want to make it
don't make sense. And that's meaningful. And there's plenty of ideas that have floated around.
But the ideas we want people to participate in the game portion of this merch, even if they,
you know, let's say you don't buy like a bunch of card packs, we want people to be able to
experience this event for the community. However, that is that we're still trying to
figure that out. And if it's not, I'm telling you, no, that's not what it is. And also,
this is an interesting kind of thing to talk about, too, is if we do have a version of the game that's
on that's a that's a mod, or that's a standalone thing, whatever, then our game designer can
continue to be kind of in control of that game portion. Right. So that's very interesting. That
means that there's things that can happen to that version can be maybe and I'm speaking
completely candidly right now. This is not anything that I'm planning. And this is not
something we have planned. But maybe the game designer can make balance changes possible.
I don't know. That's possible. But the game portion of this merch product, something that
we're trying to figure out how to let anybody really participate and not need to be in the same
room meaningfully and have it make sense. It's a long process. We're really trying to figure it out.
But trust me when I say we are trying to make it so as many people can enjoy this event
as we can. That's all I can really say. Game designer is sweating right now. Is it going to
be a Minecraft mod? Well, we definitely we want it to be easy. We want it to be something that's
simple, that is not you can just jump in it and make it easy. We don't want to make it where,
oh yeah, and then by the way, while you're in here, you're gonna buy packs. That's not we want
people to be this is for the game portion. It's not about anything else. Because we've seen people go
wait, like the game seems kind of there's a game. What is the game? That seems kind of interesting.
How does it work? The rules are being worked on right now. Well, that while the rules being
posted are being worked on right now. The game is completely is it's complete. I don't want to
say that incorrectly, because I have a tendency just to kind of be a stream of consciousness,
right? The game is the game portion is done. But the rules, we want to make sure there's a place
for people to see the rules. And what's being worked on right now is the page that we're putting
the rules on. So that'll be in the next day or two of the next couple of days. So I need to make
that really clear. Like, what the fuck, dude? What do you mean you don't know that what the rules
aren't done? The rules are done. They've been done for a long time. The rulebooks are printed,
by the way. We're not still making the rules. I just I have a tendency just to fucking talk.
And that was not correct. The rules are done. The rules. The rulebooks been printed. Don't worry.
Is he groggy? I mean, I showed you the rulebook already. I mean, that's bold. That's the way it
is. Yeah, that is what how we're our stance on sort of the digital aspect of this. Let us try to
get it right. I'm going to say four or five sentences. Yeah. But, you know, is this guy
going to play Traveler's Rest or not? If the game takes off, will you? I don't even I don't even want
to go that far. Right. I don't want to go that far. This was a project for this community.
It's a merch for this community. And that's my stance on it. And that's our stance on it.
I do not want to tell. I don't want to say like, oh, wow, look at this. And we're going to do this.
And we're going to do this. I can't say that. We really can't. All I can tell you is it's a really
it was a really, really crazy project that is finally at its completion. And we finally get
to show it and finally get to sell it. And that is the stance. And now, ladies and gentlemen,
if you could please get comfortable, we're going to play Traveler's Rest again. No digital card
pack openings. I need to make that like one, two, three, four words. This game has been requested
a lot. Seems pretty comfy. Seems like it's got a lot of inspiration from a lot of cool stuff.
But what if I want to open digital card packs? Well, then you're probably going to have to do
that somewhere else. I don't know, man. I don't know what to tell you. All right, let's go.
New. Oh, OK, here we go. Beard or no beard. What do you think? Definitely mustache for sure.
I think I'm done. Yeah, I like that. I like that. I like these. That's perfect.
Give him the Nightwing shirt. Oh, wait, I can do different shirt colors.
I don't know. This looks fine. Dude, you literally just made my father. I like this.
All right. Looks good. So now you made Ron Swanson. I think it's no, this is not.
That's not Ron Swanson. Ron Swanson. Are you talking about the guy that talks like this
when he's very upset about something? He's pulling a prank on people in that office.
Are you that that what are you talking about? I just want to make sure I know where I'm getting
the right person. Is that it? I've only seen two episodes of that show that that's right.
I did it right. All right, let's go. OK, except welcome to Traveler's Rest.
The game is in early access, which means it's still being developed based on your feedback.
If you're enjoying your time, please start leaving a review. I move the trigger is run
and then and that's decoration mode. So this is wait. So these are the ales.
Is this like this is what I have on draft? Yeah, I'm definitely put an orange juice on draft.
Would that could you do that? Could you imagine fucking orange juice like on draft?
It'd be so cool. Just like to work. Why is that weird? OK, let's go.
Decoration mode. You can place items like an object, move the cursor over it, get close
and press a. OK. Oh, maybe in the corner. Just initially. I don't I don't like it over here.
There you go. But the benches are facing the wrong way. Hey, wouldn't this be wrong?
Yeah. OK, there we go. Customers will also expect their table to be well lit in the evenings.
Try placing the candle on the table. Candles are consumed over the course of days,
so you'll need to replace them in the future. OK, isn't the right spot style.
Ooh, is it on the table? Yeah. Get close to the book on the bar and press a to open your stock.
OK, so this is book on the bar. How much money do I have?
You're going to burn this place down. Why is there only one table here?
I guess I just opened. I got here. This looks cute. It doesn't cute.
All right. Storing food here will add it to your bar stock while your bar isn't stocked.
You will serve gruel. Oh, gruel only rewards a small amount of money.
Should I serve gruel to people? OK, so storing food here. I need to store food.
Trends. Oh, you can see what people like. That's cool. Press down to open your tavern and serve
some gruel. You have a quest. I don't want to serve gruel. OK, first customers to serve six
customers. All right, come on in. We have gruel. That's all we have. You want some gruel?
The customer has requested an item. Let's serve them with a must have had a problem with the
decoration mode being left on. All right, here you go. That's that's all they get to have.
They can't even have any beer. You want more? You want more gruel. All right. That means it must be
pretty good. OK, close up the tavern so you can place your new items. Call last order is by
pressing down. This will prevent new customers from entering the tavern. OK, we're closing.
Pressing that again will force your tavern to close, but you will lose reputation.
You should wait for your customers to leave. So if I hit that a button again, I force everybody out.
What even is gruel? To me, gruel is just a kind of a catch all or slop food. What is it? Is it like
is it like gluten? Is it is it like grains like oatmeal? I think when I think of gruel,
I think of oatmeal. It's grains and water. Flour boiled in water. What? Hold on. Let me look that
up. What is actually is it gruel? A thin liquid food of oatmeal or other meal boiled in milk or
water. Some type of cereal such as ground oats, wheat, rye or rice heated or boiled in water or
milk. Thinner than porridge. That doesn't even. OK, that doesn't sound bad. In my brain, gruel was
disgusting. Like it was like, I don't know, all kinds of weird fucking parts. We're just gross
shit in it. I thought it was like, I don't know. I thought it was just gross. That actually does
not sound that. That sounds like oatmeal. That sounds fine. That is gross. No, it's not. Oatmeal
is not gross. OK, set up a table using your new items enter decoration mode. All right, so I need
to do a new table. OK, it's like the item on your. Oh, there it is. There it is. Table.
It's a little table. All right, this is this is like a like a couple's table, right?
Or like a like one one person here, one person on the other side. This is like for like dinner.
Oh, it has to be over here. Why not fit? I only have one stool there. What? Hold on,
because the tables against the wall. Yes, it is. OK, OK. Open your tavern, serve new customers,
complete more quests, get more gruel. I think it looks good so far. All right, let's go.
We're open. You go on a first date and bring them to the gruel restaurant.
What if it's the best gruel in town? One of your customers has dirtied the floor.
Tavern vision will highlight important objects such as dirty tables,
floor dirt and important customers. Clean the floor by selecting the mop and then pressing X.
What the hell? How long does it take? Don't do that. You want gruel? Who wants some gruel?
Go on, there's not enough room for all these people. What did I just get?
You now serve porridge and grog. All right, I can put grog in there.
Grog. What is grog? Why do I feel like grog is gruel with vodka poured on it?
OK, you now serve porridge. Grog. OK, and there's porridge. So I just own it.
Why near the beer tap and at the keg of grog? Wait, I can have soup on tap? Tables dirty?
Can I put whatever I want on tap? What a lovely clean tavern. Thank you. Can I make it? All right,
what do I make one? How do I drink this? A customer has requested a beer. Move next to the
beer tap and press and hold A to pull a beer. Then get close to the customer. Oh, I have one
right now. Is this what you want? There you go. Oh, one silver. I love that sound. Gruel, you should
go back to only serving gruel. Nobody wants that. Imagine you're doing this for meta bucks
in the metaverse. Yeah, meta bucks in the metaverse. I love meta bucks that term. Remember,
you're bad at this. Hey, what are you talking about? I've only served everybody. I've served
everybody very quickly. Very. Hold on. I got an axe. Can we get this table wiped down? Hold on.
Close your tavern and go outside to chop trees. Let me take care of that real quick.
All right, this place is fucking disgusting. Well, maybe if you didn't miss your mouth.
Hey, look, people are dumping shit everywhere. This is disgusting. It is not. Oh, I gotta close
this place. All right, we're closed. Everybody get out. Better not rain tomorrow. And they watch
your stream in the bar. Thank you. Thank you. Thank you. Thank you. Thank you. Thank you. Thank
you. Thank you. Thank you. All right, nice. We're closed, right? Outside your tavern,
you find a post box to order in supplies in a delivery box. A notice board to accept order
quests. Hire staff and check the calendar. A well to collect water. Natural resources that
will allow you to craft new items and harvest fruits and vegetables. And add carrots to the
grill. Here you can order items for your tavern. Select an item to add it to your basket or press
UI select game pad to add five. Three hours. OK, so we can buy this stuff.
Oh, ale yeast. I get some of this. All right, I'm going to get one of those.
I'm going to get one of these. I'm going to get two barley's. I'm going to get two barley seeds.
I'm going to get a bed. I don't have enough money. All right. OK, buy that. Oh, shit, this is
expensive. Fifty seven. What's all the bed? Seventeen. All right, buy that. What is all this?
OK, hire staff. I can't do that yet. Orders. I don't I can't do that yet. Calendar. All right,
so there's important events. That's kind of cool. I don't see any events here. All right,
so I think we're good for a little while. So didn't want me to cut down trees. How do I attack?
Does this count? Happy gruel Saturday. Where do I go to do this? OK, there we go.
Can I replace these? How much wood should I get? Wood in the gruel. That'd be such an
unbelievably awful filler. OK, one more tree. Historically accurate filler. What?
That's not true, right? OK, you've turned your first work area, the sawmill. Build it outside
the tavern using the decoration mode like the copper sickle. They're going to clear the weeds.
Sawmill. All right, I'm going to clear this shit. Star gruel valley. I mean, it plays pretty nice
so far. I mean, I, I really like games like Stardew. I should probably plant some trees,
though. All right, which sawmills would probably be if this is my tavern, I don't want the sawmill
to be that close. So maybe back here, like to the right. All right, sawmills going on the right.
I'm going to go right here. OK, oh, I thought that was way bigger than I thought. That's OK.
I thought this is a big building, like a big lumber mill. This is a table. OK, so it's just
a table. So I'll put it over here. I think this is fine, right? I don't want to go that far to get
this. I think right here is fine. Hey, hold on. I like the sound of the grass. It does have a good
sound, doesn't it? All right, let's put it right here. I think that's a good spot. OK, now each
crafter has a list of recipes these show the required ingredients, fuel, and time. Click the
recipe name to begin crafting wooden planks. So OK, I make how much of these should I make?
It's very crunchy, smooth and crunchy. Each recipe takes time to craft. Once the timer is full,
move closer and press A to collect it. It takes 10 minutes, like actual 10 minutes or in game
world 10 minutes. Oh, OK, it's just in game world. OK, what do we do with the planks? Nice. Family
guy mobile game. Hey, whatever. I need to make one more planks. Your character is very stylish.
Character is very stylish. Thank you. Thank you. Appreciate it. Who are you? Can I talk to people
in town? All right, so now I have pickaxe. OK, they keep telling me the decoration mode needs
to be turned off. I bet you in the play testing of this game, people probably were walking around
whoever being like, why can't I play? What's happening? So they that's a good reminder to
turn it off. That would have been you. Yes, it would have been. Absolutely would have been me.
How do I? I can't get rid of the stone. Does this grow back? Can you pass out?
I wonder. Dude, it's dude. It's not a rock tree. Yeah, but it's still here. The smelter and the
anvil. OK, you build a smelter, a new working area dedicated to metals will be created.
This cannot overlap any other working area to know. Well, if the if the lumber mill is going
to be right there and the smelter needs to be right next to it, I can't get rid of this right
above it. I'll do right above it. It's going to be ugly, but I don't care. Can I actually hold on?
I can't clear it.
Let's put it above. It's fine. Games kind of like Battlefield 20. All right, let's put it down.
I'm thinking just right over it. We can make this look nicer later. Now what? Open fuel.
Fuel. All right, so here's this. How much should I do? Iron bar. Not enough fuel. I need 10 fuel.
Why so much fuel? That's way too much fuel. All right. Iron. OK, I can only make two iron bars.
Where the heck up? Oh, that. OK, I can do that. Put all these logs in it. Iron sheet. All right.
Copper. Smooth and slim. I'm going to make this. I don't even know what it does. I know people will
say like I'm seeing a lot of the D face and but I think this is I used to not say any bad words,
but guys, this is just that's how I talk. All right. I'm sorry that a lot of people aren't used
to that. This is how I talk and that's how it's going to be. So you might see, you know, me being
like, what the heck? It's just that's how I talk. It just doesn't feel right when you curse.
That that has so many layers on it. That comment has so many layers. It's just like, god damn.
It doesn't feel right. I'm going to make a couple of sticks. I have an anvil too.
Oh, nice iron nails, hinges, candelabra, candle holder. I make some nails. Carpentry
is carpentry. Would you restream Stardew? Yeah, probably in a format like this where we're just
kind of hanging out. Sickle somebody walking by. Oh, we know why you're here. I can't. All right.
I need let me. How late is it? What time is it? It's kind of late. I'm going to bed.
I got some deliveries, didn't I? Oh, shit. I did. Cool. All right. How do I go to bed?
What? I can't put firewood in here. Cellar. Why do I have a cellar? There's a crafting room.
There's a cellar. Here's my personal inventory. All right. Fine. I'm going to bed. This is your
bedroom. Sleep in your bed to save the game. If you stay up too late, you'll pass out.
How late is too late? This is a horror game. It's five p.m. too late to take a nap. No,
it's not ever too late to take a nap. Nap should always be considered whenever you think you need
it. Right. So if if it's six or seven o'clock, maybe there's something, you know, you really
need to do. You really want to get done. I don't think it's ever too late. I think after when it
is pitch black outside, I think that's no longer a nap. I think that's you going to bed. But I think
that doesn't happen till about for me, seven to eight p.m., I think, at least. OK, don't lose
progress. OK, I did it. What about winter? I mean, you really should be trying to awake during the
day and sleep during the night to try its best to get your body on that schedule if you can. But
guess what? A lot of people don't have working schedules that do that. Some people start their
job at some people at six, seven, eight o'clock at night. The number one thing that you need to
be aware of, try to get at least you know, you really want that six day. You want six to seven
to eight hours. You want those. You want eight hours. You really don't want to try to get it
hard. You really want it. OK, before opening your tavern, because they're stocking up the day,
you'll need more logs for crafting in the fireplace. Is it the post box order? OK,
consider stocking up. Why do I have so many of these? Why do I have this many? I'm not going to
open this place yet. We're putting candles around. I'm going to get another table probably, right?
Another table is a good idea. Do I have enough to make another table? Oh, there's a tech tree.
How do I make a table? We're not open. I screwed it up. I'm in decoration mode. I didn't listen.
Blacksmith table, brewing coal, firewood. How do I make a table? The rocks are here. They are here.
Oh, wow. I imagine you can probably permanently get rid of these somehow. Hey, can you please
boot up Fallout 76? I need another member for my expedition. Well, I can assure you it's not going
to be me. Let me just make sure I can assure you of that. OK, this thing really wants me to
still use the smelter for some reason. You obtained the smelter and maybe have to make something on
the anvil. Didn't I have? I do. So let me make nails. Why the fuck not? You actually hate
Fallout 76 unsubscribed. I need fuel in this. All right. Should I make a? OK, I'm going to make
nails. I'm going to have five nails. How long does this take? A long ass time. Why are you dying on
this hill of playing Fallout 76? What do you mean? I don't want to play it. I don't want to play
Fallout 76. Isn't that just a personal preference of game that I like? You would play it. Why not?
I never was a big Fallout fan. Not really. There are two franchises that I have close to zero
experience with. One of them is Fallout and the other one is Assassin's Creed. Those are two
franchises that I have very close to zero experience with the entire franchise. Fix that.
Play it. I did play New Vegas. I played Fallout three a tiny bit. I played Fallout four a little,
but not. We're talking all of those experiences, even Fallout New Vegas. We played it for a couple
of days and then I just started spawning easy peets and it was over. That was it. I got a lot
of room up here. This so badly wants me to keep you. Why is the tutorial for the smelter still
there? OK, maybe I have to make some more stuff. But anyways, all right. How much stock do I have?
Can you spawn easy peet now? Um, no, dude. Sorry. I want to make firewood stockpile. No.
Plank stockpile. What do I wish I make? Hole stockpile. I'm just gonna serve gruel. Fuck it.
I'm sorry. Um, let's go for it. I have plenty of beer. I have plenty of the stew,
porridge or whatever. Can I put porridge on tap? No, unfortunately. Oh, I gotta plant these trays
before I keep going. It only needs a certain area. Oh, it's good. OK. All right. Well, those
will grow. It's pretty good. What about quests? Quests. Quests. That's a weird word to say.
I want everyone to just say quests out loud. Quests. It's kind of weird, isn't it? A lot of
quests. Stop saying it so much. No, but like quests. All right. It's time to open. Did I just?
Oops. All right. We're open. Come on in. What can I do for you? Gruel? You got it. I need more
tables. Nope. Shit. All right. Thank God half of you only want gruel. I need employees too, don't I?
What do you want? Customers being rowdy. They're marked with a angry face. Press A next to them
to try to calm them down. Who's rowdy? Calm down. OK, OK. I'll pipe down. Do I have to throw people
out? Can there be fights in here? You should encourage it. All right. Let me. Here, just
put that there. I'm going to need to make. I have enough beer, I think, to last another few days.
Buy a table. Yeah, I think I have to make it. Can I buy the tables or do I have to make a table?
Shit. There you go. Stop cleaning the table when they're eating at it. It's weird.
Well, would you rather be all right? Would you rather go to a restaurant and have the table be
disgusting and have someone come over and clean it? Or would you rather it just not get addressed
at all? Hey, I feel like I would want to just I would want it to be addressed.
Oh, somebody's getting somebody's getting rowdy. Calm down. When was the last time you ate gruel?
Uh, I had oatmeal not that long ago. It's not like it was ages ago.
Crash and bottom left. I didn't even see it. Thank you.
More ale? Here you go. You want some more?
You should really eat a lot of gruel. You want more? This this this shit's probably good then.
I make a I make a mean gruel. Pilk and gruel on the menu.
I mean, pretty dirty in here. No, it's not. I mean, their table over here is dirty. Yours
isn't. Yours is immaculate. Oh, calm down. Calm down. This guy's had a few. I think I'm going
to close up in a minute. I have 30 silver. I thought you wanted a beer. Oh, new items and
mechanics. I leveled up brewing and cooking tech trees. All right. We're closed, closed.
Wait, what? Wait, what? Why can I use this as a weapon? I don't know you could swing.
All right. Bye. 30 bucks. Why are you closing your bar at 4 p.m.? Because I need I need to I'm not
ready. I'm not ready. I have like a tech tree now is how you learn new recipes.
Each tech cost skill points which is earned from crafting physical nature and mental.
Oh, God. All right. So mild ale order, pale logger, mead, mead. Oh, I need OK.
So I need to I have one point with the red crystal. I need two blue and two green.
We'll go in mead. We're doing the mead tree. Porridge to soup, roasting, sausages.
I kind of feel like I want to do sausages and mead. I think that's the tree I want to go down.
Let's just make wine and cider eventually, too. Yeah, definitely the bottom part of the tree.
No soup on tap. I don't even I don't think you can't do that.
Soup, stew. Oh, I do like a good stew, though. A nice hearty stew.
Well, we have to we're here anyway, so we're either going this way or that way.
All right. Sir, five bowls of porridge. Craft 10 iron nails. All right. I can probably do that soon.
I need iron. I need fuel. I need one more. OK, I need I need fuel. 15 fuel. My goodness.
Small batch draft micro stew. I need to I need more materials. We're going.
This is a material day. Materials only. Do I have an energy meter or no?
I think it's time. Looks like it's just time. Is there a town? I think there is.
At least it looks like it. Yeah, I think there is a meter at the bottom right.
I think that's experience. Yeah, that's that's the XP, I think.
Collect water. I need a bucket. Shit, how do I get a bucket?
Town, town, town, town. Don't waste time on the grass.
One of my favorite parts of Stardew Valley was just cutting the grass.
So I really hate to tell you that that's one of my favorite parts about this game.
Walking around and clearing a new area was part of the fun for me.
Lawn mower Larry, I think something happens to you when you hit a certain age.
Let me tell you, let me be very, very honest with you.
You I think you hit a certain age and then you just go like, yeah, like,
I don't know something about cutting grass. That sounds kind of awesome.
That's that's an interesting day. I don't know why. I don't know why.
I used to hate the notion of, no, I don't know, cut the grass.
I don't want to cut the grass. And now I'm just sitting there thinking like,
yeah, cutting grass, planting. I want to plant some fucking tomatoes.
Oh, you know what I think I'll do this year? Green bell peppers.
To me, that's excitement. I fucking scare.
Scarce. OK, I'm looking I can't say that because it's not true,
but I think it's funny to say anyway, so I'm going to say it.
I'm looking forward to this season's tomatoes that I'm going to plant
than the Elden Ring DLC. Is that fucked up?
Is that like bad? Like I'm looking forward to the sunflower harvest
more than like the next Call of Duty. Is that like weird?
I don't know. That seems like funny to say that.
But this is, I mean, that's arguably just completely not true.
OK, I need I did the quest, right?
Craft a small table using the workbench.
Ooh, where? I need a new table.
That's the workbench, right? Have I not on?
Oh, wait a minute. What's? Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa.
Something has appeared in my inventory. Oh, I don't like it there better.
I don't like this. I need to move this.
I hate it. Oh, I hate it.
Give me this too much space on the right. I hate it.
Wooden jug. What is this for?
Small bench. All right, individual.
OK, I need a I want another small table for lonely people.
An individual table. 30 cents.
I think I want to save to get the bigger one, right?
Two more nails. What's the quest for?
It is a small table. All right, so I need two more nails.
Damn it. Oh, I can make it.
OK, we're good. Do a gardening stream.
I mean, that's a kind of a nice idea.
Maybe let me ask you guys genuinely speaking and be honest.
I don't want people to be dishonest.
If I were to let's just say for the sake of argument,
have a portion like so let's say like once a week,
we check on the garden and we just kind of plant stuff.
That's something that you guys would actually think was kind of interesting to do
just to kind of relax and be like, hey, look, this is kind of how it looks.
Hey, here are the bell peppers. Here are the sunflowers.
Here's how they're doing. That'd be fun.
Agricultural stream.
And these streams would not be long.
They would be just check in on the garden streams.
Oh, shit. Wait, the bar is open.
It's been open. Oh, no, thank God.
I was like, the bar is still open. What is this?
Unironically, that would be something I would look forward to.
Huh. Maybe I'll think about doing it.
You know, make your bed. No.
I mean, I've always had this theory that I only make my bed
if I know that there's going to be company over it,
that I'm going to want a tour of your place.
Oh, let me give you the tour.
So here, you know, hey, this is where I'm living.
Yeah. Okay. Come on.
Oh, there's the bad areas.
It's the it's the you're giving a tour to somebody that has not been over yet.
And they're just peeking in for a second.
Oh, wow. Wow. Interesting.
Okay. So that's where you sleep.
Wow. Pretty much it.
All right. I need to make my table.
I have a cat. Where do I get a cat?
Okay. How about I like that.
I like that. I like I like this one.
A cat has wandered into your tavern.
I guess it lives here now.
Buy a bed and a water bowl to keep it happy.
Oh, well, we have to do that.
We have to make sure this is going to be fine.
All right. How do I do that?
I haven't even left my fucking house.
I need to go see what's in the town.
Do you know what I mean?
I'm sitting here. I haven't bought anything.
I've you buy it in the mailbox.
That's true. Where is it?
All right. Order.
Every five days, five random ingredients
will be available to order marked with a star.
Some ingredients can be farmed
after unlocking them in the farming tech tree.
Butter. Potatoes.
You probably make your own booze.
That's kind of interesting.
All right. I need it.
First of all, I need a thing for the cat.
Cat bowl. 20 silver for this.
20? That's all my money.
What about cat food?
Can I serve cat food to people?
I know the answer is definitely no,
but it's worth it.
It's worth the question.
Cat bed. Cat bed. 25.
That's all I don't have.
I can't even afford it.
Well, at the very minimum,
let's at least get the bowl, the water.
Okay. I need to make my table.
Open the damn tavern and make some money.
Yeah. I'm trying to make money
because I'm trying to make a sec.
I need a second table.
That means more customers can be served.
That means more money.
That means more ingredients.
All right. I think I have enough.
I need five more of these
and that'll be it.
And I can make the table.
That means better pizza.
I might be able to make better pizza.
What about benches too?
Oh, that's right. Good call.
That's true.
It's going to take an hour and 10 minutes.
I'm not opening until I have it.
What about a stool?
I can't even make a stool.
Oh, wooden planks and iron nails.
All right. I need more iron and more.
All right. I can do that.
Okay. I need more wooden planks.
Good. I'm not opening the store yet.
You were reincarnated as an animal
with all of your memories.
What animal would you want to be?
There's a couple of really interesting answers
to that question.
I would, I mean, is tortoise a weird answer?
Because they live to be like a hundred.
You don't want to say any kind of insect
because most insects live very, very short lives.
It's like, oh yeah, I'm going to realize
I'm going to be I would love to reincarnate as a spider
like with all your memories
and you just, that's not long enough.
What's an animal that lives a long time?
Tortoises live a long time.
Don't elephants live a long time?
Parrots live a long time.
Yep. Some birds live a long time.
That's right. One of those.
Maybe a bird, some type of bird.
One of those birds I can, you know,
I want to be intelligent too.
Okay. I can unlock the crafting room.
Done. You make.
All right. So to make a bench, I need these.
I need fuel to do that.
I'm running out. I need more wood.
Candle holder.
I'll make one of these too. Why not?
What is this thing?
The oldest tortoise was thought to be over 430 years old.
Oh my God. What is this?
What if this is, this is new.
It's to make firewood.
Ooh, now we can actually have the, yeah, that's going to be better.
My birthday on Monday. Say happy birthday to me.
Happy birthday.
I feel, I don't know if I'd want to be a turtle though, a tortoise.
I feel like I, I just need to move so fast.
Like I'm all, I feel like moving really slow would drive me crazy.
It would definitely be a bird.
Birds can just make noises and shit and it's completely fine.
It's totally normal and expected.
Birds just going like, it's like, oh no, no, look, that's normal.
That's a bird.
Like, of course that bird's doing that.
Right. I could just do that whenever I felt like it.
Yeah. Nobody's going to be mad that I did that.
Like a bunch of you just got mad right now, for instance.
For instance, some of you just got very angry with me.
If I was a bird, you would be like, that's normal.
That's a normal bird behavior.
So I don't care. Should I buy these?
No. All right. So what do I need to make this?
Okay. I have, I need two more batches of nails and then that.
I need more fucking fuel.
Two more batches of nails.
And then I need to make those wooden sticks.
20 of them. Okay.
Well, being a human certainly has its perks.
Wait, what is this? This is long.
Being human has its perks.
The majestic albatross offers several advantages to make it a compelling alternative.
For starters, albatross are incredible flyers
capable of traveling thousands of miles in a single journey.
Their long lifespans of up to 60 years also make them ideal for those seeking longevity.
In addition, albatrosses are known to mate for life, forming strong bonds and that endure.
Where did you get this? What is this?
Well, being human certainly has its perks.
The alternative of being an albatross, where did you get that?
I, I, I, it's alternative.
Oh, look what I can do.
Small table.
And then I need two more batches of nails and two more batches of wooden planks.
You go through fuel so much. It's crazy.
I guess I can start using the coal.
I need more iron.
All right, coal is worth a lot. I'm going to do 100.
Okay, we're good.
Professor Oak.
That was a professor Oak ass answer.
It's like 2 p.m. and I haven't opened the bar yet.
Well, whatever.
Professor Oak.
Albatross just got here talking about albatrosses.
They're very goofy guys.
Say more things about them.
Albatross Andy.
You can't, all right, hold on.
I'm not Albatross Andy for, I was reading a comment.
Play the game.
I'm, I'm, I'm, I gotta wait for this because I want to build the bench.
The quest that I have is to have a small table and then have a bench next to it.
What about the cat?
Cat's fine.
See, I'm going to redecorate this place.
This place sucks.
This is a coaster.
I'm a square coaster guy myself.
I feel like it's a little more surface area for drips.
Okay, that's good.
Here, play graveyard keeper.
I have not.
All right, I'm going to, not going to light the fire.
Crafting room.
Unlock the crafting room for $40, 10, and 11.
No, I don't, this is my house.
Why can't I just walk in?
Okay, I'll get it right now.
Table's going to be done.
Okay, bench, small bench.
We're good.
In the meantime, I'm going to do this stuff.
I said, respond.
You know, I'm just going to walk over here.
I can't.
Oh, there we go.
Should do a charade stream.
No talking and chat has to guess what I'm doing.
That's not a bad idea.
That's kind of funny.
This needs to grow back.
Emote only for the streamer.
Speaking of Breath of the Wild,
you guys played charades with me during Breath of the Wild.
Let me just make sure.
All right, this, there is a town.
All right, I'll probably get a map eventually.
This is all, look at all this.
Should I break this?
I'm going to smash this stuff.
Can I, it's a dock.
Okay, it does seem to be an outside world.
Just checking.
Why the Doritos?
They're referencing when I couldn't figure out
that the Lost Woods, whatever the hell it was
in Breath of the Wild, kind of about 45 minutes
to an hour walking in a circle and people screamed at me.
It was very embarrassing.
And I have not played the game since, but that's not true.
All right, it's time to not open.
Here we go.
Now make another bench.
Shit.
Okay, make another bench?
I can do it, I can do it, I can do it.
I just need nails.
Yep, okay.
Fuel.
I'm going to make a ton of nails.
I might as well.
And then do I have the wood for this?
Wooden planks.
What time is it?
Getting late.
What's going on up here?
Clive and Rochelle wanted to detonate the ice block
to gain access to the mine.
How can they dare to suggest such a thing?
I understand that Brock is furious about detonating the ice.
But what else can we do?
Chief Petra is going to kill me when she finds out.
Oh, hold on.
What time is bedtime?
Is horse riding in Fistful of Frags?
We'll definitely go back to that one of these days.
I imagine for sure.
All right, I gotta go.
Is pass out time midnight in this game
or is it one, two, three o'clock in the morning, I wonder?
Oh, remind me to get a bucket.
No, wait.
Come on, hurry up.
I'm going to do two benches.
I feel like I need it.
And then I'm going to wake up in the morning and be ready.
I do have the cat bowl.
Let me put it down.
What?
No, the cat bowl is in here.
Okay, here you go.
How about right?
I want you away from customers.
You know what I mean?
No, I want you right here.
That's good.
All right, I need water.
This is a lot bigger than I thought it was going to be.
Uh, where does this go?
I need to put candles in here.
I'm going to sneeze and I apologize in advance.
Ooh, nice.
Okay, what else?
I have that table now.
I got two small tables.
This place is going to be flooded with people now.
Um, I think that's all right.
I need more benches.
Have this one.
Way more people are going to show up.
Okay, that's good enough.
I at least want them to set it.
At least have one at each table, right?
That makes the most sense.
All right, we are closed.
Good night.
Getting up in the morning.
First thing I'm doing is opening.
Can you explain how this game is any different than Doom Eternal?
Yeah, sure.
Good.
It's not in this game.
It is in the other one.
It's a pretty major difference.
Okay, I'm we're working today.
I'm opening the store.
We're open.
Oh, shit.
Hold on.
I was supposed to close it immediately.
I got to throw all this bullshit in my inventory.
Oh, I can't place it when it's open.
All right.
Well, whatever.
I'm just going to I'm ready.
Is there enough beer?
We always get girl.
It's fine.
I need employees.
This place is going to this place is going to get trashed really soon.
That's just okay.
Somebody's pissed.
Why are you so pissed off?
What?
The customer has become a nuisance.
They will annoy everyone around them.
Hit them with your mop to kick them out of your tavern.
Are you serious?
That's so fucked up.
That is already just getting beat with a mop
in the middle of your enjoyable gruel luncheon.
Let me take care of that quickly for you.
Yeah, this is a dirty mop, too.
This is not a clean mop.
You know what?
This would not hurt as much as it would be a total imagine.
Get imagine a wet mop like all the little pieces of mop would just kind of mold around
your face and around your head.
It would be fucking awful.
It would be terrible.
And it would spray everywhere.
Wouldn't it just water splash everywhere?
It would be terrible.
We're making money.
I'm so glad that we're mostly you just.
All right.
You just took that.
You bought that gruel and threw it on the ground.
You should definitely clean.
You should clean that up.
I just handed it to you.
Oh, oh, it's funny.
You grow the car out.
It's always served.
Nobody wants any beer from the tavern.
They just want.
Oh, there we go.
Why I beer is what makes this.
I want more of that.
Come on.
Warm food and a cold drink.
This place has made my day.
It makes me happy.
Here, give us a good review.
Just leave out of the review.
And I hit that guy in the face with a web mop.
We don't need you don't need to write that part running back and forth.
I must know how you clean this place.
I want to speak to the barkeep.
Oh, what's wrong?
Wait, what's he doing?
What was he supposed to do?
That guy, he just he went behind.
That guy was like menacingly going to like hurt that guy.
Why did he do that?
He was trying to start a fight with that guy.
Why I always wanted to see what happened.
He went to a random party at the bar and just started like trouble.
I want to speak to the bartender.
Just kidding.
I want to punch this old guy.
Yeah, I'm not closing.
We need to make at least 50.
You beat a paying customer.
I'm sorry, but I don't care how much how much money you're spending in here.
You're not going to you're not going to fuck with the other patrons.
Sorry, that's not how it works.
You need to close and find your cat.
Where's the cat?
This place is bollocks.
Okay.
All right.
I'm sorry.
I'll be quiet.
Hey, barkeep.
This place sucks.
Hey, come on.
You know, I'm sorry about that.
You're right.
I'm sorry.
I probably should have been a little more courteous.
Is there no beer left?
Stop.
Nobody's even order.
Why are they all getting so there's no alcohol being served?
It's they get there.
Oh, you know, this person drank like too much beer and now they're like
drunken and being rowdy.
No, they're eating gruel only.
They're not why I had a little too much gruel and I'm fucking mad.
It's fermented gruel.
Is there no beer?
Oh my goodness.
That's what's going on.
Where's the cat?
I don't know.
I don't know where the cat went.
What time is it?
Is it two or three o'clock in the morning?
What day is it?
I don't know what time it is.
It's 2 p.m.
Why do I feel like it's 2 a.m.
Upper left.
Yeah.
All right.
Everybody get out of here.
I got to find my cat.
Oh, wait.
Oh, your tavern has become cold.
It wasn't cold before.
Way too hot in here.
Wait, what?
What do you mean?
It's way too hot in here.
It just told me to do that.
You're smoking everybody out.
But why is it too hot?
It just said it was too cold.
Turn the fire off.
No, I like it like this.
Okay.
Fifty three bucks.
Unlock the crafting room.
Your tavern is cold.
This is your crafting room.
Let's make some porridge.
I have so much porridge already.
Bucket with water.
Okay.
So I just need a bucket of water?
That sounds awful.
Extra ingredients.
Some recipes have mandatory modifiers.
Porridge requires a grain.
Barley porridge.
I want seeds in it.
I just put seeds in this.
Where's the cat?
Cat's right here.
There it is.
Cat's fine.
Porridge.
Now let's brew some beer.
Need a malting machine?
Start crafting malted barley.
So malted barley.
So I need barley and water.
I need fuel in here.
Malting takes a while.
You can reopen your tavern and serve porridge while you wait.
Have I not even had porridge an option?
Porridge has not even been a food option.
I was wondering why we're only serving gruel.
I don't have any cat food.
The cat's fine.
The cat's got water.
I need to get a cat bed eventually.
All right.
I'm going to open this door again.
This time I got more options.
Yeah.
I got plenty of porridge.
I got plenty of beer.
Let's go.
Porridge.
Oh, I do have porridge.
There we go.
Finally.
This is making way more money.
I was going to say, why am I serving gruel?
Five bowls of porridge.
I got a rug.
I'm already making way more money.
What's wrong?
Calm down.
All right.
I'm just making four.
Can I put them on the bar?
They don't go bad, right?
Do they go bad?
They do go bad.
Okay.
So I can't just pre-pour a dozen of them.
You can pre-pour.
Nothing will expire.
Actually kind of seems like that.
All right.
I'm going to do it all though.
Somebody just said, I love spreading misinformation.
Well, stop.
Don't do that.
Get out of here.
It's too dark in here.
It's dark in here.
Is it really that dark?
I guess there's one source of light.
All right.
I'm going to close pretty soon here.
Here.
Here, here, here.
I got it, I got it, I got it.
I already got it.
I'm doing it.
Look.
Better.
It's cold in here.
Everybody good?
Everybody's good.
46 bucks.
How many more of these do I have?
I got plenty.
I'm also going to beer.
All right.
I'm officially out of alcohol.
I got to close.
I'm done.
Do I have to hit everybody or will they?
Because when they stand up like that, it goes.
It usually means somebody's about to get in a fight.
Hey.
What's with all the bad reviews?
Bad reviews?
For what?
What did I do so bad?
Hey.
Be lucky we ain't selling gruel anymore.
I got better reviews when people were eating slop.
Bring the gruel back.
It was way better.
Yeah.
I made a nice stew and people say gross.
This stew sucks.
Bring the gruel back, bro.
Okay.
Create wort by boiling grains.
Place the mash ton and create some mild wort.
Check back later when it's finished.
Oh, my goodness.
Cool.
Why mild wort?
Some malted barley, bitter hops, and three buckets of water.
I need more coal.
All right.
I need more beer.
I'm out.
I'm almost out of beer.
You fell off.
Plus ratio plus gruel.
All right.
What else do I got?
Another candle holder.
What is this?
Empty keg.
Oh, I guess I can fill it.
I don't know what to do with that, really.
Okay.
All right.
So I got to make.
How long does it take?
Takes a pretty long time.
I can make some more barley.
I mean, I can make some more.
Yeah, I'll make some more stew.
Yeah, I'll just make everything.
All right.
Time for bed.
Tomorrow's a resource day.
Speaking of resources, I should keep that out.
I guess I'm not stressing for space at the moment, so I'll be fine.
All right.
Bed time.
What do I think of the game so far?
I think it's fun.
It's pretty cozy.
Let me restock this.
Okay.
Yeah.
So now I don't.
What about trends?
Oh, I can't do that yet.
Remember when Jerma talked about one of his ingrown nose hairs coming out the other side?
Yes, it's actually kind of cold.
And I'll keep it going.
Yeah.
For those of you that don't know, this happened twice.
This is not something that happened once.
This happened on two distinct occasions years apart from each other.
So yeah, I was gross or whatever.
I'm just going to talk about it real quick.
So inside of one of my nostrils on the inside, not the outside.
One of my nose hairs, it was like it just was painful inside of my nose.
And I don't want to skip this because I want to read this,
but I'm going to go quick.
So I had a really painful area inside my nose and I was like, what is going on?
And it was like, ah, this hurts in here.
And it was like, it's probably like an ingrown nose hair.
Fuck, whatever.
So a week goes by or so.
And I started getting a painful bump on the outside on the front of my nose.
And it was just, what is going on?
This hurts so bad.
Another little bit went by and I'm telling you,
this nose hair went through the other side of my face.
It ingrown haired out the other side through my whole nose.
Crazy.
It was like, how was this impossible?
How did you get it out?
Eventually it just came out.
I could pull it out from the front.
It was wild.
That's a very, oh yeah.
That's so ingrown.
It came off the other side.
All right.
Oh, I skipped it.
I skipped it, I skipped it, I skipped it, I skipped it.
I didn't want to.
Oh no, it's in the corner.
Okay.
Fermentation tank.
I need a better spot for this stuff.
All right, let me put this down.
Let me move this out of the way.
Put this in the corner.
Put this next to the bed for all I care.
No, I need to put it in the order that it happens, right?
Okay.
For the last stage, fermentation.
Place the fermentation tank and create some mild ale.
You can add modifiers such as fruit and hops
and give your beer a custom name.
Ooh, mild ale, aroma hop.
Wait, I'm gonna make it like berries or something.
Add gruel to it.
Yeah, can I?
I don't, I don't think I, no, I can't.
But this is aroma hops and bitter hops.
That sounds kind of cool to me.
All right, this is a resource day.
I need to collect resources and need to build some more stuff.
Another day without feeding the cat or giving it a bed.
Hold on, hold on.
I want butter.
Butter, chili, gruel and honey and chili and butter.
Cat bed, $25.
This is wiping out my bank account.
I need staff, butter.
It takes a few hours for it to get here so I can do other stuff.
Right, it's a resource day.
You guys are distracting me.
It's a resource day.
Ingrown nose hair grotto beast expansion, when?
Do you actually have to feed the cat?
I don't think there's cat food, is there?
Feed the cat, where do I get the cat food?
I'll do it, just wait.
I need to, I don't know, I need to get it.
I need to find a place to get it.
There's no mechanic to feed the cat.
You guys, who do you want to vote?
Remind me to do this every so often because I will forget.
Ooh, there we go.
Deforestation to build parking lots.
I'm replanting.
Parking lots?
This is a...
I just want to share a little wood.
I don't want to cut it for a while.
That's why you do a resource day.
Hates polar bears.
This tavern is really shitty.
Converted into a TGI Fridays.
This tea is...
Are those places good?
I feel like it's been so long since I've even sat down at a place like that.
No, people saying no.
But then, are people going?
People have to still be going.
The business still has to be doing okay.
You know, I feel like a lot of those restaurants
they're so consistent with what they have and what's on the menu and how it tastes.
I'm trying...
I can remember distinctly what it tastes like to get a food item from a Chili's or a TGI Fridays.
I know what it's like.
I know exactly what it's like.
And 10, 20, 30 fucking years later, it's going to be the exact same, isn't it?
That's not really a bad thing.
It's really not a bad thing.
If you really think about that.
Okay, I know exactly what it's going to be like in there.
There's no variables.
I know exactly what it is.
Stop cutting the grass.
I do what I want to do and you do what you want to do.
There's nothing else available.
It's fine in a pinch.
Yeah, I think that it's fine to operate it that way.
I feel like a lot of people go there for that reason.
Aren't those restaurants really, really kid-friendly too?
That consistency carries over with young kids, right?
Yeah, so it definitely has like a pretty good purpose.
You have the palette of a 10-year-old.
Hey, man, I never told you.
Huh?
I'm telling you, I haven't eaten here.
I haven't eaten at TGI Fridays.
I don't even have a memory of eating at one.
It's been a very long time making chocolate chip cookies.
That sounds awesome.
I want to do more of that.
I want to bake brownies and stuff.
I feel like I want to connect more with the world.
You know what I mean?
I want to bake fucking brownies.
I want to bake cookies.
That's a great idea.
I'm just going to get the materials.
I'm going to get the milk, the flour, the eggs,
chocolate sauce and powder, whatever.
Let's do it.
I need to connect more with the world.
I want to get this to a clean 100 and I'm done for a month.
Replant the trees.
I will.
Beauty does that.
Beauty does do that.
It's like, it's cool.
I'm so paranoid though when it comes to anything.
I'm the type of person that if a burger is,
make sure to cook it for two to four minutes
aside.
I will freak out and be like, it's not done.
Is it done?
How red is it in the middle?
Get a meat thermometer.
Is it 140 degrees?
How many degrees is it in the middle?
I will crack the egg sort of slightly incorrectly
and just rage quit.
The egg will break and a shell will get in
and I'll just be like, I'm done.
I'm done.
I fucked it up.
It's over.
I fucked it.
Everything's messed up and I'm done.
Drama queen.
I would be such a bad contestant on a cooking show.
I would crumble if Gordon Ramsay came over to me
and said anything.
I would crumble.
But that's not how you crack an egg, you donkey.
Gordon, I'm just going to leave.
Gordon, this is a really fun experience.
I've been here for five minutes.
I'm going to leave.
Thank you.
Appreciate the opportunity to be on kitchen craziness.
But I'm going to leave now.
Are you going to leave?
You can't just leave.
He's leaving.
And then it would be like,
while I walked out and I'd be like,
give me the fuck out of here as fast as I can.
He's leaving.
And everyone's just laughing and making fun of me.
And I'm just walking.
Just give me my fucking car and get me out of here.
I would be out of there in a second.
And then the fart reverb version of that weird violin sound would play.
And then as I'm leaving, I would be the idiot.
I would back into a pole.
I would be like, I'd back up.
I'm getting out of here.
I've got to leave.
And I would be slowly back up and hit a pole.
And it's like, fucking goddamn it.
I don't know how the cameras are going to come out here.
And it's going to be like, what did he do?
Oh, that idiot.
He backed up into a pole.
Oh, yeah.
Let's go talk to him.
And I'd be looking out the window.
Hey, Gordon, I'm just trying to get out of here, man.
What are you doing?
You're backed into the pole.
I'm so sorry, Gordon.
I'm sorry I cracked the egg wrong.
Please don't hit me.
And please delete all this footage.
And then they would edit it to make me look like a fucking maniac.
All right.
At least I have fuel.
Let's get this all to 100, or at least high enough.
You know, Gordon Ramsay is mostly playing a character.
Yeah, of course.
All right, everybody.
We can all collectively relax.
Everybody just chill.
I have the cat fed.
There we go.
By the window?
Yeah, I don't want to.
Yeah, I want it to be a nice, comfortable place.
All right, that's better.
I got some more stuff, too.
I want to make like a buttered chili pepper beer.
Congratulations.
You have brewed your first beer.
Experiment with new ingredients to create your perfect brew and food.
Time to farm.
The first thing you'll have to do is clear the grass of an area of land with a shovel.
Oh, all right.
What kind of beer?
I need to make some barley.
So this is where I need to make it.
All right, I'm going to say over here, take a little section like this.
Oh, shit.
Okay, now plant.
What am I planting?
I need seeds.
Barley seeds, rye seeds, wheat.
I want corn.
Five, let's do 10, 20.
I need 20 spots.
Corn is overrated.
Corn is like one of the reasons why modern society developed into the way it did, isn't it?
Isn't corn one of the most important pieces of agriculture ever?
It is?
Yeah, it is.
Okay, now the land is free of grass.
It's time to till like the hoe and till the land where you are going to cultivate your plants.
In America, yes, but not the rest of the world.
And it's still very important.
The amount of things that are made with corn are unbelievable.
It's like, really?
That's a lot of stuff.
Really?
Okay, now I got to get my seeds.
How many spots do I need?
I need more than that.
Tobacco as well.
Yes, tobacco as well.
I was just going to get it for free.
How many spots is this?
Yeah, you would know about tobacco.
Cigarette.
Cigarette meme has kind of really...
What?
The cigarette meme.
Isn't that...
Why is that a thing now?
What happened here?
What's going on here?
What's happening here?
It's because I've shown myself like smoking fake cigarettes.
What is with the cigarette?
That's like a thing that has really gotten popular recently.
Don't...
You've seen it too, haven't you?
I've noticed it.
Have you seen it too?
He still doesn't get it.
I'm going to go this way.
How many does...
I got to count this.
Okay, so we've got 1, 2, 3, 4, 5, 6, 7, 8, 9, 10, 11, 12, 13, 14, 15, 16, 17, 18, 19, 20, 21, 22, 23, 24, 25, 26, 27, 28, 29, 30, 31, 32, 33, 34, 35, 36, 37, 38, 39, 40.
I want it to be...
Wait, what's going on here?
Did I do something wrong?
Wait.
No, that's correct, right?
Yeah, this is the shape I wanted.
All right.
Now we just plant a shitload of these.
Crops will grow over time in three stages.
Once fully grown, harvest the crop with your sickle.
Where's my delivery?
You can't...
I bet you can't name 10 prime numbers.
Do you think I cannot name 10 prime numbers?
Well, I had to put my phone down because it's dead.
And I was going to kill some time while I looked it up.
But you're right, I can't.
It's late.
Oh, my God.
I was going to do the thing where I repeat the question
and then slowly talk and distract you while I look the thing up.
And then I say the thing while talking
immediately finishing a sentence or two.
So it's like, there's no way he looked it up.
He's been talking to us already.
Damn.
All right.
Hold on.
I need...
Where's my delivery?
There it is.
All right.
Let's get this planted.
Okay.
I will tell you, I thought this game was way more limited than I thought.
It's slowly kind of ripping in stuff to do.
I need more of these.
I need way more of those.
How many do I need?
One, two, three, four, five, six, eight, nine, 10, 11, 12, 30, 40, 15.
I need 15 more of those.
I want corn.
I don't want anything else.
Is this ready to harvest?
Not yet.
No, there's no corn on it.
Let's go.
I'm going to make...
So what do I actually want to do here?
What do I need?
I need more ale, which I have some up here.
Let's make a new thing here.
I need water.
How much water do I have?
All right.
I need water.
Should I get this game?
But that all depends if you like what you see.
I think the game's fun.
Scratching a couple of decent itches for me.
But that's a decision that you need to make.
I think it's pretty cool, but I'm not you.
Cat's heart is increasing.
I'm not ready to open.
Are you actually that moisturized or is that a lie?
That's got to be the stupidest thing I've ever heard to lie about.
I can't really think of very much that would be dumber to say than...
Yeah, I moisturize my face and I just don't.
Why even bring it up?
I can't think...
Why would I even bring it up?
That's such a strange thing to lie about.
Yeah, I like to moisturize.
I don't, though.
But if I just don't, this just doesn't make any sense.
Why even bring it up?
I have points to spend.
We're going to go the mead tree, right?
Cabbage.
Root?
Apples and pears?
Basic carpentry.
Large bench, large table.
Lighting.
Oil lamp.
I want to go...
Let's go mead.
Mead.
Wine is next.
And...
What about food?
Buy a wall calendar.
Plant 10 season heart.
Okay, so I need to buy a wall calendar.
I'm playing with the controller.
If a controller is available, I will play with it.
Playing games with the keyboard,
I think the last couple of years, I want to say, hurts my hands.
Not anything too extreme, but that WASD position,
and I really noticed it last night,
that WASD sometimes, and even the arrow keys,
can kind of cramp up my fingers for some reason.
So if analog is a lot...
Resting my hands sort of on my lap with the analog
is a lot easier for me at this point.
Okay, well, I needed to buy...
What was it?
A wall calendar.
I want a mental armor sack.
Probably going to need the scarecrow.
Could be arthritis.
It probably is.
I imagine it's something like that, probably.
There we go.
80!
No, thank you.
I'm not spending $80 on a wall calendar.
Does it have any game mechanic?
80 for a...
What does it do?
Maybe it will.
Does it do something?
Probably RSI, not arthritis.
Well, I don't want to speculate on what it is.
Yeah, what does it do?
No lewd pics.
What?
Just adds comfort.
Okay.
Well, that's...
Yeah, okay.
All right, plant.
Hey, it's full.
Why did I make all that corn?
Is it for a purpose?
This does take a long time.
Okay, I can make the mead.
The mead needs...
Oh, there is honey.
Wine yeast and an empty keg.
I have an empty keg.
Let me get some wine yeast.
I want mead.
You sold out to big corn.
Orange.
I got plenty of orange.
It's not worth it.
Okay, I want the empty keg.
So I have this.
I have this mild ale.
And oh goodness, I'm sorry.
But this one's going to be where I put the mead.
Mead is going to be one.
In the man of Medan stream, you used a controller,
but then in the next dark picture stream,
you mocked italics for using a controller
and proudly used a keyboard instead
because you were a proud PC gamer,
which then caused you to miss an important QTE
because your DPI settings were fucked up.
Yeah, that was so fucked up though.
Needing to move my mouse like 10 times.
That was really funny.
I'm glad it was funny because it was incredibly embarrassing.
Oh, I got to plant these trees.
Any more?
Cool.
Resource day or no?
You know, it's so funny about what we just said
and what we just talked about.
Some of you guys know this channel's history
more than I do.
Isn't that interesting?
Like specifically for streams,
I stream and I say a bunch of stuff
and we fuck around, we make some jokes.
Maybe I'll chill, we'll just talk,
we'll bring up stories, whatever we do.
We just kind of hang out, whatever it is.
That conversation is usually gone
from my brain a week or two later.
So there's almost like this encyclopedia
of things I've said that I don't even,
I remember talking about it for sure,
but I know it's not like up in the front of the brain.
It's funny to look back and have it be like,
oh yeah, I like using controllers.
I like them, it's much, much better.
Hey, three years ago,
you said that controllers were stupid
and people that used them were dumb.
And it's like, oh, I did.
I mean, I didn't mean to, I guess, I'm sorry.
You have talked about how corn is the basis
of civilization at least a few times already though.
All right, so I'm consistent on that.
That's good.
That's why you could be gaslit so easily.
Where's my wine?
I bought it.
I had to wait three hours.
Finally, I want to make mead.
Didn't you say that corn grew on trees before?
Hold on, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait.
No, stupid idiot.
Can I cancel it and get it back?
I didn't, I wanted to add ingredients to that.
I just put like basic ass bullshit in that.
No, I never believed that corn grew on trees.
I tell jokes.
It says cancel.
I know it does, but I just want to fucking.
I don't think that corn grows on trees.
I think a lot of people,
some people take the things that I say on the stream sometimes.
Some people believe that I think that corn grows on trees.
You know what I mean?
Like, no, I promise you, I don't.
You don't tell good jokes.
I never said the quality of them.
You said I do.
That's for you to decide, not me.
What do you actually believe about bananas?
That they are a nice snack and slightly ripe bananas
are I think better than I'm a big fan of.
Slightly ripe bananas, bananas are a good snack.
That's it.
Oh, Pog.
Oh my God.
Yeah, he loves bananas.
Do I have enough?
I need this mead to hurry up.
I'm just gonna go to bed.
I'm just gonna wake up and it'll be done.
Nice.
All right, I got mead.
I've ruined everything, unfortunately,
because I need an empty keg.
I guess I'm going to buy honey
and I'm going to put the empty keg in here.
Because I want to add chili peppers to it and all this stuff.
I have that, so I need, I have, I already have an empty keg.
I need honey.
I think I can open the store, though.
Yeah, I, I, I, yeah.
Let's open the store.
I already have this one on tap.
That was my, my mild brew.
And we can put the mead in here.
Several unique items in stock.
The more unique items you have in stock,
the more reputation and money you'll earn.
This only counts the base item, ignoring any modifiers.
Okay, well, that's good.
I got plenty of porridge.
Make sure the tables are set in the right way.
I could make another bench, but open.
Does Holly ever remind you of stuff
that you have said that you forgot?
Yes.
For instance, you guys will like this one.
Oh shit.
What is it?
This one?
Um, my mother sent me a message the other day.
Would you like to know what it said?
It said, face cam or riot.
It is my mother.
And I was just like, uh, ma, hold on.
She's one of us.
You got to do it for ma, do it for ma.
Hey, I was on face cam yesterday.
All right, I'm making way more money.
All right, come on, hurry up and give me a good rating.
The best meat in this whole town.
Thank you.
Is it good?
How's the stew?
How's the smell in here?
No keg.
Oh, is it cold?
Oh shit.
The meat is popular.
Meat is very popular.
Wait till I add a little bit of spices in it.
Yes, I'll wipe your table.
Just wait.
This shit is flying off the shelves.
This one's pretty good.
Oh, no one's bought a single meat.
Nevermind.
Am I supposed to take my shoes off in here?
What?
One feels like a noble here.
I'm the best.
I want to speak to the barkeep.
What's wrong?
I want to...
Nobody touched that corn outside, by the way.
Ladies and gentlemen, I have an announcement to make.
If anybody touches the corn outside, you're dead.
All the corn is gone tomorrow, by the way.
I wake up and it's all gone.
What do you think?
100 silver would probably do it.
How's the temperature?
Too hot?
I got it.
Bro, it grows on trees.
Chill.
Where's the nearest poplar?
Is it gone?
Close it up?
No.
I'm not closing it until at least 100.
I think I need more money.
I'll try to make another couple of stuff to do fermentation.
It's only noon.
I'll probably run out of product before then, though.
How much is left?
I'm just going to go to these both.
I'm going to go till I sell everything.
I think that's the play.
Do I have a favorite season?
Not really.
I like winter and I like summer.
Fall in Vegas is really, really nice.
It's not hot, but it's just kind of nice out.
If I were to take...
I don't know.
I'm not like a big spring person.
I like it.
I don't know why.
I like the cold, crispy air of fall and winter.
And I like the heat and kind of outdoor, kind of hot stuff.
I like the outdoor heat of summertime.
I like spring.
Spring is nice.
Wouldn't a gardener love spring?
Yeah, but I mean, sunflowers...
When we grew the sunflowers, that was May, June, right?
Wasn't it like May?
That was like May, June, July.
Until like August.
That was summertime.
I'm so glad I'm actually making money now.
They grow in the spring too.
All I remember is I just need a lot of sun.
It is in the name, isn't it?
Right?
Oh, this is popular.
It grew.
All right, this is empty, so I got to sell out of the mead
and then we'll close up.
Sell out of everything.
Winter has really beautiful moments,
but it's overall dark and lonely.
You know, so the thing with winter,
something about getting up in the morning,
still really, really cold outside,
just having a hot cup of coffee just in your hands.
It's super cold.
Everything's really chilly, but you just,
you got that hot coffee, just hot cup of coffee right there.
It changes everything.
I really, coffee to me, it's not even,
I mean, maybe it is a little bit for the caffeine at this point,
because obviously I've been taking in caffeine
pretty much every single day for a long time.
But it's almost, I just, I like, I just love that.
Tea, you can do this with tea.
Tea hits a little differently for me though.
I would rather drink tea in the evening hours,
not in the morning.
Tea is an evening thing for me.
Nice, hot, just black coffee.
And it just, it just, it's got that scent.
It's just there.
It's just hot, steaming, freezing outside.
It's cold, absolutely rigid outside.
Sometimes, sometimes even just kind of go outside
with the coffee and just be one of those
cheesy commercial motherfuckers that has the bathrobe on.
You know what I mean?
Just like wearing their like morning clothes.
It's like, ah, and all those coffee commercials.
What's wrong?
It's a Hallmark movie.
All right, I'm out of, do I have any more porridge?
All right, we are out.
I've got two more of each and then I've got no more porridge.
The smell of coffee to me is what I like the most about it.
To me, smelling coffee and hearing like a coffee being brewed,
it doesn't matter what kind of coffee,
what kind of coffee machine you have
or whatever, if you have like a coffee maker,
it doesn't matter what kind.
That like, here it comes, like, and it's,
it's almost, it's like you opened up like the,
where the treats are for the dog.
It's like, what, what's that?
Coffee, somebody make, somebody making coffee.
Somebody's making coffee here.
I want one.
I love coffee.
It's too dark in here.
What happened to my candles?
All right, somebody buy the last two beers,
last four beers so I can close.
That coffee maker sound, then you all know the one.
Like that drip coffee that is one of those things
that just is one of the little things in life.
It's just, ah, yeah, that's a, that's great.
Whatever is going on right now.
You fucking weirdo, go outside.
I, you're acting like I just drink coffee
and sit in that, I don't just drink coffee.
What?
I'm talking about a morning routine.
I don't just make coffee and like, ah, ooh, yeah.
Like, hey, what's that?
Is that coffee being rude?
Like every 25 minutes?
I'm talking about starting the day.
I'm talking about you make coffee
and then you start your day
and you do whatever you're going to do.
No, the thing I say we're talking about right now
is not the only thing I do all day.
Oh, you know what?
Man, I love corn.
Corn's so great, isn't it?
All he does is eat corn.
It's the only thing he does.
He has corn just growing all over his house.
What's wrong with him?
Why does he just only eat corn?
He has corn.
This corn, he has corn and he literally is,
he's sitting on a furniture made out of corn.
No, I just like corn.
We're talking about coffee.
Somebody buy this.
I don't want four beers just sitting here.
Character upgrades.
What's that?
Hold on.
I don't have any candles left.
I have to make some new ones, I think.
Everybody get out.
I think they have to order it if it's still on the tap.
Make sure to give us a good rating.
Plus one.
Is that even really a good rating?
All right, let me turn this off.
That was a good day.
I have almost two gold.
What about the germ of corn gift?
That's right.
There's a corn gift.
I need to sort this.
How do I get this off the screen?
Whoa.
All right, I need candles.
Make mead again and this time.
Ooh, here we go.
Ten seeds and harvest crops.
I got something for that.
I shall mine and none of it's for you.
What is this?
A grinder.
Grind cereals and other ingredients.
Yeah.
Where can I put this?
In the house?
Can I make the house bigger?
Okay, wheat flour, barley flour, rye flour.
Where's corn flour?
I don't want to buy that many candles.
I have to be able to make them, right?
You can't make beer from corn.
You can make other alcohols, though.
Isn't moonshine corn?
The corn mash can be.
Moonshine isn't beer.
You can probably make it in the game, though.
And it's a game about making alcohol.
All right, material dump time.
I want all right.
We're gonna make a ton of make a bunch of copper bars.
Good idea.
Bunch of screws.
Maybe a bunch of maybe some hinges and birdhouse.
Make a birdhouse, birdhouse.
This is kind of expensive.
It's actually really expensive.
We talked about the bird watching stream, right?
And I'm just going to give some stuff away.
It's not this train is probably never going to happen.
But like, maybe if it does, you'll be able to remember this.
I want to like the bird watching stream would like,
look, we're going to go on a bird watch.
And then, I don't know, like get like a Bigfoot sighting on camera.
And the rest of the stream turns into like there's Bigfoot.
And he's like fucking hunting us.
Don't tell anybody.
I think that's a fun idea.
This stream is not going to happen though.
It's fun to talk about things that would have been or may have been.
Time, time.
Here we go.
Barley going in.
That going in.
Mead going in.
But first, I'm going to make sure I have chili pepper, butter.
All right, chili pepper and butter in the mead.
Let's see if anybody pukes.
I can't.
Huh?
I don't think I can do it.
I can put honey in the mild ale.
That's probably maybe that's a good idea.
And what else can I do?
Serve cups of melted butter.
Oh, aroma hops.
I should probably get some aroma.
Bitter aroma dual hops.
Just mix it all together.
Who cares, right?
Just mix everything.
We're going to have we're going to have wicked bitter ale.
I'll buy candles too because people complain.
They're annoyingly.
Where are they?
Cobweb.
Where are the candles?
There you go.
I think alcohol is your next big merch idea.
No.
What are the quests right now?
Calendar.
It's the only thing I have.
I want a large table.
I need another bench.
Another bench.
And then I want to make this really, really good.
Do you have water?
OK, now I'm going to go to bed.
I might reload the game so people don't think it's always 3 a.m.
I don't like title screen.
Barley flower.
I have to probably level up or something.
I'm going to get my delivery and make some beer.
Craft up some beer.
Go to bed again.
OK, mead.
I want dual hops, aroma hops, and bitter hops.
I want this thing to be just all over the place.
I want people to take a sip out of this and go bananas, barley seeds, rye.
Should I do rye?
Hold on.
What's in the tree here?
This is white wine juice, white wine, white grape must, red wine juice, red wine.
I need one more blue.
OK, so this is wheat.
Wheat, rye, and cider.
Let me be able to make wheat beer.
I'm going to buy a bunch of wheat and plant it.
What was it?
Forty?
This stuff is cheap.
Shrimp and white wine.
Guys, remember, isn't there a scene where Tim and Eric are in the hospital or something
and the doctor comes in and he's like,
I just want to say we're really, really getting concerned about your white wine levels.
We want to bring those up to make sure they match the shrimp levels.
That was so funny.
Yeah, we're getting really concerned here.
Because they don't they like eat too much shrimp or something
and it's like, oh, wait, wait, sorry, we want to make sure we get you.
But we got to get your white wine levels up.
They're kind of talking as if it's like plasma or something or like white blood or red blood count.
Tim and Eric really did set the stage for that kind of humor.
I think they really kind of set the bar on a lot of that stuff in a way.
All right, I want my stuff.
Deliver it.
I want a plant.
I'm just going to sleep.
I'm going to go sleep.
Wake up and be ready to start the day.
I could go collect resources, but now I'm going to bed.
Twenty two hour nap.
Stuff like Steve rule to just kind of funny.
I have not kept up with any of those people or shows or anything really at all.
I remember like 10, 15 years ago, it was kind of like they were really
especially like 15 years ago.
All right, let's begin the process.
I want my deliveries.
This inventory is disgusting.
I hate it.
I need to clean this up.
It's just it's so messy.
I need to get I need to get my act together here.
There's no watering, right?
I feel like this could be a problem.
Here we go.
All right.
How do I get the cat to like me more?
I need water.
There we go.
All right, let's fill the tap.
This one is going to have two different brews, don't I?
No, I didn't start making it yet.
One's fine.
It's the one I wanted to buy anyways.
I think it's all right.
Can I make any new food?
Spend your experience upgrades for your character.
Cleaning speed increase.
Better bargaining, better price.
Yeah, that for sure.
Everything.
Yeah, better price, better price and faster cleaning.
Don't forget about the bench.
That's true.
I'll try not to feed the cat, feed the cat, feed the cat.
I swear I don't think you can.
Planks as the bench.
All right, now I'm going to make a birdhouse.
So I'm going to wait for these planks to get done
and I'm going to just build a birdhouse because why not?
The bird in here.
I've seen that make the rounds again.
Oh, there's a bird in here thing.
I've seen that people have been sharing it recently.
A gift of you eating the bird is the first time I ever saw you.
Well, thanks for hanging out.
This is expensive, but I'm going to build it.
Do we get to have bird friends?
Do I still have that birdhouse?
Maybe.
Might be in a box somewhere.
I hold on to a lot of stuff, especially stream stuff.
I mean, that Reddit shelf, I know is a joke.
Kind of nice to just remember things that you've done.
Like, oh yeah, I remember that.
Like a little token.
I think I'm pretty sure I still have it.
I think it's in a box.
All right, where do we put the birdhouse?
Maybe they hang out right here?
Away from the foot traffic.
We don't want to scare them.
How about hanging out by the wheat closer to the window?
I think back here is all right.
No, that's too loud.
Too many sounds.
I think back here is fine.
Right here.
Behind the well.
Yeah, right here.
Okay, there it is.
Now we just wait.
Okay, I got my new bench.
Should I make another table?
I'll just say no.
All right, soup, bread.
Maybe I should make a roasted chicken.
Maybe that's a good idea.
I could do any one of these right now.
Soup, try to go down sausage.
All right, I could make roast fish, roast chicken, roast beef, roast pork, roast barley.
I can make roasted barley.
Maybe I'll do that now.
I want to cultivate the wheat because I want to make a wheat beer.
All right, when I go to bed and wake up, we're doing a resource day.
And then I will make my two beers and then I'm going to open the store.
Roast chicken sounds delicious.
It does, it does.
You like ketchup and grilled cheese?
Yeah, it's good.
Okay, let me see.
It probably takes a few days.
Stardew Valley and some of this stuff takes a long time.
I imagine it's probably only a day or two.
All right, resource time.
What's the worst thing to put on a steak?
I don't know.
Do you mean a steak that's cooked on the grill, not a steak sandwich?
I think the easiest answer is not very many condiments.
I don't think it would go well on a steak.
I don't eat very much steak, but I can't imagine everybody.
I mean, I like mushrooms, mushrooms on a steak, onions on a steak.
Steak and eggs is really good from what I remember.
I remember being like, oh, yeah, that's great.
I think an egg is great right now, doesn't it?
From what you remember, I haven't had it in a long time.
Steak is nasty.
I mean, look, I could sit, I would sit here and agree with you.
I would sit here and say, yeah, you're right, but I would be full of shit.
I like steak and cheese subs and sandwiches.
I like them.
Hamburger, all right, like that's essentially beef.
The idea of a big meaty steak, though, is not appetizing to me.
I'm like, yeah, no, no, thank you.
Steak to me is a rare thing that happens every so often, sometimes.
Me having a steak, a steak steak, that fork and knife steak,
it's probably realistically only,
and people are going to be like, what the fuck is going on over here?
It's probably realistically only a few times a year.
A fork and knife steak is only a few times a year for me.
With that being said, I eat hamburgers all the time.
I eat beef, I mean, frequently.
I love carne asada tacos, but I'm not really a big fan
of just the steak with a fork and knife on a plate.
Never really did it for me anyways.
Okay, so now I can buy that calendar that wants me to, a specific quest.
Hey, it got cheaper.
Oops, what is that reward?
A lot of shit steak opinions being thrown around in here.
Yeah, I mean, well, to be fair, there are 15,000 people here.
Who knows what everybody's diet looks like.
You got a pretty large sample of people here.
I feel like there's lots of opinions with the 15,000 people.
How do you like your steak cooked?
Whatever, I'll just get like a thousand on followers.
That's just whatever.
I like steak, I will say medium in a restaurant setting.
I will say medium, and then I'll kind of, I'll put my hand up.
I'll say, I'll take medium.
And then the waiter's definitely like, all right, here it comes.
Medium, well, medium, like I order a steak medium at a restaurant
because I think that's how you do it.
But for me personally, I prefer not medium well.
I wish there was another tier because there is well done, medium well, medium.
I like the in between, between medium and medium well.
You know what I mean?
I like that area in between medium to the second tier.
I like, I don't like it any other way, really.
Medium rare to me is just not, just no thanks.
And rare, no.
You want the non-centrist take?
Fine, take a stance, Andy.
Take a stance, Andy.
That term doesn't even make sense right now.
I don't even know why I keep saying that term.
You want me to take a stance?
I think rare steak is fucking disgusting.
There you go.
I just think rare steak is gross.
I'm sorry.
That's just the way I felt since I was a kid all the way through my teenage years.
Rare steak I think is not, it's unappetizing to me.
Medium rare, medium rare on the other hand is like, okay, I get you, I get you.
Rare, I do not find it to be appetizing at all.
There's you, fine, I took a stance, finally.
Took me 13 years of doing YouTube and Twitch
before you got a real fucking take from me.
Rare steak is disgusting.
Took you 13 years.
You finally got something out of me.
He's so brave.
All right, let me go back.
Let me, oh, I got deliveries.
Show the, hold on, I'll show this.
All right, I'm gonna show meat on, okay, let me show some steak
where I would say I like it.
Not a bad idea.
Stages of steak doneness.
All right, let's put this on camera.
Right, okay, so yeah, medium, medium to medium well I think is perfect.
Anything under blue, like blue rare, uh-uh.
No, medium is, I think medium's where it's at.
I understand medium rare.
I like medium, medium to medium well.
And honestly, I will try to cook my own steaks to be medium
but I get a little paranoid
and I end up making it medium well almost accidentally.
Medium is fine, medium's perfectly fine.
If you ordered a medium rare steak
and I was sitting next to you at a restaurant,
I would say, nice dude, cool, that sounds good.
But I would not order a rare steak.
No, I just don't like it.
If you ordered a rare steak and I was sitting at a restaurant,
I'd be like, ooh, okay, all right, rare, rare steak, all right.
Damn, really, rare.
I've had blue rare before.
Blue rare steak is seared on the outside
almost entirely raw or uncooked in the middle.
Called very rare or blood rare.
In contrast, rare steak is cooked longer
so the middle is warm but still very red
without melting the fat in the meat.
I'm curious, yeah, be honest, what do you actually prefer?
Yeah, I don't know if I want my steak
to be classified as blue, right?
How would you like your steak?
I'll take blue, please.
I don't want it to be a, can it be a steak?
Blue rare is safe to eat.
I mean, I'm not arguing if you should or shouldn't.
I'm just saying I do not find it to be appetizing.
Blue, is there an option for steak is boring?
Um, yeah, I just wouldn't answer it.
Medium, a lot of medium rares.
A lot of medium friends though.
I'm seeing a lot of medium friends in here.
Okay, so for all you medium rare enjoyers,
if you were at the restaurant
and somebody orders a medium steak next to you,
you're cool with that.
That's cool to you.
It's like, yeah, of course, that's fine.
Yeah, of course.
What about medium well?
Medium well is fine.
Hey, how about this?
Let people eat the food they fucking wanna eat.
How does that sound?
Even if somebody ordered a blue rare steak
and I was sitting at the restaurant,
I would internally be like,
holy shit, wow, that's,
I've never happened to hear very many people
order like that before.
But I'm not gonna be like,
oh, what the hell, what the fuck, dude?
No, you like it, eat it.
Hopefully you enjoy it.
50% say medium rare.
That's actually pretty,
that's really interesting to me.
All right, any more quests?
No, time to open the store.
I'm gonna make some money.
Only 8% for well done.
There's a couple of important distinctions to make.
I think with well done,
I wouldn't order a cheese steak with rare steak in it.
I wouldn't.
I think there's a different flavor profile there.
Does that make sense?
I think that most cheese steaks to me need to be
at least medium to medium well.
It depends on the cut of meat.
Yeah, exactly.
We're talking steak as in the cut, yeah.
We really do only talk about food.
If you put together every single moment
I've been on stream,
you could probably extract 30 full seasons
of a food podcast out of it.
Cook it with Jerma.
It would probably last like 30 straight seasons
if you just took the food conversations.
What do you think?
What is that?
It's like a refinery or something.
What is this?
Stone block?
Polished stone.
Okay, I don't need fuel.
All right, time to open the store.
We got plenty of beer.
I got my new concoction open.
Candles.
I can place them during the game day.
Hold on.
I'm just making it nice.
I know everyone's excited for gruel.
How much did it cost?
150?
I feel like that's not that much.
That kind of suck.
I feel like that kind of sucks.
Places bollocks.
Get out of here.
How do I put this in here?
I don't know.
That was a blue rare enjoyer.
Too hot?
Sorry.
It's filthy shit.
I need some better food.
The food is where you make all the money.
Yeah.
I was selling those porridges for what?
Two silver?
Can we have this be a poll stream?
Or just ask questions and poll the chat?
Yeah.
It's a good way to farm viewer engagement.
These drinks are watered down.
I don't like the beer.
It's a good way for viewer engagement.
Yeah.
But I mean, I don't have to engage you guys 24-7 here.
More polls.
All right.
How about the poll with this?
It's your...
How is this for a poll?
Coca-Cola tastes better out of an aluminum can or a glass bottle.
Run that one, I guess.
I don't know.
I have a pros and cons for either one.
Coca-Cola or any soda out of an aluminum can to me can be somehow is colder.
Be like anytime I've had any soda out of a glass bottle.
It's been the preferred way for me.
But it almost feels like it's not as cold somehow.
Even if you get it to a point where it's nice and cold,
it's not quite as frosty chilled as a freezing aluminum can.
I don't know why.
And Coke is crispy.
It's funny.
I actually...
My favorite way to have a soda like that is in a cooler covered in ice.
It's buried.
You have to dig in and actually pull that shit out of the ice from the cooler.
And it's an aluminum can and that shit is freezing.
And it is just boom and it makes that exploding sound, right?
And it's just so cold and so perfect on a summer day.
There you go.
Add this to the food podcast playlist.
When I run out of this beer, well, we're closed.
Chill your Coke in glasses.
I do prefer...
I actually like it out of a glass container.
And I probably agree with that, but sometimes you can't beat the can.
You know what I really prefer in the aluminum can?
Oh, man.
And it's honestly...
You want a food take here?
It's only gotten better.
It's just gotten better.
Brisk iced tea out of the can.
It's only gotten better as we've gone forward here.
A nice freezing cold brisk iced tea.
It's actually really bad because anytime I've had brisk iced tea,
why is it like this?
I feel like when I open a can of brisk iced tea,
I have to go like...
And half the can's gone.
It's almost like that's what you do when you open one of those.
And it's just...
In almost two or three moments, you look at it and go, wait a minute.
I just opened this fucking thing.
Yeah, to me, a brisk iced tea is...
You are sweating.
It's hot out.
It is really, really...
Wow, the sun is...
I'm wiping the sweat off my brow.
Boom.
Ice cold brisk iced tea smash, slam that shit.
That's to me how that works.
That's one of the number one ways to enjoy that.
What are you talking about?
I'm talking about brisk iced tea.
You never had it?
All right, I want to do wheat.
The wheat will probably be ready tomorrow.
This is surprising to me too.
Let me see.
I want to make sure I don't say this wrong.
I was actually surprised.
Last time I had brisk iced tea was kind of not a long time ago,
but I feel like it was a lot less sugar than I thought was in the can.
Because like a bottle of...
Oh, not a bottle.
Like a can of Coke is what?
30 something grams of sugar.
I want to say it's under 20 for a brisk iced tea.
And I remember looking at that and going, wait a minute, really?
That's kind of surprising.
Let's look this up.
Brisk iced tea like sugar.
I promise you it was like surprising in a 12 ounce can.
Well, not 12 ounce can.
I remember looking at it.
Is this accurate?
I don't think that's accurate.
20 grams?
17 grams?
17 grams is in the can apparently.
I mean, it's a lot of sugar.
It still is, but it's not like 30 plus.
17 grams Coke is 39.
Yeah.
Hey, look.
Is this ready?
I thought I just ruined everything.
Wet socks for 24 hours or no underwear for a week?
I mean, that's a no brainer to me.
I could hand...
I don't...
Actually, wait a minute.
I thought that was...
Actually, I don't know.
Yeah, maybe I would just maybe pick the no underwear for a week.
It does not go anywhere.
And just stay here and fucking leave.
Malted wheat.
Wheat flour.
Just wear pajamas for a week.
Yeah, that makes sense.
Oh, you like me.
Roasted barley.
All right.
Look at all this.
I'm going to make a barley snack.
Do you not wear underwear with pajamas?
Um, I mean, are we really going to...
We're never having this conversation right now.
I feel like a certain percentage of you just fucking turned your volume up
and put both your headphones on and leaned in.
Like just listening intently.
The next thing I was going to say.
Settle down.
Relax.
He's going to talk about it.
He's not wearing any underwear.
Yeah.
I'm going to clip it, clip it, clip it.
Oh, fuck.
I just...
I...
Whatever.
I want to make my beer.
My bitter wheat beer.
I want it to be gross.
I need water.
It's really funny because I actually do...
I do like wheat beer.
I think wheat beer is the only beer that I really would actually enjoy drinking.
Kind of funny making my favorite beer.
The tea.
Wheat.
Not weed.
Can you say wheat wart 10 times fast?
Probably.
Wheat wart, wheat wart, wheat wart, wheat wart, wheat wart.
It wasn't 10, but it was pretty quick, man.
Can you please talk about Arnold Palmer's now?
Arnold Palmer's are really good.
All I have to say about that, apparently.
Favorite fry dipping sauce.
I don't know why.
I find it so funny.
I don't know.
I'm just imagining that we're all at Comic Con and it's...
I have a panel or something and everyone's getting up to the microphone
asking their question to the guy that's at the panel.
And you're asking me these questions.
Oh, hey, hey, Jeremiah.
I just have a quick question.
What's your favorite fry dipping sauce?
Well, that would be...
I like honey mustard or ketchup.
I'm a ketchup guy sometimes.
Oh, cool.
Thank you.
The next person.
Do you order medium rare or is it medium steak?
Well, that's a good question.
Appreciate the comment.
I think that...
I mean, I do like a medium to medium well.
I like a medium steak.
Oh, awesome.
Thanks.
Hey, dude, what do you think about...
What's the hottest level of chili pepper you're willing to eat?
Awesome question.
Thanks for asking that.
And this is what I do for like an hour and a half.
All right.
I want my wheat beer.
Come on.
Hurry up.
Let me just have that stream forever.
I feel like after this many years,
you guys have most of my food preferences
and beverage preferences down to a T.
I'm just gonna go to bed and wake up and then finish it.
Okay, there's wheatwort.
Wheat ale.
Wow.
This is worth a lot more than this.
Why did I even go down this path?
24.
Everything else is 61.
These are way better.
Honey wheat with a little bit of bitter in it?
Let's go.
I'm going to bed.
No, I'll do a collection day because I want food in here too.
Can I sell the roasted barley?
Can't.
I can't put the roasted barley up into the bar.
That's technically food, right?
Hey, Jerm, I heard you once ate an entire kong full of peanut butter.
Oh, man.
Expensive kong with peanut butter and...
Are curly fries better?
It depends on the day.
Sometimes I prefer a fry that's got...
It's a very firm and crunchy.
Sometimes I prefer some curly fries.
I think it depends on the day.
We're all such complex beings.
Fry wedges?
I get more food-related questions than cooking channels.
And you know, I'm not even upset about it.
I like like talk.
I love food.
I really do.
It's like one of my favorite things ever.
Honestly, some of my fondest memories were around kind of eating something and hanging out.
Not only do I have the memory of the thing that I thought was interesting,
I have the memory of the food I was eating.
Pretty cool.
Aging shelf.
That's probably for wine, maybe?
Whiskey or something.
My beer ready yet.
I need some more seeds.
I have so much corn in my inventory and I don't even know what to do with it.
I'll get some rye seeds.
Oh, check on the birdhouse.
That's cool.
Good idea.
Are you in there?
Not yet.
Taste is said to be linked to memory.
Yeah, smells are like that too.
I don't know if I could really do a full on what is your favorite foods.
Buffalo chicken is up there at least in one of the top three.
And let me make this clarified.
Not buffalo chicken wings.
Buffalo chicken cutlets.
Buffalo chicken tenders.
I like wings but it's not as good for me as the cutlet version.
Like in a sub.
Buffalo chicken sub is...
I'm like the dog running around in the fucking bacon commercial.
Like, give me, give me, give me.
It's bacon.
That's me with the buffalo chicken sub.
Fucking bacon strips, dog.
Salmon is up there too.
I'd say at least in the top five.
I'm making materials while I wait.
Yeah, pretty much a chicken cutlet.
Flat chicken cutlet.
You can turn that into buffalo chicken or chicken cutlet sandwich or chicken parm.
I think that chicken cutlet is number one.
So maybe it's not buffalo chicken.
It's probably like the way that the chicken is prepared.
Chicken cutlet.
Because I'm not...
Fried chicken is not really what I'm all about.
I like fried chicken but not that like kind of KFC style.
I do like it.
Not the way that I like chicken cutlets.
Chicken katsu, yep.
Precisely.
Pesto on a scale of one to ten.
Probably a nine.
Yeah, it probably is.
I have to really be in the mood for it when I do like it.
And I'm ready to...
Well, yeah, I want that.
It's definitely at least like an eight or nine at least.
Oh, is Diablo 4 going to be fun?
Please, please tell me.
Is it?
I feel like a lot of people are probably doing this.
I am setting my expectations to zero.
So there's only one way to go.
You know what I mean?
There's only one way to go with Diablo 4 for me.
Is there anything else that I need that I haven't bought yet in a mug?
I was not a huge fan of Diablo Immortal.
I tried it and I was like, no, no, no, no.
I just was like, no, thank you.
No.
I'm not a huge fan.
Yeah, I'm not a huge fan of that game.
I know I'm such a nostalgia person and I just want it to be this.
I don't know.
It's like, dude, you're boring.
But that's what I want.
I really just want a Diablo 2 that is expanded graphics or unique items.
Just uniques.
I love uniques.
It's like one of my favorite things about that entire game.
The whole franchise.
Uniques and not random uniques.
I like randomness, but only built into the item itself.
So for instance, if you have a pair of gloves and that pair of gloves is 100 to 150% enhanced
defense and then between 5 and 10 strength and then this between randomness inside the
item is fine.
But I want the item to be unique.
I want the item to be a unique item.
Yeah, that's I just I want more of that.
I feel like a lot of the games recently, it's kind of just throw a bunch of random
fucking numbers on everything.
Like here's a sword and it's got like a bunch of crazy fixes on it.
And it's just a bunch of look at how crazy it is.
There we go.
Finally, wheat ale.
Let's go.
I have to open.
So I've got this one.
This is my wheat ale.
I'm going to make the stew because it sells really well.
And it's the only thing I can make.
I'm just going to make corn a spicy corn and wheat spicy corn porridge with wheat sprinkles.
Never got into Diablo.
It feels like a ton of shit's happening and I need the wiki pulled up for everything.
New Diablo is like that.
Diablo 2 was pretty easy to understand.
Diablo 2.
I feel like it was just is this thing better than what I have on?
It's very simple to know.
And I know it's really simple to know the other games too.
But I don't I don't think you need a wiki for Diablo 2.
It's just yeah.
Diablo 2 is more about the skills than it is about anything else.
Learning what synergizes with what and where you want to put your points.
Diablo 2 is just get plus skill level stuff.
That's what you're striving to do.
And then what something else was important to have enough.
Making money today.
All right I've got corn.
This is corn chili starch veggie starchy seedy.
That sounds awful.
If you explained to me a soup that was seedy starchy with veggies in it.
I'd be like well I'm not ordering that.
But it's okay because this is a video game.
All right I'm ready to open.
I forgot to put the other bench down but whatever.
Can I do it now?
We're closed.
Okay we're open.
That's a lot.
330 for that.
160 and 330.
All right let me get everybody at a table and then I'll clean.
350 actually 360.
The cat helping you serve.
That's funny but I don't think so.
Have enough beer.
Everybody doing all right.
Getting clean.
Where are the cats just hanging out?
Too hot.
All right one gold is 100.
Yeah it's kind of the 100 copper is one silver.
100 silver is one gold.
It was worth waiting for the wheat beer.
What's up the stairs?
I think it's a it's another storage room.
Must be two gold.
Oh my god I'm so sorry.
I didn't mean to bump that.
You can play Dead Rising again.
Oh yeah that's not what you asked.
You said when is the Dead Rising stream?
I played the first two.
I played the third one almost what a decade ago with stir.
Well we kind of just messed around.
We didn't really actually try to play the game for real.
Maybe I would just stream it.
Those Dead Rising 2 streams are some of I think the
I feel like that's some of the most fun I've had on broadcast.
Ever.
That game was out of control at some points.
Dead Rising 1 and Dead Rising 2.
These games are so much fun.
But Dead Rising 4.
Dead Rising 4 I think was a monumental disappointment.
I think I streamed it and it just wasn't very good.
Or just not it wasn't what I wanted.
It wasn't what I was expecting.
Didn't have very much fun playing it.
You know I always thought that something that they were going to do was they did the mall.
It was like oh the mall you're in the mall look at all the stuff at the mall.
I was under the impression I was like you know what what if I'm thinking okay they're doing
where is there a place with a ton of random shit kind of random stuff.
I thought they were going to go to an amusement park.
Imagine like roller coasters and stuff and like all the zombies like
imagine that how crazy that would be.
You could do a full amusement park.
And I think that keeps it fresh.
Just think about all the random encounters you could do with the midway games and roller
coasters and different rides and different bosses that would be I imagine you can fight
somebody a boss on one of the roller coasters.
Wouldn't that be awesome?
It could be a whole giant cinematic scene where you fight a boss on the roller coaster.
I'm going to go through all this inventory if I have it.
I'm supposed to stay open.
You can do that in the Jimmy Neutron game.
That's pretty fun.
Oh this person's gonna get pissed.
I can make at least another 40 or 50 silver here.
Unless it might get too late people might leave.
Please play Jimmy Neutron Attack of the Twonkies.
That sounds like a made-up game.
You didn't just make that up.
Now it's real okay.
That fire wood here yep.
What Nickelodeon character wouldn't survive the zombie apocalypse?
Oh Patrick.
Patrick is fine.
I don't know.
I feel like Patrick would just think it was like something something wasn't dangerous was
happening or something like oh here's a bunch of new friends in town or something right.
Patrick no those are zombies.
Patrick be careful.
Don't go near those things.
Those are zombies Patrick.
What's wrong with me?
Oh shit I gotta close.
Everybody hurry up and get out of here.
All right everybody get out.
Thank you.
I appreciate it.
That was a really good day.
Get out one last spot to clean.
It's 3 a.m.
I feel like you started streaming and then we instantly just asked a bunch of questions.
This most kind of just like a question stream.
That's fine we're just hanging on.
I want bigger tables but let me see you.
I have a lot of experience points.
I could go for rye.
I could go for wine.
Well not yet actually.
Soup oh here we go sausages.
Where do I get meat?
Where do I get meat from?
I want apples berries.
All right let's do apples and berries.
Let me go check out the town.
I feel like it's been a while.
Probably something I can.
Wait what about the calendar?
Eh whatever.
Didn't it say to take a look at the calendar?
Because there's events right?
I guess not.
I need more of these tanks.
Because I really should have more than one to go explore today.
Yeah probably the plan.
Is it done?
I'm gonna go down.
How many fingers am I holding up?
Three.
I wonder if that just freaked you out.
What if it was three?
That's like an excel the window shot down computer.
What the fuck?
This is like a stardew like how is it?
So far it's it is very much like stardew.
I think it's a lot more about to me.
I would put the actual video game play to something more like Diner Dash in a way.
Like serving and then running around and wiping the tables.
And the customer is complaining and kind of like that in a way.
And I imagine later on the game probably gets a little more hectic.
But there are you know all this crafting and resource management.
I don't see any there's no birds.
Look at the birds.
I think is this still in early access or is this out in 1.0?
I think it's early access still.
Well okay if you like Stardew Valley and you like alcohol I guess.
Because this is just you it's you run a tavern.
Hit somebody with your axe.
Twitch chat is such a funny place.
It really is because in between in in between.
Hey what do you think about this game?
This is a really interesting video game.
But kind of like looks like Stardew Valley.
What's your opinion on it?
Oh hey dude like do you like medium rare steak?
Hit someone in the fucking head with your axe.
So many different worlds going on.
There's so many different things happening at once.
It's such an interesting dichotomy.
I want to spend some money on something nice.
I have three gold what am I buying?
Oh frying mat?
When you shut down your computer do you close everything first?
Usually yeah.
I always hate seeing that that screen.
Especially in Windows when you're shutting something down.
And it's you know your computer's almost like hey dude.
Some programs are not closed.
What's wrong with you?
What are you thinking?
And it just goes oh fuck oh it's gonna close them automatically.
No what do I do?
It cancel.
All right I got I got blueberry seed.
Let's make this a little bigger.
Because if I'm gonna have blueberries and stuff I want it to be bigger.
Apples and then I'll just do make two more little areas.
I bought 40 of each.
I'm realizing that was probably not a good idea.
Why are you digging like this?
Because I messed it up and I want to make sure I'll patch out them.
Um okay so now that's how many is this total?
1, 2, 3, 8, 9, 12, 13, 14, 25, 27, 30, 31, 32, 33, 34, 35, 7, 8, 39, 40, 41, 46.
Okay so 46.
I need to take away six uh spaces.
Should I take them out of the middle?
Would it be more aesthetically pleasing if it was in the middle?
1, 1, 2, or 1, 2, 3.
All right this is kind of just a big booger in the middle but it'll be all right.
It's uneven.
I'll fix it.
All right this is gonna be apples.
I almost tried to just plant the porridge.
This is not right.
They're trees.
I for some reason was like why can I buy so many of these?
Okay we're gonna have a whole and we're gonna have a whole orchard here.
No, no, no, no, no.
Blueberries are going here.
Remove, remove, remove it.
How do I undo it?
There we go.
All right blueberries.
Here they come.
I have one left.
I didn't calculate this right.
I got an idea.
The bar open?
No it is.
Oh shit oh I'm sorry.
I didn't read.
Here take some stew.
Everybody's so hungry.
What is he doing out there?
He's he's trying to plant a bunch of he he's trying to plant 40 different apple trees.
Oh thank god everything's fine.
No I'm sorry I just screamed but it was actually scary.
I thought I was gonna lose or something.
That was truly terrifying.
Why is the store open?
I didn't how did I not?
Oh this drink sucks.
It's because I don't have anything on tap.
What are they even drinking?
Oh no oh no I have to I'm gonna have to attack somebody.
I'm sorry all right now get out get out of here.
I'm sorry I opened up so late but that's no need to throw stuff at people and attack anybody.
I'm serving water.
Make it nice and toasty in here.
Listen I'll I'll it's only gruel that's the only thing I have.
All right we're closed thanks for coming in.
I'm gonna get such a bad rating.
I'm gonna rage quit this stream I think.
They're all gonna give negative I'm gonna lose negative experience.
How?
I spent two or three days crafting a recipe and making honey wheat beer with like a hint of cayenne pepper in it and I get shit on.
I serve gruel out of a fucking an old refrigerator out back and this I get the rave reviews.
Okay this one is mild ale.
Did I have anything anything cool with this?
No I think it's just regular ale.
Okay back to what I was doing.
Can I plant a apple tree in the middle?
That'd be pretty cool damn it.
Well I'm sorry guys but I have to plant 40 apple trees.
Don't be mad at me.
Shit okay hold on.
I mean I bought them.
It's a waste huge waste of money if I don't.
How many was it eight?
Okay so I need to it's gonna take so long.
It's gonna be here for days man it's all right.
I'm not gonna plant all 40 but just enough for it to make sense.
Three four I'll do three and then yeah okay I'll do four.
We'll do four right here that's easy.
Maybe maybe I'll just go all the way up.
Yeah all right I'm going all the way up.
Everyone just look relax it's late at night just chill.
That's what we're doing.
It's so uneven okay it doesn't matter if it's uneven.
Just matters that it's there and it's growing.
And look is it really that uneven?
You're forgetting about the seeds we're planting here.
No don't be an idiot.
Don't be an idiot.
Just what I'm playing the game.
This part is already done for me.
That's one going on here.
Why can I not go this way?
Okay so what's going on what's going on?
Oh right because yeah I know what's going on.
You can't do it in the area of a piece of machinery.
Well that's fantastic.
Okay it'll be fine I'll just plant them here.
Two more and that's it.
Now this is one more one more.
I gotta go bed I'm gonna pass out.
How long do these take to grow I wonder?
All right I'm going to bed I'm going to bed right now.
Look see and I'm gonna buy a big wooden framed painting.
And a blue rug and a couple more candles.
I'm going to bed.
How's our growth look?
It's ready I think this is ready.
It is oh this is rye.
I'm gonna make a nice super super mild.
Are these done too?
Pears raspberries strawberries what?
I gotta get strawberries.
Grapes how about raspberries?
I didn't mean to buy that many I'll get 45.
Pears all right we got a lot of stuff incoming.
Pears grow on trees I yeah I know but I just bought a ton of them.
They were cheap.
I need to unlock rye.
Is wheat here's rye oh I have so many of that first category.
I can't even make the rye berry yet like two more points.
Why am I messing up?
That's on tap right now.
I have some forages that's the corn and rye treat one.
Okay it's a rug down painting up.
Oh that's nice like right here.
The horse feels like pac-man.
Candles I want to move this too.
This thing's annoying.
I want to put them in here.
I did it before I don't know how to do it.
That other one will burn out it's fine.
All right I'm almost ready.
I want to okay I've got a lot of shit.
I don't know wait I gotta put that calendar up too.
Yep here we go.
I am almost ready to open.
Apple seeds apple seeds rye and corn sure.
All right wheat lager.
This needs lager yeast wheat wort and a keg.
This is ale let's make this wheat lager.
I need wheat wort which is being made right now.
Is that what's being made?
I believe I need bitter hops.
Okay I need hops.
Hops and what was it hops and lager yeast.
Then I'm going to bed.
Get a bunch of shit right.
I need some more decor.
There's so many pear trees all over the hell.
God damn it that's right.
I'm so embarrassed.
All right well I'm definitely doing
strategy strawberries or raspberries.
Strawberries for sure.
And then surrounding the trees
we're gonna plant raspberries.
Is that possible?
Only in certain places.
That's fine.
Are these ready to harvest?
Probably not till tomorrow.
All right I'm going to bed
because I want to wake up and see the plants.
Going to bed at 10 in the morning.
Yeah but it's the video game equivalent
of time traveling to speed up the timers.
The wheat all right I need hops and water.
Did I bump you?
I'm sorry I did I didn't mean to.
Is there a take all button?
No what just happened to that?
Yes there is okay.
Blueberries are ready.
Okay so now what can I do with the blueberries?
I can make like a blueberry blueberry flavored ale.
Blueberry ale yep.
Well I'm gonna do blueberry raspberry wheat beer.
Blueberry mead blueberry mead.
All right let's try blueberry mead.
What about like a banana wheat beer?
Is that weird?
Oh I need water.
Why does it hold on?
Has anybody ever made a banana beer before?
I feel like I would like it.
Banana beer?
That sounds actually kind of good.
Banana beer is amazing.
I wonder if I could track some down somewhere.
That actually sounds good.
All right wheat, fuel.
I need to make a second one of these.
All right we can do a mild ale.
So this is just ale yeast.
And let's throw some fucking blueberries in there.
Blueberries with some aroma and dual hops.
There we go.
That was so loud.
Oh wait what about a blueberry porridge with corn and hints of rye flavoring.
Another wheat beer.
That was a shotgun.
It was.
I'm sorry.
All right the next day that we do this.
Look at this.
I'm gonna I'm gonna have like three or four different taps.
Pies five three or to make pies.
I want to make like blueberry pie and stuff.
Jam shit.
I'm gonna make bread.
All right I'm overwhelming myself.
What am I doing?
Tea?
I want pie.
We'll do we're going for pie.
We're probably not even gonna get there.
Make apple pie.
I have a lot of wheat.
I probably make bread.
What do I need to make bread?
I already can.
I can make sausages.
Corn blueberry sausage.
What?
Corn sausage.
I don't know if that's gonna be any good but whatever.
They're gonna eat it.
Bro what the fuck?
What?
Hey if it's available I'm putting it on the menu all right.
I'm putting all this weird shit on the menu.
We're making 10 gold tomorrow with the rest of the raspberries.
Okay get a pear tree up.
Okay I'm gonna make two pear trees one.
Hold on.
Yeah I can make one here and one down here.
It's four by four.
Strawberry rhubarb pie sounds pretty good.
It's good with ice cream.
Sounds good.
It's better.
All right I want two pear trees and that's it.
I bought 40 of them but I'll never have to buy them ever again.
Get this rock out of the way.
Can I clear this rock?
Probably not.
Well it's all right.
Can I even fit it here?
Shovel on the rock?
Probably better tools eventually.
I probably can't remove it so we're just gonna have to be sad and go this way.
Really?
How much surface area does this rock take up?
Why can I I can't till this though.
Why is it so weird near the rock?
What the hell?
Oh my goodness.
Okay well and it's just going up here.
It doesn't have to look fine.
It just has to look just has to produce the fruit.
It's horrible.
Yeah see I can't.
There and then I'll put something else here.
I'll put like raspberries or I got all the stuff coming to the mail.
Okay cool check on the other stuff.
Cooking a lot of things.
There's the sausage.
Wheatwort.
There it is.
Good good.
There's the mild blueberry ale.
All right wheat lager.
Blueberry.
Bitter.
Dual hops.
Whatever.
All this dude has is blueberry ale.
Hey it's different and it's cool and it's unique.
Do you know the amount of people that are going to be looking for craft beer that come in here?
It's like oh blueberry malted pancake batter banana smoothie beer.
And they're going to go oh and they're going to take one sip and be like.
But it's a craft beer so I mean I think I get a little bit of points.
All right I'm ready to start the day after this.
I'm going to bed.
I'm waking up.
I'm going to be fresh and we're going to start the day.
Hello.
Okay that's all my material.
This is a mild ale.
Just kind of like a just a regular just like Bud Light I guess.
This one is the blueberry aromatic properties and some extra spice in it.
That's a wheat beer.
And then over here we have our our lager.
This is a wheat lager with hints of blueberry.
Bitter with some extra spices on it.
This guy thinks Bud Light is an ale.
I don't drink that much beer guys.
Raspberries are done too.
All right I'm going to do a raspberry strawberry rye beer.
All right what about a strawberry raspberry corn porridge.
Oh wait can I not do that?
Oh I need fuel.
No I don't.
Wait what?
This restaurant is disgusting.
Corn blueberry sausage blueberry corn soup.
Corn wheat soup or corn starch seeds.
We got blueberry corn soup blueberry corn sausages blueberry corn.
Beer we've got everything is blueberry.
I think it's gonna be all right.
I need I need to get butter.
Why can't I put butter in any of this?
Well can I just like have people eat the strawberries?
Dude apple seeds are toxic.
I think it's comparing.
Raspberry blueberry strawberry sausage.
I mean this is just a fruit roll-up.
This is just like fruit pectin right?
All right I'm ready to open the store.
I got what I want.
Wait didn't have an extra table.
I'm getting another table.
No I'm not who cares.
Yeah I'm getting one more table.
And then I'm done and I will open the store I promise.
I just need a bunch of wooden planks.
I want two more tables.
Blueberry corn muffin sounds pretty good.
Yeah.
Fence the farm off so nobody sees this atrocity.
Get away.
Mine.
My strawberries.
What are you looking at?
What do you want?
Small table and then we need four benches right?
I just need a ton of everything.
Is this game better than Stardew Valley?
I mean you can't you're comparing something to the Mona Lisa.
It's kind of hard to do that.
I think it's fun.
Obviously I've been playing it for five hours.
I've been having a good time.
It scratches that sort of make stuff, collect stuff, sell stuff.
I'm having a good time.
It's not the Mona Lisa but I mean how do you do that?
How do you compare something to the Mona Lisa?
Just that you can't.
The main lasso.
I know.
Bro the Mona Lisa sucks.
All right art critic Andy.
That's all right.
Mona Lisa's overrated.
Yeah but still it's one of the most important paintings in human history right?
We all kind of say that.
We all agree with that.
We don't agree.
Okay well what are the most important paintings in human history?
There's probably a few dozen I could probably think of.
Uh let us not forget Socrates drinking the poison.
Sorry that was probably loud.
People sleeping.
The Socrates when he's when he when he knows they've called for his execution
and he's got that finger pointing up.
And he's like I will drink this potion because I know it will kill me.
Therefore I have my philosophy.
Like that finger pointing up and everyone's like what the fuck?
That painting goes hard.
What is the name of that painting?
Socrates's um execution right?
Socrates's demise what was that painting called?
The death of Socrates yep.
I think that's a pretty important one.
Creation of Adam.
The death of Socrates yeah.
Um actually that painting isn't even good.
It's only famous because Socrates died.
Socrates and Plato.
I mean those people those were incredibly important people in our in our history.
Plato.
Guys um Socrates uh invented soup.
So what do you got to say?
Can a lot of the like modern philosophy be tied back to what Plato and Socrates were doing?
Yeah but I need to make two more benches.
I'm out of fuel.
Socrates invented critical thinking.
Um no was it Socrates that invented the the scientific uh theory whatever it is?
One of them did.
Who who no no no no they did.
The scientific method was Socrates wasn't it?
Who came up with it?
Galileo.
All right but yeah but whatever right?
Gala Galileo did.
Aristotle.
Galileo.
These people are important Socrates, Plato, and Franklin.
I'm kidding I'm kidding.
I'm not starting that up at fucking midnight.
I'm not starting that up at midnight.
I mean all of them are in hell but you know.
Did somebody just say all scientists are in hell?
Bro you need to fucking relax.
You need to relax.
Is that what you said?
What the hell?
Oh that's that's funny.
Every single one.
What did you say?
Can you just get your stupid Boston ass together?
You fuck Jesus Christ.
You're like the worst Red Sox fan.
What are you doing?
Leave me alone.
What the hell?
I just imagine some Boston fan just pissed.
You didn't even fucking talk about the fucking trade that happened.
Does he not understand the fucking Patriot season coming up this year?
Is he not fucking paying attention?
God fuck this guy.
Why are you not talking about the management?
General manager.
You didn't even say the Red Sox.
You didn't talk about the fucking Red Sox.
I've been here for over an hour.
I thought you were from Boston.
Fake fucking fan.
Was this Grotto Beast shit?
Grotto Beast?
Fucking loser.
Hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey.
Come on.
Grotto Beast.
What fucking minor league team is that?
What town do they play for?
I never heard of the fucking Grotto Beast.
Red Sox would destroy them though.
That's all I know.
All right.
I'm ready to start the day.
Let's put the benches in.
I've got a lot of stuff now.
This is going to be a crazy day.
This place is too small.
You're going to have to be a little more cramped I think.
Benches.
This now needs to move here probably.
All right.
I'm going to move this.
Whoa, whoa, whoa.
What's going on?
What the fuck?
That can stay over here.
Where's your depth perception?
I'm just looking at stuff.
I want the big table where the fire is.
That thing costs extra.
Good luck anybody sitting on this side.
This seat sucks.
All right.
I need my one more bench.
Didn't I make a third one?
Shit.
I didn't.
OK.
Wait.
Do I have a third one in my inventory?
I need one more.
Do you make the restaurant in the game?
You make the...
It's limited to the point of you make beer.
You can add flavors to the beer.
Different fruits and different wheat and barley.
And you technically do make the menu.
I need to go fishing or something.
I don't know.
Make the tables vertical.
If I make all the tables vertical then I won't be able to see all their smiling faces.
At least for the people facing this way.
Come on.
OK.
It's time to go to bed and then open the store.
I'm ready.
This is going to be the biggest day so far.
Apple's ready or no?
Yes.
You take the raspberries and you can make a raspberry beer or maybe eventually whiskey,
vodka, moonshine.
I don't know what their plans are.
Game is still in early access.
So I don't know.
Take a raspberry corn sausage.
Yep.
You could do that too.
I think I want this just because I have a lot of firewood.
I like the footsteps.
It's nice.
How big is the area?
As of right this moment in early access,
I don't know if they're planning on adding a full town or anything,
but it looks like there is an up.
There is a down.
I think there is a I keep talking about a mine.
I don't know if it's up here.
Like what's up here?
OK.
Blocked off currently.
They're a waterfall.
Amusing me so much when you stand completely still while reading chat.
I can't multitask either.
Well, I let's put it this way.
If I'm walking and I look away from the screen,
I'm not seeing where I'm going.
I can't really know if I'm looking over here and I don't know where I'm walking,
especially when a game you need to have a lot of attention problems.
Anyways, I need to stop the read.
There's a bridge.
I bet you have to put a certain amount of wood or money to make the bridge go.
It looks like it's planned to be here,
but all that matters right now is opening the tavern.
We're going to do very soon.
All right.
Firewood stockpile.
Does it just go there?
Maybe it does it automatically.
All right.
Let's go.
Big day.
A lot of customers.
I need to be prepared.
I got all my food in here.
Cat has water.
Lots of food.
Tons of shit on tap.
Get a little bit of everything.
Oh, he ate the blueberry sausage.
Are we clean?
They're pretty clean.
Oh, shit.
I'm out of light.
I think I got it.
Hold on.
We got people in.
Good choice.
Blueberry raspberry sausage stew.
People seem pretty happy.
Menu selection.
Service here is terrible.
Oh, free sausages coming up.
Sausages are flying off the shelf.
People really like it.
What's the thing in the bottom right mean?
That flower.
I mean, there's not enough decorations.
It means it's dirty.
We're going to level up here.
How much inventory do I still have?
I can stay open for a long time.
As long as I have the candlelight.
Random order quests are available at the notice board.
Really?
Oh, my God.
Level up.
Did you call it the sus guy tavern?
Yeah.
Oh, shit.
Hold on.
Getting out of hand.
Well, I'm only one person.
Hold on.
And crack that person in the face while they're eating.
Is this a medieval tavern or fantasy RPG tavern?
I would say medieval tavern.
We've been seeing very many fantasy characters walk in.
Service here is terrible.
Relax.
Calm down.
Oh, shit.
What do you want?
The owner of this place is a cultist.
Why do you keep saying that?
I almost said four gold.
That's pretty good.
I want to go through all of the inventory.
This is definitely the stage where you get a little bigger
and you need somebody to help.
You need a staff member running out of beer.
It's Gruul.
Oh, shut up.
Get out of here.
Yeah.
Once we get to about midnight, that's when Gruul is on the menu.
Looks like that was the most popular.
That blueberry lager is the popular one.
Whatever that stew is, everyone's ordering it.
That one.
That was the one everyone said was poisonous.
They're all ordering the apple seed one.
This table is getting gross.
Time for the fire.
That's empty.
All right.
For a second, I thought this was a skeleton.
Like whose bones are over here?
People are ordering this shitty beer now.
Oh, shitty relatively to my blueberry lager.
That's it.
That's empty.
How much food is left?
We got a lot.
I can probably stay open until I pass out.
They're only ordering the one beer.
That's all I have left, right?
I have one more of those.
Yeah, there we go.
Hey, you got the last one.
Good for you.
Clean the throw up.
I can only move so fast.
I'm cleaning.
Does the health department know about this place?
The health department back in the old medieval times was,
hey, I found a fly in my drink.
I'm going to hit the bartender with an axe.
There's your health department.
No, they just ate it.
Yep, I can wipe it down.
There you go.
Enjoy your banana encrusted raspberry filled freaking vegan sausages is what I made, I think.
Hey, you got a bad review.
Now it's just down to the food.
All right.
Look at this 5.5 gold.
This is kind of filthy over here.
Hey, food is great, but the owner won't stop talking about the Red Sox.
Two out of five.
Yeah, right.
And then the Red Sox guy comes in and gives me a two out of five
because I didn't talk about the Red Sox enough.
Understand how I cannot win here.
You see, you guys understand.
5.7.
All right, I'm almost out of stuff.
What happens if I just serve gruel until everybody passes out?
Like, is that possible?
Can I just serve gruel until I go to bed?
I'm very curious, but I don't want to lose all this money.
It'll be bad.
No, we found him.
We found him in the morning.
Face burst into a bowl of gruel because it grew some sight.
One man Applebee's.
I like that.
All right, we're at gruel hours.
It is 1 a.m.
All I have is gruel.
And imagine complaining right now.
You've eaten all of my food.
You've eaten, you've cleaned out all of my inventory.
This is what I can make right now.
I really don't like the atmosphere right now.
Like, well, all I have is wheat and water.
All I have is rice and water.
That's what we have.
Start fucking them up.
Yeah, how long can this actually go for?
It's 2 a.m.
Oh, wait, somebody's pissed.
Eat the gruel.
Why are they still here?
One gruel, please.
Have it right up.
I'll take a gruel.
I'll have a gruel, please.
Any more gruel?
Yep.
I mean, at what point am I just taking
what everybody has left on their plates
and just mixing them together
and putting it on another plate?
I don't have any more ingredients.
Should I kick?
Is that it?
All right, everybody get out.
All right, one more gruel for the road.
There you go.
All of you eating gruel.
Now get out.
Did somebody punch me?
Oh, no, it's a mess.
Yeah, I passed out.
I heard this place has super good gruel.
It's neat like people on Instagram talk about it.
Guys, I went to this restaurant yesterday
and they had the best gruel I've ever had.
It was super fruity and it had hints of raspberry.
You guys are not going to believe this spot that I found.
I wish I'd sleep.
Secret menu.
Vibes were amazing.
And I think that's probably where we're going to call it.
Right exactly at midnight exactly.
Exactly at 12 a.m.
It's 8 a.m.
Where are you?
Europe?
Good morning to you.
Yeah, we'll call it here.
This is fun.
I don't know if I will continue to play this,
but it was that was really fun.
It was really cute.
I liked it.
I think there's probably a lot more to do,
but it's pretty cool.
It's called Traveler's Rest.
Pretty comfy.
Oh, hold on.
One apple off of this whole tree.
One singular apple per tree.
This does not seem very sustainable.
That seems kind of one.
All right, that's it.
I'll see you guys later.
I'll probably see you guys on.
I'll see you probably on Monday.
I'll see you guys Monday, Monday or Tuesday.
Again, the SUS is going to be more of a general guideline.
I don't want to do like reverse delays and delays.
So they will not be a stream until early this week.
Somewhere around Monday or Tuesday.
Keep an eye on the SUS.
I will change it when I know for certain exactly when it's going to happen.
We'll see.
I say expect to stream early this coming week.
That sounds good, right?
And again, to touch upon the Grotto Beast stuff one more time.
We are exploring a digital version of the game.
Maybe just parrot one more time what that means.
We're exploring it.
It's being investigated right now.
We're trying to find a good way to do it.
And whether it is a mod or an existing platform or it is something standalone.
We are going to try to make sure I get all this information correct.
The channel merch that is Grotto Beasts has a game on it.
There is a trading card game on this merch.
And we're very aware that there's a lot of people that either can't afford it
or that don't really...
They want to participate in the game maybe.
They don't want to collect the merch.
So we're probably going to do some form of a digital release that we can be in control of.
And they're absolutely one thing.
I mean we want to get this right because I don't want to screw this up anyway.
This would not be a digital card pack opening version of Grotto Beasts.
It would just be the game that you can play.
And it would not be any additional purchases after getting it.
And we don't know what that means.
We're not turning this into a...
Oh yeah, go get the digital version and spend a shitload of money on digital card packs.
That's not the point.
The point is to just try to let as many people participate that want to.
Because obviously it's an expensive piece of merch.
And we've seen people obviously say,
The game? What's the game? The game seems kind of interesting. What is that?
Which the rules will be posted.
That's actually being written up right now.
The website version of this, by the way, the rules have been written.
They've been written. They've been up for a long time.
I keep saying that wrong and that's my own fault.
But the rules, the game is completed.
It's just we need to post the rules.
The rules on the website is currently being worked on.
I want people to participate.
I want you to be able to check it out.
And we want to make sure that the merch is valuable as merch to the community.
But I also want to make sure that we...
Whether it's a mod of something or it's something that...
We don't want it to be a huge money sink.
We just want it to be available for people to just play with other people.
It's important.
Whatever that means, you will know.
We will tell you very, very soon.
I'm hoping in the next couple of weeks we'll have a really clear answer.
Would be fun if it's electronic too.
Yeah. We want to make sure that there's still the value of the merch.
Because obviously it's a lot of money. It is.
So I want to make sure that that stays as like cool community merch.
There's also an opportunity to actually play the game.
I hope people understand that.
And there's a lot of other things to talk about.
Trust me when I say we're trying to make this as good and cool as we can.
Without...
Again, I don't want the digital version to be anything more than...
Hey, do you want to check out the game?
Here it is.
Whatever that means.
Take care of yourselves.
Just want to reiterate that one more time.
A one-time purchase or something would be cool.
Yeah, but that's what we want to do.
I don't know the exact things we want.
We've been talking internally about this for a little bit longer than you might think.
Of just what do we do?
What about online matchmaking?
Yeah, we're...
I don't want to count the chickens before they're hatching here.
Just be aware.
It's going to be some form of official digital version of this game.
That will have official support on it.
That we will just be releasing.
That will just have everything in it.
So people can enjoy the game.
We need to figure out exactly what that means.
Why do you like Applebee's?
Because it's waiting to give you a reason.
Is he going to do online microtransactions?
No.
No, that is not happening.
That is...
The answer to that question is no.
Oh my god, not again.
I just got back.
Do you...
Whatever.
Unlocking cards maybe by winning games?
Yeah, it needs to be...
It needs to be an accessory to the merch, right?
It needs to be something that is not...
Because I don't want to have people pay a bunch of money again if they already own it.
Trying to be...
Trying to just keep my brain grounded on this stuff.
Whether it's a mod of an existing platform or something else.
It will be available.
I can promise and guarantee you that.
I've seen all the theories and all the people.
We're exploring pretty much every option.
We are exploring corporate speak.
We are exploring our options.
We will give you an update soon.
Just know that it will exist.
There you go.
And we'll see you in a day.
See you guys on Monday.
Have a good night.
Have a great rest of your evening or morning.
Good morning to you.
That was fun.
I respect that you're not promising too much.
There's already been a lot of time that's gone into this.
And a lot of thought.
So we don't want to get ahead of ourselves.
I don't want to tell you guys something that's not going to happen.
That's why we've been kind of...
The last, I want to say four or five days,
been really trying to trickle out info that's correct.
But the rules will be available for you to look at.
We're hoping the next day or so.
As well as the FAQ would be posted on the website.
So even if I'm not live, if it's there,
we will direct everybody.
We'll probably do a Discord announcement.
So people can go kind of peruse the rules.
With the actual game portion of this merch.
Take it easy.
I, of course, will give you updates when I get them.
Take care of yourselves.
Call your mother.
See you soon.