I didn't guarantee that, right? Did I 100% guarantee that I was gonna be here at 358 Pacific?
I don't remember. Did? Did I? It was a 100% guarantee. Shit. Well, whatever.
I'm here now, and that's all that matters. We're here now. I don't even link it. Link it. Link it. Screencap it. Screencap it. What?
I will start at the latest
358 Pacific, and then I said screencap this. Well, what?
Screencap it. Okay. So what? You screencapped it, and you proved me wrong.
Hey, you got me. Hey, guess what? You got me. By the way, can I just say, how do I sound?
Don't you think this is an immense improvement from the last time you heard me talk? I mean, an immense improvement.
Worse. Get out of here. I spent like 45 minutes making sure this sounded good.
I had the things in my ears, and I was leaning forward just being like, hello. Hello. Good afternoon. Hey. Hey. Hey. Hey. Hey. Hey.
Hey, it sounds fucking clean. You should try whispering. No, I'm not. Why would I do that? I'm not gonna do that.
No one cares. Oh, right. No, hold on. We'll go over this.
Interesting.
Interesting week. Interesting few weeks, to be honest.
With all the stuff, all the moving, all the everything that happened with the dog. I said I didn't want to take any more
extended time off, but that
ended up not being the case, and somebody just gave a hundred dollars.
We had ten community subs from LM Man, five community subs from SoyDev, and then a hundred dollars from Gimme20Dollars.
Why didn't you give me 20?
Your name, Gimme20Dollars, gave me ten thousand bits. You went way over what you were supposed to give me.
No, does that mean I'm supposed to give you 20 dollars? Is that how that works? Anyways,
We are here after an interesting week. Those who don't know, I'll go over it briefly after I tweet this.
So just relax for a second. I just had to tweet that. It's gonna be hard to drink this.
I'm gonna dump this all over my nice microphone. It's a nice microphone. Can you tell? Did you tell that I got a nice microphone?
You couldn't. Let me get a little closer.
Anyways, let me see this. People made a Get Well cards for Otto, which is very, very nice. Very sweet of you.
I'll go over the story real quick. So
Otto,
four or five days ago now, whatever it was,
he
was going outside to go pee all the time.
I was like, what is going on? He's going outside every five, ten minutes. He needs to pee every ten minutes.
I'm like, this is not right.
Just because I was curious, after like the seventh or eighth time and two hours or so of him just peeing, peeing, peeing, peeing, peeing.
I'm like, you know what? Let me just put like a paper towel underneath
when he pees. So he went for like the tenth time, whatever, he goes out and pees and I put the paper towel under and
his blood on the paper towel. He's peeing blood.
At that point, you know, you have a fucking meltdown. You're like, what is that? Why is he doing that? What's going on?
And I just, I just brought him to the
emergency room. I brought him to the vet and
thankfully, they did a couple of tests and it turned out that he doesn't have
his like blood work was okay. His kidney function was okay.
And they did an x-ray of his abdomen to see if there's any growths or tumors or anything. And thankfully nothing there either.
But he had to go on antibiotics. They thought he had a UTI and
if you don't know this, Otto has Addison's.
So what Otto cannot produce, steroids. His body physically can't do it. There's a spectrum of steroid diseases.
You can either have Cushing's or you can have Addison's. Cushing's is way too much steroids.
Addison's is not very many or none at all. So he needs to get, every month
he gets an injection and he has to get steroids every month and
every other day or so, depending on how stressful the situations are, he has to take steroids.
Now,
because of the move,
it's been very, very stressful for him. Obviously because we moved to a new place. So he's
been very stressed out, you know, what's this new place I'm in? I don't like this. You brought me to a new place.
It's hard for dogs to kind of acclimate and a dog that has Addison's,
they think, at least the vet thinks, that
over the stress from the move and not producing, he gave himself a UTI.
Essentially is what I was told. But he's doing all right now. He is back to high spirits.
He's running around. He's almost done with his antibiotics. And I just wanted to take the time
over the last few days to make sure that he was all right.
Because obviously when he's peeing every 10 minutes,
somebody's got to be here to make sure he can go out and we can take care of him, make sure there's no blood.
So that's why I was gone for like another five days.
Sorry that I was gone. I really don't mean for this shit to happen.
It's just kind of bad timing as I come back like last week or so and I'm like,
Okay, we're gonna be doing four streams a week at least and I'm gonna be here every day. See you later.
I'll see you in a week. So I do apologize for that.
But we can go over how this is gonna play out here over the next
seven or eight days because obviously that was just that happened.
You probably noticed the title.
HULK ULTIMATE DESTRUCTION HAS COME IN.
And that it that supersedes literally everything else.
I was under the impression that HULK ULTIMATE DESTRUCTION wasn't gonna come in for like another week or two.
So I've decided I want to play HULK ULTIMATE DESTRUCTION.
I hope I got the right one. And there's a funny story with this one too. I'm full of stories today.
Let's just move over so you can see it.
Anyways, so HULK ULTIMATE DESTRUCTION. I bought this for GameCube and
I didn't get the GameCube one. I got the one for Xbox.
So I bought the one for GameCube and I got sent the Xbox, the regular Xbox one.
So thankfully I have a 360 and it can play Xbox games.
If I didn't own an Xbox or a 360 that would be probably pretty mad right now.
Is this the right one? What do you mean the wrong game? The incredible HULK ULTIMATE DESTRUCTION.
8.9 out of 10 from Xbox magazine. This is the right game. Wait, hold on. Is it it's not is it HULK ULTIMATE DESTRUCTION?
Or it's not THE INCREDIBLE HULK ULTIMATE DESTRUCTION. This is wrong?
No, it's not. That would be the dumbest thing ever.
If you made a game called HULK ULTIMATE DESTRUCTION and then somebody else made it THE INCREDIBLE HULK ULTIMATE DESTRUCTION.
There's a lawsuit there somewhere. That's stupid. No, this is the right fucking game.
Anyways, that's what we're gonna do today and maybe tomorrow depending on how much fun I have playing this and
we have a lot more money come. First of all, 10 community subs
I said it but I wanted but I don't want to just skip it.
10 subs is a lot of money from LM man. 5 from SoyDev. 100 dollars from Gibby20 dollars.
200 dollars from Fatal Finale.
220,000 bits and they say auto healthy.
Thank you for the fucking 20,000 bits.
That's a shitload of money to give a
fucking e-clown on the internet. Thanks for the huge amount of money Fatal Finale or Fatal
Fainal or Fainal Fatale.
No, Fainal Fainale?
There's no T in Finale. All right. It's been a long week. I feel like I've said it's been a long week.
Every time I come back to do a new stream week. Do I say that's like the last three weeks?
Rip Alex Trebek. Thanks for the five community subs. Fatal Finale again another 50 dollars.
You give him a shitload of money.
Yeah, I just want to look this up. Yeah, Alex. Alex Trebek is...
Okay, I was about to be I was about to get very very sad right there.
Anyways, a
Fatal Finale. Thanks for the 250 fucking dollars. Oh shit. I'm getting the screensaver in Xbox. That means like play the game, right?
Yeah, I see the card here. This is very very sweet of you guys.
It's always a scary thing when one of your most favorite things in the world might be very very sick. It's it's not good.
It's not fun. I really appreciate all the support and everybody that said all the nice things.
He's doing fine though. How do I play Hulk the incredible Hulk?
Ultimate 50 community subs that just came in from Zyxia.
Thanks for the 50 subs. Oh my god. That's a lot. That's a shitload of subs. That's that's ten subs times five.
It's a lot of money. That's an extreme amount of money. Thanks for the 50 subs.
Thanks for the five subs from Wingman and thanks for the 50 dollars from Dupa.
5,000 bits they say blush. For some reason blush. Why are you blushing? Thanks for the 50 fucking dollars.
Difficulty easy or normal you're gonna make me look bad if I pick easy, so I'll do normal. Thanks a lot guys. Seriously opening cutscene
I'm gonna be quiet and by that I'll probably maybe for the first 10 seconds. We'll be quiet, and then I'll be like
This is what happened to me today. That's what happens every time right? Not this time.
There's a thin line between good and bad. As you know how long my ethernet cable is right now.
Every single day when I stray from it, and this is me.
This is me.
Is this game any good? Were you guys lying to me? This game is terrible.
Why does it look like GTA 5? That was just a GTA 5. That's a GTA 5. That's the same graphics.
Branson military base present day. Is this where I punch a building once and it explodes?
VR?
Welcome to the HULK survival program.
What?
In this series of exercises you will approximate HULK's basic abilities.
Someone's playing
Someone's playing a VR game of the HULK of me controlling the HULK in an Xbox game.
Hasn't been following that?
Try running into various obstacles here to get a sense of the creature's power.
All this is merely a virtual representation of the beast.
It's not that impressive. Be reminded that HULK is actually capable of most feats demonstrated here.
Hold R. Another example of HULK's immense strength.
He seems capable of picking up virtually anything.
Cool!
Approach any object and press B.
Press the grab throw control to lift it.
Okay, that's a... am I gonna lose like the mech warrior stuff on the HUD on the screen?
Holy shit, that was insane.
A is jump.
Pressing X once performs a basic attack. Use X, X, X to do three punch combo.
This is already more fun than the last one.
Pressing the special button will activate HULK's more advanced techniques.
Unleashing everything he's got.
These will often launch or stun.
Knee smash, uppercut.
As with HULK's other techniques, holding the button will increase the power of each technique.
It is vitally important you research HULK's various combat abilities.
Wait, it's... it's like X, X, Y?
Extremely fast.
Y, X, X.
This is cool.
This is a complete list of HULK's known combat techniques.
This sounds too low in the game.
Should I blast it?
Chew... uh...
Alright.
Let's ultimate destroy, right?
Did that guy just say game on?
Wait, can I hold jump down?
That guy gave me a 10. I shouldn't have killed him.
Ooh, a cow.
Oh god, that was... Tara, that was horrible.
Okay, I don't want to do that again.
I don't want to kill cows.
Alright, let's do a mission.
This is just a sprint. This is sprint really fast.
Okay.
Am I the only one that played this game as a kid?
Now you learn how to... I thought that just said regret.
Now you learn how to target and attack enemies
by throwing objects at them.
Helicopters don't fly around, they just get them.
Once the beast has located a perceived threat,
he will launch objects with no
regard for human life.
Tap or hold the designated
grab throw button to launch
an object at your cost.
These guys don't even care.
Can I sneak up on these guys?
Holy shit!
Okay, look at helicopter. Pull and hold L
to target the helicopter.
Okay, throw.
This is stupid.
I got it.
That was not effective.
Can I grab another helicopter to throw
at the other helicopter?
Whoa!
Alright, let's go. Where's the helicopter?
Holy shit, that was
destructive.
It's almost like I can feel the Hulk hands.
Okay.
Why is he...
You can switch targets while in targeting mode.
Target a helicopter, okay.
Awww!
This game makes you really feel like Hulk.
Why did he curve?
Why are these guys ping pong balls?
Alright, let's just get out of this
tutorial. They're homing.
This is fun.
I think I'm going to like this game. Now I understand why
you guys told me I bought the wrong one.
Oh, come on!
Was that a roller coaster tycoon roller coaster?
What was that?
That guy went far. Okay, I want to keep going.
This is fucking loud.
He's a strong one!
Look out! That's so...
Oh, god.
There's not a pigeon in the road, man.
This dude's throwing shit.
He's throwing whole tankers at you.
I need one more helicopter.
This one's pre-recorded.
Stop blowing
my fucking cover, dude.
Got it. No, I didn't.
Oh, yeah.
Show your new apartment.
Show my new apartment. Okay.
There it is. Bang place.
Or is it though?
Or is it though? Hold on a minute. What's this
big reveal?
Look at that thing! Oh, by the way,
it's Roger Rabbit, Slimer,
Qbert, and Carnage.
The four horsemen of the fucking apocalypse.
You're a nerd.
Welcome to Twitch.tv, you fucking
weirdo. What shirt is this?
Captain Marvel, I think?
Clown. It's a clown shirt?
I mean, this guy has a clown shirt.
There you go. You got to see it.
And I got the Binding of Isaac board game.
Look at my displays.
You see what's up there? Binding of Isaac
board game card game. I never played it once.
I just bought it.
I bought it a year ago.
Also, Seaman's up there.
This is a kid's apartment.
How is this a kid's apartment?
Is this a kid's bedroom?
Look, I'm at...
It's a kid's bedroom.
Look at that display.
That's Blinky. That thing turns into
Blinky, Stinky,
Guppy, and
Ralph?
Who are the...
I know Blinky's the only one. I'm a fake fan.
Clyde. There it is.
Show your face,
Carpet.
He's a man-child.
It's a coaster. Relax.
It's a fucking coaster,
guys. Man-child.
No, I have a look.
I have a streamer room now.
I thought about it and I was like, you know what?
I got to have Blinky back there like
Pac-Man. Cheeto.
I got like Q-Bird and stuff.
I'm a fucking streamer. This is a Redditor
room.
This is a Redditor office.
All right. Relax.
Relax, everybody.
This is a Redditor office.
No, it is not.
Redditors don't even fucking like Pac-Man.
If the Witcher,
if I had like a Geralt statue
up there, I would agree with you.
That's fucking Blinky, Stinky, Guppy, and
Brutal.
OK? That's not a
Redditor shelf.
Geraldo.
All right. I got to fucking read this shit.
You're distracting the fuck out of me.
Eggscramble just gave $50.
Not a Redditor shelf.
No, I'm sorry.
Q-Bird. You think Redditors care about Q-Bird?
Or Roger Rabbit?
OK, I'll give you Carnage.
But I liked Carnage before Redditor did.
Fuck. I got to stop saying that.
Slimer. I liked Slimer
before Reddit was even a website.
That's my favorite Ghostbusters character.
That shit was 1987.
OK? Reddit didn't come out until like
95. So please.
I'm a huge Slimer fan.
And by the way, that's the
rare, that's the rare Pog.
What are they called? Pog with Pops?
That's the rare Pog.
That's Slimer with the hot dogs in his mouth. That thing's worth like
$400.
I bought it for $500, but I thought
it was going to keep appreciating, and it didn't. It went down in price a little bit,
but it's still worth $400.
Nice apartment, man.
Hold on. What?
OK, you make me
want to get one of these.
You make me want to get one of these.
I think I want to get one of these. That would be so stupid.
Imagine having like a Pepsi
fucking vending machine in your office.
That would be so annoying.
And I would pay it.
I would put money in it and shit.
That's so small.
I'm going to get one of those. I'm going to get like an old
Pepsi machine where I have to put money in and press the button
and it's wicked loud.
And I'm sorry, a Gumby sofa?
You wouldn't have a Gumby sofa in your
house? What's wrong with you?
Why? Why would you not
want a gum? I don't care if you're
12 or 80.
That's fucking awesome.
Alright, if
you're 35 and you still get
to play Pokemon, then I get to be
35 and have a Qbert Puck, OK?
You know, that's how it works.
None of us are doing it. Yes, you are.
Alright, another
fucking huge amount of money just came in.
Guys, I haven't even done the first part
of the tutorial in the Hulk.
Thank you, Egg Scramble. They say
that's $50 from Egg Scramble.
Mmm, yummy bits, yum please.
Pass the parmesan. Parmesan in eggs
is actually really, really good.
You take the eggs, beat up your eggs.
Like three or four of them.
Add some pepper.
Add a splash of milk and put in
a bunch of parmesan cheese.
Go...
until they're nice and smooth and then
make scrambled eggs. They're delicious.
Trust me. If you don't believe me,
try it once and then don't ever do it again,
but then I'll be right. It's OK.
Anyways, thanks for the $50. Thanks for the $50
fucking dollars from Filactory Lich.
5,000 bits.
This is an R
slash male living space.
Burn those Funko Pops.
That's the only ones I have.
What do you mean burn those Funko Pops?
Roger Rabbit, that's a fucking rare one.
You can't even buy that one anymore.
I knew I shouldn't have fucking shown you these.
I have four Funko Pops.
Oh wow, I don't have a fucking
closet full of these things.
I don't have like 300 of them.
They're just like, they were like, OK, over the last
like six years, I've gotten
four.
If you have less than 10 Funko Pops,
that's fine. More than 20?
You need a space for it, and if you don't,
that's a little too much after 2030, I think
that's, you don't have, who has space for that?
I got four. I have to play
the game. Four, uh, people start
to get mad at me. Make it
zero.
Why? They're like,
they're fine.
What's this one? OK.
A series of markers will appear above the base of
OK, this is jump.
Cool.
OK, yeah, so you can jump.
Jumping is cool. Jumping works.
There we go.
That's his primary ability?
I mean, is it? I guess.
Is this a cow?
Why is he making like,
you know, find somebody
that can make a good cow noise?
He can't. It's really hard
to do that. Everybody
always does that.
No.
Dude, a cow actually goes like
nobody
can do it.
It doesn't go moo.
It's a white stain in your office.
What the fuck are you talking about?
Yeah, you can charge. Charge.
Did I get all the markers?
Final tutorial incoming.
Germon face can't be light. What the fuck is this?
It's grow time.
Grow time. Grow time.
Grow time.
What the hell is this?
Why is this so high quality?
Are you going to go on a rant yet?
No.
All right. Half of you guys want me to go off on a fucking rant.
And the other half want to see Hulk
Ultimate Destruction.
No, I'm going to play.
Two of sixty comic books.
Oh, cool. Extras.
What's the last thing that it wants me to know?
Hulk can climb and run up walls.
Oh, he can run up walls. I didn't know that.
Run up walls. Good thing I didn't.
Press and hold the grab button to approximate Hulk's
ability to climb sheer surfaces.
Try it now.
Do I have to hold
the whole time? No, I don't.
Holy shit, this is actually kind of cool.
This is like a Spider-Man ability.
All right, let's go. Time to play the game.
It's only been thirty minutes, guys.
Germa, get more funk. You already ranted
about Funko Pops.
You can run. Oh, God.
It's kind of hard to control.
Was it Sick Hulk?
Don't say cool, say Pog instead.
No, I'm thirty-five.
You might be like under
the age of thirty or twenty-five or something, and that's
like fine, but my generation says cool
or sick.
Pog. Right? No, I get it.
Pick up a missile pack
from the roof of the building.
Missile pack?
And then weaponize it.
Wait, I
This is so stupid.
Why don't I just shoot?
Just use it as a rocket launcher.
Oh, because I have to, I get it.
I was going to say, why am I not just using it like
shooting it out of my shoulder?
Hulk's ability to apply his incredible
strength to create new powerful weapons.
Spend your smash points to unlock the many
and varied weapons. Cool. All right, let's go.
I'm done. Smash? Okay,
this grow time thing is over here. What is that even
from? Is that like a Fruit of the Loom
commercial?
They've unlocked a cheat code.
Hulk Canada.
Once Hulk has acquired an object,
the creature will frequently manipulate
it to fashion a makeshift weapon.
Such as a missile.
If Hulk uses B to grapple an enemy if his size
are smaller, using B again will throw him.
Or battering ram.
A favorite ploy, often referred
to as the steel fist technique,
is to turn a vehicle into a
pair of metal gauntlets.
Press the special button
to demonstrate this weaponization.
Wait, I can grab a...
I need a car.
Weaponize it. Weaponize this.
Oh, this is not technically
not a car.
I need a car. I feel like this game is gonna be
a blast.
Is this a car? No, it's also like a
truck. Is it only trucks?
Okay.
There we go. They're the Hulk hands.
Actual Hulk hands.
Why does Hulk need
Hulk hands? That doesn't make any
sense. All right, let's go. I'm out.
Is to make you stronger.
All right, I'm starting to get the feel for that one.
We found comic book four.
It's a movie. Speaking of movies,
here comes a cutscene. It's been 40 minutes.
Return to the bug menu.
Save. Hard
Xbox hard disk. All right,
should we... Let's go. Oh, by the way,
how's the internet? Hey, how's
the internet?
We good? Cool.
Those of you that don't know,
I'm going to link the fucking
Giazio. We got fucking
fiber.
That's right. We're on fiber now, folks.
I've been trying
to get fiber for five years. I finally
fucking have it.
Out getting some fresh air.
Bruce, he's requisitioned half the men and supplies
in the bay.
If I came into town, everyone would be
in danger. He's better looking than me.
I'm urging you to reconsider.
Your health's deteriorating.
I'm going to attack on Titan's stomach.
And pull his hairline back
or tent it like maybe
a half an inch.
Make him back long
and roll his shoulders forward.
Send a warning shot his way,
General. Wait, he's in there?
I want him to get the point.
Why does he feel like a Gmod map?
We'd give away our position.
This is a Gmod horror
map.
Towards the outhouse by the west wall.
Holy shit.
Don't stand behind it.
Wait, I was
in there?
That's a small little shack.
Get to the jump marker and use
it to escape. Let's go.
Whenever an enemy is defeated, you get smash
points. Power-ups are also
spawned. Wait, you collect these?
Power-ups are also spawned. Do I have to
collect them?
Collected a power-up. Keep track of Hulk's health
using power meter.
You can move much more quickly by using R to
make Hulk run.
Maximum speed can be attained by pulling and holding
down R rather than tapping it.
Can I get a tree?
That was kind of dumb.
General, wait, I'm getting food. Well, hurry up.
Don't hurry up.
Slow down.
Get it slow. Don't rush.
Pause the game.
What? What the fuck? Pause?
Do you know how fast
it takes to heat up even like a bowl
of EZ-Mac? It's like at least three or four
minutes. No, we don't have time for that.
Get to the jump marker.
There we go. Nice.
This runs through people.
Why even
wait, no, no, I want the power points, right?
As an alternative to throwing,
use X while Hulk is an enemy to do
an attack on them. Cool.
Cool.
Well, now you're dead.
I actually have to run into the
power points, don't I? Just pick up the
tank and throw it.
Certain enemies are armored. Uncharged
attacks will not damage an armored opponent.
You must charge your attacks to be able to damage
armored opponents. Tanks are always armored.
Why is this moving so fast?
What?
Where, where, where, where, where?
Did I catch the missiles?
Why? There's like too much
I can?
I'm going to catch a missile.
I'll try.
What the fuck is happening?
I just feel like I'm playing on
Battlefield 64
versus 64.
Catch it. Oh, there's the tanks.
I'm going to die.
He's bad. I mean,
I guess. Can I throw these?
Don't stay initially explosive.
Nice. Wait, I can get power.
Just throw shit. The movement's actually
pretty fucking fluid, right?
No, I don't want to throw it at you.
Alright, I'm just going to run.
Who cares?
No, I have to kill one tank. No, I don't.
It doesn't matter. I just have to go.
What happened?
You're dying to tanks. Yeah, because Tay is strong.
Why are they getting health?
I got it. Oh, good. Power up.
There we go. I know what it is. I know what it is.
I've been trying to figure it out. I've been trying to find out
what the fucking sound is that Hulk is making
over and over again, and I haven't said
anything about it because I didn't want to fuck up the scream.
It's Diablo 2
Diablo boss sounds when you attack
Diablo.
They're like...
I've just been waiting to
figure it out. I figured it out.
When the Hulk's power reaches critical mass, his rage feeds
his strength. Later, you'll be able to
buy some devastating special attacks that are
fueled by your critical mass.
Alright, so am I at critical
mass?
I like that one the best.
Let's go.
Stop. No, it's called Hulk
Ultimate Destruction.
Not Hulk Be Gentle.
Well, that would be pretty fun.
That would be kind of a fun game, don't you think?
Where the fuck am I going?
What the fuck is going on?
I made it to the drop zone.
Let's go. I'm at critical mass.
Why do I have to power up? Okay, I get it.
Another $50.
Holy shit.
So much money.
Noooo!
No, doesn't he become other Hulk?
Yeah, he turns into Hulk
other Hulk.
Orange Hulk, right?
Whatever his name is.
Abominable Snowman.
Mega Agro gave $5,000.
That's $50.
That's a lot of fucking money.
Don't listen to chat. Your office looks comfy.
And I hope the rest of the place is too.
Long time fan since 2013. Yadda yadda yadda.
I love ya.
I also hope Otto feels better. He's a good boy.
I wasn't just skipping that. That was in the message.
That's not me being rude.
That's in the message.
I appreciate that. Thank you.
It is comfy.
Does the Hulk not have nipples?
I don't understand the jean shorts, by the way.
Why wouldn't you just wear like Spandex?
Like really stretchy Spandex underwear.
And that's it.
Why do I have to do VR?
Hulk Ultimate Destruction.
Is it just like VR?
Or do I actually do Ultimate Destruction?
Banner's remaining hope for a cure for his affliction, a machine designed to delve into his psyche, by all the beast within, has been left in ruins as a result of the attack.
Good job on the fucking teleprompter, idiot!
Thanks a lot.
Now that Banner has-
Fucking dumbass.
Adversary a former NSA operative named
Milblonsky
Is it taking a joint who cares?
Everyone knows what the fucking Hulk is the Hulk like
Radiated guy and there's another guy that wants to be radiated in strong 2 and he's huge and he can fucking punch through walls
You don't need to know anything else
Like what else do you need to know about the whole of a handheld neural interface?
It can perform read or write operations directly into a patient's mind
You've read or write in fact without fucking Windows permissions mission objectives into your mind. Holy shit, man
violently transformed
Be pleasant, but it's the only chance we've got
Read or write man. I don't know. I was I didn't know I was using a CDRW fuck man. I don't care
See look, that's what I'm saying. Just wear fucking stretchy underwear
Why rip through a good pair of jean shorts when you could just wear a bathing suit?
Just get one like one or two sizes. Look Hulk's waist is not that much bigger than Bruce Banner's
what is he like a
what is Bruce like a
38 like 37
What is the Hulk like a 60?
Just get like a 50 or like a 55 and it's gonna be a little loose on Bruce
But that's alright and then when it expands he just expands into its spandex. What's I don't why where's she like jeans?
It's a fast travel. Wait, there's a super fast jump to city
All right, the till boat brand hotel
You can't do this
World
Batman music that's pretty cool. This is an objective defeat the police resistance. What?
go
Wait, this is pedestrians walking around right now
Why would you walk around right now?
Come here. Hey, you're green me too. We're now best friend
Hulk is bouncing off. Do you got to watch out? Hope Hulk is really pop it off right now
What was that? Sorry
I'll never understand this shit man. They always do this in like movies and TV shows and
Freeze, that's it hands in the air
This is a fucking alien mutant person that is that can kill you in one punch and no bullets work
I don't think they're going to freeze and put their hands up that we continue to see this in media
The nine millimeter is not gonna work against the guy that can literally pick up a car and throw it into it and it explode
Into another car and without any problem
media
Like you don't tell this guy holding the giant fucking ball
Put that ball down and then you go like
It's not gonna do anything. What you should have just not done that
Okay that car
Car humping another car. Okay, that's that's just
Oh
Yes. Yes, they fit in this one, too. It's in this one, too. They just drive into stuff. I'm so happy
Why was this one better than the last one? Oh, is this one a better game?
You're getting away
This one's just the same game except a little bit better frame rate and not based on Edward North
Break a building. All right, I'm gone
It's like rampage. You have to climb up and break and hit every part of it
Like you have to punch here and then here and then here and then here for the building fall
How's work
It's a good game. Didn't they bring make it to maybe I should play it. Wait, what's this coin? That's 2,000 fucking crazy point
Break the targets. I
Want to how are these people faster than me? All right, what's over there?
This would be fucking horrifying. Can you imagine this shit?
I think you could have thrown up like five times by now
Your head would be in your stomach your stomach would be inside of your esophagus
All right new objective this is over here what is up here what's with the green with the black in the middle
What does that mean? Oh
That's a story mission. What is this one then get gorilla get gorilla. We didn't get the eight
We mean get the eight
Use the cheat code wait instead of it so you missed it. What do you mean?
I yeah, are you telling me that I get to be a gorilla instead of the Incredible Hulk for the rest of the game?
No, no, so we grab the gorilla. I don't even
cheat code
Lightning strike we need to take a big risk Bruce
We're gonna use the Hulk to help us build the machine through hypnotic implants and auto suggestion blue thing
Watts to run the equipment and you want me to smash up the main grid just the relevant parts
I've identified three key substations that need to be taken out, but be careful. They're surrounded by high-voltage Tesla fields
Okay, so destroy substation a B and C
Okay, easy enough sounds easy
Destroy the 5g towers put up the moves list to see what you could do now if you couldn't do the other game
I'll give it a try
see
Diablo I move gallery steel fists. It's only what I got
Destroy the power substations. You got it. Let's bust
Person alright, okay destroy substation a I grab the spotlight. It's too bright. I don't want it. You're a psycho
all right
Hmm got it. It's two more. Oh, it's I'm turning off those lights. I get it
It's well if you tell if you can find all these hints you unlock a special prize
Seems a little extreme. All right, let's go. I
Like the jump the jump is a lot of fun power 12 foot tall mandolin
Something about that doesn't make any sense
Let's put on the steel fist
AC
Dive to go in the water
Flicked her and it killed her
But please but put your hands up Hulk
Hands up, please
I'm getting able vibes. I would
Every five to ten seconds somebody in the town said Oh
chicken chicer
It's not that chicken chicer. Oh
And I would say it would make more sense to me
Bloody food chicken chicer
Never change your name. No, why would I it doesn't add anything to the gameplay?
Use the eight balloons
All right. Where are these eight things? You guys are talking about my critical mass
Well, I think I got a critical mass fucking back in this guy you get up you can play as Ben Stiller
It's been still it in the whole movie
And it was no it wasn't was he
Ben Stiller was the Hulk. Oh
Get the hamburger. No
That's so funny. I would actually a Ben Stiller Hulk would probably pretty good. I don't think it would be bad
Do you really think of Ben Stiller Hulk would be a bad Hulk?
Wait, what do you mean F? What do you mean F?
F where I don't have any drop frames. I have zero drop frame
What I think it was your computer I have no drop range I
Think it's your computer all of our computers. Yeah, all of them is all of you
There's everyone's computer at the same time. Oh, it breaks. That's dumb
I don't have any drop frames. I don't I don't know if it's weird usually if it was a problem to be a drop right?
Now I think I got them all right. Oh, there's the star
There are two types of missions story missions and challenge missions story missions of those which progress the story
Build a machine to find a cure for the gamma mutation challenge missions are additional objectives and challenges
They can be annotated by Hulk during the course of play and their exclamation point
This is incredible Hulk ultimate destruction wiki guide gorilla balloons everywhere is King King
We I've played for like less than 30 minutes you want me to cheat
I'm not cheating. I'm not gonna cheat right now
Let's go to the buy menu
dashing straight air recovery running grab ground smash backhand punt kick
It's high power kick is useful for distancing troublesome phones X X Y. I want this
sonic clap air stomp
Slam down to clear. Oh, yeah
It's why in the air you just fly down. That's perfect
smash express
Run with a two-handed weapon the smash express pick up any two-handed object and deliver the pain
X or Y when you run with a two-handed weapon and press X
I'll try it
And then Sonic clap create a sonic wave. Yep. All right, let's try these
Can you hear it? No, my noise gate is there
Let's try this that's gonna be so much fun. I can't with the one two and then punch
Okay, this is Sonic clap
Nice. Okay. What was the other one in the air? Oh
Gonna have so much fun with that one
All right jump to the city
Shit, there's a lot of stuff here
Stomp move is great. It looks pretty good
Next story need to know
What are the challenge mission?
You just turn into a meteor nice the punt is fun
Sonic boom
Let me try challenge it use code King. No, not yet. I don't want to cheat
Is this bulk ultimate cheating?
Please cheat. No, I'm not cheating
destroy as many spotlights as possible before time runs out destroy as many
Okay, destroy as many spotlights as possible, excuse me, by the way, don't do this again
I want to oh, by the way, I get something out recently
Everything I've ever recorded on here has is saved
All right spotlights go
for one
That's another spotlights. That's just a regular light. It's just a light
spotlight
Spotlight, where are they got to three? I didn't get it. All right, it's kind of hard to control
this two three
Four
My where they um, um, um, um, um over this way, um, I don't know. Um
All right, just climb the fucking tower thing
Beautiful Joe go fur
No, it's like glue and sticky and shit. It's weird. Oh
Okay. Now I got the bronze medal
Silver's gonna be right here. Check it out
Let's just go ran over
Beautiful. No, you can't play this game. It's I don't care that you think it's fun
Where the viewers was it? Oh, he has it. Come on. Give me silver
Holy shit. Look up there 20 seconds. Go all the way up. This is like no
I got the bronze medal. That's worth 6,000 points. What am I here? The shark tank sound effect? What's the shark tank sound effect?
He doesn't know no, I have no idea what you're talking about shark tank sound effect
We'll have to be quick. Blonsky knows we're on to him according to an intercepted memo
His which one the one that goes computer terminal inside division
Before blonsky realizes his mistakes the song the information it contains could be vital to our chances of success
Is that the one?
When does it happen?
Run run run run run run run run run
It does that when I need to hear it. It's the oh the one that goes
Sharks have introduced
This guy with his new serial company, whatever. Okay. I know what you mean. Yeah, I got it
Reach the hq and locate the mainframe computer. Oh shit. I thought I was gonna fix that shark tank
Noise, hold on the greatest shark tank invention. I have to hear this
Yes, it goes like that's not the sound. Where's the actual sound?
That was so loud that's not this is hell's kitchen is this it I had it right let's hold on shark tank
Uh clip shark tank song
There it is
Don't even say this no, it's not it's not
I can't even do this shit, man
Free to beware. You're in for a scare
Well, we figured out something today can I pee I gotta pee real bad beer back
Um
Shark tank is a cool show I just tell you that
I like when they fight over how much equity they're gonna get the company
But the best part
I also love all the people always start off with the they're like the little production they put up. They're like pitch
They do the exact same thing that I taught you guys
The look left look right the look left look right
look forward
Present look left look right look forward
both hands up
Presentation it works every time look left look right look straight ahead. Just keep doing that
You don't never have to look at anybody reach the division headquarters
Keep presenting crack
No crack. Ah
All right, let's go
Play hulk ultimate destruction gerba play hulk ultimate destruction
Sure thing man
I'll play it right now
I'll play it now
Sure, i'll play it right now
At first did the cop just shoot that car?
Is that why that happened?
The telephone pole
You guys aren't very good
I just find her rocket directly into like one of the thinnest objects on earth
Who is talking to me retrieve it retrieve the power
Wait
That coin
Come on. Give me the
Give me the coin thing
Give me this
turn the slab
Oh a 10 000 smash point bonus
i'm
fucking
Ecstatic
All right, we're gonna break break break break
I got the mainframe computer
All right, throw box at helicopter
Whatever mission objective requires hulk to protect something the health of that objective is displayed by the blue health meter
Weak objects may not have any additional pips while strong objects like buildings may have several
Um deliver them
Uh, this is gonna last
Dude, this thing's almost fucking dead. It's almost destroyed
Where do I have to bring this?
What did it say?
Bring it back to okay
I I feel like this is what happens
This is like what goes through my mind as to why when when my like when like warcraft used to fucking lag
Like this is what was happening in my mind. Like what's going on? It's fucking server
This could play out in my head
This was the problem
Here you go. Here's your computer
The key to all our problems is emil blonsky
We know he was sent by the nsa to monitor gamma prisoners held inside the vaults the shark tank narrator given the intro
He's a very dangerous individual his record suggests an emerging persecution complex
Perhaps a borderline personality disorder, but you better believe if he's here to supervise ross
He's trying to find a military application for gamma transformations
Here he is sharks i'm here today with gamma radiation
And they all lean forward most of it's a
It's hulk progresses through the game here in smash point smash points are easy purchases new moves from the buy menu either in the mission success
Greater back at the back door of the church
You now have enough smash points to purchase them and move
Going in the mini one go find it
At the top right corner of your display the enemy response system
Meter is about to turn on smash stuff and the enemy response system
threat level rises
smash lots of stuff and a deadly strike team will be sent to combat hulk just like your favorite game grand theft auto
three
two
four five
And possibly six because I don't think this was in yes it was it was in all the grand theft autos every single one
It was a an integral part of the whole game since its franchise's inception
I don't know why I didn't think stars
Were in grand theft auto one
That's gonna be the big change. That's gonna be the big gameplay shift in gta 6 no more stars
We've decided to get rid of the star system
Fuck what that's insane. How are we gonna?
How's we gonna do like the police cops and stuff and like uh, there's a new system
All right back hand for sure x y x
round smash
Running grab. Yep, that looks pretty good. Yeah while running you just hold
Yeah, would you like to try out the move?
I can try this out
This is a weeb hulk
Oh
There's no winks guys. They're gone
Can't trick me try following the
That's you can nice throw whiz running throw
Why on earth did I decide to do this to make a loading screen to do something that I know I was
completely capable of
Okay, that was
Why did I even need to do that activate the jump marker?
How big do you think hulk's shits are?
um
I have a better question for you
This is the questions that people don't ask
so if hulk
eats five pizzas
When he turns back into bruce banner do those five pizzas still sit inside of bruce banner and does he take the mega shit?
You know what i'm saying?
if the hulk drinks
Five gallons of liquid because of the hulk and these you gotta stay hydrated
And then he gets really really happy. What happens to that pee?
Let's just say come out of him like spongebob
You know like the spongebob square
And like the water comes all out of him and shit like is that gonna happen would that happen to you
Would come out of like his skin what why is this such a fucked up thing to ask?
What you never thought about this in your whole life
If you have a guy that's 12 feet tall and can eat like
20 pounds of meat in one sitting
When he turns back into bruce that's gotta go somewhere. It's gonna come out his eyes like the play-doh toy
like the spaghetti
my play-doh spaghetti toy with like the
Apparently that makes me a fucked up person to bring this up. I guess
Yes
Protect and serve one two three
That was awful. Hi
guys, there was like a
Shitty little meme on this channel for like a couple of days about somebody talking about
Shit and you all thought it was hysterical
A specific copy and paste shit thing everybody thought was the funniest thing in the world
But I talk about bruce bannard. You need to go to the bathroom after eating
12 hamburgers at the hulk and i'm the psychopath
I don't have any I don't have to move on long. Oh, well, where is this?
To a challenge fast movers six run through the course as fast as bugging to do this. This can be bad
This is gonna be real bad. We hold you to a higher standard
You shouldn't that's your biggest mistake
So where where where's this race?
Right here. Ah
What what kind of kind of track was this?
Okay, uh that didn't follow any logic at all
don't jump
Hit it
silva
Ah
I told you I was gonna fix this and I didn't fix it
If hulk eats a person and then turns back into bruce bannard does banner still have to digest the person hulk aid
Yes
Read it. I don't want to read it about eating right now
All right. Do I not have another story mission? Where is the story?
There ain't no story mission here. Oh there is I need to move
Fuck I need that. I need a new move. All right. I need to buy go back to the church
What moves do I need air?
Air recovery, okay. I gotta just go this way
Honey over here get it. And why am I illiterate? Look at the link. I already did
Shit in a blt sandwich and nobody bats and I talked about bruce banner's monster shits and everyone loses their money
Yes
exactly
You know when people just get maybe we just get you
You know when people just get you
This is one of those scary
And by the way, how the fuck are you guys?
All right. All right. I gotta buy air recovery. This game is
fucking awful
Kidding kidding kidding kidding kidding kidding kidding kidding kidding air recovery. I don't even know how to do it
Recover instantly from any attack that floats hulk into the air. This is important
Okay, how about dashing straight high speed attack great for clearing just about anything
All right, we need double fist tossed is a mission thing for a while on the move. Yeah
Okay, 25 000 for this. Why do I feel like all these moves?
I feel like I got them all so early. I just bought them all i've done two missions
There are more sick. There's a fuckload more
You don't have to say the f word
Why would you say the f word?
It's like kind of rude and shit
It's the part where I say too much to the f word. No swearing here. Fucking idiot. Like I say fuck
You know what I mean? Like I think don't say that and then I say it and then everybody laughs
Is it guys this streamer is kind of toxic?
And then that's when I go i'm not toxic. What are you talking about? We just have fun here
Just chill. We're having a good time and then I say you fucking idiot. Oh
Ha ha ha
Why didn't I grab?
Grab it
Eat the giant hamburger. You can't I already tried
Wait, I'll try the new move
Holy shit, my whole body is like shaking right now. How cool that was
All right. Here we go
We have a target of opportunity. I've hacked a lab computer at a division research facility, which is illegal very
I just tripped a fail safe. So blonsky knows i'm inside
He'll destroy the entire place before he allows the download to complete
You're asking me to run protection while you loot the network six or seven minutes. That's all I need seven seven minutes
Seven minutes is all I need to destroy bio research center
Defend the bio research center until the data downloads. What kind of connection do you have?
So oh I need data so you're downloading protect. It's probably text right how much data is on there
if you need to wait 10 minutes to download like
Three to four thousand k of stuff
Get another fucking service provider get another computer. I can I could I recommend fiber internet to you i'm on it
This is 2004. Oh shit. It was
Wait average
That's broad a broadband existed in 2000 average
internet speeds
in 2004
oh
uh
2000k is what the average was
This
Fuck how is that so spot on the average cable is 21 78
avps
Okay. Well, that's accurate then we're still on wi-fi. Am I on that or am I on ometer? Which one? I don't know. I'm not sure
Uh-huh
Three and a half. I thought whatever happened seven minutes. That was an incredibly wrong estimate
Hope this is gonna take you seven minutes to do just getting three minutes and 30 seconds
See the target
Get out of here
Oh, yes
Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait running running crap
I love the wind up
Backhand is back in
Wait destroyed
Where this tank?
critical massachew good
Try this shit get rid of this tank. Come on kick it
How many tanks are here?
Dude, how many stars do I have?
This shit didn't even happen in gta. Oh, maybe one would come down the road
Do we take
Two more minutes
dead
When let's command and conquer when hulk's power gets low he experiences an adrenaline surge this increases his attack the image
Give some access to special moves
Okay
I'm an adrenaline surge
I have the hulk mod unlocked for command and conquer
There's too many
What the fuck?
Kick him
There we go. All right hunt one two hunt
That's so good
Blood. Yeah, this blood is fucking game. What do you think about it now?
Let's throw trees
Command and conquer tanks get the fuck out of here
No, please kick it kick it kick it kick it smash it do anything
Why won't you die?
Do a falcon kick. I'm I got I've got armor there right now
Mission complete do some jump cancels
Wait now I have to destroy the building
Hold on
What the hell do you mean need to know bases?
Calm down. You've commandeered the interval and established a level 15 clearance only the president senior cabinet members have that access
Surely you of all people don't need a lesson in protocol
That's what it looks like a minute of fondant
You'd be more concerned with keeping the hulk in check
You're not as clever as you think you are blonsky if I so much as imagine you're keeping anyone
But god almighty in that cell i'll find out and be on you like a dog
Oh, no, I thought he's gonna turn around and be surprised by the person behind him. No
No
Is the green goblin no
You can't kill them all
That's a green goblin scenario when you look in the mirror when you have hulk powers the green goblin talks to you
Samson captured top secret files from the mainframe you obtained from the roof of the division building
Bonsky's files contain vital division intelligence
Useful for samson and hulk in accomplishing their goal as you advance through your missions
Samson will continue to unlock these secret files and new ones will become available to you
Proceed to the church in order to read the files
Okay, that was his dnd character
Maybe I should go to the buy menu
You guys understand
I was around and I know here come like the boomer emotes and the old person emote
But I remember being on 28.8. K
That was back when if somebody picked up the telephone
Your whole your whole computer crashed
Can you imagine being in the living room on a 28.8k connection in some random chat room somewhere?
and somebody
in the upstairs
Bedroom picked up the telephone
Your computer crashed
I remember it would be like if something really important was happening
It would be like some reasons like if my father was on the computer and he's like
He would always just scream up to everybody whoever was upstairs or wherever he'd be like
All right. I got an important thing going on here. Nobody pick up a phone
And it's like oh shit. Okay. Nobody could we can't do anything
We cannot communicate with anybody
Ever for the next like probably two three four hours, but you would forget
And you would pick up a phone and it would do that
And you freak out and hang it up immediately and hope to god that it wasn't gonna fuck up the connection to fuck up the computer
And all of a sudden you would hear it would be like this be like
Oh, yeah, I gotta call uh, I gotta call mike. Yeah, I gotta talk to mike. Let me pick up the phone and
Fuck fuck fuck fuck
Fuck like a god. Damn it. It went
shit
I'm gonna pick up the phone
No, no, I no I I may have
It's like gah
That was life. Tell us more stories grandpa. I'm gonna save up for critical atomic slam
Plonsky files on samsung minimal contribution. Ouch
whatever
But I have my own file. This is worrying
I don't care
That's lore. Somebody else will read it. You took a screen to take a screenshot. You can read it later
You know that when me and burger boy used to sit in in burger boy's room and play video games all day
Every time there was that's like that's from me and burger boy
Anytime there was like something to read it was like, oh somebody else will read this and we just skipped it
For everything it didn't matter what it was if there was like a note on a table that was more than like four or five paragraphs
Long it was instantly skipped
If it was not integral to the video game
It was never read
Is that why you can't read? How did I read your comment then?
Maybe if you thought about shit before writing it
Put text to speech on I told you that I was never gonna do that
Oh gorilla
Pick up gorilla. All right, i've got gorilla
finally
This is like annoyingly in the way
Fire saver have to start putting the machine together
I'm stuck without a hydraulic lift to move the heavier parts
I need a generator for power conversion and a cat scan apparatus to get an accurate topographic image. I can deliver this shit. Okay
You gotta go on a home depot run
Oh, no, I lost the gorilla
Get the steel fists
Sucks I don't want to do this
This is pissing me off
There's no ninja turtle
Remember what ninja turtle game would come out every year?
from like
1989 to like 1999 or like 2005 or something. Where's the ninja turtles games? Yeah, what the fuck are they?
Ninja turtles games come out every single year
Across the whole city
Nice I can destroy buildings now do I need bulk hands?
This shit loud
Oh my god
You're standing on top of it. All right
What is this thing it's like a sonic the hedgehog spring dead the nintendo labo piece
Yeah, this is a nintendo labo completed construction
After using it one time. It's all bent and torn up and shit
gorilla
Wait, because they uh, he's an omen during here. Do I get this right jump to the church?
This is prototype, but the hulk
Yeah, I couldn't play prototype so
Is this this works for me?
It's the same devs as prototype. Is it really?
That's like kind of a pogchamp moment. Don't you think?
He's using emotes now and he thinks he like it sounds normal does not sound fucking
Natural at all. Holy shit go back to 56k. Stupid
The hulk has done billions of dollars in damage
Yeah
There's a lot of damage even just walking
Just look at this
I know a lot of people say like oh, yeah, what about the superheroes when they destroy stuff
We're just talking about like walking through the town
Like right there. This is this is like a four to five thousand dollar repair just from me walking on him. Just walking here
This is like a thirty thousand dollar repair job now
Gotta get in there like go in the beam
How well they have shields?
Don't worry. I'll take care of this
What's up, dude?
Oh, is that who's that?
Is that somebody, you know?
We'll say hi
How do you get rid of the shield?
Can I go in this? Wait
Did I get it?
Are they just all over the where are these shields?
I fell off
Sorry, man
Charge
What do you mean charge?
Charge?
Are you throwing shit?
Charge your phone
Why can't I pick up a phone?
All right, that's how you do it
Oh
Was ivan ooze the power rangers or was that the ninja turtle?
My god, they're firing
What the fuck get out of here, man
It was the secret of the ooze was a teenage ninja turtle
But ivan ooze was power ranger
ivan ooze
I feel like if I watched that movie again
I would probably really I probably like that movie more now than when I was 14
I gotta watch that I gotta watch power rangers
And the pursuit of ivan ooze whatever it's called in the
What's the name of that movie? What's the name of the power rangers movie? Well, if that's power rangers the movie too, right?
Name ivan ooze sounds like a german character
ivan ooze
What was the first power rangers movie about?
And wait, wasn't there a thing with like zordon?
Like zordon was like a guy like lying down on a coffin or something
Like zordon doesn't like zordon wait, what what happens to zordon?
Zordon was the weirdest character
He was just the wizard from the wizard of oz
And then why did they listen to zordon? Who was zordon?
Why would they listen to zordon?
Power rangers took all their orders from a guy that was like a floating
Uh hallucination in a tube, right?
Well, who was it? Did they ever go over the lore?
They did it was an alien
Yeah, uh, but
Was this a toilet or a fridge? What is this? I got all right. I got the toilet
Now hulk hulk hulk you brought back a fucking toilet. That's not what we wanted
We were looking for the uh, the cat scan machine
Oh, sorry. Yeah me dumb right?
And then it goes to the next part of robot chicken
Plus two I guess yeah, thanks
Yeah, I got 25k
What are we gonna spend our 25 000 points?
that was pretty uh sick like you won in smash brothers end of the
Completed right or something
Now put the phone down put the phone put the phone put the phone down you fucking asshole
Trying to save that
Don't try to cut me off. I'm done streaming right now
Don't open that phone. Don't pick it up
critical atomic slam
Extra range extra power no calories. So that's good
so in critical
mass
We're gonna get another one. Oh, I need ground smash first
I can get them both. Can I?
Brown smash and then super critical smash. All right, I gotta remember to do this
I bought them all didn't I?
I think jerma plans the jokes pre stream
I think you severely overestimate. Um my preparedness for each stream
Usually go something like this
I'm hungry. Fuck. I need to eat something before I sit down
Okay, let me eat. All right. What am I playing today? I have no idea. Um, well wait the incredible hulk was delivered today
That's uh, sure. Let's do that
Does it work? I don't know. When does the stream start? Um in like 40 minutes
Let's see if this stream can even happen. Okay, put it in. Yeah. No, it works
Okay, 20 minutes till the stream starts. I have I forgot to eat right? I did this first
I gotta eat something. Oh, I've had to take a shit for the last hour
Okay, let me do that too end of eating while i'm taking a shit
Which is i'm just trying to get double time there to make so I can get on here on time
And then I turn the button on
He's 10 steps ahead
At the end of a chapter a star marker will appear at the church. This marker will take the hulk to a new challenge
These guys are tough. So spend your smash points on new moves
Nemesis, oh here we go
Let's do it. We're gonna get our first boss fight. There's something happening at the military base
Listen to this transmission
Did he say some kind of creature i'm pretty sure that's not you bruce
Better go check it out before someone decides this is your fault
Okay, that was the equivalent
Of when you're writing on a piece of paper and you you wrote way too big
the first two or three words
and then when you get you're at the edge of the paper and you just got a fucking I
just fill it as many letters as I can and then
All the way to the edge of the paper. We're under attack. I'm kind of monster
Like you didn't utilize your four seconds of recording that you were allowed. Well, we're under attack
It's some kind of creature
Oh, you only got five seconds man, you gotta make it count give me info that I need not enough space on the disc
Why does the monster always attack mid message too? Yeah, why why does that happen? Why can't somebody?
Like call or leave a message
It's like the monster is fucking sprinting at them while they're talking on the phone
Yes, leave your distress call
Uh, yeah, there's um, i'm looking at him right now. He's he's he's about 200 300 feet away
We have a problem. It looks like there's some kind of monster. He's getting close. He's coming up
Like don't you see him?
Why don't you just like fucking hide behind a dumpster or something for a minute call like
Call when you when you see him for the first time not when he's running at you like a train. Uh-oh
It's a hulk turn me into an abomination
This is when the hulk goes see how powerful you are
Join me
The health of major enemies like bosses is displayed by the red boss health meter
Each pip above the health bar indicates another full bar of health the more powerful the enemy is the more pips they'll have
Here we go
Yes, it will it will work
Get out of here. All right, I got it. Here we go. One two three eat shit
Did I just cave him in I think I did yeah I did I didn't even mean to do that
Oh
some more
What?
Oh, no, he's got a warhead
I can't pick it up. We can't play catch
Wait, don't lie. Hold on. Wait, don't touch the scab
Why don't you shut the fuck up man, I got this
Eat this
Take this idiot
By the way, why are we fighting?
We shouldn't be fighting
Son of a bitch
Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, hold on time out time out time out time out time out time out
Just supposed to let me time out
Now I got adrenaline now you're dead
You're on a sack for you
Hey, I gotta tell you be careful
What's what's up with it when you go to the bathroom when you change back?
You're gonna be shitting all the air because you ain't up dead. I couldn't even get the joke out
I feel no pity
I was trying to say if I didn't die, I would have got it out
Just trying to say that like hey, this is the first time you've changed over
Listen to me like when you would you think you can eat everything you want
But when you change back, you're gonna be shitting bricks is what I was gonna say
But I died and it would have been funny. Try it again
What did you do to me you freak nation? That wasn't funny
I thought it was funny. Do you have the guts? Let's find out and I thought it was funny. Therefore. I would say it
You sure
Oh, no
Oh
Don't let him get near me. Nice throw smore. Oh, I know what this is. Oh, this must be liquid nitrogen
Can I grab him?
Come on, you mindless freak. I can't grab him. I'm gonna die again
Wait, I can run and throw
This is so like it's stupid looking
Get out of here
Nice elbow laugh
That was a real laugh. Yeah, I went
Oh, he didn't get to throw this I can throw it at him now
What is going on
Did he actually just grab me? No, fuck he's gonna belly to belly suplex me again
Kick him kick him kick him kick him
I was just pretending to be dead you fool
I just just showed his head. It just
Roshed by a cinder block and just blooded and guts and brains
I saw it happen plain as day. Okay. I saw what happened with my own eyes
The hope was to play
what
Is he is he like ratting out his other personality? No, you say like, I don't know if fucking it was an earthquake or something
I don't know
Oh, that was that was the other guy. Okay. Hold on
shield
weaponization create a shield from large vehicles
cool
shockwave smash
slam kick
Slam a two-handed weapon into an enemy and then execute a punishing follow-up
And I shockwave smash again
Long-range ground pound powerful against ground-based opponents. Yeah, i'll get it
I was saying f f what do you mean f?
But what is it f? I still have no drop frames. What's what's going on?
Why you guys why why would you guys do this to me fine not f what?
Fell for it again
Wait, are you guys fucking with me because i've got a fiber optic internet now and you guys are scaring me
I have zero drop frames the whole stream. Why has everybody be done? Why would you do this to me?
First time it was real. I think the first time was twitch
I have zero drop frames
There's no other internet that's better than like fiber. Uh, what i'm gonna have to like
What do you get better internet?
There is no better internet
Oh, it's good. It's fine. It's been rock solid the whole time
Maybe if he keeps saying that he he can sleep at night
You have an internet curse. Well, no, I think the curse is broken. I've got zero drop frames
I've got it's been rock solid for the whole stream
Bruce banner. All right
rock solid
You finished a chapter of the game. Hooray
right
Meaning that new moves are available to buy at the church end of the church and access. Why is it the church?
Demented streamer talks to empty chat
Am I demented?
All right. No, I want to go to uh
Come to the badlands
last chance cafe
This is dollar store fiber internet
It's like great actually. I have like six to seven hundred down and like a thousand up. It's so it's so good
Guys, I downloaded an entire movie on netflix in like three to four hours
It was crazy
Wait, why can I?
What?
Holy shit that guy
That guy just backed up never back up more than 10 miles per hour ever under any circumstance
Do you understand? It's impossible to control the car once you go that fast
I'm not even doing anything. I mean, this is odd
This is a little odd
It's it's I wouldn't say this is dangerous
This is it's not even dangerous. It's odd
you see
Oh
You're lucky you're not targetable
If you were targetable, you'd be in big trouble
I was
Wait, that's some brave little toaster shit right there. He ran into the pole and died
Where's the cop going?
I told you never back up more than 10 miles bro. The the car the cop was a cow
You just got out of the car
Satan
Who?
It must be satan
Was that a tank? I don't know. I don't know
Oh, doesn't it? Oh, doesn't it just make the devil mad?
Stop stop stop. So what?
The gamma detection network is under construction destroy all the uplink hardware to deny
The division access to their precious satellite intel
Brave little toaster is a movie you fucking idiots
Well, i'm reading that that's highlighted look it's right there right now you can't you don't say I said that but it is
You don't know what the brave little please do yourself a favor
Watch the brave little toaster
I can't believe that people that have not seen them with okay
That's required reading for the stream if you have not seen the brave little toaster. You're not allowed to watch the stream anymore
It's serious that movie's fucking awesome. Just go watch it right now. You have you have to do it now do it now
I don't care if you leave the stream. Just do it now do it right now. Yes required locate and destroy the satellite uplink
Quick transfer where he is
Using satellite technology, although a text on a cell phone would do fine, too
Could just text me
No beam up the satellite
I see one more 5g joke. I swear i'm gonna laugh because they're all funny
All the par I I really believe that
Congratulations, you've unlocked a movie my god
Oh
All right, I get smash points, yes
I can't take this noise
Climb climb climb climb and then do a one punch
one two three
round pound
Don't let the fact that you distract you that you're looking higher to defeat
Who did I?
Can somebody do something about this helicopter here, please?
This guy's fucking don't look at I was freaking out
Holy shit
um
This that shouldn't be happening. That's he's too erratic
I can't even stop him
He's going insane
How do I
Did I just punch it?
This is ridiculous. This is ridiculous
All right spear
Okay
Oh, come on I didn't even do that you did
These guys are not very good at this
He's drunk with power
Where are these?
Look at how fucking far away these are
I climb
No, I gotta run all the way
I need a new trailer
Ace tion's like jumps with rose can be charged up while you're doing something else. Yeah
I already know
All right now I get missiles
Can't break this up into missiles
It's a long time for updates
Update me every four minutes
I've destroyed whole cities in less than three
This is 2004 by the way. What what about it?
It really with hulk's moves. They're so cool
Who's this green Thanos?
That's so that was not even funny
but
I was like i'll give it to you. You can have it
That's not funny like at all, but like I guess it is
Destroy five. What is this?
Oh, I knew I got a new jump out
I'm a book seven
code retro
All right. I'm gonna collect the I want more
smash
Okay, that was the homing capabilities that were fucking cartoon. I know this is a cartoon. You're right. Whatever
You know when this stream ends, you're gonna laugh at Thanos car
I still don't know what that is
People have tried to explain it to me. I still don't get it. I don't know who this
Have them destroyed fine shoot it with a missile
Thanos car Thanos car. I don't I don't know why it's funny
No, that's like a car that looks like Thanos, right?
Critical mass I can do the super bomb thing
Oh
That's it. That's literally it
Then I got it
That it or is it this one this one what oh my god, that was insane
It's a nuclear bomb
I mean, let me save you some bandwidth though. Oh, here's a psycho copter
Just run just run run run
I'm gonna say it again. Here comes another jump that you've heard before
That was just like playing smash brothers online
Like I said, i'm gonna puke i'm gonna puke this one's very heavily guarded. Uh-huh. Oh god put that out
All right, I need to uh, give me pick it up. Oh my god
You fucking idiot, okay
Do that
I'm gonna I'm gonna just slow it down a little because I need to kill those helicopters
Why are you blaming hulk when you control him?
Yeah, that's a myth. That's just a myth
There could be tons of different reasons why you fuck up something. It's a myth
Okay, all right swing self-checkout
Oh
And it gets to be a point where these things are uncontrollable. Just just throw a spear at it
What what do I how do I grab something?
Oh, it's the same
Can I pick up?
Oh, give me one. Give me give me give me a rock. Give me rock
I threw that I threw it behind me
Okay, so four
um
Helicopters that can fly into the ground up here. I'm just gonna stay right here and i'm gonna throw i'm gonna throw rocks out
Yeah, look at all these rocks. I have here. I'm ready. I'm ready for the invasion here
Spears and rocks. Let's go
They come right? Okay. Here we go. I just see they spawned instantly that right there. Do you see them?
They come
It comes there like the jpg
Fuck, I almost just hit me in briefcase. Shit
All right back back back back back back back back back back back back back back
Back back back back back back. They're almost here. Where are they?
It's alive
No, I don't throw a guy throw the helicopter. Not a guy
No throw at
I think I got it. Yeah, i'm good
Good good good good
Wait, what's that? Oh fuck it. Let's go
Beautiful joe go
nice
We get that heal to get those right now. I have to go which way to go where where where this way
Only one more
I need to go back to beautiful joe. I'm not sure that's gonna happen
In fact, i'm certain it's not gonna happen. I can tell you it's not going to happen
I was attacked
I was verbally attacked
Oh comic book and 2 000, uh gamer points
Careful 2 000 more points. Oh and uh unlockable
Chat always does
Yeah, it's almost like there's the most predictable group of people ever
Don't you dare play this anymore. Get out of here. Don't play beautiful joe. This game's dumb
I don't like beautiful joe. Beautiful joe's stupid. I don't like it. This game's boring. This game's stupid
All right, I haven't played beautiful joe in six days. Where's beautiful joe? Look at beautiful joe. It's not bad
I mean it's beautiful joe. I like beautiful joe. It's a good game. You should play that play it right now
Play beautiful joe right now. I like the shark. Shark was the best boss in the game. Why did you stop playing? What's wrong with you?
Then I play it again
It's a meltdown. No, it's not. This is just truth
You're hearing the truth
He hates us
Chat is not one person. Yes, you are
so one
person with like 5 000 mouths
Back up back fine back up. I
Okay, seriously just die. Oh, please
We're all one guy. I'm just kidding guys. I know
I think I really believe that
Really believe that
new blonsky detected
Blonsky files are emily blonsky's personal data files decrypted from his stolen mainframe after
Certain story mode mission completions. You will be rewarded with more blonsky files
If I hate us, no, I don't i'm just fucking around
How long you guys been on this channel for like six months to a year some of you?
How many have been here for like 13 14 15 months not even ever 10 years
This way too many
Take a copy of yourself. What?
Bought yourself a convoy. What's going on?
All right, I don't let's go. I don't want to get i'm gonna get killed here
All right, just leave leave. Ah, that was cool. Hold on
Fuck me leave leave
Oh my god
Leave leave me alone. Oh i'm dead
I just like flanked
What did I just really mortal combat die?
Did you get me in like a 30 hit combo and I stood up and fell down, please
Just go back to the church
Wait 35 000 points
That seems kind of pog
An 8.9 out of 10 from official xbox magazine
Here's what I don't understand. Here's the conspiracy theory
um
weird
So it says an eight it's on the box
It says as you see
it says
Take a look eight point eight point nine out of ten
on the box
How did they know it was an eight point nine out of the ten before the game was released?
That's kind of a fucking conspiracy theory. I think what's going on there?
But you like my cuber you like my I know the camera's in a fucking weird place
The reddit room
Don't I do do not make that be what you call this room
if
If you call this the reddit room
I'm gonna move to a new room
Not a fucking reddit room. Did you see it?
I didn't know even so I just I got on the shelf there
I got the thing the movies black and white is up there. Why is there a stepladder?
Oh, I don't know because i'm not uh
12 fucking feet tall to put foam up on like where the ceiling is
Uh, you guys realize even if you even if you were
like
If you were like fucking 15 if you were 10 feet tall you'd still need the first rung of that stepladder to touch the ceiling
I'm talking like this. This is like 12 feet tall to like put foam
Oh, yeah guy that's six feet stand in the middle of the room and go like this and put and you put the foam on the ceiling
Yeah, what's not gonna happen? What the fuck are you talking about?
What is it going? Hold on. What are you linking?
Stand by the door. I don't have to do anything
Imagine thinking it's it's a stepladder. What about this image? I don't know. That's how posters not even in my room
What is all of this?
Reddit room. Oh and I i'm doing like the the like pog phase with the high score
The reddit room he's doing the soy face with the reddit room
God damn it. What the fuck?
No, but I want to look at this one more time because like this is just fucked up. So I want to see it again. Okay
Vegas arc two
Anime figure collecting reddit room
Great. Um, I like that little pac-man lights not going away. Um, it's not nothing's changing
I got buying. Oh, look. I have a little shelf here now. It's cool
I have like a cool shelf
I mean do I need to move this back?
No, i'm not moving anything. I'm touching anything
I'm not touching anything. It's staying exactly the way it is. I'm never gonna change it
What's above spider-man? I don't know. What is above spider-man?
Where is spider-man?
There's no spider-man in this image. What are you talking about?
That's carnage. That's not spider-man
That's carnage
Oh, I think you guys are gonna think oh it's so cool
Oh, man, look at my look at my like a page up there. No, uh, it's now the reddit room. I'm I'm so disappointed in you all
I'm so disappointed. I thought everyone was like this is cool
And now all of a sudden i'm like the weirdo loser guy
Where am I going to the bad land? Where's the next uh mission?
It's funko pops
Yeah, but they're rare. Oh, that makes it even worse me saying that
Who's above carnage? That's slimer from ghostbusters. What would you rather me have back there on the shelf?
Do you want to put like books back there? You want me to go buy books that I don't fucking read that I've never read?
Oh
George Roy Wells 1984 is being displayed back there
I've never read that fucking book, but I want you to think I did
Would you want to display that back there? Would that make you think i'm like smart and cool and shit?
You don't need to read it. We're just living it. Yeah, read books the way you watch movies
Actually smart
No, I didn't mean to do that
It's fine fine
Skip a hundred pages read and then skip a hundred pages read skip a hundred pages
Well, there it is enter the following code king king
Get yourself a coffee. I've marked a location on the map near the division weapons test site
There's word the military is sending vital parts through for the construction of more hulk busters
Then you want me to head them off destroy this destroy that destroy this cool
I'm sorry. I I there's something going on with how i've changed this i'm gonna i'm gonna bump into you all the time for some reason
All right, how do I do it? It's king king
Is that to be main menu?
Fuck destroy the convoy truck before they've reached the military base
Thanks for
Cutscene right before you hit with a missile appreciate that. Thank you
Chase indicator shows how far your target is from reaching its final destination if the target reaches the end of the bar you will fail
Hurry up. It's the wrong way
Don't buy funko pop. I haven't bought a funko pop in like two or three years
I just have them I didn't buy these
Guys, I didn't like go and buy these funko pops like yesterday to show you how cool I am
This is my collection. I've bought a one every like couple of years
I i'm not buying them. I'm not actively buying funko pops and even if I was
What's it to you? Huh?
What?
Hey, I can't buy a I just looked over and saw all this on the other monitor and I immediately stopped talking
I thought you said I could catch those liars
Just trying to make me fail
You guys you guys
What website do you use then?
Huh? What website are you going to for like news and random shit where you go to like yahoo.com?
What the fuck are you doing?
Yeah, I go to yahoo. I go to news.yahoo.com man
Oh, yeah
He's already way ahead of me. Is that the convoy right there?
I'm gonna lose already
I use dspn for my name
What are I?
He's upset by this, huh? Yeah. Yeah
And i'll tell you why
Because everybody uses ready. I don't give the people that say they don't like reddit. They use it
You go to red.com. Let's go to the front page
And like okay what happened today? This is an easy place for me to see it all
Did I get him?
I got him. I didn't
wait
Oh, he's about to leave
I use it. I hate it. Yeah, I don't have to I don't like I I don't like own the website
I don't own like shares in reddit guys. Give me that tanker
reddit gold
No, I didn't want to pick up just the front part
I need to find shortcuts. I gotta play mario kart
All right mar sorry mario
Here we go
Come here
I gotta cut him off. Here we go
I'm not cutting him up. I'm just running behind him
Flash r whoosh am I right chat?
lol
What's the mark? Hey, what's the rarest punko?
What's it? Where is uh?
I got it. Holy shit. That was actually not even that art
Where is the punko?
What's the rarest punko?
Damn it. I got flew into the rock
All right. What's the next mission?
I did it. I win. All right, we're going back to the church
Which what is it? It's eddard stark. Not a joke
Is it really?
It's the holographic darth maul
How expensive is that?
Because what's what's the rarest punko pop the rarest one the one that's like the most expensive rarest one to get
Holographic darth maul is the most expensive punko pop and it's 1800 dollars
That's insane
It's an insane amount of money
That's gonna be on the fucking shelf
In like a couple weeks whenever I can get it
Justice. No, what a waste. No, that's not a way. I don't say that out loud, but it's the collectibles
I almost just said that
Okay, where's the next mission?
What the fuck destroy all trucks and wait the convoy still moving
What?
Didn't that say mission complete?
Where the fuck is this thing? Where is it?
The dumbo one the disney dumbo elephant is
6500 dollars
Green dot. Oh, what I thought I was looking for red dog
60 it's
6500 bucks. I don't I don't want to spend that much money
I don't know man. I don't want like a
I don't like have that much expensive shit. Can I be honest with you here?
I don't want like a
Ten thousand dollar fucking punko pop sitting in my on my shelf
You know what I mean? That's like
That's just put that's like putting a bar of gold
On like your counter
I don't want just like a bar of gold on my counter. Why the fuck would I want that?
All right, here we go convoy leaving. I'll get it. How much is one bar of gold? Like how much is one ounce of gold?
Get it
Oh
I've missed by a lot
One ounce of gold is what?
1600 1500 dollars
Okay, so you're talking about that's like having three ounces of gold sitting on your shelf
1600 dollars an ounce
Yeah, so that's correct. How am I getting question marks? That's how much gold that's how much an ounce of gold is right now
What?
1600 bucks an ounce
1700 bucks an ounce
All right, would you rather buy three ounces of gold or have dumbo on your shelf?
That's what you have to ask yourself
Not fucking reddit gold get out of here
I have to destroy these convoys
Jump it up
Go go go go go go go go go go go get out get out get out
Oh
No
Oh, come on
I'm wrong. Is that how I'm having a mic? I think I made a noise too weird
too loud
You just kind of ran over
All right, this convoy mission is gonna be such a it's gonna be such a meltdown screen
Through this convoy mission all crossing my fingers meltdown stream incoming
I'm just trying to get on our i'm not gonna say any words because
I don't we don't know stop. It's quiet
It's quiet
Give me my busted up car
convoy
There it is
A queue game why?
Hey
No, why would I do that I I like roger revan
Ban the guy spamming the link ban him
Ban that guy
You fucking idiot you threw it at the wrong guy
Okay, got it. There's no timer right? It's regenerate my um, what does it?
He's germa alone. So what if he has hobbies you don't like fuck you
I
Appreciate this bet I do I it's not a hobby. I just have four
Funko pop I just own four. It's not a hobby. I'm not I don't
I see
What can I say here? Why do they display them? I knew it. I knew that oh wow
Maybe we should kill him
Oh this guy have funko pops he deserves to be dead
It should have known
Where is it? No, this is not even the right circle
Damn, bro. I feel bad now
escalated
Oh
Gerber has showed four funko pops on stream
Anybody else hope he drowns?
Why didn't you use the jump point? Wait, I don't i'm gonna get over this fucking month
Stop stop. I know it's an invisible wall. I figured it out
Used to jump jumping use the jump point
Look, i'm having i'm having some trouble defending my use of uh of funko pops on my shelf
All right video game is not in the front of the brain
I like him this thing
I like him so much that i'll open the box and show you the image and get my dirty
Greasy fingers all over the fucking funko pop and ruin the value
Oh, no, no, no, no, don't do that. No, don't do that. Sure, but don't do that. What are you doing?
What are you thinking? I thought you didn't care. I thought you don't I thought you thought funko pops are dumb
No, don't do that. Don't ruin the value
Okay
We just went over how dumbo is worth almost ten thousand dollars. Yeah, they have value
They do somebody's gonna buy that carnage for like thirty nine dollars because it's it's all right
I gotta get these coins
smash 15
They don't have a soul
No, they don't not until somebody leaves the room and the lights turn on
Then they get to play and have fun run around the room and shit
going adventures and
gotta fly out windows and
Go to eat pizza
Get it. Oh my god, get it the worst hulk ever. All right, let's go to the next one
Nice sick. Yeah, sick
nice
sick sick sick sick
sick
Like henshi
No, nobody said that. Yeah, they did go look at the logs
Wait, it's a flying person. Is that iron man?
Is iron man in the game?
It is it's like an iron man guy. Look
Who's that?
Looks like a few of them
Cut it off
I know destroy it. You don't have to be in my head
Oh you piece of shit
Hey, give me a break
Give me this now
It's the psycho chopters again
You can always tell because they just fly. Look at this. Wait. No, it's not
Yep. Did I seriously get fucking grabbed?
It's getting away man, it's gonna get away I have to get the fuck over there now
I could have used that jump pad couldn't I?
Oh my god, these guys are fucking so annoying
Yeah
Get what is that?
I'm dead
Get the get the coin
It's the thing. Just look how far away this fucking thing is now. Like there's no way
There's no way I can get over there
It's over I gotta like teleport around god damn it
We got any mods in a minute I do what we mods we mods good get out of here
Uh, come on
Okay, I need to I'm gonna tell after I just destroy this right here, right?
Fuck I can't I have this counts right now ready. I have to hit this right now
Ready one
And a half
Why would you go into a cut scene?
ah
port port port port
Uh, the kids can't even watch all these two final
How am I supposed to look right back to the church?
All right, like is uh, it's like ridiculous
Go to the badlands. All right, where do I need? I don't even know I need to go
Is who's still in vr?
Yeah, he's probably gonna get sick. He's probably like sweating his eyes probably hurt
Okay, give me some health first
I'm not gonna be ready for this
Okay
Give me a stone
I know let me go follow it
All right, wait, where's it going?
Okay, i'm gonna go to i'm gonna teleport to the one down there teleport. Let's go
Use your moves. What moves do you want me to do right now? I'm 5 000 feet away from this shit
Okay, i'm ready
He's gonna come down this road. No, he's going down the other road. I got a big rock
Coming down here. I'm off
I gotta get rid of this. It's gonna cause some problems
Okay, good
Any more bullshit that I have to deal with up there?
Oh, all right critical
What's this? Is this a muffler? This is a big muffler
I'm gonna bridge they come
Fuck i'm gonna bounce on this motherfucker when he comes over here
Wait, yeah, he's going this way. Okay
They move not moving. He's driving into the wall
Fucking what am I doing?
Get out get out get out get out get out get out
That was like a weird i'm like pretending sound. You know what I mean? Like
What was I doing? I can't I don't know what that was
Why did I do that? What was it for? I don't know
I'm so I was like pretending or something. Well, I don't know for what though
Uh, you were just rp. Yeah, but like very poorly
I can do way better than that
It's because i'm like i'm in a new room and i'm like, I don't want to be too loud or something
And my god, I don't know what the feel of this room's volumes. I have something like that. It's weird
All right, we're gonna go up to that one
Let's kill this guy
I hate these things so much
Just throw it at him
Rabbit rabbit
Dude, okay. I'm
Actually getting annoyed by this shit
Are you fucking dead?
Can you cut the shit?
Is his voice getting higher?
The effects are not what did I get this? Where did this come from? Oh nice. Okay
Stop doing a cut scene. I don't care. All right, I gotta get it right now. I'm gonna get it immediately
All right god
I gotta kill these guys. They're gonna throw a dumpster. I did it. Yes. Thank god
Put this titanfall shit get out of here
Just get me the fuck out of here all these things
Fucking come in and conquer bullshit
What? Okay. I'm good. I'm going back to the church. I'm fine moves
We got you on video
Oh my god, they got me on video. Okay
70 only that's a lot
It's the most expensive funko pop air critical atomic slam. Oh, I don't have it. Uh, i'll take a head butt
our surge level one
Increases total power capacity. That's probably a good idea to get
air dash
Ooh air dash allows you to move faster and jump further than ever before great for dodging. This is an important move to master
are in air
I don't need a tutorial. Okay, let's do it
air dashing sonic clap
A lot of moves tornado uppercut max charge this uppercut to float the enemy high
Okay
sonic brap
Fuck whatever rapid punch burst xx pause x x x x x x s
All right, I got a lot of new
This is a ripoff of ben 10 for the ds
Um, well, let me just correct you there. Um, they have the same color scheme. That's the only thing that's the same
I think that's where you're having some trouble
All right, let me try some of these out
I already forgot them. All right, it's x back in big running grab. Yeah
sonic clap, yeah
Air stomp smash express. I still haven't done this x or what? No. Yeah, I did
Okay
So critical atomic slam we've done that
The two-handed weapon it's x and then y
Oh air dash, right?
Am I doing that right?
Yeah dashing sonic clap. So what about like this?
Oh, okay, so that is very helpful
I can actually dodge moves now
If you don't die if you go in the water good to know let's get a new, uh mission
bugleberry waiting room
Okay
It wasn't the right voice resident hog jam
It was rovo berry I like the run mechanic
Critical mass. Oh, okay. So hold on
So it's y and then y at max power, right?
They're not gonna work. Let's see critical atomic slam
shockwave smash
tornado uppercut
Oh, I want to try this too
That's so dumb punch punch punch punch punch punch punch punch punch punch punch punch
It's a long time to do that though
Oh, okay, what should I do?
Headhunter we're going head hunting
I need a neural interface from a hulk buster cockpit
They're primed to self-destruct when taken out of commission
So you'll need to separate the head from the chassis and deactivate the mechanism sounds like fun
Where am I going the military base break in take up the strongest tactical position?
You can and wait for the fireworks and break into the Hulkbuster field tests
All right, I chat obsessed with chickens
How'd you just say that now? I want a McChicken sandwich, and I'm gonna get one. I'm gonna have one
I will have a McChicken before the end of the day
Oh
You don't scream nah, I want to enjoy it. I want to enjoy it just slowly to myself
Whoo, you got running grab throw these guys aren't so bad when you pick your remote. Where'd you go?
Dad no stop doing that. I do that so often, but I love saying it. It's like something. It's so fun to say that
Yeah, dad dad
Dead
Anything anybody know what that is? Let me guess don't even know what that is. Probably
Go down here. I don't know. Can I laugh? Oh
That was a huge brush you gonna explain. Oh, right
Lightning bolt lightning bolt lightning bolt lightning bolt and then when the guy runs out of HP they go dead dead dead
Yeah, dead
Dead. Oh, I remember that one minus two
And I'm not saying it was funny. I just like say it a lot. I just took in my brain a lot. Oh
I just killed people I didn't do anything else
What the fuck does minus two mean?
Actually, I don't know plus two means that
You're at the screen the screams quality works
That we're running at like a good quality of like the screens actual quality
It's running it like like 720 so like I know I look over and see that
Where's this going backwards turbo that's because I was not even looking at the screen I was looking over at you
Boxer plummeting cell cell cell cell cell cell cell cell cell cell
Make a funny joke, please. Okay
Maybe on a few days. You might see like a funny joke that you'll like in like a day or two
Why are they fighting by the dip dummies?
Will I get involved with my whole hands?
invincible
Wait
Am I gonna get in this oh
Now I have to deliver it right?
All right, they gotta go they've gotta go hey, I got it
Come on, I got a super frog
DBZ no this one person fighting you in DBZ not like 30
Oh
My god, you're fucking driving me nuts
Where am I?
You little shit. Can I leave yet? Yeah, I admit I was trying to punch that lady
All right, bring back the fucking car battery over the hell. This is
Come on
Oh
Okay, I'm gone. Where's the teleporter?
No, I gotta put this shit down. I'm gonna fight these guys. What was that the whole truck?
Hulk ultimate destruction aka
floating I
Can't even I'm too angry to like even make it like a snarky little comment right now
Oh
Floating around juggles time
I don't know. I'm I'm mad. I'm mad. I'll tell you I'm mad
That was a reddit. It wasn't stop saying that you guys fuck
guys
Damn it, man. I know if you say time at the end of any
Jokey little comment. It's like a shitty cop-out joke. I
Know I know I trust me. I know
You look like socks. How is the whole case again to hit so many times?
Now a whole ultimate destruction. No, no, no Hulk. Look at my trampoline tricks
There that's what this game should be called and Edwards Norton's not even here. So like the Edward Norton
Game volumes really loud turn it down then. What the fuck am I thinking?
Hulk look at my trampoline tricks time
You get it you you you get it, you know
Blonsky I don't get it. I do not I just that's fine. Okay, what it's too quiet. It's too loud. It's too quiet
Because it is oh wait, I want to do um, all right, let me go turn on King King mode. What does that do?
Save it here and I'm gonna go turn on King King. I'm curious what it does. Say hi to my brother Seth. What's going on Seth?
How you doing? Hey Seth, what's up, dude? How's it going? Okay
Bachelor party. All right, Seth. Hey, be careful. All right
Have a good one. That'll be that'll be $80 on cameo, please
Crystal crystal what's going on? Hey happy
Baby shower. That's you happy baby shower crystal
Uh-huh. Good. Hey that baby's gonna have to feed that baby a lot. Okay, have a good one. Bye
Heather Heather got that new job Heather. Okay, Heather. Goodbye. Good luck
Hey, don't work yourself too hard, you know
They just turn on their webcam and they just do $500 in a row and they make a hundred dollars for each one
Do me next do me do me do me do me
Hey
Hey Steve
Esther but what was I doing extras King King? What are you do K?
How do I input letters? Oh
You have to was it cat? What is it in King? This is gonna fuck up my save file
by the numbers
King King no King
Who unlocked guerrilla invasion it will turn it on is this cheating I mean it yes
Ready to go to the city
Oh, I see
You can like at their heads. All right. She alive. All right. This is like funny. I guess that was fun
I'm done with that one. I guess
Turn off guerrilla invasion right back to the story. You have to jump with them
Oh, I guess more cheats. No, I want to play the video game
And I want to get to the story and to the stream. No, not yet. I know not yet. We're still gone
I'll do a little bit longer
All right. Oh, wait, I got something important. I gotta look up on
I'll play tomorrow. I'm not done streaming. This game's actually pretty fun. He was visiting reddit. What about the movie night?
All right, so I will talk about it again because a lot of people weren't here in the beginning of the stream
So we'll go over it again
They weren't
Happy you probably weren't even here
because of
This last week getting sort of deleted
Because of the all this stuff for the auto
Uh, I've decided that we're just gonna play games
I'm gonna stream for these three days in a row here
And then we're gonna do it this coming next week the same streams that you were waiting for
For this past week
They've been deleted and they've been replaced
on next week
So we're gonna go friday saturday sunday wednesday thursday friday saturday. I just essentially moved it
recorded
Um, do I not have any more missions transit?
um
Do I need to unlock a move or something?
There's no missions on the
fire emission. Um
I guess I could do one of the challenge ones
It was so uncalled for that for I feel bad
Okay runs the course
Let chat redecorate what no just say bazinga to step
um big bang theory
What are you talking about?
It's quite the race
It's hard to control this shit
Did I even get it last one is up
With the sheldon funko pop boy, this is pre-recorded
How much is the sheldon funko pop
sheldon funko pop
It's like 40 dollars
Jump to the church to acquire a mission
It all started with a large dense gas
Yes going to church but why is everyone freaking out what's going on
Okay
Wansky files
Bruce, this is a partial decrypt. I've also discovered an audio file. It sounds like a surveillance tape of some kind. Listen
You place the prisoner inside the inner vault in direct contradiction to my orders and you've established a level 15 clearance
the president senior cabinet members
Surely you of all people don't need a lesson in protocol general
Well, what are they talking about is mission directive a person
The cork board back there i'm not only cork board
Although I do love the noise that a cork board makes when you push a pin into it when it goes that
Where's this? How do I do the story mission acquire mission next story mission proving grounds?
Oh, it's right here
Small problem some of the parts got through to blansky's people while we were busy with the convoy
They're looking to put a new home. That's you killing somebody. What so let's take them out one
When am I gonna have a funko pop?
Who would buy one of those?
Would you buy a germ of funko pop and put on your shelf?
If I ever did like a funko pop I would just cover it in
Inside jokes and references that didn't exist
You know i'd be in like a beach towel
It'd be like
It'd be it'd be like a rubik's cube on my shoulder
Oh my god, I gotta be some funny thing going on there
I would just have a bunch of it all over me. Nothing would none of it made me mean anything. Who is boss fight?
Well, that wasn't fair. Oh shit
Hey car
eat car
Did he just say don't worry the cavalry's here?
I think he actually did just say that
Did he actually say that?
I'm just asking solve a rubik's cube
Solve a rubik's cube on stream. Oh, this is gonna suck ass
All right, go take out the
gallon
Oh shit, the the mama showed up
Hi
beat
Ah
Nope. Yeah. I know. Oh here come four more of these guys. This is not gonna be good
I gotta destroy these now
I don't know what the hell I just did there, but it was bad
All right, don't kill me please get the muffler get the muffler get the muffler
Who's hurting who right now? Okay, get out. I don't have enough health for this
Jesus
Oh
No, throw it at the big guys
Big health. Thank you
Jesus
All the satellites are dead, right?
help
Come here
Oh, where's the big one? You're not still alive. Are you oh so many missiles too many missiles man
Too many
Oh my god, an endless supply of trucks the problem
next slide, please
That's funny. That was funny
All right, so he only has one more fucking health bar left
I gotta just get in there and start just beating the shit out. I'm gonna do the super fast punch
We got ready
So I thought that's never even gonna work man
No, that shit will that move will never be used you will never use that move
You have to stand in the same spot for like eight seconds to have that move happen. That's not gonna happen
He's mad. Yeah
All right
Why am I not allowed to be angry?
Of course i'm gonna be like fuck shit fuck
Stupid i'm gonna say that
Of course I am the fucker has a shield
Oh fuck
Well, at least there's a health up there
sir
Losing a kid's game now that everything is a kid's game
Not everything is a kid's game
It really has to be a kid's game
uh
He has a whole nother health bar, too. Fuck
Video games are for babies
What's the esrb rating on this key 13? Okay?
That means there's violence
Means there could be swear words
I just baited the fuck out of him so bad
It didn't really help me though
Jump oh brother the same idea
No
I got it
Him wants to know why you're grunting
Well, I why can't I jump like that?
Why can he get like sucked into a willy wonka tube? Why can't I do that? It's because i'm playing an intense video game
50 000 points cool
tornado frenzy
Oh, you can combo in the air. Yep. I want this how expensive was that critical thunder clap
Club smash
Oh rising uppercut
Cool little move air ground slam
Sounds cool
Nice kim said he's outside of his office with me
What me? I'm out there. How am I out there?
Oh auto, okay. Let's get a story recap
Him confirmed pre-recorded
Oh mercy
Why does this look better than the wii game?
In the week that we came out after the xbox didn't it?
This is on the
But here's another thing though. This is xbox 360
Emulating the xbox game and let me tell you something
um
Of all the systems that like have emulated kind of backwards compatibility the 360 with xbox original xbox games
It's this this shit is phenomenal
This looks fantastic
It's phenomenal. This is an original xbox game. This looks like it could have came out like five years ago
Well, maybe 10
10 is probably pushing it maybe like 15
Which is when it did come up. So let's just say whatever I acquire a mission
Is it what do I want to go?
add lands
Jump to the city
The original xbox supported 720p. Yeah, pretty good
Why did it show this to me?
I'm gonna have to give a couple of criticisms of this burger by the way lettuce on the bottom of the meat and lettuce on top
By the way, that's not even less. That's like kale
that is
kale
Where's the cheese?
lettuce tomato
Way too thick of a patty
You gotta cut that in half. I don't like big thick burgers like that. No, thank you
The lettuce underneath
I I don't think this this is just not made right
I have to say about that
Bad news blond skis developed a new funny bit buster mech. No, that's on the real criticism of a gross hamburger field tests
Who for?
Everyone I guess we'll have to get in there and take these new machines out
The specs and locations are uploaded into your subliminal program, but kim kim. No, no, no, no, no kim
Don't don't don't don't talk about all the other don't talk about all the other funko pops that we own
um
Don't don't do that. I said we only have four
I said we only have four we don't have like 12
don't
Don't do that. Don't talk but we don't have to we have four in there on the shelf right now
Definitely not at least 10
Some of these are not mine
I just want to make sure where this like some of these kim kim has
gotten some of these something that had the ones that are mine are the ones that I showed you except of course for ren and
Stimpy that I got those two guys. I like that show
um
I got uh
Mega man and proto and is it proto man? I got them too
um, and then sailor sailor mars
uh
sailor
Chun-li and those are not mine. Those are kim's
Those uh, that's not
Chun-li's not mine
Kim kim wanted Chun-li and there's also the little egg guy that that's not mine either
Why are they in the box because they
They're you don't you don't take them out of the box
You're gonna get your fingerprints on them and you're gonna get cheeto dust on them and then they're gonna lose value
They're like 20 more downstairs. No, I'm kidding. I would that's this is it. This is it. I had to come clean
I came clean right here. I came clean. That's me coming clean. There it is
They're not even half of those not even mine
Half of those aren't even mine. Oh, he's got box box just raided with like 2 000 people. What's up box box?
Thanks for the raid
What does box box have to say about my fucking reddit room? I know I I know it's dark
I'm working on the lighting in here
Look, let me tell you look at those
I only had four displayed up there
Thanks for the fucking raid, dude
You're a nerd. You're a nerd. Look at this redditor reddit reddit reddit
I'm sorry. I'm gonna go over these one by one. I'm gonna talk about if reddit would want them or not. Okay, let's be honest
Chun-li
Ding, okay
Ding ding ding sure fine brandon stimpy
No happens have people on reddit don't even know what that show is
No, uh proto man ding ding ding ding ding ding ding ding ding ding like ding ding ding ding ding
That's a huge. Uh, absolutely mega man
Proto man's like cooler than mega man, right? Ding ding ding ding ding. Yeah ding ding ding
Uh roger rabbit don't fucking think so if you roger rabbit would not be
By the way, like this has got to go i'm gonna cut i'm gonna cut this off with my bare hands in a minute
Um, there's no way roger rabbit is is a is a reddit. Don't go pop. There's no fucking way
Is it why would no we have no way?
Slimer
No, I don't think so
I don't think so. No
Qbert, nobody knows who the fucking qbert is only I do only I know who qbert is
Okay
Carnage, I give that to you
Rush the dog the rush the dog from mega man
Yeah, that would be huge on reddit, wouldn't it? Uh, yeah
Taylor mars, yeah, that would be huge on reddit too, wouldn't it? Um
Okay, so
One two three four five six seven eight nine ten eleven there are twelve there two of them wouldn't be on reddit
I like those shows. All right
I like bread. I like steve. I like
Roger rabbit and iqbert
I don't even give a shit. I don't even care about qbert
Guys, I've played I think I've played the first level of qbert
Three times when I was like six and I just walked off the edge and died
I just got gut qbert because I want people to think I'm like a gamer and like like qbert and stuff
It's like a cool
Thing like an old arcade thing. I don't even like qbert
He's a fake fan. That's fine
I got I thought people were gonna look at that and be like, oh nice qbert, man. That's fucking sick
Qbert is cool. And maybe though he swears. Don't you guys think that's cool?
What am I doing?
That's you just explained reddit at its core
No, I didn't I didn't his fur it's for
I like reddit's fine. There's none. It's a place for news and for pop culture and for uh up to date being able to stay up to date
Guys, I have a reddit account. I posted on it like three times
All right. I'm just all right. Let's go
By the way, I think every single person left from that rate
Just like all right. I'm out of here
This guy's got red and stippy funko pops
God if he only like fell on a cliff
All right, what's happening?
They were uncomfortable with your shelf
I have to travel here
What do I have to fight these guys?
This is brutal. It's brutal
Not brutal
You can have funko pops
And not have to use the website reddit.com
Damn it. I knew it. What what? Okay, what would be back there that you guys would be like happy with?
You know, that's my question
Like a live rattlesnake. Ooh, that would that would be better for you
Just it's sitting there out of a cage
a skull
I'm gonna how do I make a funko pop? I'm gonna make one. I'm gonna make sure
And i'm gonna make sure and it's like on like you felt reddit
How do you make one?
You should put an ant farm back there. No, fuck that if that thing even breaks out the whole entire place is compromised
Holy shit, that was a lot
U2 get a germa u2s u2s. What is what is u2s?
u2 sounds like a
Is that like a youtube vpn?
For you to like be able to watch stuff that's not allowed in your country or something. What is that?
Chat hates funko pop, but will buy a u2s
Well now you're understanding the irony I would buy neither
Oh
Watch out funko pops. Oh, I got it off like this out
ultimate destruction
Nice. All right. I can't even see him
Give me a car get the back hand off. I'm so sick
We want a whale lord on the shelf I can whale lord is not a toy for me anymore
never was
Whale lord is now an auto bed
I'm not gonna take an auto bed away from auto. He's at least like six of them
Dude, i'm gonna get like i'm fucking i'm gonna get them. What's the little reddit guy's name?
40 right?
What's the little reddit guy's name? I'm getting them on that shelf
Let's get oh fuck. I could get out of here
All right, where?
Don't let him grab you
What I can't even man, where am I this is fucking bullshit
Good
Ah health got it get him in the air upper cut
Okay, I brought it back
What are you pranksters doing right now?
Is this shit? Is this supposed to be me?
Is that me?
Now, how is that even auto?
That's like that's not even the same doesn't have the right dog
Who is this? There's not even me. Who is this?
It's like it's like a different youtuber
Who is this? What is this?
I actually have a
It's not grill master
No, I don't I don't I don't I don't want to funko a funko of me could be literally anything
This could be anyone
Like a funko of me would look it would just be this
But it could be anybody it could be literally anyone
It's new
our products new
Uh-huh
At first I thought that was eight hundred and ninety nine dollars. I was like get the fuck out of here
like I I have brown long hair and like I just put like a i'm just like
I would look exactly like half of these funko pops that exist. I would look like all of them. I'm proud of this
glue man
just needs a blue t-shirt just put a yeah, but that I
I would look I look I would look very similar
I've got to hold on a second. I I have to be I have to spend half of the stream in the air
Did you actually just catch me in that?
What was that priority?
Damn it
countered
How do you even get fucking countered?
And he's broke my neck. All right. I'm moving you want to come to me come to me. That's fine
Kill him. Give me that health. All right, we're good
skate on a bus
Game cube sucks. This is not even a game cube man. It's not wrong system. This is not the game cube
Oh my god
Dreamcast fucking sucks laughing my ass up destroy chief combat warden
Sure, i'll just come down to the vans
Say I handle this shit
like
One on one down here. Let's go kill me one on one
None of these other fucking idiots just us two nobody else
Do me do me do me
There we go
It's like no fucking rhyme or reason to any of this shit
i'm dead
All these fucking people have like a homing missile and I can't like close the gap
I didn't buy the missile blocking move
Fuck should go play binding of isaac. That's an interesting request
Uh, i'll do this whole thing again
Shit just explodes so easily
Last try last try
No, no, no i'm doing it
Ultimate destruction
Hey loser
loser by beck
Thank you so much for 537
Hey loser
No, you know that wait a minute
All right, keep moving
He was checking the name again
In what world is a tank as fast as a fucking Lamborghini?
This one it's a sports tank. Oh, please
All right, here we go
and bush
It's another fake pretend thing again that i'm doing
This game is fucking ridiculous
I can't even fucking tell you what's happening. This is just
Ask me
Tank in here
This guy is drunk
I have not drunk
I have not had any alcohol in like months
where
Poop line that was coffee. That wasn't even poop
Of course, it wasn't poop. Why would I need to make that clear?
What is that do I have to clarify that I wasn't drinking shit out of a glass
Is that where i've gone now?
Come here
uh
I can't stop this
We're getting to mmo levels of just like shit is not even getting hurt just huge
Obnoxious moves are being used every five seconds
This is just yeah aoe spam. It's like we just pulled a trash mob in a raid of 40 fucking people. Why is it doing this?
All right. I'm gonna kick the shit out of this guy
There you are. Okay. Wait, I got critical
I'll get up there eventually and i'm gonna do the critical move
and
Here it comes
Oh, I got it. I did a full bar. This guy's health. I'm not messing around anymore
No, this is fucking ridiculous
What the fuck? Oh, I need help help help help. I can't fight this guy. He's just chasing me
I can't even like grab onto buildings. All right
How the fuck did you get up here? And why the fuck are you up here? Oh my god
Why are you dropping this guy off on top of a building like this?
When is somebody gonna pick him up? Why is he up here just in case the hulk jumps by?
I hope that guy has like sandwiches packed
Get over here. Why can't I not fly?
Am I making me hungry? I'm making myself hungry. What did I say I was gonna get a grilled cheese?
No, that's not what it was. What was it?
McChicken. Yep. There it is. I'm gonna wait for him. I'm gonna come i'm gonna come right back ready watches
Goddamn guy back here
Oh my god
You fucking asshole
wait
Pog coin, what is pog coin? Oh that thing I just got. Yeah, that is a pog coin. That's right
Need help mini f somebody said mini f. I still have no drop frames
Fuck you. Oh
Give me this. Where is he? Where the fuck is he?
Where is he?
Die one more health bar and i'm done. He's not flying so high up. This guy's such a noob
Oh, yeah
Would a noob get like four McChickens after this stream eat them and be wicked happy and then take a bath
I all right. This is starting to make me like sick
He's he's gaining health
I why?
Why the fuck can't why can't people fly in this game?
What the fuck come on he's
He's dodged the homing
You fucking asshole
Am I ever gonna fight this guy?
He could have caught him
No
He's just gone again. This guy's gonna make me fucking have a pass out. I'm gonna pass out
He just gained another bar
I can't
Is he gonna run away again?
No, what is this supposed to be happening?
I feel like this shit's not supposed to be happening
He's already he's gone
He's gonna get all of his health back like every single cent of it. Look at how far away he is
He went across the entire city
The entire city
He's still where is he what it was supposed to happen?
It was scripted. I thought
I thought he's just getting the fuck away from me
People are nexting this game because of this performance
Well, i'll be
What is happening?
What dude the performance of this game is just a firework exploding in your face
This is whole game
Yeah, I can't believe yeah, what's with this performance of you holding a fucking roman candle up to your eye
You you you lit a piece of diamond held in your hand. You could have done that a little smoother. I think
Dude, what the fuck?
I need fucking help
Why does this whole game have to have people that shoot missiles?
It's just this constant
missiles
Going faster screen
There's not been one moment of this game where a missile has not gone
It's just fucking missiles
If only i'm bot no i'm not
Get me out of here. I need to get like the fucking anti-missile move
Where's this? Where is this fucking thing? All right, pick up large vehicles and just hold them
Okay, I need to i'm getting more moves i'm gonna do a couple of those other ones
I need to get some more points. I want I want new moves. That was the wrong move
There's another shield. I thought that was the one that I needed
All right. I'm going i'm just gonna i'm gonna do like these two missions here
It's a punch rockets move
serious
Tell me it's not this
It's just even working
It works sort of go
Go buy ah
Whatever
I thought he was safe. All right, let's go i'm going this way
I'm just gonna do these some of these missions
race, okay, my shield grind wait the same people made hit and run
Really?
No, they didn't
No, I didn't want to do that. It's so finicky and I can't even on your screen. It looks like oh wow
He's so dumb. He can't even jump in the right way, but it's like if you glue on to ship
It's weird. Trust me
Down what? Oh my fuck
Stop doing back flips you motherfucker and stop gluing to walls
Where is this one?
Here's the last one having a cranky wanky. It was an 8.9 out of 10
Hey guys, that's the same score. I gave outer wilds
What? Hey, you were supposed to go this way
He hated outer wilds. No, I didn't why did I even say that people gonna think I mean like why is it?
Are you trying to say this is bad? This one's bad
What is he trying to say trying to say this one's bad?
No, should I go for it?
Just do it
Just do it bad news blonskies develop. Just do it. I'm just gonna do it
I'm gonna fucking just be quiet and i'm gonna beat this right now ready
I'm gonna beat this right now
Do a trump impression. Okay. Sure. Good. I'm gonna beat it right now
Uh, right
Don't look at his tight jeans Jeremy. Okay. I won't I won't do that. All right, do I have full health?
Taking this shit with me right now. Give me the bust and turn it into a shield
Look at my tight jeans
All right, cool
Stop imagining him in spandex
No, i'm not gonna stop imagining that because I think that's more
His his energy and his source of his kinetic movements would be better in spandex i'm not gonna not imagine that
Shit actually works really good as a weapon, too
Charge it. You should not be able to get grabbed in this game. It's not fair
You shouldn't be able to get grabbed. It's just like a bad game
Yeah, oh my god
Kick it critical mass
Good
How much health do you have?
That was a good headbutt
Okay
Here it comes
Let's go
I want a weapon for this
If you beat this we'll take you to game stop and you can get any funko pop you want
Hmm. Cool. That sounds like
Any funko pop I want?
Nice. Hey tipped over. Thanks for the five subs. Appreciate it
Have you tipped over? Let's make this shit quick
Give it no. I didn't want to throw it
Fuck out of here. Yeah
Why are you still here? Fuck off. Okay. Fine. I'll leave then
Imagine locking on to somebody and your character swings the other direction and you imagine imagine imagine imagine imagine
There is again
You fucking put the fuck away
We don't need
50 fucking
missile launcher guys
on every fucking rooftop
in the fucking game
Now get out of here
Wait, gotcha
Holy shit
I just hit him
Don't fucking die to this. There's got to be health somewhere
Please no, please god do not die to this
I don't care if he runs away
I need health this guy hurts so much
Fuck fuck fuck fuck making a shield quick making a shield
Making a shield
Just don't move and regenerate all your health
Okay, where is he? I think he's right behind me. Is he right behind me? He's right behind me, isn't he?
Oh
boy
but
Fuck you. Ah
Get rid of that tank
Need that health in there
He grabbed me and he instantly killed me
The hulk isn't supposed to get scared
This is not like his character
Okay heel right here
Fuck and all of a sudden he's just up my ass
The last time I fought this guy he was running the fuck away from where's the script that I run away from you seen
Don't move
Oh
All right, he's dead
Here he goes
Is he gonna fly away? No, can I just kill him here?
There he goes. Wait, where is he? Is he running away?
I can't tell the fucking fourth of july finale. It keeps playing
Where'd he go? All right. Yeah, there he goes
Uh
I'm doing like peter griffin
That was going into peter griffin territory there
It started off. All right, but then it started going to like
I had to stop immediately
Full health critical strike remote meter remote peter
Script this guy doesn't even know what the script at events. How was I supposed to fucking know?
Although the only instructions I had was kill guy
Kill guy smash
Oh, you're good
You're good. Aren't you?
All right. This is where he lands
He's healing. Yeah, this is just what happens scripted
I can't catch him guys. He has wings. He can fly
I'm just a big guy that weighs like
2,200 pounds or something. That's it. I don't do anything else. Hope doesn't do anything else
He's just a huge guy that weighs 2,000 pounds
That's it
Here we go. This is it. He's a living nuclear bomb
Uh, yeah, that's kind of cool
Now you're in my territory and like a little corridor
What the fuck were you thinking guy with a jetpack?
That was stupid of you
You know what else was stupid getting too close to the nuclear bomb
Get away from me. Get away
Oh fuck. No, that's just so much damage. Why does it do so much damage? That's just so much damage
Oh, make sure you target the fucking guy
Make sure you target that guy
Come here. Come here. Where'd you get the tanks from?
It kills me. I think no you better fucking not kill me. Oh my fucking god. I have to run now
Where did you get all the fucking tanks from man? Where'd you get all these tanks?
All right. Hail Mary. I got I gotta just throw this tree behind me and I'm going to kill him
I have to fucking oh my god. Oh my god. Oh my god. Oh my god. Oh my god. Oh my god
Why why
Why
What? All right banner. That's enough out of you
I spawned eight tanks right behind the wall. I mean might as well. He called in reinforcements
He was fucking dead, too. Oh my god
They were already I I can't believe to do this shit
I can't believe he had that much health. He had one hit
Come on, what the fuck?
Keep throwing shit up, but it's
Okay, I know throw shit at him, but when
200 fucking projectiles are spammed on your screen like the military don't even have this much firepower
This is what even possible
Like the military doesn't even have this much power. This is like eight different militaries here
It's like 12 different countries here in fucking like new york. Whatever the hell we are
We have more here. We have more than eight tanks
Yes, yeah, yeah, do we I guess maybe we do
I'm so sad. I can't believe I didn't couldn't hit that guy was just one fucking move
All right. We may have more tanks this but we definitely don't have this many missile launcher guys. Okay
There's no way we have this many missile launcher guys
Oh just throw
Do it
Oh
No, you know, this is we made we mentioned mmo. This is mpvp and mmo
Everybody has the same like four moves and it's just a mess
Listen to chat listen to chat
I thought you just said farts increases all damage and I was about to say I was about to ban you but you said steel fists
Farts increase melee damage
All right. This is it. I'm beating him right here and then i'm then i'm going to bed
Give me steel fists
Okay, here we go
Don't fuck it up and i'm going to clear out the bullshit
When we get to that next zone where he gets in the middle and he flies away and shit
I am going to kill everything there
I'm not going to let it get to a point
Where it is like 15 where every tank in america is on screen eight all eight of them
I'm not going to get to that point again charge the jump. I'm doing it almost every time
I charge the jump 85 percent of the time
Okay, oh go go go
Don't let him get away
Don't let him get away. Don't let him heal
Shit
Where are you going? What's the matter something wrong?
All right. Yeah, there he goes
No, not yet. I need the heat. I want to heal
Steel fists again
All right. Now you get the fuck out of here steel fists. Give me another car
I'm not messing around right now. I'm going full on super trying as hard as I possibly can
Steel farts, that's right
You don't only run in one direction, you know, I kind of curve your body but you can't
Collectible. Sorry. I don't care about the collectible. I care about punch this guy's head until it explodes
That's what I care about
He's yeah, I have
How would you go that way?
He's crazy
Absolutely bonkers. There we go
We don't care about collectibles. We don't care about anything interesting. We just care about the game
the game playing
Imagine that right right actually give me that thing
Okay, I got the fog point
Nice shorts, dude. Thanks
All right. Here we go
This is it
I'm gonna move one more time
And then i'm gonna start i'm gonna here we go kill the tanks shit
I'm ready for this
Going right over there. I got full power
Let's go kill all tanks kill all things
Anything that moves attack it
This guy's moving
We can't have that
Where am I? Here we go. Come on
This is it
I'm on
He grabbed me
What the fuck?
Oh my fucking god
he
are
Uh
What?
The fuck now I gotta run the fuck away. He gets two grabs and he's dead
Fuck he's behind me. Get away from me. Get away
Get the fuck away from me, please
Okay. All right. All right. All right. Oh, no, no, no, we uh, giving me the fist
Here come look the tanks weren't even here before you can't tell me this tank was fucking here. It wasn't even here
It wasn't even fucking here
Here we go. I'm gonna punch this in
I can't believe it. That's gonna grab me and kill me run run run away from him. He's coming. He's coming with me
Don't grab me
I can't see
All right, run run run run run run run
This is a coward move we're doing full-on coward place here. I don't care
No, no
No
What the fuck? Why does it have to do so much damage?
Please don't kill me. Please, please, please, please
Lots of cars and shit here
No, don't throw that guy
Ah, okay. Okay. He just hit himself with the car. I'm gonna run this way lady
Uh, uh, where'd he go?
Just fucking die
Come on, please
Just die
Oh, yeah
I did it
Wait a minute. I didn't do it. Get out run
Run run run get out get out go go go go
I have to teleport the fuck out of here
I don't want to do this again
Who's behind me? I don't even look behind you. Why would you look behind you? That's a mistake
I didn't even want to do that
Okay, where's the jump point? I need to get to the jump pad
The fuck out of here
Where did it go? Okay settle down. I just forget this and get in the jump pad
It's not a big deal. Just get in there
Okay
Good. I'll just get in it and jump out
ah
Okay, we're good
That was fucking ridiculous
This game is fucking crazy
All I want is loyalty and patience. I've been patient. I'll be the judge of that
I can't afford no more mistakes mercy. Not at this juncture. Oh, all right. Well worried about you a meal
You should be i'm not stupid. I know what ross is doing
What's happening to you?
Nothing
I suggest you concern yourself with the problem of unless you want my headache to become your headache
Just go bring me banner. Who's that?
Who can do that?
What character is that?
What character can do that?
me
All right. I'll see you tomorrow. It's a good place to stop it after um
I'm planning about the game for an hour while I lose to the same boss like four or five times
Then I finally do it
Uh, I think I might just play this again
I i'm just gonna beat it. I think I'll just beat this tomorrow
I could beat this game and I could then I could say I beat this game
it's either that or
There's a lot of shit I could play but
I I think there's like about another four hours of the game left. Maybe five according to
Uh the how long does this game take to beat dot org? Whatever it is. It's it actually is very fun
But yeah, we'll we'll continue tomorrow. I'll beat it tomorrow
And i'll see you then
Thanks for watching
Uh, let me just check the internet here
uh this
Statement here says that I have no dropped frames first stream from uh, the new internet
and it looks like
Now i've no i've no dropped frames
F F F
Yeah, so that's a good sign
good sign
I'll see you guys tomorrow
Have a wonderful rest of your night. We're gonna do the bits and everything. We'll hang up for another few minutes
And i'll see you tomorrow for more hulk
punch walls
And have missiles explode in your face
either those either staying
you're obviously going to
Do the bits and subs and everything we will chill animal crossing sure went well, huh?
I kind of missed the boat on it because of the move
and it was one of those things that was
just
It was being played off stream and it it that was like what was played
While kim and I were moving
so
Okay
So let's do the bits
Thanks again for joining me everybody. Let's go back
I had sticks renegade 250 from sticks renegade
Uh captain nemo also signed it, but I was dumb and forgot to add them. I believe talking about the auto card
I really appreciate that. I'm gonna show that to kim
After the streams over i'll say kim look at this
Very touching very nice. Thank you everybody
Wyatt archer, thanks for 1500 bits buy auto something nice for being a good boy
I will auto gets showered with gifts and presents and toys. He's such a spoiled little dog. It's unbelievable
But I wouldn't have it any other way. Thank you for the 15 dollars. Appreciate that atro lux atrix
Thanks to the 250. Hey man, happy to see you back and andy when community content night's gonna happen
There's so many submissions so many good ones
Yeah, the the last week's streams are just gonna be next week. So
We're doing friday saturday sunday here
And then we're gonna do wednesday thursday friday saturday and the wednesday thursday friday saturday
Is going to be the stuff that we were going to do last week
It's just going to be pushed to this coming week here. So it'll be thursday wednesday for watch the public domain movies
Thursday community content night friday mystery game and then saturday the easy bake oven stream. That's the plan. This is pretty good
Look at these guys, man. Why is it not showing up?
Why is this not showing up?
Uh, why is this image not showing up?
Where the fuck is it?
I swear to god sometimes it's like this like just phantom shit that happens
Here we go. I did the same exact thing three times
Very funny
But thank you
Thank you to uh atro lux. Yeah, it'll be thursday community content night. It'll be thursday zyxy. I get 50 community subs, which is insane
Thanks to the huge subs
There were a shitload of subs today
I know i've been gone for a while when I cut and it's it shocks me
When I come back from like four or five days in a row of not streaming
and it's like
Hundreds of you guys just fucking subscribe
I'm it's shocking. Thank you
Kill kun. Thanks for the 300 bits germa. Don't forget about joel's 3d movie maker movie on movie night
Ooh, should we tell him should we tell should we tell him?
um
We already we watched it. We watched it like a couple weeks ago
Thank you for the 300 bits nonetheless
Smelly boy, thanks for 250 got to say. I really like the funko pops and pac-man ghost
They really helped give off the mid to late 2000s angry video game nerd knockoff vibe
pac-man ghost light
I just it was like cute
And I think it's it's I think it's cute and it was a gift
Yeah, dark soul says nice apartment man. Yeah, thanks
And they show the link of like the gumby chair and everything
Uh k
Rys k riz thanks for the 1500 bits 15 dollars play the game. We got to it. We got to it appreciate it though
Thanks for the 1500 bits
15 dollars a lot of money that was from big. Yeah, I know a two-headed boy gave five community subs. Thank you two-headed boy
Dr. Clay, thanks for five dollars out of curiosity was the ladder in the background meant to be a joke at your expense?
Which did you actually need that to reach the shelf?
At germa sour hope auto as well
So that was to reach the ceiling that was to reach the ceiling
Uh the ceilings, I don't know what houses you live in but ceilings are not five and a half feet tall
They're like somehow some ceilings are like 12 to 15 feet high
If you can stand up in your room right now put your arms up and touch the ceiling you are fucking huge
You're huge. You're like it's you're like at least you're like six four six five
You know, you have to be at least like six three six four six five to do that and it'd be like you had to stretch
That's you're like talking about hitting your head on the top of the door, right?
And by the way, it's to it was to put foam up on the on the top of the walls
Which I have to you have to like lean in and put a bunch of pressure on but there's a stick there
Six four is not huge six four is fucking huge. Where do you live with six foot four is not huge
What
Six three is average
You guys are fucking crazy
If you're like six four six five, you are a monstrously that's a tall person
Anything lower than six eleven isn't human
Six four is the world average for adult height. Holy fuck. We'd that would be crazy
Actually, it's like five nine by the way, buddy
anyways, I don't know what i'm not gonna get like fucking trolled right now and like
Gaslight we're gonna just move on
Uh, thanks to lizard amiibo for the 250. It looks like you're in a basement closet
With a single light bulb hanging from the ceiling. Well, there's a single light bulb hanging from the ceiling
Eventually here over the next few weeks. I'm gonna have some lighting in here
I'm gonna get a couple of lights maybe one over here or over there. I don't know. I just
Just got here. It's the first stream from the new fiber
Yeah, I see it. Yeah, and that what's wrong with it. Look at that. They got two
They got more space there too. Hey, that's fine. If you want to collect this shit, that's fine
What is this guy a redditor or something? This is a person a redditor because they have like a shelf of funko pops that they like
What have you said that to this person? This guy was like, I have I don't even know what that is. What is that?
Right reddit. I don't know if that is
What is that? That's impossible. No, no, it is possible
Find me a find me something from the witcher here and I will just and I will agree with you
I don't say anything witcher related on this shelf therefore cannot be a redditor
Right, what is this gold and bits and I don't I'm not gonna get i'm not gonna leave a look at this image
Guys, what the why did I even hold up that thing and do that? Whatever
Anyways, thank you for the 250
Ocean dweller. Thanks for 250. Excuse me. German. This is important. When when did you say
You put your milk in the eggs
Did you say you put your milk into the egg and then mix it and pour it into the pan? Yes
um
you put
That two percent whatever it is. It doesn't matter what milk it is two percent. Just don't do like like almond milk
Or like soy milk or something just regular milk is better because it makes the eggs fluffy and there's a lot of big fat
So you pour a little bit of milk in there?
Heat them up
Add a little bit of pepper beat beat beat beat beat put a bunch of parmesan
Not shaved parmesan. We're talking like the powder shit powdered parmesan cheese
Beat beat beat beat beat beat to your liking and scramble them. You will love it. I guarantee it
You're gonna like it parmesan pepper eggs. Trust me. They're my specialty. Hey fancy jack. Thanks for five dollars germa
I love you. Do you though? Thanks for the five dollars fancy jack. Appreciate it
Uh, thank you to ninny
You can do flying ddt's and elbow drops in this game. Try grabbing a person and a charged x in midair
You have to unlock it first, but that's awesome
Say it back
Why won't you say it? Why won't you say it back?
Germa sucks. He won't say it back. What the fuck you had specialty eggs this whole time. You didn't tell me
Yeah
Parmesan cheese pepper
You beat him up
By yeah, it's it's a specialty because it's only made on special occasions. Maybe once or twice every two to three years
It's very special
These buy this
Hold on. There's a mist of bean turkey head
up
What is this real?
Is this actually real? Of course, i'm gonna buy this. This is rare
This is not like a dumbo where it's sixty five hundred dollars, right?
That's so funny. Haha. Well, you weren't you probably weren't here when we went over the turkey thing
forty two dollars
It's kind of
That's like five to ten dollars more than i'm willing to pay for something like that to be honest
I mean
Wednesday movie night it is
Wednesday
Oat horse, thanks for the twenty five dollars twenty five hundred bits from oat horse. It's hulk
Woo cha chao
This is the best hulk game great gdc talk from this dev team, too
It is good. They made simpsons hit and run. I mean, it's sure i'm i'm certain it's gonna be
Very very fun game. Thanks for the twenty five dollars. That's a lot of fucking money
You guys give a shitload of money to this stream. You guys give so much money to this stream. It's unbelievable. It's insane
We need more supplies for his cringe shelf
Okay, I can't even I just wanted to have a I thought it would be nice
Like I got like seaman up there. I got binding of isaac board game thing. Like that's cool
You guys are focusing on one item that happened to be up there for fun for one day
You're focusing too hard on
The proto man funko pop and you're not focusing enough on the thing for pc being displayed
It stains
Thanks for the fifteen hundred bits fifteen dollars. I hope auto gets well soon
I just want to say that I just recently started regularly watching your streams
I want to say that your streams are great
And your comedy is incredibly fun and comforting in these odd times
Talking comedy here. Thank you. Thanks for the fifteen dollars. It's a lot of money
15 a lot of 15 15 20 20 15 for you guys have showers of presents to me
Thank you. Yeah, I wish there was more I could say. Thanks a lot. It's a lot of money. It's for the funko fun
Uh, thank you. Loli blaster for the five dollars duct tape germa and kim back-to-back to make a super person
Also, please consider playing custom robo. I believe it would be great
game for your stream
Stop fucking looking at the shelf
They're not multiplying
You know what? It would be fucking funny. Oh, i'm my it's like part of me just wants to fucking do it and just do it
I don't care how much money it costs
Every stream going forward every week
Five is like two to three get added to this shelf and I never talk about it
Until it is full with like 60 funko pops behind me and I never say a goddamn word about it
But then I think about the future and the future of that
That means what am I gonna do with like a hundred funko pops? What the fuck am I gonna do with those?
They're just gonna take up a shitload of space and I don't want them. Just give them away. I could
We'll see
I'm not gonna talk about that anymore
Also, thank you to apple shift
For the 250 yo, I completely forgot rampage existed. I used to play it all the time on the n64 with my brother. Oh my god
As soon as you mentioned it it unlocked a lost childhood memory
Yes, I think your streamer room looks hella cool
Yeah
It's not even done. It's gonna be like lights and
Sounds and like spotlights and disco balls and shit. It's gonna be awesome
Thanks a lot. They say also say hi to auto for me. I will
yoda 985
Funny name you got here
It's funny. Thanks for the five dollars absolute chad wiener dog has too much sex and gets a pee pee disease
And they also say glad auto is doing better my dog
Jenny peed the couch like 10 times in the last few days
We got her tested and she weird coincidence also has a uti germa suspicious wonder how she got it germa suspicious
That's not even an emote
Stop
Thanks for the five dollars though
Yoda 985 again 250
Germa, I can't stop giving you money but skip to 25 seconds in this video is teaching chat how to do a presentation
screen is
Let's see
to 15 seconds
From community
Second when you want to drive home a point hand them a sandwich try it hand them a sandwich
I'm all right. I'm gonna tell you guys something. Okay. It's not a community
Um, i've only seen like three episodes of community
Yeah, i'm one of those guys that hasn't seen it seen like maybe a few episodes
I and I know gotta watch community gotta watch community gotta watch breaking bad. You haven't seen breaking bad. You haven't seen community
You haven't seen ghostbusters one and two
How could that how's it possible? Let me say who cares?
This is a resident. It's a reddit show
so
I I haven't so i'm a i'm like this super redditor guy, but I haven't seen the reddit shows
Are you having a problem with that?
Should I tell you that community is my favorite show ever would that help with your you this this bullshit that you're weaving this web of nonsense
You're a shitty redditor. How can you be a good redditor?
It's like a site for fucking news and funny pictures and shit
You just roasted reddit. It's just a it's a website
It's a it's a website. It's that's like saying wow, man. You're really good at uh, really good at twitter
I'm really good at telling you like 15 times a day the food i'm eating
And how annoyed I am at the guy that cut me off earlier
Am I being too harsh?
No, no, okay, maybe a little
Remember you're really good at animal crossing. I'm i'm not though. I don't even play it
I played it like a little bit during the move, but I haven't
Been busy
You have to hulk up
Oh, there he goes on the reddit rant again
It's not my fault. It's it's
It's not my fault
I've been getting blasted for having funko pops on the shelf
Like if you're gonna spray me in the face with a hose, i'm i'm not gonna just like i'm gonna move
i'm gonna be like hey
I spray him again spray me the face this time
Okay, sure
Uh
Why would I let you do that?
No, i'm gonna be like hey get the don't fucking spray me with a hose dick
Whoa? Whoa?
Whoa?
Jesus
Oh
You're hey, your hands are around my neck chat
You're choking me. You're choking me. You're choking me with your you're pushing your thumbs on my trachea. Stop. Stop. You're a fucking idiot
What did he say to me?
He just called me an idiot. I was just trying to choke him to death
I was just trying to fucking murder him. What did he say? Hey
Hey, you asshole
You believe he said that to me
I'm just trying to fucking murder him. Hey abomination zero. Thanks for the 250. I'm the bad guy
I'm sorry that everything is so bad. Jeremy
No
That's fucking funny
You have a funko of a movie you've never watched which one
What movie have I never watched?
Ghostbusters
Ghostbusters is one of my favorite movies ever made
No, everything on this shelf i've seen
except for the sail
I've never seen sailor moon. That's kim's sailor bars
and
What uh, what's this thing's name?
You what's it?
Who ditama
Go ditama go ditama. I don't know what that I don't know what that is. It's like an egg thing
It's kim's
You didn't see the cuber movie what his 12 second appearance in wreck it ralph. No, I haven't seen that movie. You're right
Anyways, thank you to uh dork cube for the 250
The question of what happens to food in hulk's stomach when he transforms back into bruce banner is actually answered in one of the marvel
zombie comics
If I remember correctly hulk eats like five people
And then when he transforms back all the people's bones that weren't dissolved by the stomach acid poke through his rotting skin
Okay, now what happens if he's not a zombie will that same thing happen and will it just kill bruce banner
Like if the hulk were to eat five people and not be a zombie would when he shrinks down
Would they just poke out through?
40 parts of his body and just fucking kill him in like blood everywhere and shit
a shower thought
Also, I missed a five thousand. I missed a fifty dollar donation
from vim thrall
Thanks with 5 000 bits they say i'm praying i'm paying you this much to never talk about hulk piss ever again
I don't remember what it was. I don't know. What was it also?
I still want to put the nose of that one final fantasy character in my mouth
Who the nose of that one final fantasy character hulk is a vegan. You don't even know that it's because he's green
Oh, you're thinking of the jolly green giant. That's the guy that that has like the frozen peas and shit
And he might be a vegan. I don't know but thanks for the 5 000 bits
Thanks, yoda 985 for the 250 speaking of the hulk eating people in the current hulk run
the hulk is
Dissected and taken apart and then all right this but what bucket but what if I?
I don't want to what if this is like a spoiler with the story though
Like I mean i've read the first part but the second part could be like a spoiler or something. Yeah. Hold on
I saved it, right? Nobody reads comics
No, but talk about the ending to
The 1980s willy wonka movie and all of a sudden i'm i'm oh everything is so bad germa
Every i'm sorry. Everything's so bad for you
I'm gonna think about that like every time I complain about like anything
That comment is gonna stick with me for a decade
i'm gonna be in
I have so many like daily little annoyances
i'm gonna be in like line somewhere like eventually or i'm gonna like something's gonna happen where i'm putting together like a
Something for the office and i'm gonna be like this fucking stupid thing. What a piece of shit
I'm so fucking in i'm gonna think of that person. Oh, wow. Everything's so bad, huh jeremy
i'm gonna be like fuck that person's just fucking with me. They're always in my head and it's
They're right. Okay. I'm gonna slow down
omega lullethis
Oh, sorry, uh what I better say was clown room
a door cube
Thanks for the 250 door cube 7 000
I'm almost certain someone has already suggested this but you should play prototype two
And movement mechanics and beat them up gameplay is similar to this game
I just played through recently and I might suggest playing it on hard
As once you upgrade your powers past a certain point and none of the enemies are threatening
I tried to play prototype
There was a lot of problems with it
I wanted to do them both
But I got to prototype one and it was like a bunch of frame problems
I'm, not sure what it was. I don't even remember
It's because I think I was trying to play it on pc and there was some problem with it
I would have to just play it on like xbox or something
Or on like ps4. Yeah. Yeah. No, it's something I wanted to play
I mean, I tried to stream it like a couple years ago. So
Let's see
Uh king swagus. Thanks for the thousand bits. Here's some money to fund rat movie three's development. Okay. Thank you
Thanks for the 10 bucks
Hey xx deadly donut. Thanks for the five dollars. Jeremy today's my birthday. Happy fucking birthday
I was happy to see that you were streaming today. Thank you for keeping myself and others entertained during this weird time
Also shout out to my brother john
For introducing me to your stream. Thanks to your e3 stream last year. Stay safe. We love you. Happy birthday
Thanks john for introducing you e3 streams are always fun
Although we're not going to get an e3 this year
At least it's gonna be being postponed or pushed or something maybe or even cancelled all together
I don't know. When is e3 typically?
Just cancelled all together
Remember, I wasn't being sarcastic when I said i'm sorry things are so bad
Even if you I know but like even if you were or weren't
It's still like it's like funny to me. It like it makes me laugh
It's like just humorous because I was sitting i'm like complaining about like the hulk missiles and it's like dude
Sorry, things are so bad like the hulk
Missiles are hitting you like all right. It's humor there. It's just even if I even if it wasn't being sarcastic. It's still it
It was a fun comment. I appreciate it though. I really do. Thank you
He thinks care and sincerity are humorous
No, like in the current like situation for when that comment came through I was like
I was like talking shit about like cubit or something. I don't know. Whatever it was. I think you're just a psycho
Maybe maybe one day we'll take that test. Uh, maybe maybe one day i'll do
like
Psycho analyze me thing
Where I get somebody that would be comfortable being on screen and we do like a full like like do like a personality
Analyzation funny. Hey espada escalata. Thanks for the 250 the air conditioner in the brave little toaster scared the hell out of me
When I was a small kid. Yeah, uh, I'll one-up you on that one
Um the clown the clown was the scariest thing in that entire. Yeah horrifying the music in that movie is awesome, too
I took a man of graveyard
Worthless that movie's so good
Oh my god, it's so good
Just please go watch it. Just delete the stream. Just don't just like just delete your just check that x and go watch it right now
Where how are you get it?
It's so good
Why is it none of my top 10 listed movies ever made?
It is no
Hey curr bumble. Thanks for the five dollars. It's great to see you finally play this
Other than gotcha force. This has been what i've been looking forward to the most
By the way, you can put things down with the d-pad. Thank you so much
There's a special funny animation for people good to know
Dorevereen classic name there. Hey bub
This hulk guy seems pretty tough, but he's no match for me dorevereen the wolverine door
Well, thanks for the ten dollars wolverine door. Thank you
Nv
One one casting thanks to the 250 ignore the haters king your item shelf is fun and cool
Yeah, I know I wouldn't have done it if I didn't think so shido's up there
You're gonna talk I can't believe you guys talking shit about shido. He was like he's right in the middle
But let me thanks for the 25 dollars
Jeremy you got to give us a tour of your anime figurine collection. Thanks for the 25 dollars
Hey dark soul. Thanks for the 250. I have to take back making fun of your reddit chamber
I got a stormwind city steam vr home map on my index and fucking pogged
It has the music and everything. I'm just as much of a child. Well, that's that just sounds really really great
That's I want that
That's so cool you walk around stormwind that's so awesome and then dark soul again
Thanks to the 250 any uh any funkers in chat derma walk judging by the extreme backlash of having four on the shelf
I don't think there are very many. Oh, i'm i'm like on the wrong screen. This is just a hulk
No music or anything. Yeah, it's been a while. Sorry about that
We confused a lot of people that thought the game was still going on. Sorry about that. Hey
Peep kush. McGee. Thanks for the three dollars. Thanks for the genuine laughs germ
I've been a fan for a couple years and rediscovered you through a friend
and germa 2
Keep doing what you do
Thank you. Thanks for the rediscovery. Hope you're still having fun
See 4g. Thanks for the 250 germa. Stop, please. Don't melt my funko pop dude. Come on
I'm still making payments on it. I had to remortgage my house
Please dude, just let go of my diamond peter griffin comic con exclusive funko pop. Come on
That's fucking funny. Thank you. Uh, gleg gleg dali for the three dollars heard you loved no more heroes
I do you ever heard or played a killer 7 suit of 51's other most well-known game. Yes, I have
I need to beat no more heroes too before I consider playing killer 7 by the way
We need to do that soon such a good game like this. I'm not putting it off for any particular reason
I love the whole series
And I have to play the one that came out on pc. I want to play them all
Travis strikes again. Yeah, that's what i'm talking about the one for pc
But yeah, we'll cross that bridge after the other
No more heroes series
Thanks a lot boiky. Thanks for five dollars one of these days. She's just actually listened to one of the guys
One guy who said to play some random game burn off the current game and switch it and see how chat reacts
I did that. I did that with rain world
Uh, you are describing the exact scenario of rain world
It wasn't it was right. No rain. I rain world was like more than 10 people
But I did just stop what I was doing an open rain world
Yeah, I mean here's another here's another scenario that's funny that that's funnier than that
I mean like we're talking comedy for like levels the thing i'm gonna say is just funnier than what you said
um, but no, uh
It'd be funny
If I had a plant in the chat that said like oh dude like will you just fucking next already?
and like beat the fifth boss of dark souls 2
with uh
With unarmed and i'm just like, oh fucking oh, yeah
Let me just do this real quick and it's I have it queued up already and I turn it off and I go
Right to it and I do it
And i've like practiced that boss like fucking a hundred times to make sure I can do it
I already did that joke. Did I?
Maybe I did
Silent serenity. Thanks for the 250 here. Are you the guy from reddit?
I saw the photos of your collection on our funko epic stuff, dude
I hope you enjoy this gold and put it towards some more pops
I don't know what you guys deal is with people that like stuff
So, oh no or funko
I like that shit and it's fine. It's fun. It's collectibles. Who cares?
Like people owning funko pops are not going to give you hemorrhoids
You know, that's like don't it. We'll worry about it a beast of blastik. What?
He's so defensive over his funko
He's a moderator. No, i'm not and relax relax relax relax
Relax
What is a beast of blastik? I don't understand
Okay, if you're gonna say it's just a piece of plastic, I would love to see your team fortress 2 hat collection
How much do you spend on those?
A lot of those were hundreds and hundreds of dollars
I feel attacked. How many did you have? I had quite a few
Not really though. I never really had a lot of unusuals or any expensive hats
What did I I had one unusual for the demo man?
What was it?
Gibbous friend feels good man. I used to like to love if there was a especially a heavy gibbous
That was the best
It was so it was the most adorable thing ever because you just knew
Everything about that person's entire life. You know what I mean? Like if I saw a gibbous heavy, I knew everything about them
And I loved them
That was the best thing the gibbous is the one of the greatest additions to any game
You made multiple unboxing videos. You're guilty on both ends. I made like three
And after and this is like two, okay
I made like three unboxing videos in like 2012 and after the third one I was like, oh, this is kind of dumb
I don't want to do that ever again
And I didn't and I haven't
Three is multiple. Yeah, but I I made three unboxing videos because I don't know if they were popular people thought they were cool
I'm like, oh should I do these people like these people want to see this?
I guess i'll try it. I did it a couple times and it was like, oh, okay
Okay, I guess and then after the third one is just like
I don't really want to do that. I don't want to do so I want to do something else
I don't want to do that anymore
It was popular. I tried it, you know, obviously there's like something interesting people think it's cool. You want to try it
We need another gate queue
All right, let's finish up here. We still have like another probably five minutes or so
Uh, mr sneak, man. Thanks for the 250. I have a sneaky question. What's your favorite sneaker? Stay safe
Um, I like
my favorite sneaker
Uh, it would nike prestos
Best thing of ever one of my life and i'm talking nike prestos from like 1998
There you go
Autumn dragons. Thanks for the 250
Good evening king. I adore the mullet hair you have going on. Also. Do you not realize that funko pops are objectively ugly?
Here we go again
uh
And but it but it's me
Who is talking about the funko pops? No, i'm just addressing and reacting to the constant
Slander and attacks that I've had to see over the course of this five and a six hour stream
Uh, anyways, why would you look at a funko pop and think why I want to own this?
Anyways, thanks for the cool stream dad. Hope everything's settling in the new home. All right
I don't know. Why do people collect why do why do people collect anything?
Why do people collect stamps?
It's just something it's a I mean, it's just a piece of paper and it has like elvish on it
Those are those are cooler. Those are valuable
Valuable dumbo is 6500 bucks
Okay, I don't even know why i'm defending funko pop so much because I don't even care
Like I did up until today
This stream I did not even give a shit about any of these
I thought they were like kind
Okay, like they were cute and they were like interesting. I got them like two or three years ago
I i'm not some like funko pop aficionado that like cares this much but yet i'm still here defending
And I will continue to
I was gonna add a motherfucker on the end of that but i've refrained from it. We're making progress
But yeah, we're uh, we're settling really well anytime you move. It's it's
Takes a long time before you actually yeah, this is this is just where I this is where I live, right?
It takes a little while. No, it's been it's been going good slowly but surely, right?
Uh kale
kale
kale the chain
kale to
I can't read it's
Changa
Chale to changa boy. I hope i'm saying that right I get to drive the car today because it's my birthday
It's not much but it's my birthday
Well, thanks for the five dollars and give me five dollars on your birthday
Wish it's my birthday wish to give a little something to one of my favorite people ever. Have a good night
Thank you so much kale
Let me that's an incredibly nice thing to say. I hope you had a good birthday. Happy birthday. Give him 10 back
Thank you over think for the $15 jeremy, please tell auto I love him
I guess you're not too bad either
Really though. Thank you for just being you that's the only person I know how to be
I don't know how to be anybody else. I don't plan on trying to be anybody else but me
That's who I am
Thanks to the 15 dollars
uh
Oh my god. Damn it
I've even moved
Places and that's still happening. Why is this happening more frequently? This shit didn't happen this often
More like a week or two ago. What's going on? Am I am I am I getting more like animated with my hands?
It must be like an extra animation here with my hands. I don't understand
The mic is in the same spot
Ocean dweller. Thanks for the 250. I'm embarrassed for you seeing those funko pops. Please use this money to throw them out
okay, uh box box came in with
2 000 people in a raid
Thanks box box with a huge raid really appreciate it
If those of you that's still here from that
Thanks for sticking around
Hope you enjoyed what you saw and if you didn't sure you'll tell me all about it on reddit
My favorite website
Swiggity-swanky. Thanks for the 250 nice pajamas. By the way, it's a captain marvel t-shirt
This could be this is like a business casual shirt
But let me thanks to the five dollars germa. I demand that you cover that shelf in high quality anime figurines
I will never do that
Not gonna happen
Thank you
Uh, thank you lesbian bigfoot for the fifteen hundred bits
Fifteen dollars absolutely lost it at the funko pop reveal
Be proud of your non reddit collection jeremy
Also, I missed the beginning of the stream. Hope auto is doing okay
Thanks to the great content
Yeah, he's doing better
he has
One or two more days left on the antibiotics the idea is he's getting better and after the next few days when they're all gone
Hopefully he's back to normal
He is going to go back in
for an evaluation
Just to make sure he's
100 fine because if there's a case where this comes back
after the antibiotics
And there's something else that has to be done here and we got to figure out what's going on
But we hope it doesn't really get anything too serious
As it stands right now, he's doing just fine. So thank you goose goose. Thanks for the 252 things. Love the collared shirt
Professional as fuck
And two i'm glad auto is doing better. I'm thinking about getting a dog any tips for first-time dog owners
um
yes
rescue rescuing a dog, um is an amazing experience because
A lot of times they'll be
Already a couple years old. They might already be used to people. They might already be
uh house trained
And you get to take a dog whose life may have been
turns completely upside down because think about rescues is
sometimes rescues are
Dogs or cats or animals or whatever bunny rabbits doesn't matter who just kind of with circumstances got placed in a bad spot
for instance
if somebody's owner passes away, I remember when I was uh,
When I was doing stuff at the animal shelter
If you don't remember some of you guys were alive you weren't here three four years ago
Maybe a little bit longer than that. Whatever it was. I I volunteered at the animal shelter for like a year or so
And animals would come in that was just perfectly normal. There's no there's nothing wrong with them. They weren't doing anything bad
They were just brought in and one of them was because the owner's uh,
Their owner had died and they were like four years old, but it was just a great normal just
Loving dog that is now displaced completely and in a fucking animal shelter
And it's just like completely different than anything they've ever experienced in their whole life
And it was just heartbreaking to know that like wow you spent like five years
Living a potentially normal life in somebody's house and then all of a sudden now you're in an animal shelter can be a lot
so you get to kind of come in and the cycle the circle gets to
Complete, you know get to help out when you can and get a dog or a cat that's sort of already
Got some stuff going on. I would recommend that you rescue your dog. I got my dog from a rescue eight years ago
And he's so sweet. Yeah, that's auto
Auto is it as I auto was a rescue. It's the best auto was like the best dog i've ever fucking come across
I love this dog. He is like the best dog in so many ways
He was a rescue he was like two or three years old when I got him if that's any anecdotal
Evidence of how a rescue can be
There he is. Yeah, hopefully that helps thanks to the 250. Good luck on your dog
Adventure we also had some subs and by the way, we're gonna do the credits here
We had five from germa sucks five from tipped over and five we caught already from loser bybeck
Then we caught tipped over as well. But thanks for the 15 subs in a row there guys all three
And that will bring us to the point of this stream where we roll the credits right about bumping you in the face
Thank you all of you for your subscriptions. They I told you I told you this I told you this is just like fucking hundreds of them
it's crazy I come back from like not streaming from like
What five days and it's just like boom you guys
You guys are too good to me. Thank you. All of you appreciate it and let's finish the bits
Boiky thanks for five dollars question because i'm kind of torn on it myself who wins in terms of video games alone dc or marvel
Je- in just in terms of video games only video games
um, I mean the
How much weight do the arkham batman games carry because it's probably dc trying to think marvel the the spider-man ps4 game was
awesome
um, maybe one of the
marvel ultimate alliance games maybe like the marvel ultimate alliance 2
Uh, I don't think they can be held up to
Like arkham city or arkham asylum. It's it's probably dc
Yeah, dc probably has better games in quotes
Another fifty dollars come in five thousand fucking five thousand bits another fifty dollars
Remember today is my one year sub anniversary. I want to do something big to celebrate and thank you for all the laughs
That you've given me this past year
These dreams have helped me through so much and have made me laugh when I thought I couldn't anymore
And led me to meet the most important person in my life
my boyfriend
Friedl schlitz without you. We wouldn't have we would have never met. Thanks so much for everything
That just makes me feel so fucking happy. That's so that's so nice
I can't yeah, like that's
I don't even know what to say. That's unbelievable. Thank you so much for the fifty dollars for sticking around both of you
I can't believe people have met and had
created long
Lasting friendships and relationships through this channel. It's mind-boggling to me
Thank you so much for the fifty dollars. This janitor sucks at his job
Does he suck at his job or do you guys just keep throwing shit on the floor like right there?
Maybe if you'd stop throwing things the janitor wouldn't have to come out and clean every single second
And maybe if they would have somebody rats in here. Thanks a lot. Hey have gone. Thanks for the 250
General I found it today that I passed my state's bar exam. That's incredible
Thanks for all the awesome streams that helped me get through law school and bar exam prep
Also, when are you gonna play morrowind multiplayer with joel tomorrow? Yeah, you guys didn't know tomorrow literally that's happening. Uh on
On sunday, I mean playing hulk tomorrow and then playing morrowind multiplayer with joel on sunday. I probably shouldn't do that
That's like that's probably that's not cool
That's not cool. You can't like you can't do that. That's not cool. That's just not even cool
Um, so, uh, that was a funny joke that I just did
I acted like that was just so not cool. Uh, i'm just gonna pretend like I didn't say that
Hey cat boy, thanks for the 250 high king
Being another person with adhd. It's super great to see someone else face the same struggles and shit
Uh not to be epic cringe
But as someone raised with a not so great parental relationship
Super nice to have someone like you be able to look up to dad as I go. I must say thank you for the
Kitty floss
For the cat with a three face and play super paper mario. I also have funko pops
I bought years ago. I regret if you want to buy them off of me. I should never even show I
Whatever. Are we talked about roger rabbit a week ago? That's why I figured he had to show it to you
Whatever i'll be laughing my way all the way to the bank in 10 years when I sell that roger rabbit for 10 grand
Or two dollars when that market is worthless. I'll still make some money. Thanks for the 250
And yeah, I I have adhd as well. It can be it can be annoying
But you know what? I just try to deal with it. Just try to do it. Remember walk
Aren't beanie babies the worst bitcoins?
Guys, I hit something. All right. I'm gonna tell you something about bitcoin be all a bitcoin bitcoin
bitcoin is still like
$7,000 for one. So I mean it's not worth like 30 cents beanie coin
Here we go again a crypto rant. No, my dad did was a crypto sentence
Hey hair on flow. Thanks for the five dollars. Hey, germa. My name is chase watching since I was 11
Making me feel old you make me feel old in like 10 fucking years
I'm now a freshman in college
You've been a role model for me for how I act and treat others
For about half of my life. I truly cannot thank you enough for the joy
You brought me and for truly saving my life a year ago
expression is a bitch
Regardless, you're an amazing person to thank you for being you
You don't realize the extent that you reach out and touch people. Thank you for the five dollars first of all and second of all
I sometimes I forget
That some of you guys have been watching since you were kids
Like teenagers and now you're you're fucking fully grown adults
Some of you were fully grown adults before and now you're super fully grown adults like me
10 years is a long time
I can't believe there are some people that have been watching for that long. It's still are here. It's still like this channel
Thanks for watching for that long
a long fucking time
gen z boomers
Another fifty dollars. This is another money stream. Thanks for the five thousand bits tipped over
Fifty dollars. Love your stuff man. And hey if you want you can use this to get a u2's of yourself
Is that how much they cost a u2's is fifty dollars can I make it like eight
but would I be the dickhead that has the u2's
that's like
It's 75 percent cheaper than every other one on the website. I even can I even I couldn't even do that
Probably wouldn't even let me do that
Just do it and buy but get a bunch on your shelf. Well, I just it's not a scenario where hey just go do it
Don't like they have to want to do that
That's not like my decision to make
Now, you know, I just I don't just like call up u2's and go hey, I want one of me
Okay, see you next week when it's done
Do one for fireman. That'd be kind of cool. But I don't know but we'll see we'll see if the funko pop meme continues to have legs
I'll think about it
Stripes beast. Thanks for 250 germa. The average height in 1800 was five six. Cool
You see when the chips are down these uh tall people they'll lead each other. See you aren't sure you're just ahead of the curve
Thank you tipped over again three dollars get a u2 is I don't I'm I'm not gonna explore that
For at least a long time pixelated cabbage 250. Thank you
Is that a minecraft chest on the shelf if so, please if so
Wait, if if so, please sew it. Love the new setup, please sew it please show it
Oh, that is the binding of isaac
Hard game. I haven't played it one time
Thank you pixelated cabbage. It is not minecraft. It is the binding of isaac card game board game thing
Orange lane. Thanks for 250. Listen here you chocolate fudge william defoe hair villain wig wearing
Uh taquito eating funko pop buying chad pac-man redditor boomer
Today marks the second year mark of me being subbed to you
I know i'm just one donation amongst the millions of dollars you get e-clown, but I appreciate you nonetheless
Uh, not even close
Uh
Millions of dollars. That was pretty comprehensive. Yeah, he's a confirmed millionaire
Confirmed millionaire
There's a lot of oxymorons in this sentence, baby
But thank you. Thank you for
just one
amongst the millions
of dollars
um, you do realize
that if
If a thousand of you give 250 bits
You can do that math
You know what i'm saying? It's a lot if a lot that's
Don't ever think that you're not giving that much money a lot of you
giving a dollar
adds up to a shitload of money, so
It's not
Don't ever think that oh fuck i'm only giving them like a dollar
Don't ever feel fucking bad about that and don't ever think that you should be doing it in the first place
Because even giving one dollar to the stream you are part of contributing to
To this to me
And sometimes I can't fucking believe it trying to get us to donate. Oh streams are pretty much over
So no, it's not. Well, we got a lot of bits tonight
Speaking of money
Don't ever feel obligated to give me money and when you give me money, don't ever feel like it's not enough money
Don't please don't feel that way
Judging by my last comment about statistics and evidence and math
Thank you. Thank you to
One one one two e for the three dollars epic streamer room dude pog love the funko's
Thanks a lot with the pogchamp me too slimer's got hot dogs in his mouth. It's pretty cool
Hey drysis seven the great
It's the five dollars
Thanks for being a constant source of entertainment since back in your tf2 days
Even though you collect funko pops. I still respect you. I don't collect funko pops
I just have a few of them kim has a few of them
And together that makes six times that by two we have 12 of them total
We just have a few we don't have that meant we have a few of them
And I haven't we haven't bought any in about three and a half years
Just because I display them today does not mean I bought them today. Yubskidoo. Thanks for 250
Hey germa, sorry that chat is being so rough with you today
But since I know for a fact you don't collect dorky figurines. You don't sniff your dogs while he's sleeping
You don't eat shoes and you didn't outright abandon rain world after only playing for an hour
I know you're a good person. See I am a good person. Thank you for the 250
I I see you've said it yourself. Thanks for the 250 dubs kid
Raddus raccoon. Thanks for 250 germa. You truly do have a fake gamer room. I love it
Here's to help fund your funko pop collection as I got
Fake gamer room
It's a shelf
With some lights on it and like some old pc games
Now that funko pop with the clown on the bald head is not even accurate
10 community subs from tipped over. Thank you
Evan jelly on thanks for the thousand bits 10 bucks. Hey, man, love the stream speaking of one guy
I think it'd be cool idea for a stream if you just played a bunch of shitty games
And if a large enough percentage of chat votes next you actually go to the next game
The ultimate culmination of that meme anyway, just the thought hope auto as well. Here's a pog coin king. Thank you
Um, unfortunately you are describing
Every stream that ever happened when I had the next emote activated
Uh, that was just every stream
So I don't I don't know if I want to go back to that
That was uh, maybe
We we we bury that one
Um
Yeah, um guys it's evan jelly on
e v a n
j e l l y e o n
Evan jelly on i'm saying it correctly
That's their name
Bulbaswag desu. Thanks for the five dollars. Hey jerma. I love your be the best you can be thing
If you ever do want to write about another children's book, that would be a really good one
There's be you just got to do you you got to do you the way, you know
How because only you know how to do it and i'll keep saying that over and over again until the day I die
Be the worst you can be. Well, no, that's that would be the psycho way to say it but you pedal to the metal
Goose goose. Thanks the 250 my dog will be a rescue. I'm between two
Let you know what I decide next week. Good luck. I'm sure you make the right choice. Any choice is the right choice
They're the great dogs
Sprio, thanks to 250. Hey jerma. Just wanted to ask what is happening with the asmr stream that you were talking about a while
ago
That's pretty hyped about it, but the news about it went poof
Anything about it?
Uh, I severely underestimated how hard it was to hire an entire marching band
Uh, that's way harder than it looks
um
Like we're talking like a 20 to 30 40 plus person marching band
Was it going to be on that stream?
Uh, it was that was the only way I would I would have allowed that stream to happen
That had to be a thing that had to be on that stream or I was not going to do it
I don't care how I how funny I thought the other shit could have been
No without the marching band walking through that stream I've refused to do it
uh
I was ready and willing to pay the money and and put up and have it all happen
But it's hard to hire an entire marching band. I wanted them in full
costume with with like the trumpets and they're
Like have I want to have the hats and shit it's still possible just to find a marching band and I gotta want to do it
You're gonna do it and you're gonna be in your house
See, but yeah, I mean that's like you don't think that's funny to have like 30 people fucking walk through on webcam
Playing and like blasting marching band music
For my asmr stream auto would freak out auto wouldn't be here
I would make sure auto was out and taking a walk or kim would take him somewhere or something and he wouldn't be here
What about the neighbors?
I would have to like
I would have to give probably a couple knocks
On some of the doors and just be like, um, can I ask you something?
Do you like marching bands?
You do you do that's good to hear
It's very good to hear how does a free concert sound?
tomorrow
At seven o'clock pacific
No
Well, no, the idea was if I I would do it at the studio in vegas
Studio that that same studio. I've been to a few times. I would do it there and that doesn't matter
It's a fucking tv studio
But that is uh, that's for another time for another day
Uh, why mog gave 25 community subs?
25 subs. Thank you for the insane sub drop. That was only a few minutes ago
Thanks for the 25 sub y mog ponder lane. Thanks another 250 by the way
It is absolutely unbelievable that a pac-man fan such as yourself
Uh, he owns a ralph plush pog has never played the best pac-man game pac-man world 2
It's a collect-a-thon platform a very similar to banjo kazooie. Please play it. Um
Yeah, whatever. I'll play it probably enough for a while. But yeah, put it on the list
Trog bomb. Thanks for five dollars. Thanks for being such a great streamer. I've also watched you since I was 13
See that's what i'm saying
Long time enjoyed stopping by and seeing all the hilarious stuff you put out
Thanks for being around and being so creative
Thanks for watching and thinking that this is any good
Sometimes it surprises me still to this day. Thanks for the five bucks
German lied about moral wind multiplayer. Thanks for the 250. Yeah, that one might last a while
Thanks for the 250, uh, also to guillotine senpai
As possibly the richest clown on earth. Have you thought about creating an organization organization to support underprivileged clowns like dr
Phil what you want me to be like dr
Phil and like bring clowns on here or you are you saying that dr
Phil is a dr clown whatever dr. You're saying that dr. Phil is an underprivileged clown the latter. Okay
I had clowns on stream before
They were great
But I don't know. We'll see thank you cloers
V for the 250 german my king. Why haven't you enabled bernie pogg? We're waiting
I'm not gonna enable somebody's face. That's not my face. I'm gonna take somebody's face
And charge for you to put their face in this stream when it's not my face. I ain't gonna do that
And then finally
to
Wrap us up here and end us. See you guys tomorrow, by the way for more hulk
Ultimate destruction probably around the same time around four o'clock or so pacific a gooberry juice with 250
Guten tag hair derma. Listen, don't worry about your weird hulk poop fetish and funko addiction. It's kinky. Ah
Glad you're catering to your fans that are into that. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah
Plus, I mean you gotta remember in america some people want small sheldon funko pops with small
Ha, but we need to make sure the stream is big enough for the people that want big sheldon funko pops
Sure, please god. I need this pepe hands. Okay, great. Thank you
Uh for the thank you for the pop
Comment sprio. Thanks for 250 another thing germa if you're on germa mustard website
I'm wondering what the logo on the site is about just click on it
If you aren't that is all right and forget about it. Thanks, man. Love you
Uh, it's the seagull mascot the seagull is called savvy. He was hatched and created under karma
Kameda's care and saved years later by sprio
They are after being lost in a desert. It is distinguishable by its big heart
Savvy the seagull. Oh, that's cute. I didn't even know that that's cool. Stop advertising. What this website's great
I'll see you tomorrow. Be ready to pog tomorrow when I beat hulk ultimate destruction or play for an hour and say i'm done
And move on to the saw the video game cool. I'll see you guys tomorrow night. Goodbye zero drop frames
I'm happy about this stream one from fiber from the books and it seems like it was just
Solid no problems good good good. See you tomorrow blueberry juice right at the buzzer here 250. Sorry
I'm very drunk. Please forgive me pepe hands. Don't worry. You're already forgiven
You're always forgiven ever you all forgiven all of you
Also, I just wanted to mention since people are saying how they first found you my friend showed me the spi video no joke
Happy that you continue to watch after that. Thank you father
Except for you
You know who i'm talking about
That's you did you did shit that was too fucked up to be forgiven. You know who you are. That's right you
All right. See you tomorrow. Good night. Goodbye. Take care. That was a simpsons joke. I guess it was
I was it. I don't know
Simpsons has been on the air for like fucking 60 years guys
The simpsons have said every combination of every word in the dictionary over the last 40 years
So, of course that simpsons already said it. I know. Okay. Good night