What's up? How you doing? Late? I know. Yeah, by five, by just five mini minutes, okay?
Five mini minutes. I think within five minutes is fine. Don't you agree? Look, they cancel your
doctor's appointment within 15, right? After 15. So if you get to your doctor's appointment
14 minutes late, they still take you. I'm here five. And then, hey, and then you gotta wait
40 for the doctor, right? You know what I mean? How you guys doing? I wanted to pop in. I know I
told you guys last week that the next few weeks are gonna be really tight, schedule-wise. A lot
of stuff going on. But I did not want to just disappear. I did want to hang out and have like
a chill stream and hang out with you guys for a while. You know, you've been calling me delay
Darryl, delay Danny the last few months. You're gonna have a new name for me. It's gonna be
Announcement Andrew. I'm gonna have like three things to talk about. I'm gonna be Announcement
Andy, like in a few weeks. Delay Dongus. Play Halo 3 with me. Like right now? You wanna play
Halo 3 with you right now? Not right now. No. Look, I don't wanna say no, but like I can't.
I don't even like, I don't play Halo. I can't, why am I responding to this?
No, I'm sorry. I'm not gonna play Halo 3 with you. Not right now. But look, just be honest. I'm
gonna be honest. I'm probably not gonna play Halo 3 with you. He's so high. No, I am not. I've just
got a T here. So today we're gonna do... Sorry. Today we're gonna do a couple of interesting
things. We're gonna play a game that I've been wanting to play. It's been on a bunch of polls
and it keeps getting vetoed. How dare that happen? We're gonna play Leaf Blower Revolution.
Just a chill game. We're gonna hang out. We're gonna see lots of resident sleepers tonight.
That's fine. God, that T was so hot. It's just like, it just like changed my voice.
But we're also gonna do something today that I've been kind of sitting in the back pocket
for a long time. We're gonna go over the Jerma Census that was taking place earlier this past
year. I'm not sure a lot of you've seen it. This is very interesting. Finally. Yeah. So we'll go
over that. It's pretty elaborate. The 2020... Yeah, we're gonna go over the 2020 census in 2021.
Come on, I'm a John Madden game. No, wait. It would be the reverse, wouldn't it? It would be
the 2021 census in 2021. Yeah, I fucked it up. It was the other way around. Reverse Madden.
Catboy waiting room. Yeah. Well, you're gonna have to just hold on.
Just let me do that the way that I want to do it. Please. Thank you. And thank you also. And thank
you. Please again. I did that as a joke to make like a funny slurp sound. And the T went underneath
my tongue and hit behind my back bottom teeth and hurt. This is so hot. And I thought that was so
funny though, right? It was so funny to go like... But the way that I moved my mouth, I just burnt
underneath my tongue behind my back teeth on the bottom. Nice. That was wicked funny though.
Everybody thought it was fucking funny. Everybody laughed at it. All right, let's go. Leafblower
simulator. I keep saying leaf blower simulator, but that's not what this is. Thank you Slimes for
the five community subs. You got Slime in your name. You are automatically a family member
in the Slime family. Not my family, in the Slime family. Which I mean, what is this,
Jerma? I told you I wanted to play this. I told you I wanted to play this. We went over
this like a million times. How many times have you guys been in the pre-stream chat and I was
like, I'm going to play leaf blower idle game. And people were like, oh man, don't play that.
That game sucks. And I'm like, I'm going to play it at one point. I'm going to play it.
This has happened like 10 times over the last two or three months. Hey, easy cash. Thanks for the
10 subs. Go get the Catboy dress. You're going to get the Catboy stream when I deem it necessary.
Okay. I can't wait for you guys to get so into this. You guys are going to, oh man,
it's a leaf blower game. This game's stupid. I don't even like leaf blowing. It's not even
the fall, Jeremy. Wait, what year is it? It's winter. It's not even the fall, Jeremy. It's
winter time. Why would there be leaves on the ground? Do it again. Ooh, all right.
I'm an engineer. That means I like guns. More guns. I've never seen that video in a long time.
All right. This is way too loud. Ha ha. NG joke. Band that guy for five minutes. All right. So
what do I do? Oh, you just have to get them off the screen? Do I have money? How is this leaf
blowing? I'm just sprinting and the wind that I'm making from running is getting rid of this.
This is epic. What is this thing? Gold leaves, trees. Okay. This music has to go. Can we put our
own music on? This is going to drive me crazy. This is going to drive me crazy. Sound effects,
volume, master volume. Wait. Alternative font. No. But on Doom? Hold on. I don't even hear any
sound effects. Where's the music? All right. I need to find the music button. Hard reset. Oh,
it's right here. What am I stupid? How do I drop it? All right. We need our own OST. I am so dumb.
All right. We need our own OST. Look, the leaves are getting out of control. Hold on. What should
I put on? How about the one that goes? The Flintstones. Pushing away leaves with your
bare hands is so much fun. Okay. I get a rake for 50 leaf dollars. Get a rake. Pushing away leaves
with a rake. Guess you're doing it wrong. Oh, shit. This is perfect. Big bang theory OST. You
want to try to get me banned from this website? Wait, that made sounds. How do we get one sound
effect? That was it? I just get one sound effect. This is epic. Just wait. Just wait until the huge
crazy dark twist happens. I don't want to tell you guys about it, but man, you guys have no idea.
It's like a leaf blower again. No, there are bodies buried here. There are bodies buried here,
and slowly as he cleans up the leaves, some of the bodies are going to get exposed,
and there's going to be skeletons and dead decomposing bodies and coffins and shit in here,
and this is a guy's backyard and he's a fucking serial killer. There you go. You play the game
now? You spoiled it. All right. I need an OST. Give me something. I'm going to beat this whole
game on stream, by the way. I'm on Doom 1. Turn it off. Bet on what? Put on Final Fantasy. How
about Silent Hill? Okay, I'm into that. Let's put on Silent Hill OST. That changes this whole
thing. This makes this like a scary game. Let's go. I'm getting overwhelmed by leaves here.
I have $600. Hold on. I have $600 bucks. A $500 rake? Large rake. Better, but still feels wrong.
That feels pretty clean. I like it. I like it. How do I make the leaves produce more trees?
How do I make the trees drop more leaves on the ground for me to rake? That's important.
Come on, I need more money. Gold leaves. Trees can drop 10,000. Spawns one more leaf per tree each
step. Oh yeah, let's go. I'm making trees. I'm actually spawning trees around. This game is
fucking crazy. I like that. That feels pretty good. Yes, I am very well aware that this looks like
one of those mobile on your iPhone ads where the ad forces you to play the game for five
seconds before you're allowed to hit the X in the corner. It's always really laggy too.
How do they even do that? Why do they even do that? All right, I got $500 bucks. Wait,
I got a trophy. So many leaves. That's one Golden Emerald claim. How many Golden Emeralds do I have?
I just got another one. Fruits. Wait, that you can get fruits and stuff?
Time played. The longer you play, the more achievements you get. Simple progress.
Playing that. How many minutes is that? It's an actual phone game. Yeah, I'm kind of having fun.
I like this. I've been waiting to play this game for months. I've been trying to find the opportunity
where I can put it in there. Leaves drop faster. 5% faster. All right, the leaves are dropping 10%
faster. I love it. I got to get a good strategy here. Up and down, up and down. That was a fruit.
That was one apple. I was waiting to play this. Yeah, this is like my most anticipated game of
the entire year besides Hitman 3, which comes out in like fucking eight days. So we're going to be
playing that. Is that me? All right, can you believe? I got to give some praise here. You
want to talk about video game companies? Here we go. How happy are you guys that IO Interactive
bought their assets out of Square Enix? And we're like, fuck this. We're buying ourselves out and
we're going to go independent. That means we got to get Hitman, the new one, and Hitman 2,
and now Hitman 3. And they've been coming out like every two years and they're fantastic.
Just so much fun. Let me give like some claps in the chat here for like IO Interactive and the
fact that like they're pumping out these fucking awesome games like once every like two, three
years. It's insane that they're able to do that. I got a thousand. What should I do? Leaf marketing?
No, I want to do more trees. Why is there somebody just hitting like pans or something? What is that?
All right, I'm out. It's Pyramid Head. You guys know that I played Silent Hill 1 when it first
came out and I thought the game was dog shit because I didn't get it. I thought the game was
terrible. I was young. I look, it wasn't like it wasn't fun for me. It was just like, this is stupid.
I hate this. I've walked around in like a bunch of like steam and I couldn't find the like diner or
whatever. And I was surrounded by mist. I was like, this game sucks. And I never played it again
until I was like 30. Leaf marketing, you dingus. Hold on. I want to get over 2000.
I really don't like this OST. It's too, I don't like it for right now. I feel like I'm playing,
I feel like it's like Halloween. And you guys feel like this is Halloween right now? I need like a,
a January soundtrack. This is October. Here we go. That's a good technique. Feels good.
Fucking satisfying. Reddit. All right, wait, wait, wait, hold on. Well, I need 10k. Fertilizer?
Nuclear fuel? Holy shit. I'm already going nuclear. That just turned off really fast and
fucking freaked me out. What's going on? I don't like that. Get a leaf blower, you idiot. Hold on.
Get a leaf blower. 5k. I need 5k. I don't even, I need $5,000. Look at that blowing power. This is
perfect. Oh, I love it. The apples are worth, okay. What are the apples worth? 200? That's it. Wait,
we got achievement. Fruits. What does that currency do? It's claim all, whatever. What's,
what's the apple currency? Okay. Plus one apple. What does it do? There are 10,000 people watching
this man clean up leaves. Yeah, that's it. Look, it's the experience. Right now you probably looked
outside and you were like, yeah, I still haven't done it. There are probably like a bunch of old
leaves on the ground that you didn't do since like November. And you just shut the window closed and
you go, nah, I'll just watch him do it instead. Break your leaves all the way into January. What
would even happen? The snow, it just decomposed. Oh, that would be bad. There's snow on the ground.
But don't you understand? I've wanted to play this game since like September or October of this past
year. Why would I have wanted to play leaf blowing simulator now? No, I'm catching up with what I
wanted to do four months ago. Otherwise, what? I got to wait a whole, I got to wait another year
to play this. No, you're going to do it. You're going to sit down and you're going to listen to
me play this game. And hold on, I got to get this off. This OST. This OST is making me nuts.
Make me crazy. I got to turn this off. Let's skip halfway in. No, I don't like this. I want
something else. Give me something else. This is too much for me. I don't want to have like
pyramid head chasing you down a hallway for an hour and a half. I don't know. Put on herbs?
URB herbs? What's herbs? Hotline Miami? That's a good one. I'll do that one. Yep. Oh yeah. Yeah,
this is like a 9.4. One reason why it's not a 10 is because I fucking hated every second of this
game. Wait, no, no, no. No, Hotline Miami 2 is the one, right? Look at that. Look at that. Look at
that. Look at that. Look at that. No, Hotline Miami 2 is the one that I didn't like. I liked
Hotline Miami 1. I liked Hotline Miami 2 though. I just hated it. You guys get it. We're all gamers
here. All right. Let's get more trees. Yeah. No, I was supposed to get a leaf blower. Whatever. I
got plenty of time. Oh, it feels so good. It feels like I'm just like shaving. You guys ever shave
in the mirror and you have a ton of hair and you get that one clean line and you just go,
oh, you know. None of you guys have ever shaved before? You don't know what it's like to get like
the clean line of like a... Oh, but I don't understand. I don't shave. I let it grow.
Maybe you have to have shaved at least once in your life. I'm 12. We're 12. No, you're not. You
know why I know that? Because I've got the goddamn census right in front of me. You're 12. Are you?
Well, that's interesting. We'll find out because I've got the census in front of me. I can see
exactly how old you are. I got to get a 5k. We lied on the census. That's illegal. So no, you didn't
prove it. But is that not illegal? I mean, it's illegal. Are there people that like take the
census and say that like 400 people live in their house? That's illegal. Do you go to jail for that?
I don't think you're a court date. The judge is proceeding. Now, Mr. Albertson says here
that you are said on your census that 250,000 people lived in your residence. Is that correct?
That's correct, your honor. Now, why did you think that was so funny to mess with the census?
Very important thing, the census. We need to keep track of all kinds. You know what that does? You
know, that makes us so we can determine where the tax dollars go. That's what it's for.
I'm sorry. I'll never do it again. That's right. You'll never do it again
because you're going to spend 24 months in prison. I'm sorry, doctor. I'm sorry,
Dr. Phil. I'll never do it again. That's right. Adjourned. Hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, guys, guys,
guys, guarantee you. He's a 100% guarantee. Dr. Phil is going to have a Judge Judy show eventually
when he doesn't feel like doing the Dr. Phil show anymore. There will be a Dr. Phil has the big
Judge Robon show. Now you, now you tell me. Now you, you're going to get that. Now you,
you'll hear it 100 times an episode. The court of Phil. He's going to do it. I'm telling you,
he's going to do that. It's okay. I'll just be right. That's fine. Just wait for the battleship
meta to take over Twitch. Just wait and then come to me and tell me that I was wrong. I'm
waiting for you to tell me I was wrong. When you get like the people freaking out at each other
and like bunch of like threads about like the fucking battleship drama, you come to me and
tell me I was wrong. I want you to do it. Just give me six months. Wait, what happened? Oh shit,
we had a fucking raid. We had like a couple of braids. Kit Boga comes in with a raid. What's
going on, Kit? Kit Boga, resident funny man on the internet. Go follow Kit Boga if you haven't. He's
got one of the best streams on Twitch. Guaranteed by the way. That's a German 985 guarantee. Hope
you had a good stream. Hope you had a good new year too. That means nothing. Wait, what?
Hold on. The German 985 guarantee means nothing? Yeah, it doesn't at all.
Oh, you got to get the leaf blower. Hold on. Let me get the leaf blower. Leaf blower. This is fun.
Oh man. Look at this. Oh man. I need extra spawning. Oh, thanks for the, thanks for the raid.
Welcome guys. We're playing leaf blower simulator. That's not the name. The game is called leaf
blower revolution. We're just chilling today. I'm just having a chill stream. You know, nothing
weird is going to happen today. This is just leaf blowing, collecting apples and just hanging out
with you. Thanks for being here. We had another raid too. We had nice beaver. A few hundred people
came in from nice beaver. Thanks for the raid. Where's the cat boy? Hope you had a good stream.
3000 people are gone. That's all you guys know how to raid works? All right. Let me ask you a
question. Everyone's saying 3k people left. Let me ask you a question. So when we raid somebody,
here we go. Here comes the census. When we raid somebody, how long do you stay there for
after the raid? Tell me. Five minutes, 10 minutes, an hour, few hours. No one's obligated to stay here
and watch me. They just consumed probably an awesome kit bogus stream. You know, maybe you got
to get stuff to do. You come in and say hello, jump into another stream and raid, and then you
got stuff to do. You're like, all right, I'm going to take a break. Yummy stream. Hey, Seb,
Seb Burrito, thanks for the five subs, community subs. Thank you, Seb. How long is this song?
Is this like the 10 hour version of the first song? There we go. All right. There we go. I
feel like I'm playing Hotline Miami. Don't you think so? Can you imagine like three guys coming
down here and it's like, next area. Hotline Miami is such a weird game. I always feel like I want
to play it again because it's so much fun to play it. But I've gone back to it once or twice, I think,
and you just instantly die like five times in a row in the first few levels. And you're like,
no, I forgot. I don't want to do this ever again. Do a freestyle rap. All right. Okay.
The leaves have fallen. It's time for fall. It's having a ball. I'm off the wall. I'm seeing you.
I'm seeing you with my two eyes burning you through those, those, uh, those thighs and then,
uh, whatever. That was fucking awful. No, what do you want me to say? I try to find a word.
Don't ever do that again. All right. Upgrades 500. Wait, where's my golden leaves? Wait, what?
Where's the golden leaf currency? Holy shit, there's so much. All right. Where's the golden
leaf? Trees can drop golden leaves. I need 10,000. One leaf per level. This is expensive.
One leaf per level by using advanced marketing techniques. Holy shit. That's two. That's plus
two. That's plus two. That's all plus two. I need more spawn. I need more spawn. More spawn. More.
Bye bye. More marketing. All right. I'm going to save it for marketing free.
I need to take a sip since I burnt my mouth. There we go. Here's the ultimate test for all
you guys said that you would sit here and watch me like paint a fence or something.
I mean, you're struggling right now. Hovering over the X button. Just trying to find a reason to leave
that you said in chat a year ago. I would watch you paint a fence. I would watch you do anything.
I would watch you just sit and stare at a wall, would you? Hovering over the fucking X button.
Remembering the promise you made to me. Are you going to keep your promise? Or are you going to
be a liar? We'll find out. We'll find out if you actually did what you said you were going to do.
I'm just really glad that you heard. Ah, they clicked it. They clicked it.
How much is it? Uh, two. All right. It's 12,000. Should I just go? I'm going to do it again.
Will you succumb to the boredom? Will you succumb to it? Or will you click that X?
You won't click that X. You won't click that X. You won't click that X. No, no, no, no. Wait.
There's a Jedi mind trick. They tell you to do it and you don't do it. You will click that X. No,
don't click it though. Does that work on you? What's the Jedi mind trick one? You wave your
hand around and you say it, right? You will. You will shoot me in the chest.
Shooting in chest. Roger. Force gas light. Oh no, not a robot chicken joke.
Obi-Wan's at the fucking grocery store and like his coupon expired. Sorry, Mr. Kenobi,
this coupon expired. You will give me another day on that 25% off laundry detergent coupon.
I will give you that 25% coupon. Yes. Oh no, he'd probably go, Jedi mind trick. Yes.
Damn that guy. Me? How come every robot chicken reference that we've ever made has been about
a Star Wars routine that they do. Probably because that's what they do. It's either like
Thundercats, Star Wars, or like the Hulk. It's like every single joke they've ever made.
How does Mike? What? What did I say? It's whatever action figure they can get on sale.
All right. I need 12k, right? I need to buy any more leaves. This is bullshit.
You cracked the code after 15 years. Family Guy, Star Wars. Hey, you guys, you guys still make,
you guys make Peter Griffin references all the time. I'm not sure what's happening with Family
Guy right now, but so Family Guy is like not funny anymore, right? Like I don't think it is,
but people, it like, it was funny for like five or six seasons and then it got like canned. They
brought it back. It was all right for a while and then everybody hated it and now nobody cares about
the show. They just like to meme the characters on the show. Like I see Peter Griffin fucking
everywhere, everywhere, everywhere, but you don't, nobody watches that show. I've seen like the holy
crap lowest like people are using Peter Griffin and like Stewie and stuff, but the show doesn't
even matter to them. It's weird, isn't it? Yeah. He's doing what? You are describing yourself.
Yeah. Of what? So are you sure? But people like, all right, but wait a minute. Is this a scenario?
Okay. Are you telling me to like put milk up my nose in the cafeteria? Not because you like want
to watch me put milk up my nose, but you think I'm going to do it and it's funny that I will
actually put the milk up my nose. You don't actually care that I'm doing the milk up the
nose. You just know that I'm going to do it and I'm going to be like, holy shit, the guy put
fucking milk up his nose. You don't actually care about the milk going into my nose. You just like,
shocked that I'm going to do it in the first place. Really? Okay. Excuses.
All right. I need 12,000 and then I'm going to move on to a new weapon. Catboy stream. You need
to lap up milk. Let me tell you something. If you think for a second that it's just going to be me
with fucking cat ears on, if you think I'm just going to have cat ears on and like eye makeup on,
you are so wrong. It's insulting. Just wait. Just you wait. You'll see.
All right. 12,000. I'm almost there. Maybe I should try horizontal. Yep. That's cleaner to me,
I think. What do you think? Is that cleaner to you? All right. 12,000. Here we go.
Leaf marketing level three. Oh, that's a lot of money. All right. Now I have plus four. Let's go.
Now I'm going to get the leaves spawning here. How much is that? I need golden leaves to spawn.
50 subs if you drink milk out of your nose. No, I'm not like 10. Okay. No, I don't want to do that.
I'm not going to drink milk through my nose. No, that's not happening. I'm sorry. If you think
you're going to get a guy drinking milk out of his nose today. No, I'd rather piss my pants on stream.
If you have that on the scale of things you would embarrassing things, oh my God,
of things you'd that, oh, but look at how crazy that was. That much hurt. I would rather stand up
and just pee into a pair of jeans than snort milk in my nose on stream.
I'm serious. I really mean that. Two billion off the debt. Yeah, there won't be a debt anymore.
Won't be a channel anymore. Hey, if I get like permanently banned on Twitch, that means like
the debt goes away too, right? Like I can't pay it back. I'm going to like streamer prison. I mean,
no. If I go to like streamer, like banned streamer Twitch prison, how am I going to pay you back?
I'm literally in prison. What are you talking about? We will find you. Yeah, I'm in prison. You
can come like visit and I'll pick the phone up and you pick the phone up and you can just say like,
hell you well, I had you made it and hang up. Like I don't have to pay you. Oh, that was a good line
right there. All right. Let's go. I got to claim some of this stuff. What do we got? Healthy fruits.
Uh, I, I don't, I want to hit claim all, but I want to see what I'm getting. You guys like that?
Oh, whatever. All right. I need 500 golden leaves. Freeze can drop gold leaves. Oh,
now I have that currency shit. Okay. How often does it drop? Not, not that often. Can I make
them spawn faster? Exchange? I didn't read it. So this is a huge spam and I missed it. I don't know
what I said. This is your lawyer speaking. I need you to whatever it says. Hi. This is your lawyer
speaking. I need you to pay me the fee and kisses this time. I saw your stream on Thursday and it's
being deleted. So I'm not going to read it. It's being deleted as fast as I can read it.
That's so funny. No. New upgrade menu. Where? Oh my God. There's a new upgrade menu. Platinum
leaves. Holy shit. I'm going to be here all day. We're going to go through like four OSTs today,
guys. I can't wait. Poggers. Pog. Poggers. Poggers. Poggers. Poggers. Poggers. There it is.
Does Chuck E. Cheese even still stream? Or did he do that for like a week when Fall Guys was popular?
He quit because of you. All right. New OST. What do we got? Let's see some. Okay. I can do
spawns more leaves. Oh, wait. But hold on. What is this? I got to max this out, right? Fertilizer.
Dust Force? Nah. Nah. Maybe. Doom Eternal. No, we always go to Doom. No more Doom. Something else.
Smite OST. Auto leaf blower and automatic leaf blower. What is that? Oh shit. This is where the
game starts to play itself. Perfect. The little Roombas. Oh, that's so cute. I love them. Wait,
why are they out of batteries? Are you serious? Stardew Valley. How about Pokemon Mystery Dungeon?
I'll do Earthbound for a little while. Who doesn't love the Earthbound OST? I want Toe Jam Eternal.
Just because I want to hear the... Yeah, there it is. Am I delayed by like fucking a thousand seconds?
No.
Burp. Dude, I gotta tell you guys something. I watched my new favorite YouTube video.
It's this guy. It's this guy, Badlands Chucks. You ever heard of Badlands Booker? I love this guy,
by the way. He slams like sodas. He usually competes in the Coney Island hot dog eating
competition. I love this guy's channel. I love him. He gets like a bunch of sodas and Gatorades.
Yeah, enough talk. I love this guy. It's like a new favorite channel. He has a video
where he burps so fucking loud and so long it's almost like it's not even real.
It's been dubbed over, but it's not. You have to play that video. We will. Hold on. It's insane.
You would love that. I love this guy. He seems like a nice guy, too.
He like scream burps into the camera and it just kills me.
But he has a bunch of world records for like eating and drinking and stuff. I'm on a Badlands
Chucks kick right now. I'll tell you. Play it. Hold on. It just comes out. I love it. It's just
ridiculous. Longest and loudest burp video ever created. You better not because this channel is
perfect. Hold on. I'll get it. Show it. Show it. Hold on. I'm working on it. Disney Plus, Hulu,
and ESPN. Don't listen to that. Some characters. The largest streaming TV library. Stop. I don't
want to hear it. Skip that ad. All right. We'll just get to the part. He's drinking a like a
two liter of soda. We'll get to the part where he does it. It's ridiculous. Can you see it?
This is the most ridiculous video I've ever seen. You guys ready? All right. Let's go. Three, two,
one. This is currently the best channel on YouTube, by the way. We're going to make that clear.
It's so hard to do this. I think this is like an old video of his, too. Here it comes. Here it
comes. Here it comes. I turn your volume down. I'm serious. I can't do it. It's so insane.
Oh, it's the best. It's still going. Okay. All right. It's the best video on YouTube by far.
It's Badlands Chugs. Go follow Badlands Chugs. Put it at half speed. Do that on stream? You serious?
No, these guys are like trained professionals. He has world records. I don't know. I can't do that.
I don't have a world record. That's the sample from a dubstep. Oh, it's so loud and just so
powerful. It really is like a it's like a war cry. I got 75 golds. There we go. You're dead
as a world record. Yeah, I know. 80. All right. We got some we're upgrading to do here. Link.
Look at this link. What link? No, no links right now. Look, look, look, look. Hold on. Wait,
wait, wait, wait, wait. I can't even click it. Pee your pants right now. No, I'm not going to
pee my pants right now. I'm busy. How about more trees and more fertilizer? Yeah. Yep.
Here's another one. No, let me get to like at least $100,000 and I'll click it. This one,
please, please. Are you kidding me? You're useless. Well, I click the link. I click the link.
No, no, thanks. That's not good enough. What do I owe? I still owe like just around $4 billion.
That's got to be at least a 75% wipe. All right, that's not happening.
Haven't people already done that too? I know of at least like three or four like to at least two
or three streamers that have done exactly what you were describing. RT did that like very recently
like a month or two ago. I love this game. He dated chat for free. Well, that's the difference
between him and I. That's the difference between him and I. You're not going to get anything for
free here. Everything has a cost. Everything has a cost. It's implying that you're good at it.
What if you're good at something? Never do it. I need more leaves. This is not enough. I need
more leaves. Not enough. Nuclear fuel. No. Can I spend some of the gold leaves? How much? It's
500 for the next tool, right? Can I just save up for the next tool? No, no, no. I need more leaves.
No, fuck that. Unlock the leaf portal. You can restart your leaf blowing to gain coins. What?
Is this prestiging? Spawns one more leaf per tree. Yeah, let's go. Look at that. It's filling the
screen now. Remember, you idiot, the devs in the chat and you missed it. Were they?
Are they still here? Look at the chat. I didn't see. Where? Is it a bait? It might be. I don't
know. I don't know. It might be a bait. Behind you. I look behind me. Hey, man. Hey, what's up? Hey,
you playing my game? The thing is though, anybody could just say that. I could just be like a crazed
person. That could still be somebody pretending to be a dev. The whole dev in chat thing, we need
some form of dev ID, don't we? Twitch should implement a feature where they have another badge.
If they're actually the game dev and they can prove it, when their game is being played from
the directory, they should pop up and chat with a dev badge. Why is that not here, Twitch? Why have
you not implemented that? Why is that not a thing you have here? You just put me in a clown costume.
I'll get in there to a Twitch meeting and I'll give them all these things. I want a percentage
though. It's not for free. It never was. And I make sure I say that in the boardroom. And then they
say, Mr. Albertson, you're not getting any, a fraction of any of these royalties. Okay, that's
fine. That's cool. Cool, man. That's cool. Hey, man. Just give me a call if I can do anything, okay?
Just give me a call. I'll be around. You can use any of those. Just use them. You can use any of
them. All right, cool. Yep. See you. Thanks for having me. Thanks for having me. Yeah, call me
again if you need me for anything. If you just want to hang out. I'll be around. I don't live
here, but I could be here. I could be here. Just let me know. Then I'll honk the nose like three
times and they will never call me again. In fact, the door will lock behind me. The door will lock
behind me and then I will have forgotten something in the boardroom. And I have to stand there and I
have to text somebody that's still in there. Hey, I left my jacket in there. And then they all have
to go, fuck, he's going to hear the door unlock sound. It's not just, oh, yeah, open. Here we are.
He's going to sit. He's right there and he's going to hear chunk chunk. And he's going to know that
we locked the fucking door. Grab my jacket. Toe Jamming Girl is a great soundtrack. I didn't even
think about that. All right, I got money. Where's it going? Freeze. More of them. And a third auto
leaf blower. Is this a Family Guy skit? I hope not. It is. No, it is not. It's not. That's not.
Not. You know, we're going to get to a real weird part of like human history here in the next couple
hundred years when like every conceivable thing that's ever been said, every conceivable joke,
every piece of music, every combination of sounds have been done. What happens in like two or three
hundred years? It's never going to happen. Are you sure? I might. What happens when every possible
joke can be made and every possible song is written? Every movie's ever been made? How do
we entertain ourselves? I think we're going back to the gladiator times when every piece of music
has ever been written and nothing else can be written again in like a thousand years. We're
going back into like we're going back to the gladiator pits. Just listen to old stuff. Yeah,
you could. Or you could watch the new like UFC card, UFC 1600, where they just give two guys
two rakes and and they add like lightsaber sounds over the footage, like live. And there'll be like
two or three ads for like fucking like the new Spongebob movie. That's what we're looking at.
Jeremy, you always reuse jokes. We're used to it already. All right. Yeah, but I made them up.
But I made them up. I made them up. You know how difficult it was and how hard it was to sit there
and have writers block and craft over and over again in my head? Well, what would that be? Like
it was there was so much thought that went into that. It was I had to sit there and write down
hundreds of pages of scripture. I need five hundred leaves. I need more. I need more. That's
the I'm trying to yell, but I'm not trying to actually yell loud, like pretend yelling. I hate
that. I'm not doing that anymore. You'll never hear that again from me. I promise. Stop pretending.
Look at how many leaves are on screen, though. You guys didn't like this game. How dare you?
More leaves, more. Prestige already. Should I, though? Leaf portal is 300. Um, gained coins.
But what what do you mean coins? I don't know what that means. Is this the whole game? Um,
for the most part, yeah, you just just chill and just blow leaves and stuff, man.
Well, this is going to be just a chill stream or just talk to you guys and hang out with you.
Why don't you? I've asked you guys a bunch of questions. Why don't you ask me a few questions?
What do you think? Any questions for me? I will answer anything. Let's go. What do you have? Any
questions? Old to you. Thirty five. Next one, please. What are the announcements? The announcements
of three different projects that are going to be shown and seen very soon. Two of them will be in
the month of February. One of them will probably be in April or March or April. We'll see. Are you
the Zodiac Killer? I was not alive. So no, that's not an excuse. I knew I was. I'm sick of this one.
I need a new one. More trees or should I buy? Should I do it about a maple story? All right,
sure. Let's do maple story. Maple story 2006, two hour compilation. Is this the one you're looking
for? All right. This is good. I'm going to buy more trees and more fertilizer. The same thing over
here. I'll buy more nuclear fuel. I love when there's a million on the screen and you just go
like that. Is it Castlevania? Maple story. I've heard this before. Where have I heard this?
Have I heard this somewhere? It's in maple story, but I feel like this sounds pretty
close to something else. It's toxic. No, it's not. I thought about that for a second, but it's not.
It is. It's not. All right. You guys don't think we're going to get to a point in like 100, 200
years where every song has been written when already you're telling me that all songs are
toxic from Britney Spears? And that's now. Really? You don't think in like 500 years that you...
There's infinite songs. Is there though? Yeah, that's what these scientists say about the
planets in the solar system, but I can only see a few hundred up there. I can only see maybe a
few thousand up there. And they say there's quadrillions. I don't know. Yeah. Prove to me
that we don't live in a dome. Okay. You proved to me that we don't live in a dome. And I'll shut up.
There are only eight planets in the solar system. Like go outside, dude. We're in a giant snow globe.
Just wait till somebody shakes us. Yeah. We're just an old snow globe in some alien's attic
somewhere. And that old alien's going to like pass away. And so the old alien's like young
grandson is going to come up and go through the stuff in the attic and be like, what's this thing?
Flowing like a bunch of dust off it. And all of a sudden a huge amount of wind hits us.
Oh, beautiful. Gonna pick it up and shake it. And just, we're all going to turn to fucking liquid.
That was Men in Black. That's a really, that's a really great concept. Yeah. It's a really
interesting concept, isn't it? It's a good movie. Why are you playing this? Um, because I wanted to
and it was something I wanted, it seemed like a fun game to chill and just talk and hang out.
While I have, while I'm doing a bunch of stuff and doing a bunch of work and, you know, I'm working,
you know, I'm working, you know, got a lot of things going on, some projects that you've got.
Hopefully you'd be very excited about soon. I wanted to come and pop in and say hi for a little
while. This is some OSTs. To explain to you that there's only maybe 30 planets total in our entire
galaxy and entire world. Just easy stuff like that, you know? Planets in the world. All right,
here we go. I'm going for it. Advanced leaf blower. Holy shit, this thing's a shotgun.
It's so much better. Yep. Look at that. Should I prestige? Should I try it and see what it does?
It's the same blower. Yeah, but it's bigger and stronger.
Look how much more powerful it is. Don't do it yet. Does it matter how many apples I've collected
too? It does. Okay. Chilling out while having existential crises. Is it crises or crises?
Crises? Crises? How many? Multiple crises would be a crises. Crises. Sounds weird. Crises. It's
not like a crisis. It's not crises. Crises. Oh, I like this one. Crises is plural. Okay. Yeah,
that's what I meant. Yeah, cool. I'm getting a lot more gold leaves. That's good. Maybe I should
stay at the bottom. No, that's not going to work. They don't go far enough. You're going to, oh god,
I've been on a 20 second latency. Oh shit. Buy combo, you idiot. Gold leaves. What do you mean
combo? Buy what? Buy a combo? Scroll. Whoa. Whoa. Okay. Leaf combo. Blow leaves away quickly to get
more leaf rewards. 500. Increase max combo per what? Combo multiplier? Gold apples. Eat some
gold apples to get gold leaves instantly. Yeah, I want that one. How do I eat it? I'm looking for
gold apples? You need to talk like Markiplier. Why? Gold apple. No, that's just green. Just eat a
gold apple. Can I eat an apple? Supporters shop. Leafblower startup pack. Get 400 gems, 20 more
gems per daily reward, and one times six time travel. Wait, I have this? I bought this? 400 gems,
one times six hour time travel, and then two times 30 minute time travel. Whoa. What do I do? I've
got it. What do I get? I press this? It's mine. Gem shop. I'm not buying any of these. I got 400.
What do I use them for? More trees? Leaf combo. Leaf combo. You just clicked on the gem shop.
Oh, I thought I was buying 250 of these. Keep your tools after prestige. Increase your leaf
reward by 750% for all leaves? Like permanently? Permanently. Increase your prestige coin rewards
by times three. Should I do these? Increases your BLC coin rewards. Ultra fruits. I don't know what
I should do. I only have 400. Get the first one. Keep your tools after prestige. I got that one,
okay. Increase your leaf reward by 700 for all leaves. This is the only time I'm ever
going to play this game. Prestige coins rewards? This one? Prestige coin rewards, time three,
right? Increase all fruits by 800%. Is that after the prestige as well? Which, by the way,
what a wild movie. God, it's Christopher Nolan. He's the best. I'm buying it. That's it. I don't
have any more. This is 34? 34 per leaf? I was doing four. Oh my God. Okay, this just sped up.
Pay to win, apparently. Well, let's get some more trees. Oh, now we're heating up. This is
going to heat up like crazy. I have 1.7 thousand? Leaf combo. Combo 50 times two. Max combo increase.
Holy shit. Plus 102. Don't heat up leaves. What do you guys think the first food that a caveman
ate was? What do you think it was? Is it weird that I'm going to say other cavemen? But wait,
no, that would imply that they have to get older. Okay, so hold on. Berries? It started eating stuff.
How do you know what hungry is? You just have this awful weird stomach feeling and it's like,
what's this? The first person to ever eat food. I didn't know what that meant. Who was the first
person? Who was the first person? Bible logic. Who was the first person? Well, it was Carl the caveman.
He decided that today was the day he was going to eat. He's going to chew with his teeth
everything he could find. Carl the caveman died very shortly after this, but Cindy the cavewoman
watched what Carl the caveman ate and noticed that he stopped moving after eating this particular
rock. So she was like, I'm not going to eat that one. Not going to crunch up that one. So she
started to eat just random shit until she died. And then Steve, caveman Steve came by and realized
that cavewoman Cindy ate a branch that he's not going to eat. And he also knows that caveman Carl
consumed a couple of rocks that were, that made him stop moving. And eventually it got to a point
where they figured it out. Evolution pretty much. God, can you imagine, can you possibly imagine
needing to just take a guess? Like, can I even eat this? Like guys, I look at the back of like
a fucking almond milk and if it's like close to like its best buy date, I go, I'm not sure about
this. I'm not sure about this. These, these people had to fucking eat just random stuff until they
died. And then other people just like, what? We've got it really good. He's like caveman
caveman Andy. And the worst part about this is it's like really think about that. Like water,
water is essential to live and it's essential to life. But back like hundreds of thousands or
millions or whatever, whatever it is. Even water could have been dangerous. You know,
it's like why did he die after drinking that water? We drink water. We drink this liquid.
Some water cannot be drank and consumed. How the, what? How do we keep track of this? That water
has like fucking bacteria in it. It like killed him. That water is like salt and it's bad. How
did they keep track of this? It had to have been some big giant caveman notebook that you went to
before you went up to go eat food. And you just kind of looked at it and been like, okay,
green rock bad, red, red, orange rock. Good. Red berry bad. And that person has a huge list
and that's something that you have to borrow. You do, you can't remember all that. Why are
they eating rocks? To find out how do animals live? Animals like just eat, but they had to do that too.
I need more combos. Yeah, I do. Poop diary. A large green bean, poop red. Stay away from green,
large green bean. Somebody had to keep track of this. Yeah. All of your history books that you
read in class are just the evolution of the don't eat the bread rock book. That's the first thing
they had to write down. Ooh, nice. What about bread? They didn't figure that out for like a
thousand years. He's doing crack rocks. A thousand from what? I don't know. I don't know anything.
You know, as much as I do, as there is a part of our human history that we have no idea what the
fuck happened. Cause I have a blurry black and white picture of like my great, great grandfather
with a top hat on. I don't know what he ate. We don't have, what do we have for barometer? Bro
history. We know what they, yeah, we know what our like great, great, great grandparents looked like
but what about their great, great, great, great grandparents? Wild stuff, man. This dude is
absolutely zonked right now. All right. I'm going to buy some stuff. More marketing. Should I,
should I prestige? I feel like I kind of should. Combo duration longer. Combo multiplier. Holy shit.
This is going to be crazy. Hold on. Nice. Get a new leaf blower. I could. It's 5k. All right. I'll
get the new, uh, stop hogging the bong. Well, we can't have, we can't have like, listen to this music.
I'm sitting here just blowing leaves and we're listening to like Zen music. We can't have a
conversation like this. Highest stream 2021. New category. You guys are going to be like just on
the lookout. You guys are going to be like on the frowl just on every stream. No, that this is, but
okay. Fine. Add it. That's funny. All right. Fine. Fine. Fine. You can have it blowing leaves and
talking about like what caveman eight and how they recorded history. Yeah. I get, yeah. I guess
that is a, that is a, yeah. You're literally blowing the leaves wrong. What? How would you,
how should I do it? How did they learn mate? I don't know. I didn't know that they had bones
in their body. They didn't know what they, like you, how did they even? All right. I'm not, let's
go. This is not going to be highest stream 2021. They did. Yeah. But, but they didn't get it. They
just knew that they had like stuff in their arms. Let it pile up. All right. Fine. I was language
made. What the fuck? I know. What the fuck? I get a new lawyer. Nuclear leaf blower. You need to
take care not to blow away your house with this. Oh yeah. That's a good one right there. Oh yeah.
This feels good. Yep. Oh, that's perfect. I'm going to let it pile up and then I'm going to blow it.
Perfect. Watching the stream drunk today was a bad idea. Why? Oh, let's wait. I'm not going
to do it till it's a ton. Stop, stop, stop, stop. You're ruining everything. Get out of here.
That's like the dog just did that. You, you scraped up the leaves. You got a nice pile.
Like the dog just ran out and was like, I'm going to go like that. It just runs through and you're
like, no. The dog got to have fun before you did. That was fucking fantastic by the way. That felt
great. What do you think? Should I prestige? Is it time? I got max trees. Should I get to max
everything and then prestige? Prestige now. Do it. Leaf portal coming up. Platinum leaves.
I got platinum leaves. No, don't do it. Should I not have done that? Sorry. I got 20. Max everything
first. I just added a ton more. All right. I added so many more trees. You've ruined it. No, I didn't.
Chat's omega stupid. Oh, bismuth leaves. Trees can drop bismuth leaves. Dude. All right. This is
pretty cool. Can you switch to streaming on YouTube so you can, you can watch on your Nintendo switch?
Um, I'm sorry. No. Just open up a stream on YouTube so this one guy can get to watch on
this switch while he takes a dump. Ah, that felt good. One million. Guys, I don't even know how to
stream on YouTube playing this. All right. I think I'm going to prestige. I'm going to go for it.
Let's go. Yeah. It's time. It's time to prestige. Let's go. Unlock the leaf portal. I bought it.
Enter the leaf portal to restart your blowing adventure with some coins. 20 plus coins have
recommended at first prestige. I have 522 coins. All right. Hold on. No, no, not yet. I have the
counter going. Sorry, one guy. I guess he fucking hates you. 55. Yeah. Well, I want like a thousand
coins on my first prestige. God, this OST is so based. Is it? That's the first time I think I've
ever heard it. I felt good. All right. Make sure to do some more upgrades. I'm going to lose it on
a prestige, right? I might as well just get as much as I can out of this. Based. Based on what,
Jeremiah? I don't, that's, I know that you're making that joke. You bought the upgrade. Well,
I have to activate the upgrade. Okay. We can get so many more coins. Look at the percentage just
ticking up like crazy. I'm going to wait till this is like a thousand. Buy more multiplier.
Nuclear max combo and multiplier. All right. We got a higher max combo and then we're going
to do multiplier. Bang. Oh, I don't know what that was. I'm sorry. You need to, you need to
prestige to get to platinum leaf. So you have to keep that in mind. Okay. All right. But I just,
I look at the, look at these coins just ticking the fuck up like crazy. I'm not done yet. I want
those out. I don't know a lot. What do the coins even do? I don't know, but I want them. I don't
even know what they do. I don't even care what they do. I just want a ton of them. This is what
it's like having a lawn. Uh, yeah. Pretty much, pretty much this was, is this a act two Diablo
2? It sounds like that. I love the act two music. Let's go a little more. Uh, I want a higher
multiplier and I want max out the fertilizer and nuclear fuel, but on Naruto just whip the mouse
around. No, I don't like that. I don't like that. That hurts my head. I just, I'd like to cleanly
go through clean lines like that. It's a little slower, but it feels much nicer on the front of
the brain there. It feels so much better. Yeah. Nuclear, nuclear. You know why it's hard? I usually
say nuclear. Sometimes like nuclear, nuclear. Sometimes it's fun to say nuclear. Are you eating
the leaves? Um, I think it's just spraying them off to the side. I get more room. No. Okay. I think
it's time. How are we looking? When that gets to a thousand, I'll do it. When that hits a thousand,
I'll go. A Hollow Knight? Uh, no, probably not. Sorry. I'm sorry. What's the OST? This is Maple
Story 2006 GMS edition. I'm not sure what that means, but that's what it is. Like Dawn of War.
You mean the good one? Dawn of War 1? Warhammer 40k Dawn of War? The good one? That might be fun.
That's like my favorite RTS ever. Dawn of War 2 was good. I'm sorry. I'm going to have to disagree.
I like, uh, I like a lot of units. I like base building. I like the map. I like, no, I don't,
I didn't like Dawn of War 2. I actually didn't like it at all. I'm sorry, guys. I know a lot of
some people might be really happy about it, but because we got Dawn of War 2, that's why we got
Dawn of War 3 the way we did. Keep that in mind. Dawn of War 2's existence is the reason why Dawn
of War 3 was what the game it became. No, it isn't. Yeah, it is because they got rid of all the
stuff from Dawn of War 1 and they made Dawn of War 2 about more about, um, like commanding a squad
and less about like building a base and having like a bunch of units. And then they were like,
well, what the fuck did we do with Dawn of War 3 now? I don't know. Let's make Dawn of War 2 again,
but this time worse. Dawn of War 2 campaign is fun, but everything else sucks. I could,
yeah, I could imagine this probably the case. They have such cool characters too.
They, um, the orcs. I love the orcs. It's such an interesting, uh, it's an interesting group.
What's the boss? The big boss, right? What's his name? Big boss. Big. What's his name? Big boss.
Gorgots here is Gorgots. I'm the boss. I'm big boss Gorgots. I love Gorgots. Now, the cool part
about the orcs was you just had to have a ton of them. The more that you had, the more population
like the better you did, right? Oh, that's a great game. It's too bad. Too bad. Pepe face.
Are we good for coins? Oh, we're, all right, here we go. We're ready to prestige in a minute
because look at the, look at the counter. All right, I did it. Let's go. Why does it feel like
it's zoomed in? Is it zoomed in? Daily reward. Oh, sick. Offline. Leaves spawn to each interval.
10 leaves. Time played. Blowing power. Player HP. Why is there HP? Did I just spoil something?
You can, Santa. Angel for supporters only. Wait, I can be an auto blower? Leaf cape? Free? Afro?
Rainbow? Robot? Alternate garden gnome? I have enough to buy one of these. Hitman? Grandpa? Gray,
green, orange, pink, purple, red, turquoise, white, a bee. Oh my goodness.
Wait, I need to see the other ones too. Let me see what the other ones are. Bird?
You could just be a leaf blower. It kind of looks like a, like a astronaut or something.
Ace of spades? Fruit? Printer? Why would you be a printer? Auto blower? Dangerously funny.
A cookie? Printer? Go burr. All right, I think I want to be the bee. I like the bee. Or the bird.
I'll be the bee. Okay, so I now, gold leaves, a shitload of trees, a bunch of fertilizer,
and a couple more trees. Let's go. Now I can get platinum leaves, you said, right?
It's the funniest movie of the year. Why are you saying that? Spend the coins. Wait, purchase
upgrades persist after stepping into the leaf portal. Indeed, travel to faraway places and
discover new leaves. Unlock areas? Unlock printer. Leaf print machines print and collect leaves
automatically. Hide it from the tax authorities. How many coins do I have? Not a ritual, but a
really fancy and useful machine. Unlock converters. Trees upgrades will be purchased automatically.
Auto buy LBs. Okay, well, first of all, I got to buy the new area. Unlock the auto printers.
Leaf print machines. Converters? Converters? Oh my God, I have so many more menus.
Uh, add a printer. Plus one printed leaf per level for all printers. Increases printer leaves
by a hundred percent. Um, okay, let's auto printer two and buy it. I don't know. I don't know.
Okay, I'm good. Now wait, hold on. Home garden. Neighbor's garden. This is your neighbor's garden.
They wonder why there are so many leaves around so recently. And another one too. I can buy this one.
Mountain. Which way should I go? Should I go to the neighbor's house? Whoa. I go to the mountain?
Bold converter. Converts a hundred leaves to one gold leaf. Start. Per second? Converts a hundred
gold to one platinum. Per second. Okay, um, I'm gonna keep this one turned on. Converter batch
enabled. Start them all. Okay, hold on. We'll keep that one running. Printer shop. Printers print
leaves every second. Prints and collects 39 basic leaves a second per level. So I'm printing 78
leaves a second. Print plow. So what's that? What's that? What's that? What is this? What do I do
about this? There's a bird in the lawn. How do I, what do I do? Do I collect it? Do I spray it?
Kill it. I don't have any weapons. What do I do? Okay, um, I have no more coins. You have to blow
leaves into it. Oh shit, really? All right, hold on. Wait, wait, wait, wait. Platinum. Spawns more
trees. All right, I'm gonna, I got two platinum trees now. I got 27,000. Let's get some more
trees in here. Marketing. Get some auto lowers, auto blowers. There we go. Let's, yeah, let's
kick it up a notch as Emeril used to say. Go to the mountain? Um, everyone in the mountain is
annoyed by leaves. I can't hit him. My, that's too powerful. He's too powerful. I need more leaves.
There's not enough to hit him. My blower's too powerful. Oh shit, I didn't get it. Oh my god,
that's huge. Come on, come on, come on, come on. I need more leaves. More. I need more. By maximum.
That's okay. Wait, wait, I have a, I have a lot of gold, right? Gold trees. Gold fertilizer. Trees,
trees. More, more, more, more, more. Good, good, good, good, good, good, good. Oh, I'm fucking
excited. You're bad at this game? You can't be bad at an idle game. Addicted. He's addicted.
Come on, spawn leaves again. Damn it. Equip your hands? That doesn't do anything. What about a
rake? Oh shit, there's another one. I almost hit it. 63,000? I have 600. Hold on. I need more
trees. I wonder what you get for, like, killing a deer. Do the neighbor's yard, it's easier?
I think I'm already invested here. I want the other leaves. Heal. Heal? Why are you guys saying
heal? Click on this. Sing toxic by Britney Spears for a billion off the debt. I'm not sure that's,
I don't know if you guys are going to agree to that one. I doubt that's actually what you guys
are going to do. So I still have the gold converter going. I'm just going to keep that on. 101 gold.
I have some, I need more platinum leaves. Leaf combo. There it is. Let's go. Come on.
Max combo. Come on. What the fuck do you think this is? Bunnies have a lot of health. Start
platinum converter. Should I? It's a hundred. It's a hundred per one. I'm not, I don't,
no, I don't think so. I'm going to burn through that. Not yet. By the normal upgrades too. Yeah,
yeah, yeah. That's right. Deal, deal, deal. No, no deal. I was so insulted by that initial offer
that I just walked away from the table. Prestige again? I could just buy the portal just to have
it. I have 171 right now. No, I'm not prestige until I have at least like 5k. Look at the snowman.
You played these shitty games to spite your viewers? You think this is a shitty game? I don't
think that. Of course, of course it's to spite them. Every time I see the word bald in chat,
I just add another 30 seconds to when I'm going to play one of these games.
Kill it, kill it, kill it, kill it, kill it, kill it, kill it, kill it. Oh, this is a good song.
All right. I got a lot. Let's spend some money. More trees, more leaves, more nuclear fuel. And
then let's do, I need to unlock platinum leaves. 10k. I'm almost there. Let's get upgrades. There
we go. Nice. Get combos. I will. That's the next thing I'm going to work on. 10k, Andy.
A little more than 10k here right now. Here's what we're going to do. You ready?
I'm going to pause this. I'm going to go take a pee break. We're going to come back. We're going
to do the germa census and then I'm going to continue to play this game. How's that sound?
You ready for a little break? Sounds good to me. I'll be right back. Oh, we're going cheesy.
All right. Let's keep going. First thing that somebody writes, whatever it is,
it's edible. I'll eat it for dinner. Pizza. All right. Cool. Thanks for the help.
Maybe it should be a hamburger. That's boring. So what? So what? Let's go. Oh,
I just got 1.2k platinum leaves. Holy shit. All right. Hold on. I can unlock
bismuth leaves. More trees with these. I don't know. It's probably a mistake. Whatever.
Census. Oh, oopsie. All right. Here comes the, yeah, let's do the census.
I'm going to turn this down. So this is an interesting set of images that we're going
to look at. Here's the 2020. This is very elaborate, by the way. Out of 1,985 respondents,
I was there. If you were one of them, this is so old. This is very old. This is from like
May of last year. Let's make that really clear. But a shitload of you probably have not seen
this before, so I was going to go over it. So how long have you been, out of almost 2,000 people
that responded, and took the whole thing, how long have you been watching the channel?
Some of you, as of last year, 15.2% less than one year. 30% of one to four years. The most
surprising thing for me here is that 54% of you, more than half of the entire channel,
has been here for five plus years. That's pretty surprising. 2012 gang. They're lying.
Now, you had to prove it. You had to prove when you made your first YouTube comment.
So I'm sorry. A lot went into this. Easy. 50% have been following German for five years,
yet 50% also say the most recent ARC is their favorite. The recent ARC is the favorite.
And we can look at that right here. Favorite ARC. TF Tuber ARC, Boston ARC, and then Vegas ARC.
Half of you think that. Interesting stuff. All right, the one guy experience. What do you watch?
Jerma's stream, Jerma's second, or both? Those of you that ask why I have the second channel in the
first place, it's because look at the amount of people that do not watch a stream. Ever.
You got 36% of every single one of you. Maybe. That's the thing with sample sizes, you know,
maybe. That's why the second channel is trying to, you know, put some time and effort into it,
right? Because more than a third of you just don't watch the stream. In fact, I'm talking to
people that might see this on YouTube. So to the YouTube crowd, we love you. Thanks for watching.
Wherever you watch. Have you ever shown Jerma to your friends? Yes, and they liked him. Okay.
No, you haven't. And yes, and they thought he was weird. That's pretty high. Yes, they thought he
was weird. Oh, and Jerma Pluto in the chat. Up here. By the way, it's only a 2.24% margin of error.
By the way, you see who made this, Krosky. This is the one who put this together.
Of our resident mods. How often do you watch the stream? Every single stream is only 12% of you
guys. Several streams a week, several streams a month. Well, let me be fair. Sometimes I only
stream several times a month. Sometimes you only get like two or three streams a week. But besides
that, every stream. Well, the highest percentage is the several streams a week. That's my fault.
12% are lying. And then only, look at this one though. Look at the purple one. Only the Jerma
second and only the main channel. 20%. That's bigger than all the other ones. Besides the
several times a week. Several times a month. That's a huge percentage of you guys. The 1.4%
statistics shown below could be possible, could be people who possibly do not exist due to the
margin of error. Do you watch Jerma alone or in a group? Alone. In a group or sometimes both.
69.9%. We don't exist. Oh no. Very cool stuff. Very cool stuff indeed. There's more. You thought
there was just one little limit. Let's keep going. What kind of psycho watches Jerma985? Let's find
out. I asked in 2016, I wrote, how many women do we have in this chat? I'm curious. We'll find out.
79% male, 10.4% female. Look, I just was, I was curious. I was just curious. I was not,
what do you want me to say? 7.8% non-binary and then 2.8% other. I just wanted to, I just asked,
okay? I just had to ask the question. It was 2016. I just was like, I was just barely live on Twitch.
I was just barely live like every other day. I was like, I'm curious. Because we didn't have
those statistics on Twitch. And then from there, so 79% male audience. How old are you though?
This is why I can tell you guys. He said we're 12. Are you though? 18 to 24 is the largest demographic
here. 73.5% of you guys are, I would, in the 18 to 24 range. Not 12. 17 or younger is 14.6%. You're
not supposed to be watching this stream. You're, you need, you're not supposed to be here right now.
What's an R rated movie in the United States? 17? Well, okay. And them. And then the 25 to 34
is 10.7%. There are a pretty significant amount of people that are older. 35 plus is 1.2%. That's
where I sit. Yep. A whopping 0.2% said they were a rat while one guy said they were Jerma. I didn't
take this by the way. Here we go. We got kind of the world here. Those of you that always say,
Jerma, how come you stream so late European? Jerma, it's like, it's two o'clock in the morning EU.
Why do you do this to us? It's because almost 67% of the entire audience is based in the United
States, North America. EU still takes up a significant chunk of 23%. But, you know, I got
almost a 70% group of you guys that are in North America. And I'm in North America. And then after
EU and NA, it really shrinks down a lot, doesn't it? Asia at 2.1%. Oceanic, 4.2%. The next one. But
after EU, Oceanic. Interesting. And Antarctica. Almost 1% of you guys live in Antarctica?
That seems like a lot. Margin of error. I'm the biggest streamer in Antarctica. I guarantee it.
And then 0.3% Africa. Interesting. South America is up there with 2.7%. Very cool. Very cool.
Highest level of education. Here we go. How many fucking doctors we got here? Let's see.
Highest level of education. None. 1.8%. Middle school. 6.5%. High school or GED equivalent.
56%. Okay. That's good. Look at this one. We got college degrees. 10% associates. 16.7% bachelors.
2.2% master's degrees. 5% of you guys have doctorates. That's a huge amount of people
that have doctorates in this channel. Oh, sorry. It's 1.2%. 5.3% of you guys are other,
which means it's even higher than doctorate. You're a PhD or something. So we got 10. 26.
Like 27. 28. 29. Like 35% of you guys have doctorates. Rough estimate of annual income.
Okay. Here we go. $0 to $99 is 30%. $1,000 to $9,909 is 14.5%. 10 to $24,000 is 12.9%.
$25,000 to $49,000 is 7.3%. $50,000 to $100,000 is 3.6%. And then 1.8% of you guys have $100,000
a year in income and then 30% of you don't know. Looking at this list here, you don't have to give
me any fucking money. You understand? It's part of the reason why saying like, only pay me money if
you really are able to and you take care of yourself and your entire life first. You don't
have to pay me anything if you don't want to. Ever. Don't ever. Here we go again with this,
but I got data. I've got data here that you can look at now. 1.8% $100,000 plus a year
is those doctors. But seriously though, you don't have to pay me any fucking money.
You got data now. You thought that was it? Not even close. Here we go.
What are the top five best emotes on the channel as picked by the census?
Thanks catgirlheadpat for five community subs. 11.4% said fireman's their favorite.
And that's very close between the German Pluto and German Venus.
And then the German Defoe is up there over the rat, which is surprising.
I don't know how that's possible. And here we go. Here we go. You want to see how powerful you guys
are? Do you hang out in the pre-stream chat or post-stream chat? Pre-stream chat, for those of
you that don't have any idea, is the time before a stream starts. I don't know why I have to explain
that. Why am I explaining that? You should get that. Everybody gets that. Almost 25% of you guys
hang out in the pre-stream chat, which is where a ton of decisions are made. I would say 40% of all
stream decisions are made in the pre-stream chat. That's pretty accurate for those of you pre-stream
chatters. I think that's pretty accurate. Don't tell them what? Wait, what happened? Don't tell
them. Don't advertise pre-stream. Oh, all right. Yeah. I thought you were talking about me. Both,
which is interesting. So 11% plus 24 is like 30 to 40% of you guys that are making very,
very strong decisions for the rest of us. Neither though. So 60% of you guys just kind of,
yeah, that's fine too. That's good. Who else do you also watch? Yep. It's like this is funny
because this is like, I can tell you this is the my list. Vinny at 58.2%, Joel at 51%,
Stir at 39%, Kraikin, Italics, James, which is UberHacks on Uber, Tomato and Kiwo. I could see
that. I would tell you like all these channels here are absolutely worth watching. More than
half of you guys are Vinesauce crew, which I mean, these guys have done so much for this channel over
the last couple of years. That's not surprising at all. Yeah. Cheers to Vinny and Joel, obviously,
for an incredible amount of support and attention I've gotten from like the Vinesauce community
over the last few years, I'd say. Yeah. That's not surprising at all. I just like that to your
head. Hey, yeah. Lean in. Hey, cheers to that. Oh, sorry. You'll be fine. All right. So what
about these? The top five worst emotes. Data may be fucked because I forgot to include German mustard.
The TV is the worst, but you can't delete it. Something always has to be the worst. There always
has to be like a lich king, right? If I get rid of German TV, something else will take its place.
It just has to be there. Bald coin, 10%, but I don't know. Nowadays, I'm not so sure about that.
We already went over this, but like, I mean, look at it. Look at it now. I didn't delete that emote.
I left it there and I was ridiculed for having the bald coin emote all the way through 2017,
2018, 2019, and here we are. Then just take a look at the price now. I'm not a bald coin.
That fucking is worthless. But the real one. German slug is a bad emote. What's wrong with
German egg? Can you reverse this? German dab goes up to the top, but I can't, you know what?
I can delete that now because it's not the worst one. Oh, this is actually a great data.
German Merck received the least amount of votes for best emote at 0.2% or only three people.
Only three people. I never see that emote, I'll be honest. In fact, it's probably the same three
people that are using that emote on a regular basis. German pain, on the other hand, received
the least amount of votes for worst emote. So 12 people, that's it. German pain is apparently very
high up there, very highly regarded. What's your subscription? Here we go. I am not subscribed.
More than half of you are not subscribed. That's good. Just watch. 15% of you are tier 1,
2% are tier 2, and then 0.8% are tier 3, 20% of you are Twitch Prime, which that's a huge number,
and then 10% of you are a gif sub. Here we go. This is important. This is important. Oh,
wait a minute. Wait a minute. Oh, I'm going to pat my back on this one. Hold on, we'll get to it.
How much have you ever donated to German? $0.75 of you. What's this one? 1 cent to $2.50? 9% of you
have. $2.50 to $10? 7%. Over 10 but under 25? 2.8%. And then this is interesting here. So less than
50 but over 25 is 1.1%, but over 50 but under 100 is 2.4%. And then over 100 is more than under 50.
That's pretty interesting. But yeah, again, 75% of you don't give... I don't. Just don't do it.
Just hang out, enjoy the stream, chill in the community. That's 100% cool by me.
So what's the best content? Here we go. What is the best content on this stream?
Old games, 47%. New games, 32%. Talking to chat, 48%. Playing with others, 27%. Playing the game.
Playing the game is at 13%. So those of you that are in this chat right now,
that yell at me to play the video game. Dude, what are you doing? Like, play the game, man.
That's only 13% of you want me to do that. It's like 80 fucking 7% of you do not want me to play
the game. German having fun is 60, whatever German like, 70, and anything is 61. They have buzz kills.
The math doesn't add up here. Oh wait, it doesn't. What's that based on?
Stop. You can select multiple answers. Oh, okay. Multiple choice. Okay, cool. I see.
Oh, German heart. Well, thank you guys. Yeah, playing the game, 13% of you.
Just remember that the next time. Remember that the next time we're talking about like,
eating dog food for five minutes. And there's that. And there is one more to look at. Really,
really cool. Last one. Very elaborate, I told you. This first one is no longer relevant.
You watched the end of the stream bits portion. A lot of you actually did. A lot of you did.
But a lot of you didn't. Do you take showers? All right, cat or dog? Let's see what we have here.
Both? Neither. 5.2% of you said neither. Hmm. Looks like we have a little bit more cat people
here than dog people. I would consider myself to be a dog person. Although, I do enjoy cats.
I just think I enjoy dogs a little more. I would probably say I was a dog person.
Do you prefer Twitch chat or Discord? I thought this was going to be a lot
larger of a gap here. But tons of you guys prefer Discord. That's why it's there.
Do you like Bugleberry? No, that's not... That majority rules here. He ain't going anywhere,
ever. That's a large amount of people that say no, but that's a much bigger amount of people
that said yes. Have you ever canceled plans to watch this stream? Yes, 38% of you guys have
canceled plans. Is that what happens when people say, hey dude, I took work off to watch this
stream and it sucked today? Oh, I get it now. I feel bad. Well, sorry to the 38% of you maybe
that took off work or told your friends you were busy for the Die Dallas encounter stream. Sorry
about that. FTK, oh no. Do you take showers or baths? 84% take showers. Yeah. Does that mean
you never take a bath? Because I do both. Put me in that 11.3%. Where's neither? I don't fit in the
tub. Who takes a bath? Well, I take a bath to relax. I take a shower to clean, a bath to relax.
I think they do different things. Would you beat Jerma in a fight? No and yes. I think a lot of you
just underestimate how explosive I could be. People just underestimate me. No, don't underestimate me.
I'm explosive. No, I can fight quickly, very strongly. Explosively cute.
Would you attend a JermaCon or a Jexpo? A lot of you said yes to this, but I feel like this number
drops a ton when the tickets go on sale. This probably drops to like 4%. So I'm not so sure
about that. Does Jerma make your day better? No or yes? 0.6% said no. Does that mean I'm making
your day worse? That seems like a lot of people. How many people here right now? 13,000. What's
1% of 13,000? 130? So there are 130 people here right now that are making your day worse. Oh,
I'm sorry about that. Do you eat ass? Of course I do, of course I don't. A lot of you guys eat ass.
A lot of ass eaters. That's a majority ass eater. Are you single or in a relationship? Single. Hey,
got a lot of single people here. A lot of people in a relationship too. 25% in a relationship.
25% of people are lying. I don't know. I don't think about that. I'm not so sure about that.
That's cool. There you go. That was Krosky that made all this. Krosky, you're going to have to
work your magic again in like another couple of years. You need a dating app. Like a Jerma
dating app. Do a Cupid stream. No, I do not think so. No, no, no. I'm not having any hand in that.
Oh, and you two can be together and date. Oh, that's so cool. Like fucking six months later
when you have a ton of relationship problems. You guys are going to blame me. You guys are both
going to be thinking internally, why the fuck did I do that? That asshole for content got us on there
and like fuck that guy. That's what happened. I'm not doing that. You meet somebody, you meet
somebody. You need to do a Cupid stream. I think we finally do a fake one. Do like a
have a fake dating show. Too many projects, guys. You don't have to put it on the bottom of the
list. There's too many things that are happening. There you go. That was the 2020 census that we
did in 2021. Pretty interesting stuff. The bachelor Jex. All right, let's go back to what
we were doing here. I need a new OST, please. Something we haven't seen. Sims furniture. The
Sims by theme. That's not bad. Sims by theme. OK, what the fuck was that? All right, that's good.
Let's go. So nostalgic. After this, I'm picking streamers choice. We're going to do zoom out
roller coaster tycoon music. Zoomed way out song. I don't know what it's called. That's what I'm
going to type into search. How much money do I have? Only 375 coins. Not doing that yet. What
about the printers? Leaf printer. OK, I need to I need more coins. I need more coins. All right,
I can start this now. Let's do some up wage. Oh, airplane turbine. I could get the other one,
but should I? No, no, we got to do upgrades. Get the other one. Leaf powered leaf blower,
a leaf blower powered with leaves. Full circle. What? I don't get it. I don't understand. What does
that mean? Is it more powerful? Ow. Like I think ow. Ow, you're right. That hurt. There we go.
Undertale. I want to hear that. Undertale. Dog song. That's the one, right? Dad. All right,
let's go. All right. Upgrade, upgrade. Platinum leaves. Drop them. More trees. Drop them. Gold
fertilizer. Dump it. Marketing. Yell it. Auto leaf blower. Buy it. Nuclear fuel. Turn it on.
Max combo. Up, up, up, up, up, up, up, up. That was it. OK, now what? Let's go to.
Oh, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah. Roller coaster tycoon zoom out song. There it is. Oh,
fuck yeah. This is the best one. Here it comes. This is the best part. This is the best part right
here. Fuck, I got it wrong. Not yet. I mean, wait. More, more, more, more. Trees, trees, trees. More
trees. More fuel. And here. Now we have another one. Bismuth. Bismuth leaves are now dropping.
This was my printer. Oh, it's the converter. 100 platinum to one Bismuth. Start it. New leaf drop.
Yep. It's more. Another one. I have a lot of gold. All right, I'm going to dump the gold.
What do we got? A ton of trees. Fertilizer. More. More. Play Rimworld. I will after this.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no. The OST. No, I won't. I'm not going to play the Rimworld OST. I'm not
because I want to play Rimworld. I don't want to hear the OST before I play the game.
Kill that snowman. I need more combos. Somebody's freaking out right now going Max combos. You
stupid streamer. Like Katamari. I do need to play another Katamari. Kill, kill, kill, kill.
How about the Sonic? Yeah, how about the Sonic? Rolling. Yeah, that's a good one. I feel like I
play this every time we do songs. I play this every time there's a song request portion of the
stream. Sing it. No, I can't sing it because it's going to get added to a list somewhere.
I know. I have 2,000 of the rainbow ones. Sing it. Fine. No.
The amount of people that sing this song and hum this song and have played this song.
This is such an iconic song. Is the guy that made this song like get anything for this?
Is he the official Sonic the Hedgehog music producer? Is this guy's band still doing the
Sonic the Hedgehog music stuff for all the other things? Yes. All right, that's good.
I wonder if there's any pressure there. Look at it like follow me, set me free. Everybody loves
this song. I think he sits there and he's like, fuck, I need another escape from the goddamn city.
I think this guy makes this fucking gold. It doesn't matter. This song sucks. I don't even
like Sonic the Hedgehog and I disagree with you. I've not enjoyed a Sonic the Hedgehog piece of
media since probably 15 years ago. It's honest. I love the character. I think the character is
awesome. I think the songs are great. I mean, it's what? It's iconic classic video game history.
This is just auto playing. I'm just going to let it do what it wants to do. All right,
let's spend some money. Let's max this all up. I said I didn't want to do it. This is why I said
I didn't want to fucking do this. This doesn't count because I told you it was going to fucking
happen. It doesn't count. I try. Of course you can't do that. It's an incredibly difficult
thing to do. It takes like years of classical singing training. It's already put out. Fucking
learn. You need to fucking learn. You're a dumb time to learn. You need to fucking learn.
That was mean. I'm not talking about you. I'm talking about whoever's
currently listening to the song. But the artist decided that was what he was going to do. I'm
not talking about you guys in particular. Oh boy. Large paint roller. What? Does it hurt?
Oh, he doesn't. He does not. Um, what does that? It's, um, from Tony Hawk. Tony Hawk's
Pro Skater. The yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah. So fuck all your rules and fuck all your. Offspring.
There it is. Is this the one? Can't play the rest of it, but I just wanted to make sure.
Does that happen in the Sonic song? It definitely does. Somewhere at the end.
And it goes yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah. Wait, did it just happen? It just happened? Wait,
did that just happen? Holy shit. Okay. I guess I found it. I guess I found it. Okay.
Oh, all right.
All right, it's time to, what do I got coins? Nope. I want 5k. I don't want this 1.2k
bull crap. 1.2k Andy. He's got a huge raid just came in. I love that monster raid. This is monster
raid number two for the day. It's from Five Up. What's up? Five Up. Welcome everybody. Thanks for
the raid. Welcome to the stream. We're playing Leafblower Simulator. Somebody just, I killed
somebody. Raid song? All right, here it comes. This is the raid song. I made this. You think
it's pretty good? I think it's kind of good. But no, thanks Five Up. That's a, that's just a fucking
shitload of people. Hey, what's going on everybody? Hope you had fun. Welcome, welcome, welcome.
Thank you so much. This is Leafblower, Attack of the Leaves. The whole thing is you clear.
It's an idle game and it's so good. It's so fun. It's engaging and it makes you,
it gets your blood going. My blood is on fire right now. I have to play Splatoon. Oh yeah, sure.
Splatoon. What's the one that goes? What's the one? Does it a few times? All of them do it. Oh,
okay. All right. Which one's better? One or two. Splatoon OST. Yeah, this is the
that's like the royalty free version that I just did, but you know, the one that's a song, right?
All right. Spend money. I got 1.4 million. All right. Max up the trees, max up fertilizer,
and then I'm going to start banking money. More combos, more combos. I need way more combos.
More trees. Get them. More fertilizer. Get them. More marketing. Get the leaf blowers. More trees.
More fertilizer. Dump it. You're a squid now. You're a kid. You're a squid. Scroll down.
I will. Change locations. The trees spawn business leaves.
They what? Couldn't I stay at the other one? Go back. That was wrong. Oh.
Mm hmm. Oh my fucking God, dude. What the fuck? Oh, that's another rate. What is happening right
now? This is like the, this is a 10 K rate from Fundy. Oh my God. I got to play leafblower simulator
every day. This is, this is 10,000 people from Fundy. Fundy. Uh, thank you. This is insane.
This is like two or three in a row here. Holy shit. Uh, thanks. Welcome, everybody. Hope you're,
uh, hope you're enjoying your day. We're playing leaf, I got to do the intro again, right? I just
did it, but I'm going to do it again. Hey, welcome or welcome. We're playing leafblower simulator.
Uh, leafblower revolutions. Pretty, it's pretty sick. I highly recommend it. If you don't have
you kind of bored one day, you just want to play a game where you scoop up some, uh, leaves and
welcome. Thanks for the rate. This is huge. 26,000 people, 25,000. Holy shit.
Leaf. There's the thing, right? The day that I'm playing leafblower, uh, extreme simulator,
it's like a stadium full of people just walked in and I'm sitting there just like, I'm playing
solitaire with myself and like 20,000 people just fucking showed up. This is like how you feel
if like you have a party that you're throwing and all you have in the fridge is like milk
and a half eaten bag of Lays potato chips, like the crunchy crumbly part of the bottom.
And it's like, I'm, I don't, I'm not ready for this company. I guess like you can have some milk.
You guys like milk. Do you want some milk? Everyone's got like big foam hands and I'm
passing out like two teaspoons of milk to each one of you. And I just put the TV on. I'm like,
ah, I got Netflix. I put on, uh, have you, have you seen, have you seen the wire? That's a really
good show. They will put that on. And then I walk upstairs, there's 25, fucking thousand people in
my house and I'm just like throwing fucking cold water in my face. All right. I'm going to get
down there and I'm going to, I'm going to pause the wire and I'm going to piss everybody off.
Cause it's a great show. I better have something to say that's better than the wire. I better go
down with like magic tricks and stuff. I gotta, I gotta open up my old like kids magic trick booklet
but on there and do like coin tricks. The music. Oh shit. You're right. But thank you guys.
Seriously. This is a, this is just, that's three monster raids in like an hour. Hey, split down.
Do Presto Magesto again. Yeah, I know. I have to pull up Presto Magesto.
Put on Xenoblade Chronicles. All right. You're like, give me, uh, give me two minutes.
Cosmic Leaves can spawn. I can't do that yet. Shit. I keep forgetting to do the combo. I need to do
combos. I have to do more combos. Another raid? No, it's not. Don't say that. That would be insane.
No, no it isn't. Put on Tropico. Oh, the Xenoblade is, okay, we'll do Xenoblade after this.
Put on Chuck E. Cheese. Chuck E. Cheese has songs? Does he just dance to like generic advertising
music? I feel like Chuck E. Cheese's song, Chuck E. Cheese just dances to like generic rock riff
four. Okay. What do we got? This is the part. This is what I like this part a lot. Wait till that's
5k. Not yet. Is this like a, is this a Bon Jovi moment where like Bon Jovi's doing this with his
mouth? With like a weird like kazoo in his mouth going like wah wah. Oh, that's not Bon Jovi.
Right. That's not the guitar. That's not the guitar making that noise. No, it isn't. What's that?
It's my life. It's my life. I can only play the first five seconds of this. Yeah, that's somebody
going wow wow with like a weird device in their mouth. Yes, it is. I thought I just died. All right,
we're going Xenoblade Chronicles. Xenoblade Chronicles. Which one? The first one or the
second one? What do you guys think? This is a little too sad for me right now. This is a little,
this is kind of sad for me. Who doesn't suck? I don't know. I haven't played it. I need more
combos. Gold apples. How do I not have those yet? Combos. It's 6.5 million. I'm going to,
it's got to be, I'm going to have to prestige here soon. Yeah. What is this? All ALBs. What is it?
Auto leaf blower. Oh, okay. Platinum apples. I don't even, I can't even, I shouldn't unlock them,
right? Unlock Bismuth apples. Yeah, definitely. Hit damage. Oh, they can actually damage enemies.
Okay. That's cool. That's too sad. That's too sad for me. Unpluck. What do I need? I need 500
cosmic leaves to get the new one. Bro, turn this off. All right. Let's get to the middle.
It's too sad for me. Skip, skip again. It's too sad. This is too sad for me. Skip again. Like
halfway. I'm six hours into the OST. Are there any snot sad songs in Xenoblade? I'm looking for
a little bit of pep. Where's the pep? This is good OST, but a little too sad for me. Here we go.
I need coins. All right. How are we doing on the converter here? Oh yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah. 3000.
Come on in. Get 5k. These Bismuth leaves are just racking in money. Racking in prestige coins.
What is it? Racking? Raking in? Racking in money. Yeah, racking in money. Yeah, that makes sense.
Everywhere. How about some original Nier? I'll give it a try. Just not Nier Automata, right? Nier
1 OST. Is this the right one? Is this correct? We wanted Plok. Well, hold on. I need more
Bismuth leaves right now or I'm going to be very upset. Can cosmic leaves even be picked up?
I don't have to know. They don't. I have to go to another location. No, something else.
What are you saying? Almost at 5k and then I'm prestiging. This boss is going to be unwatchable,
will it? Isn't video game music fine? A video game OST should be fine, right? Otherwise,
how would you like play any of these games on stream? Play Shadowlands. Um, I already did.
Dermot, I'm shaking. You need to play Killer Instinct. All right, fine. I just want to hear
Killer. Will you just remind me? I just want to hear that. It goes like this. Hold on. Let me
see if I can get this out of memory. So anytime that you, I would, I could do an ultra combo in
that game and you would catch somebody in an ultra combo. I think it was the, it was the wolf.
I remember I used to play against a friend and I would ultra combo the fuck out of him and this
is always here every time. And then we have a go. Hold on. Let me get it. Hello? Hello?
Did that work? I'd just be sitting there going like.
And I would fuck him up every time and he would, I would leave my house because it was just, I was
he was so bad. He couldn't even do anything. It was a precise button combo with a glacial,
glacier. That was the guy I could do it with. I'm sorry. Killer Instinct ultra combo on what's the,
what's the dog, what's the animal's name? What's the dog? Folgor. No, no, no, not Folgor.
Oh, what's the, what was the name? Saber Wolf. Okay. Killer Instinct ultra combo on Saber Wolf.
Like doing it to Saber Wolf. It needs to be done to Saber Wolf. Let's see. Glacier ultra combo.
Let's see if we can find one that's on Saber Wolf and I'll show you guys how fucking nuts it was.
Okay. Here we go. Now this is the new one. Do it. Finish the combo, dude. It's 150 hits.
Holy shit. That was crazy. What's the next OST? Catherine. Okay. Catherine OST.
Is the complete OST. Okay. This is DMC here. Okay. Catherine, let me ask a question about Catherine.
So I've looked at it before. Oh wow. That looks kind of interesting. But isn't it kind of like
a Qbert game where you just like climb blocks? That's where it lost me a little. I feel like
I probably wouldn't enjoy it that much. It gets disturbing. I'm sure it does, but I don't know
if I want to do the Qbert stuff. It's also a band game on Twitch. It is? Is the music banned on
Twitch too? Should I not play it? No, it's not. What? I'm not going to pop like the Twitch algorithm
off, right? Everybody's playing Catherine. It's a band game. Turn off their stream immediately.
All right. What do we got? All right. I can prestige. Hold on. Not yet though.
Let's get a few more minutes of this. Play Katamari. I will. I'm just trying to get as
much as possible out of this before I prestige. All right. We're at five point. Maybe I can get
it to like six. More. So we're going to unlock like the next two or three areas
and I'm going to dump all my money into, I don't know. What should I buy? We'll find out very soon.
Katamari. Which? All right. What Katamari OST? I've really played the first one already.
Which one? Your choice. What do you want? What do you feel like? We love Katamari. Oh,
I thought you guys were just saying that. 55 gems. All right. We love Katamari OST.
Kind of loud, but all right. Does this one go, no, no, no, no, no, no, no? I hope. I'm just waiting
for the song to hedgehog guide if this sounds like that. No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
You should get them to do that.
Turn it up. All right.
I can't do this. Beatbox with them. No, it'd be embarrassing. It's so much better.
All right. I'm ready to prestige at 6,000.
Turn it up. I just I will. I don't want to be able to hear after the talk.
Nothing I hate more than going to like a bar or a party or a restaurant or something.
And the music is over a level where I cannot talk to you. That's the fastest way to make me
to fucking leave your house or whatever. If I have to lean in and yell into your ear for us to talk
about, like what drink you ordered. All right. Yeah, let's go over here.
Wait, did that happen? What are you saying? I'm talking.
All right. I'm ready for Steve. Go. All right. I have. All right. Turn this down.
I have 6,000 coins. Auto upgrade freeze. Should I do that? Let's go down.
ALBs can collect fruits for you now. Should they also do your tax report? I mean,
might as well get it. Higher chance to spawn multiple fruits. Yeah. Yes. Yes. Yes. Yes. Yes.
Yes. Yes. Yes. Yes. Yes. Yes. Yes. Yes. Yes. Yes. Yes.
Yes. No, that's too much. How do I unlock that? More leaves. Yes. Yes. Yes. Yes. Yes. Yes. Yes.
Yes. Yes. Yes. Yes. Yes. Yes. Yes. Yes. Yes. Yes. Yes. Yes. Yes. More coins. I'm done.
Space. Oh, my good thing. I clicked that and had enough to buy it. Let's go to space.
Gold leaves. Come on. More trees. Come on, Gwen. More fertilizer. Come on, Gwen. More marketing.
Come on, Gwen. Automatic leaf blowers. Come on, Gwen. Scorpions in space. I can't. Next one.
Hmm. Okay. More. More fertilizer. Enough of that. More money. We are in space. It's perfect.
I feel like I am one of the princes right now. I feel like this is going to live in that same
universe right now. Another gold. I do. I have enough for a trees. More trees. More fertilizer.
Do Mechanicus OST in a little bit. Just hold on. What even is that? What console is that for?
It's not for console. It's for PC. These things are heavy. Look at it. More trees. I'm going to
set the converter up now. Old converter. Get that started. And the platinum converter. Get that
started. Yeah. Printer. How much money do I have? I want to get a cosmic leaf printer just because
I'm going to get it because I want money. Stop talking. Nobody cares about this game.
Well, I'm going to beat it. Do you beat it? Do you win? Or is it just never ending? Well,
I'm going to play until I don't feel like it anymore. How's that sound? Be swore. Oh, let me
change my skin. Bird. Ace of spades. Okay. I have a lot of... Let's get... I need... I actually need
to turn that converter off. Turn this off. Buy more trees. Play Sonic CD. All the stuff is at the
bottom. What? What do you mean? I'm buying it. Oh, I can buy business trees. Void leaves. Trees can
drop void leaves? What about bismuth? Yeah. More bismuth. I need a better... Oh, hold on. Okay.
Rocket engine. Pretty powerful. It's hard to blow the cosmic leaves though. These are very heavy.
Too heavy. I don't like that. Katamari, I love you. All right. We'll do one more Katamari song,
and then we're going to move on to mechanical OST. Okay. Not this one. Increase your coins. All
right. Hold on. How many coins do I have? Time travel by 30 minutes. Receive offline rewards for
the next 30 minutes instantly. Do I do that? Is this going to pretend like I've been playing
for 30 minutes? No, don't. That's correct, right? Do the six hour one. I just use it? Holy shit.
Oh my God. What happened? What happened? Holy shit. I have 13,000 coins. Just do that again.
Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait. Void leaves. Holy shit. I have so many now.
I'm about to just go nuts here. It's going to be so much more spawning.
Get more fuel. Get more blowers. More speed. More battery. More power. Power up.
Up. I have to. I'm going to do it. Power up. There we go. I feel a little bit better.
Let's take over the whole screen. I don't have any combos. All right, let's go. 13K.
Oh, I killed the Vulture. I can sing a song for you and me. I can sing a song for you and me.
I get it. There's a technique to get the cosmic ones because they're much heavier.
I love it. This is a great song. What a great song. You guys ever think that when you listen
to a video game soundtrack and there might be an artist on there that you listen to,
you're like, oh, holy shit, this is really good. I've never looked up who this person was.
I don't know what band this is, but I probably would like their music.
But I just don't. I'm just like, oh, I'm going to listen to that one song that I like that I
know that you made great. But I'm not going to listen to any of your other music.
Anybody else do that? Yikes. Yikes. Why yikes? What are you talking about?
I'm going to do it at 50,000. How's that sound? More, more, more, more, more. Oh,
I can go up to 50. All right. At 50,000 coins, I'm going to do it again. That should happen
pretty. Yeah. I'm already at 16.7. I'm like red flasks. More, more, more, more, more, more,
more. Give me more. Everything. I need more of everything. What song was the one before this one?
Um, that was called Everlasting Love. 60 coins. Can I do that again? My time.
Time travel again. 30 minutes have just gone by. How much money do I have?
I'm at 41 fucking K. This is huge. I need higher combos. Combo multipliers. That'll help.
Times 31. Play some 8-bit song covers. I'm going to start all these. Then I can get some void ones.
Holy shit. This game never ends. Okay. Void trees. I'm going to get this to over 50 K.
Shit. I should have held it and still, ah, I should have held that until I had void trees.
I can buy one. That's a much better technique. Bottom to top. We'll wait for a few spawns.
One more and then I'm going to go top, bottom to top. Ready? Oh yeah. Oh yeah. That's the one.
That's the technique right there. Let's do, wait to, oh, my automatic pushers are doing great too.
Oh, you know, I love it. More void trees and more void fertilizer and more void apples.
Tell us a story. One day there was a little boy who went to get a pail of water. He got it. He
filled up his burkey and he loved it. It was clean water. It was crisp and all contaminants were
removed. What do I got? 45. I'll wait till 50. Maybe I should just do it now. Fuck it. Right.
Just do it now. I think I'm just going to do it now. Oh wait. Maybe I should buy another. What?
Oh no. Okay. Use it. 70,000 fucking coins. Oh, a laser.
This is much more powerful than the cosmic ones. Oh, look at this. More coins. Shit to do. All
right. Hold on. Is this all max? Buy max. Buy max. Buy max. Buy, just buy, buy max. Buy max on
everything. Hey, what about four? Buy max on everything. Yeah. This is not gas. Max, max, max,
max, max it all up. Buy an enemy bumper. Okay. More. Max out everything. And then I'm just going
to coast for a little while and then I'll prestige. And I'm going to buy like an area that's like five
times over here. Okay. Here we go. Let's just collect for a little bit. 71,000 coins. Promise
center, second opinion. Yeah. We've been hunting for long enough. All right. Persona four, golden
OST. Sure. What the fuck did I just do? I think I just print screened like five times. Oops.
Persona four, golden OST. DFCA? Oh. Should I be aware of that? Should I be aware of that?
Are we sure? One guy. Okay. Oops. I think a bug just flew in my eye.
Like a bug just tried to desperately get into my eyeball, I think. I freaked out and just
grabbed my face. I don't know. I have no idea what happened. I could feel like a bunch of legs
climbing into my eyes. I just, I just slapped and grabbed him through. I'm not going to look down.
You promised a mechanics. Oh, all right. Do that next. 73. It's not going to go up any higher.
I don't think. Time for Steve's. Let's go. Go 70. I want 75k. I need to, I have to see it. 70.
No, fuck it. I don't care. All right. 73,000 coins. We are looking for a new area. There's
the void. And then there's 990,000 of these potions, whatever that is. Okay. So upgrade,
auto-upgrade trees. Let's get it. Auto-upgrade fertilizer. Get it. Auto-upgrade marketing. Get
it. Auto-upgrade nuclear. Get it. Buy everything. Buy everything. Auto-unlock flasks. Buy them.
Add a bunch of printers. Add multipliers to those printers. Increase that converter count.
Increase the converter output. Prestige. More coins. More leaves. Come on. I ran out of money.
Give me the leaf portal. I want it. All right. We're already at 2000 coins.
Okay. Mechanicus. Mechanicus OST. There you go. 72 hour time travel. The game's running for three
days. Why do I want to buy the pack to do that? Just see what happens. All right. I got the
converters going. Get them started. Let's go. Boot them up. Turners going. Boot them up. All right.
We need more combos. Praise the Lord. Praise the Lord. What is the potions? Green flasks.
Science research? What? How do I make a flask? Is it voids? Oh, red flasks. I have the auto leaf
buying going on, right? Yeah, I do. Yeah. Everything is on auto-buy right now. I just have to collect.
I have to collect and watch this number. It's already at 15,000. Holy shit. Okay.
Maybe should I get to like two 500,000 for that? A million? It's a 900k? What's the next? All right.
It's 500 red potions for the next upgrade. They didn't make a potion though. I feel like it would
be here. Unlock red flasks. Did they just show up? You buy them from the potion seller. Unlock a
green flask. It says converter under it. Converter. Let's go. Reduce. Doubles the resource input output
for all converters. Oh man. All leaves plus 20%. Holy fuck. Okay. 20% per level. Reduce the converter
cost. Increase the output. Increase everything. Make it all huge. 495 million. Oh Jesus. Okay.
Hold on. Reaching leaf end game? Maybe. When you can play meat. You guys keep trying to get me to
say that and I'm not going to say it. You guys keep trying to get me to say meat, the meat and
something. Game. Oh, I don't know what it is, but whatever. Alien turbine. Where did you get this?
That's pretty good. This is a big blue popsicle stick. Geez. It's getting, all right. It's getting
kind of hard to manage. Look at all these achievements. It's a popsicle. It won't say
meat and fuck, but we'll say fuck and learn. No, I said fucking learn. Like as an adjective,
like you need to fucking learn. I already have 50k. I'm going to get this to at least 500,000.
At the very least. I just love clicking stuff. All right. We got, hold on. Green flasks have
been purchased. Where's the converter? Start converting green flasks. Oh gee. Unlock blue
flasks. All leaves plus fucking 50, 100%. More converter output. More. Um, what is this? Buy.
Ace of spades. If you'd like to blow leaves, I tell you you're, I'm your man. Going with the blow.
It's all a game to me. I am the ace of spades. Wait, is that the?
The same to me, right? That's also from Tony Hawk. That's a great game.
Back, back, back, back. Okay. Uh, more converter damage, more output, more leaves. I think
we're about to cross where we just stopped. 75 K a slime rancher. I do have to play slime
rancher. You're right. You don't just fucking just skip 30 minutes. Yep. 225 K blue flasks are open
all leaves, all leaves. All right. Blue. I need the converter. We need to do blue flasks
now that we have blue at magenta flasks. What the fuck? This is just, this is too much. There's
too many like compounding things to touch. I feel like we've listened to the same song for like an
hour. This is dark night music. Not anymore. Okay. Blue flasks, more, less resources, more
leaves. Let's go to magenta. Convert to magenta. Unlock orange flasks.
But we can't. How many are there? I need more blue flasks. I need more output on the converters.
God, 250 K. Should I? Oh, was it half a million? Blowfish. Uh, okay. Cool. A graphics card?
An overclocked graphics card with a large fan. Okay. I need orange flasks. Where was it? The
bottom of the list, by the way. Unlock black flasks. Um, unlock big leaf crunch. Unlock
the big leaf crunch. Okay. I need more. I don't have enough. Reduce the resources and make the
output bigger. The end of everything. The big leaf crunch met 358,000 by the way. Prestige now.
Hold on. Not yet. I need to see what it looks like. Does the converter look like? The converter
has to be better. I have to prestige the converter. Yeah, let's go. I'm out. Like 990 K. I can't even.
What kind of potion is that? I don't have any of those. That's like a yellow and red potion.
All right. What's the next OST? All right. I'm, I'm doing it. I'm pressing the button.
I'm going to press the button really soon here. I'm going to buy max on everything,
run around in a circle for a minute and then we're going for it. All right. Let's do it.
What do you think? 400,000? Oh, pluck. Right. People were looking for pluck.
Here we go. Prestige. All right. Now this is very important. I have 370,000 coins.
Cannot buy a new area. All right. The printers need to be better.
Leaf printer. Let's get this up to like 2K or so. Okay. I need way more of these.
Void leaf printer. Okay. What are these? Now converters. I need better converters.
My money. Printer. One printer added. Printer multiplier. Increase converter count.
Where's reduce? All printers. All printers. Get better. Increase the converter count.
Increase converter output. Oops. All upgrade discount. Oh, that's expensive.
More void leaves. More everything. More money. More leaves. More printer multipliers.
Hell yeah. Oh, hell yeah. Oh, man. Look at that number crawling up already. All right.
Let's get started here. Turn on the converters. One, two, turn them. Start them off. Whoa.
Okay. They're on. Converters are on. How come they're green? Where's my potions? It takes years.
Shouldn't.
What do the apples even do? Reduce those resources, dude.
Reduce the resources. Reduce the resources. Increase the output. More leaves.
Oh, I love it. More leaves. More leaves. I'm turning into Jerry Seinfeld. What the hell am I doing?
More. That's going up even higher now. What was that? 300? Let's try to get to a million.
Put on DuckTales OST? Yeah, that's way better than. Well, that's not way better than Pluck,
but that's a way better idea from me. That's way better from me. We have to skip the first one.
All right, we're good here. They should be in Smash Brothers. This is fucking stupid. He should
be there. Scrooge McDuck should be in Smash Brothers. Think about the songs. The remixes
they would have in that. I don't care if it's been Disney. I don't. It's like a classic Nintendo
game that everybody knows. If you've opened up a fucking console and put a disc in it,
you know the DuckTales game. You don't think they could do it. Look at the moveset. It would
be amazing. You could do like the... You could bounce around and be down B. It could even be
recovery. Whatever. You do the golf club side B. The gems. He has the little diamonds he could
throw out like a standard B. Oh, it's Disney. I don't like Disney. Well, it's a classic Nintendo
game. I don't care already. It's not about liking Disney. Disney would never agree to it.
I don't understand. Think about a bunch of classic Nintendo games that required
Disney to be on board. Think about all the Mickey Mouse games, all the Donald Duck cameos that were
in fucking Nintendo games. It was like a hundred fucking Disney games, like Mickey Mouse games
on regular Nintendo and Super Nintendo. But now all of a sudden they don't want to be put in video
games anymore. I can name you at least like 10 Mickey Mouse, Donald Duck goofy video games
that were on Nintendo and Super Nintendo. And now that is what? You have to be part of Kingdom
Hearts now? Do it right now. Fine. Fine. Let me just think for a minute. Magical Quest starring
Mickey Mouse. Mickey Mousecapade. The Great Circus Mystery starring Mickey and Minnie. Mickey Mania.
Adventures in the Magic Kingdom. And this is just Mickey Mouse, by the way.
Plus we have Mickey's Adventure in Numberland. Mickey's Safari in Letterland. Disney's Magical
Quest 3. That means there's a 2. Legend of Illusion starring Mickey Mouse. Mickey's Ultimate
Challenge. Mickey's Dangerous Chase. Mickey No Tokyo Disneyland. Donald in the Magic Cap.
There's like 50 of these. Donald in the Magic Cap. What is it for? Donald Duck No Maho No Boshi.
Disney Wiki is what this sounds like. Donald Duck in the Magical Hat and the Magic Cap was
released for Nintendo Super Famicom by Epoc in Japan only in 1995. Starting Donald Duck with
guest appearances by Daisy Duck, Pete, Grandma Duck, Butch the Bulldog, and Goofy as the announcer.
Why do they not make video games anymore? What happened to the music? They do. What was the last
Mickey Mouse video game that wasn't Kingdom Hearts? And by the way, I don't count Kingdom Hearts.
That's not a Mickey Mouse game. That's not like you control Mickey Mouse and jump around.
They made Epic Mickey like 12 years ago. Epic Mickey was shit. You can control Mickey in 2.
Epic Mickey came out for the Wii in like 2009 or something. Yeah, you can control. Yes, yes,
yes, sure. Spoiler alert. In Kingdom Hearts 2, if you have it on like easy mode, if you turn the
difficulty down, you like can't lose because something happens and like somebody comes and
like just make sure you don't lose because and they made them all like Jedi's. I don't know.
I don't understand it. Stop talking. It's not even, what is, how is that a spoiler? How do I
know this? I play, what? You don't think I played Kingdom Hearts 1? Holy shit. All right, I gotta
focus. Let's do, how about Magical Quest starring Mickey Mouse OST. By the way, this game is
incredible. All the old Disney games are really, really good. All right, I need some converters
going here. They are going already. Produce those resources. Make it more. I want more stuff. I'm
pissed off. Green leaf converter. I'm gonna say, all right. Play, pray, devils make, never cry.
Mouse is gonna get you. Mickey Mouse is gonna get me for playing the OST for a game that's like
30 years old. Yes. Really? Mickey has no forgiveness in his heart. He's just evil.
I'll just buy one of these. I've been playing this for like four hours. Holy shit.
Upgrade your leaves. Pepe mad. Upgrade your leaves. Pepe mad. All right, let's do it. Four,
five, six, more, seven, D. God damn it. I need more of this shit. Come on. All right, G. Here we go.
H. Orange flasks. Not yet. All right, we're at 200,000. Payday two. No, what else we got?
Remember, don't big leaf crunch. It sucks and made me want to cry. Oh, sorry. Turtles in time.
That's a classic. You're flushing a bunch of flasks down the drain, am I?
Rollercoaster Tycoon 3. Play it. It's so good. I have this weird memory where I played Rollercoaster
Tycoon 2 on stream. Did I play Rollercoaster Tycoon 3 on stream? I don't think I have. I made a video
on it. I don't remember. Do the arcade OST. Is it different? This is higher quality. This is fantastic.
What is this? Turtles in time arcade soundtrack. Okay.
Sounds like worse than though. Let's see. Okay. Big Apple 3 AM is a really good indicator if the
SNES version is better. I mean it. SNES one's better. That's much better. I would put that.
I would have to say it's way better. Let's see. Oh yeah. That's way better.
The trumpets are way more prevalent.
Big Apple. I feel like this just fits everywhere. It's so good. It goes everywhere. My toe. My toe.
You're 78. All right. I need to get at least a million. I beat this game probably a hundred
times. We've already talked about it. Where the fuck is the narrow toe OST? Why would I play the
narrow toe OST right now? That's just. That's DMCA. That's just songs. Come on. 300k. Come on.
More green. Converters create more output resource. Increase converted output by one for the current.
This is a good one too. I love this one. Remember your red flashes. Holy shit. What? What? What is
it? I got tons of these. I need more output from. I need more output from here. From red. I need more
red. Stop converting. What do you mean stop converting? Why? Turn off the flash. Red flash
converter. Why would I do that? Finally. What? Don't convert until you upgrade red. All right.
I got you. What's my favorite one? Technodrome. I love the train and I love prehistoric turtle
source. This is a good one. I love this part because it's the guys that charge. They just
run straight at you. Now how are we doing on red? We're doing really good on red. All right. More.
That's good. Where's the skull and crossbones? No, not that one. There it is. Oh, this is a
classic Jerva making my day worse. This is one of the train, right? What was the alligator's name
in Ninja Turtles? What's his name? Leatherhead, right? Leatherhead, right? I forgot about
Leatherhead. Oh, Neon Knight Riders is awesome too. This whole thing is awesome. This is a really
good game. Just about to cross. Scream it. Yeah. I should just scream it and beat it. You want to
have a nostalgia scream where I beat turtles in time like three times? All right. Turn it on.
Let's get green going. You cowered it out after dying once in the retro scream last week. You
think you can beat it three times? Well, I mean, that's a little different. The retro scream was
there were 620 games on that box. I needed time. I wasn't going to give every second dedicated to
Ninja Turtles. It was like 600 fucking games on that thing. All right. How are we doing on green?
More. I forgot about that. Where no turtle has gone before. And let me tell you something about
the Shredder, okay? Super strong, super powerful, has a cool group. I'm not going to do that again,
no way. All right. 55,000. Almost time. Almost time to just absolutely let this just fly off.
Want more converter count? For Shredder Synth. The boss theme. Let's get that going.
I love doing the Shredder. Let's take my favorite thing. Get into it. I need one million.
All right. Let's turn on the blue. Coming up next. We've got blue. I know you're all
so excited for it. Once this crosses like 50k. Here it is. Turn on the blue.
Blue. Devils never cry. Let's see. What's the versus mode one? That song was good too,
wasn't it? Yeah, here it is. This is a great song. Not this one. It's the one right after this.
This is the one I like. If that's 10. Devil will cry. Got a link. What do we got this time?
What do we got this time? Joe Biden will erase a billion dollars off the debt. If you stream
Bionicle Mask of Light. What does this picture do? Why is it Joe Biden? Joe Biden will erase
a billion off the debt. The nation is watching. Germany, do our country proud. J-Dog from Joe
Biden. Stream Bionicle Mask of Light. It's free on YouTube. Lego will not DMCA you. They allow
the movie to have free online distribution. What? This is a movie? You want to watch this movie?
Okay. All right. Fine. I'm going to look into this. I will stream Bionicle Mask of Light
on a stream coming up soon. Probably in the next week. Is this for real?
Do it right now. Should we get a pull for this? That's a pretty significant amount of money.
This is just a simple yes or no. Is it? Okay. One billion off the debt if Bionicle
Movie stream. Okay. Here we go. I didn't vote. How much do we have for current? We're at four
billion right now currently. 92%. Holy shit. Well, I think we have a deal. This is a landslide.
This is Joe Biden that's going to do this. All right. That's unanimous. That's 90%.
All right. Let's go. Let's do it. Not now. But at some point, one of the next streams that you
see on this channel is going to be Bionicle Mask of Light streamed movie stream. If that's actually
true and I can do that. If I can truly actually stream that movie, I will. I got to look into that.
Hey, thanks a lot, Joe Biden. All right. What are we doing? Oh, I get to look at all my money.
I got to turn on the purple now. What's this? Oh shit. Perfect. Yeah. I'm keeping this on.
It's Mega Man X. All right. This one's ready to go. I have so much blue. I'll go too crazy with that.
I got to get these all 10. All right. Hold on. Let's get it to 10. You have to get Joe Biden
on the stream to watch it with you. I don't think that would. I don't think that's going to happen.
I'm sorry to say that would clear the debt. That would undo. I don't know. That's not going to
happen. It went to the part when like the Bionicles are about to lose. Oh, come on, man.
No, this is this is malarkey. I hate everything about this. I know Joe is fucked up. Hey,
watch that language, please. I'm sorry, Joe. I mean, Mr. Biden, President Biden, Mr. President,
Mr. President Biden, Mr. Biden, please. I'm sorry. I didn't mean to say those swear words.
That's OK. But here's the deal. You say one more of those swear words, we're going to have a big
problem. He says Bill Clinton. I'm trying to enjoy my gosh darn. I just made him say my swear.
I just keep being like the Bionicles. Oh, Joe, Joe, the Bionicles are never going to make it.
I don't think they're going to make it, Joe. Chad, what do you guys think? Will you just shut up,
man? What? Trying to watch the movie here. Yeah, of course they're going to make it.
They're the damn Bionicles. Now hear me. How much do I have? Oh, five hundred and eighty two K,
Joe. Can you believe it? Biden onicle. All right. It's time to turn on the orange ones.
More, more, more, more money, money, money, money, money. Bidenicle. Actually might be kind of funny
just to have like a few Joe Biden clips of him just telling me to stop talking and enjoying
something, being like, oh, this great. Wow. I'm going to watch Bionicle with Joe Biden.
Just have a bunch of soundboard here of him enjoying the movie with me.
I mean, that's kind of a layer there. Iron impersonator. And we have a cam on in the same
room. No, but then the real Joe Biden has to open the door and be like, what are you doing in here?
And then the audience track has to be like, and he looks side to side and they don't stop clapping
and he's waiting. He's smiling. Yeah, it's me, the real Joe Biden. Not a comedy here.
And like two full minutes go by. All the actors on stage are all looking around waiting for it.
Yeah, it's Saturday Night Live. Yep. And then he just simply goes like, this is malarkey.
Everybody's fucking screams, class, everybody smiles back and forth. And then he just leaves.
It is getting him to do two things. And then, no, no, no, no. Then they all crowd together
and they're all trying to wait for each other to cue each other to say like live from New York
at Saturday night. And they all mess it up. So it's like, because Joe Biden is not like an actor or
anything. So he leans in and he's like, it goes something like this every time. No, not like that.
Live from New York, it's Saturday night. Live from New York, it's Saturday night. Live from
New York, it's Saturday night. And this is what happens. All right, everyone's clapping, everyone's
clapping. Live from New York, it's Saturday night. They never get it right. They never get it perfect.
They got to work on that. Get to a million. Upgrade the other flask. Oh shit.
Wait, is this on? Is this shit on? I can't. Oh, it is okay. All right. I need to upgrade these.
All right. Do I turn on? It's time to. Whoa, what's going on here? What's going on here? What's
going on with the red one? What happened here? Turn that off for a second. Five plus minute
political bias joke. Wait, what? Talking about Joe Biden watching Bionicle with me?
Turn it back on. Turn it on. Oh, Big Leaf Crunch is activated. Liberal Straver. We ain't getting
into this. Oh, strange flask. All right, stop. Omega Low. Stop it. Stop it. Stop it. Stop it.
No political talk unless we're making jokes about the way that. Unless we're making Saturday night
live themed jokes. Here's the only political talk we have on this channel. Excuse me. Excuse me.
That and. You just shut up, man. That's like the extent of the political talk on this channel.
It's me just putting my hands up and going. Excuse me. Excuse me. That's it. That's all I've ever
done. Or I've ordered like fake hamburgers as Bernie Sanders. Mitch McConnell. Yeah, but is
that political talk or is that me doing impressions of public figures? I mean that guy's a dick.
Let's be honest. I need 999,000 of these. Oh, he's getting political politics. We care about
Bionicle. Yeah, that's what really matters is the Bionicle mask of the mask, whatever it was.
Stream. All right, I need to upgrade this once because I need 999,000 of these. He's a registered
Bionicle. That sounds odd. That sounds bad to say that. That sounds weird. I don't. OK, but
registered like I got millions of these things.
I'm fucking this up. Hold on. I got it. This is very precise. I cannot mess this up.
Oh, Jesus. OK, I can't. I don't want to mess this up. Stop. Stop. I already screwed it up.
All right, I need nine. Wait, enter the big leaf crunch portal to restart your blowing adventure
with some BLC coins. What? I don't want to crunch. No, I don't want to do that.
Grease can drop exotic leaves. I'm going to start converting these. 292,000 gets you 700 of these.
I need 900,000 of these. Oh, Jesus. I need prestige. Let's go. Wait, a drill fan is the highest
thing I can get a fan. Use crunch. Use crunch. Don't prestige. Use crunch. Use crunch. Crunch it.
A crunch. I'm going to crunch. I'm going to crunch. But again, I've got one crunch coin.
Grease prestige coins reward by 200% per level. Holy shit, that's insane.
Grease the combo multiplier by 200%. Coin upgrade bought. What happened? Wait, actually reset it?
What do you mean? Actually reset? Wait, wait, wait. Hold on a minute. Somebody just said
actually reset Omega L and I remember their name popped up. They said do it. Crunch it. What? New
deal. I don't even know where I start with this. I don't even know where to start with this.
New deal. If you can get a Biden impersonator to watch the whole Bionicle movie with you with
camera on for the whole stream, the entire debt will be wiped. Don't waste this chance.
I'm seeing a lot of no deals though. I'm seeing a lot of no deals.
It has to be the real Joe Biden. Well, that's not going to happen. We can have a fun little talk
here of like, oh, that's funny. That's never going to be a reality. Make it a reality.
No. Okay. For that to be a thing, they would have to be... I think I got to have like 200,000
concurrent viewers. I got to be a 200k Andy for that to even be considered. That's not going to
happen. All right. No, that's not going to happen. He responded. Well, of course I'll watch the
Bionicle movie with German added by... Oh my God. No, we'll keep it the way it is for now.
All right. Did I really fuck this whole thing up? Is it time to... Is it end of the stream
voice right now? Don't leave us. I can't wait to watch Bionicle. Realistically, Jeremy,
who do you think is the highest ranking member of the government that has ever seen one of
your streams or videos? I mean, it's got to be... It's probably going to be something like
some random like selectmen. You know what I mean? It's got to be... It's probably like the
local like treasury secretary or something in like Nevada. I don't know. It's probably
somebody like the local level. It was definitely Dave State. All right. I think I kind of think
I'm going to call it here. Wanted to stop by for like four or five hours. I'm still in the
middle of doing a lot of things. I will have a shitload of announcements for you guys very soon.
There's at least one or two announcements and big things that we're going to talk about this next
week. Delay Danny, delay Darryl, break Andy. I'm going to go back to it. I will see you guys.
The next stream will probably end up being either probably Wednesday, Wednesday or Thursday. Keep
an eye on the ground. But I didn't want to just disappear. I wanted to come back and at least hang
out for a little while. So when I come back though, we got a lot to talk about. A lot to talk about.
Thanks for watching, as always. And I look forward to the Bionicle movie stream
next week. This game was actually pretty fun. I did not think there was going to be this much
in this game. It's a good background game. I recommend it. Is this game free? I think this
game is free. Is it free? It might be. I think it is. Yeah, I think the game is free. Cool.
It's free. So just go grab it if you want to check it out. A leaf blower revolution, leaf blower
revolution. All right. We are going to... What are we going to do? We are going to go. We're going
to raid. Who are we going to raid? Let's see. Who have we not raided in a while?
Let's raid Boxbox. It's been a long time. Boxbox is playing poker right now. I saw the gambling
and I immediately said, okay, let's go. I see poker. I see like blackjack. I see slot machines.
Let's go. Go say hello to Boxbox. Hey, tell them German985 sent you. Let's do the credits first,
though. Of course. Again, thanks for watching. Kind of just a chill stream today. Playing an
idle game. I'll see you guys on probably Wednesday. Keep an eye on the sus. It might change the
Thursday. Thanks again for your community subs. Everybody that's subbing and everyone that's
given money. I know a lot of people have given lots of money. Even today, too. Just huge, huge
money drops. I appreciate it. Thank you. We had massive, massive raids today. Kitboga came in
earlier. We had Five Up came in. Fundy came in. We had like 30,000 people come in over the course
of the four and a half hours here. If you stuck around from those raids, and also from Nice Beaver,
too. If you stuck around, cool. Glad to have you. We'll see you again. If not, thanks for dropping
in. Thanks for parachuting down into the base. And we'll maybe see you soon. Parachute.
Yeah, it's a raid. They're parachuting in. So many subs. Holy shit. I know. That's insane.
It's so many people. Are you thanking people that are not here? Oh, you don't know that. German985
sent me. Oh, you don't know that. Somebody may have stuck around. At least one person.
Let's get the raid queued up for Boxbox. Go say hello. And maybe give me a few tips from this
poker game. Thanks for watching, guys. We'll see you probably Wednesday or Thursday next week.
Lots of announcements. Lots of things to talk about this coming week. I can't wait to tell you.
You're going to be like, holy shit. Good night, guys. See you soon.