Hey, what is going on everybody? Jerma here with a Team Fortress 2 gameplay commentary, and tonight I'm going to be playing as the Sniper with the Heatman's Hitmaker.
What the Hitman's Heatmaker? Why did I mess that up? And the Cozy Camper and the Shahanshah.
So what I want to talk about in this video, I want to talk about this combination right here, the Heatmaker and the Cozy Camper.
It is an incredible setup, and I'll go into why I use it, why I think it's good, and that sort of thing.
First and foremost, I want to talk about the Cozy Camper buff, and what it means to snipers everywhere. It's a very good thing.
So if you missed my video from a week ago, or if you missed the buff in general, the Cozy Camper now regenerates 1 health every second.
Now it may seem like it's doing 2 health a second, but if you really do the counting, it's just giving you 2 health in 2 seconds.
So if you look in the lower left and you're like, wait, why does it say 2? That's the reason why.
Now the question you might be having is, Jerma, why do you like this thing so much now? And here is the number 1 reason.
As a Sniper, you pretty much, well as a Scope Sniper, let me rephrase that, you stay back and you stand still.
You move around maybe a little bit, you go to a different spot, you'll hang out over there, hang out over there.
But for the most part, you are standing kind of still shooting your Sniper rifle.
This allows you to heal for a medium health pack in 60 seconds.
Or 63 to be exact, because a medium health pack does 63 health for a Sniper. That doesn't have the Darwin's Danger Shield.
So let's go back to what I was talking about.
If you are standing still as a Sniper, and you don't want to move, and you're confident that you're not going to get shot at,
you don't have to go looking for a health pack anymore. You don't have to go scouring the map looking for a medium health or a small health pack.
Especially if you're above 50% health, you will heal that back in like 20 to 30 seconds.
That's not that much time if you really think about it.
Also, I didn't even think about this until I put it on and got sprayed by a Pyro.
This is the anti-afterburn.
There's been at least a few cases since the update launched where I've been lit on fire and should have died,
but I had the Cozy Camper on and it negated a lot of the afterburn.
So that alone is reason to put this thing on.
So now I want to talk about the Heatmaker and the Cozy Camper and why they are a match made in heaven.
So as we all know, the Heatmaker uses the new mechanic of focus.
When you shoot somebody with a full focus bar, it's going to start to drain the bar and you can stay scoped in.
Now think of the Camper.
The Camper allows you to not flinch when you are shot and reduces knockback to your character.
Now imagine this.
You get into focus and you are uninterruptible by anything besides maybe a compression blast.
This whole time, you are scoped in and don't have to scope back out.
This allows you to only rely on your aim and nothing else.
You're not going to be knocked back. You're not going to be flinched.
You're not going to have to reload, come back, zoom back in.
It's just a game of how many people in the head you can shoot.
It's ridiculous.
Now you aren't totally invincible. In fact, you're very vulnerable because spies can take you down.
Of course, scouts. I mean, you've already seen a scout kill me from behind already.
So you're not invincible, but it really helps with your aim and really helps with your concentration.
You just need to hope that your other teammates are keeping people away from you.
And if you want my thoughts on the Heatmaker, my general impressions on this weapon and what I think about it,
I think this is the best sniper rifle in the game right now.
I actually never really liked the Makina because of the no-no scope.
I couldn't get over that because I would be in so many situations where I'd want to no-scope somebody I wouldn't be able to.
And the only downside to the Heatmaker is just the minus 20% damage to body shots.
That's a pretty big downside, but at the same time, you've got to remember,
most snipers are going to be aiming for your face, not for your chest.
And it does the same amount of damage as any of the other sniper rifles, except, of course, the Makina fully charged.
So it's, I mean, the body shot thing is not that big of a deal.
If you want to balance this weapon a little bit, or if you would think about a nerf for this weapon,
in my opinion, take away the 25% faster charging.
Because what that does, that makes it better than the Bazaar Bargain.
That does what the Bazaar Bargain is supposed to do.
I think if you get rid of that and you make the damage penalty on body shots a little bit higher, maybe 25% or 30%,
I think then you have a very good sniper rifle that's balanced with all the other ones.
We'll see what Valve does.
They're always changing things. They're always making little tweaks to the items.
We shall see.
But in the meantime, that is going to wrap up the video, guys.
Thank you all so much for watching. I really do appreciate it.
And also, I want to bring this up.
Yesterday, my Facecam Fortress 2 video, I don't think made it all the way through publishing and got to everybody's sub boxes,
because I had at least a few people tell me, I didn't even see this. What the hell?
So if you missed it, it's going to be in the description.
The link will be there to yesterday. It is a Facecam Fortress 2 video.
And I do apologize, guys, because YouTube is always screwing things up with the sub boxes.
And if you've been missing videos, I'm sorry. There's nothing I can do about it.
And I wish there was something I could do.
But whenever it's very evident that a video has not gone all the way through publishing,
I will just put an announcement on the tail end of another video like this,
just letting you guys know in case you happen to miss it.
But again, thanks for watching. That's going to be it.
And I'll see you guys all next time.
So take care, everybody.