How you doing? Hey, welcome back. Welcome back. Good to see you again. Just typing some stuff.
Getting some stuff ready. Hope you're having a good day. I'm having a pretty good day and I'll tell
you why. First of all, I am negative for COVID. I don't know how. I'm better today. But if you
heard me a day or two ago, holly is positive. So I mean, I've been in the house. I've been sick.
I don't have COVID. I have symptoms. It's weird. Negative on a PCR. Whatever. All right, let's go,
I guess. There's no way it's a false negative. Dude, I took if that if it's a false negative,
then holy shit. I've taken probably eight at home tests. All of them are negative.
I took a PCR that had to get sent to a lab. Negative. At this point, I don't know. I have
absolutely no idea. That's just strange, right? Holly's fine. Yeah, she's fine. She's getting
over it. She's over the over the hump. I got COVID and it took three days after I had symptoms to
show up positive. I mean, I've it's it's been three or four days, five days, whatever it is,
right? It's been a while. It's been at least four or five days. And I I feel better today,
and a little bit into yesterday. So when I was streaming that my time at Porsche, that's when
I kind of felt the worst. So I don't know. But anyways, yes, negative for COVID. That's good.
For now, I guess we'll see. Probably gonna take another test at home, maybe another day or two,
just to make sure. But so we've got a lot to talk about today. A major amount of things to talk
about. And some of them you're going to be very happy about. The first thing we're going to go
over today is wait till people get in. Wait till people get in. It's a very big deal. I think a lot
of you guys are going to be really happy to hear this. This is a big deal. Huge deal. Big deal.
Incoming. How many people are here? 100? How many people? Wait, are there 100 people here?
Was there 100 people? Is there 100? Is there at least 100? Okay, this weekend, first of all,
yeah, I would just relax for a second. Sit down. You're gonna have to sit down for this one.
This Friday, because we passed a million followers on Twitch a couple days ago,
I thought, wouldn't it be fun? Maybe I'd never I told you I had this idea. Well, I'm gonna do it.
I'm going for it. This Friday and Saturday back to back for a million followers on Twitch.
Ladies and gentlemen, we're going back to sorcery. That's right. I'm going to play through
sorcery again. The first game that I started with on Twitch, we are rewinding all the way back to
sorcery episode one. For those of you that have no idea what this is. Good. Don't even look it up.
Well, yeah, you should look it up because it's awesome. Yeah, we're going back and redoing it,
man. Recycling content. That's what we're doing. That's the that's the first game I streamed on
Twitch. I think. I think I didn't even think I had 500 viewers on those streams. It's been a long
time. So we're at least going to do part one and part two. And I mean, there's a lot of new viewers
here that have no idea. The sus command that you all know sus in the chat is from that game. It's
not among us. It's from fucking sorcery. It's sense danger. It's not sus. So we're going to do
that with Friday. This Friday, we're going to do it. I'm going to get wicked into it. I'll have a
few beers. I'll do a bunch of shitty voices should be fun. And then probably do that into Saturday
too. Maybe we'll see. No rewinds. We'll we'll come up with a rule set. I think it'd be fun to do
though. And then on Sunday, guess what's happening on Sunday. It has pretty much been confirmed.
A green screen movie night. Episode three. Green screen movie night is this Sunday.
And I'm ready. Now, if there is a hang up, then we can we'll do it another time, right? We'll do
it another day or two later. But I think we're on pace to be able to do the first one at least.
So that's that's exciting. A lot of shit happening this weekend. My grandparents are coming over. Can
we do this later? What do you mean? Can we do what later? I'm on your television right now.
Hit pause and come back. Okay, hit pause right now. Just leave your you know, leave the tab open.
Whatever you minimize the screen, whatever, put your computer to sleep, whatever.
And then come back after and so so pause right now. I'll welcome you back. There you are.
How was that time with the grandparents? See? And you got to have time with your grandparents. And
now you get to watch the rest of the stream. Welcome back. Let's go. Can we switch the stream
to Tuesday? No, it's it's Sunday. So today, we're I'm very excited for today. I've been waiting for
this game to come back as one of the best Bugs Bunny players in the fucking world. Okay. And guess
what? I can say that. Do you know why I can say that? There are 8 billion people in the world.
Probably only like maybe a few million have even seen this game or played it at all multiverses.
Of those people, let's say maybe like 10 to 20,000 of them play Bugs Bunny. And let's say that maybe
5,000 of them have played more than 20 games as Bugs Bunny. That's small company right there.
That's 5,000 people in the world. I'm one of 5,000 people on earth potentially,
which is insane, right? I can say that. This dude's on meth. Oh, egotistical math. I can't read it,
guys. I'm sorry. But I'm I'm very excited for multiverses. This stream is going to be sponsored
eventually here. There's some things that I told people I was going to do and we have to wait a
little bit. So yeah, I'm so happy. I I love this game. I think it's fucking awesome. And it's going
to be a sponsored stream. You kidding me? Like, are you kidding me? And this is going to be drops.
So just wait, we'll go over that later. But I have some important things to do first.
I believe the drops will get you access to the game. You have to watch for a certain amount of
time with drops enabled. We'll get there eventually. Drops, drops, drops, drops, drops, drops, drops,
drops, drops, drops, drops, drops, drops, drops, drops. That's what I want to see in the chat when
I play. Oh, stop. Come on. For those of you that don't like bugs, I'm about to ruin your life
because I have to do a bug tier list. There's some, I don't know, some weirdo in the chat said,
hey, dude, you should do a bug tier list while you hang out and wait. And I'm like, well, hey,
okay, fine. So if you don't like bugs, if you don't like the sight of bugs, they're going to
be on the screen. So I want to make sure people know that before I switch over right now. Bugs,
bugs, bugs, bugs, bugs, bugs, bugs, bugs, bugs, bugs, bugs. Spider is S rank. Nope. I think I'm
going to surprise a lot of people with what my S rank bugs are. So we have to let's go over what
this means, right? Come on, let me, let's go over here. Okay. So there's bugs on the screen right
now. I just want to make you be aware of that. So here's how this is going to work. Yeah. Somebody,
somebody made this list and put it in chat. It's a comedy list. All right. We're going to,
there's a comedy tier. I, it's, I'm not going to put, okay, it's a comedy tier.
So here's what's going to happen. This is based on how much I like this insect,
not about how effective they are in helping the environment, ecosystems, nothing like that.
This is just how I feel about this bug. Okay. So this is how I personally feel. So let me,
let's, let's break down what this means. So if I saw one of these bugs crawl across the ground,
this is the reaction like, oh, or like, oh, look. Okay. Are you ready? I don't even know. I,
I think this is a fish. Whoever made this list. This is a comedy. It's a fish. This is not a bug.
It's a fish. Let's look. Okay. Let's do this. Let's get this out of the way. This is comedy.
This is Bugs Bunny. This is not a bug. This is Bumblebee who is not a bug. It's Bumblebee,
the character from Transformers. Cool. Hollow Knight is also, what kind of bug is Hollow Knight?
A beetle? I'll, I'll put these in the right order. And by the way, why the fuck is Plok not playing?
Okay. B-movie. No, you're, it's a comedy thing. That's a little loud. Let me turn it down.
I'll fit, this is a Mega Man character. So I'm not going to, who cares? This is a crab. Is this
comedy? This is comedy. This is a lobster. I honestly thought this was also a lobster,
but that just shows you how closely related these things are to fucking bugs. You know what I mean?
Look at that. This is just like Chad and Virgin, version of this animal. They're the same exact
animal. They're the same exact animal. This one just had the Ninja Turtle Ooze put on it.
I'm sorry. And this one has like a stinger, whatever. This is two lobsters. These aren't
even bugs, dude. All right. This is the first real bug. You, okay. This is a lobster and a
cooked lobster. What are you doing? Who gave this to me? All right. Scorpion. Scorpions. Okay. If I
saw a scorpion crawling across the ground. No, that's, they, they fucked up. They're scary.
I'm not into it. They're terrifying. And they, I mean, are they cool? Not really. Sure. I guess
they're, I don't hate scorpions. I'm not afraid of them, but I would put it in C.
I just, who cares? Should I do my S one? Cause people are going to, people are going to hate
me for this. Are you ready for my S tier bug? I don't know if you guys are ready for this
cause I know exactly which one it is. And people are going to freak out. I don't hate these. I
think these are cute. I think these are fun. They have like little faces. I don't actually
hate these. And I know people are going to be like, what the fuck is wrong with you?
I in fact think earwigs are really, really interesting animal. I think they're really
cute. I think they're really interesting. I, people hate earwigs. Why? They don't hurt,
they don't bite anybody. They don't do anything. They just kind of walk around and they're,
they're cute. This is a cockroach. No, it's not. An earwig is not a cockroach. And they have like
a cool, like cut butt. I don't think it's all the way at S tier, but I think it's up there.
Oh, we can't see S tier. Well, now you can. Oh, this is comedy. Ants are high too. Is it,
okay. That's, that's red ants though. Are there regular ants instead of red ants?
Just ant. Cause that's a fire ant technically, right? Which I wouldn't put fire ant up at A.
They, they're, they're scary. Can it just be like ant in general? Fucking beetles. Can I just say
this is just, just an ant? Let's just, cause if it's a fire ant, I don't want it up there.
But regular ants are really cute. Also, when I was younger, I used to love this movie called
Honey I Shrunk the Kids. Rick Moranis was in it. And there was a scene where Auntie protects them
from the scary scorpion. And Auntie was awesome. Auntie helps the kids and fuck this thing. You
know what I mean? I like ants. So that's how I feel. What is this? What is that thing? I don't
know. Whatever it is, it's dumb. It's an aphid. Oh, these things are all of a plant and they're
annoying. Yeah. Get rid of these. I hate these things. These things just appear magically on
all of your crops. They're the worst. This is a butterfly. Butterflies are, I mean, it's easy to
put butterfly up at S. And I'm going to. And it's, yeah, I would, it's cooler than an earwig.
Bumblebee. No, this is a honeybee or whatever. Just bee in general. Bee is S tier. I'm going
to shrink this a little bit so you can see more of it. There we go. That's better. Okay. What is
this? It's just like a kind of a cool beetle. I don't know what that is. Bees are based. Yeah,
bees are based. It's definitely S. What's that called? A bee drill? That's a stink bug? That's
American beetle. Butterfly S. This is a, this is a pre-evolution butterfly. I actually, I don't know
what, something about the way they move is weird. I'm going to put it down at B. F for a centipede.
No thanks. That's cool. Whatever it is. This is a crane fly. I would put this at F, but I'm going to
put this up here because everybody always points at these and goes, no, they're good. They don't
hurt. They don't bite you. What do you mean F? What do you mean moth at A? What are you talking
about? This is a moth. So what? Moths suck. A moth is a butterfly from like different parents.
What's with this, this anti-moth propaganda that I've been seeing? Why do you like butterflies,
but not moths? Explain that to me. Because moths like will, will, I don't, please explain to me.
They're just a fuzzy butterfly. Now some moths are kind of weird and gross. I agree with you,
but not all of them are. It's a, it's a, it's just a fuzzy butterfly. You like these because
they have prettier colors. Oh, this one's blue. Therefore I like it. Huh. I, I, okay. I, I think
butterflies are more like, oh, they, they drink and moths are, aren't they like nocturnal? They're
like the cool like nighttime version of butterflies. They're cool. That's cool. I don't know why
everybody hated moths up for, for no reason. I think it's just because that people think of moths
and they think of the weird like paper mache white ones, right? And everyone's like, oh, gross.
The ones that are like, they look like, like, like paper mache and everybody, then everybody hates
all the other ones. It's weird. Yeah. I, I, moths are fine. I, moths are fine. They can be, they can
be cute. Moths ate my pants. Well, keep your closet door closed. Keep your, you know, what are you
talking about? Inspect your clothing once in a while. If a moth is able to eat your entire
wardrobe, you probably should have paid attention to what was going on in your closet. Would you
just open your closet one day and there's like 12 moths in there just eating the, your whole,
all your fucking dress shirts? Like what are you talking about? Keep an eye on your shit.
Is this a locust? Because these are F. Is this a grasshopper or a locust? What was the last time
you opened up your closet? That's a cricket? Oh, this is a good, this is one of the good ones.
Here it is. Grasshoppers are green. Oh, it's a cricket. Crickets are really fucking annoying.
There was a cricket outside last night. I swear to God, I always wanted to record it, like,
just get audio recorded because this thing was so loud and it was going super speed. It wasn't
This guy was looking for somebody. It was like, just like, what is it? It was hurt. It was like
static. I couldn't stand it. It was just like the cricket sound and that went on for hours and
hours and hours. They had to like turn a fan on to block it out. It was horrible. They're cute.
They're fine. I don't have a problem with crickets. It was really down bad cricket.
I just imagine him sitting on his back with his legs in the air, just like, come on,
there's got to be somebody out there. His legs catch fire.
Dragonflies, Esther, don't even need to spend time on it. Don't even need to spend time on it.
Dragonflies, Esther, please rate non-insects. Look, I know there's a lot of, a lot of,
turn this down. It's kind of loud for me. I know dragonflies are really awesome because they're
kind of like hummingbirds where you almost feel blessed when a dragonfly comes near you.
You put your hand, you're like, oh my God, because they're one of the only animals on earth that
will freeze in front of you and stop time. What do you mean false? Yeah, a hummingbird sometimes,
especially out here, it'll be sitting outside just hanging out. You'll hear
and the world stops. All time stops. And it's just this thing frozen, floating in front of you.
Just it's like, holy shit. And then they're gone. And it's just like, whoa, like, I feel like magical
dust just got kind of sprinkled on me. Dragonflies do that. A dragonfly will come zooming by. Zoom,
zoom, zoom, zoom. I love it. It's so cool. That's why they're up at S. And they're, by the way,
they're cooler than butterflies. Put moth and S tier, please. I, I, we'll see, maybe. Dung beetle,
uh, I want to put this at S tier because they're funny and they do like that. They move it. Yeah,
come on. They're so fun. I could, okay. If there was a, a YouTube channel or like a
Twitch channel that just streamed dung beetles pushing around shit all day,
it would just be in the background. I would just have it up all day. It'd be up all day.
No, that doesn't go in comedy tier. They're not a comedy insect. This is just somebody put these in
here to be funny. There's another moth. Put it up here. There's another fuzzy one. What is that?
Whatever this is, this is cool looking. I like it. I don't know what it is. Those are pill bugs.
That's a firefly. Yep. What a remarkable creature. This thing can produce light out
of its anus. No, nobody else can do that. No other monster on earth can do that.
No creatures on earth can do that. It just generates light. How? That makes no sense.
Like an angler fish. Yeah. There are a couple of creatures on this strange wild earth that we have
that they can just make light from nothing. How do you make light without electricity or without
some type of source? It's so strange to me. How does it work? It's magic. It's a chemical reaction.
That's what I mean. It's so weird. So chemicals mixed together can make light. What? It's
bioluminescence. Some fucking scientist made that up. What you should have said is it's a glow stick.
I know. I'm just kidding. I just made a lot of people very upset and I was fucking kidding.
Just relax. So it's like a glow stick. Yeah, you go. I'm fucking kidding. Relax, everybody.
Slow down. Does he actually? But stop. Oh my God. Oh, we're moving on. This is like a peapod. It gets
F. This is a kangaroo bug. F. Fly. F. I. Okay. Let me tell you a quick little story about flies.
I love most creatures on earth. I do. But I don't know what it is. If I saw any of these,
I wouldn't want to smash it with a shoe as hard as I can. Right? Sometimes, yeah, it's like,
okay, get it, get it, get it. Something about a housefly makes me just want to just smash.
Just smash it. I hate them. When I see and hear those motherfuckers, I swear to God,
it just triggers something in me where I'm just like, get out of my house. Get away from me. Don't
come near me. I hate them. Ugh. And they piss you off because they're so hard to get rid of
because they fly see the world and a lot of insects see the world. In my opinion,
we've talked about this a little bit briefly. Insects, you know, when you go to slam something,
you end up being like the attack on Titan, like colossal Titan, and it's like,
you're moving in slow motion. All these bugs that have their heart rates at like 6,000 beats per
minute, whatever the hell it is, they are just like perceiving the world at like 0.2 time speed.
So that's why they can dodge you all the time. The reason why bugs only live like fucking 12
days is because their 12 days is like 50 years to us. Just look at how an insect reacts. Just
look at an insect under a microscope, whatever the hell they do, or with like a times like 50
million zoom camera. Their eyes and their hands, like they, it's fucking crazy. There's no way they
don't perceive the world like 400 times slower than we do. Birds do this too. Birds being able
to go from here to here by the time that you blink your eyes is, that's like mechanical. Birds
are almost mechanical. Bugs are almost mechanical. It's wild, but I want to crush them every time I
see these guys because they dodge everything and they, they don't care. Most of these other bugs
will just leave you alone. Like an earwig, for instance, based. An earwig is just going to kind
of like, I'm an earwig and just kind of walk around and who cares? These don't, won't leave
you alone. They land on your head. They land on your food. They get, they're horrible. They,
they won't leave you the fuck alone. Most of these others just kind of live their life. Dung beetle
doesn't give a shit if you're taking like, like, nevermind. I was gonna say taking a shit next to
them, but they would probably really care about that. This guy does. This guy would freak out
and would, would be all over you. None of these care if you, of your existence. Earwigs, ants,
they just kind of do their own thing. They, these are in your business all the time.
They're the worst insect besides like a tick and a mosquito, which if they're on here, they're
getting put an F. Here they are. F. What purpose does a mosquito serve besides to just be annoying
to every single other species on earth? I don't know what this is, but it looks cool. Yeah, I,
okay, am I weird for saying this? Little fruit flies, I hate them and I can't stand being near
them. But if this thing is like three or four inches long and walks across my floor,
I'm not going to freak out. I'm going to go, whoa, that's awesome. That's so cool. And I'm going to
put an old piece of mail down so they can get on it. And I'm going to slowly help them get back
outside. And it's going to be a story. It's going to be this weird storyline that I make up. Oh,
I'm like, I helped these things. You know what I mean? What do you mean? Yeah, you guys don't do
that. Based bug saver. I don't know what this is, but it's cooler than a than a scorpion. What is
that? This looks like this guy's wearing a Halloween costume. This looks like something you would find
in the aisle at Target. Like it shoots discs out of it or something. What is this? What is that?
Is it a cicada cicada cicada? Wait, are these the things that make the like emergency broadcast
sound? Yeah. F. What is that? I don't know what that is. But it looks it looks kind of weird.
I don't know. This thing is cool. This thing's got a cool giraffe neck. It's going to be
be like a scarab. I actually don't really like grasshoppers. They freak me out. They can move
too quickly. I mean, they're too erratic. Grasshoppers and locusts are in the same category for me
because, okay, you know, you know, those toys that you press them in and you put them on the ground.
They're a little circle. They're like a little like a dollop. They're like this big and you it's
made of like silicone or plastic or whatever. And you push the middle and you leave it on the ground
and then after a little bit it pop and it just kind of just goes in a random direction. That's
what those things do. Yeah, you like flip them upside down. You press them in flip them upside
down and put them flat and they a grasshopper will just be sitting there and all of a sudden
will just pop in a direction and it's just blah. I don't know where they're going. That's why I
don't like them. This thing's kind of gross. I don't know what it is. This is a big beetle. Cool.
I'll fix this. Don't worry. This is a hermit crab. It's comedy list. Is this a honeybee?
Because if it's a honeybee, it's probably the best.
Even just the, you know, it's so kind of annoying about doing this list and we kind of get to see
our own bullshit. The difference between this and this is really nothing at all. The difference
between this and this is just the way that it looks, right? It's really not that different.
It's it's a bug and it looks pretty similar. But man, I know that these things are kind of vicious
and they're horrible or whatever, right? But I, my reaction to this is, oh, look at, he's got a
cute little face. My reaction to this is get it the fuck away from me and remove it from every
city on earth, right? It's kind of, it's crazy, right? This one's just like cute and does nice
things for the environment. That's why we like it. And this one's, I think this thing's just to kill
stuff. Yeah, there's a reason why we hate these. This is like a fly that somebody's stepped on
already. What, this is just a version of this that got like stepped on. What is that? It's a
horse fly. Get out of here. What is this little thing? Look at this guy. Look how cute that is.
What is that thing? It's A. This is not a bug. This is not a bug. It's a shrimp. Ladybug up here,
at least at A. I'll figure it out. This is just a squeeze of black paint. This is, this is acrylic
paint. This is not, what is this? This is not even an animal. It's a leech F. This is some kind of
weird tick or something F. This is cool looking. Oh yeah, the mantis. Explain this to me though.
This is another thing that I don't understand. This insect is a murderer, is a cannibal, kills
everything, is incredibly dangerous. But we all go, yay, yes, yay. This is a killer. It's incredibly
dangerous. They're mean and we all go, ew, no, boo. Why? If you put your finger near this thing,
it's going to grab you with its spike hands and it's going to try to eat your hand and it hates you.
They do similar kind of things. The mantises don't hurt me. They need to make a Pixar movie
about this one and then maybe people won't hate it anymore. What would that even be? Aren't these
called murder hornets? Disney Pixar Presents Murder Hornet. And it's just him like just sticking like
ass first through somebody's head. Well, how would you even make that movie? Nevermind. F, gross,
gross. Yep, F all the way at the bottom. Okay, this is one of the, this is the type of moth
that everybody says they hate, right? Which I agree, they're kind of like, yeah, I'd put them
in the same category as this. I put them higher than, no. We'll think about it, right?
My reaction to seeing a moth like this is, oh, oh crap. Oh, moth got in, right? You don't care.
My reaction to seeing this is, what do we do about that? Right? Like you kind of don't care
if this is in your house. I've seen at some point like three of these just kind of floating around
and I'm just like, oh, whatever. I don't care. So it's definitely probably higher than, I just
genuinely don't. I'm just indifferent to them. What a filthy house. Filthy. Because a couple of
moths were in the house one time. Guys, I remember I stayed over a relative's house one time. It was
a long time ago and they had this place up kind of in like the woods and I'm not kidding. It was,
they were probably, if you just were lying in bed and looking up the ceiling and just guessing if
whether or not the like the dozens of like kind of specks that were on the ceiling and the dozens
of little things that were on the walls, if they were bugs or just marks and it turned out all of
them were bugs. I remember seeing just like just shadows just floating. You know, you can see the
shadow sometimes. You just see it kind of pass by the light. Just, so when you're in a situation
like that, I put, you put your head under the covers and you try to get a full night's sleep
by being completely protected by the, by the covers. But you got to be, you have to give yourself
like kind of like a hole for your mouth to like, but then you start to have the panic attack where
you go, wait, this is the only entryway to me and it's in my mouth and they're all going to fly in
my mouth and I'm going to eat them. I'm going to be like, I'm going to, I'm going to wake up tomorrow
morning and there's going to be like seven like dead bugs in my mouth. I still do this every time
before I go to sleep. I just check kind of every corner. I'm just like, okay. I like shake the
blankets a couple of times. All right. Where are you? Anything here? Turn the lights off.
Turn the lights on. Oh, no. Okay. You check. Look at this little guy. What is that thing? What's this
like pistachio bug? Oh, this is cool. That's a stag beetle. That's a stag beetle. What was this
one again? S tier? Well, hold on. I, this is, this is, this list is not correct, but let me get
everything up there first. Um, I don't really know what this thing is, but it kind of looks weird.
Oh, look at this guy. This one has a chrome finish. It's cool. This is a shrimp. Oh,
fuck these things. These are the things that are underneath a box in your garage. Get rid of these
slug. Is a slug a bug? I thought slugs are not a bug. Are they? Are they a bug? I don't think of
insect when I think of a slug. They're cool though. Slugs are cool because they kind of look up and
they, they, their antennas are like, anytime you, if you go near, they kind of do this. They go like,
they look around. They're cool. They're mollusks. Yeah, they're not really a bug, are they? They're
cool though. Snail. A snail is, a snail is just like an armored slug. Do these go in comedy?
It's a crab. This is just literally me in a Spider-Man costume. This is just, this is the
Spider-Man symbol. It's not even, this is not even a physical object. Oh, dude, bite beetle,
whatever this is called. I don't know. I don't, I don't like that one. This is, this is in every
Nintendo game, first party. I don't know whatever it is. It's, it's like C. All right, the list is
getting a little big here. Just another butterfly that can go back, that can stay at S. This is a
worm. List is getting big. We gotta move this a little more. List is getting bigger. This soundtrack
really is good, isn't it? Okay, so now this is a worm. Oh, but worms aren't bugs. You can't
hear the soundtrack. You can. Worms aren't bugs either. What music? You can hear it. Quiet. Um,
this is a, the way, this is a parasite. What do you mean this is a parasite? What do you mean by
that? This is just a tapeworm. Oh, hey, this is a soapy jit. Thank you. And they are cool. You know
why? Because they eat the scorpions. These things eat the scorpions. It's a termite. Never mind.
Oh, I wonder where I'm going to put Tick. What kind of sick mother fucker would put this here?
You know what I'm saying? Oh, yeah, man. Tick, tick, tick, tick, tick, tick, tick, tick, tick, tick,
tick. Why would you put this here? Like, put the air guitar down, dude. Ticks suck. Why would this
ever be higher than F? What? Why? You're making shit up. If you, if this, if you put this higher
than C, you're making it up. You're making it up to seem like harsh. You know what I'm saying?
No one is ever going to put this in B. You're making it up. Stop making it up. Just, you don't
have to do that. This is, this is the word, one of the worst insects in the world. Everybody hates
these things. Nobody likes this. You don't have to pretend to be like, oh yeah, I like that. It
sucks blood. Stop. You don't have to do that. Don't do that. Just put it in F with everybody else.
Just put it down here with everybody else. No one's doing that. Yeah, I'm making up. It's called
a straw man argument. Go look it up. It's literally half my conversations. What is this? I don't know.
It's green and I like it. Wait, it's a flea? No, it's not. Don't some of these look like they're
taken from a certain perspective where this could be as big as a dog? Can you imagine?
This like freaks me out. Would that be better or worse? It would be a Jurassic period bug.
Well, I mean like just for the environment, right? If bees were as big as a small house cat,
would that be better for the environment? Would that be worse? It would be much worse.
It'd be worse for us. But what's, okay, like an earthworm, right? Where's the earthworm?
The good old earthworm. If these were as big as like a gas pipeline, right? If they were huge,
like tremor style, would that be better or worse for the world? If these were huge, but they weren't
gonna hurt anybody. All right. No, no, no. Forget about if they were as big as like a whole like
pipeline or something. If they, if an earthworm was as big as a house cat or like as big as a dog
and as like like a snake, if they were as big as like a python, wouldn't that be better for the
soil? They would be kind of moving more soil, right? It's an earthworm. I'm not talking about
like a scorpion. It would mess up foundations of houses. Yeah. I don't fucking know, Jerma. Just
rank them. You want me to be out of this, don't you? You're over this. You're done with this
segment. You don't want this segment anymore. At the end of the day, who cares, right? Does this
really matter to anybody? Does it really matter where I put bugs on a tier list? This is meaningless.
It's fucking meaningless. It's meaningless. I can understand like fast food restaurants and soft
drinks and different cheeses, but bugs? Wow, I'm out of tier lists, huh? No more to do. This is it.
This is where we are now. I hate these things. Just the thought. Not, wait, not these ones. The
ones that are under the water. You guys know the ones I'm talking about? The ones that dive? Oh,
those are so gross. What are the ones that dive called? The ones that you can in pools across
America. They're shaped like a little oval and they have two legs that just go like this.
Ah, God. I remember being in a pool and just having the goggles on and just jumping in the pool
and just going face to face with one of these little aliens just swimming underground or under
the water. They were, oh, I just hated it. This is a walrus. This is not, that's a walrus. What's
this next one? This is a cartoon. This is, I don't know what that is. This is a crab. No,
this is one of those Australian spiders, which, yeah, no, fuck that. This is half a picture of
something. I don't know what that is. And this is, I don't like that. This is, this is the thing
that like kids put on the end of their pencils where the eraser is. This is just an eraser toy
thing. This is not even an animal. All right, let me fix this. Where's the music? This is not
the music I wanted. I can't connect. Kirby 64, the crystal shards. That's fine. Whatever.
It's a fuzzy caterpillar. That's kind of cute. It's not, it's probably the seat here. All right,
let me, let me start from the top here. Okay. So, honeybee. That's probably the best. Firefly.
These are probably the best. I'm okay with this. I'm okay with this. Praying mantises are really
cool though. Then those of you that remember Cromwell was the praying mantis that was with
the hanging out with the sunflowers. Dung beetles are cooler than butterflies. Lady bugs are cooler
than butterflies. In fact, butterflies are going to go down at A because, I mean, they're cool,
but they're just, they're like the, they're like the vanilla ice cream of the bug world.
It's just, yeah, vanilla ice cream's fine. They're cool and it tastes good and I would, I would,
it would be fine. But I don't, it's like, it's cool, but it's just kind of just generic in a way.
It's great, but there are many other things that I think are more interesting than butterflies.
They're just generically great. Generally good. Forget about what I said about taste. I'm just
talking about just making a comparison. Would I rather have an earwig or a slug in my house?
I really don't mind these. They have such a cute face. If you, okay, if you've never seen
the face of an earwig, get out of my Discord call, whoever you are. Um, what was that? Okay.
Uh, they have a cute face and they look at you. They look up and they're like,
hello, it's me, earwig. They're, everyone hates earwigs. Earwigs literally crawl into your brain
through your ear. That is horseshit. It's not real. That's just somebody from like the fucking
1400s made that up for one day because they, I don't know what they were doing. No, that doesn't
happen. They used to say that happened back when the, like the queen ruled the earth. Okay.
That this is not real. This doesn't happen to people. I feel like just fucking get up and
spinning with this one going. This is too much. I have to like blow the volume.
Alternate history, Andy. Okay. This nobody has an earwig in their ear. It's just called earwig
because some somebody like a fucking thousand years ago was, I don't know, just maybe they had
one in their ear. Who knows what they were putting in their ears at the time. You're talking about
like the fucking 1500s, 1600s. They were probably putting like fucking the ground beef in their
ears to cure the common cold. Of course a bug is going to go in their ear. They were probably
putting like a delicious succulent honey in both of their ears to prevent coughing. You know, come
on. I don't buy that. So is it any surprise? All right. This day and up there. Okay. I really
actually wouldn't want to see an aunt in my house because that means that you have aunts
and they follow that. If there's a bunch of them, I don't, you know what I mean? It's like, okay,
then I got to, I got to take care of this. I have to be, I have to be like, what am I,
what do I do about this? You don't want, I don't mind ants. I think they're cute,
but you don't want ants. Seeing one aunt, two aunts like, oh, okay. Look at ant. But once you
turn the corner and there's like 10, you're like, okay, this is a problem. This turned into a
problem. But what about ant man? Don't worry. We'll get to that. Don't worry. We'll get to that.
By the way, how is there not a single spider on this whole list besides the jokes? There's no
spider on this list. That's weird. Um, okay. All right. So let's, let's continue. That's fine.
This is fine. Um, do I really like these this much? Not really. I would probably rather see
these in the house than any of these. I mean, come on. It's beautiful. Why would you be upset
about that? This is, a lot of these are changing here. What is this? No, you got, I'm not going to
put this up here just because you, you see it's cute and it's in Pokemon. I'm not putting it up
here. These things suck. There's a lot of Fs. You ever have that moment when you're looking at a bug
because the hardest part with this, especially with any insect, there are like 400 billion different
types of insects of the same genes and shit, right? So I'll look at a bug and I'll be like,
oh, cool. Look at this little beetle. Look at how cute. Wait, is there a raid? Oh, there is a raid
from Cottontail. Cottontail VA. Thanks for the raid. Welcome everybody. We're raiding bugs. What's
up? Thanks for the raid. Hope you had a good stream. We're raiding bugs right now. And then
we're going to play multiverses. It's going to be fun. Ow. I can't do that unless I have like,
have had two coffees and I haven't had that yet. Okay, so let's go. What was I saying? Oh, right.
Okay. So there's, there's like millions of different kinds of bugs and types of insects, right?
So if you see like a cute beetle, you don't, there's no way to know what the hell it even really
actually is. It could be something really shitty. And you sit in there going, whoa, cool beetle.
What is that? Does this thing have poison in it? And you'll get it wrong. Oh, that's definitely,
that's a, that's a, that's a carpenter bee or something, right? And it's just wrong. And it
was a fucking moth and it stung you in the mouth. What? I have to turn this off. This is like making
my brain all messed up. It's speech jamming me and making me say weird things. Okay. But you know
what I mean? Like you'll just get it wrong. And then you, oh, I'm going to rescue this bug. And
it turns out, why'd you rescue that bug? It just ate all your plants and like killed 50 other bugs
that were good bugs. And you did that. You could have, you know, you should have gotten rid of
that bug. It's so hard to tell. Like you might save this bug and go look it up online. It's like,
oh yeah, by the way, if you see any of these, get rid of them immediately. They will breed and you'll
have 50 million in your backyard within two, three days. And you're just like, okay, that was great.
I just was trying to be like a nice guy and like not been saved like my beetle friend.
That's what earwigs do. Can you shut up, man? Do earwigs do that? Okay. So when I,
when I see an earwig and listen to this music, right? Imagine an earwig looking up at you and
he's like, and I'm like, oh, get the envelope, save him. And I get the envelope and I put it out,
get him on the envelope and I put him outside. Am I just creating another 5,000 earwigs?
And then the next day it's like three that you see and you're like, oh, wow, cool. Let's save these
three to the same fucking soundtrack. Oh, save us. 50 in your house. And they're all dancing in a
line doing one antenna, two antenna, one antenna, two antenna, top hat, top hat, top hat. It's like,
well, 50 earwigs. Oh my God, they're so cute. Get the, get the envelope. They all start crawling
on it. You get them out, you save them, save the earwigs. And then it, you know, me lying down in
bed three days later and I'm drifting off to sleep. Ah, what a nice day that was today.
And the second that I fall asleep and I go into REM, they can sense it. And 2,000 earwigs just
make a trail up the bed and just go into my brain to this music. And they all going in, digging in,
like eating pieces of my brain matter. And I'm just asleep. And this, and some of them are still
dancing with the top hat. Is that what you think? Is that what you're saying is going to happen to
me? Oh, because I saved the earwig. I didn't want to kill the earwig. That already happened.
Why do you think you're like this? I don't see an earwig in this room. I don't see, I don't,
there's no earwigs crawling over the lens of the camera. Do you see one? I don't see one.
It's because they're inside of you. All right, we're moving on. We're moving on. Next up,
we're going to do real quick. This is a, but here's my list. I think it's accurate.
That's accurate. The next one is a bug movie tier list. I guess we're going to stay with this theme
here for a little bit. This one won't take long and then we'll play multi-parties. Wow, why is
Pinocchio on this list? Oh, because Jiminy, because, oh, Cricket. Spider-Man is on the list.
But that's, that doesn't make any sense. Spider-Man is not a spider. He's a guy with a suit on
that was bit by a spider. Neither is Ant-Man. So these are both D. I'm sorry. This does not fit
the criteria. It doesn't fit the criteria. Hold on. Oh, shit. Hold on a second. No, it doesn't. It
does not fit the criteria. It has to be a movie based on an insect where the main character is
potentially an insect. Insect, not guy in a suit and he calls himself an insect name, right? But
could you say that the spider that bites Spider-Man is essentially the character of Spider-Man? Ant-Man
is not an ant. He just calls himself Ant-Man because he can shrink and grow. That doesn't make
any sense. All right. This is a bug's life. I haven't seen any, I haven't seen any of these
movies in probably 10 years. Ants, this movie is weird. Dune, I haven't seen Dune. Freaks,
I don't know what that is. Honey, I Shrunk the Kids, that's S. James and the Giant Peach,
I remember this being okay. Men in Black, S. Pinocchio, B. It's two different Spider-Man movies,
three Spider-Man movies. Starship Troopers was crazy. Tremors, I haven't seen it in a long time.
Turbo, Turbo to me almost feels like I know the movie existed, but it feels like a mobile game ad
that I watched. Right? I don't have a memory of this. What movie is this? Is this Alien?
What movie is this? The Fly? I mean Pinocchio, could I put Pinocchio here? It's just Pinocchio.
This was the animated kind of stop-motion one, right? I just haven't seen any of these in so
long. I really don't even care. B-movie. B-movie is like Morbius, guys. You only like the movie
because you saw Copypasta one time. This is not a good movie. This is not a good movie.
You only like B-movie because somebody made a GIF of the whole movie and it plays in five seconds
and it's funny and Jerry Seinfeld's in it. It's C. That's a bad take. No, it's not. It's just like a
general animated movie with Jerry Seinfeld. I mean, sure, it's fine, but yeah, it's weird,
isn't it? It's the worst ever take. B-movie is actually good. I just remember them in a car,
like they were driving in like these cars going to work or something and that's when I fell asleep
in the hotel room. I didn't watch this because I wanted to. I don't think anybody's ever seen
this movie. It's not S. I'll put it B because that's funny. I mean, the Spider-Man movies are
great, but it doesn't make any sense. Alien should be higher. This isn't Aliens. He said this is the
fly. That's not the fly. This is like, what is that? I can't read it. It's cut off. It's called,
it's actually the fly. Men in Black has bugs? I mean, the main character, the main antagonist
of Men in Black is a bug. He's the bug. He's an alien, but he's a bug alien. He's an alien bug.
The main character in Spider-Man is not a spider. He's a superhero that got bit by a spider
before. The movies aren't even about the spider. The movies are about Spider-Man
taking on crime and fighting people. He shoots webs. Not in these ones, not in the Sam Raimi ones.
Excuse me. He has a device on his arms, doesn't shoot webs out of his arms. Have you seen the
movie? Oops. Which one's more accurate to the book? Okay, which one's more accurate to the book?
The web coming out of his arm or the devices? Which one's more accurate to the book? The device
is more accurate to the book. Thank you. Thank you. Thank you. That doesn't mean anything. Yeah,
it means he's not a spider. It means he's a guy that can shoot webs that he got made in a laboratory.
He's not a spider. He's a man that has abilities of a spider that also is supplemented by technology.
Ant-Man uses ants. Where even is Ant-Man? He does? I don't... All right, who cares?
Let's play multiverses. Who cares? He controls ants? He controls ants? I know he doesn't. He does
like quantum physics. When does he control ants in the movie? He controls ants. He does? I've seen
these movies before. Wait, so you're telling me that in the movie Ant-Man at some point goes like
this and the millions of ants do his bidding? Have I just... Did I forget the whole movie?
No, he doesn't fucking do that. He does not go like... No, you're... Sorry, guys. You're thinking
of... What was that movie with the guy that controlled the rats? Willard? You're thinking
of Willard? That happened... That's a different movie. He rides an ant. What? Did I forget this
whole movie? No fucking way. Ant-Man trailer. No way. I don't believe it. Why is it so
weirdly shaped? Where are the ants? There's no ants!
Okay, hold on.
Did I not watch this one? Did I only watch the sequel?
I don't remember him breaking into places and stealing stuff.
I never watched this one. I only watched the sequel. I never watched this movie.
What the fuck, dude? I never watched this movie. I've never seen this movie. I've never seen this
movie. Holy shit, I was so wrong. Oh my god, I was wrong. He controls ants. He's Ant-Man. Of course
he is. Oh my goodness. Wow, I just pretended to watch this one. Okay, but hold on a minute.
Hold on a second, guys. They made all these... The ants was such a big deal in the first movie.
Why were there no ants in the second movie? Why were there no ants in the second movie?
No, there's no ants in the second movie. There are no ants I've seen in the second movie.
They like go into like the quantum realm and who's... What even happens in the second movie?
I don't... Whatever. I don't care. An ant plays the drums in the second movie.
All right, give me two seconds. We're gonna play multiverses. I'm excited. I am very ready. Are
you guys ready for me to go nuts in multiverses? I am. You're literally insane. I'm sorry. I just
did not see the first movie and I thought I did. I have this distinct dream where I've seen it
already. I don't know why. I have this insane dream world.