No, I'm not back yet. I'm not back yet. I want to I want to refill my drink. I'm not quite back yet.
Not quite. Give me a sec. Hold on. I'm not quite back yet. I need to refill my drink.
I do have something really cool though. I think I've showed this already, didn't I? I probably did. It's cool though.
All right, actually, you know, I'll be all right. I'll be I'll take a break in a little bit. Let's just get to it.
Okay. Hello. How are you? There's that. There's that. And of course here am I.
I'm back. Welcome everybody to season two of multiverses. It's been a while since we played this.
Thank you Warner Brothers for sponsoring the stream.
This is gonna be a couple of hours of sponsored content. By the way, just in case you didn't know. What's it available on?
Do we know? PlayStation, Xbox, PC, cross-platform. They just did a huge, huge
internet change and it's apparently really cool and it's apparently good.
There's some new characters we haven't played with which I need to do that first.
But yeah, season two, I believe just started right now. You'll see Marvin Martian at some point soon here. Show us your legs.
They exist. Here, you wanna, you wanna see what, okay, fine.
You wanna see what kind of, you wanna see what kind of pants I'm wearing? Here, you wanna see? Yeah, there it is.
There's, there are my pants. There, I ripped the leg. It's fine. These things were already ripped.
Did you, could you hear the tearing? Could you, did it come through?
Let's get to it everybody. Okay, I actually need to practice first.
But yeah, thanks again to Warner Brothers. Warner Brothers has been incredibly awesome to this channel. Let's see who's here.
I know there's another Gremlins character, which is pretty sick. So let's see who we got. They've added, of course,
there's Rick from Rick and Morty. There's Black Adam. There's
Stripe. Let me see Black Adam. Let's see what you do. Okay, that's cool. Looks, looks pretty good.
All right, so what about the specials? Let me read about this because that's pretty cool. Whoa, a lot of Bugs Bunny stuff.
Yeah, I'm a little rusty, but let me go to the move list. Okay, so let's see. That's a, okay.
Black Adam releases a beam of lightning to, this is just neutral, why?
Damaging them repeatedly and applying shock before tossing them either up or down.
Can I choose which way they go? When the lightning hits a target it searches for nearby
targets, jumping to them to repeat the move in a chain of electric attacks. You can charge it.
All right. Dash forward and is chased moments later by a bolt projectile.
This bolt will reflect off the force field generated by Black Adam's grounded down special. Okay, let's see.
Let's see what that looks like. So what's the down special? That stays there.
It bounces off that. So what does that do? Black Adam briefly gains the ability to fly in any direction. That's awesome.
Generates an electromagnetic force that it blocks enemy. That's actually insane. It blocks all projectiles.
My voice did that. It was a weird thing that just happened, but trust me, I actually think it's interesting.
All right. So what about this stuff? Holy shit. Seems actually pretty good. Lot of cooldowns though, it seems.
How long can you fly for? A pretty long time. I'll give it a try. Okay, so what about who's next?
There's also Stripe, which is, that's definitely, I'm gonna play Stripe for sure.
Gremlins.
Already like it. Already like the moves.
It's, you know, it's kind of funny.
I never thought in my entire life that they would bring gremlins back, but they did. All right, that's a pretty good combo. What about down?
Sawz?
All right, let's take a look at the moves. Stripe fires his gun at close range. All right, there's a gun.
I believe that means that they're targeted. Okay. He will shoot at them. Okay, if Stripe has targeted an enemy,
he will shoot at them instead, regardless of distance. That just seems like a better version of
Velma. Doesn't Velma put a target?
All right, Stripe charges a push with his skateboard and shoots across the area. He also can combo into a backflip.
Oh my god, that's fast. Okay.
That's terrifying. I like this character. Oh, I like this character a lot.
Okay, cool. What else we got?
I could just kind of learn as I go. Stripe dashes upward at his target.
If he hits any projectile while leaping, he will destroy it. Stripe pulls out a bundle of dynamite that detonates after a duration. Press input
again to detonate it immediately.
Detonating ignites and hits enemies outward. Stripe also receives damage. What? So I get her too? Oh, okay.
All right, I'm taking Stripe into ranked. Show Marvin? I don't know if Marvin's available. I don't think he's out yet.
There's no- I have to- we have to look at Rick for a second at least. Just for a second. Actually kind of cracked.
Actually kind of cracked. I think I might be playing Rick Sanchez.
That was funny. I'm sorry it was. That was actually pretty funny. That was funny. Yeah, it was.
All right, let's give it a try. I'm in- I'm in fucking wood league, so it really doesn't matter. Let's look at the battle pass.
Astronaut velvet. Pretty cool. Utility belt Batman. What else is here? What's the very last thing?
Shield and bubbles.
I love the ring out effect stuff. What is this? What's this? Taz taunt. Taz hungry. What's this?
Bug's bunny taunt. All right, I'm ready. I think I'm- I think I'm warmed up.
Gotta take a real series, huh?
I think I'm ready. Let's go- let's go play wood league. I'm ready. All right, let's get out of here.
How do I get out of here? Oh, there we go. All right, you guys pumped up for season two of multiverses. Let's go!
Top 10 most pumped up moments.
There's- they added a bunch of weird shit too. This is cool.
Arcade classic? Yeah, like look, there's like weird like silly mode. We definitely have to play silly mode.
Let me get back into- should I do ranked? This is gonna be so embarrassing.
All right, I'm gonna do ranked one-on-one and it's gonna be a desa-
Should I warm up first? No, we're going right in with stripe. Let's go. I'm ready.
I think I got- I- it's like riding a bike. Yeah, silly mode activated. I wonder what it is. Where's the level-
Any perks?
Oh, this is gonna be a disaster. Um, all right. Well, let's see what happens. Uh, my rank- rank-
Excuse me, didn't even show this bad boy off. That's a multiverses controller.
I didn't think I was gonna get a multiverses control. All right, let me actually be real here. Let me try.
It's all about the gun. It's all about the dynamite.
Here we go.
Ooh!
My audio is all messed up.
Ah!
Oh, that move is gonna be so cool if you can hit it. Ooh, I can throw blades too. That's cool.
I just hurt myself.
Oh!
How am I still on the stage? That's crazy.
Oh, not good. It's all right. I love the screams. Come on.
All right. Come on. Come on. I got four minutes. I got four minutes.
Don't do it. No!
It's all right. It's a warm-up. It's a warm-up. It's the first match I played in like three weeks.
That was- I did pretty good. That wasn't bad. That's the first match I've had in like three weeks.
Let's go again.
You don't have any perks. You lost to an Xbox player? So what?
What do you- should I- who should I play with? I'm gonna stick with Stripe.
No, no. We change it up.
Bugs.
I got perks on Bugs. Level 11. I was pretty good with uh- what's the name there? Um,
Gizmo.
Yeah, go ahead. Bet. Hey, the rust is gonna shake off here and I'm gonna do just fine.
Uh-oh, he's bringing out the main.
I got one minute. I don't want to- this is a nice controller. I don't want to mess it up.
All right, let's go. Don't be messing around.
Check this out. What the hell is going on?
Shit. All right, bring it back. Let's go.
Oh shit.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no. Sorry. Sorry. I got plenty of time.
Don't do anything stupid. I got the advantage here. There it is. All right. We're good. We're good. We're getting it back.
This is ranked, man. I gotta get out of Wood League. I mean, we gotta go for the whole thing, right? This is it.
Do I stick with Bugs or should I go- no, I gotta stick with what I know, right?
Hmm, land the first knock-up, knockback. All right, cool. I'm gonna stick with Bugs. It's like riding a bike. I remember all the moves.
Go with Rick? I don't know anything about Rick. I would have to go with not in ranked. I'm just gonna joke around with it.
That's why you have to practice.
Yeah, I'm doing it right now.
All right, let's see if I can pull this out. Let me get into my zone here. All right, let's go.
I feel like my eyes are bugging out of my head. All right, just let's do it.
It's my odd one. All right, this is the Rick Sanchez level. Gotta keep the pressure up. Shit. Oh,
Ooh, oh, it's gonna come. Bad. Come on. Come on. Sweaty hands.
What was that? That was a dog toy. You have to go off the line.
I could never make that sound ever again if you- if you told me to, right?
I gotta turn the camera off for that. I don't- the camera's not linked up to anything. Good game. Good game.
What did that even sound like?
Multiverses is on the Xbox,
PlayStation, and PC with complete cross-platform.
By the way, season two is out now and it's pretty damn fun.
All right, I'm gonna do-
Gizmo was fun. Let me see if I can remember how to play Gizmo. I'm not doing ranked. We're not- we're just gonna play normal.
I don't think I'm ever coming out of wood league. Let's do normal and
let's just maybe- no, no, not silly mode yet. Not silly mode.
Let me try stripe again.
Why did he squeak? I do- I-
I don't know. I don't- I couldn't make that sound ever again. I'm telling you, even if you- it doesn't matter what would happen here.
So I'm trying to think of the combos to do with stripe. It seems to be you want to get the target,
bop, bop, bop, juggle, and then do an up smash. Okay, let's go for it.
What the heck?
Was that- what happened?
Stripe's fun.
Do you want to go again or
start over?
Nah, I'm good. Okay. Well, thanks for playing.
I guess that was- we- we got it. I'll take the win, whatever.
Oh, do I have any points? No, it's okay.
I'm never doubting ever again.
Thanks for the refund. Oh, yeah. I mean, yeah, sometimes it doesn't count, right?
Is the chatbot working, by the way? Let me make sure it is.
Should be- I believe so. Okay, it should be popping up.
All right, this is versus a high level shaggy, so I gotta be- I gotta be ready for this. I'm trying to learn stripe.
I'm a gremlins franchise only player.
Oops.
Dang, when I run out of booms!
Oh! How did that block?
No! Don't! I got perfect.
Bro, he got owned. Yeah, this is a shaggy that knows what he's doing.
I got a better idea. Pulling out the LeBron.
Do I have this? Oh, I don't have that. Oh.
Oh, no, why? I'm ready.
Oh, let me pull this one out.
Yeah, there is- there's a new battle pass. Is that part- is that part of a battle pass? All right.
Let's see if I can pull this out.
I lost the ball already.
Oh, man, this is bad. It ain't over yet.
This guy's a good player. I don't- this guy's- this guy's not in wood league, okay?
It ain't over. It ain't over. It ain't over.
Oh, I'm just getting combo'd.
Oh, he's mad.
So am I.
Let's go, man.
I just fucking freaked you out for no reason. No, I want that- I need that ball. Fucking really- I'm in wood league!
Your eyes popped out of your head.
Dude, you fell off. Just fine. Does he really- he isn't- no, no, no.
I don't want to play ranked because I don't want to go up against people that can beat me bad.
I gotta stick with one character and play.
We're gonna stay on Stripe. We're not moving off Stripe for at least 25 minutes. Okay.
What's going on?
Oi!
Stop! Don't taunt! Don't taunt! That makes me angry!
Yeah, I mean, this is a spider in the room. A huge spider just went down. You can't revoke my gamer license.
That's not fair.
I gotta get like a few warm-up games in and I- well, I am so red and it's because they can't- hold on.
I'm not this red, I swear.
Look at how red the room is! Have I emanating heat from my body?
I'm not red. My room is red. I'm not heating up the room, right?
All right. Okay, it's against level 8 Morty. Everything's gonna be fine.
Shit.
I'm starting to get it. We'll be good.
You should stand up. No, I'll fall down. I'll be good. We just gotta warm up a little. I'll get a few wins.
Was that a grenade? So many places to fall down. Damn it! Oh my god, we're on a boat!
Yeah!
Got it. Ah, that felt good. That felt good. That felt good.
Over Dean?
Yeah!
Somebody said I move around too much. I know. I do. Again, season 2 is out. It's on everything.
PC, Xbox, PlayStation. You can play this complete cross-play. It's all there. Season pass is available right now.
I like Stripe. That's gonna do better.
This was the Rick who gamed on you, is it? I gotta get my revenge. This is the Rick who's dude who absolutely just dunked on me.
Oh, it worked out!
Oh, what happened, Rick?
That's not even fair! You did a...
Whatever. I mean, it's just well known that Rick is a complete hard counter to Stripe. We all know that.
Oh, what'd I get? Oh, wait a minute. Oh, I got the astronaut Belma. Cool. I'm buying my lip too much.
Profile? 50 coins? I feel like I would like Batman a lot, but I just never get him any time.
At all. Okay, this is up next. Maybe I should change some stuff up here.
This is not... Okay. Do you remember when I played last time and I had like an 80% win rate? I've played like five games.
That's like only today. That's today. What do I got? That's cute.
Somebody said, can you please do the Stripe impression? Yeah, sure.
That'll be a thousand dollars, please. I'm kidding. Don't do that. That's not worst impression. That was pretty close.
Both had the same idea. Both brilliant players.
All right, I'm getting too fancy. Don't get too fancy. Just play. I'll just play. Oh, I got it off first. That's horseshit.
Oh, Snipe. Stripe is fun.
You're sim...
Why are you squirming around? Whenever I play a game like this, my whole body has to move back and forth.
I just have to be... I'm inside the game.
Do you guys remember back in the day when they talked about those, oh,
like, oh, you can wear this thing that when you get hit, you get hit. They like toyed with that idea.
Like it was like a dun dun dun dun dun dun dun, or something, right?
I feel like I have one of those on. Let's go back to Bugs for a little bit.
I do want to mess around with Black Adam, though. Seems like his move set's pretty fun.
Start time. Maybe Velma.
Maybe, yeah.
I played Stripe for 25 minutes.
All right, no more like high stress. I feel like I've warmed up. I feel like I'm good to go.
Don't let him do that.
What's happening? Keep letting him do it.
Careful. Oh, I thought I could just drain him. All right. Okay. All right.
Oh, sandwich versus pie. Don't let him do that!
What?
I'm not playing it up. I genuinely move around. I don't even know what I'm doing. Am I like moving too much?
That was a good fight. That was very good. Stop pretending. I'm not, I'm not pretending.
Oh, what's this? Oh, a shaggy ring out. I'm curious about what that is. Oh, that's cool. Also cool.
Oh, that's cool, too. Didn't I? What did I get? I'll do this one. This one looks good. All right, one more.
One more. Wait, what's this? I don't want to activate that yet. Okay, one more
of these will do a little bit of silly mode. You're doing video game commercial acting.
You mean when they're like this and they're like, oh,
and they're pressing buttons really hard. It really, ah, whatever. Whatever. It's fine. You need something blowing in your hair, too.
Yeah, make it some uh, fuel in me. This level is really hard. I think there's some new maps too, right?
All right. Come on, let me play.
Oh, the snipe at the end. Oops, it's on fire.
snipe
See, I just had to play a few games. Everybody said, oh my god,
this dude is awful. I can't believe this guy thinks he can play this game. What are you? This is a joke.
What do you think you're doing?
He's gonna, you gotta warm up a little bit.
I'd be careful where you put your uh, channel points at this point, guys.
Uh, you're too confident now. That's it. That's good.
Gotta have a little bit of confidence. Dude, you're still in plastic league. That's all right. I'm still, I'm still going somewhere. You go from
water to wood to plastic to steel to bronze.
I got a long way to go, but what did I just do?
Come on, pick character.
Skipping cardboard.
Dude, I guarantee you if I grinded rank, I would just be at bronze two.
I would, I would always win one, lose two, win two, lose two, win one, lose three, win three, lose four.
I would never climb. I can never get something going where I win like 10 times in a row.
I would always be bronze two or bronze one.
I get in my own head way too much in competitive games because I start doing
well and then I get a little bit too comfortable and relax a little bit and then no, no, no, I lose two in a row.
Then I get angry
and then try as hard as I can for the next two, win both of those, get confident and comfortable and relax a little, lose two in a row.
Are you, are you not fighting me?
Okay, are you, are we playing?
All right. Yeah, okay. Yeah, yeah, we're playing. We're, we are playing.
Risky.
Oh, got my static. Did you actually get that off? How did I not hit you?
Let's do it. All right. Yeah, look, you're gonna, you gotta learn how to play. I have to learn how to play.
I'm gonna play, I'll play Black Adam.
You don't know, who knows? You know, sometimes they have bad games. Sometimes you're trying to learn a character. Well, hey, hey,
relax. Okay. Oh, you're looking for a mirror.
I have no idea how to play Black Adam, but we'll try. Don't get cocky. I'm not gonna. Somebody just wrote, am I banned?
Testing to see if you're banned in the chat. Okay, here we go. See, we're good.
Black Adam is disgusting.
That's my bubble. Get out of it. We were just like two dogs playing. Just like, we're gonna play, we're running around having so much fun.
Stop. Okay, let's go again. Oh, we just died. Okay. That was fun. That was fun.
It's a fun game. It's a fun game. People are gonna play the fun game. Oh my goodness. I'm so sorry.
I, I, I had warmed up. Do silly mode.
How about one more with Stripe and then we'll do silly mode. Does Stripe have an announcer pack?
Because I have to have it, if that's the case.
What's this? That's, oh, that's good.
Anytime for three seconds after knocking back an enemy with a projectile. That's pretty good.
Uh, this is a level 13.
Uh, Garnet, so we're gonna be prepared. I don't really know Garnet's, but I forget Garnet's moves. And we've got, um,
home field advantage here.
This is, uh, it's gonna be hard.
All right, that was an extreme move. I will agree. I'm on a ride right now. This is the multi versus carnival ride.
All right, focus.
Don't do that. No, no, no, no, no.
That was such a good match too. Dude, you're a freak. Okay. I gotta, I gotta bring out something.
Good.
What's wrong with him? I'm gaming, man. Yeah, we'll do silly mode after this. All right, level 19 Batman. I gotta be prepared.
You guys having fun? All right, should I do, we'll do silly.
All right, silly Q. Do we have to pick rules or what is, uh, what is silly mode?
There's also a, I think, a versus,
like an arcade mode versus boss or something. I want to see what that is too. I, I, I don't know why I left.
Okay, so it's a 2v2 silly mode. Yeah, I'll do some 2v2s now. Refund the point.
Uh, was there, did it go through? I did. Okay, good. What is this?
Okay, I'm not gonna almost fall off the stage and squeak. I'm gonna be relaxed and we're gonna play. Okay, four ring outs.
What? Okay, so we just have big heads.
Why did Morty already lose? I don't think Morty's here.
This is truly silly.
Last box is shrinking.
Well, we didn't, I don't want to just end silly mode right now. Oh, man.
Okay, that, this is a literal 2v1. That Taz was actually holding pretty well.
Uh, yeah, I don't think we continue this. I think we go do it again. Some gold, nice.
Forget how to play with gizmo, but it's silly mode, so it's okay.
Yeah, well, no, we don't, don't run bets on, uh, on silly mode. Do a gizmo impression.
No, I did a stripe impression. Everybody told me it was embarrassing. So I, why would I do another one? Do it now.
All right, level 19, but it doesn't matter. It's silly mode. I remember gizmo being really fun.
Oh, yeah, then you shoot the popcorn. I remember. Okay. Isn't there also a little car too? Yep, there is.
I loved gizmo. Dude, I'm giving my teammate a bunch of, a bunch of juice or whatever that was.
How do I shoot the bow and arrow? I forget. Is it down?
Up? Or how do I do, how to shoot the bow and arrow? Come here, take some of this juice. Right bumper?
Oh, that's what it is. Right. Okay. I was like, where the hell is it?
Was this TV?
Oh my goodness. Where was I going? It's too silly. There it is. All right, we brought it back. Brought it back.
Take this juice. There it is. Give me a hand here. Give me a hand here. Who am I talking to?
We got it.
All right, give me a hand here. Juice over here, man. Like I'm, you know, nobody can hear me besides you guys.
Alting.
So what's, let me see the other mode. See this arcade classic?
Play a series of enemies that will take you on a journey across the multiverse. Do you have what it takes to make it to the end?
Three stages, unlimited tries. Let's, let's do medium.
What is this? It's arcade?
I wonder. So it's an adventure mode?
Okay, so let's see what this is. I'm interested. Stage one of five.
Sorry, kid. I know you got this game for Christmas, but
try to rank up here.
I know I'm doing the I'm trying really hard face, but I kind of am. Oh, that was it. There it is.
By the way, the game's also free to play. Get it right now. Season two has officially launched Xbox, PC, PlayStation.
Can I hear it please?
So it was just another round?
I'm curious what happens at the end of this. Do you get experience? I will say
Let's be completely real. I have never played an online fighting game. I would have never played this ever again. Let me be very honest.
Um, like I don't really play fighting games. I don't. The net code of fighting games is always
unbelievably awful.
This game
feels like I'm not even playing it online. It feels like I'm playing it and the person is sitting next to me in the
room with a controller plugged in.
It's just, I'm telling you that's what it is.
I've never played a fighting game that was like that. I've never done it. It's never happened.
I always play a fighting game online, have half a second of input delay, and never play it ever again.
I'm just telling you the truth. That is what has happened.
Being able to play this game and not have to think oh, I have to do my moves
like a second early.
I can't do it.
I have to be completely honest. That's honesty. It is.
When I play this when I'm playing online, it feels like the person I'm playing against is sitting right next to me
and we're trash talking a little bit.
I don't know what magical powers it takes to get the game to do that. I heard it's very difficult to get it right.
And it's very very good.
Yeah, rollback netcode. It's just good.
I would not make that up. I'm serious. The last handful of fighting games that I ever played,
I was just like I don't want to do this. It's like it's horrible in my brain. I can't do it.
All right, so what's the question mark mean?
We believe you.
You don't believe me. You don't understand. The gremlins movie is so good.
They're both good. Gremlins 2 is better than gremlins 1.
Gremlins 1 is a little more serious than gremlins 2, but gremlins 2 is just a big comedy show.
Feral gizmo.
He's a good player.
Trying to bait me. I gotta learn how to use the um saws better. I feel like I haven't been utilizing very well.
Do I do that?
I feel like I'm hearing myself. Didn't I do that? I do I I like just kind of scream make weird sounds like that.
Don't I?
Don't do that. Oh shut up.
Not you. Not you. Him. Oh my god. I lost the computer.
I just wasn't paying that much attention.
Okay, let me let me just get I'm gonna get to it. All right, let me get to the end of this
So just let me pay attention now in my brain. I didn't want to try so hard that people are like dude
Why is he trying this hard?
Against a bot
Like dude, relax, you know, this is not a player like why are you trying so hard?
So then I pulled back a little ended up losing because of that, but now i'm mad
Here we go. Check this out
Goodbye
Where's the commentary?
There's no commentary on these
Okay, so i'm almost done trying hard against a bot. Well, I want to beat this
I don't want to have to retry twice bro is mashing buttons
You know what the worst part about um, what you just said was I know that you can tell when I do that
because you hear the
Because I can hear it I wish I could turn it off because I don't want I
No, but I like having it on because I like to know when i'm not supposed to be doing something
But I I just don't want you to know that i'm messing up. You know what I mean?
It happens all the time
I don't want you to know that I screwed up. Does that make sense?
Even though it's an incredibly incredibly useful feature
I'm gonna make sure it doesn't happen this time
Is it weird that ever since i've been really conscious of you saying that i've been playing better because I don't want you to hear this
Because that's what you hear the whole time. I play this game
I you got in my head and I heard it and I all right. I'm not even listening to that person
Jesus jerma, i'm sorry. No, it's all good
Your head moves around when you do it. That should be a poker table
Well, I got I got pocket aces I would be terrible at poker. Yeah, I would get pocket aces
I'd have sunglasses on a hat hoodie zip up and pocket aces. I would just stand up and be like
Look at that. Look what I got. I wouldn't be able to contain it. I would turn around
I'd like look under again and be like whoo
I would just I'd just be a weirdo and people wouldn't know
But I would also do that if I had like a three and like a three and a six
That would work wouldn't it do you think that I could do pretty well in a tournament
If I had a three and a six and I did that I got up and did a bunch of movements pointing
Pointing a tip in the hat and shit. Do you think it would work?
Oh my god, why are you so huge?
What how did you get that?
Is that part of this?
You can somebody said I can throw the dynamite. I don't think you can throw it. I have it before. I think I dropped it
Hey, one more tap. Come on, dude. Get out of here
Oops
All right good
Was it raid who raided somebody raided? I didn't see who raided an engineer. Thanks a lot. Appreciate it
I don't know. I can't see it. Welcome everybody. There's no no, I don't know raid song
No, raid song you guys are digging up memes from 2021. All right, so I just did it. That's cool
All right, I want let me do some team action here teams. I'm not doing ranked. I got absolutely dunked on
I got destroyed
You should do another meme funeral. I forgot about that stream. The thing is though it worked that worked
All right. This is 2v2. I think why do you hate fun? I don't what I love fun. Hmm. That's kind of good
This has got to be one of the wildest group of characters to be in the same room
It's pretty crazy bugs bunny harley quinn stripe from gremlins and aria stark. It is very very interesting
Oh shit, that's I went right into that get him out of here get him out of here get him out of here
Got it. Sorry
Where'd we go? Oh shit, don't say he's so bad. That's the thing that makes every streamer angry
Hmm
I don't know how to play with rick, but we're gonna go. All right, if I win i'm gonna do a huge rick like who?
That like big yell, would you guys uh stay will you guys still be here if I do that start?
Somebody said yes, unfortunately. All right focus time will be immortalized in story and song a nice face
Have I've only been doing the same attack
Here we go. All right, it's tied up. It's all set. So it's tied up. I just put the sandwich down
Keep the pressure up pressure pressure
Good, keep it up. Just get the bugs
I don't know what he does for moves. We're good. We won. I said it was gonna stop screaming
Come on pick character
I don't care. Whatever fuck it
I got it wrong doesn't matter. It's our I thought I had it lined up right ended. Sorry
Remember, why did you eat all my peanut butter? I mean peanut butter lasts a long time
All right, let's do it for real. Don't mess around
Let's try to hit my own teammate. Things are going great
So much going on here. Don't get up there. Don't even don't even think about it
Not the will of the gods
Can I hit the jake with the mallet, please
Thank you wonder woman, I really appreciate it you did a very good job
Dude, I can't hit anybody. Why did that mallet not hit? I I don't understand it. Why?
Uh crunchy or smooth peanut butter, uh smooth every time smooth every single time no matter what hey
All right, we're going back to strike
We're going to back to one of you once
Boom. Oh, okay. I want to play some stickers because what about I can do my banner, right?
There it is. I can put stickers on this, right?
Oh, okay. Definitely this one this one and this one. Oh, I don't have it. That's 20 000. Okay, but I had it
Here comes the heat
All right, one v ones. Let's go back to one v one. Here comes the heat play a few more
Back to stripe. You look like a ferret today. It's kind of hot in here. All right this time. I gotta relax
I just can't help it though when I play competitive games like this. I just get so
My whole body just starts to react
Uh guys, do I make silly noises like a gremlin?
Damn it. Everybody stand up. No more talking. Here we go
Oh
Good dodge. Oh got it. All right
He's sitting on top of a washing machine. That was very funny
People can do some crazy combos in this game. It's actually pretty impressive
See, I relaxed. I just chilled out didn't make any weird sounds or anything
We were just hanging out playing multiverses. It was easy. It wasn't easy. Actually. It was very difficult
It was easy to relax
How do you get into this?
Uh, you go get it right now for free. It's just you're just gonna go get it
Available right now on pc xbox playstation. You can do it
Play it pretty much anywhere
Free to play
All right. Let's relax again try to get another good game in
Here we go
What? How did I get hit by that?
Damn, you're good with that charm
Yo, what?
Whoa
Oh, I told you we got this
Whoa, what happened wrong button? Maybe he's playing really well. I feel pretty good in that one
Please if you keep your head still I will give you a hundred subs
How do we determine that if I did it right?
I don't think I can do it. You caught him jumping. Oh, okay. He didn't have a second one left. Okay, so
Wait, wait, wait, we gotta do this, right?
We gotta do this right
I just need like a shape and I want you guys to really really pay attention to this
Needs to be like a bright red. I mean I
Wait, wait, wait, wait, you know what I mean? I I have to make it so
I right because if I come out of the if I come out of these lines and it's over
We'll do it next one next one next one next one next one. Goodness. What were we just doing?
I quit i'm i'm i'm raged with that wait
What would uh, i'm i'm raged but you want to play that game? We can both play that game
You want to play on the fucking edge? Come on to the edge. Let's do it. Come on. Come on here. Come on here
Stop taunting me
Shake it up
Okay, that was if not that wasn't even a real fight. No, i'm sorry. I have something to do. That was mr
Pancake, you're very good. That was very good, but I need to go back
Because I need to go back good luck in your the rest of your fights for the rest of the night
I have something important to do. I'm gonna try to make 100 subs here. Okay, so
Let me get this straight. So if i'm like here, right?
We have to make the camera big so you can actually zoom in and see it and thin enough
How much room do I get is this okay?
Or do I have to not move at all like completely still like this just not move from here
Is that all right right here? Because if I come outside of the lines here that that's it, right? Are we good?
Tell me if i'm in the right spot
Let me itch my face because i'm gonna i'm gonna freak out and halfway through this
Okay
Is it okay? Okay, so don't move from here and I get 100 subs
Don't move. I i'm not i'm not I just was looking to see what was in the right spot show them what we got
You got this i'm gonna try
As I fucking hate this I need to move
I lost what?
No, I didn't
You know what a harder thing you know how you would guarantee
That you would win that bet against me
Is that i'm going to make a screeching sound through my throat with my mouth closed at the end of every match
That's how you win. That's a guaranteed victory. I'll try it one more time
Here comes the heat
Is that all right?
Right there your ear is poking out
I thought I just got a exe crash. That's what I thought. That was because I wasn't looking show them what we got
Your hair is out. I mean that nothing to do about that hair doesn't count. No, it's it's like my head and face
I don't care. I don't care. I just don't care
It hurts to do that. I don't care
I'm so i'm sitting doing this like lock my head in place routine and I can't play the game get these out of here
No, I don't want to turn the stream off
All right last game. This is gonna be the last game. This is it. I'm gonna try as hard as I can. I'm gonna try to win
rule of thirds
Here comes the heat
Yeah, again, thanks. Uh wanna brothers for sponsoring this part of the stream
Uh, I genuinely do really like this game. I think it's really fun
It is out season two. It's been out for a while or season two hasn't but season one has you know where to get it
There is a current season
uh game
Pass, right i've been losing for fun. No, I was playing something else earlier
You don't play it without being sponsored. I play it. I've actually played it a lot off stream
On the xbox actually show them what we got on a different account
Battle pass. Yeah season battle pass. Yeah. Yeah, there are a lot of mr. Pancakes
Is this also a mr? No, this is the snow guys. It's the same. Mr. Pancake
Let's go down a good one. It's a mirror
Oh, you snuck out. Oh, come on really. Holy shit. How are you still here?
Oh my
I am so confused right now. Will you get off the stage?
Oh
The spike that's a good one to go on him. That was unfortunate
Yeah, let's do another one one more
You end up getting right to the edge of the right right when I did the down and just caught him at the perfect angle
That's that was painful. I would have been annoyed at that one changing to shaggy. Okay
Game is cross play
Yeah, it does. You might run into somebody on the xbox
You might run into somebody on pc playstation really win the final match. We'll find out careful careful
Oh my god
Fine I threw so hard there. Oh, where are you going? Don't even think about it. Oh my god
He beat me
Shit
Oh rematch one more. It's one to one. Come on. We're not doing it like that
That stage is hard because all the stuff on the edge. All right, i'm fine. I'm fine. We're gonna win
Everything's good
Okay, I understand. He's he does he tries to bait you to the edge of the map so he can do the step move
And he tries to jump jump out all the way and do like that's not happening
Sorry, it's just not what we got last match of the night is right here
Okay
That's it
I told you we got this
He jumped so far out man
He did a max jump then another max jump. I am don't look at that
Good matches though. Good fight
Good fight that was a that was tense. I could feel that I toasted back this game just does it to me. I just get so
Intense when I play this hits me in a certain spot and i'm not even that good
Some people that are so good at this game. It just they can just do so much cool stuff. All right, one more funny one, right?
Let's just do like a joke one
Are you over covid yet?
Uh, i've been testing negative so that's good
I definitely still feel a little
sloppy
My throat's still kind of messed up
Um, i'm a little tired still but
I am I would say operating probably like 80 at this point show them what we got
Did you shave your eyebrows and what thanks for watching though guys?
Let's give it a go i haven't played taz in a while
Okay, whoa, whoa, whoa I told you we got this
Good fight is taz a dog taz is a tasmanian devil
Continue
All right. That was fun one more for all time's sake. All right fine one more
I want to get at least one good lebron game in I try to play him in the first 10 minutes and I just
Was bogus. Oh tom and jerry. I haven't seen one of these pretty rare
Is there a stripe announcer pack? They actually might be i'll go check that out before I leave
So if you guys are curious what we're doing, um
Um, we'll be back on monday. I think we're going to continue the sims for
Um mcnulty arc that's what's happening on monday. So that should be fun
All right, this is truly the last one even if I lose I screwed it up. I was trying to do this
And there goes the there goes the second ball great good start
There's but I got no games on lebron in the last like month. There's no way i'm gonna be able to pull this out of my
You know
All right, it's not over it ain't over
I don't understand
I turned it into mario
I literally just like just like just a frozen frame like about jumping what happened. I said good suck. I turned it into one frame
I was just like
I just went that was ridiculous
Level 10 is for the big perk, right?
I'm so sweaty right now
You're gonna try god of war. Um, I don't I gotta play the first one through all the way
I'm gonna play the first four or five hours of the first one. Well
The new first one like that. I can't move
Check it out. Thanks for watching everybody. Appreciate it. I ripped like I ripped this out halfway through when I turned around
I ripped out my headphones accidentally and I couldn't hear anything. I didn't say anything one more
No, that's it. No, no, that's it. That's it. That's it. That's it. That's it
Dude, how is he keep?
He does this like weird rocket move that I land on top of and I just go soaring into outer space
Okay. Nah, that's it. That's it. I had fun
I had my fun
Immediately following this one
Is it immediately concluding this match that's the end of the stream i'm gonna lock in for this one
Show them what we got. All right locking in
Play jack too. I've never played those games. All right, here we go
Scum like this never lasts long
danger
That was fucking wild
Oh, that was tight. That was very tight. Good match. I thought I lost that one for sure
I thought I was done. I thought I was dead in the water
All right, all right thought about it for a second he thought about it
I feel like I might see him. He might change up. We got to go to sleep
Yeah, I mean you can't go out on that one. This is a oh no. Okay
I mean you when you're in a match like that, that's a best of three. You know what i'm saying?
It's not that late show them what we got
7 pm pacific
Can't go out on a heater
Well, I mean it's just this this that was a good match and it's like one to nothing right now
We just gotta make it happen. Let's go
Damn what a move
It's too good. That was uh, that's cheese. I got cheese. I got cheese. I got cheesecakes
That was a cheesecake move. That was a good match. That was a really good match. We're gonna do one more. I um,
Very good. Very very good match
You got me now. It's time for me to get serious. I you I can't just leave that guy just absolutely slam dunked on my head
Shattered the rim all the glass just fell all over me. I can't just go out on that
I got he slammed dunked on my head
Like i've it's one to one right now. You need to take the l it's one to one. Nobody's believing
All right, you gotta believe I know that trick now. I'm not gonna fall for that trick. This is it. This is the one
The stage I don't like this stage. Sorry. Here we go. Three two one action
Why did I press?
My fingers are so greasy. Everything's falling off the controller. You have no idea
Let's just go to the game. He's just gonna get plays a lot. He's just going to the game. He plays a lot
That's it
All right, it's been fun. It's been fun. Just wipe all the water off the controller can't go out on the loss
Polish this up a little you can't leave us like that. No, I can't you're right. You're right. I'm gonna get my ass kicked
It's all right. Why am I so addicted to this game?
All right. No, i'm good. Those are some good games that play that guy was really good at the game
He was just a better player and he got the opportunities, you know, like the catch down like you know what I mean?
This is a good player. All right, let's see how long I can last here get away from the edge
I have a terrible edge game. It's like the worst part about all of my gameplay
All right, we're good. We're good. We're good. We're good
That's not like a seal
Stop, this is a close game
Stop, I can't even land him. Oh, check it out. We only get stuck
Remember you're supposed to hit the other player. I want that person timed out for one second
That was fun. This game's really fun got really into it. All right, I gotta call it. I gotta call it
I'm getting too addicted. That's it. You can't end on a loss. Yeah, I can because it's a quite a few games
I play ending a loss the last few really brought my
My thing down. All right, that's it. Let me look i'm gonna look at the battle pass for a second. That's a lot of fun
I don't really play video games that well
Right, but when you sit down and you play a game like this and you just try hard
You get into it you get like oh, it's a really great feeling
Good games all the players
You deserve your wins
That was a lot of fun and Warner Brothers. Thank you again for sponsoring. I
It's it's so much fun. I'm happy to do it
Hopefully the the streams are fun to watch. I feel like they have fun to play so
Big huge. Thank you to Warner Brothers again
And uh play first games obviously so that is going to be the end of this
It is available right now if you want to get it. It's free. It's on everything playstation steam
It's season two right now. I think marvin martian is coming really soon. The netcode is phenomenal
I think it's really worth playing. I genuinely believe that so thanks again one brothers. Thanks for watching
Thanks to you for watching as well and i'll see you guys on monday
We will do some sims 4 is it on xbox? Yep
We'll go back to the mcnulty family and I need to go take a cold shower because I am sweating
It was a lot of fun though looking forward to what season two has to offer and that's it. Appreciate it everybody
Yeah, i'm definitely feeling better
So we'll see over the next couple days if I get back to pretty much normal
Again grotto beasts dot net is a sign up there. We're trying to sit
We're really trying to figure out how much inventory we're going to need
So if you really do think you're going to want it go sign up on that page because we need to figure out how much inventory we need
That's coming very soon
Keep an eye on the discord as well because the end of the year awards
Uh nominations are going to open the categories will be there just like previous years
So keep an eye this weekend on the discord we will obviously be it'll be announcement for it and i'll talk about it later
too
This coming week on monday
See for the sims 4 and we also got a christmas stream. So a lot of exciting things happening
Hope they are good
Take care of yourselves everybody. Good night
And I will talk to you guys very soon. See you monday around 1 pm. Same time. We're trying to beat the internet crashing
so
And all of you that stayed and stuck around for the multiverse's stream
I appreciate it
Hope it's still fun to watch. It's definitely fun to play
And i'll see you later. Good night. Goodbye
Take care