Hey, what is going on, everybody? Jerma here with Facecam Fortress 2, Saturday's edition,
for people on the point right now. We're gonna take care of that right now. Oh, did that
hit anybody? Apparently not. Come on, get lit. Playing as the Pyro with the Scorch Shot,
as you can see on the screen, the Flowgestinator, Flowgeistinator, however you want to pronounce
that freaky weapon, and the Neon Annihilator, trying to get a little interesting setup going
here. Whoa, whoa, whoa, lag. What the hell was that? Trying to get an interesting setup.
I'll explain it in a second once I have a second here. Oh, come here. Oh, oh, oh, flug.
Oh, where are they? Where are they? Where are these rat bastards? Oh, sneak attack, baby.
Oh, boy. Maybe not. Oh, crits. Oh, hey, how you doing? Oh, my God, it's chaos. This is
absolute chaos. Oh, my God. Oh, my God. Dude, dude, this is chaos. I just killed like nine
people. Okay, so let me... Oh, heal me, please. Let me try and explain what I was trying to
say in the very beginning. Oh, my God. This weapon is such a goofy weapon. I always forget.
Come here. Oh, get... Well, that was absolutely insane. Let's do this. So what I wanted to talk
about in this video has to do with the scorch shot and the flow-gistinator. Whoa, I just like
freaked myself out right there. It has to do with the combination of these two items and how they
can be very, very good when used together. Now, that can be said about the detonator as well,
but I feel like with the detonator, you do more damage, but you still have to detonate it.
And I'm one of those people that I like all the stuff done for me. So it's detonating it by itself
when you knock into somebody or when you hit a ground, and plus it knocks people away too.
And I was a very, very big advocate of somebody that was against this item when it released,
and I'm starting to have second thoughts about it. I think this could really be an interesting
item when you use it in the right situations. But we are back here now at their spawn,
and let's see if we can't be a real, real bastard here. So you know what? They're all out there. I
might as well just go to this. No, I'm not going to, I'm not going to hang out here.
Let's go up to where they are. Oh my God. Come to Papa.
That's the music I want playing when I have the plug detonator up.
When I do the crits, that's the song I want playing.
Dun, dun, dun, dun, dun, dun, dun, dun, dun. If only I had custom sounds.
All right, get on that point. We're already on it. Oh, they got a sentry.
That's not cool. That is not cool, man. Click, click, click, click, click. Boom. Boom. I love
the sound this thing makes too. It's so awesome. Also using the neon annihilator. I almost said
lionator. I've been watching too much Game of Thrones. He's a lion. He's a Lannister.
Oh, that was pretty sweet shot. Just defend the point. Keep the point defended until King Kong
and Godzilla come have like an epic battle. Come here. Yeah, you can blast me around all you want.
It's still going to be a firefight, bro. Damn. Damn. Not good. Not good. Where are you going,
man? Pyro versus Pyro. Come on. That's what it's all about. Damn. I got to get that hit.
I got to hit somebody with this. Damn. Come on. I got to get to somebody live with this thing.
Oh my God. Why can I not hit anybody? I don't know where the health packs are.
Oh, you son of a... I was going to light that guy on fire from behind,
activate my crits while he activated his crits. Man, that was going to be crit-ception.
It just didn't happen. Damn. It's all right. They're going to win. Just run. Just barrel
right through. Oh, this guy had the same idea. I need a medic. I need a medic. Where are you going?
What? I thought that was a spy that backstabbed me. I got like launched. Wow. Good show, bro. Good
show. No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no. Come on, King Kong. I want to activate my King Kong powers
and have them drop from the ceiling. Why am I looking at my actual ceiling? Instead of looking
up like this, I looked over at my actual ceiling when I said that. Let me get an overheal. All
right. We can't... They can't just take this from us like this. Time to activate the flog rage.
Oh, rage. We got it. Damn. I got to hit him. Oh my God. I can't even air blast that either.
I got to work on my skill here. Finally. There we go. Knock him around. Now he's going to run.
He's going to think I'm going to chase him. I'm not. This is so stupid. Oh my God. I'm going to
run out of bullets. Okay. Now I have to... Okay. Come on. Come on. Come on. Did he just blow himself
up? I think he just blew himself up. Oh, crits. Crits everywhere. I'm holding down the button. I
don't know where anybody is. Come here. Dude, this is ridiculous. I love this. It's so goofy.
Come on. We got to hold him. We got to hold him. This guy won't die. Oh, somebody on it. Somebody
on it. Knock him off. This is it. Oh my God. This is going to come down to the wire. Oh, oh,
no. Oh, this is bad. Get him off. Oh, good game. Good font game guys. I'll take that loss. That was
a close game. Over time, over time. Holy crap. Let's do another one. Nobody, nobody. Engineer on here
would be really fun. Whoa. My God. Where did that guy come from? That guy just like launched out of
nowhere. Oh, no. This is bad. Oh, this is bad. Get one of them. Get this other guy too. Did you see
that medic though? That was crazy. That medic just like appeared right in front of my face.
He must've jumped down from the balcony. Respawn. Man, my whole body hurts right now. Every time I
move my arms, my whole body hurts because I was at the gym and I went... Oh my God. I'm
going to get beat right here. Oh, nice shot. That was like a little pellet shot. But anyways,
yeah. Whenever I do this, I got back to the gym. And if you remember old, old, old German channel,
I used to go to the gym all the time. I used to go to the gym literally... We were getting spawn
camped. Literally every day I would go to the gym and I... That hasn't been happening lately. I've
been going to the gym like once every like three months and I really want to change that.
So I went back the other day and if you don't go to the gym for a while after going for a long time,
every... Why am I not... What was just going on right there? I was holding it on their backs.
My ping is 11. What? But anyways, when you go to the gym, if you haven't gone for a long time,
your whole body hurts. I did curls and I seriously feel like I want to die right now. Let me get some
heals, man. Let me get some of those. Let me get some of those beautiful heals. Whoa. Please heal
me. Oh my God. Oh my God, man. Oh my God. I'm stuck right here. I need to get like one hit on
somebody. Geez. There it is. There it is. That's what I wanted. Get rid of this. Oh yeah.
That was beautiful. That was so lucky, man. I can't believe I did not die from that. Same with
that. I should have bled to death right there. No, this is where we go down. Oh, so much stress.
Hi. How are you doing? My name is Joma. What's your name? Oh God. Night of Purgatory. Interesting
name. Very interesting. Dr. Pepper. Dr. Pepper. Oh, you make the world taste better. Remember
that jingle? 30 seconds. We're going to lose. Come on, guys. I have faith. The Flawgistinator
has faith. Damn. Oh, he's. No. All right. 50s. I got to change to something else. Boy, before pyros.
Soldier. Soldier with whatever. That's fine. I'm just going to like rocket jump over there.
Come on. Oh, we're going to get it. Teleporter. Where's it going to take me? Come on. There we go.
Get me over there. Oh, that was a bad rocket jump. And so is that. What did I hit the ceiling?
Oh, God. Fantastic. Just got it. Oh, get them off. Covet and P. Why am I doing that? I should
just shoot. Oh, they have a sentry too. You know, back to pyro. No, stay soldier. I don't know what
to do. I'm so scared right now because they only have one second. No, I'm staying soldier.
I'm going to stay soldier right now. Level one. Not worth the wait. They have one second.
Get me over there. Hey, hello, Mr. Spy. Hello. No, no, no, no, no, no, no. Wow. He could have
just won that. I fell down the stairs. Oh, man. Maybe I should have like not picked up. No,
this is bad. Scout. Scout. I'm just like being an idiot with the soldier right now. Let's just
regular scatter gun guillotine. I didn't like relax. I'm going crazy. I'm just so scared of that one
second. We're okay now. We're okay now. See if I can guillotine some mother effer. Oh, sister lag.
Just hit that into a wall apparently. Two scouts, two scouts. Oh, what do we got? What do we got?
Oh, you son of a. You son of a. Hey, I'm not really doing a whole lot, but my team is
really pulling through right here. Maybe I could even go back to pyro. No,
it's going to be five pyros on the team if I do that. We'll stick with this.
We'll stick with this for the last 30 seconds. Why not? Let me just scoop somebody up with this.
Come on. And nope. Shoot him in his face. Oh my God. So the last like two and a half minutes,
I think I've killed one person and I've just been like jumping around like a freak. Hey,
whatever works, right? I think that's going to be it. Hey, we did it. Ghost buster. Third place as
the scout, except that didn't really happen at all. But yeah, that's going to wrap things up,
guys. Thank you so much for watching. I really do appreciate it. And I'll see you guys all next
time. And of course, take care everybody. This is going to grow from here to here. That's a lie.
I would never get that up that big.