Hey, what's up?
Still late?
Oh, I am very late. I'm sorry, but you know, hold on. I'm like gonna fuck up
Uh, I had I had to use the bathroom
I had to uh, whatever. I'll do it. Who cares?
I really need to tell you what I was doing
Let me just let me just tell you it was gross
Anyways, how you doing? Welcome to a stream
How are you? Good to see you again
Dude what the fuck tmi what stop
Oversharing
um
For all, you know
I don't know. I could have been brushing my teeth
And I like oh my breath was bad
What where's your why is your mind?
so
Where are you going? Stop?
Anyways, how you doing?
Welcome to another stream
I had a lot to go over today
first of first of all
Let's talk about this
Uh
Playing hylix tonight. You probably saw by the incredible title
Which I have not updated
Uh one of the mods will fix it probably like an hour
Oh, yeah
I
It is the way it is the way that it's gonna be for now
Yeah, i've heard this game is very weird
I've been told it's gonna be right up my alley. It's not that long, but we'll see
I've heard that before
I've heard it's very good
There's also a sequel. So if I like this
then
I have probably played the sequel at some point
We have grotto beast stuff to go over a little bit later as well
kind of a
secondary clarification
An amendment to the faq we saw a couple days ago
A lot of really good news with grotto beasts
I'm also going to show the box today. I'll make sure to show you what you're getting. There are some things missing from this box
because
They were
Yeah, I didn't mind out of the grotto beast group chat is gonna be mad at me if I say anything else
Yeah, some things are missing from this box. I just want to give you a basic idea of what you're what you can expect
But that's the plan
That's the plan for today
No, this is by the this is not an unboxing. This is not an unboxing. This is essentially
These are printing samples
Is what these are
Because everything is still in production right now
So these are printing samples just want to show you what you're planning on getting
No, there's no i'm not gonna be there's no pack openings. That's not i'm just this is these are printing samples for you to see
What is being printed?
Unbox, please
It doesn't exist. I'm telling you
All right, but anyways very excited. It's been going incredibly well
Everybody on the grotto beast team is is completely blown away. It's been more than we ever thought
so
People go over it all
But I want to obviously not do it immediately i'm gonna do the same thing like we did a few days ago
I'm gonna play hylix for a little bit
And then we'll move into that
So let's go you guys ready
Heard this game is a little weird
But let's uh, let's just chill and play it gonna be kind of a chill stream today. I really well besides maybe the grotto beast stuff
but
Uh, I kind of want to just relax
That's what we're gonna do
Let's see what we got here
There it is. I wonder how loud this game is gonna be
I gotta get comfortable
I think it's arrow keys
Yeah, i'm not comfy right now. This is a
Bullshit
There we go. All right, let's get started
Here we go
cool
hylix
If you want me to explain what this game is
Um, I don't I have no idea. All I know is that it's a it's a game. Let's go
psychic land
Miraculously purifies the chemicals people hark out of a field. It is a chemical below a product. It is a memory
beside truth
Meanwhile, give me king of the moon
Works a engine
Beside the shrunken vessel memory the title what you guys are gonna get me in trouble
Thus your story begins act one. Okay
Interesting, so it's arrow keys or wsd. Yeah arrow keys interesting. All right, so this is a different character
It's your life savings. You got 53 bucks 53 bucks. It's not that's not a lot. Meow. Is that cat learned?
a
Blative hollow
Pleather what did I learn? This is a horror game. I don't think it's a horror game
I think it's more of a surreal experience learned a blative hollow leather
So you're gonna people are gonna be like, oh wow. Yeah, he what is that? I think it just makes noise
Outside you accidentally crushed it. Oh shit. Oops trash can lid was found. Okay, I got a trash can lid
But yeah, I want to go upstairs bugs. Those buzz. It's buzz. Maybe you should bathe
Okay, your flesh and will were restored toilet paper was found. Okay, cool. I got toilet paper warm burrito was found
Let's wait what you sure that's what that is. I don't I don't
Yeah, I don't know about that one. I don't know about that one. That's fucking gross
All right. Do I have a okay? Hold on. Yeah, I did as you see I did just want to make sure that I could capture this game
So I did open it for like two minutes. I didn't do anything
I didn't touch anything but we can just save over this. There we go
Things warm burrito plus one revives dead and restores 50 flesh. Okay
Instruments outfits can be worn. Wait, I can I can wear this. These are items. Okay, that's cool get dressed
Okay, trash can lid and toilet paper. Is that doing anything?
For me, I have a pistol a trash can lid and toilet paper. I'm ready chip chip chip
Oh, yeah
More this is animals acquired a vegetable. Ooh, okay
Can I take them all I think I can this is bad. This is bad. I'm not be doing this
This is just kind of like a garden like a vegetable garden or something things. Oh shit. I have 13 vegetables
50% of flesh and removes a negative status. Okay. Well, actually it is a good thing to have a weird house
Okay, hold on. What about back here? He's finally playing it. I know a lot of people were waiting for this
All right, who are you for the northeast is the juicy city of bang refrit?
May its apparel endure a thousand years inside correct fire, but far beyond government
What doth
Deli kitley remember our sustenance of field to the northeast is the forbidden city of azul
Nurpan may its vacuum endure that what's going on change the soundtrack. Is this guy just dancing in here?
Wait, how do I get out of here? Oh, I like this song. Oh, it's just random. Okay, it's random text generation
That's funny. I don't want to miss any easter eggs. Whoa. Okay, where do I go?
Also nor upon the forbidden city actualize despite another crystal extrudes below her sound not below her product
Everybody's so weird remarkably falsify burning extra eyes. He considers it near a high lick memory
What is high lick ahead lies mount morn footh?
Beware of the wicked cone cultists all these things talk welcome to azul norpan the forbidden city
I grow the insects chest over here. There's a stick of dynamite in the box. Of course you take it
Yep, hold on. What about over here and go up here pardoned fate. He was pleasantly smearing another wheels
Cavity. Oh what you want to use the tub? It's going to be 25 bucks. No, thank you. You stink
No, i'm not spending that I like this letter
So do I need to talk to anybody like should I be talking to anyone or is it just kind of just random nonsense?
You can learn special abilities from the televisions which are scattered throughout this realm. Ah
Sorry, I did that already. I got one when fighting a flesh stash
You must attack then rest and then guard lest you suffer the creatures
Really the night pawn gorma is said to be immune to the deadly touch of ambulant skulls
He resides on an island of the west behind a sealed door
My armors will raise your maximum flesh points some have additional bonuses behold their magnificence
Torso should I buy one of these is it worth getting some of the stuff looks like it can take about one or two hits
And then it's gone
3 000 bucks. What the hell are you talking about? You only have 53 bucks. Yeah
Uh, no, I don't want it. It's too expensive
Please speak at me over the counter. Oh, sorry. You heard about our bleak cellophane
Quick describes this as a milspec bio mod allows wearer to wield two weapons
Formed into a nugget for easy portability 20% of wearers normal attacks inflict poison
Okay, so it's a bunch of okay. This is a bunch of like status armor. Oh wait television television
Microwaves of yeah, you don't have frozen. Yeah, I do. Oh, no, that was a toilet burrito
Frozen burritos can be effective projectiles feel safe when you walk outside
Oh what 50 50 bucks nice title, dude. I didn't make the title. My title is really boring and plain
Uh, should I was there another way to go? I had a perfectly plain title. It was plain
Let me ask you something when you get a bagel do you get a plain bagel does it have to be something wacky?
When was the last time you had a plain bagel just a plain just regular bagel
I feel like to me it's got to be there's got to be something on it everything bagel
Seeds, you know like cheese on it and stuff like that, you know, they bake them with stuff in it
I'd like a plain bagel, but I don't think i've had one in a long time. It's usually like an everything bagel onion bagel
Yep, onion bagel everything bagel is what I buy. I don't buy plain bagels. It's kind of interesting
All right, so I did that
I've seen this need an instrument
I buy this I buy the bat i'm gonna buy it. I don't care. It's probably stupid
People can be really mad at me about it. There we go. So they're wait. This is like I have weapons and items
Shrish found meat. Yeah, that trash man
Those of you that have been around for a long time. Do you remember that was a sub sound for a while?
That was one of my favorites. Yeah
The trash man
Okay, let's go. Wait, I didn't go in here. You're the bug guy, right?
She's more beast than prison now. Did I go in here? Yes. All right, so let me leave
I got what I wanted. Let's explore the rest of this place the bird sound
You know the bird sound I actually am sad that I did because a sub sound is like, okay
everybody pause for a second the
We're gonna the funny line is gonna be said the bird sound
Ruined old streams because it was just noise that just would happen randomly instead of it being like
I'm in the middle of saying something or talking. It's oh, hey guys. And by the way, here's what we're what
The trash man everybody stops and we just listen to it for a second
But eventually it got to a point where it was so in the background
That you would just randomly talking over me would be like
I've gone back and watched old vods and gone. Oh, but turn that off. Okay, so I looked at that
Let's look at this
Can I go that way? Whoa, can I not leave yet? Can we just listen to this for a second? You watch yourself?
No, but sometimes I'll go back and just check on old vods and stuff
You know, you never know. I just want to know I want to see if what kind of
Something interesting too is I've been doing this for like 12 13 years now
That's kind of interesting sometimes just to go back and be like what was I like like five years ago two years ago
Eight years ago interesting sometimes
So looking at old photos. I mean, I don't do this that often
This is maybe like once every maybe like once every year or two
I'll go back and look at some stuff interesting and we've done this on stream before. What do you mean?
Mysterious tower do not touch the ambulant skulls or you will die to initiate warp make contact with the central node
Unauthorized access is discouraged. Thank you for understanding. Am I gonna fight mirror delusions may rock this sort of chemical
Warp access is currently infested creature spirit the dotted red line
It will not cross it. Enjoy your time in the warp access like a safe zone. What does it go? Are these enemies?
These are enemies
Okay. Whoa. Oh my god. I'm gonna die. How do I run? How do I run? I'm gonna die
I think i'm gonna die right now. When's the last time I saved the game? How do I run?
I haven't saved the game in like 20 30 minutes. How do I run? You can't am I in trouble?
Wait, I could eat a bunch of vegetables. Is that am I all right?
Should I just you can't run should I just eat vegetables and just make it happen? Wayne was slain
What what the hell just happened? So this is the afterlife feel free to crash on the couch
You can use the machine over there to convert any meat you found into flesh points
I have a meat deposited one meat into the grinder your maximum flesh point rose, too
That's cool. And these are fast travel points. I get it. But where am I?
Where did I end up hot dog was found creepy. You can build sand castles on the beach. Try using the space bar
What oh cool
All right, hold on. I don't care if this takes me like half an hour. Oh, sorry nice
No, I want I want just like yeah like that. There you go. That's not bad toss fish into the ocean
No, okay. Well, uh, yeah, maybe maybe you belong in there. You all right?
I I didn't know this was I thought this could have been poisoned for all I know
I think I can hear a tv set behind this wall if I had dynamite I could put
This is where you learn abilities learned calibration. I love this game. Hilux 2 is also really good
No, i'm into it. I'm into it for sure powers. Okay guards and heals 30 percent temporarily increases in mightiness
Very cool. Let me actually save it though, bro. Are you high? Wait, what are you doing back out here? Are you drunk?
No, like I told you for the last like couple of years the last like a year and a half two years
I have not at all
It's just it's just I have such attention problems in the first place
That it became really clear that I was just fucking myself up so bad
Even when not even just like taking a little sometimes so it's just like no no, not anymore
Not anymore. Can I throw these into the ocean? Wait rest on the couch take a nap?
Yeah, take a nap on the couch. I'm just probably full heel
I'm with the lilies floats the moth the mole along his galleries goeth in the dark earth. Okay, so that's a full heel
Responsible germa. Yeah, I mean, I don't know such an active crystal to tether the portal
Oh, this is where I'd be teleporting to. All right, let's go to the orange one. Very cool. All right this game
Just leveled up it and me caring about it juice box. This is back in the city, but I didn't have the juice box
All right. So this so this is like the town with the shops. This is my house
This is a some kind of monument or tower or something. This was where I got killed
So where do I go from here? Go back to that other place and just try not to die or try to avoid don't fight anything
Just avoid stuff. Yeah
So many of them access warp where we going oh god, what's this thing? I want a paper cup. What is that?
Well, I know what a paper cup is. But what is that fucking brain mysterious glyphs and vegetal motifs adorned?
So this is a key. Okay. Oh dear. I'm kind of scared about where I am right now
If I touch these is it a fight? I'm afraid I don't want to touch anything. Oh, no
Okay, good somebody's house over here. It is somebody's house. You got a lot of money in there
All right. Do you want a paper cup? Um, this vault is off limits, please go away. Thank you in advance for your cooperation
It's like i'm gonna have to destroy you if you don't leave you made me do this
Most delay day I summon thee. Holy shit. Oh, yeah
Yes
That's weird
Everybody missed
Oh, all right. I'm gonna reload. I'm gonna reload. I just want to see what happened. I just want to see what happened
I'm reloading. I won't I promise I won't save scum. Uh, how do I oh I can't save scum. Yeah
Dying. Okay, you're supposed to very I get it. I get it
But I want to I want to go back there. Okay, does the yoinkies flunky
I think that's a that's not quite that plus the yoinkies flunky is something I I you guys gave that term
To a little thing I did on the dollhouse stream. I mean that wasn't a dance
That was just you guys called it that so I mean, is that really a dance? I said it
Did I make that up? No, I didn't. All right. So I think I think I saw everything I need to see here
Let me see. What about the pick? Can I take the paper cup anywhere here? I feel like I might be able to
What about can I go that way like up there? How do I get down there? All right, I gotta find a way up there
Get out of the way cult permits nothing to leave mournful in this way. They hope to promote a reverse erosion. What's this stuff?
Everybody's hitting the yoinkies flunky. Oh, this is mount mournful
These enemies holy shit. There's a lot of money 50 bucks
Does this have controller support? Can I plug my controller in and move or no? No, okay doubt it
What about this?
So should I just be avoiding enemies because i'm not strong enough just collecting money. Oh teleporter. Yes
What is going on in here? Is this tv? That's tv, isn't it? Is that not a tv sleep here?
Um paper cup if I sleep in here, what do I do with this? Is this a tv?
I don't think this is a tv the cup you found it. I'm an expert in the usage of the paper cup
Please allow me to accompany you one day. We may come across another artifact from the old times which will require the paper cup
Uh, okay magnificent. I will guide you when the time comes isn't a party member
What do you have dirk party member? Can you watch this tv? Where on earth are we now? What is this?
This is weird. What's the x for? Okay. Is that an enemy? I don't know. What's an enemy or a friend?
I am the sage of brains. I grant you my token
Got sage's token seek my siblings the sage of computers and the sage of death. It will also give you tokens
But therein lies the path to the enlightenment. Nice. This is the life. This is the life. I like the little birds. It's cute
I like them. All right, I feel like that's important
Should we use the paper cup here?
We can use a paper cup with this machine your companion places the paper cup into a recess on the front of the machine and
presses a small blue lever fluid flows from the reservoir into the paper cup you drink it and
Your will is permanently increased by 25 points. Oh hell. Yeah, very nice
Maybe we could uh, fuck some stuff up now. Do you think i'm strong enough? We got uh, two people here i'm going for it
Okay, we got attack cone cultist attack cone cultist. All right, I can I can do it. I love the snap. It's cool
What about um, I think i'm all right. All right wayne's crew was victorious 150 bucks who died
Oh, I thought it was wait. Can I like do anything with that? I think scary. I don't like that thing
All right. Do you have any special attacks panorama can confuse enemies? Let's try it. Okay confused. Oh shit
Use vegetable
That's cool looking
I think i'm all right. Yeah, let's kill
Take another uh vegetable
Good and clean it up
150 bucks frozen burrito meat meat meat
All right, easy. I don't want to I don't want to aggro that thing. All right. I'm good for now. I'm good for now
I don't I don't want to die
There's a tv right here
Get over here get over here
space shurikens
Cool this game looks neat. This game is pretty neat. I don't want to miss anything though. Hold on
Shit. All right. I don't want to get like collapsed on is that it? Okay. Yeah, that's it. I got a lot of money
I'm gonna go buy stuff. Oh, this is more money money money. You found 50
Money, make sure I don't miss it. Yep. See this is why it's kind of like a maze too. It's fun
If I aggro this thing am I dead dead dead like no like guaranteed. Oh fuck. I'm terrified of this thing
I don't know how strong it is 103 bucks. Damn. Uh, let's take out one more. Oh, what is that double damage and
vegetable to wain
44 colon statue that thing's got to go first. I think it's got a lot of health
I think we're all right
Yeah, we're good
175 meat meat a lot of meat for the uh, the meat grinder. He said it. Oh my god. He said it finally finally
clip clip that
Get that part
Drag forward to a timeline clip the end of that 12 seconds. Got it upload
Is there more money? I thought there was more money somewhere
Uh, i'm gonna have to fight. Okay. This is not great probably causes enemies to fall asleep. Um, let's try it. Damn it
Oh, no, we're good
Did they all fall asleep? Okay, two of them did
All right. We gotta we we gotta do some damage
calibration on you
and then you do
shurikens
Here it is. Oops. I don't know the I don't know the order. Oh, um, oops it is
Why they wait, they all got it. Wait, why did they all get it? They all got it. What just happened
They all just got it
Why did this do it to everybody?
They get it from okay. They got it from the statue. I was gonna say what?
Come on, man
Thankfully, two of them are still asleep
Juice box, right? Yeah
Cool. All right, they're asleep
Now I now that I have mightiness up
Let's do this
That's gonna be huge
54 damage right now get out of here
Oh that one was asleep. I'm an idiot. It's all right. I'll get it. I figured it out
I don't think I need to eat anything or I think i'm good
Backgrounds are really trippy. They're really crazy
All right
I think I want to go buy stuff
Is there anywhere I can go from here? Is it just that's it?
I think that's it. I did the paper cup here. I already got it. Yeah, I have a lot of money
I'm gonna go buy stuff. I want to watch this but the visuals are giving me a headache
Should there be something in the title? It just says like the you know, hey like
Visuals are like kind of trippy or something. Probably not a bad idea
I guess it's not too too bad, right? Not enough for like a warning
I don't know. What do you guys think?
Maybe like an eye strain warning
It's fine. It's fine. It's fine
It doesn't seem dangerous. No, I don't think so
eye strain
warning eye strain incoming
I said this actually is fine for me. I'm very sensitive to stuff like this and I've
Um, i've been okay
oops
I didn't mean to do what did I just do skip?
warning don't watch
Stop missing
Oh my god, we're gonna die
finally
Oh my god
Are we this oh wicked with blind?
Okay, well
You know something that removes this status effects, right?
Veggies do
I have a lot of money
We gotta go. I have like a couple at least two or three thousand bucks. Don't I? All right. What do you sell? Okay
turbo tendons
allows where to wield two weapons
20% of where's normal attacks inflict poison. Okay, so should should somebody have poison or is this too expensive for right now?
Get cellophane how many like two three? I don't want to spend that much. All right, i'll get two
This is i'm gonna get this so I want someone to have that
So this is this prevents blind and this is poison poison damage and then they no prevents blind set
That's actually huge right now anything else for me to purchase. There's another strap too in there. Yeah, what do you got l?
Giant metal dome apparel too large to be worn with any other armor. What does it do plus 50 plus 50 what armor?
I mean, that's pretty good
So but I can't wear this with anything else so I wouldn't be able to have this and the sunglasses on i'll get it
Okay, is that worth it? What is it? What stats is it increasing 30 30 everything looks the same
It's just an armor rating. Well, might as well give that to you. It's flesh slash health. Oh, okay
Oh that may okay. Look at 140 health. Holy smokes. That's a lot. My tortoise is watching this stream
She hates you but I think she likes the game. Okay, I think that's good
Can I where do I buy vegetables like i'm running out? Is there another there's another store here, right?
Or can you only get them from the garden? They grow infinitely. Oh that I was gonna say that makes sense
Um, um, um, somebody said that song was scratching their frontal lobe. I feel like I may have missed a secret or two here
Maybe I have trashcan
I already got it. Didn't I or is there another trash can? Oh there is 47 bucks in here. Check the tv again
Okay, something else. Um, all right now i'm pretty decked out now. I'm going to do that other stuff
I'm going to where I got in trouble last time. That's a good idea and we're probably
I think i'm gonna show some grotto bee stuff talk about it for a little bit. I think I was gonna wait like an hour
We've got to go over some questions and some answers. I want to show the box. I have it here
We can go over some stuff like give me one second. I'm gonna this can just stay right here
Yeah, we'll come right back to this. I just want to show
Actually, let me get that here. All right, I want to go over
Since grotto beasts has gone into presale. I really want to go over some of the more
Some amendments to that faq and this this whole thing is going to get pieced together in any of this faq stuff that you guys
Have seen so far will be on the website
We just want to clean it up and make sure it's correct
but there's a lot of stuff to go over because
We have uh, we have hit a very very interesting milestone and uh, we'll talk about it
So let's start we're gonna start at the top. Here comes another presentation
Presentation incoming it is only one slide this time. So don't worry. It's not like 10 slides. Let's
Do that right now. Let me get it up. It's only one slide
Yeah
There were just some other things we wanted to make sure people were aware of and i'm just going to read this stuff pretty much
Line by line powerpoint. Okay, let me get it up here
Okay
Okay, let's go over this because these are this is going to answer some questions
And go over some important, um store updates dates and limited items. Okay, so there's a lot of text on this screen
So just be aware. I want to get it on one slide. Here we go
Here are some clarifications and amendments to what we talked about two three days ago. So
Grotto beasts is in presale right now. It's available right now on grottobeasts.net. This is very yeah, there's a lot of text
I'm gonna read it
So we've had a lot of questions since this and don't skip ahead. Don't skip. I know you're gonna read ahead
Don't skip ahead wait for me to read. Oh shit cartoon mischief
All right, so we've had a lot of questions about the holographics
Wait, you've got four different holographic types. Does that mean that each card could have a holographic and four different versions?
No, there are four types of holographic film and each card has a specific holographic film type assigned to it
So for example, you will you should never find a fretsal right here that has anything but a hollow dot pattern
So I think a lot of people were saying whoa
That seems like a lot of potential holographics for if it's each one has the no, no, no, they're all assigned
So that we've had that question come in a lot
So we've also we've numbered our production so that every booster pack will have one rare card and exactly one holographic card in every booster pack
So what that means the hollow is one random card which can be either rare or common so some packs
Will potentially have two rares. We've got that question a lot too
Now for some store updates
Let's go over some updates on the store
Uh, do not read the second line yet. I know you already have but it's fucking crazy
We are going to let everyone know when we have an exact date in mind for the presale to end
The store may halt for a while in that period and depending on inventory
We'll need to see what items will be available for when we leave presale up
This will be at least 10 to 14 days from now
So we don't have a hard date for the end of the presale, but it will be at least another two weeks
So if you are buying it right now
We're trying to keep the presale up as long as we can
And the reason why we're doing that is because of the second line here
So the initial production of the boosters have all been claimed
So the boosters of of our first production run here have been claimed
So
We're already in contact with the printer to scale up the production and order more
We want I want to touch again on this presale strategy. It's important
We didn't want our inventory currently in production to sell out
Ship out and have a secondary market takeover for people that didn't get in on the presale and wanted to claim items
This presale is going to continue normally
But those of you buying booster packs now, which is over our current inventory
You're going to need to wait a little longer for the till the next order
Uh, we'll get some better dates for you in the near future
But I we want to make sure we can make this really clear that there's going to be a waiting period
For boosters purchased as of this period now after the first shipments go out. This is very corporate
It has to be because I want to make sure I get this correct
so
That being said the availability the
This is not corporate anymore
The availability of the two player starter kits as I just heard holly laugh
As of this stream right now are not affected by the new production order
So people are still claiming through the stock and each kit has two boosters in it
So right now we've not gone through all of the starter kits
So those you're still fine if you if you're during the presale buying them now if you do
Uh, those as well as the first run of boosters are planning to ship out after the presale ends
So the starter kits are still available and it's not that boosters are not available
It's just the the second order
Of boosters is gonna you you'll get it later
It's gonna be a I don't want to give you a date because we don't really know
But it shouldn't be that long, but it will be a little longer. So we want to make sure people know this
also
Important some of the we didn't make well
I want to make sure we mentioned this some of the apparel and prints are only available for a limited time until march 31st
So the the 40 the original 40 beast shirts the art prints
The grotto beast logo hat and beanies and the glow in the dark version of that ghost hoodie and tee
Are all leaving the store on the 31st. That's the plan now. I want to talk about this
Get off my screen get off my screen
So the age rating on the box, I want to make this really clear
So it's listed as six plus as more of a guideline for the physical product
There are dice in here. We wanted people to make sure that there are small pieces in here
Because if you bought this and that and there was no like, you know minimum sort of age rating on it
There are there are small physical pieces in here and we just want to make sure people know that
also
Very important. This is a mature audience channel and although there are no pieces of explicit language or imagery
There are still references to tobacco cartoon violence cartoon mischief. It's it's stream references
So if you're like think about that, right?
There are references to characters here that might not be appropriate for little kids
But we try to make this project be as general audience as possible
But also keep in mind this is channel merch for this community first and foremost
This is merch for you guys
Merch for the community. That's all this project ever was intended to be so just be aware
That there are references to mature audience streams, even though we tried
To make this as general audience as we could you understand do you feel me outrage tobacco?
But you know, we want to make this clear for people
There are definitely going to be people that stumble upon this project and just potentially have no idea who the fuck I am
We just want people to know this
I do not understand
so
With all this being said are we clear on this stuff? Are we clear on these? Is everybody clear?
Can you please put this into simpler terms?
Um, no, I can't
That'll get me in trouble
No, I cannot because I want to make sure we're very clear on what's happening
I'll look over at the grotto bees group chat and it'll be in all capitals
Stop, stop, stop, stop. Can you explain this in family guy terms? No, I don't think I I don't think I can so
I it's time
I want to show you some things. He makes us sound so angry. No, they're i'm kidding
It's been it's a they're a wonderful group over there. I promise. I'm just kidding around
They are I have some things here that I would like to show you guys ready
Are you ready for me to reveal it? Stop bumping the mic. I'm not trying to
I'm gonna show you multiple things because it's kind of interesting how this plays out just sip my drink
Okay, let's go like this. Let's go like this
And then let's go like this
Oh, they can see me. Hold on. Hold on
Hi, how are you? Where are you? Where the heck are you? No, you're up there. Good to see you again
Uh, we're gonna go over the box. You got a full beard. It's hey, it's been kind of a wild couple of weeks
I'm not I haven't shaved or anything. I've had a haircut. We're just i'm sorry. That's just the way it is
Is it really delayed? It shouldn't be. Oh, maybe the last time I used my face cam was let me see
No, that should be fine
Don't it shouldn't be that's not delayed. What are you talking about? That's fine. What do you mean?
All right. So let's all right. You ready? Sure, but you're ugly. I want to show you
Now don't look yet. I want to show you the first iteration of the box
I'm gonna get to see behind the curtain here. So this is what the box looked like
Originally, let me make sure I got that right. Yeah, so here it is
So this is the original grotto beast box looks pretty cool, right?
This is the first iteration and I want to show you like it's it's all right
It's kind of it's kind of sturdy but not that sturdy and as you can see
It's not
We didn't we weren't really happy with this. We wanted there to be something interesting in here
This is where the dice were gonna go in here in this little thing, but it turned out to be kind of annoying
Uh, it turned out to kind of it could get like kind of squished. So we decided
Maybe let's do another version right another iteration. It just it just doesn't it just it really just didn't do it for us
And obviously if i'm gonna charge
79 fucking dollars for something like that
I want to make at least fucking some you know, make it make a quality if I can right
Because I didn't we didn't want to sell this for 80 bucks. No fucking way. That was not gonna happen
So but we thought okay, what what can we do? Then we came to this one now this one
The you can even hear it the material is a lot sturdier. This is this is the box. This is the real box
So in here, I want to maybe I can show you the difference between like this
Here they are on top of each other like you might not be able to see the difference
But you can definitely feel it. This is a little I want to say flimsier. This one is it's hard. It's sturdier
So then yeah, take a look. There it is. Now you're probably saying do this stuff. Where's all where's all the stuff?
This is this is a print. This is a sample. So if you take a look down there, ooh
Cool. This is what sits in the middle, which is now holding the dice
And I kind of fucked it up a little bit. So this is my own fault
This is what it sits in now
You get this little like boat and see there you see like the glowing it's like sits on top of this
This so it sits in the box like this
I fucked mine up because I was fucking with it too much but you get a dice boat that sits like this
And then there's two starter decks right here
It's pretty nice and it's a lot nicer than this
And like I said, we weren't going to sell this for 80 dollars. That would be fucking
I would I we've no way not going to happen. So here are the dice
I don't know if I can even show these that well, but here they are these dice they have can you see
There's the the print is the light's not great in here, but there's the the j
The the germa j these are fun for all your dice needs. Yeah, you can't see it
It's it's it doesn't come out that well on camera here, but they're themed dice pretty cool
So those sit in here like that and these I think these come in a little bag
They they will come in a little bag so they don't jump around too much and then
Aha is the manual the manual is right here. I don't want to show I should I open this
It's really nice. It's nice. It's kind of like acts as like a little art book too in a way
It's not an art book
But you know, they they there's a lot it's a listen
There's a lot of nice stuff in here and take a look there you go, but now this is not an art book
Let me make that really clear not an art book. It's the manual the rules for the game
But there is like some nice stuff here. Then
Here there are two play mats here is one of the play mats and this is just standard
Paper, this is not uh, like felt or something. But here's the play mat is one of them
They're pretty big and then here's the other one. They're not like felt. Here you go. Here's the
Here's the other one pretty cool pretty cool stuff and then
That's also in that box and then we get to these these are my favorite. This is my favorite part these
So I can't open these there's nothing in here
I just want to get you to see what it looks like in somebody's hand
They feel nice. The foils are cool. Take a look back. Can you get a good view? Take a look at that
There it is
These are your packs two of these come in the box. They come in the box and why don't we
No, that's my favorite part for sure
Oh also very important to mention all the cards. This is all printed and made in america
The only difference is the dice were not the dice were made in china
so everything that this whole thing was made and printed in the united states, so
That's that's cool. There you go card reveal
Is one pretty shiny feels pretty good
Give you kind of kind of a look of what they look like in somebody's hand
But if I get it really close, I wonder if I can get it close for you
And again, these are standard these are standard playing card sizes. Hey haven't even fucking seen this one yet
You haven't even seen this one yet card reveal the lighting in the room is not great
But so this is a rare I don't have any holographics to show because they're being made so I can't really show them
But this is what one looks like you want to see the back if it looks like on the back
You know if you want to hear you want to sound test sound test flip test row test
I'm gonna move it around pretty sturdy pretty solid. There you go. You want me to fan it out taste test
Oh, wait, let me show this. This is glue man
I wish the camera wasn't so bad because this it they actually the printing came out really nicely for yeah
It's full art. Yeah, the rares, uh, i've learned the rares the
Challenger cards, I believe are full right make sure make sure somebody corrects me. Can you see it?
Well, there you go. Throw it at the wall. No, this is my glue man. I'm not doing that. You crazy
Yeah, I just we wanted to show people what because I look I get it. It's 80 fucking dollars
It's 10 bucks per pack. I I want you to be able to understand what you're getting. So let's fan it out
Sorry, i'm looking over here. I have to look at the preview to make sure i'm showing it right there you go
That's what you can expect printed and made in america except for the dice
It's been it's been quite a journey. There you go. What happens if you rip the mats?
I would just be careful with them. Be careful with them. Oh also. Yeah, very very important to remember as well
That there are two full decks that are coming with this box. I just I don't have them here right now
they're not we
I did we had printing stuff and they're they're making them. They're they're producing them
But we these are just samples of the boxes and some of the cards
So there are two full decks that will be sitting in these little wells and then everything will sit on top
Actually, i'll show you what it might look like when you open it probably a good idea hold everything back up
There are duplicates. Yes, there are the game
So besides this being channel merch because that's what this is
We wanted a good functioning game on top of it because why not like i've got originally this was going to be baseball cards
In quotes, so this was originally just going to be no game
We got in touch with the game designer and it was like why not let's go
Why not just have something fun on top of it, too?
so there are
You can have duplicates in a deck and it's the game the game wise it makes sense because I think you can have up to three
Cards, right up to three the same card. I gotta fold this up. Nice. I don't want to mess it up
So in the starter deck there are duplicates because they are pre-built decks for you to just be able to play it or just collect it
So the decks in there are pre-built. I gotta fold this. I'm so paranoid. I'm gonna rip it because I don't want to let
This is my special sample copy. I don't want to mess it up. They're pretty sturdy though because it feels like it
There we go. What do they smell like? I don't know nothing. Uh that moon by the way
That moon card comes in the starter kit
So that's good to know if you want that card
It's in the starter kit my card the germa card is also in the starter kit as well
Would you like to see how far we've come?
This is from the stream. Do you remember this? Yeah, these are these are from the these are from the stream
Do you remember the stream? These are not I would say these are not bad
You know, they're a little the cut is a little we did this happened by
Yeah, archaeologist don't bend it. I'm not I just want to show you the difference. I want to show you the difference
I'm not bending them that hard. Yeah, two different pre-built decks two different decks. You don't get two of the same one
It's two different pre-built decks. There you go. You want to see the difference might as well show the difference, right?
So the one on the left is the original the one on the right is the new the new one
The new card I guess you could say the new what it looks like actually that better idea to show it like this
Did you get a good idea of what like the first original on the stream looked like there we go
So this one on the left is the the ones we're printing one of the right is the original and again printed and made in america
I want to make that point clear in the united states of america. Oh, I dropped them my precious my precious samples
So between the two starter decks that you get there are I believe there are 40 unique cards
Because they're doubles they have to have doubles for the game sense, right? There's 84 cards total in each
Across the two starter decks. So there you go. I
More than 40 unique cards. Sorry
I'm just i'm looking I gotta get corrected by the ground abuse group chat
And then you get the two boosters in there too, which is another 20 cards. There you go. Pick them up
I they've they've fallen in a perfect position pinned tweet pinned tweet. Thank you for the demonstration. Mr
Jeremy will this be on the test if it's more than it was more than a it's more than a four. It's on the test
Thanks our grotto beast nfts. No, what's up saying that look I like this this it's cool
All right. There you go. I want to show it now you see kind of what's in the box
Unfortunately, the two pre-built starter decks are not there as well as any of the cards that obviously because we don't have that
I don't have them here. There you go. Are there any questions before we move on?
I want to make sure we answer most of the stuff right now
Why did I how am I going to answer any of these when are they shipping?
All right grotto beast group chat
Give me a hand here because we're having a pre-sale go for the next probably two weeks
After the pre-sale ends the inventory that we've already have in production right now will be part of the first things to ship out
Again, if you are buying boosters right now
You are claiming the second run of production because the first run of production has already been claimed
How many total unique cards are there 200?
There are 200 unique cards. Is it feasibly possible to collect everything?
That is a good question. I think the purpose with this was
to be interesting merch and
We don't really have a plan as of right now and what we're going to do in the future with this
So I don't know. I guess maybe I it's a great question because it's a limited run as well. What's the calorie count?
Yes, the pre-sale is going to ship out shortly after the pre-sale ends
So in a couple of weeks just check back every so often
Well, i'm guys i'm going to be talking about this every five or six days until every like but that's way too long
I'll be talking about this every day or two on stream
Until the pre-sale is over again. The point of the pre-sale is even though we've gone through
our production inventory
Of boosters. I didn't want it to say well, it's sold out and that's it
And sorry, but we went through our inventory and that's it. We have to contact the printer
Reprint do a second run but keep the pre-sale open so you can still claim it at the price
We are showing you if we didn't if it was just that one run and we didn't kind of keep this pre-sale going
Then two or three weeks from now
I don't want these to appear for you know
The price that we a price that we are not telling you to pay weeks down the road
We want whoever wants this over the coming two or three weeks to be able to claim
Product for the price that we are telling you so over these two and a half weeks or so
We're keeping a pre-sale going regardless if we run out of production inventory
How long is a pre-sale at least for at least 10 to 14 more days at least there you go
Will you play it on stream? You will absolutely see this be shown on stream. I can't say i'm very good
Good
It's very it's fun though. It's very fun
and then another couple weeks we'll have maybe something else to talk about and
Show you but from now, we're really happy
It seems like people are into it and that was a big fear is is
Are people and all the production costs and everything is this like people?
Kind of actually care about this and the answer apparently is yes. So thanks everybody
We're all you you cannot understand the the excitement going on over here everyone. That's just
So happy with the reception and we hope you like it. We hope you think it's a good enough quality
we really hope you do and
It's it's merch. It's channel merch and that's pretty much the way that it is. It's very
Different channel merch, but it is merch nonetheless and any plans on this project going forward. We don't have
There's no plans right now. We don't want to talk about any plans
Because we need to see how this goes this is uncharted territory for everybody over here
So we're trying trying we're trying to figure it out. This guy sucks at grotto beasts
What happened to the pin tweet? I deleted it because I need to make room for another one
I hope it makes it big
Well, and again, I that's fucking cool
That's really really cool. I I can't even believe that that's something that somebody would even utter but remember
It's fun channel merch first and foremost. We made this for you guys. We made this for this community
That was the intent that was the purpose and whatever people do with it
Whatever people think whatever how much fun people have with it. Cool. That's awesome. That makes all of us happy and we'll see
Let's go back to hylix. Although
I got i'm gonna i gotta pee
I'll be right back. I'm gonna go pee. Okay
I am back
Sorry, I was gone for a little bit. I wanted to refill my little drink I have here
I also wanted to
Just kind of corroborate with the grotto beast team make sure everything I said was accurate. Cool. Oh, there's no music. I'm sorry
Should have been this
Well, I did pee
I peed and then I was like, hey, let's ask a couple of questions to make sure I got this right
Okie dokie. Let's play
Hylix so what's the last thing we just did right? Okay. I came here. I did this
I'm gonna go to that place where I was before down here. Oh, I don't need to go in this
Don't you dare tell me that I need to relax. Well, i'm saying what I
I'm relaxing right now. Okay
I think I could fight these things now. Can I I should be strong enough? I'm doing it. Oh shit
I forgot to sleep vibe check. I think the vibes are pretty great. Uh, I need to heal
That hurt two damage don't do it. No, I think i'm all right. Jesus this hurts. Oh
I could revive but no, I only have one of those shit
Kind of in trouble
deal
I think i'll survive. Yeah, i'm all right. These things hurt the sauce still says you're in the bathroom
Well, the stream is live right now if that's for only when the stream is offline
600 bucks damn. Okay. Hold on. This is we need to heal. Wait, he's just dead. Oh
I have to use the burrito. All right
What the fuck are you guys doing over here?
I'm not gonna even i'm not i'm not gonna show that because it's stupid
No, if you i'm no i'm not even gonna address it it's it's a stupid meme that somebody did in the discord
I'm not doing that. I can't i'm playing a game right now. I can't show it tv
I don't even understand what this meme is
What is this meme trying to what is this meme? Can somebody explain this to me? I don't get it
I mean I get it what they're doing, but I don't get it at the same time
Bernie watching a video of me with cigarette packs smoking a cigarette. I don't get it
I don't understand this and i'm not showing it. I'm just not gonna show it. I don't get it
I don't get what does this mean? Fine. I'll show it. What is this supposed to be? I I don't get it
I understand this
Does anybody get it?
All right. I don't want to die. I don't want to lose here. I gotta pay attention. I activated that crystal, right?
Yeah, I don't think there's anything to get necessarily. I I don't get it. I I I don't get it
I don't get this. I don't get this. We're gonna kill one real quick right now. You're not gonna die again, right?
You know, you're gonna die again. What he's a full health. Why'd he die so quickly bro? You suck
No, I I gotta pay attention people are sending me bernie sanders like smoking memes of me holding cigarette packs
I'm a little distracted right now
No, no, it's fine. I am kind of in trouble though
I think I have to die because then I can put them turn the meat in right? Let's maybe that's not a bad thing
Parasite crystal. Whoa, i'm the sage of computers. I grant you my token sage's token. Okay, there's one more token
What about this?
Cool. Okay, so I have this token. I am terrified of this thing
I don't have a revive check the right side and then i'll probably leave that's the only way
I don't want to fight this thing. Oh shit
What no, I thought I dodged it. All right, i'll be all right just die. It's fine
But I want to be able to get all the secrets
Germa i'm crunk right now. I think you're cool
I appreciate it. Thanks stunned can't do anything
No, I thought I was gonna be dead
Are you scrunk
No
They explained to the bernie meme in the discord. Oh, okay
What's the last time you played with playdoh?
That would have to be
at least
25 years ago
Dynamite wait, this is safe. No, you lied to me. You lied to me
I'm actually I feel betrayed right now. You lied to me. You said red line and that was a you lied to me
Oh
I'm definitely dead
Oh shit going no way. Goodbye. I do have a ton of meat though. All right, I gotta come back here
22 meat your max flesh rose, but okay 44 extra health is huge. It's so cool and freaky. It is cool
It is cool and freaky the executive balcony is down the stairs only those who have died three times are allowed there
Uh, I guess you qualify good job. You may proceed
Nice job swish swish axe found. Ooh
Time steals away like a stream. We glide hence away. I need a paper cup. That's extra mana who can use that
Okay, so this is a ton of damage but no nothing on it greatly increases maximum will points
Oh, I don't think I want that right now, but I definitely will take this
Maybe I should be like castor in a way how much more that's a lot. That's an unbelievable amount
Yeah, I think i'll keep it on well if I get a paper cup
I gotta remember where that is, but let me sleep on the cup. There we go
All right. So it was what color was the one where it just was red or is it green? I don't remember. What was it?
Is green right? Yeah. All right much stronger now and I think we have to fight this I think we do panorama
45 damage that's a lot hit all of them. That's good. Yeah, i'm gonna use uh, stay dust as a caster killer poison
I think that the one in the middle will die. I'm poisoned right get that connor attack out of here
James freaking me out dude. Take a quick break another paper cup
Take a quick break and come back or not, you know, maybe get some food in you too muscle
All right, i'm afraid but i'm gonna do it you you inadvertently destroyed it what what just happened those things kill you instantly
Holy shit. Okay. Well, let's try it again. Did I get everything that was down there?
You ignored the sign at the beginning. Oh, those are the skulls. Well, I didn't well
I don't know what it meant by that
Everything this game is so wacky looking. I didn't know that. I don't know. I don't know what that thing was
300 bucks nice. All right. Well, I got everything here. I got everything here. So where have I not gone?
I guess I could walk around out here. Have I explored all this area yet?
No, there was that big that like big vault. I wonder if i'm strong enough orange
Which I would orange or blue blue I think right i'm pretty sure it's blue and then from blue
Was he up or was he I don't remember where he was. What was that guy the vegetables?
Oh, yes vegetables vegetables vegetables part two is even better. I mean, this is great
All right, where was that guy? It was green crystal and then from green
I just kind of don't remember where he was. Where do I go over there? Where do I go?
It's green. Where do I go?
Teleporter in the skull maze. Well, I would need to die right just go to green die and go to green
It's in the middle
Uh, okay go to the warp station. I think I don't have to be dead to be at the warp station
I thought that's the afterlife. Isn't it? Oh, yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yep. Yep. Yep. Yep. Yep. Yep. You're right
You're right. Yep forgot about this. So you think i'm strong enough to fight this thing find out maybe I mean
This is a lot. Let's try it. I can't like go around or anything, right? Can I sneak in? All right, i'll fight him
I wonder what the strategy here is take out the ads first. Yeah, and then let's do a panorama
All right, that hurts a lot
shit
There you go. Just don't die
Nope
I think we're okay
Jesus
Oh, that's all that's self only
Oh, I thought that was okay. I'll just heal
Uh-oh
Oh, thank god one health. Damn. Okay
The one on the right has been confused almost the whole time. I think we're good
That's not gonna cause a problem, right if I don't kill the ads first
Oh, all right. Let's do it. There's a lot of money back there
22 damage. That's it
good again
Dps race. I did it only 75 bucks
I kind of feel bad
Artificial bicep was found 50 bucks
That's it 100 bucks and that's it. Well, there's a tv in here detonation artificial bicep increases
HP and strength. What was that new power detonation inflicts 250 percent damage
Slow casting speed
Can you do that too? Jesus thermostreams in 864p because maximum bitrate allowed by twitch is 6 000
1080p 60 is too large for that barrier to look good
Well, you can make 1080 1080 6 uh, 1080 30. This is fine. 1080 60 is okay, too
It's I prefer it the other way. Why did I read that? I don't know. Why are you reading the
You're reading the bot messages. I don't
I don't know. I looked over and I saw it
I saw somebody do that emote where i'm like blah blah blah blah blah blah blah
I thought they would I thought they were talking shit. So it was that's an official message. Oops. That's my bad
All right. That's good. Let's go this way. What what?
Why why is there uproarous laughter right now? I'm missing something
What's happening? Visitors are rare. It's hot. Ow. Oh, don't touch it. This dude is beefing with his own nightbot
All right. So is there anything else to do in here?
Well, I don't know. I chat moves really fast sometimes and I I look over and it's
I just see somebody's doing that emote and that emote usually means like oh look at me
I'm german and I fucking talk too much. So i'm like, all right, so whatever fuck you bro. I'll tell you why
I thought it was somebody's like talking shit the bird fighting its reflection. Ooh, look at this
Yeah, wait, no. Whoa, I feel like there's a boss. All right, I don't get overwhelmed. Let me go this way
Bat-chest me you'll get timed out for that god. Are we ready for this? Only one way to find out vegetables
You crushed it. What please don't touch the device or i'll have to destroy you. It's a living nice weather
Hmm, please don't touch the device. This thing controls the harbor gate touch it unauthorized access detected manifesting horrid projection
Oh dear detonate
18 damage that's it
250 damage. All right, that was good. Maybe detonate with this character
Will be crazy. Yeah detonate. Oh, all right. Yeah do that again. It's a lot
Okay, i'm out of that, but I think it's fine. Let's attack normally. Don't be stupid. Yes
2,000 bucks got a muscle
that leak
Harbor gate opened. Oh, that's where I couldn't get out from. All right. Nice. Very cool
Let me get out of here now without dying. There was some shit over here though
I hope this is not like a big boss. I heal wonder if this thing's friendly
Mods can I read that that's funny. I just I have to read that like am I allowed to read that somebody just got timed out
This is what they said. Fuck this guy this germadude this streamer. I hate his streams. I hate his voice
I hate his face. I hate this game. I hate this chat. I hate twitch. I hate videos. I hate the internet
I hate this keyboard. I hate computers fuck electronics. I fucking hate this chair, too
I'm gonna just i'm gonna give you just a small
Small piece of go get like a glass of water and maybe come back
I hate this chair. Hopefully you get like a better chair man
Like everybody deserves like a chair, right a good chair
Get a glass of water. I hope you I helped like you feel better
Get a glass of water and then then come back. I hate the internet. I hate this chair
I hate this keyboard. I like this this keyboard, too
I hope you're doing all right, dude, seriously
Sometimes you just gotta let it out. Yeah in the event that this thing is hostile. I'm going to do this
Let's find out where to go. Where's that big thing? Where did that thing go? You passed it? Oh, right, right, right
Okay, hold on. Wait, I'm going over
There's a little thing here access terminal god. Where am I? Oh
Different part of the world interesting
Thousand bucks, that's a lot. Let's see who's in here tv. Oh, hey wane
I left my magic gauntlets in the basement and now it is infested with ambulance skulls
Maybe you could help me retrieve them. I mean the gauntlets
We should avoid the skulls. Oh
Sam snossa has joined the crew. Oh new party member
Any leech inflicts queasy status on one enemy trains enemies flesh point. Do we all learn it?
No, we don't be on this window frame a
Phantasmagoric tableau unfolds and whatnot. You can clean yourself off in the sink. Uh, sure burrito in the toilet
Ouch, though and sleep on it. Nope. Nice empty. How do I get that?
Wait
Nope, I thought I could be um juice box. I get that trash can
All right, so I can't fight any of this. I have to avoid it. I gotta use my pac-man skills person hostile
Hey
Roach food. I've got your roach food a thousand bucks for some roach food feels like this come once in a lifetime
Sure, that's a roach food couch money. I'm in trouble. How do I get out of this?
Shit, they're camping. I don't you don't uh, wait, what if I can I sleep and reset your assholes get out of the way
Get out of the way. I I think I have to die. Well, oh, yeah, you're right. I got that teleporter. That's right
Wait, where's my friend? Where's the new friend? I had a new friend. Where are they? They're not dead
Oh, all right. I was gonna say like that sucks. Is this did we does this count too then?
Okay, there we go. Look this chair this chair dude this chair. I hate chair streams. I hate his chair
I hate chairs. I hate this chair. I hate his chair. I hate that chair. I hate his chair
All right. I see we're see we're going uh off the deep end with this one
All right. I don't I want to go to the right. No, I don't there's nothing there. Shit reset it. No
Shit, okay gloves acquired magic gauntlets weird
Okay, so now I this is the person permanently in the group magic gauntlets
These gauntlets allow their wearer to convert various creatures into mightiness
Seems like a lot of damage another bicep too. Ah, there is you're right. Is that better than this demon skull helmet wrought from the skull?
So I think this is a placeholder, right? So that's that go back this way use the computer. Is this game too weird?
Um, I don't think so. This game is just weird enough. I like it. Stop ignoring me into a funeral stream
um
There is I touch it right? No, no, no, no, I don't know. This thing is kind of scary. Should I
Deutoplasm can I interact? Oh dear
Uh, all right detonate
confusion
bubbles
Let's go
three
Oh
That hurts
That did a lot of damage though. Hold on. I might be able to survive this
That's a full heal
Bleaches up expensive should I try it? Oh, it's right. It's a drain. All right. No, no, we're good. We're good. We're good
We're good
I think I'm as long as I can keep this up ancient odor
Oh poison that's bad
uh, oh
uh
Status come on. Don't hit wane
good
detonate
Sorry, I got the guard on it's not bad
60 damage nice. I feel like I don't want to use the dynamite. I think we're just going to tack tack
You use vegetable on you
Then you use vegetable on yourself
Yes
What I get?
Jerkin parasite crystal. Ooh, is that all I can do? What did I get this?
Sensible everyday wear for the modern machine prevents paralysis
Okay, we should wear that probably you um snasa
Yeah, okay prevents paralysis
Reequip the skull. It's one of the best head pieces. Is it I huh? What is it doing?
Demon skull, what are the stats on it? It's health. It's more hp
Okay
Keep that bell on what about you?
artificial bicep
Are we the poncho there? Right toilet paper is very awful
141 versus
Yeah, it's better. Telepaper really does not do anything. You can I can optimize too if I really wanted to
Well, there we go. That's fun
Back to it. So now I can leave the leave the dock thoughts on the game so far. I think it's great
Didn't want to do that. It's kind of like
Earthbound went through a bunch of I mean, it's like a really cool art piece
The music's really cool and it plays sort of like that earthbound kind of the party and do you have to I mean
It's I like it. It's really cool. Did I explore everything here? I believe the answer to that question is yes
Correct. It is an rpg, right? But it's it's like a television screen rpg. Here's what I mean by that
When you get into a battle your party members are not on the screen
It's just you you're like a pov
RPG pov traditional turn-based rpg dragon quest does this and like and like the like the psychedelic powers and stuff
I mean, that's earthbound just happened. Whoa, where am I? What's going on?
Whoa, what just happened wane wrongfully prepares many behaviors, but doth he sniff his vessel near truths
Digest the offending doom in prisons consider the dirt. Meanwhile at the moon palace gibby pilots
Soon our shrunken radiance will be greatly shunned. Every pain is a
Whatever that word is
Monculus and every chemical is like melancholy biscuit. What does it do? I just punched that thing. Should I not be doing this pneumatic?
I know. Oh your telephone interesting. Very cool. All right, we can keep going
But I want to go purchase stuff first. Yeah, the gate should be open
No, looks like it is. I'm I get 6,800 increases will buy 50. I don't know. That's a lot of money
I sell this stuff dude. You're rich. It's fine. I don't think so. You got a muscle thing in your inventory
Yeah, who can wear that? Wait
Wait
what oh
What does that mean?
Okay, permanently increases mightiness by two. I feel like it's going to be wane, right? Give wane the heaviest attacks
I think that's probably what i'm gonna do. Okay, so wane is now permanently right 59 mightiness. Nice
I need to go to the vegetable garden. Ooh
Two weapons I could give it to wane. I think i'm gonna give to wane. Okay
Mac greatly increasing maximum will losing mightiness though
Oh, it's because I lose the bicep. Damn it. Is that all right? I think I need another axe first
Let's give it to you. I don't have another instrument for you. At least for all that is holy use your muscle
I did I did you you went to go blow your nose and you came back or you went to go like
You went to go heat up a snack or something and you came back and I did it already
All right. Well, I have it now and when I find a good weapon, I will replace this go
He has no idea what he's doing. I have an I have a general idea. I have a general idea
Tell us then well, I mean I have no idea what's going on in the story
It's like a pretty trippy kind of cool interesting game and i'm just enjoying the ride and the music
And chill vibes and the the numbers that go up on screen i'm chilling out with that
That's the mountain. So I think i'm good and I go up to the vegetable garden. That's code for I don't know what's going on
I'm fine though. I whatever you whatever relax. Let me see. Where's the bugs?
Oh give roach food. Should I yes. Thanks for the snack. You can have this. Excuse me
What I just get shield made from a venerable beast. Wilder is immune to poison better than a trash can lid
This game has a meat grinder and bug food. Yeah, that's I mean, why have you not bought this yet?
How much is this game? It's like three dollars this game is I think it's less than three or four dollars. All right, let's move
Where should I land? It has to be a dock. Oh, we went over here. Whoa. Yeah, let's try this. There we go
Oh, what the hell is going on here?
Okay, this is where all the ladders are
So that all right, i'm gonna take like a screenshot of that get away from us. Whatever. Just kill it
I just got this intense craving pepperoni pizza
I'm so glad that there is pepperoni pizza in firm with you all and just confirm
There is a pepperoni pizza in the fridge. Don't worry bade magic or something. Well, let's try to kill a thing in the mill shit
There we go. So how do I hurt these bubbles?
Maybe the shirkens try the shirkens. Does it work? It does. Okay poison you're draining my mp
What I can't even do anything
I think i'm dead. I don't have any juice boxes and I could do dynamite, but that sucks. I want to save it
It's fine. You'll get more. I'm scared fine. It doesn't kill anybody. I didn't kill anybody
Now it's it's over and I just wasted a dynamite now i'm pissed
Wait, do I have I think I have wait a minute just die. What you what I thought you
Wait, no, I didn't want to you said but you told me I couldn't do that
You guys told me I couldn't do this you lied to me. What does this do? I can't touch this
That maneuver. No, i'm stuck my hand. So I had this thing when I've already used arrow keys
Um, my hand really hurts my fingers kind of get hurt. I'm an old man. Sorry. No, I didn't want to fight you run
Get away from me. Get away from me. I have to open every single gravestone. I have to this is why I can't play luigi's mansion
Everything needs to be like everything has to be sucked up
Everything has to be touched like all like all I have to suck up everything you give me. All right
I think i'm in trouble. Oh
soft-locked
Yes
Okay. Okay. Hold on. I have to die. I'm soft-locked. Thank god. All right
Oh, can I actually fight you or what? Yes. All right. We're good
Is there any way that I can remap my arrow keys to be WASD like in windows or something?
You need to do like a script to do it joy to key auto hotkeys. Yeah, I used auto hotkey before
Um, all right, let's go with the one on the left first heal you tilt your keyboard. Wait, wait a minute
You mean like move it?
Hold on then I have to hit space though. I'm gonna play with my arms crossed. I think i'm playing
Yeah, i'm gonna go arms crossed. My left hand is on the arrow keys. My right hand's on space
Turn it upside down. The enemy on your left has your hair style
It's literally you it's not literally me big damage coming out. I didn't mean to pass don't even oh come on
I should have killed this thing on the right first keyboard manager enable keyboard manager remap keys
Oh, wait, how do I do that keyboard manager? Hold on keyboard manager keyboard hardware speed
Where do I go? Oh, I have to it's a dinner. I can't everyone. Sorry crossing my arms. It's fine. There we go
I hate this keyboard. I hate this chair
Our toys is good 1200 bucks meat meat meat meat. I'm imagining I probably have to activate all these things
Let's give that to me. I'm wayne's gonna be the one that does all the damage. All right, let's keep going
Why can you phase through walls? So unfair the other one's up here over there. Yes, don't fight me
uh
Get out of the way get out of my way. There it is. Ah, you know what? Let's get the experience. These things are fine
It's jerbo. Oh my god. Look at their hands to the left
Whatever
It's uh, what I there he is. I think one hit will yeah, geez kill it
Only five why is some snosses only doing 15 damage? There we go. Lots of meat cool
This among I don't want to run out of vegetables that dudo plasm
Seems really really important. It's a full everything heal. I don't want to use it. I'm gonna be stuck here. I think i'm stuck actually
Yeah, try to get down the ladder. Nice. All right
All right. I made it. Meow tv, please get out of the way
I want to see the tv get out of the way. I want to watch the tv. Oh, it's microwave
Is there a reason to not do this with all the burritos or should I do it for all of them?
This is just better consider text consider text consider text thy prison safe. Okay weird
All right
I can actually fight these things now and I have to remember that magic's the only thing that can hurt them
All right special a lot of health seriously
Damn, oh shut up with this. All right. No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no
Get that status off. Thank you. What the hell? Why do you have so much health poison?
Shit die
What the hell will the poison eventually kill the one on the right? I'm out of mp
I can't I can't win. I have to leave bubbles on the one on the left
I think that's all I can do just hope the poison kills it. Okay
Die
Guard everybody guard until somebody dies from poison the one on the left
This is like more than three four five hundred damage. No, no, no, no, no, no, no actually
No, I can fight you. I don't even have to hog champ go go go. I think that's it down here hog champ
Food tv person health chant. Is that all of them or is there more one in the middle? Oh get out of the way
Oh my god
No the shit in the way passion three five four
No, i'm five seven and five eight with shoes on and that person for a whole at least one full day
It's blinking. Did I do it? Wait, was that blinking before? I don't remember but let's just kill this stuff as I can
No, no, no, no, no, no, no. I didn't want to do that. I hit right right like just passes and I didn't want to pass
Oh, that's bad sour patch kid. I gotta look at some snaus's gear because we are not hurting anything with that character
Yeah, 65 63 15. Oh, no, no, no it is. Okay, they're they're attacking out of order. I'm not supposed to clear it
It's based on speed. Yeah. Oh my god. That was bad. No, no, no
I want you to be healing people and you to attack. Yeah, i'm five i'm five
Hey, man, who gives a shit how tall anybody is something moved above ground
You could be six feet tall you could be seven feet tall you could be five two you could be five one
We're all so different. We all have our own things that we can do
We all have different skills
And time out everyone saying five
You know what I mean time about get them delete them
Something moved above ground. What was it? I actually like being shorter
You know how like how how much better it is to like and I can like nap on the couch perfectly great
Well, yeah, this is that's fine. Do you want to cope? I can fit into little places and shit. It's great
I don't give a shit how tall I am up here. Maybe what is going on here?
Somebody stashed two frozen burritos here. Ooh
Yeah, yeah, no, don't ever forget who actually threw the ring into mount doom. Don't forget who did that
It wasn't a gigantic orc. It wasn't gandalf. Who was it? Who did it? Huh? Who did it?
Well, yeah, but yeah, but yeah, but yeah, I don't hear any rebuttals to that
Gandalf what I've gandalf. How do you pronounce it? Get it's gandalf gandalf. That's how you say gandalf
Something happened above ground. What happened? Oh this happened gandalf gandalf
Demon skull was found. I already have one of those but cool weird. That's good
Uh, let's attack normally. No, I wish I didn't do that. That's right without being selected
It just passed the turn. Did it work? I didn't see. Ooh, they're hurting each other. Nice fused
Who has the anti-paralysis on somebody does meat found meat found?
Water blue blue was the heaven above me and the earth green at my feet
Oh life. Oh life. I kept saying and the very word seemed sweet gather our platinum art
He said and spirit considers our doom
Vegetables feel like i'm being prepared for something duck blade was found
small chance of lowering targets mightiness
Duck blade, is it worth?
putting on the
this thing
All right. Nice. I don't care about the blindness right now. This is probably better
That is what i'm gonna use
Is this still like best in slot for this person? I feel like i'm missing out. I want the damage
You missed a party member. Uh-huh. Uh-huh. Find it maybe bio wave. It's hurts a lot
Wow poison damage really kills this thing bad
They're multiplying. Ow
Ow
Wow, that hurts get rid of these things before they they probably overwhelm you
This is doing 125 damage. That's gotta be doing like two plus 100 damage every time
Stop stop spawning
Is poisoning the same one over and over again do anything? I was hoping it was gonna stack
That might not be the case though
Okay, well we need to do this now do it again. They normally don't in rpgs. That's true
We gotta I gotta start focusing on the little ones
Yeah, these little ones have to die. This is what i'm gonna get overwhelmed here in a minute
It keeps spawning
Die i'm in deep trouble. I'm going for it. Yes. I got kind of hairy. This is like a boss
This thing was pretty difficult being just a regular enemy
mini boss
Thousand bucks tons of vegetables kind of an unbelievable amount of vegetables
Okay
And are these enemies?
Delicately texturize our biscuit far beyond memory. I've died a lot here
I call this place the hall of deadly statues. I'm strengthening my leg muscles so I can run past them
This thing's attacked. Ah, yeah, they do
Of course they do
Found meat
Now how do I get out of here? Oh, i'm dead. Goodbye. I got lots of meat though
So what is this other I missed a something right? Let me see. There's an island
I didn't explore. Well, I kind of want to see it. I already remember on the island
Where are they from here? Red wrong warp water cups. It's fine. Just go down. I haven't found any more cups
I can't hear the city. What if I should buy something else here? I should probably get the vegetables. I'm honest
Yeah, let's do that. This game feels like what sleep deprivation feels like let's see that. Okay, so
Um, uh
Okay. Oh, I didn't go here. That's right. Wait, what's that? The lever is off limits
I don't recommend pushing the button either. Please don't touch the lever. Please don't don't touch the lever off limits. I can't
Can I do anything else? Please stop pushing the button. Don't push it. I'll give you these muscle apt leaks
Just stop pushing it. Oh, i'm gonna keep going that sound like fatal spirit rays. I'm getting mad
Considered delusion spirit slowly stretched. You're a button-pressing maniac. Take this nice now go
There's nothing more for you. May you prepare in lards. I got a cup that it i'm giving all the power to wane interact with the bugs
What what?
Whoa
Converted the bug into might for who is a tv inserts. Whoa
Okay, token one token two. I need one more token and then this will turn on got it. Okay
Okay
This is the only place I have not gone is the middle here little town up here. Okay, what's this for?
I don't think I can do anything here triple worm poop worm single worm
Ultra poop worm coiled worm single worm worm. Whatever somebody will remember
No, i'm trying to break that paper cup at 25
Mana bobo links at noon day sing more softly than the softest flute
And lightlier than the lightest lute your fairy
tambor's ring
He falsifies its mechanized homunculus and skeleton forgetted its convexity
Hey squirrel food. I've got squirrel food 2000 for some squirrel food
Yes, i've seen a couple squirrels for sure. I think I will just stand here forever
All right, I got squirrel food squirrels whatever. You know what I was trying to say
Okay, so it was
This one
This one this one and this one nice
I am called on gorma greatest of the dread knights of vithorn
For long ages. I have waited in this vault fight me
Uh, not yet. So it goes
I want to watch your tv first
Dark flame. Whoa. All right, let's go
I think i've got enough
Gorma prepare yourself play out the ad. It's always clear the ads first, right pretty much always
Damage is all enemies slightly stronger than a normal attack. Let's try it. Yeah, let's go for it. Just do it three times. Okay
It's pretty powerful
Nice right now. We just focus
That's pretty good 86 damage of the chant. Here we go. We're pretty beefed up right now
I am defeated very well. I will follow you and aid you in your violent endeavors
By the way, I have dominion over the ambulance skulls. You wouldn't you don't need to fear them anymore. Oh shit
That's actually really helpful
Joyous
That thing's pretty heavy
Full party. Yeah sleep on the couch too. Oh, come on really
Yeah, watch the tv so he can get the skill. Yeah, so just realizing right now. That's how this works. Very cool
All right, so we got a full party
It was one other place on this island I could go to over here in the middle. Is that something to go to?
all right
Let's continue the progress
Quick name all the people in the party right now prove. I know who they are
Wayne de das us us whatever the name was som snosa
and
this
Vithyrile or something whatever it was. Let's see
Oh, no pangorma
He said he was like a vithyriel knight
That guy was close enough. Okay. I was I was just went let's go
Just join the party and you already forgot him. It's all right. Let's go
Let's play three hours 33 minutes and 33 seconds
Kind of cool. Uh, let me heal. I have many more juice boxes. Honest to goodness. Okay. I'm from the statue
It's the red portal. I went down last time this time. I'm not gonna go down. I'm gonna go up left
Maybe wait, what about up? Oh shit. I found it. Did I get it? I got oh, I got it. I got it
I got it. I was lucky at the last at last the lard is bungled inside offending
Convexatives wane is miraculously considering a mountain below insects where it's out of mere mandibles
And memories his pneumatic being will not be actualized and now the time for
austere corrosion arts draw to an end
Maybe shining work strongly below the lordly lunar fortress this season yearns for theory below the vent. It's the mirror
Touch everything press every button summon an airship. Uh
Yes, oh
Now we can go to these other places. All right, where should I go this house up here? What's over here?
Wait, what what's going on? Do we have instruments? This is a concert. Oh when it shunned his face. I
Exalted that taste. Hey now his joyful creature. Hey now to play music juice pack. Oh tv dissect
Damages all enemies and removes positive statuses. It's pretty good. Yo
Oh
Apparel passion passion apparel and speaking of apparel grotto beast dotnet
You can find yourself some hoodies t-shirts all with the grotto beast logo or some cool prints on it
This this is my digestion jam. Oh, we actually can we play music one of our fishes is here
Shall I recite the music tutorial? Yes keys one through four play notes and key five to change style
All right, you play it's kind of like if somebody picks a guitar up
So you're a guitarist and you play the guitar pretty well
But somebody decides that they're gonna pick it up
And be like, oh, you know, I I know a little bit
I know a little bit just because they can't stand to be shown up in the same room as you
So they pick the guitar up and they play like three chords
They know how to play just just to make it seem like that
They know how to play the guitar because like you can't have this like you can't have this. I'm sorry
I have this too
See I go look at I can play that
This is a seinfeld routine
Well, whatever in that episode of seinfeld. It was funny
I'm gonna try
All right. Here we go. What should I do? Super mario make the other people in the band play
I think I already am this is the worst constant i've ever been to try harder. I am i'm trying
All right. I'm getting out of here is this
I want to check out this thing too. Ooh. Yeah, whatever. This is can I do something here?
This is like kind of it's land here. What's this place? Ooh
Use back tv illusion form temporarily change appearance purely cosmetic
Oh sick, remember that new party. Remember we got
tv
Hey, I got horse food three thousand bucks. Yeah
All right, where are the horses and where are the squirrels squirrels are back at the house?
Squirrel give squirrel food acquired head squirrel horse food acquired horse loyal head squirrel prevents a negative status effect
That's amazing increases chance of preemptive attack raises mightiness. Oh, okay. That's a lot. Yeah
Is that just an item?
No, it's an outfit. Wait, why can I not put it on? Oh, it's because of that. This is okay
What's better?
uh wane with the
axe
Should I trade the I think i'm gonna trade this thing's very deadly, right?
curious
Yeah, look at this shit
101 mightiness prevent negative status. Okay, wayne's gonna be the absolute destroyer actual bicep. It's fine
Even I want the demon skull artificial bicep is fine. I think this is all good. Wait, maybe now
I think i'm good with this or is it time to take the combat bell off of make them a little better
What the hell is that emote? Wayne's garb is useless now
It is so let's put that on let's sleep and then get the vegetables and leave cool. Very nice. Very nice
I have 32 heels. I think i'll be fine. Is this thing in the middle?
One more place up there. It's like a big castle through this irl. I did I did
This irl what is going on here?
It must be the new foreman check in with claw man before you head to the lab
You're not allowed to enter the lab without claw man's permission
It would look to be claw man if I were to guess nice to finally meet you if you'll just give me the password
I can get you set up in the lab vessel from did you forget it or something?
I'll give you another chance. What's the password pneumatic art? They keep saying pneumatic. Maybe it's pneumatic
They keep saying that i'm gonna say pneumatic art. Not that either. Stop joking around. This is your final chance
I mean, they're all these are all random
Insect who are you prepare to be destroyed? Okay and begin
might increase
confusion bubbles
Dark flame no ancient odor. No dark flame
Um confused. Nope. All right. That's it. The poison's doing great. All right now detonate
This is gonna be a huge number
Oh
Shit, that's bad
377 I think should I revive?
Jesus. Oh my god. This is fucking destructive. I need to do a group heal
Shit. Oh my god. It's bad
This thing is destructive
destructive
Uh, I I don't think I was prepared for this
What is the speed on this guy?
Yes
Obviously, I went for it. I just went for it
10 000 bucks. I I went for it. Hell. Yeah
Uh, I don't want to revive yet because I might be able to bring them back
Beside his microcosm
Avenge beside it
All right. I I got permission
It's the lab these enemies. You must be the new guy the machines have been prepared. So feel free to give them a whirl
I'll never get tired of watching the machine do its thing. I selected these specimens for their exceptionally high monetization potential
Let's smear spirit rapidly press all the buttons. I made money
Thousand dollars. What do I do with that money? What am I supposed to do with that?
Uh a half a million. I have seven hundred and fifty thousand dollars now now what does it go?
Buy every single thing in the store. That's all I can do here. I think that's it. Yeah, that's it
Seven hundred and seventy four thousand dollars. Holy shit
Okay. Well, whoo. I'm buying everything if it's in the store. I own it. Okay, the last token
Where's the last token? Maybe the place I haven't been yet. Actually, now I want to go to the other stores
Frito token is in that statue maze
Ah
I'll go back there. I guess I don't really need anything berry shield. I wish it gets just four of these
Roam bowler. I just get like two of them. I have so much money berry shield cooking greatly increases maximum health points
I wonder if I should give that to you
364 that's a lot actually
I'd rather them stay alive. Yeah, i'm gonna let them have it
Okay
I'm gonna go to the statue place because I want to see I want to see what happens. Don't use all the money
Um, I got seven hundred thousand dollars. All right back outside looking good. Let's go. It was over here
So i'm gonna say down and to the left. I did not go this way
Oh, there's nothing over there to the right should I go? Yeah, that's right trash can maybe oh shit bad
Okay paper cup. Where is it? Where is it? I'll probably I
Restart I might need to restart it
I think I have to restart it. I'm dead. Whatever. Which one of these is it red one, right?
Oh like the like the very red one. Yeah, very red one. So where is it? Oh my god
You're screwing me here. Get out of the fucking way get that one stuck. How did you make it?
How did you do that? You were stuck all the way to the right, dude
How did you do? How did you do that? Shit? I'm just trying to bait him out of here. Oh, come on
No, I need to soak my right hand in warm water
Don't because my hand is sore. All right, all three of you come down this way
You better not we got it hot dog and a juice pack. I am the sage of death. I grant you my token
Take my siblings. All right, I got it. What the hell muscle times two
Thanks
You just kill me because I want to summon the um plane
The best place to summon the plane
Wait green these don't hurt me anymore. Can I do anything else on the right side? I can do here, right?
25 points
I don't think I can do anything else here, but they don't hurt me. So this was on that
Should I do this now? Why can I summon the airship should I do this later or do this now?
It's not going to end the game or anything, right?
Because there's this one spot up here that I have not been to go use the tokens now
I have to use the boat. Let's see you play the sequel 100. Yes
This has been a really enjoyable experience. I think it's great. I will 100 play the sequel. Okay
All the tokens are there as the tv say learned legend of melting the ultimate magic
Ultimate magic randomly strikes three times may briefly stun
200 mp the only one that can cast this is you
Damn sponsored stream. Why the hell would this be a sponsored stream? This game came out like fucking six years ago
What when did this game come out like 2000 fucking 16?
2013 how long is this game been out for?
It was eight years ago. That would be crazy
I'm ready
Whatever. This is we're seeing it. You got the sponsorship eight years ago and they were just really lenient on the time frame
Oh my god, that would be fucking awful. Yeah, I mean back when I was in the middle making youtube videos
Yeah, I just didn't have a time frame on it. It just said at some point in the future and I was like, yeah sure
Always read your contracts. That's what I will tell you. There was no time frame. That would be so fucked up
But no, this game's just really cool and we're doing just hanging out. We're just chilling
That's it. Can I introduce you in a hot dogs or perhaps a spaceship key? Yes
Uh, i'll take that. I gotta look at my money. I'm fucking loaded. I could buy two if I wanted. Oh shit
Um, I want to try this. I want to try the super attack. I'm gonna try the legend of melting. Let's see what it does
Okay
legend of melting
All right
Cool. This is the spaceship then spaceship is the end game. Uh
I think I think I did pretty much anything everything I could have done
Maybe there's probably some secrets I didn't see but I think I saw mostly everything
Yeah, I think I did everything. I've been to every island. I went to everything in the underground. Yeah, I did it all
Okay, let's turn the spaceship on. I'm just gonna buy an absolute shitload of hot dogs
Do I need six hundred thousand dollars? I'm just gonna buy a thousand of these and buy fifty of them
We'll buy juice in the city. Where do you buy juice? I didn't find a place to buy it
Was there a place in the city to buy juice? I didn't see it. Juice is only from kills
I think i'll be all right. I'm gonna buy like 10 of these or like 20. I got six hundred thousand dollars
Yeah, let's go. Let's do it. I'm ready. I haven't saved right before this so oh anything else wait
What about this little thing? Can I go this way? Have you ever tried cruelty squad? I have not seen cruelty squad
I'm not well, i've seen it, but i've not played it. I feel like that the game I know is awesome
I've been I've been told it's fucking awesome, but it looks a little harsh
Looks like my brain would probably get hurt like I would be like, uh, it would probably give me a headache
Let me ask you a question if I can handle this could I handle cruelty squad? I heard it's awesome
But yeah, you think so it gave me a headache gave me a headache
maybe you know what i'll do maybe i'll jump into it for like 20 minutes or so off stream to see how I feel because I
Believe it or not. I do have like audio visual stimulation that sometimes it can actually give me a headache
Sometimes dude, I tell you when I in the half-life 2 bolt level
I almost puked and I had to lie down on my floor for like 10 minutes in between
Bits of that game. I remember lying on my back on the floor should not throw up playing half-life 2
What's going on here? Do I have to fight all these? Entering the palace is forbidden leave now or be destroyed
You accidentally crushed it. Oh
Simmery axe inflicts
Electrobiological damage
I mean that's kind of all right. I can give this back to you. See this should go to sams nasa
Isn't it? Wait, why can't you use that?
It smells I can't use it interesting. Whoa. Okay. We're just wiping everybody out another tv
Exhaled he thrums despite refugent concavity
Oh
Can we sit on the couch juice pack good?
Boy, is there any other items in this room that i'm not seeing?
I can't tell why these guys were giving us trouble before why are we so powerful kind of unstoppable as the last crystal
Boy turn back. It's terribly powerful
Rehydrate out of blatantly mild
It's an orange. Is that what it is? It's like a moon an orange a what is this you dare approach me?
My theories will rescue your apparels until you beg me to consider
Now exhumed thine zesty nerve. It is the last time you will celebrate this box
Pack. Whoa, you've got other shit in this room
Great speed guys 60 damage ancient odor. All right, we're gonna we I knew I we have somebody has to
Heal only a dust ball and do that move
Okay, here we go. Check this out
Where is it?
detonate
boom
special
Health chant. Yep. Just good to get it out of the way
Attack attack maybe kill thing on the right first. Is that anything healing? Jesus
Heal 196. Mm
I didn't mean to do that, but it's okay. I think i'm fine melting melting is 292
I didn't mean to do that, but it's fine ancient odor. No poison though. There it is. All right, that's dead
Is it dead? All right legend of melting. Let's go and then attack attack pretty good dancing gremlins
Uh-oh, I got plenty of hot dogs. I didn't do the um, the melting move hot dog hot dog
Hurry eat. I need hot dogs now eat a hot dog hot dog
Oh, you're stunned you idiot eat a hot dog. I'm gonna die. I'm dead. I didn't know he's stunned. I'm god
I didn't know he was stunned
I tried to have him do three moves in a row and I was like, why is he not doing anything?
All right, we lose. Thank god, dude. It's my speed zero. I can't even attack
Okay, this dude does four moves before I can do one piece of shit
Wow, where did I get all this meat from? Holy shit. That's insane
When did I get all that meat?
104 meat. Where did I get all that from the people in the tower? Okay
All right
Now we're ready. Let's go that would have been cool to get a first try now. I'm good to go
I got almost half of the yeah. Wow go hard on the left statue
Legend of melting go first right of that attack punch hurt kill strike do it do it. Oh stinks
Mystic meat protect everybody dark flame dark flame is better. That should kill it. No, not yet. Okay, that's kind of insane
Let's do that 157 damage. That's a lot
All right. I need to eat that hot dog. Why have you not eaten the hot dog yet?
Eat the hot dog. I told you to eat a hot dog. Why have you not eaten the hot dog yet?
Eat the hot dog. It's gonna take you so long to eat a fucking hot dog. We're just gonna go straight up attack
Eat the hot dog. All right, much better shape now
Okay, did else man is just going to feed people hot dogs
That's the only thing he's doing hot dog strategies paying off poison good the detonate should be like two or three hundred, right?
Or a hundred damage. Can I do it again? I cannot but i'll do this
What am I doing? All you do is feed people hot dogs. That's the only thing I want you to do status protection
Oh shit, that's right. All right hot dog coming up 250 for the poison. Holy shit. Okay 250 that poison is so good
Hot dog, I think we're getting close fastest hot dog shooter. I don't know. I've never seen anybody do it like this
Go ahead and do calibration die
This seems like overkill, but I have like 50 of them. So i'm gonna do it detonate
Uh bubbles because that's gonna be poison
You eat a hot dog this time and you attack
Thousand bucks found a hot dog. Wayne is now level 63
Everybody's level 63
Oh, I am defeated
Wayne i'm sorry about everything
Oh
By the way, uh, I set this moon to explode when I die say your prayers and purify your vacuums
like
Being memory. Oh
Sit on the throne anything anything. I'll just leave one check. Okay, go. Oh no
Rock amidst a remarkable juice pick this person up and carry them out, but wane hideous luxuriously adrift
Witness the chemical amidst the delusion vacuum governments irradiance renders greatly the doth her homunculus pilot side rays
So ends the tale of the modified beasts who sought to witness yet sort of expansively texturized
Radiance the lever that I wasn't supposed to touch interesting the end
Wait, what?
That's what it was
Don't touch that lever. It makes the uh, am I missing something?
The boat I broke it did I win?
So what do we do now? What about that person that was walking around act one act two act three now spam the lever
It's no I didn't do it. That is the end with apologies. Why wait with apologies?
What was that? Remember event position more self switches knight runners variable display. Oh, it's I think it's random
That was really cool. That was a very enjoyable game
Oh, what's this? Well, that's it. There isn't anything more. Shall we return to the main menu?
Okay, let's just chill out here for a while
Check your stats 1.6 million bucks
That's a lot
Damn eel
crew
fourth five thousand damn
Nine nine nine nine nine nine
Damn cool. So what happens if I say yes?
Is there any like super boss that I have to kill because now I have a ton of hp or something
Or is that just kind of it?
Spell the end with the letters. Um, I did that's the game. Well, that was cool. All right, well done
Let's see what happens. Is it gonna be? Yeah, there it is
That was hylix 1 we are going to absolutely play hylix 2. I like that. That was cool. I liked it a lot
so is hylix 2
a direct sequel or is it just hylix but a different is this a
Yes, it's a direct sequel. I just didn't know if it was some kind of
Standalone experience or something. Do we get any more info? Don't tell me it's a dumb thing to ask before playing it. But yeah
awesome
Hylix currently three dollars on steam right now game's been off for a long time
But a lot of people have been uh requesting I play this for a while and we'll definitely play the second one, too
That's a steal. Yeah, I mean like that's
That was a four like three and a half hour four hour experience two bucks. Come on gwen. I liked it a lot
Second hylix when four out of ten what? Wait, wait, wait, wait. What what happened?
Why people saying four to ten omega l what did I say that? When did I do that?
What you said it's a it was a miscommunication
Oh four hours. Okay. I was like what that's not correct
Yeah, I I don't I can't give this game a rating. I don't think it
I don't think I want to I think I would just say this is a recommended experience because to me
It was it was a great time
But I don't think that the experience that I had here I could be like well, let me say uh x out of 10
No, no, it was just great. It was just really cool
But like I gave you okay if you want it to be rated if this has to be a rating for you
This is for the experience for the experience
It is a it is a good plus good plus i'm not giving this a number rating
I don't think you can I think it's just a good plus which means that was fucking fun. That was great
This game was in a museum as a demo
Yeah, this game was to me was like more of like a an art journey and like an experience
That was good plus good plus what's what about good plus plus?
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, this was great. This was great plus
All right. I'm getting out of here. It was a very wonderful experience highly recommended
It's only three dollars and I can't wait to play the second one. I loved it
And that's gonna be the end of stream. I think it's a good place to call it
I'm gonna go eat some pizza. Well done. But yeah, I will see you guys the next time you will see me
is
maybe
Sunday sunday monday, we'll go sunday stick around on the weekend. I'll go sunday sunday night
But yeah, take care. I'm not sure what we're gonna do on sunday
I don't think we're gonna do hylix 2 on sunday change it up a little bit play the long drive
Maybe we'll see you're gonna do face cam. I was on cam today face cam is not gonna be a focus anymore
With it off. I can kind of just relax. I'm just gonna play hang out. Yeah, you'll see me from now and again
You'll see me you saw me today. It's gonna it's going back to the way that it was
Pre like 2019
pre 2020 where yeah
If i'm gonna play a horror game
It's gonna be on and i'm gonna do something where you need to see my face
It's gonna be on if I feel like just turning it on one day i'm playing and I it's gonna turn on
Which is not every single day. I'm having a lot more words not fun
But I really like this different environment a little bit more comfortable. I do like being on face cam, right?
But i've been enjoying this a lot. So i'm gonna keep doing it. What about sorcery?
I know that person's mother is pissed
Neon white on sunday. Hmm. We'll see i'll be in pre stream 30 40 minutes before the stream figure it out
All right. Good night guys. See you later. Take care of yourselves. See you sunday. Have a great rest of your evening or morning
Call your mother see you soon