Hey, what is going on, you ghouls and ghosts? It's me, Jerma, from the past or the future.
No, I'm kind of just here in the present. But we're on Man Manor tonight for a live commentary,
getting in the Halloween spirit more and more every day.
Seems like everybody is playing this map, by the way. Everybody's playing Man Manor to get themselves
pumped for the Halloween update, and to get themselves pumped in general for Halloween,
which is awesome. If you are unfamiliar, this map is the Halloween update map from last year.
It's got like, you know, pieces of pie, pumpkin pie, like candy and stuff like that. It's all
over the place. And where is everybody? Kind of weird. Getting on the point right now.
All right, there's plenty of people on each team. Uh-oh, Angie. Oh, I'm done. I'm dead. Maybe I'm
dead. So this is the update map, like I said, everyone's playing it. This is the map where
this huge boss comes out. If you haven't played this map, play it at least in the next couple
days or the next week or something like that, because it's very, very fun. See, look at everything.
It's like candy and stuff. Mm, delicious candy. Whoa, I'm being an idiot. Not paying any attention.
Let's go. Bring it on, Pierrot. Let's go, Mr. Pierrot. Oh, you're going to get away, are you?
No, you are not. Give me that help. Oh, we got crits, baby. Oh, don't you jump in here
Oh, God. Speaking of crits, he has... Oh, God. All right, we got it. We got it. Let's get on it.
So yeah, a giant boss will appear. He's the headless, haunted headless horseman. Hold on,
let me get this right. He is the horseless headless horseman. There we go. He appears and he
just melee one hit kills every single person. It's awesome. It can get really, really annoying,
though. I will say that it can get fairly obnoxious if you're trying to play. Let's say you're like
a great round. It's like, oh, I just killed 12 people. Oh, here comes the frigging monster
that's going to kill us all. It's like, great. That's exactly what I needed. Oh, God. Here we go.
We're doing all right. Let's keep moving. Let's keep moving. Oh, crit bomb. Crit bomb. Oh, come on
now. Oh, he got away. I'm actually going to... I'm at the last point. Oh, they got a teleporter.
I'm going to sneak on them. And there it goes. I didn't do it. I didn't do it. Get that candy.
So if you guys were wondering what I was being for Halloween, me and a couple of other buddies
are going to die. We're going to be the ninja turtles for Halloween. So it should be very,
very fun. We have like a whole huge getup already made. It's going to be crazy. Oh, he got the candy.
Oh, damn. It's going to be pretty crazy. We're being the ninja turtles, all four ninja turtles,
and one of our other friends is going to be Splinter. So we're going to go out into the town,
probably go into downtown Boston. Be crazy. Have some fun. Just like how you should on Halloween.
Don't get too crazy though. You know, don't let go egg in somebody's house or something,
because that's not cool. Where am I going? I keep on going way past the point.
And I keep on forgetting to not switch this. Oh, there he is. Oh, my God. There he is.
There he is. See, if you've never seen him before, there he is. He's running around
chasing somebody. I want to get a good look at him. Where is he? Oh, there he is.
And if you kill him with a melee kill, you get this. Oh, God, I'm it. He's coming after me now.
Let's see if I can just start smashing him. Oh, God. Pretty much this is where they got the idea
for the Saxton Hale mod. So if you're a fan of the Saxton Hale mod, this is pretty much its roots,
because people said, wow, that's pretty funny. And that's pretty fun. What if that person was
player controlled? And that's, I guess, where Saxton Hale was kind of born, the mod. So let's
get on. Can we even cap this point before I end this gameplay? Apparently not. Oh, lag. Lag.
So yeah, what are you guys doing for Halloween? Have you guys figured out what you were doing yet?
I'm kind of wondering, because I know some of you guys gave me your ideas, and some of them
were actually pretty good. Some, oh, God. Oh, what? What the hell? Did he just rage DC? What was that?
Oh, I got to get him. He doesn't even know where I am. He doesn't even know where I am.
All right, we got the point. We got it. Let's go. Oh, boy. Oh, can I get it? Can I get it?
Keep moving. Keep moving. Keep moving. Give me those crits. Give me those mini crits. All right.
We're good to go. Oh, my God. Out of nowhere. Oh, you want to go melee up in here? You want to
go melee up in here? Oh, boy. Somebody's spamming from somewhere. That soldier. Come on. Keep me
alive. Where's the candy? Where's the candy? Oh, boy. Oh, boy. Oh, boy. Come on, Captain. Come on.
Come on. I don't have much time. Not much time. Oh, give me that. Give me that thing. We got it.
We got this. Haunted gift. There we go. Blow up that stuff. Oh, my God. Sentry and a spy.
I got an achievement. Nice. A taco lantern. I think we're about to win this game. But yeah,
the Halloween update is supposed to come out, I think, either tomorrow or the next day. Today is
Tuesday. So yeah, it should be exciting. I saw the pyro face thing with the horns and the wings.
That's going to be pretty ridiculous. Hopefully, hopefully, they add some of that crazy stuff and
we get some... Oh, hey, what's going on, sniper? Hopefully, they add some crazy stuff. I want new
weapons. Like I said, I want new weapons. New weapons. Oh, let's do some dancing. Let's do
some dancing. Oh, give me that. It's over. If I can get... If I pick this up, it's pretty much over.
Oh, it's over. It's over. Oh, might as well taunt. Oh, my God. Get it. No.
Oh, you got to be kidding. We got it. Nice. And top frag. Cool. But yeah, hopefully,
you guys have a good safe Halloween. I got a very special video going up in the next couple days. So
I'll see you guys all next time. Take care, everybody.