Okay, you've got it. You're doing it. You must have clicked single player last time. All right
Well, it's it looks like something it's being weird. Okay, it should be downloading the mods right now
I guess it is my downloading it from you. Yeah, I assume just a chat the way it'll be worth it
We're talking Terraria
Right now I got a bar on my screen. That doesn't have any a list of anything on it. It's just like an empty bar
Just trust the bar. Okay, just don't do I'm just saying does this happen to you?
Like do you have like a no text on it? The bars are sitting there nothing downloading. Well last time
Me and Ashley played we both
like individually downloaded the mods
So why didn't you just tell me to download the mods?
Because this should be easier and I wanted to reduce the amount of pain that you would be caused like
You know
It should just download
It should I guess
But
Look, I'll show my screen so people can see. Hey everybody. Hi. Yes playing Terraria with star today, which is on TV. Oh
No, it's working
It's working installing. It's doing a lot of installing now
Is it gonna show you that should I like make sure I don't like I don't think it shows anything
Okay, I'm gonna I'm gonna squad invite you
You know, we're doing it this time. Oh, right. Okay. Yeah, I
Accepted I've accepted your squad in pleasure
All right. So, okay you press escape to open up your your your thing when you see the little shields
You click on the red shield to join my party
Brother my little brother. I just I needed to see how to jump first. All right, so I hit escape and
Then go to on the right hand side you got a little shield icon. There's a red one little bro. Yeah
There's a red one
These are so small. Okay
There right there. I just I clicked the red one. Oh, there you are
Did you make this house already? No this house starts here because of the mod
We have to do
All right. How do I?
There is okay. Is it just it's just like all these other games
So it's like all these other games, okay, you see it should be
You have a couple things in your inventory 9 and 0
9 and 0 I have 1 2 3 your top bar. You have 1 2 3 4 and it goes all the way to 0
Yeah, yeah, take the iron heart and drop it in the trash can
Revengeance drop it in the trash can
What the fuck are you talking about?
I have you not have annoying copper axe because you made this character without the mods. You don't have okay
Hold on here. Take this. Who's this? Who's Jeffrey? You're fine. Okay, I'm just gonna I'm just gonna oh
I know this one
Magical hammer, what should I do with this?
It's a hammer you can hit things with it. Let me just try watch it out. The boys are coming
Check it in
This is kind of loud
I'm just waiting for you to set up your volume. You see it's nighttime now. So the zombies are gonna come German
Okay, so what's that thing? There's slime. That's mine. That's my buddy's line. Alright, so what?
What what do we do?
What do we do? Yeah
First thing we need to build a bunch of houses because NPCs move into the houses
We need to gear up and prepare for our first boss fight German first boss fight
Yes, you don't you don't go fight the end of dragon after you download the game
Well, there's there's
Progression. It's like fighting in Dariel or the cook. Okay
I killed and then don't pick this up. All right, let's go. It's dark down here
Should I be like mining stone block sure
This is pretty damn loud
how do I settings I
Can feel this in my teeth? That's how loud it is
I
That's better. Yeah, but yeah guys are doing terraria today. This is just kind of a stars like yo, let's play terraria
I'm like, all right, you're my husband left what?
Germa has left. Oh, it's really awesome
This is probably the best dream. I have ever had
I don't that
My look my internet's fine. Everything's fine
And rejoin I'm coming in right now
Dude, this is so scuffed, bro
All right
That was weird. Maybe it's give us was I like all tabbed for a second. Maybe that's maybe can you not all tab in this game?
You should be fine
All right, so give me some like the general
Control stuff
General control stuff is just escape to open up that and you have the one through numbers
Yeah to hotkey whatever you have put up there, I would recommend to have torches up there. So how do I mean how do you make torches?
I'll give you some I have copper coins. Okay, so just hotkey torches
Just put them up in like four or something or is where I put them store brothers now. Okay
You got some weapons, you know, put them up there. There's also an auto sort inventory
The bottom of your inventory the bottom right is your trash can where you delete items
And the box next the next to that you should have you have to enable
Auto trash so if you put something in that trash can every time you pick it up from now on it will automatically get trashed
Okay, so it's which will save your life later. Okay, so like if I let's say if I put stone block in there
It'll just always delete stone block. Yeah, but you don't want to delete stone blocks right now. How do I place?
Yeah, everything just goes into the hotkey system
So if you have it, you know stone blocks on for then you're placing it
All right. You should have we should we wait till daytime or should we keep go down and look for some like treasurer?
Let's chop some trees. We're gonna need a lot of wood
No, but you're gonna have to join the red team again turn the red team, okay, it like shows us where we are
Did I do it? Yeah
The flying demon eyes have you ever played this game like ever
No, no, not really. I think I've opened it like a few times randomly and then it just that's it
Are gonna be stir sucks Terraria Jerma Saturdays
Don't say that what if this is gonna take over your life
Okay, so also when you press escape you see on the left-hand side. You have a bunch of options
Crafting down here. Yeah, so wood platforms are very important
You hold down right-click to make a bunch. You're just turning wood into wood platforms. It shows you the rest of the shit
Okay, and then it's these that you place down so you can like fall through these but also do they have to be an atom
What can I just make them like in here?
They have to be connected to something or if there's a back wall you can place it on a back wall
So I made it really I really did not know you didn't know anything
I thought you had like a base. No, I mean I just I knew it was you craft
Well, I just made like a hundred of the other day. Oh, I
Just wouldn't my wooden platforms go
That was pretty cool piano sound I drop hello. Hello. Did you pick you pick those up didn't you? Yeah, I
You threw them away and I have them as what Chad's saying. Oh, all right. Well here that made him for you. Here's um
Thanks
This inventory is junk. So let me move some stuff out of the way. I'll wait for you little bro
How do you heal is there like a food? I feel over time on
Certain well, actually there's healing potions. You won't have any and then you just press H to auto heal if it's in your inventory
I'll give you some okay. What when we start digging to help
Not yet. Okay, so what would you consider is like a good amount of wood that we have
Uh, we're good. I have like 300 we're good. Okay, we're good. Should we go down? What is this?
How do I delete the quest thing?
Ignore it. Just move it out of the way. You can drag it. I
Want to go find a desert dig straight down you coward?
First first thing I want to go find a desert. All right, you got it
Okay, I'm gonna give you a little small task
Should we know?
It's so dark
Like I should he's gonna die
Alright, I get it. I get it. I get it. You want me just to be the guy that falls in but lights up the area
No
Also, I'm I'm gonna go like healer and you're gonna have to do everything
Can you hit diagonally? Why am I only going forward?
That's the shitty sword. Oh
Yeah, you like this is a staff
Yeah, I gave you a bow
Okay, I'm gonna give me a second. Just protect me for a minute. That's what I've been doing
godly copper sword
Okay, I got a superior amethyst staff put the torches over here put torches of one
Do you really gonna put torches on one? I am this guy is really going to put torches on one. What's wrong with that?
That's the most okay
Wand of sparkling. I don't know any of this stuff is man
You brought you brought me into I've never had ice cream before in my whole life
And you brought me into a Baskin Robbins that has like 500 flavors and you tell me to try everyone and I'm like
Holy shit a flavor before though
I
Never had flavors before
What is blueberry? I don't know what that is. Let me try it. Why did I put that there?
I don't know you like really want this to be like, oh shit. That's my greatest place. I
Can't I'm telling you I'm having trouble seeing
Is there a man? Oh, there's a man of ours in there. Yeah, so hey, what's what's your preferred play style?
Like are you a major your fighter?
What are you into what's the one that wears glasses because I'm why I can't see
You're gonna die dude. I'm gonna die. I gave you potions. I thought
Okay, it's daytime. Press H
H
There you go
It's my favorite song. This is this song is great
night for a nightline
Alright, so you wanna go find a desert. Yeah change the resolution to make the game bigger
I mean it's I have it on 1920 by 1080
Should I not do that? You can also press the plus and minus to zoom in and out
There we go. That's much better. That's so much better
Yeah, that's 10. Okay, I could put the glasses on. Thank you
You're the other you're the eye doctor
Okay, I couldn't okay good I'll take them I'll take the
Should we go down down no, this is not a game we use we go down
It is a game where you go down, but not yet. Not yet. Do zoomed out mode is best. Yeah. Well, I'm gonna train my eyes
The more comfortable I get inside the game. I will zoom out a little
There are bosses that are gonna kill you for being zoomed in
Just know let him play at his own pace. Okay
Thanks, just let him relax. This is less minecraft more Dark Souls
Okay, he's not bored enough yet to do the I fell in that whole joke. That's a good sign. No, I
It's been enough. It's been enough time. Okay. No, what is this is gold a
tin
Just follow me
I want it. I'm gonna stop every time you see some fucking tin
Maybe is it worth getting?
Zoom the UI too. Wait, that's true. I can do that. I can zoom in the UI
Here here's uh, here's some potions. Whoops. I drank it drank potions. Okay, it was an accident
I can heal you now where everything is everything is great
Okay, that's a little better. I'm just playing the iPad version the one that has everything bigger. Oh check this out
Here's a here's a tutorial moment. So you have your pickaxe and obviously you're gonna click these little walls, right? Yeah
You press alt and you see how it there's a yellow marker
alt
You should press all at one time
I did like yellow block. Okay, so just aim forward and like put your mouse the left side of the screen
Yes, and then when you hold left click, it'll auto dig you forward
So you don't have to individually click each block, but you still have to like walk forward
I'm not getting the yellow thing. You're describing press alt again. It's controlled by the way
Is it default? Oh, I don't know. Whoops. Sorry. Guess don't listen to me again
Now look we're working together why is the last two games we played together mining games
And you notice that watch out behind us
We played that deep rock galactic. Oh, no, we played
Well, we kind of did it you you like disappeared you looked at the painting for too long
All right, let's go. I got tin
I'm fucking so we look at our desert. You want to do this?
This is iron there's something led same thing. All right, you just murdered that squirrel
So lead dirt was a lead stone, so what what's the what's the hierarchy here? What's what's like the the tier list for wars?
What's 10 on that?
The tier list for oars is we probably really only need lead
Here's the desert was 10 on that one 10 is 10 is non-existent. Oh
It does a thing to your screen to it, doesn't it?
Okay, Jerma, this is our new home. This is we're gonna live we're gonna live. Hey, we're already used to that
All right. Here's what here's what you're gonna do. Help me
Flatten this ground. All right, so just with the flat it out
Flatten it out because we need to build a home because in Terraria when you have homes people show up
uninvited on
Uninvited but they're very important NPCs. Should I fill this hole?
Sure, you know, just make it look nice, you know users some of your creativity. Okay
It's dirt right was it sand
Sand there's a giant hornet over here. I kind of that scared the shit out of me. Help me
Whoa, all right, that's cool. What now it's all dirty. We have to move somewhere
Okay goes away, how are you throwing these knives that's so cool
Let me get dirt in here
So, how do you just this is not dirt? How do I take it back? I put it back in my inventory
You should auto be. Oh, yeah, just delete it again
Okay, sand block sand block sand block. All right. So now I can I just fill this
How far how big do you want the house?
way too big
We're eventually we're going to be like a metropolis
What?
It's gonna be big. It's gotta be big German. Yeah, this is the most boring bar to Terraria and you need to get it done quick
So from you to me, that's not big enough
It'll do for now. It's like in real life. If this was scaled. This would be like a this would be like a 2500 square foot house
It's not big enough
For now
For now, there we go
So you I'll lay the foundation down to here's just like I have to do this and I don't know what to tell you
To do a while. I'm doing it, you know, what about that slime? I'll get it
Got it you got it. Where's my wood? Where is your wood wood right here?
All right, so I'm gonna do
What about watch up your little yeah, I want you a little guy to get hurt. Do I need wooden block? Oh
Another hornet. You can't get in though
We're protected
Okay, we're building slave encampments, by the way, I hope you're okay with that
Just control again turn off auto mine. Oh, yeah, you have to press control control also auto places blocks. Oh
Alright, so how do you want to do this?
But I want to do one. Did you just say we were doing what you just what are we doing? What are we building here?
Oh, I'm let me let me do one. Let me just do one watch over this is chicken
There's ignore the chicken Jerma stay focused there's too many enemies to look at
You get too many flavors. I've never had blueberry turkey before
Yeah, you do might need to get more wood. You know what? I'm sending you on a fucking wood errand run
You got it. Well, tell me what to do. Here. Hold on. You don't get wood
Go to the right go to the right go to the right. No wood that way go to the right
Just get as much wood as you can Jerma. Well, I gotta be very I'm gonna prepare it. Hold on
So I'm gonna get my did these degrade over time
No tools, no, okay
That would be a bad game
What it yeah?
Unanimously if your tools degrade it and if every single time link swung his sword it broke that would be a bad game
You need to not use that weapon
It's that bad
How many times can I fire this? Okay, German German German German. Oh wait. No, you can't do that yet. Come on
Just go get wood. I'm going to get wood. What is it? What's my okay? My health is up there
All right. No, how much what do you want?
Just so much
Wait, so there's people freaking out. There's a present over there
Hold on
Did you get it?
Uh, you probably did open present open present. Oh, oh
Wait
Oh
Yeah
This game's fucking pretty fun
All right, open the present right click
Candy canes walk. Can I can my room be the candy cane room?
Yes. Okay. Thank you
You bring me the candy canes i'll make you a candy cane room
Really role play in this little brother role very very
intensely
There's like a big pig over here, too
I'm almost at a man. Oh
I am at a man. Oh
Do you get there's like exp in this game, right?
God damn it, dude
Uh kind of yeah
So should I be making like a stone?
pickaxe or no
No
What do you mean? No
Isn't that how every single one of these games works
Why is hey chat? Why isn't this valid housing? What did I do wrong?
Unless something changed that's so big. It's supposed to be 10
How much I got a lot of wood I have is way bigger than a door
Oh, I don't think I have a door on the whole building. That's probably what it is
So give me a number you don't need doors
When can I turn this question to stir the npc over there?
It should tell you what's wrong. Yeah, it's just saying it's not valid
What it is am I wiping out like the whole forest here? Should I be planting seeds?
No
Fuck nature
No, hey
I feel like I should be planning stuff
so
Hey guys
anything else
No, not really
I have done this so many times
And it has never not
been valid housing germa
Do you understand?
How can you all right? There's a super dragon here now like what this is going very well
How much wood do you want is 252 wood enough?
Just keep getting wood. What?
No, you're fighting this super dragon and I don't even you're just gonna keep me on the
I am one of your like peons in warcraft. You get to play the game. I have to just hit the fucking tree
I'm just gonna make it one bigger. I guess
i'm just waiting for like 25 more of me to show up behind me and hit the uh
Tree with the pickaxe
That always ended up happening that happened to you too, right? Whenever you were playing, uh, like warcraft 2 or warcraft 3
Never that was never me
You never just like click and dragged your whole screen and put every single pea on a peasant on cutting trees
German you need to come back. I just
I was on the way. You told me no come back come back
There's there's a whole housing issue
I have 450 wood if that's not enough and I don't know what is
Wait, oh, there's extra wood over here regular room. This is a regular room chat
See i'm recycling
It's getting dark. I am coming back. All right, if I have 460 can I eat the apples? That's a lot of apples
People are screaming at me to plant the acorns and you told me no
All right, how do I give stuff like that's what I had it out originally 12. Holy shit. This room sucks
You can't be in this room
What?
This is a chair and a table and two giant indiana jones walls that are gonna crush you
I don't want to live here. That's your room
isn't all
Watch out
Watch out. This is like an air squid. Watch out
Get out of there a freak out moment
You're gonna get killed
Get back inside
Quick go down go down the top of the chimney in my safe not indiana jones room
I promise I won't crush you
Did you activate a wave and like gears of war? What the fuck is happening? It's just nighttime
I'm out of mana
They can't get up here, right?
No
Holy shit, your slime guy's really good bottom torches
It doesn't matter how many torches a room has if it has one. It's good
You guys are just like making the most insane shit up right now and i'm going to just start beating you
What the fuck? How do you open doors?
Oh you just yeah
Ah, he can cast spells. He can cast spells, but he can't open a damn door
All right
Well, there's no wall missing
This is the worst day of my life. I think it's actually i'm having a good time. This is like fun for me
I mean, this is i'm really actually enjoying it
There's no door. There's no roof
We need a roof
I this is I like this. This is fun to me
You might you're having you're like panicking right now. I'm just like i'm enjoying hanging out
Hey, hey, here's what you do press escape go down the workbench down there
Do not let this guy in this guy's a piece of shit. Don't let him die. He's uh, he's coming in
He's in the room he's in the quick crush him quick squish him in the indiana jones room
i'll get him
I got him. All right, so I get his head watch out
Okay, german german german come here next to the bench. I want to give you this thing
I want to get I can I how do I hand you items?
You pick it up from your inventory then you right click to throw it
All right, I give you one there. I just give you 460
Or just fix the what wood?
Oh, then remember the mission
Um, excuse me. Hold on. Where is my um
Immediate thing i'm gonna sell to a vendor a piece of gear you're gonna give me
Here take those walls
Those are wood walls. You see how the background is wood
We need to fill this whole place with with wood the whole thing. I want candy cane though
Oh my god, we can do the candy cane after all right, so just put these in the back
Uh, is it okay if I like don't color in the lines?
I didn't know a very long time to remove them. I what what do you mean?
It's it's a pain in the butt
Okay, it's like kind of hard to do this
Okay, no control, right?
Uh, yeah, the control thing should auto fill as well
Is that a firework?
Yeah, I leveled up my summoner proficiency
the absolute speed
And the bottom two
But everything the whole thing he's muted. He muted himself. Are you still talking to me? I'm just gonna say
I'm talking to everyone who's like going crazy mad at me because they think i'm doing something wrong
Oh, you know, I can tell you I i'm in like a great position right now
Like this is all you i'm just like building walls and like you like know things if people know things in your chat
I just live in your house right now
Like when the toilet breaks in your house, like I don't call the repairman
You do anyone who said I needed a door go fuck yourself
You apologize right now
I'm having a good time
It is like
Here i'm missing i'm making these platforms so you can remove that that extra accidental ceiling
What do you mean one up here? You need to pickaxe that ceiling that shouldn't be that way pickaxe of the ceiling
Yeah, remove the wood ceiling. That's there. You understand take out you want me to get rid of like this the ceiling
Like the let the this like the bottom but the wood of yes the bottom part of the butt, right?
This needs to look perfect. Otherwise, no one's gonna want to live here
Now these platforms could be a little better
I'm not gonna say anything about what the platforms are being removed. They're just so you can stand on them jerma
It's like a ladder you ever use a ladder before you short
Oh
You can say you can say fuck it all
This isn't this isn't uh
Yeah, I was I was as tall as you in that one picture that people refer to
I was like
What about what do I do?
You just wait for me. What? All right. So what what is mysterio doing over here?
What is that stereo?
Holy shit, are you really?
Unbelievable, you want me to get rid of this one too again. What are you gonna die again?
The mod adds these early game robbers with like pistols that just like instant kill you
Put on head or pre-recorded. All right, where's the shoe? Can I put a shoe over head in the game?
Am I safe in here?
Yes, you're safe jerma. Just don't open the door. But I like it's it's like don't press the button and i'm about to
Don't press i'm gonna go talk to mysterio. All right, i'll finish this. I would not want to live here. Go talk to mysterio
Uh, we need more walls
So we said mine straight. Yeah, can I like just mine straight down?
And have like a little basement thing
Um, there's something I want you to do before we do that then then here
This is very important before I can set you free. Sure
Can you right click that does it say spawn point set?
No
Uh, if I right click it, it does nothing now
spawn point set
Okay
Now you can dig straight down
dig straight down
Is that smart though, or is that just gonna be like a comedy moment? Um, what I would actually recommend doing is once night ends
You know how you can press m and it opens the map. Yeah
There are some tunnels that go down not this desert one. Don't do this one
But like we pass some you can start exploring those caves and if you find chests chests have uh,
special items in them
Um what I will also give to you
Can you sell stuff in this game or should I just start trying like what what should I not be holding on to?
Uh, like random flowers you've picked up are probably useless
How do I sell them? Just do it just trashing them sell
Uh, we need npcs to show up before we can sell things
Why is clicking this just making it brighter?
Oh, never mind
Uh, I have a wrath element
Um, should I be holding how do I hold blood in my pockets?
Anything that you're not sure that you need just dump in there just dump all your garbage in that box
Okay, is there a way to dump all?
No
Oh well
Gotta keep that tin
Is there like a
Shift click or something to make it so it goes do I don't click and drag?
Okay, there we go
blood droplets
Victory shard. Yeah, you're gonna have to sort through this
I've never played this really before but I know
For a fact that these seashells should not be put in here
Throw them in there deposit all
I thought wait, what do you mean deposit all?
You just told me I couldn't do deposit all everyone's screaming. Oh
I have but everybody i'm sorry. I wouldn't I didn't say but star was just telling me I couldn't do that
I don't think you could because I don't I don't know why you would want to do that because usually you have
Inventory that you need
I I would have I would have taken a look
Okay
um
So i'm gonna
You want to go into a cave?
You want to go together?
Okay. Yeah, let's just finish this room
Let me get some stuff
Let me redo this. How do you make torches?
uh, you need gel and
uh
Wood platforms. All right. How many you get gel from the
Yeah, I got it 33 torches
That's good. Okay
You'll also find a lot from going down there. Yeah, anything. What about like a better sword or something? How do I get do that?
We really don't have any
Anything yet. What about these flaming arrows?
I'm making these, you know, you know what we can go do
potions you guys how do you make rope normally
All I remember is oh
All right. I got my candy cane rolls
Never mind. I usually just make cobweb stuff. We haven't done. They come left
Here's the play we're gonna get we're gonna get good items fast. You like having good items
I guess but I wasn't really ready
I got flaming arrows at 10 flaming arrows. I got my magic wand thing
All right
The somebody said there's a funny joke I can do
There's always a funny joke. You can sell everything to calvin
Does that mean anything to you?
No
Unless our
The merchant's name
Oh, yeah, he just showed up in the merchant where you can sell stuff showed up
Here take this
Mannequin increases your maximum mana
Ooh, so is there besides?
I want to be the mage
Okay, so at night time falling stars drop from the sky and if you combine three of them you make one of those
Really? You're gonna want to collect those until you get max mana with this little pot down here
Just dude just trash that sword. I never want to see you use it again
But I need it for a little I have little stabs to break through is this what is this honey?
What's up there tin?
Uh, that's lead which we will need
Who's hitting me? This is a little green slime blending with the world over here. Oh
So, okay, what's the dirt equivalent in minecraft? It just oh, I need to read something just build build build. Who cares just dirt
Uh wood platforms or ropes if you have them like you can climb up this
You can
Oh damn
Uh, who's da dais the demolition dais the demolitionist. He's the guy that sells us
Bond I gotta go talk to that guy
I'm trying to get i'm leaving you alone for a second little timmy
And c chat he's in prison
He's not going anywhere
eat slime
All right. I need to get up here
alone
Fuck
Got it eat star eat star eat star eat star
They want you to eat me
eat star
Oh
Oh the mana star I gave you yeah, you have to actually use it
Like pick it up and left click outside of your
All right, i'm going down here
No, no
I need I need you you do you need you need me? Okay. I do need you
Actually, maybe we could go down the tunnel if we see another before we find the thing
the thing
duck
That's pretty good. Yeah
Pretty good, dude
I'm gonna sneeze and I can't do anything about it
Uh
Why would I kill the duck?
Uh, you cannot swim make sure you don't fall down that hole
What do you mean? I cannot swim. I made it a concrete
Yeah
What really?
Yeah, if I would have fallen there, but you fell in
Well, yeah, like you can only jump once you've hit the ground. Oh, okay
Well, I gotta stop
So why are we going this far away?
Uh, I'm personally personally i'm looking for corruption
Which is a a biome that we're not currently in give me your mouse for a minute. I need to do something
Are they hostile a boar's hostile is now
Cool, all right, they drop bacon, which is good bacon
Yeah, there's one bacon
So what's the first boss?
Well, the first one I want to fight is
a giant worm
In the desert, which is why we built the desert top epic
I'll see like down here this chest. Yeah, this is what life is all about in terraria, dude
It had like garbage in it here, uh
I'm gonna give you a bunch of rope
What's your what's your what's your opinion on bacon when I say the word bacon? What do you think of?
Uh, I think of slices of bacon take those potions that are in there
And there's that rope. All right, so I technically can just go like
Yeah, that's fun what are these little tanks? All right
Uh, they're little tanks
Oh, man air shot
Oh, dude food epic, bro
I know right. I yeah, that's a delayed bacon reaction
Yeah, okay. This direction sucks
It's just desert
Desert and yungle
Is that a bad thing?
Yeah
Looking for corruption, bro
Is it poisonous or something?
No
Oh, that's a cool particle there
What the fuck?
Wait, um, should I not go down there?
You can do it. I believe you need to heal
I'm good
There's a treasure chest over here. Oh wow treasure chest holly
Well, it's a festive holly
This is cool
Not the desert anymore
So you I don't think you ever said the person that you wanted to fight
The person we want to fight the first boss big giant desert worm
It's a shot like a roman candle. That's all I did
People are saying what about the slime man? What about it?
Is that the first boss?
How do I get like a little buddy?
How do I heal?
H if you have a potion I thought I did
I'll give you some
I guess not
Oh, no, I do I do from knocking down trees eat an apple
Oh, how do I eat them just by clicking on them use? Yeah, and we use everything only one
Oh only one
I did have a healing potion. Why was it not working?
Uh, there's a healing cooldown. That's pretty long
That shows if your inventory is minimized. There's a healing sickness like
40 seconds something cool down
Oh, yeah. Okay. Okay. Well fed I see
And a well thought is different
I gotta be careful here these little owls. What the hell that your little guy keeps hitting these owls
And then they start to fucking attack me
They're always attacking they are
Yeah
Don't blame me
Okay, is it like bees can they go in water?
Um, most things actually can't
No, this thing can't
Where if there's no corruption this direction, I'm if you're false
How would it be my fault? What do you do with the money the copper?
Uh, you can buy things from the npcs in the house as we made. I mean the present is remade
Is it
Is this a slime present?
Why is there something?
They're very generous. Oh, okay. I get it
Currency can be exchanged for goods and services
Oh
It's tin very helpful
We went really really really far away
Yeah, we did
Are we gonna have to make a new house?
Oh, I can't even I don't even know where our house is
There's like nothing in this direction
Is it you're looking for something very very very specific?
It's usually like right next to you
Here, you know what you have, uh the blue potion in your indoor recall potion
Yes
Yeah, if you use that it will take you to the bed
Oh, that's all right. That's cool
I can actually drown in this
Yeah
Get out of the way fucking slimes
It's something that should is it how do I make like a cool staff?
a cool staff that's
The one you have will be decent for a while. Okay
For you for you to get a cool one. We're gonna need to kill a boss
Okay
Settle down you don't have to scream at me
I'm screaming
Are you back at home? No
Should I be?
Yeah, i'm still going in this direction and it's I don't think it's gonna be this way
Okay, so you can try and go down the caves and find chests
Like an eggnog
All right, i'm going back
There's a chef in the house. There's two people. Who's this guy calvin?
They said sell to calvin
Am I about to like let a vampire come into the house?
Whoa, he just came in. I I didn't open it. Oh, oh
You mean actual vampire? I thought you meant like by selling to him. He would turn into a vampire and you enabled
Germa is it i've heard good things friend
Okay
sell price
Will this giant wasp kill this guy?
Yeah
He's gonna baseball
baseball
Don't fall for it. I tried the baseball before
Not impressed people are gonna scream at me. I don't know if
I was not this way god dang it and I I can't recall because you slept in the bed
I'm probably doing something so wrong
My iron anvil
Don't ever sell ore or gel
Did I?
You probably did no I didn't
buy the hat
bug net
Piggy bank. What about a piggy bank? Do we need that?
Uh, I don't worry about piggy bank
Okay
Where's this hat people are talking about? I don't see a hat
There's a shuriken
A mining helmet
Is there a quick way to see how much money I have?
Um
Is it I have one gold
If you're gonna buy anything talk to the demolitionist and buy bombs bombs and dynamite
Get the money when you die you drop money as well. So you might lose it
moon glow
Why did you sell the wolfram? I don't even know what that is
I I I just it's a piece of glass to me
Don't be afraid to ask, you know, you ask questions. Okay star. What is wolf from shard?
Well, it's a very early game item you can craft them into early game armor and they're pretty good. Okay. What is moon glow?
moon glow is
Normally used to make potions, but it's not important because we have a potion npc so I wouldn't bother. Okay
What is gel?
Gel is the drop from
The jellies and mostly used in torches
A couple other things what's blinkroot?
Also used for potions and not relevant for us
What is deathweed seeds?
Anything that's like plant-based or seed-based is going to be a potion crafting and does not matter
I'm helping you study for the test with flashcards
Okay
So let me craft something
Uh, what do I want to do? So we couldn't find the thing that you wanted to find you said buy bombs from this guy
Yeah
bomb grenade or bomb
Uh, not grenades but what dine either bombs or dynamite dynamite's very expensive though
How many should I have like five ten?
I have 64 right now. You have 64 bombs
Yeah, what?
I just spent all my money on bomb
Do you have any of the nature essences?
um
nature essence
It might it might be torches on the ground
what
I just like threw everything in there. So I put my bomb back
Everything that I don't know what it's used for is just going in this chest
Okay, that's how you should do it. I'll make a second chest because we'll probably need more
Before we can get the super chest
potions apple torch
Annoying how does it how does a copper axe annoying?
I don't know dude candy cane. Well, I want that out just in case I need it. No, what's my thinking?
Don't use those doesn't mind
All right wand of sparking or
Superior amethyst staff 15
13 4% crit
I mean, okay
blue good
Green great and then what like purple legendary or something hot? What's the item? Yeah, it's just like there's random names
There's like murderous godly legendary
They're all like the same basic stats still as long as it's not negative. It's fine. So green is better than blue
I actually don't know the order
I'm just gonna prefixes. Okay
All right, so um
Are we gonna stick around in here? We're gonna adventure again or what do you want to do? Um, hold on
I'm grabbing these stars and then we're gonna go to the right because it's gonna help speed things up a lot if we can
Find that the corruption was looking for it's probably just right up where we started
Make sure I get all my shit ready
Okay, I got i'm all right
Purple is the best
All right sick. All right, let's go
Uh, here's mana
Oh now I have three mana stars
Now you don't think this is too dark don't you think we should have like a path lit up maybe one day
I can do a flare
All right zombie ahead
Just I want to make sure you can see him
I can see clearly. What is that weapon that you're using right now? You have like a big like claw
You have torches in your hot bar. Yeah, I know but he got mad at me when I did this
I'm sure you can you can do that all you want. I'm not gonna get mad
You said torrent
I meant like torches on the ground and the base were annoying because you the ground on the base gets filled up by a whole bunch
of nonsense
I can make some wood armor. Do you have any armor on a tiny bit? What's that?
fallen star
That's it. That's what you need three of
Really?
Yeah, and after I have three of these I can what?
Combine them into the mana crystal. Oh
Somebody's house. Oh
Wait, this is where you built this. This is where we started. Oh, okay
Why don't we just use this place? That place is way better than yours
You think it is
But you're wrong, oh because we're not that one doesn't have people trapped inside of walls to make sure they stay there
Yeah, so what does this mean stir? I've got snapped in half by a demon eye
That's where we died
Track i'm gonna track them lead the target star got snapped
Look at these air shots
So i'm assuming we're probably gonna do a thing
Where we just both stand above cave and drop bombs down the cave
eventually
That is the plan or we get the super bomb that auto drills to hell
Auto drills to hell
Yeah, if I alt click an item it locks them so I don't auto deposit them. That's good to know. Oh, yeah
Yeah, yeah, that's important
So why don't we just like start digging down and maneuvering?
Why are we just walking left and right?
there's
Okay, we've been playing for an hour and all we've done is walk very far left and right. It's all it's all you've done
I didn't even have to make noise for that one
All right, somebody's house
This is one of the mods. It's a boss, but only in hard mode
But it has a chest up here
Listen, I had money
and nothing else
Nothing else. Okay. This is what I was looking for
Something got in here. How did this get in here?
It's not placing torches. I died
I I can't go down
Why did you bring me in this? That snowman's gonna fuck you up, dude
Remember to heal h h h
What is this?
What did you bring us?
Don't shoot
Okay, you need to keep these off of me
We need to fight these we need to fight while we descend down into the corruption
bomb the shadow orbs
This is giving too many things. This is not like the first zone in world of warcraft
i'm still right now on
kill the
boars
And you're telling me we're gonna bomb through the shaft. We're gonna run through this way. You got five seconds
Pick up the crystal
It's a very simple drama. We just have to descend the shaft
I have no torches. No
I like this music send the shaft kill the snowman
All right, if you can do the entire
Do you want to build a snowman song right now? And I mean without even looking it up and just going I will give you
a dollar
No, I would give you a dollar and store credit to game stop
Holy shit, I thought you just killed yourself. I thought I did too
Dude
You're the one who doesn't know what they're doing and you're going faster than me
I'm just trying to get back up
Give me the apples
All right. I'm good. Remember one apple right right right right right right one apple
You brought me into the first like wow dungeon before I even know what my character's rotation is
Your rotation is shoot staff i'm the person that gets screamed at in the dead minds because I don't know how to heal somebody
I'm the person in the dead minds that's playing a healer. That is auto attack right clicking on people
And cannot figure out why all right, let's go
It's too fast, okay, see those orbs under the ground are you zoomed out enough that you can see them?
um, no, yes
I can see the pearls. That's what we're here for. We're here for those pearls. I need the bomb
Should I just should I just kill the enemies?
Yeah
Don't fall in that hole. I'm gonna try not to
How do you just how do you throw bombs?
In your in your spot holding dude, you're gonna don't die. Don't die
That worm's coming up again
Okay, I hardly knew you
I was gonna hang out in the house
Can I just lock myself in here? Yeah, I'll be back, honey
Yeah, give me my give me some wood here
I'm just gonna block myself in here. I'm a i'm the fifth npc
All right, i'm gonna make some armor
Oh, man, I forgot you can be annoying in this game
You're like the moment, you know that you can be a bard and play music and enemies you
No, that's i'm i'm that's not gonna happen. All right, let me go
So arcane dust no, no, no, I need to pull some materials up wood. Can I just make wooden armor stone armor?
Uh, you should be able to make wood armor. There's a bunch of cactus around make cactus armor cactus armor
Yeah
How much does it take to make one?
I don't know. We'll find out
But also in terraria when you have a full set like if you have a helmet armor and leggings of uh cactus
Then you get an extra bonus
Okay
cactus
I had to do that. Hold on. Where does this go?
All right, that's better. How many do I need? Oh what?
When I was only two
Why is it?
Why is there a uh metal gear rising?
Like bar down here how well I did on the level?
No reason
Are you fighting a boss right now?
No, I ran
Okay cactus lamp
Cactus, how do I make cactus armor?
Uh stand near the anvil
And you have enough of it and it'll show the option when you press escape
You bombed a second. What it's supposed to be three to some of them
I only thought I did the two
There were two right there. Okay, whatever
I didn't pick anything up from it. Did I?
How the fuck I need my axe
I think I have to go back
Where's my pickaxe? There it is
Let's get
Cactus
You can't even cut cacti with a sword zero out of ten
You can pickaxe the sand underneath the cactus and then the whole cactus goes away. Oh
Do you get more for doing it like this or does it not matter at all the same?
Oh hold shift to auto select the correct tool
Well, that's the best fucking advice. I've heard all day
I didn't know you could do that
Holy shit, that's that's that's amazing
Wow
um
That's the best. Yeah, that works wonders
Like I had 32 copper
Hold control while mining to make it easier
Gotta hold shift gotta hold control gotta what else do I gotta do?
Hold me in your arm. I think I have enough
I remember watching you play this before a long long long time ago
and eventually you got to a point where
There was so much going on on the screen at the same time
Yeah, it turns into a bullet hell. Yeah, it was just
This fire everywhere. You would just like
Like a machine gun out of your hands
Yep. Right now. This is our humble beginnings
but you turn into like uh
All right a jojo character you guys like jojo, right? That's all you're talking about. It's like underwear cactus bikini
Ooh, I have a good spell for you. And now we're ready to slam a boss cactus leggings
cool
Cactus breastplate
cactus helmet
So is it boots or is it just legs head and uh breastplate?
Legs head breastplate. Yeah, and is there a certain place I have to put this?
Uh, if you right click it it goes to the right side of your screen. There's an inventory over there like what you're wearing equipment
If you right click it'll auto equip
Oh, I see. Okay
Why does this guy keep talking to me?
Trying to get past the
All right, so I have uh, i'm i'm
I currently am
Uh aquaman
Gingerbread cookie
mistletoe
Oh
Modern improvement to all stats for 30 minutes. Do you want this?
Uh, I feel like this is a u item
What are you? Hey, what is what have you been doing?
Don't tell what the fuck are you doing?
What are you doing?
That was my lamp
Oh my god, our beds are right next to each other
Well, no, they're not our heads are
All right
Are we ready to fight this boss?
Um, there's a couple things we need hold on. Let me look up the other one rotten. All right
I need to put some stuff away
Wait, I gotta make the don't deposit this thing, right?
Can you alt click? What is it?
And my bombs? Yeah, does that work?
Kind of you look very good. All right
You can hover over your armor to see the set bonus
Plus one defense. Oh, that's cool
Okay, we need to wait for night. I need to get one of those stars
Also, we need to kill a storm antlion, which is going to be in this
Antlion, but it's blue. It's very different than other animals
This is way more than I thought this game was
This game has a lot
and like I said
It turns into a bullet hole
All right
So what i'm going to do after I do this fun
We do this fun little tutorial session where we hang out and we fight a few bosses and we play for a while
Uh, i'm gonna like look up those wikipedia articles of this game
And then determine after reading the wiki pages if it's like yeah, i'm gonna do this long term
We'll get well like after we start killing the first few things here. We're gonna pick up
The pace really quickly in a moment
What are you doing? I'm broken
Oh, I have to give you the thing
thing, uh
That i'm dropping it right here
Is that in vile thorn?
I pick it up again
So what is this? That is that is your new wand
new wand
Oh 10 magic damage, can I is there a way I can like compare two items?
No, just trust me. That one's better. This one's better multi hits a lot
So the damage is misleading
Whoa
Not as far though
Yeah, it's pretty short range, but it's
Especially because the first bosses we're gonna fight are like worms it multi hits all the segments of the worm and does a lot of damage
Oh, that's cool
A lot of stuff down here
on healing push off
God damn
See what you're standing on right now. I don't think we can mine it yet or bomb it
I don't think bombing works, but we need these fossils
We need better pickaxes, which we'll get after we fight the first bosses. Okay
It's really good in tight spaces
Oh, you can do a little a little in between huh? Yeah, it goes all
Oh, yeah, it shoots through walls too. Oh
Kind of out of mana
When you do get mana potions j
Uses them
For germa day for germa. I know that and that's my name
Oh and enemies drop stars that give you mana. Yeah
Picked up on that a little bit
These are the ones we I need a a mandible from one of these these blue boys, man. Okay, we got it
Okay, we can leave
What about that coin?
a coin
There's a coin over there
It's a it's a silver coin. I don't care
Well, what an adventure that was feeling germs never gonna play this again
Uh, I don't know it seems like it's kind of fun
uh
Walk left and right find one of the fallen stars and don't combine it. We need one. I have one
Uh, okay drop it. I love this dude. Oh my god
I know
Oh, I know two enemies are nearby. We need another one
And we need a furnace I need to make torches rope coil how can I can craft copper coins?
Uh, it changes your silver coins into copper coins
Find the fallen
Uh mine some stone. We need stone or drop bombs on it
stone
Issue here
All right. This thing actually is pretty great
That's shit. I need
torches
Yeah, this is bad and I gotta go get I gotta make torches
This thing is fucking awesome
Holy shit
Yeah
Magic weapon proficiency leveled up
There's a guy with a gun
I'm dead. What's going on? You have to wait to respawn
I'm not dead
I killed the I killed the guy with the gun
Holy shit. I did it
And I still can't even see I gotta come back
Okay, they're like 5000 more enemies or something
Uh, no, it's wood for
torches, right
Do you have sand block?
Uh, I can you probably do right?
I can
Why would he need sand for?
I'm crafting the thing that summons the boss
I'm getting sand right now
I think I have enough
He's just in darkness. Yes, I am
All right. I have some sand blocks
If you have any leftover cactus, I need five more cactus five more cactus. I got some sand blocks for you here
I think I have some cactus stored
I do sneezing again, by the way
No, i'm not
That is not enough cactus
Right the shackle
Oh, this is gear
One defense plus three melee speed
Okay throwing knives
I'm gonna sell this
to calvin
Can you make another room and you use the room example to make a new room?
Yeah
And maybe trusting you with a lot here
Uh, do we have enough wood?
We only have 11 wood
Okay, uh, I have wood
Yeah, I can do it. I dropped the wood on the bed
Uh, I need a wooden platform is what?
I got it. Uh, here's one platform
No, okay
Three wide with a torch
And then it gets down to the bottom and you need a chair
Three wide with three wide
Well, no, just do it in here like uh
actually
But like yeah, just start up here. It makes it come down three wide one
One two three
How come I don't have where's my my indicator?
Oh shit, I left the door open
one two three
That's not it
Okay, that's it
Okay, what do you want me to do with this and then put a chair in here
A torch first
I don't have any torches
I need to make some
I got all
Uh, give me my wood didn't I?
Yeah, you didn't hear you want some
Yeah, what did I just do?
Oh, no, no, no, don't auto throw away wood
here
Uh, give me a sec
Somebody's get 50 bucks tim
timmy
The trick is to make cactus chairs so they're definitely in prison
Thank you for that minecraft stream
Pog
Once it's daytime we can fight this boss tell star he's handsome. I will that's a lot of money
Thank you so much tim and then the ball is really going to start rolling
Uh, somebody said that you are handsome that tim says you're handsome. They they paid me 50 dollars to tell you that
I'm streaming
Yeah, you you are streaming
You could have paid him 50 dollars and say hey, you're handsome you paid me 50 dollars to tell him he's handsome
All right
so now
um
Why are we trapping people in these like cages here?
Um, this is to make sure that they don't leave is that what i'm understanding. Uh, it's easy to talk to them
Um, so it's efficient to just walk through here and talk to them because you need the npcs
There's like you need like collectively 30 rooms by the end of terraria. There's a lot of people
So if you would like to make them an actual house for 30 people you're more than welcome to start doing that
I'll tell you you're handsome for free. Thanks, man
But you'll get but you'll give me the money to that's funny
All right. I got a lot of burgers. So i'm gonna go to the food department
Why is there a goldfish walking around outside?
I oh
Get up
That was terrible
I saw that coming from a mile away, too. I couldn't do anything
I couldn't protect him
He didn't seem to be bothered by it though
Ooh, that was close
Yeah with the um, the way the ground is in front of the door
Normally monsters will hit doors, but they have to jump first because there's a gap they can't open these
So you can just shoot them through the wall
You freaking cheater so you have to summon bosses
Uh
Not all of them, but generally yeah, what does jeffrey do?
What does jeffrey do? I don't know. What does jeffrey do?
Which one's jeffrey their names are randomized. Oh jeffrey. Okay, this is important
Okay, he gave me 50. Oh, he's just he's just a nice guy. He says sorry
Don't be sorry
Thank you very much
When you talk to jeffrey you click crafting
And then you see on the left side of your screen says place material here
Uh, hold on
Crafting place material here
So if you put a material there, he'll tell you everything that material can potentially make
Oh, man
Now I know why you have like five million hours in this game
He's like making in-game wikipedia
Starting to make sense. All right, so
I'm not using this cop the bow. Do you want the bow?
Uh sell it
Girls
Okay
All right
I sold that sword
I sold the sword. Are you happy? Are you probably?
You mean the bow?
No, the sword. Yeah, the sword that you hate
What the fuck three dollars germa is a bald loser
Oh my god, dude
Should have given that to me. I didn't know you had haters
I didn't know I was streaming with a person who had haters
haters
My social media is clean
Well, my social media is barren. I don't even I use it like once a year
Okay, you're ready to fight a worm you are you're my cosplay bodyguard
I'm the guy in the gigantic suit that like can't really move around and needs like four people to show them where to go
And then you have to like guide me around and then stop me when people want to take selfies with me
Oh, you know what? We haven't gotten any of is life crystals. So we're both chums eat an apple
Eat an apple
Yeah
Um, why don't my grenade? Why do we both eat apples?
Because we're about to fight a boss. Oh shit. Hold on. Let me get ready. All right, so
I got apples. I got burgers
Eat them
Eat one eat a burger
Yeah, but I just ate an apple
Eat them both
what
Titan increased knockback full stomach. Why did you make me do that? Those are expensive
Because we're gonna fight a boss right now like right now you're gonna spawn it right now right now
Like right now you're ready right now. Um, all right. I'm ready. I i'm
Hit it in the face hit in the back hit in the butt
We kill it. Are you throwing bombs? Yeah
You blew up our fucking house, dude
What did he drop
You don't even get to know you blew up our house
You were throwing bombs too. I just I was throwing grenades which specifically do not blow up terrain
I just saw the explosions and I was like, oh yes, I'll do that too
I felt like I was supposed to be doing that
It's all right. It was just this side
All right, there's somebody in here
That's the traveling merchant. He's a hot guy
Okay, what about it?
angel halo
paint sprayer
He sells a random. It is a dps meter
Oh shitty. I need money. I need money
I have four silver
Where did my money go?
I thought I had like 80 silver
Uh, have you died?
Monster twice. Oh the burgers burgers the burgers the burgers gold piece
No, the burgers are like I bought like fucking six burgers seven burgers
tiki torch
All right. Can you make um
Can we make my candy can room, please?
Uh, can we find another boss real fast? Uh, I didn't I did not know that we are going did we do that right?
Yeah, sure. Okay. That's how this works. Let's do it again another boss
What was that?
That's the trophy from the last one
It doesn't do anything
Uh, do you have some platforms fifty dollars fifty dollars just came in right now from chunky baloney
Thanks for the 5000 bits. They say hayster. There's a great stream. Keep it up, buddy
Hey
No problem
All right, you gotta be ready for this one. Okay. No joke. Do I eat the hamburger again?
It should still be going. It's not
This one might kick our ass actually. All right, so give me some tips
tips, uh, if you run too far away, it will teleport on top of you so like
You can actually use your recall potions to teleport back into the base
And we don't have the medic yet, but dude, just we'll be fine
You know, i'm gonna summon them over here. I think should I not throw you're not gonna throw any bombs. Don't throw bombs
Don't throw bombs only use my auto attack
Where is he?
Ow, yeah, we're still slowing like don't have any movement
You can't get me
He can teleport i'm dead
You can do it. He's almost dead. I was a distraction
four percent
Zero point five percent zero percent. Come on fill the dots
I got him nice. Why don't I spawn all the way back here?
Oh, that's it's some I don't know if it's a random bug that it spawns you there sometimes or you
Accidentally right click your bed and it unsets your spawn point
Is it very annoying?
You might have
So I I think we need to put our beds
Somewhere else. Oh, so we don't accidentally right click them people saying I blew up the bed
You
I don't think you did. Did I not?
Yeah, no, the bed's still there. I think he just accidentally right clicked it
The wall was damaged so that room no longer counts for a bed to work. Oh, that's actually true
Uh guys do you make the um, I have cthulhu summon at a demon altar or can you do it in an anvil?
Uh guys, do you know how to play the game because I don't
Why don't I have a door in my inventory?
Yeah, i'm gonna make jerma jealous
He wants to ride the slime
How do I put the door down?
Uh, there's no wall
There you go, okay, so now we can right click this spawn point set
Oh, you trapped him. Okay
all right, so
You're doing a lot of playing and not a whole lot of describing
Describing so we just killed two bosses. We just killed that guy. He got me this
He got you that
Yeah, what is he getting?
What did he get you? I want to he got me my hidden blade technique throwing knife technique
Cool, you're getting a lot of fun stuff. Um, when do I get the super mario shoe?
Um, their percentage chance drops and he didn't really drop any mage shit, so you didn't really get anything
Sorry, dude. All right. Bye. So let's go
i'm ready
um
We could probably
Kill the eater of worlds
the eater of worlds
Yeah, and then we'll start getting
We'll start getting
Games with stir. He takes all the drops and leaves you 10 miles behind. There's actually there are clearly no drops for him
I didn't yeah, I didn't say anything. I know it's true. It's fine
Uh, i'm okay with that. I need to go see down here if dynamite
Destroys fossil. I don't think it does
I'm gonna go i'm gonna go over here. I'm gonna go over here
I'm gonna just go this way. Wait, are we leaving our friends vulnerable doors open? It does not um
They're a little vulnerable. All right, I closed the doors. I'm you know, i'm gonna go down. I'm gonna go down like a little cave
There's another boss we can fight right now
Uh, I think I think I can do it right now. Oh my god, can you fucking refill this sand? Can you show some responsibility?
What's sand?
The hole you made refill it with sand is it's keeping it keeps up the enemies but it's keeping me out too
How do I open this door?
Oh, you can't open it inward now because I placed the furnace there. Oh
We're running out of space. All right, i'll fix it. I'll fix the sand just hold on. Yeah, and I can summon a boss
Let me fix the sand first
We have to do it before tonight time. Let's do it now
And then you fix the sand
The grand thunderbird has awoken
He'll like charge at you. Do you need to jump over him?
No
Oh, i'm out of musket. Oh, he's like glitching out. What the fuck
It should be easier than the other ones we fought
Theoretically, I can't really reach him
I can't reach him
I'm not big enough. Okay. Here you go. Jerma. What do you got now?
Oh
Let me look at a bird a bird friend
11 summon summon damage very weak knockback uses 10 minutes summons a hatchling to zap your foes
So I should use more than one item ticket, right?
Yeah, you can always that summon will always be out as long as you cast it. Oh, okay. Cool
Wow, he's going down again. It follows things and shoots things. Okay. Now take these
This is a learning moment because i'm not gonna leave you 10 miles behind. These are sandstone ingots. Yep, take those to the guide
Okay, and do the crafting thing so you can see what you can make from sandstone
Okay
But first let me do my responsibility
Which is fix this shit up
He's gonna craft a sandstone bath
I mean if you're dirty
Can you do that?
And maybe
I don't think so
The sand also always falls when you place it so you can place it from up here and it'll drop down
Fixed it
Stop, stop, stop, stop, stop, stop. What what what we need the tube below the door so monsters don't get in
Oh
Okay
All right
for the sandstone
Into this guy's uh slot here
Showing recipes that use sandstone ingot
so i'm wand and
uh
Wand guy, right?
Oh sandstone pickaxe
We need one of those really bad actually sandstone pickaxe
What about um sandstone greaves?
Uh pickaxe 100 we need it
Okay
I'm sorry. I've made this seem like you're gonna have choices
Uh, did I make it?
You have to actually go to the anvil and make it. He's just showing you what you can make
It's not in your inventory while you're showing it to him
What did I just do I just heard like that
What the hell was that? Oh, no. No, he just gave it back to me. Okay, I get it
Yeah, all right anvil
Uh sandstone pickaxe should we both have one do you want one too?
um
Only one of us needs to have one. Okay, so then should I make
like a
Sandstone big yeah, we if there's also something you want to make I can summon the boss again and we can get more sandstone ingot
We can
Yeah, actually
I'm remembering the sandstone armor set is really really good, but we're gonna kill him like twice
Okay, so I got sandstone helmet sandstone greaves
Yeah
Two percent movement speed five percent throwing damage
All right, i'm gonna make the helmet
Are there multiple helmets?
This nothing I don't think so
I've made sandstone helmet thrower class fuck
Did I do something wrong?
No, you're fine
There's not like a mage class
Sometimes armor sets have multiple helmets so you can make it your class, but I think that set only has one. Okay
Well, I have it on now
Oh, that looks cool. You can only summon him during the day though. So we've got some time you have the pickaxe
I do
Let's go in this hole
So the pickaxe this pickaxe is like really weak and slow and stuff
Or is it is there any is there any reason at all for me to ever use?
The copper pickaxe ever again. No, once you get a new pickaxe, the old one is done forever. Okay
I'm gonna sell it
The like old shit like copper pickaxe is really not even worth selling either. Oh
Okay, so we this is how you can get that. Uh
This is how they get the shit that we couldn't get before the fossil stuff, right?
I'm pretty sure we can get fossil with that pickaxe. Yeah, and we need that pretty bad willy the traveling merchant has
Disappeared okay right down here. This like dirt ground is possible
Okay
Does that work?
Dang, then we still can't get it. I'm pretty sure we're gonna need to get demonite pickaxe
So what can we do with this? Is it just faster?
Just faster. Yeah
It'll if you look at your pickaxe it says pickaxe power
Something percent 55 percent power. Yeah, my power on my wood pickaxe is 30
Oh, so it's like that much faster demons
He did it he did the star
Mine mine mine. You're a newbie
You I gave you the other one. I I gave you mine anyways
noob
Wow, I'm almost dead. The campfires give more health for jen
Oh, isn't the meteorite fault? Yeah, we could go get the meteorite, but we don't know where it is. I don't think
and
If you think row right would actually become somewhat irrelevant soon here. It's good for mage so we could go do that
Don't don't drop those stars in daylight. They break
Yeah, i'm yeah
Yeah, I don't know if you knew that. All right, so I got
All right, we need to go in the jungle to get them. We need more minerals people saying
more minerals minerals
Come on minerals. So who are we going to lock in here?
Uh, who shows up is kind of random
It's if you meant the prerequisite for the npc to show up they show up
And I want the um, there's a guy who sells bullets that I really need
Because I would like some bullets. Can you make you your those two guys stop jumping around. It's distracting me
I can't squirrel
Can I pick it up? Wait, in fact, i'm gonna call you a golden fox just came in the house
Hey, it was a squirrel germ. I'm gonna trade you. I'll trade you my helmet for your helmet
We could have no if you have my helmet you can have two birds
You should have two guys
I think about it. Okay here am I getting scammed? Oh, oh, I'm sorry your helmet
Yes, you were getting I was I was getting scammed you made a fucking cactus bath towel that's what that was
What what did you you got a rivet? Oh wow
Can you throw me you gave me the cactus bathtub no you didn't
No, and I deleted that
All right. So now what?
Are we gonna fight that boss? Um, I think we have to because we have to wait till morning anyway
We can go and fight. I actually know it's starting morning
Everyone's yelling star roof
Star roof everyone's like saying star roof
I get on it. Let me make sure I can summon this
Yep, it tells you how fast you're running 18 miles per hour. That's really fast
Oh, did you buy the stopwatch?
No, I just have it on
I just have I think it's a helmet
Why do I have this?
I mean, I bought a stopwatch. I
Maybe it like works for you too because you're near me. I don't know maybe
Awesome bullet guy on table
Oh bullet guy is on table
Wait, what?
When did that person get in here I love my laser hawks
illegal gun parts mini shark
So if i'm gonna be like mr. Magician, I don't want a range damage is not the same thing as magic wand
specifically magic damage, okay
you'll get
um
Spell books and wands in general
All right, so we're just waiting for daytime you said
Yeah, no, let's go this way
We have time
I also bought
I didn't get rid of them, right? Inventory is such a pain in the ass in this game
I just bought like 200 grenades and I can't find them
star
I'll take that one. You've taken all of them so far. I deserve one. You have more man than me
Don't eat
Yeah, but i'm the magic guy go I use man. I shoot man up
Didn't you say we needed stone?
No, not anymore. Let's go
We actually really
Look like an element. Okay, wrath element. Oh, we're up there
Oh, come on. You've got them all. Oh
come
Let's just shut the fuck up
Looks like darnell's throwing a party
Darnell can we miss the party?
the drug dealer
does wait
Did mom and dad go on vacation and the kids are throwing a party in the house?
Yeah
All right. I got an idea. Let's call let's call his cell phone
What do you mean? It's daytime. Let's call the recall potions. I do
um
Alt select them so they don't move and like put them at the bottom right of your inventory
So the next time you're dying
And you need to like get away quick, you know where they are
Uh, did you just do that? Yeah use a recall potion. We're gonna fight the boss because it's daytime
I was gonna say call his cell phone
And tell them we're coming home early and then they have to have a whole entire movie
The grand thunderbird is awoken. Well shit. Hold on
This is quite the fucking party look at this
This balloons everywhere
This can't be good for the environment
This is really messed up actually
Letting out that many helium balloons into the atmosphere
These birds are awesome
A bird mask germa did zero damage. Uh, actually I did I got an absolute shitload because my two birds
I can't reach with the staff. The birds did a ton of damage
What are you guys talking about?
another
bird another bird
I want us to both have the armor set
Oh, why you'll you'll fucking see you
Okay, it's just that reach my look at my birds doing all that work
Is he dead?
Yeah, everything I get star has to have two
How many ingots do you have? I am the little brother I have
uh
three
Hand him over
I was gonna wait till you said please but it is your game. I'm making them for you. It is your server
Yeah, we need to kill him like maybe one more time. This guy's having a
Are they having like a tea party on a grave?
He's so loud. He's pretty loud. He's a screecher
What he's too far I keep he goes too far away from me
You have the thing that goes across the whole screen. I don't
Dermar you're contributing a deadly didgeridoo
What's up? Why do you have?
What is over your head?
uh
Bard inspiration they can only cast like that many times for using music
oh
And then it buffs people near you and stuff which also
Isn't magic damage
So where are all these people there are like hundreds of thousands of people at this party
The painter showed up
He can he can just go die
I came for the party
So what do you say?
Go my inventory and what?
I gave you the armor
You that's all you have now, right? Because you gave me the helmet. I don't see
It's on the roof. Oh armor on roof
Is the painter gonna be okay?
Yeah, let him die
Seriously, let him die. Why is he bad?
He doesn't do anything
All right, so we rely on unless you want two birds, but this makes you double jump
I kind of I want two birds. I think but hold on
I can do the the helmet. No, I can do the
the greaves
And you need the whole step for a double jump
The two birds are really good
No, i'm gonna hold on. I want the two birds
Yeah
I like the two birds
There's another armor set here that we could make you but it's these are such an you're so annoying
no
This painter
Get him bruno
Should we actually let him die?
Yeah
Are you sure?
All right, let's go. Let's go chop chop chop chop. What does he do? Okay. I'm gonna what does he do?
But he like lets you he put you can put wallpaper in a room
Uh, cool. Yeah
Why do you want to get with the right candy cane?
yellow paint
Rainbow wallpaper. Come on
Brown paint white paint gray paint pink violet purple blue sky blue
What?
Okay, my room my no no my room is bigger than this. I only remember for like a bed and shit
No, you're a prison
It they're all prison rooms
Look, it's a candy cane
Oh man, you could you could be really slim and slender just like a candy cane. Oh, whoa
what
All right, get the fuck out of my room
I'm get out of my room
Get out of my room
If you need me just right click me and i'll give you something. Oh, let's I want to leave. Let's go. Who's this?
Who's up there?
Somebody else just showed up
All right, let's go. I don't know
Oh, that's the sand guy
Yeah, try double jumping up here sand guy
Yeah, I don't know put the full set on
Yeah, but i'm gonna lose my bird
And you're better off having the double birds
That's so good though
That's uh, this is not a double jump. This is a jet pack
Yeah, here's a book take that book. That's you can shoot things at a distance with that book
It's a spell is it better than the vial for
Well, it shoots further you're complaining about not being able to shoot far enough
You can have two
Okay. Oh cool. How fast gonna do it?
This is very overwhelming, but it's very fun. All right, hold on
10 mana 5 mana
fast
16 damage 4% for it
All right. This is this is good
golden duck
Can you actually do anything with the gold animals besides think they're cool?
I mean that answer is no. I thought that was a sound board that you just put in
That boing was oh no, what?
Jump makes you go forward a little faster
Don't leave me hanging
Oh, yeah, you don't have it
You can sell them for gold
So why are you killing them?
Okay, jerma
Go through the process of like taming an animal do it
Is it a pain in the ass?
I don't know how to do it. It's I know it's 10 gold never done it
Put them in a net and sell
We only we only imprison people here
Hey, i'm not the expert. You're supposed to be the expert
So what's the current objective now?
The current objective is to go back to that
Corruption area the purple area when you destroy three of those shadow orbs it summons a boss
Oh
We want to kill that boss
Because then we can mine the fossil
And then when we can mine the fossil we can go to hell
This is cool
Not on expert mode
No, what would expert mode change?
bosses get more health deal more damage and you die a lot
and it takes like
Three times as long to play through and do anything
I uh, we would not have killed one boss yet
Hmm. That's good. I've got like a spelunking potion
What was that?
It's way more good
Yeah, you get there's more interesting drops than expert but I i'm
You wouldn't want to play it
I just try I probably wouldn't not on my first ever time playing the game
I think you like don't even know what anything
And you're like, where am I not expert mode?
Would I do it like would I talk like that?
No, that's what the other guy would talk like
Oh
Dark too dark. Oh
Holy shit. Thank god
This little thing just saved my life
No, it didn't um
How did you even get over there? Oh, you have a double jump, right? I can't just follow you blindly
How do you heal yourself?
Ah, I can't mine this
No, all right. I gotta put a platform down on that helmet
Especially for this boss trust, but you're gonna need it
Let's sacrifice the one bird for now
Really? I just hit my fucking head on this
You have to hold space you spend longer
All right. I think i'm good
A horrible chill goes down your spine
Okay, take this
as well
Musket
And i'm taking this for what specific reason because it does 32 damage
Oh, that's a lot
Um use that as your long range
Your vile thorn will be a lot better on this boss though
Okay
all right
vile thorn on the boss
Oh, don't don't walk in those bombs
I need more light down here, man. I'm gonna have to put some hold on
If we're gonna fight a boss like right now, I need to be able to see come back come back
What you need to start doing is go to the left
And make a rope up to the surface make a rope up to the surface
Yeah
Remember you can't mine through this so like go back to where we came down and make it as easy as
Possible to get up to the surface
What?
How did I fall
There's too much pressure
Was it here?
Was it right here?
Uh, actually you can wait on the surface for me
Ow, i'm gonna die
No, don't i'm not i'm not i'm fine fine
I need you fucking dark down here
Uh, tell me when you're on the surface, uh, not on the surface
Here's I am ready to pull the trigger on the fuck fiesta. Uh, do not do that yet
Dude, am I out of torches?
And we still like really only have 100 health each
um
His rope sucks just warning you
Okay
I need light
I don't know where the fuck i'm going man
I don't know what i'm doing
Oh my god, I
I don't know what i'm doing make it as easy as possible to get to the top
hell
I got stuck down here. All right
You know what you just wait on the top and I have a potion to tell it to you
Why do I have to wait down here?
Because a giant worm is going to come out on the ground
And if you're inside these tunnels when it appears
You just get warmed
All right, so i'm worried that i'm on the surface
Okay, uh, can you build like a platform above the ground with uh
Wood platforms. Do you have any? Yeah platform above the ground
You want me just to like go like you had like the other one you had?
Yeah, yeah
I don't have any fucking torches though
I can't see shit
Uh, i'm gonna be i'm gonna be very very like just franking up front about this
I don't know if i'm okay. I can't do this
Um
It's okay to admit it
I i'm not gonna be like yeah, sure man like here we go. Um, like i'm i'm kind of i'm kind of stuck
I'm kind of like overwhelmed. I'm gonna summon the boss
Okay, I need wood. Hold on and then i'm gonna teleport to you
And then we're just gonna make the best of it with our double jump
Okay, hold on. I'm gonna turn his brightness up now. I'm enjoying this
Where do I go?
Doing good
I can handle this
Hey, uh, I can handle it. Don't worry. Yes. So I believe you
Uh, I a little overwhelming I need
You see if it would be playing I would probably still be cutting down trees and building a house
We're fighting like monsters and getting new gear and I I would have just built a candy cane house
All right. Hold on. You don't have enough candy cane
What the fuck already here?
I'm just i'm just gonna wait for you and do some other stuff
I was gonna keep him
Get me please. All right, just
I'm losing my fucking mind
I'm losing my fucking mind. Okay torch. I need just give me a bunch
How many of these do I have? What is he overwhelmed by? I don't get it. Oh, he made tiki torches. Oh
fuck
What am I overwhelmed by? It's just I with um, I don't know. It's like a lot to take in in an hour
Get out of here. All right
I need to like relax because i'm like actually like panic getting overwhelmed by all this shit in the inventory
And all the things in the game. All right
Okay, get my book up here. No, I don't need that. Okay, I have potions
All right. Let me just deposit this bullshit
I don't know what the fuck I even want with all this. No hold it here. It's fine
Fine get rid of everything else. I I guess
All right, so I have
Stupid fucking tiki torches, man
I'm gonna build the thing that you wanted to build
Right, you're gonna you're gonna do it
Are you sure?
Probably not
I'm worried about is there wood even in do we have any wood?
I I cut down trees trees on your way back, but I died. There's plenty I died. I fell down a hole
I think you missed that part
Yeah, but you still have all your things
Buy torches from the merchant. You see here's the thing. Uh, he has locked
Like seven people in here. I don't know what any of these people do besides this guy. He sells dynamite
I'm worried about you. No, I'm good rescue
Rescue them. I just start breaking them out
Okay
I'm just gonna need to come back. I have so much junk in my inventory. So all right. All right. Okay, it's just I
It's just too dark
What is your gamma at? Tell me what it is
Uh, where is gamma? I don't know. I don't know. It's in nvidia settings
What is parallax?
Real
All right. Um
Did you you're coming back, right? I'm in here with you
So you wanted to deposit stuff? I'm doing a drop. Do you need torches? I can make you torches
No, I have torches
I figured it out. I have potions. I have torches. I have food
Video settings change lighting to white
Why is it like a sandstorm?
I don't know
I'll get like 50
50 is 50 torches good
You should get more more than 50. Okay
Because you'll always be using torches. There's no reason to not have more
If you can make 100
Like 300
I mean how much you panic when you don't have a torch. Do you ever want that to happen again? No, never. Okay
So I got gun. I've got food. I've got health
I got my bird
All right
Hey, are we good to start this?
Why would you build a house in the desert? I don't know. This is not my i'm just along for the ride guys
Do another shift? Yeah, no shift takes out the best tool, right? Yeah
I think also
Oh, is that a different spot?
Hmm
Never mind ignore me
That's such a cool item
Oh my god
I don't think hold on imagine you died from up there. That would've been so funny
I don't laugh normally these don't let you jump a second time
You know, we also need is an anti-gravity potion
What is that?
It turns gravity upside down so you fly up in the air and there's planets in the sky
Do a zombie impression?
Like I feel like that's a star thing. That's a star request
Here take mana crystal. Yeah, I just take that right now, right?
Yeah
Uh, so you brought wood, right?
Uh, hold on. Let me
You brought wood, right? I have wood platforms. Yes
Okay
Uh 39 of them
Is that not enough?
That's not enough. I didn't tell me a number. I didn't I didn't know if more if yeah, I needed more than like 40
39 is not enough like 200. I did 200
Okay. Well, let's get them now
All right. I don't I don't even have an axe anymore
I'll get it. I'll get it
I'm just along for the ride. I'm just along for the ride
Yeah, I got I i'm i'm about to see i'm a seafood guy. You know, I see food I eat it, you know
Thanks to the 50 bucks
Indeed
Okay, i've got
You see how long this took? I have
Okay, so I have a lot too already, uh, but honestly tim tim gave 50 more dollars
This is addressed to you. So you might want to listen to this
Oh, this is to me. Yes, uh tim
96 give 50 more dollars and they said don't tell star this. Oh, okay
I won't read the rest then
I brought some people
By the way, uh spoiler alert. He said I am much more handsome than you
That's fine
I told him
How?
Okay, I feel like this is cheating you're making your own final destination
You wait there
You can do that, right? I can do that
Finally, I can see the sun
I could see the sun. All right. What are
What are this guy's mechanics? What does he do?
Does he you know the first worm we fought that died really quickly?
Yeah, uh, I guess it's it's one of those worms are like that are common enemies
But uh, he splits into segments and he you have to like kill every single part of the worm
Because they just keep worm that flies around so if you're above the ground it makes it a lot easier to dodge
Because he's gonna come up at you
Okay, are you ready
I am I guess as ready as i'm gonna be
I'm not sure what that means, but I guess so
eater of worlds segments left
That seems like a lot. Yeah
Oh these stick to the fucking thing
That's him down there
I didn't though. I'm fine
Nice. All right. Careful. He's coming in. He's wrapping around you
Careful
All right, you see now he's like 30 worms now. Yeah, he's a lot of worms gonna eat the world next
Oh that hurt
Inside of my nose is it's it's just it's ever been in my whole life
That's somebody put like sneezing powder in my nose they just came in here and just like blew it up in my nose
Is that it?
I think that's the last one more
There's two segments left scratch it. I can't you did it you did it
All right, you okay, you're like sniffing in your microphone and I really appreciate it
So what do we get?
Oh, hold on. This thing is actually really good
They were just lined up on the bridge and I could just run this way and go like that
Yeah, that way. Oh, yeah star the master looter
Every single one of those little splits drops, uh demonite ore and shadow scales make sure you picked them all up
That's around here. Yeah, i've been running around looking around
on the top here
He dropped a healing staff
Healing staff
Am I doing lines of coke to be able to play terraria?
What are you thinking?
What are you thinking with that nonsense?
Get that out of my chapel
Don't do it for a lot less
Yeah, hey dig into hell still the title of this ring. When are we going?
Uh, we should be able to go now
So that ore you're talking about
I have a lot of it
Yeah, uh recall potion go back
Come on. Okay
So then i'm gonna give it to the jeffrey and he's gonna tell me what it does
Okay, i've made the pickaxe so you don't need to make one
Okay
Yeah, okay, so I can make demonite brick
demonite bar
Why would you make demonite brick?
Just because you think it looks cool. Oh, okay. So demonite bar. I think he has a summon. That's pretty good
That should be a little bit better than
So do I have to make a bar and then put the bar in here?
Yeah, make a bar at the furnace
and then
Here i'll drop you the shadow scales. Here's the rest of the bars. I just needed the um
pickaxe
And you can do whatever you want with those. Oh, okay
There's a lot of stuff here
Fisher of the souls 20 more fishing power
There's a whole fishing thing. I've never done it
You would probably what the fuck is going on
Uh, all right, I did put the scales in trash
What does that mean did I accidentally trash the bars you threw the bars in the trash
Where's the uh, don't I have demon ore still? Yeah. Oh
Okay, if you need any more shadow skills, I have 20
Is there a way to quickly just go to uh, here we go
When you're crafting there is a button you can press that makes it show all on screen. Yeah, it's a lot easier
All right
So now i'm gonna look at this again
I just I try to shoot him
jester shirt jester's mask
minion damage, ooh
This increases minion damage by 15 by 20 percent increases your max number of minions
Oh, man
So wait, I can do
One two two extra minions with this set on
Uh, yes. Yeah, this i'm gonna do this
How many what does this cost?
seven defense
I need
14 bars five spirit droplets and 40 bones
How many materials do we cannot get those yet? And if you're seeing like some really weird items
There's items that are animated. We cannot get those good
No
The I think generally speaking the further you scroll down the list the less likely we are to craft them. Oh
oh
Really?
All right, you're just gonna have to keep playing bar. No do the magic storage. We need uh emeralds before we can make a heart
It's bane demon bow, is there another uh, is it like a demon wand?
If it's not on that list there isn't one
I think vile thorns better than what dark wave here we go dark wave
Sends out a wave of dark energy. What does it take? Oh, I can make this 18 versus
What's the book 16?
The book is better
Fast speed versus fast speed six mana versus five
That's not very good walking gold fishing desert star
Yep
16 versus 18
I'm gonna i'll try it. I'm gonna try it. I'm gonna make the uh the dark wave
I forgot to craft the uh
I need your money
My money, what do you mean my money? Hey your gold the gold money you have I have 82 silver. I don't have very much
You don't have any gold pieces. No
Do you have any dynamite?
Uh, I have 27 bombs
I mean i'm gonna try this this new wand out though
Oh, that's pretty good it's fast
We need money
And I am not joking around germa i'm gonna sell some stuff
Uh, what about the shadow scale? What can I do with these?
They
Are also used with the demonite ore i'm pretty sure
Just for random recipes
Yeah, I'm a little unsure. I think they just kind of also use those same stuff
I just feel like I shouldn't even delete any of these things or sell any of them. I just don't know
I'm just depositing all my shit and I don't even know what to do with it
Buying net for the gold critters. I'll do that
a bug net
Can you catch them in a bug net?
Can you get the duck in a bug net? Can I can you?
I don't know. Oh, I okay. I gotta get this in. Yeah
All right. What can I do with the shadow scale stuff?
That shit didn't
Uh, can you organize this stuff? I don't know what to do
Um, eventually we're gonna make a super stash that will auto organize it. Oh, okay
We just really need emerald before we can do that
Ruin of bleeding the only critical damage restores life
Can't make any of these though. I don't think
ooh
Sorcerer's pants sorcerer's robe. I just do much more magic damage
Um, if you want better magic damage, we need to find the meteor
Should I just get some of the how much should I just do these now just to have it?
No, those are really
You're better off with a double jump for now
Really?
I think so. Yeah, I mean if you want to make them and you want to look like a wizard
I'm not gonna stop you. I'm actually I need disciples hat
I don't have enough
All right. Well, let's just let's just keep going. Let's just keep doing whatever
Make sure I have stuff. I have food
Okay, I got the bug net
I need some more potions
Those are very important. How much money do I have?
I can buy a ton of these
Get the 20
20 and 20
Yeah, I think so
The disciples hat is easy to make
There's an upgraded version of it with one of these mods
And we would we would need like a loom it's like a three-step process to get to a loom to make silk to start
If it is what I think you're talking about
hold on
disciples hat
Is how can I see what that takes?
I don't know
All right. I'm coming down. I'm gonna store this stuff
Wait, i'm coming back up in like one second. You're coming back up here
Yeah
I found a bunch of stuff to just sell really quick
I'm gonna look for a gold animal
And is it is it as easy as just like catching it like that?
Kill the pig for money
Really? Does it put a dot?
Uh, we don't need money anymore. I got it. This is a dot. I like this a lot
I got it
wait
I just like throw him
Just hang on here. It's safe in here. Stop
He's not gold so it doesn't matter
kill pig
Star should we kill the pig?
Yes, he drops bacon and a lot of money
You're not doing it
Why are you not killing this? I'm out of mana
I gave you a musket
I don't waste this thing's really powerful. You know, i'm gonna waste it on a little pig
the
Yeah, I could buy you a thousand musket balls
That was nine gold yeah
What?
Is it buy as many musket balls as you want?
Uh, come over here. Uh, hold on. That's a lot of money
Sandstorm is one gold
Invest invest but it's a big moment step aside step aside
What am I doing?
Now we can go to hell
What?
It that it's that easy to do that
Yeah
How much does that cost?
15 dynamite desert fossil
rope
And just go straight all the way down
Yeah
So we're just skipping the whole game
No, not but no not at all
Uh, let me block. I don't know why I like this one spot
What's the point of this?
What do you mean? We're actually the people are saying we're actually skipping the whole game
We're not skipping the whole game
Uh, how do we are you sure you didn't just make a well?
Yeah
You can drown in there
We're under water right now, dude. Should we not be doing this?
No, we're we're okay
We need to get it to the bottom and then cut a hole in the wall
So the water goes out the wall so we can get it on the lava so that we can get obsidian
I feel not accomplished at all
You've dug to hell. What do you want? Can I not go anymore?
No, there's a bomb
I just got a hell forage
Uh, so we're just
Help me jerma. This is still the beginning of the game
Don't worry
um
Okay, what happened to the rope?
All right. Oh, so we're just gonna go down here and just mine and dig and grab things and attack. Uh,
Yeah, so there's a whole bunch of really annoying things that spawn and if you you see those demons on the left
Do them the demons on the left?
Come over
crash
Okay, actually there's one over here, which is the perfect example of the thing we can't do
Okay
What is that exactly?
Do you see the demon carrying a guy?
Underneath his feet. Yes, I do
Okay, if he drops that in lava or you throw that guy in lava if someone's a gigantic super
Wall thing monster flesh thing. We're not ready
Don't don't let don't kill one of those
over the ground
over lava, I mean
Okay
I I guess i'll try not to do that
Okay. Thank you
Did you make a demon bed?
Oh, I know these are all these just were in the demons houses they sleep in beds. Yeah
Yeah, they're upset that we're here
I don't think I would assume a demon did not sleep in a bed
I always picture them hanging upside down with their eyes open and they sleep like that
Nope, they get under the covers very comfortable obsidian beds
You cheated not only gave it yourself. You didn't grow you didn't improve you took the shortcut and you didn't gain anything
You experienced a hollow victory. Nothing was risked
And nothing was gained. Yeah, okay
stir
Please tell germa to get mod
When you're done
I don't know. I'm just relaying the message and it doesn't matter if it made any sense or not
Oh because the other they're referring to the coffee pasta that was spammed like probably four or five thousand times
I see
Do you have any normal blocks like placeable blocks?
Not the blood forms
No, I have demon bikini
hell forge
Obsidian, I don't have like any regular blocks. No
Sorry
What's that wormhole potion?
Uh that teleports you to me
Oh, that's cool
ye
What is this like demon clock demon clock clock?
I got it
He's got it. I got it. I got the clock
Is that an emerald boober?
There's a chest down there
Yeah, you can't open those what?
Oh, that's unfortunate
Uh, i'm pretty sure that's enough. We might need one emerald
So what's the next boss we can sell?
We never killed the eye, but that's like the first boss you're supposed to kill. I don't even think it's there anymore
um
We can fight crab you on
Sounds fun to me. Let's fight crab. I don't think we have
A way to breathe underwater
One of the demons dropped a sword
And that's a piece of bacon. We could be doing the wall of flesh
On this job. Do you do you like do you like do you want this?
Blade crest oath sword
You're gonna die
What?
These guys shoot your walls. Oh, you're getting shot. Uh, what do you have for a sword?
What the fuck is he gonna hit? Oh, just drop it
here
This is not the place to read things
uh
Come get the oversized sword here
It's on the ground. Have I put it down? Yeah. Yeah. Yeah
I yeah. Yeah. You're right
Yeah. All right. Should we get out of here?
um
Here's what we should here here. Let's go back
We can you see these like uh, these cheetos on the wall cheetos on the wall?
Yes
That's magma. Oh
He just snuck one in
And then also we need to find life crystals because our max health could be like two or better under right now
Yeah
Magma ore how much do you think we need?
Um, forget what magma armor does
I don't think either of us are actually really going to use this but not much. There's a chest over there
Um
Where the fuck did you come from? He lives here
Let's take over that chest
Some more magma ore down here. Don't want to pass this up. What the hell is that diamond? It was a ghost
What did it drop that was that?
Uh ring stones pretty good accessory you can make with them. I forget exactly what it means. I know it needs 10 ring stones
What's in the chest? Uh, this is for you take one of these
Help me. How about how do I what do I do? What do I do? I'm on fire. What do I do?
You're dead
You know what you do is you respawn you heal really quick
and then you use your
Wormhole potion you press m and just click on me on the map and you'll teleport to me
I didn't know lava was that dangerous
It's yeah, it's really it does like 60 damage when you first touch it
All right, so I can teleport to you
and then
Yeah, drop off any items if you were full. I mean that demonic bone ash
All right, well, I don't know any we need to make like a super stash and I got a big yeah
I can make it now. I just found emeralds
I know that i've been putting in a lot of like actually don't waste a little potion
You're just gonna come back up you got the sword right and end word
Right alongside the fucking giant hole. Anyway
quick stack
Restock sword items
Yeah, I got a lot of just random junk in there. I don't I don't really know what happened necessarily does
Uh, i'm gonna start setting up the thing
I'm gonna put it in your candy cane room. Oh, thanks
Uh jerem what stir is making you do is like skipping to the end levels in legend to zelda with only two hearts
It is not
That was that was a real quick response to that. It is not
What i'm doing is like you know in diablo 2 when your friend gives you the waypoint to the catacombs
All right, this will make act one a little bit easier you literally have base health
That's what somebody said
literally
Okay
So, um, let me take a look what I got here. Um demonic bone ash
Are you making the super stash?
Yeah, i'm working on it
Store your gold so you don't lose it next time. Oh shit. We might be missing
I didn't I was I didn't know you could deposit gold like I forgot it. I didn't realize it took up slot
I guess it does, huh?
Have you gotten one of those shadow diamonds by chance, I don't think we would have another yet
shadow diamond
I have demonic bone ash magma ore
No
It would be in one of these chests. I just dumped everything in here. I'm sitting in table. We need to kill the eye
I think
the eye
Unless you miraculously found diamond
No, I don't think so. It would be stuffed in one of those boxes along with
15 weeds take this two mushrooms
wild band of regeneration
slowly regenerates life
Oh plus one percent melee speed
That's cool
Filling that cheater hole next to you
So are we are we on are we out?
Uh, I I just have to like go touch that thing really quick go touch a thing. All right, I will take
I'm gonna take this opportunity to open this door
To fill up a cheater hole
I'm gonna go cover in the our cheater. I'm gonna get to put a cheater manhole on our cheater sewer
I didn't have any wood. I thought that was a diamond for a second and I was gonna say hey I found a diamond
I had a kiss you
Waterleaf waterleaf
Simon's got coppa
Do you best?
Thick boston accent. I can't I don't even want to embarrass myself. I love this room, by the way where you panic and 30 torches
Which one
Like every time I walk by it
I'm gonna remember well, I was not I was not trying to put a torch down. I was trying to hit the thing
I know the monster that was in there
But it was very scaly
It sure was. All right
With my
Oh my I should totally make like a bacon bridge
Dude I think i'm gonna i'm gonna make a like my walls are gonna be made of bacon
Hey cap this shit
I missed it. I should really probably give you one of the life crystals
You really just stopped hoarding all the items
I just gave you a band of regeneration
Yeah, you've probably been holding on to that
ow
Is this your grave?
Probably extremities were detached by a zombie
We're the best monkey streamers
What are you doing?
Keyboard mashing is it night time? Tell me when it's night time
Just look outside why'd I have to tell you that i'm underground right?
Just look outside
That was that was a
Is this your grave
Oh, what are you doing?
What are you doing? Nothing. I'm sealing your fate is what i'm doing. What does that mean people that are watching my stream?
No, and they they know what i'm doing
No, guys, i'm not trying to like mouse trap him by having that hit him in the head
I was sending his gravestone to hell
That's kind of fucked up
I'm bored. Okay. What am I doing up there?
Is it daytime?
Uh, is it night time? Oh fuck. It's been daytime for a very long time. No, no night time. It's it's it's dusk right now
Is it night time? It's it's dusk. It's the sun's going down
Okay, why are the pics of so much health?
Uh, because they give so much gold and bacon
It's just kind of a joke, you know, you ever laugh before. Oh, right bacon like money epic bacon
11 gold
That's so much. What is a huge amount of money?
What'd you say? What's like a what's a decent amount of money in the game?
uh for this early like
30 gold is pretty solid. I mean eventually you get platinum
Oh gold turns into platinum
That's pretty awesome. But the the most expensive things will be the traveling merchant has some things that sell for like 50 gold and usually they're
in their goofs
That's cool. And then beyond that you buy
dynamite
Is like one of the more expensive things I stored my money. I got like I got like 16 gold in that
case
So in the meantime, is this something I should be doing while i'm waiting for you to collect the thing to
uh go do uh
You can build a rope that goes to the sky are you just trying to like keep me occupied?
No, no, there's like uh
There's that's in the sky that's like a keep the like keep like the dumb guy occupied joke, right
No
I'm like digging underground just finding random chests
Uh, all right, and in the sky there are planets and there are floating clouds with buildings on them. Um, all right
That sounds pretty fun. I'm gonna go do that
Where's like rope? How do you how do you craft rope?
Do you have cobweb? You know, you haven't like really been underground much
Can you buy rope? I'm not sure
They're so hard to find without flight
There's a lot more in calamity mods. So the odds of you going up and they're being a planet are actually pretty high
These are expensive, man
What it's 10 copper for one?
That's rope nothing
There's nothing
Yeah
Are you sure?
That's not expensive
Don't I need like 500 of these? That's one bullet. I don't I need I need like 500 of these
Okay
Here I have a gift for you. Do you like gifts?
I have a thousand rope
Take this
I wanted to give you a mirror a mirror
What does it do?
It does the same thing a recall potion does but it's infinite. Oh, that's cool
He was never gonna tell me it was nighttime
I told you what I said. Hey, it's I said it's dusk. It's dusk. It's dusk
Like that means like it's dusk. It's gonna be nighttime in a minute. This guy's a piece of shit the eye
This thing's kind of a chump
It's it's been first boss and like normal terraria
Oh
Is there a way to um regenerate mana?
better
Than uh, there are some items later. There's a lot of stuff but not yet. Do you here?
I'll give you my the mana potions. I know I I already I have a bunch of like lesser mana potions
But is there like an effective?
there's ways like the the health regeneration band I gave you can be turned into a
Mana regen actually, I think this orb I have can make something for you
Stand still. Oh, look at that
It dropped right next to us. So did you get the thing we wanted?
Okay, faun star
Doing it we have to summon him again
Uh, no, I got the thing. I need it. Oh, so what were you looking for?
I was looking for a shadow diamond so I can start making that crafting thing
Okay, so I got I got three stars
Should I what should I use these stars or do you need them for something important? No use them
Do I just use them like just put them in my hotbar and use three?
No turn them into the mana crystal
Oh, you have to have to craft it like that, huh?
Yeah, okay in here take these two life crystals. I'm being i'm being kind i'm sharing
life crystal
So that gives me another health pool
It gives you 20 health per
Why did we not do this like an hour and a half ago because you have to find them and or
It's just like random if you find it or not. Oh, okay
So we could have been looking underground for him, but clearly we didn't need it
Because we're so strong
Why does the guy have a health bar did he get hurt?
Yeah
All right. So we're gonna do anything do anything else we need to do at night time
No
um
What's your pickaxe?
Uh, it's the sand
shameful sandstone pickaxe
Yeah, yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah
I have the same like you a demonite one
I mean, uh, I think I deposited them i'm depositing. I'm just putting what about the magma stuff
Uh, I don't think we have enough yet
That's what see magma ore makes a magma bar, right?
Magma factory block magma bar. You can't you can't ore mag. You can't mine magma
Or you definitely can't mine hellstone. So take that pickaxe
So this replaces this pickaxe now, I don't need this one anymore you don't need it
Okay
The sandstone pickaxe is a piece just just shell it sell it sell it garbage. All right
Do you have any more of that gingerbread?
No
the gingerbread cookie
You know the wall
What do you mean? What?
the the candy cane
It's in one of these chests
It's in one of them
I got it. I've been just like panicking and throwing stuff everything I get in here
This is superior ball of hurt in here. It's 33 melee damage. Is that good?
Okay, but it's
Okay, you you need to like fact check me here
You have to like check my work because i've just been throwing random stuff that I don't even know it does in there
So why are you making this bigger?
for this
so it's nice and even
and this is a
This is complicated. So you make one of those
And then you have to connect other storage components to it and then you click that and then it's basically a combined storage
Very cool
Very cool. Do you have any lead bars on you?
No
Like I said everything but I have two pieces of bacon on me
and like a clock
There's a new pig over here
new pig
Are we getting luigi'd right now?
Is it just spawning us pigs because hey you've been standing still for 15 straight minutes you might need a pig
They actually spawn a lot when you're above ground
Oh, dude, do you have any wood is there wood in there? You got any threes?
Dude, you got no fish
uh
So we should just go down and explore someone said just explore
Said you're doing a whole lot of nothing
I need to make this thing
And then we can do something
You just got all of that. I just like deposited that into your bank. All right. Thank you. Why don't we just go explore?
I'm going to i'm going up to hell
Going up to hell. Oh go
shooting star
Wait this fall damage uh shooting star to spell to the left
How high do you need to go?
Uh, you can actually go all the way up to like space and it'll be low gravity
What and there can still be planets up there?
Am I gonna get attacked by something?
Yes
Yes, okay
Harpies that's like it
ooh
What is that star?
Star star I found something star. I found uh, what's the merlin sword? Excalibur?
What's the thing that merlin is strong enough to pull out of the stone sword in the stone? Excalibur? It's right up here
Pull it out
How of your hand?
I I can't
Can I dig it out?
Do I have to dig it?
I do. Okay. I got it. I got it. I got
Archilus?
Oh, no
I'm falling did I use my?
No, I'm not. Oh, you got it
You oh
Can I see it? Like I think you might have found the broken weapon
I'm worried if you want if it is what I think it is. Is that it?
uh
Okay. No, this is not what I thought it was
It's not it's not
It makes the thing that I thought it was
But it is not that thing
So we just need to hold on to that. So it is the thing. It's it's like the thing. It's a it's a part to the thing
So what should I do with this
Uh, hold up. Hold on. I'm gonna explain in one second. I just went straight into the sky in love with me
That was just a random shot. I just went right in the air. Did it come over here?
You right click on the green thing the green cross. Yes
And you get that's our super storage that has 160 slots and you can search the name of things, okay
You just put everything in there. So take everything from these chests is just going in there
Yeah, if you don't know what something is just dumping it just dump them
Just dump it. Okay
Use the fucking sword. Holy shit, man. Who is streaming out of my okay?
Actually most items that we're not already using you can sell
It's like a lot of junk like mandible bow and ice blades
If you look at an item actually
All the weapons that can be crafted into other weapons say material on them. If it doesn't say material then just sell it
Uh, I i've just i'm just depositing everything in here
Okay, you know, that's fine, too
So arkylus should I use it?
Is it i'm not like melee person though
You shouldn't
I shouldn't
Should not don't get self-conscious because your chat tells you to do something
I remember when they told me to use doors
They remember when they said the problem with those rooms was that there weren't doors
I mean, we're talking about a literal 100 unanimous. Everyone is saying yes at the same time
You don't what?
Why am I not going to use this?
No, just don't even use it. Do you see how fast this is?
Don't use this
I think chat
Like if chat's not okay with the the dig the thing to hell. I don't think they can be okay with you using that sword
You're a mage, right?
Yeah, I mean that's so fast
I feel like I would kill things in two seconds
Oh, i'm gonna play with my new toy outside. This is great
All right. What are we doing? You want to go you want to go exploring?
Yes
Okay, you know how fast yeah, you know how fast i'll be able to kill the pig with this
I'll show you
You don't want to use this
You you can do whatever you want
I'm gonna use it sometimes
This would be my close range. But all right, uh, let's let's go explore. Let's go do something
I've been kind of i've been really just housebound here for the last like 20 minutes. We're we're going to go look for
Uh life crystals and just chest
Life crystals and chests should we fall all the way down?
Or stop like stop and then go to the other half way. It's like you catch up to me
actually
The crab guy's in this area, which is the next boss we would be doing
But we would need
A way to breathe underwater
I think we had gills potions
Did we?
Well, you know, oh I went by you. Oh stop falling
Actually come back up. Yeah, we'll start here
Left or right matter
Just going in left. This is a gold portal
Luke get
That's my thing
I see up there this thing
This is a life crystal you mine it and then you use the life crystal
Oh
So they just randomly around here. Yeah, they're just they're just out and about
Damn, um actually also with these mods
Actually, no, we need to get the max health first before we do that. Oh never mind
I'm just gonna go this way should I there's like water over here. Is that a bad idea?
Uh, it's a bad idea to spend that much time mining
I was just digging down because there's a bunch of open area over here
You I have a spelunky potion
Don't waste that yet
I mean
It depends how long do you are how long you're gonna play?
I don't know
Because they become very useful later on
How many bombs I have a lot of bombs I think
Should I just start throwing them?
No, I I when I did the the mass depositing I got rid of all of them
Ah, let's go the same way come over here
You're underwater. I know
There's a air pocket
Where is there an air pocket?
Over here
Are we gonna drown before?
Sorry, I couldn't see it my game was a trillion degrees too dark
I'm trying degrees. Yeah, i'm out of torches. I didn't flying ahead. Oh, you're almost dead. I'm gonna fucking die
No, i'm not. I'm fine
Occasionally there's some traps. I don't know who set them up
Just don't smooth cold
Yeah, forget what that actually makes
I'm just gonna keep going this way. What there's like a little spot to drop down here
I'm not gonna drown us or anything right if I drop this down here with you
No
That's definitely not enough water to drown anybody, but it could be
Fuck dude
You all right?
Yeah, I accidentally lobbied myself
Don't get bothered
Oh shit, that's right
jest
Actually, we haven't had a blood moon yet
That holds us back from all this stuff
Silver bar jester's arrow spiked cloud in a bottle
Dad, oh dad come look at this stuff. Let's go. Look at that. I don't know what it is
Cloud in a bottle is basically one of these jump like an extra jump so you can do spin and then a
a third jump
All right. Do you want it? I just took everything
I took the cloud in the bottle. I was saying you could do you'll get more use out of it
Okay
I'm gonna have a lot of stone
It's mine frank tonight
Where are you going?
Nothing up here
Uh, so skeleton drops something over there. I think
to the right
Thank you, man
I didn't mean it that way. You're welcome. We're silver. What do you got?
Bomb, okay. I got bombs
You want to start throwing them around?
Oh, I got a runestone
Should I just stop dropping bombs? Am I muted like
I you didn't say it
whoops, uh
Sure, I was gonna have a long answer. I'm just sure well the reason why you probably shouldn't do that
But if you're going down you should just throw bombs down and then they all fall down in a line
And it's much faster than a pickaxe
There's there's
If you're like going sideways
I'm just gonna drop them down. I have like three so i'm just gonna throw them down
Okay, I hope they land on me
How much damage does the bomb do if you if it lands directly on your head?
I don't know
Not dropping bombs on my head too often like 80 maybe
Oh fuck oh my god 246 for a fall maybe
I thought you were closer
I thought you were closer. I didn't I thought there was a platform down where you were. I didn't think it was just fall. Fuck
Uh drop bombs not yourself
No
Damn it
It's okay. I got all your money. Did you?
Yeah, okay good
I don't worry soon. We're gonna be playing hardcore mode on expert
All right, everything's a figure biceps are
They used to be pretty big. All right, so
um
You keep your items though, right?
Yep
tin ore bomb
Rune dirt block and we just got such a bunch of just shit
Uh, let me put the mirror back
Don't you put the mirror back? I don't think i've even had it
Oh
Stacks
default storing
Where is it?
filter all
Just search a mirror. Oh, I can just type it
So what what does this thing do again?
It's a recall potion and I can I can I recall to you
No, no, it always goes back to your bed. Okay
All right. I'm gonna use
Where the bombs i'm gonna bring some i'm just gonna throw them down near you
You actually do have a wormhole potion so you can teleport to me
Okay
Wormhole potion what do they look like you just press m on the map then click on my icon underground
Do I have to use the potion or just does it consume one? It'll auto use the potion when you click on me
If you have one, yeah, I don't think I have one
No, I don't have one and it's in the box
Uh
I don't think we have any
Wormhole. Oh, all right. We got one. We got one
All right coming back
Okay
Okay, this is for you I got another cloud in the bottle
So that so equip this shit and now I can
double jump
Again, I have to triple one two three one two three
Very cool. All right
Is there something specific besides life crystals we're looking for here?
um chests
and life crystals that's about it red husk and
Any kind of gemstone if we come across it is also helpful because we don't have hooks yet
That's my bird i'm just safe without the bird
Oh, and we found the mushroom kingdom
Which is also helpful
Because there's a boss we can summon in here
we can
I'm like too tall if I have a glowing crystal
Or glowing mushrooms then you can summon a boss in here
chats talking politics in the chat
Stop it. Let's get political. Stop it
What about hillary's emails?
Don't act
Oh, that's a nice point you have there. But what about hillary's emails?
Oh like right above us is topaz
topaz
Yeah
15 of any gemstone gives you
A hook and hooks are very good
Where do we go now? So where should we go now down here?
I'm just placing torches. I'm holding shift
Be aware of that
You're freaking me out. I don't like this doesn't go that far
um
I hate we don't have the dryad yet
too scary
Can you do it?
Probably not mario maker. Can you do it? Oh easy. He's a pro
I played mario maker a few times so you're not you're not wrong
Should we dig down this way around here?
I feel like we're getting too low
Too low there's some really good chests that appear at this level
There's like a band that makes you immune to lava for seven seconds. Should we go this way?
Uh, how many bombs do you have a lot?
I'd just start dropping them
Okay
much faster than that
Not not one at a time you're not too worried about what's gonna happen
All right, well watch out watch out
What's that?
Uh, those combine into life crystals if you get 10 of them really how do we get it? How can we give it a lava?
Uh, just blow it up. Just keep blowing shit up
I just blew them up
They're still in there
So we're
Keep going down
Yeah
Keep doing this
Keep going. I only have like eight bombs left
All right. That's enough. Oh my god. Oh my god. What what?
I'm down there. I know but I you told me to keep doing it
Well, okay, that's enough that's enough more bomb him more
I'm gonna go this way. I don't have any bombs. Those are grenades
You like really don't like working together
We kind of like wherever I dig isn't good enough for you
It's not yeah, no, it's not
control
I did it already. I think I found something
platinum ore
platinum
Good, I don't think it's really useful for us anymore. Demonite is better and we have a lot
Did we skip everything?
All right, so we're i'm above you
So i'm in hell
Do we go back up?
uh
Yeah, I have a lot of stuff I can put away
How do we sum up the next boss?
That's how hold on. Hold on. Hold on. Hold on
Uh, we could go to the beach and fight the giant jellyfish, which I don't even give us anything beach we need
It's all the way on the left side of the map very very long walk
And it will be a pain in the neck
Wait, what's going on people arguing in chat sub only?
Oh, I know what we can do
We should be discussing terraria strategies
One moment, then I have a plan go caving
We just did some caving didn't we just go caving
camera mode
All right, should I just get rid of this book? I feel like i'm not using it at all
Uh, sure
You're gonna, you know, stop using things a lot and you don't have to ask my permission. Yeah, but yeah
I know but you're the most
You're the most addressable person right now
Okay, you know what? I understand. I apologize for being
Abrasive
You're very abrasive right now
Hey, what video is that from?
Hey get that a star right there you're gonna get that star
I'm selling something
I am gonna get that and i'm gonna use it because I think I have three now because I have one
star
No, I have two
Two enemies are nearby. What are these uh, two like tesla, uh cannon things?
Uh one is so you can make furniture out of snow and one is so you can make stuff out of slime
or gel
How do I take it off? So how do you take a room off sub only?
Slash subscribers, I think
How do I turn it off subscribers off why does it feel like that means I delete everybody
Subscribers are subscribers are removed from the channel
Hey, hey, wait, what did it? What did my wife say?
Where's uh
Where is it?
Here I have three things for you. How the fuck do I do this?
I don't even know how to like I don't even know how to fucking turn it off on my own damn channel
Am I about to google how to turn off sub only and get mods?
Don't tell him how to do that
Yeah, i'm searching for it. Okay, how to turn off sub only twitch
How do you turn off sub only chat?
It's likely visual bug
Subscribers off they would write
All right, everybody behave yourselves
I somebody did
Behave
Don't no more. I don't want to I don't hear about any politics talk
Don't let star talk about like
hillary's emails
Germa thinks his stream is more important than the future of america. I don't want to hear about the damn emails anymore. Okay?
The whole entire country is sick of hearing about your email talk about
This importance of all of our futures and where it's headed talk about me instead
All right. So wait, what are we doing? What's what's going on?
two one
Zero the countdown come to the right. All right. Are you summoning a boss?
Uh, there's two bosses. We're gonna fight two bosses. Are you gonna summon those bosses two summoning stones?
Straight above us is a planet with a giant bee in it. Got it
Okay, so go up
Uh, did you take all the ropes that I had I had like a thousand where we're going up we're going up bone rope
this is uh
Ah, you wouldn't appreciate that
I just threw up a bomb in here
I'm helping i'm helping i'm helping i'm helping
Okay. So once we dig inside of this, yeah
Of the bee queen or whatever will spawn
This is a bee queen
She's similar to the bird we fought where she dashes left and right at you
But also she shoots a lot of things. Hey
Okay, so okay. So we're probably going to fight her
on the ground
So go down after we summon
Yeah, or fight her on the rope
Well, I don't if you want to fight her on the rope
Queen bee is spun. All right, so just be careful, right?
It's just like contra
She's gonna hurt
There's a contra level just like this
All right. Well, she's
Oh
Add a mana add a mana
What okay, I guess the best you can do is stand still
I'll wait for you. I'm good. I'm good. I'm good
I got mana back
I think you would get a lot of enjoyment from the bee items
ow fuck
Hold on I can potion in four seconds
That's a lie
I just missed don't die. Oh my god
I
It just I need mana
I run out of mana that I just
Stick my fingers in my eyes. I gave you a fucking musket. This doesn't cost mana
Okay, actually, no, this is this is what you want. Trust me. I think you're gonna love this
Take this
We're going step by step take this as long as you're shooting wooden arrows
So like make sure your your ammo on the right isn't like flaming arrows or something. You shoot a line of bees
I'm gonna get as much did you pick up my money?
I did
Okay, jerma
I'm not done with yes. What is it? I'm paying attention
Take this i'm downloading an entire class into my brain in the first day of school
Okay, jerma take you're the teacher and i'm sitting in a fucking chair and hey, welcome to the first day. Here's the syllabus
Oh, by the way, uh, here's every single test do it now. It's a lot jerma. It's a lot. I know
All right, what do you want me to do with this as long as that's in your inventory other bees are friendly to you
Which is only in the jungle. It's up to you if you want to waste inventory space on it. I'll keep it
Okay, and this you take this
If you get hit bees come out of you
All right
Okay, and this
What do you get hit it feels damaged everything around you which will actually hit every segment of a worm. It's pretty good early
Okay, take this
That'll increase your minion damage where
Okay
Equip material equipment equipable. Where does it equip to?
uh
Underneath the armor the slots are all for accessories
And I think that's it
I would highly recommend use of that bow
Uh, um, yeah, i'm gonna i think i'm gonna give it a try
Especially because all these once they come out they become homing and they just follow everything and then you just like you can read your chat
And become a boomer
So, what what does it use for um
For wooden arrows turned into a column of vehicles wooden arrows
So I don't need I don't need like cobweb anymore
Uh cobweb turns into rope. You might as well just turn it all into a rope. Okay, so I need wooden arrows
You know here I have 400
Okay, i'll take 400 arrows you're gonna want more let me check
Let me test this out
They're saying you didn't get the money
I have 21 gold. Oh, there is gold over there
Yeah, you can just have it that that that's like that's like my like fuck face fee
You know what I mean? Like that's yours. Like I you could have it
What okay, but queen bee
Discouraged the giant insects are they can prove useful in certain situations?
Giving the ability to control them placing your image and make all small bees weak
All small bees and weak hornets friendly. I have two of these though. I don't do I need does it make them extra friendly?
Oh, no. No, you don't need both
And again bees really only exist in the jungle, but it's probably a waste inventory spot
But I thought you know, maybe you'd get into the whole bee thing. So what's a strange plant?
Uh garbage
bee nade
All right, that's kind of cool
feather
Deposit this stuff avian cartilage
Do you have any more? Um stars
I have one
You can trade the strange plant for dye. That's cool
You have one can I have it or do you need it?
Uh, it's daytime. I can't give it to you
oh
Right. I don't think i'm gonna use
Maybe I will
No, i'll use this i'll try it
Try what?
That bow if you're not gonna use it
I'll use the bow but i'm talking about the vine. Should I get to replace the bow with the vine?
You know what I mean? What's the vine? Oh vile thorn. Yeah
Nah, keep vile thorn keep vile thorn and just when you run out of mana just shoot bees
What do I do with it?
I guess i'll put it up here
I like dark wave though. I like the dot
Uh, I think magma ore
Actually makes them a good fire spell
I think we actually have enough to do it
So what's next on the agenda?
You can hear me, right? Yeah
Okay, i'm gonna make you this
spam
Never mind. I don't know how to make it
Let me ask jeffery
Jeff, how do you do this? It might be hellstone actually
I wonder if I get hellstone. Let me look at this again. Okay, five percent increase minion knockback damage
So it regenerates health. I want like a i've won a bunch of mana regeneration
Uh, then we need to find the meteorite
Because that gives you an armor set that reduces the cost of spells mana
And gives extra magic damage
All right, I just send it flying. All right. Well, what what's the second boss that you wanted to do?
Uh, we have to go back to the corruption. There's another boss we can fight there
You wanna do it?
Can I pee first? Yeah
Yeah. Yep. Yep. Yep. Why don't you it's been like four hours. Why don't you go on a pee break, too?
No, i've never peed before. Okay. How how often do you like when you stream how long do you stream usually?
Like five or six hours lately six hours like maybe five to eight hours something like that
Yeah, how many times do you go pee in like a seven and a half hours? I don't I don't get up
You do not get up. I don't
I've had like 12 hour streams where i've not peed
Are you drinking water?
Yes, ever since I was a child. It's one of my you know, one of my past times you go to the toilet
You have to make sure you remember to count how long you're peeing. I've told you this before. I know I have yeah told everyone
What's your longest pee?
my longest pee ever
Well, it was probably like it was probably like 45 seconds and then it stopped
And then I thought it was over and then another full like probably 35 seconds
after stoppage like stopping
For at least five straight seconds, then it doesn't count. No, it does. It's the same. It's actually continuous
That's the same session. You don't leave the urinal
Well, see because the problem then becomes if if you're allowed to stop then a whole bunch of people would be stopped start
Stop, and then you get like an extended. Well, that doesn't happen all the time. That's only happening like twice
continuously
My the longest pee i've ever had it continuously where i've just been looking down going what the fuck is happening
Whoa
was
No, you you have that reaction because where does it go if you pee for 60 straight seconds
How what where is that shit inside you?
Your bladder is not that big you're peeing out like a whole body full of pee
That's like two 32 ounce gatorade bottles like that can't fit in there
You're right i'm laughing because you're right
Uh, probably like I don't know 50 60 seconds, maybe tops you can't go for that long
But uh, all right, whatever i'll be right back
Give me a second and tell me more
I'm gonna be muted on my stream, but not on your stream
Okay, yes, I when we hear the okay
BRB
Well, it's just me and you guys
Okay, okay, I understand I understand okay, I understand it's all clear now
All right, just out of the way unmute you or prison, uh, dude
Hello. Hello. Hello. Hello
Hi, hello. Hello. Hello
Hello
All right. So what have you got done in the my absence? Oh you made like I made some rooms
You made a little another section. This is a science section
indeed
Okay. All right. You ready?
I'm gonna head out. I guess yeah, what do you want to do the other boss?
other boss
What is this one is the jellyfish boss you're talking about
No
This boss is the hive mind
So
Is it big? Is it cool? Is it scary?
Uh, it's kind of a blob
And then you destroy the blob and then there's a phase two and then it's a floating blob
introduction of uh faces
I've seen that before
It's obviously you cannot defeat reddit
Well, I would agree normally that guess you cannot defeat reddit
What about hillary's email?
We had we had we had moved on it was already over we had moved on from that
Because all right, you do realize that when you say that
Everyone like laughs like oh
Yeah
Yeah, that was but what about them though?
And then it's just and then it just becomes like a politics chat
Well, then then you have to look deep within yourself again and figure out if you're more important than the future of america
And then if you should stifle the conversation
I guess yes. I apologize for restarting it
Okay, we're in the corruption. We are looking for remember
There's that thing on the ground before and you're like, what's this? And I was like don't shoot it. It's a cyst
It grows on the ground
And then when we destroy that it summons the boss and I hope we can beat it
That's kind of how it goes. So would you say would you say it is some kind of?
sis lord
I don't get a reference. You've never seen
Like a sith lord
Like like a star. Oh, here's one
Yes
Like don't die, please
I'm but I need I need help
I'm not I don't think i'm capable of doing this on my own make ropes
I don't think I have any you took them all
Well, no, no, no
I'm good. Okay. I don't know. I'm fine. Help me
Help me climb this hole
I don't want to hear about those emails
All right, are you ready? What do you mean? Are we gonna go up go up when it first spawns?
It's like stationary. I'm just gonna chuck bombs at it
Just chuck but I have like b bombs
So are we fighting this in any particular place?
um
Just around
Okay
And its move set is
I honestly don't know. It's really
It's like the lamest move set of any boss and doesn't really do anything
Whoa, you came out of here you see it's just kind of there now is the second phase
I think it does what the brain does
Like teleports around and then comes at you again, but never gets near you
And it goes
Ohio I think that's what it's saying which is uh, well, you know why a lot of damage numbers
Okay
How would you explain this move set?
Now that you've seen it you like get like I didn't know what to say
What the move set? Yeah, like you said once it's move set and I didn't know what to say
Uh, yeah, it's just kind of
It just it just kind of exists and moves around the circle
Yeah
And then something it turns into another thing that moves around the circle
Yep
That's the one
It gives us a true shadow scales which you can craft with demonite bars and I do not remember what it makes
It's not at all hive mine
So did you did you get anything interesting? I didn't really get I got like this. I just got
I got true shadow scales for crafting and
throwing weapons
Place in your inventory for all your projectiles to inflict cursed flames when in the corruption
the hive mine
Wait all projectiles in the crump. That's pretty cool. Yeah, as long as you're in this area, so like
So does that have to be like in my hot bar or just in my backpack in your inventory anywhere? Okay
So when I shoot somebody with this they get like burnt. Well, that's awesome. Yeah
That's pretty good
Are we good? Is this another one? Yeah, let's do one more
Just in case shadow skills do make something good because I don't remember
Oh god, i'm stuck down here. It's tim allen noise
Is it though kind of is I think we need to go
go
To the beach
Did he drop would drop something?
Uh, he dropped a staff for you. It's pretty decent. Did he here?
Let me see that thing
Shadow drop staff. I think that's not what I thought it was actually
Summons dark or rain from the sky
Let him get the drops. I I should
So just
It's just a rain projectile
Yeah, all those bullets deal damage
That's actually that's pretty good. I think i'd rather have this than um
There's there's one of those that you can make with a hellstone which we can mine down in hell except the projectiles go through the ground
So because like if you're underground that rain doesn't do anything
Oh, really?
Well, it'll come from the top of your screen. It's also kind of hard to see
I can't really tell like exactly where it's going
I think it's just because where you are in the background is purple. All right, so we're just porting back, right?
Yeah
I love watching derma progress in this game from an insignificant caterpillar to a big beautiful slightly more competent caterpillar
Okay, i've got the i've got the real deal for you
Yeah, I guess
You got the real deal for me
I gotta hold on
Uh, did you ever give me that star?
Nope, I have five of them now I can ask you
I thought you can't do that
You can do that with the blue ones. Oh
All right. What I need to change my hot bar a little bit here. This is kind of a mess
I fuked up
You have to crap. These are the demon altar
I forget that every time
So should I just be putting my gold in here too in the big box?
Uh, yes, no reason not to
I'm gonna make some more torches
And all right
I think it's time to make a change here
I gotta go make you an item. So i'll be back
This is called I like this b thing
This can just it's a one use essentially
Keep the apples over here
All right, I like that little setup
If you press the item in an empty space
So you don't have to put it in the hot bar
If you believe me like if I just if I click this it'll just use it
Thank god. He's learning it
No, click outside of the inventory
Oh, I see. Okay. I see what you mean
So if I click on let's say this I just
No, hello
To use items like the mirror you don't need to put them in your hot bar instead
You pick them up from your inventory then left click outside
Oh cool
So hold on for instance like a healing potion I just
All right. I get you. I get you. I get you. I got it. I got you
This is lady
I'm gonna make some more rope
And some more torches
Did you figure out what you could do with the uh?
Stuff that we just made i'll be back in a second. I'm making the stuff for you
Making the stuff for you
Thanks
You know how sometimes I have trouble
You're a real friend here
Uh, take this it's a new summon. It's not a bird
and this
uh
This and this dank creeper to fight for you and then yeah
Yeah, get the freaking dank creeper
So can I have can I use both these to get like together with the bird and the dank you have one minion slot?
What's better bird or dank?
Uh dank is better. They their type of summons
Seeks out enemies a little bit better
Their AI is better even though their damage is not that different
so what's the dark wave or
Shadarian stuff
Shade rain shade rain. Yeah, come use that outside
I want to make sure what I think
okay, yeah, so you have you have one minion slot and
I think those count as a sentry slot
Yeah, so you can have two sentries in the clouds count as sentries
So they just kind of sit there and they they pour rain
So if like there's a boss just you know, get those clouds above it and does a lot of damage because each drop is a projectile
So what the hell does it?
Someone's a dank creeper to fight. Where's my dank creeper?
You have to go to the top left and unsummon your bird to be able to summon something new. Oh, okay
And that thing's better just the stuff. Oh, yeah clouds are
My never mind
So I'm gonna have two clouds out at the same time
Yep
I don't like this this thing moves around too much. She's annoying
All right. I guess i'll just be place stuff and aoe guy
And I have the b thing. Okay
All right. Um, I think i'm good to
We can fight the slime god, but i'm not sure if we're ready
Don't know if you're ready to fight the slime god
What do I have potions?
Hmm
That's enough you should place down clouds and switch to your other weapons. Don't need to unequip your other staff
Yeah, that's true
That's very true
So essentially it's my rotation would be
uh
like two
two three four
Yeah, okay, and then five
Because this would be a setting up. Hold on. Let me see
I don't know
Get the clouds out switch to here throw it out there get it out bang bang bang
Wait for the overpower to proc get it guaranteed crit switch back inner rage
Okay, bang bang
we can
Prepare to fight the slime god
It's kind of hard
Or we can prepare to fight the wall of flesh which will change the whole world into heart
Which will open up a lot of new things
or
Can hold down this button from massive aoe
Or we can go look for the meteorite. That's how we can get you meteor armor
And then there's also a boss we can summon with meteorite
All right. What's the what's the the the progression from here, you know, what's the oh, no
Don't just like make a well and go to the bottom of hell
What would you say is? Okay. Here's like the next step
All of those were very good next steps doing the only thing is the little wall of flesh will
Turn it into hard mode. It doesn't stop you from doing the bosses, but it's kind of
If you want to do everything before you change it to hard mode, that would be the last thing you do. Okay
Well, I would say because you want to be caster guy we need to find where the meteorite landed
But I have no idea. I think we just have to walk right and I know how much you hate walking, right?
Eventually you can actually like create minecart tracks and stuff about you torches. I only have 31 torches
I have seven
Probably probably should make some
uh
Do we have materials in here for this?
The torch is in here. What is what is it wood?
uh gel and platforms
I don't think we have any gel do we
I'm just gonna make a shit look
We do. All right. I'm just gonna make a bunch
Oh my god, i'm gonna buy germa a gift a gift. He's gonna love me
You know how it's like your birthday right now
uh
Am I stupid or something what's going on here wood platform, sir
Term i'm trying to i'm right next to you. Happy birthday
Equip that and then press the r
How long can I stay like this forever forever? What?
Yes
Okay, thank you for giving me my first sona
No problem
You can see your first sona. Yes it is
All right, wooden flat not wood wood. Oh, yeah. Yeah, okay. Okay. Okay. I see what you mean
All right, pause that and then we can go
I'm ready
Where'd you go? I'm coming. You went I went to space. Why'd you go space?
I was waiting. Oh, I need my mirror too
Sometimes you just go to space
All right
so
What's happening?
Are we ready for this?
Uh, what do I say we were doing? We were going really far. You said you go really far right to find the meteor
Okay, while we're there
Actually, no, we can't do it on the right
We'll figure it out. You know, it's a journey together. Yes it is
Can you eventually get in a fast travel or car or something to go here fast
I was gonna say you can set up minecart tracks. There's also like redstone like there's in minecraft. You can set up a teleporter
Uh, there's also boots that make you sprint but we have not found any of them and the cobbler has not arrived because he's an asshole
It's gonna be nighttime. Is it a bad thing or a good thing?
It doesn't matter doesn't matter
also, eventually you get yeah, there's mounts and they're
Um wings that are pretty fast
Cool
So I know when you make when you make a new minecraft seed
It's oh 30 times the size of earth
How many times the size of earth?
is terraria
Uh, i'm gonna i'm gonna say 600 times
I'm gonna say actually we should abandon earth
And just live in terraria
Upload our brains in here
He uh, somebody's calling us a dean dingus
They're saying build more rooms you dean dinguses
Yeah, now they're right. But building rooms is the most boring part
Here's the trick here. I want to show you I can't do moves. How do I get out of this?
Oh, okay trick
um
So this this room pre-exists
Okay, where is there? Uh
I need a chair
What you do is you take someone stupid like the painter that you never want to talk and then you force him to live way out here
Why?
So that the rooms in your base free up
But I don't have a chair to place in here
Painter all the way over here
But does why would he have an axe?
I do
Can you chop down these trees?
Yeah
Like I can handle it
What do you need these chopped down for you need the wood?
Yeah, so I can I can make a chair and force the painter to live in exile
Normally, I build them like on the planets
pet snow owl
I don't want it
Painter is a god npc. You're really making a lot of people very sad right now
Summoner weapon proficiency level up. So what what are you doing?
Apparently it didn't have a table
These things are pretty good
So equipable, what do I equip it though?
Oh
Uh, it's in the corruption. It doesn't count as a house
Never mind is that is it just right there. What does he do just stare at me?
Oh, yeah, that's just the pet most pets don't do anything
I have the I have a bee following me. Oh, I was wondering what the bee was
There's some good pets that like provide light and stuff, but most of them do not
So we're just walking to the right until we find
the
meteor
Yeah
But there's no other goal. We just walk right until we see it
Yep, because on our map we explored left and I didn't see a meteorite on the map. The map always updates automatically
Oh
So it should be this way
Then there's gonna be some sick sick ass meteor heads
So when we get to the meteor, does the boss just spawn after we touch it or something?
No, the meteor is uh, you just it's
A resource just so you get meteorites from it
What is this?
Uh kill that kill it kill it kill it i am i am i'm killing it so we need the blighted gel from it
Oh god, oh god, dude
I dropped 22 gold in that hole. I'll get it
We still haven't made hooks
How far down is that hole?
So i'm gonna rope down there
It's not that far. Should I just jump?
You can see where you're dude
I believe in you
Do I have any rope?
Are you even in the right hole? No, you're not other hole. What do you mean other hole?
There's another hole right guy. I don't know if it shows for you. Oh, no
Okay
So are you
Stay trying to stay down here or what are you doing? What are you up to?
I'm coming back up. I'm just making sure I get the gel from that thing
That's over here
rotten chunk
I'm afraid to just walk forward now because of that
I've got the grab arm
I'm just gonna hold my torch out
That's bright. Oh, we still have to do this actually
I forgot about this guy
Huh? Hurry we need to build platforms
Hurry
We're gonna fight somebody
And he's a pain in the ass
Fight pain in the ass guy
Yeah, you have to uh, you talk to the old man in front of this which is the dungeon
You can only enter the dungeon after you free him of his curse and his curse is that a giant forearm skeleton lives inside of
His body and you gotta fight it
It's a pretty wicked curse
That is a pretty big curse
Yeah
This is a big platform you're making
He's a piece of shit
In fact, I worry about us
Do you?
Yeah, I do. You ready? I guess eat your food free food
Okay
I've free fooded
Oh, he doesn't have four arms. Is that only the
Mechanical guy
I guess we all have a curse
Oh, he's a chump freaking normal mode
Oh bees
There's a certain place we should be aiming
into his head
chump
I thought you said he was really hard
He can be but I don't usually play on baby mode
Let's turn the drop. Sorry drop anything. Sorry. I'm the anchor
No, it's fine. Like really normal mode eventually when we get into the
Still hard. Okay
So now we can go in the dungeon
Uh, yeah, I want to keep looking for the meteor though. Oh right, right, right, right, right, right
Though the dungeon has a couple of things we could really use
We are very far away from our home
Here I got two
Manicristo
Yeah, I gave you two
zombie banner
Uh, it auto gives that to you when like 50 of something dies and if you hang out at home
You deal like two times damage for that enemy
Cool
It's a neat little game
So there's no meteor
And your follow-up to that?
No
Uh, I guess I was wrong. Let's go in the dungeon
Into the dungeon it is
Ow what these crocodile things geez who the fuck is who's tyler?
Oh, he's the fishing
No
Don't die don't die, dude
You're gonna die
You're gonna die. No, i'm trying to avoid being hit
No, that's oh, that's my stupid
I thought the owl was coming to get me
Thank you, dude. I was on a healing streak
These kids don't even know about me
I'm out of ammo
Uh, somebody said the meteor is probably on the sky that's pretty likely
God sky meteor, I guess
In this particular seed
I don't think i've ever seen that
Thank god i'm so stupid
Uh rope oh because I have
A lot of jump
You could probably turn into a frog and do it
Would that be better?
Oh is that do I jump higher?
The first jump you do is higher. Yeah. Well, I you didn't tell me that
I thought it was just a cosmetic thing
Nice automatically update. Isn't that a lie though? Because you can see plantera's bulbs when they become available
If you've already been in that spot
It's very dark up here
Where are you going?
I'm going to the dungeon
Oh
I was just hoping there would be something up there
Okay
Into the dungeons. This is this is the dungeon
This is the oh, yeah. Okay. So what you need to find and make sure you
see him is uh
Uh golden keys gold because there's gonna be a bunch of golden chests down here that you need keys to open
That drop from the enemies
Okay, so look for golden keys and inside a golden chest the number one thing
We're looking out for yeah
Is a uh shadow key
Shadow key so we need we need a key to get a new key is what that's that's the goal
That's like best case. Otherwise, there's just like decent stuff in these chests understood
So how far down does this go?
Uh, it's pretty big
It's uh pretty
Pretty pretty big
Oh, and we got the uh, the the mechanic who is my terraria waifu
Just in case you're wondering
We got wire cutter
She's the person that lets you set up like the wires to set up teleporters and stuff. Oh, what's this do?
There's like a switch here. I can't press it
Waiting for you
What's the switch do?
Uh turns on the lights. Oh, so why didn't I turn it?
It turns on like one small lantern you probably just didn't notice
chest
This is the key needs to have one of those golden keys. Yep
the ultra stream sting i'm a streamer
There are spikes on the walls and floors that hurt
That are they are hurt. There's also traps down here. So like dark traps that'll shoot things out
You step on the pressure plates great
Really looking forward to that
And those things that go along the ground
The heck is that you just like summon a bunch of spots
So there's the key that we don't have
What what just hit me?
uh dart trap
They're hard to see
rained on
Do aggro them up here and they'll get hit by my rain clouds
all comboed
And the thing he's standing on are spikes. You don't stand on spikes spikes are bad wand core
Uh, they craft some really shitty wands that are really complicated to make
There's like one decent one
If I remember correctly
Um, what do I do? Uh, you see i'm attached to the ceiling with a I thought
The fucking painting was like a platform
This game is so dark
Oh
All right. We're uh, how did you make that hook that you're attached to the ceiling with?
um
You can check the box
You need 15 of a gem so if we have like 15 amethyst or something
I don't think we have
enough
No, well, we're coming back. Uh, I think I didn't have that much money. I don't think but there was some gold down there
I would go get it
Put the stuff away
Our we're we're full
We're full our box is full
We can take some shit out
Cane dust
Making night owl potion
Really? Is that gonna help me?
Not really. Oh, yeah, maybe
We need there's a potion vendor too and he would sell them for cheap
Then where was it?
He is not enjoying this yet
Can I craft that or did I have here it is increases night vision?
Uh, give me that please because also I think it's called a shine potion
What the fuck is going on right now in the house
What if I die in the house i'm gonna
What is going he's still alive?
Hi, yay
Who left the door? You left the doors open
You let in a draft
Wait, you've been at home for how long now and you're gonna start blaming me all of a sudden
All right. So, um
Do we have any more of those wormhole potions or am I uh screwed here?
Uh, I have four on me
Does that help you?
Can I buy them or can I make them? What do they take to make?
I don't think you can
Well, I mean you can I just have no idea how who is somebody does somebody sell them
Does anybody know?
I need blink root
So it looks like I have to just come come follow down here
Why are you doing something else?
What do you want me to do?
I don't know
Yeah, we have no more. What are you gonna do? Uh, let me see. I think there's like mushrooms in here
I'm gonna get like the bacon the mushrooms don't get rid of those fucking mushrooms. Why?
I need them. You actually need these mushrooms. Oh, no. No glowing mushrooms. I need
Um, did this like random little materials that I just what the hell are they doing in here?
Yeah
Uh, hold on. Don't don't don't delete anything. I'll come home
Yeah, I feel like you're gonna like
Delete the secret recipe. I'm probably gonna delete the secret recipe
I can just leave you know, I can just
I can just leave
I can I can just leave germa germa distraction baby toys. Oh look a new staff. Look a new staff
Oh, that's two new stabs
Doesn't hey germa. Do you see this thing over here? That's not as cool. It's not as cool if I didn't earn it
germa
a floating book
Yeah, I guess it's
I guess it's cool
When you come over here and you right click the floating book
Yeah, you're gonna have an additional summon for 10 minutes
Um, I guess that's cool
It's really cool dad. Like thanks
It's just too bad. You didn't earn it
This game is dark
Okay
So you said you're gonna
Uh, this thing is what what's going on with this thing guys?
Hold on
I gotta try
Where are you? Oh
I thought you jumped in a hole
Ooh
Ooh sparklers 29
magic damage
That's pretty good
So this next one is high tide
Sends out a droplet of water that will create small tidal waves
Ooh, that's cool
Takes a lot of uh, mana
Oh, there's too many items for me to I don't know what I want to do with any of these. Um
Uh
It's a lot i'm gonna this is a lot of damage and it's close range
I don't know. I think i'm gonna get rid of dark wave
That's not close range
Oh, all right. Yeah. All right. This is awesome. I thought it was
Okay
All right
That's really really good actually cool
Yeah, i'm i'm gonna sell dark wave
Dark wave is out
and I think
High tide isn't doing it for me
I like um, I like
I like them. Yeah
I appreciate you giving this to me
But i'm not for me
Yeah
You gotta get eyes on
So i'm gonna store it
Have you done any uh consolidation here?
Yeah, i've got a lot of stuff out
Like that. I like that and now I need some I need some like rope and materials or
Um, what do I want to move the gold in here?
Weapons are used to make better weapons later
Just a
never-ending trade
Take that back
Okay, um
potions
um
Give me this I want to use that
I cannot believe we haven't had a blood moon yet
What happens I cannot believe it
What's a blood moon?
Uh, it's just at night
A blood moon status and a whole bunch of enemies attack you and they drop some things
And then after the first blood moon, there's an npc that'll join you
How do I just take them?
Stop stop stop stop stop stop stop
I just want one of these. Okay. I got it
All right
I'm ready to attempt that again
I got food. I have uh tortures. I need some rope though
You can start walking there and I'll teleport you rope rope rope rope. What's the quickest way to make a rope with the spider webs?
Uh cobweb. Yeah
I can make you some if you don't have it
I don't have I don't have very much. No
There you go
That's a lot
Okay, i'm gonna touch this thing. They're not run out. Okay, i'm going
See
See you later
See you there
Is there can we put like a checkpoint flag somewhere over here?
What is there? We can't put like a checkpoint flag. We have to always have to go all the way over here again
Mm-hmm unless you want to build a wine cart
That goes all the way there
You just make a bed there
Yeah, but then you won't have this bed
That's true
You make a sleeping bag
Or a tent
Sounds interesting
I don't even know what the hell that was but
Got hurt from it
I gotta build houses man. Like I don't wanna
But I gotta
Are zombies in raincoats?
Yeah
That's that's very cute
I'm just gonna that's just like what else do you want me to say?
Oh, that's your spot on
I mean, it's raining
This fishing in this game. Yeah, didn't you say that you didn't you didn't really dabble into fishing at all?
I have never dabbled
you have
How many what do you have like six seven eight hundred hours in this game?
Uh about 200
Really even after all the other times you played this
I mean I had I okay I had
Uh 160
And I didn't play it that much when it was new. I played like 60 hours and there wasn't that much to do
um
Way back when the game first came out that skeleton that we just beat was like the final boss
Are you serious? I think when terraria was first released there was nothing after that. Wow
That's so that's so
Early
Yeah, and now he's like
Yeah, there's there's a lot of shit
Only the game's been out for so long
Oh cool
I'm freaking out. I didn't have enough
Do I have three? No, one more big snowball head
I don't think i'm gonna be changing weapons for a very long time. This thing is unbelievable
Does a bunch of damage
It's got a nice spread on it
Nice spread doesn't use that much mana
For the first time in my life
I feel like i'm truly true. No, I can't do that
Yeah, and it lights my way
I don't even need torches anymore. I can just go like this
I need torches
Uh, I have 76
You should definitely make some though. So I because i'm a very unreliable person
Don't like rely on me for that
Because you know what's gonna happen torches you're gonna be very disappointed. I
I need torches
Am I there where is this place
Where the hell is this place?
I'm not even there yet. Yeah, you're not there yet
I thought you were the guy
No, i'm not. I have a mini map open
Okay, I have 1800 torches i'm ready to go
All right. Well, i'm like almost there
I'm at where we bought the skeleton guy
What flavor jawbreaker do you want when I go to the jawbreaker store?
um
Uh plain chocolate. No, just plain
All right. I've made it you can teleport to me whenever you want whenever you feel like it
Concrete plain the one that is just the white one that has all the other ones inside of it
Did you know that fish isn't good for you?
Um
I don't I don't sure what I I can't even give that a response. It's actually true
the new reports
Yeah, I think it's like doctor sign sign wiser
I'm saying that like you're a dummy a fisher from the ocean and you're not
Stop eating them
All right. Well
I forgot to buy musket balls your mercury
Not every fish is full of mercury
And all that mercury and like cod
That's no joke
All that it's not
Yeah, and guess what?
when you cook
meat on a grill
It releases a shitload of carcinogenics
All that stuff that you like to eat. I like those crispy edges and the little charcoal crispy
It that's it's awful awful for you, but we do it. Oh, everybody does it
I don't do it
You've never had a grilled piece of meat. What am I fucking bumping my head on i'm getting too angry at this game
I gotta slow down
Who's who actually has grilled pieces of meat?
What like your grandfather maybe?
What is it coming over here? What is that thing? What's this plan destroy that as a trap? Oh, all right, this is kind of
So is there a boss at the bottom of this?
No
Uh later there is a boss here much much much much later
For now, it's just kind of a pet
And bones
All the money down there, but too, uh scared to go over there. Oh my god, what are you doing dying?
you
Okay
Yeah, we're fine. All food is bad. Just eat air
Actually water is bad for you
It's true
dungeon heist
Blue candles spawning more enemies kill the blue candles. Don't kill the blue candles
But somebody on the internet told me to do that
But that somebody doesn't know that we really would like more of me so that they have a higher chance of
That's where I died before
I'm gonna make the same mistake twice
Yeah, yeah. Yeah
All right, so is it not safe to go down there?
Did you get my stuff down there by the way on the bottom here? I did I did
I'm just making sure I'm just making I know I just I know
No, you don't make sure you think you know, you always talk about how you know
My wife gets me dinner
Slot machine, what did you say? This is I that thing you just pulled it looks like a slot machine
I didn't know what it was
You're not calling my wife a slot machine
No, that is not what I said slot machine as in like a question. Is that a slot machine next to you?
I don't I didn't see it
You pulled a lever and it made the whole room dark you get any keys I don't think so
I have two
I have one
I have one key
Are you do you want to bring these pianos back? You want to make a dungeon room?
No
You don't just want to chill out and make like candy rooms and dungeon rooms. No, the candy room would be fun, but
Everything else is
Well, that was horrible that hurt
Hey, holy shit, man
Sitting up here. Um, how are we doing down there? All right, i'm gonna open this one
I already opened it. He did
Mystic magic missile
Would you just drop it?
Yep
Wait, you're gonna get to use some magic myth
Did I pick it up?
Yeah
Well, i'll look at it later. Look at it now
Look at it now. I can't we're being fired at from all directions. I'm not just gonna stop and let me look at my items
It's a new item
What does it do?
That's okay. That's a lot of guys. Can we get some uh, I don't have this mystic magic missile
There's a rod. Oh 31 damage. All right, i'll give it a try. You're gonna see give it a try
Do you want to know why a magic missile is so good? What does it do? No
I guess it's
magic missile
Very fast very strong nine mana
It's just like a fast good item just goes like bang bang bang bang bang
It's like a little solo target. I like it. I don't love it though
Yeah, I think if you hold you can
But also your other thing does feel a lot better yeah, the other one's more mana efficient
Is that what you guys think a meteorite?
Hold the button
Oh you can
Hold on. Can I just like
Have that sit on somebody?
Can I sit that on somebody?
and it
No, okay. I didn't know if I could just hold it continuously on them
You got any keys now we need to stay I do we need to stick together
I'm looking for chests. You're just fighting the same old thing looking at your dumb item
How come I don't get items? You should check on how that item works. Jeremy
So you said and I said, okay i'll give it a try I was joking
How much further are we gonna go deep dungeon, isn't it?
Is there a golden chest thing?
right here
This isn't a locked one though
unlocked
It had a gold cannon
cool
The skulls they explode. They look like they explode
Nope
I'll kill this guy
Can I have that sword you don't use?
Uh, it's in the box
Uh you fucker
Why would I just carry that around with me if i'm not gonna use it?
I thought you were using it. I mean I I have too many items
I have too many cool things to use. I can't carry it around
You're the melee guy. You're the one that should have had it
Why did I why am I holding? I didn't want to be a melee guy
Well, what are you?
Oh, you didn't want to be melee guy
I want to play my tuba. How do I get what's going on?
Why am I stuck in this chest?
Uh
Oh happened to me too
What?
Yeah, that's uh, that's a bad program
Do I
Can I like put something in it?
I can't teleport. Yeah, it's just broken
I think we're fucked
No game over. Did you open it? Why'd you open it too?
Because I wanted to see what you
Open it
I just wanted to see if there was really a problem. I said i'm stuck. What's wrong?
And then uh
Are we sure there's nothing that can happen here?
Uh, you can leave and rejoin
Well, what would that was it gonna put me?
Uh back at your bed
What?
Yeah
Wait, okay. What if you stay here then the server will go down. Okay. What if you stay I come back and then teleport to you
Do you have a wormhole potion?
Uh, I I have them but I can't give them to you because we're both lost
I'm gonna have to leave too. No, can I I think I can I make
I think there might be a wormhole potion in the chest. All right. Hold on
I'll be back. I mean i'm i'm going to have to leave as well because i'm just talking but you own the place
I own the place
Fuck
No
I got it. Yeah, I saved an exit and got a bigger. Uh
Oh well, we have been live. Oh, i've been live for seven hours almost eight actually
So are we gonna keep going?
um
you uh do
You want to just let's get to the bottom of that dungeon
Okay, will that be like significant?
More time
No, not really. All right. Let's do that. It's don't open any chests
Any chest that isn't a golden chest you can't open anyway, so don't
Don't touch them
Okay. All right. So are you going back in?
Yeah, one second
You let me know you let me know when you're in there
I'm in there
Okay
I want to join off of you use that character
Joining in game. Here we go
Yeah, there are some people here that like do not deserve to live in this house
Who are all these people?
Wait, hold on
Who the fuck are all these people?
Why did this become a hotel?
I like this is not even all of them
Hey paul
Is why you talk shit about the painter like like if you really need some painting done
You can go seek him out. All right. So listen what so what happens?
So these are just npcs that they just wander around if you don't lock them in a cage in your house
Where do they go? Just they all just scatter around where their home is
So the strategy is to keep them into little cubicles like it's an office
Yeah
And there's different departments. Otherwise they wander around and if you want to talk to one
They could be like next to someone and you'll like can't talk to them because they're under the other guy
But okay, okay, let's just say for instance if I threw a bomb in this room right now, uh, please
I'm just theoretically
Is it is that bad?
Yes, okay
I didn't know if they can be hurt or friendly fire. They can be hurt and more importantly you destroy the room and I you know
Who's a rebel?
Yes, i'm aware who's going to rebuild it. All right, let's let's go. Are you already on your way there?
Hold on. I'm like in the sky and I found three
planets
three planets
I'm just gonna like
Make people live up here really fast
I didn't bring like a workbench or wood
Mining potion flip. Yeah, we don't have any um
Any wormhole potions anyways?
I gotta join your team
Uh, do you want that?
What sword the cool one?
Yeah
All right. I have that
Is there anything else that I should take out of here?
That we I mean actually want to have with us
No
Rope. Um
I think I deposited accidentally
uh, yeah, um
Rope
All right, the specimen is gonna live in the sky pyramid because fuck that guy spelunker
Night owl potion. Okay. All right. I think it's we got we got some daylight here. Let's go
Time start going time to go
That's enough for one day
We will come back another time
time to go
Are you following me?
I'll be there
All right. I'm going
Yeah, and i'm gonna make you a grappling hook
You're gonna make me a grappling hook
What a swell guy
What color would you like? How do I skip forward to when you guys are in the dungeon?
Uh, it's it's there's only one way. I'm really sorry. There's only one way that's possible
You have to
exit the stream
Take a bath
And take a nice long bath and by the time you get back the stream might not be live
So then you can
Load this back up get to this point exactly and then skip like 30 40 minutes ahead
That's really i'm that's the only way
If there was any other way, I maybe I can help you out here
It's not i'm sorry. I wish there was
Four days and I this is the fourth stream in a row four days in a row
I haven't done four days in a row in like at least a couple months
I don't usually do four days in a row. Congratulations. Hey, thank you
Wow
That's something
Throw bombs at the house before the stream's over. No, i'm not gonna like ruin his game
This is your game
You're the host as in this your like file dude. I have so many worlds that I wouldn't care
What no, no, no, no, no, no, but I might want to like play again, I don't
I don't want to just ruin the entire game. Yeah, just like you wanted to play edf again
We did play edf like seven or eight times. Yeah, and you said we would definitely play again
Yes, and then what happened was uh, you were going to sleep
You were going to sleep at like like 10 pm your time
Which is six what eight pm seven pm my time
You were on this schedule where you were waking up at like six o'clock in the morning
True all right true or false statement
Were you on a schedule where you were waking up at like five or six am during that time you were playing again?
Oh me and italics did we're false question me and italics did yes
Oh, yeah
Yes, we did me and italics played that game like at least four or five more times without you there. Sorry
Oh my god, you you wake it up at like five and go to bed at like seven
I don't believe you also you put the most useless shit in this fucking box
I
We're gonna need these 40 acorns
I told you that I didn't know what I needed to do
Because if okay, let's say I trashed those acorns
I don't know. There's like a rain hat
I don't know. What if there's probably like a scenario where you'd be like, hey, dude, uh, whatever the acorns
Acorns, I threw them away. What dude? Uh, we need to plant. Uh, I don't know. I just put everything
I don't know what I need to do
Fuck dude ice blocks worth the money. No
Okay
And don't put them in the chest
I I like got rid of the mushrooms from here before and now there's more mushrooms
I had some extras
There's a copper axe in here
the starting hammer
This guy's wild
I don't know
But you can't just put me on a bike
With no training wheels and I don't know how to ride the bike and then you go. All right, son
Come on up here to the top of
the biggest hill in the town
Uh dad, I don't I should I am I ready for this? Yeah
And then just let me go with no training wheels going straight down like 70 miles per hour. We're ready
I was not ready
There's an immediate cut after you let go and I i'm flying down screaming going like 75 miles per hour
Of me in a hospital bed
In like a full body cast
It's one of those one of those like comedy scenarios where i'm in like the full body cast and i'm like trying to drink soup
And it's like I can't drink the soup
He opens the chest and clicks deposit all
Oh, man
what
They're riding on you. How is it? Who knows? How would they? Oh, yeah, we're in a squad
This is literally a spongebob episode that happens to squidward. So it's so that's what i'm saying
All right, teleport to me so we can
That I did wait does that actually happen?
Does anyone have a clip of squidward eating the soup? No, that does happen
I need to see that clip. I forgot to buy musket balls again
And whose fault is that? He deposits everything in the chest you forgot every time
So let's try this one more time. What do you think?
RPG RPG
Wait, hold on just stay there. Just you just help progress. I need to watch this
That's a video I need to watch
Do you tell me am I gonna like die?
I have to watch this
Just like just protect me for just one second while I watch this i'm protecting you with all of my heart
Uh, you're so protective right now
That's not it doesn't suit
That's pretty that's close enough. All right. Thank you
All right, can we play the game lull?
All right, let's speedrun this
Okay, but I mean like a jeremy speedrun not a star speedrun
Okay, so like a normal person's pace
Oh
What's that horn that everybody uses them that funny meme horn
the one that goes
Defeated what I do
Not down there. I am hungry, dude
Like come on, dude
You're making me play like come on, dude
Hey you
Let's just be really really clear about this you invited me to play this you were like hey play terraria with me
I'm like, okay
And now you're like
No, I don't want to do this anymore. Well now i've streamed for eight hours
And i've streamed for more than
More than four days in a row
Have you really?
Yeah
Wasn't there like a string of star streams or you only streaming like once a week
Are you back to like star streams every day now?
I don't know. I feel like i've streamed for two weeks, but that's definitely not true
That's the right clip. Uh, I watched it after we beat the dungeon
I think it's been like 10 000 days actually. Did you throw your schedule away, too?
My stream schedule. Yeah
I haven't had one in a very long time
Yeah
I like it better
I have like an estimation of what I think i'm going to do when I think i'm gonna stream
But no one really knows
I don't even tell people that
So what you just like turn it you don't have like a way for people to know when you might stream
Because that's how I do it here
It's like oh I I might stream
Like no, that's not true. Like I have like a day to advance usually a couple days in a row
I have like I don't know command. I have to ask my chat. Do you guys know what i'm gonna stream?
Answer. Oh, I know
Do I you don't have your summons?
um, but did I
Deposit my I think I deposited my oh, here you go. Take this
The room was torn in half by what?
Oh, I forgot to give you the hook
Yeah
Take that equip it and I think it's default. The button is e
e
Okay. Yeah, so like if you jump the dot like attached to the spikes
But if you jump and attach the ceiling it resets your jump
That's uh, really great
I wish I had one of these
You do
And you said thank you
Okay, i'm gonna give this to you now because I made this mistake with ashley i'm giving you
wormhole potion
What potion wormhole potion?
When you die
Thanks
And I thanks for reminding me i'm going to take the night out potion
Did that do anything it really doesn't do much
Why would you make my
Did you if you drink more than one or two of these does it work better?
I don't think so
I love this weapon. Yeah, because it sounds like you when you talk
Uh, all right, I can I know I know we're getting to that point where you're like done streaming
Because
Because every other comment is like stupid. Yeah, I don't you I hate your voice. Yeah, you're ugly
Ow
Oh my god
Did you give me the potions?
I did also fun fact. You uh, you can pick x those spikes
I don't think you gave me the potion. I had 100. Yes, you did. Thank god. You are 100 accurate
Okay, go get my gold
I can tell you're done because of how bossy you're being right now. Well, that's a huge map
That's actually a medium map
I have returned. I'm just like follow references
Your summons your summons dear
I know I
Look, I just got back
Uh, did you forget to touch the bewitching table dear? I did not there are two
Are you sure?
All right, why are you destroying this?
Because your gold was over there and I didn't want to walk across spikes like you did
You got hit by you got hit twice too. All right
And perfect
Yeah, because you had more hp than I did
What's
Can they hit us to the ground?
Very cool to try and open this box. I'm not gonna touch that box
All right. We've made it to the point where we last were killed. No, we weren't we didn't
You're right. We went down. You're absolutely right
I've actually never been wrong on my stream before
I don't know if you know that
We said lol, how are they still in the dungeon and that person that no backseat gaming?
When was the last time that you were backseat gamed for real? Not just like oh
not real, um
Ashley showed me a funny picture the other day. I mean maybe it was this morning
Where someone like had police surrounding their house and they actually threw like tear gas in their room
What and the the screenshot of the chat was them all backseating what they should be doing
Like get milk. It'll make your eyes stop burning from the gas like i'll do this like
Every single comment was backseat
The presence of running around their house not even looking at the computer
So to answer your question, uh, when was the last time I was backseated every day all day
How how what else is there? What's the other option? I kind of need to respond to how how absolutely fucked up what you just said is
Yeah
No, it's pretty fucked
That's fucking horrible. Um
but
Every day you're backseated
Yeah, but like no i'm not talking about like you you should have pressed your alt in overwatch like faster
Like somebody was really like trying to teach you how to play a game
Because you already know how to play overwatch
A game that you like maybe didn't know
What like every day?
I mean, doesn't that make it worse for you saying you already know how to play overwatching
And
But that's that's not backseat gaming that's just like somebody being like
Mean about how bad you played
Are they one in the same? Not really
They think I did something wrong, but I didn't
Like like today when people were telling me that those the houses weren't working because I wasn't making doors
Is that backseating and then it was today?
Every day
There there was today's
One of see you just
You don't read your chat enough. It's going too fast. I know
All the time
I read my chat all the time
Why would you type out something he should do? You know, it's a waste of your time
By the time like he reads like two words like 16 jupiters would have gone by
Uh
I paid very much
One would say the reason why I have so much trouble sometimes in games is because I am
engaging with the chat
More than I saw you playing against the pig yesterday
Or instead of playing the game you were reading the chat talking about how a baseball player would never do that
Yes
I was there. You know what you were I didn't know you were there. I would have said what's up
Every time you've seen me in real life, you've actually spit on me like first interaction
Now you miss understanding that I I I do I do chewing tobacco
It's just you might you might do every time you walk up to me. I just might be getting I'd expect it's not
It's not i'm spitting like at you or anything
I just show up at a bad time
What was that stat? Uh you picked it up
treacherous
sphere
Someone's a treacherous spear
What?
57 melee damage on this
really nice
Good in my small escape of this game would I have knowledge of the last few hours like at this point?
The highest i'm seeing are like 30s
But also it's one of the awkward weapons. I don't want to use
What if it does that much damage? I don't give a shit
Remember that deleted germa or star video where they met in real life and germa punched him in the face
And we like we've gotten over that so that's why the video is that's why the video was deleted
Because we've like kind of gotten over that
There's a lot of enemies over here. I mean like too many for me to handle
I'm coming with my 57 godly mace
That sphere is amazing. Should I give it a try?
Whoa, it does it shoots the things that I shoot. Wait, what did you get? Oh
I got double like shooting stars now. Oh, is that your does that count? Hey chat does that count as a sentry?
That's pretty nice
That's amazing
Yeah, there's some equipment later where you'll be able to have like four of those out
I gotta put this in it. This is like
It's broken. I don't know what it's doing. It's doing it through the walls
Wow, you win the internet
Oh, I hate that
That's like the worst thing that's the worst thing ever i've got one too
Oh man, you win the internet. Oh
But you have one too
This is fun. I gotta see I told you you should have stayed for an extra like 10 minutes
Yeah, otherwise we wouldn't have gotten
The uber gear from the uber dungeon
Are we farming for anything in particular or are we just kind of sitting around?
um golden keys so that
We open one of these chests and get a shadow key
interesting
Is what I want
If you only need one shadow key to open every shadow chest after that and there's a whole bunch of them on the far left
side of the map
There's so much shit down here
Uh, there's a key right there
Where I got one is this one is this uh chest not open?
Uh, the chest is locked up. I feel it looks different
Now i've already opened this one's open already
midnight oil
Silver bar magic missile. I already have one of these
I I don't know where to take it. Maybe we don't take the other magic missile
Uh, my my inventory is so full. Mine's pretty full, too
I bet germa has read it open right now
No, I don't
Turn on screen capture right now. No, all right. Let's keep going. I think it's still good
Can you cast it real quick
I think we can only have one between us, which is doesn't make any sense. That's odd that they
Seems like a patch
Like this has been patched
How much further down are we going? This is really far down
jump with that thing
Ancient necro helmet. I didn't know those
Update my facebook page. I have not logged into that germa 95 facebook in probably five years
I don't use facebook. Did you just throw that sword away?
No
If you follow germa on facebook the cool thing about it is that you get to be one of the germs
Yeah, no, my favorite part is when I join star's congregation of smashing gents
My favorite part is when I clearly make the mistake of naming my group that and then you name yours something even worse after me
uh
What was yours the inhumane psychopath?
Fun fact fun fact. Yes fun fact years later. I determined how fucking terrible and awful of a name that is
That I I tried to delete it, but you can't delete groups
valve remember we talked about valve has like 2019 paint with the 2005 engine
You cannot delete a group
If you make a steam group do it right now and have a hundred people join
All of them have to leave before you delete it. It can't be deleted
That's why I support the epic steam store epic steams steam steams steams steam
All right, I don't want to die down here
Steam
Uh, did you open that chest?
This one over here is not open that I don't have anything in here. I I couldn't even see what isn't being attacked
That's some stupid staff. It's a it's a shitty stuff
Uh, but anyways
Yes, I realized
Yours was congregation of smashing gents and I was like, oh i'll have mine be the inhumane psychopath
I can't remember why it was
Someone started it and was not me. I think it might have been shivvy
Of just like having really stupid group names
It's like shivvy's club of awesome. I believe is what it is. If that is correct, I might be wrong, but it might be
I think it is someone else
No one has a group name though, I can tell you that i'm sorry, but I I think I was against the uh, the grain there
with my group name
Inhumane psychopaths, you're very proud of that
No, i'm just saying it wasn't like the smashing gents or the the cool group or the cool group of dudes
Okay
Good job
Good job. So I made another group
Because I was like, I don't like that group that groups
I don't like that name and I want to like make i'm gonna actually do stuff with this group
And I changed it to even worse
What do you think I changed it to?
I don't remember I went so
generic
Just safe name
Jerma's group. Yes
Really
I don't know. I I was I don't know. I I went from one extreme to the other
I don't think that steam group has a name. I think it's just jerma's group
Can we even cut through this place?
Uh, I don't think our pickaxes can do that yet
Oh, no, I can and then I
I haven't used that group and I can't remove it people like hey dude
You're like your steam group's like all fucked up and there's a bunch of like dumb shit
And it's like all kinds of like crazy like discussions that have to be removed. I wish I could
Steam does not allow me to delete these groups
And like having a steam group that can be posted on just means there's going to be like a whole bunch of people speaking
Russian and saying like weird shit all the time or just like virus links. Yeah virus links and like
Like
And then I was like, oh I have moderators a long time ago, by the way
This is at least five years ago four or five years ago
Maybe you should have moderators for that and then it would just be impossible to keep up with
Can we not break through these? I guess we can we can
We're almost at the bottom of it
I'm digging down
Let's go to hell, but let's earn it this time
Uh, oh, uh, yeah, don't let him in here
Keep digging. Hold on. I need to like protect us
Those shadow keys never found one
We have to earn our hell is what they're saying
Earn your hell
What is that?
Why is it is that helping us mine?
No
Oh god
Do you see that thing below us? Yeah, what about it? If we kill it the wall of flesh will summon. Let's do it
Let's no preparation wall of flesh right now. Why did you just drop that? What are you doing?
Why did you do that?
you just like
You just like dropped me out and I had like no health you better stay alive so I can teleport to you with the worm
Oh
Where did the uh, where'd the voodoo doll go? Also, this is not regular health stone. This is oh my god
Warn me. Oh my god, dude
Oh, it's because I have a dangerous sense potion
Oh
No
Are there any more of those in the inventory?
I don't I don't think so. How do I make one? How do you make them?
I don't I don't think so. Oh, I got it
I think this is where we call it. No, how do you make one?
I don't know
And we definitely don't have it because we've been deleting everything
And look, i'm not even there anymore. No
No, I wanted to see it. Oh
I didn't summon it
Oh now that we we earned it
I didn't I I guess I
I don't know why my brain just thought me teleporting over there was going to teleport me to a safe place and not just like
Where you are? I I didn't think of it either, but it was like the moment I was
Yeah
What about the cheat hole?
Cheat hole. Let's go. You can get spirit droplets right now
cheat hole
Uh, oh don't tell germa but
That you can craft the armor now that gives you two minions and the bonus is probably like a third
Shouldn't have told me
All right. So where should we be stopping?
Just right here what we were last time
Um, wait, what do you mean?
down the cheat hole
I think I think we should stop
Oh, you see because we are very close to you getting okay number one
It's a 38 damage ghost summon and then you can summon like a whole like ghost necromancer
Minion set
There's a whole like we could all go and do that
But if we do it now, then you're not going to play next week and we can make saturday terraria day
And you you want to keep saturday terraria night?
Terraria day day
Terraria day, okay
I'm gonna do it
Ow bill my wife is saying wall in all cap
No, no, no wall
Maybe ignore her ignore her
Das fridays terraria saturdays that's gonna have to change. What is going on over here?
This leaf shield thing. What is this?
Uh when enemies are near she does that
Oh, and it's like a hell for jen
Yeah, I I will play terraria again
Definitely interesting enough to do it again
You haven't even gotten a hard mode yet kid. I know
fucking kid
But yeah, um
That's it, right?
Yeah, now it's just the only thing left to do is talk political
Well, the only thing left to do is
Five and a half hours like five to six hours. That's that's good
This is a bonus stream for me it's a regular stream for you
Hold on. There's like get those stars
so how does
So if I take this character into my own terraria game, it's going to be just empty, right?
Yep, this is on your local drive, right?
If I open a new terraria game, just not multiplayer will I have to be a level zero?
Shitty you can join with that with this character again
But everything in that world will need to be done again like how we feed it
The skeleton gets to go into the dungeon like that hasn't happened in that world. You have to beat him again
If you want to continue playing
I can just like leave it open
Uh, no, I probably i'm just gonna i'm gonna like do some reading
I'm gonna mana crystal. So
My max metal if you can't use them. Yeah, then give me the ones you haven't used
I'm gonna do a little bit of reading so i'm more knowledgeable next time at least like by two percent
Okay
And do you do you actually want to do this again like on saturday like next saturday just do no
I was I was joking. Well, I don't know
Sometimes you say things and then you you you write like in discord after the streams of it
You write like you really think that i'm gonna play with you
That's definitely happened
And then I have to pretend like oh no something that something came up. I don't know what happened
All right. Well, i'll i'll just see you later
Have a well-deserved rest after eight hours stream
Thank you, honey
Oh my god, I hear more stars and you didn't give me the mana crystal that you didn't use I just threw out
Yes, I did
I just gave it to you
No, you did I threw it right down
I want more
I will see you guys. Um later
we'll do the
the end of the stream here, but
Goodbye star
Always a pleasure
We'll see you next time
for terraria
He's still on the call. I thought he's gonna do his thing that he does
No
I don't do anything
Where you just you're gone
I'm going are you actually gonna say goodbye to my stream for the first time in like four streams
Goodbye germa's stream. I hope that you had I hope you enjoyed the playthrough of terraria
And I hope you look forward to the continuing episodes that will result from it
I don't think
You have ever done that in at least the last like seven streams. You've always just kind of been gone somehow
There you go
I think you're wrong. I'm not
I think I left one time as a joke. No the last three or four times. It's been a joke
You and you've even turned your stream off
And like ceased all contact for the rest of the day
You dedicated i'll give you that
Uh lang says germa usually mutes me. Oh, okay
Thank you
You're not muted now, are you?
All right. Well, goodbye. I don't do I have to how many times do I have to do it? Are you satisfied?
One more we'll do it. I think goodbye germa and germa's chat. I hope you enjoyed this. We'll play again
Goodbye star and stars when I say things it's not a joke and i'm not sarcastic
Actually mean the thing
So I 100 mean it when I say what about hillary's emails?
I'm like just realizing right now that like that
That that joke that came up like four or five times would have been funny like three years ago
what we were on that for like
At least 10 minutes. All right, give me the spongebob soup thing
There's even a time stick
This is it i'm so ready for this you have no idea
I've never been more ready for something in my whole life
Why is it not showing?
How about some soup on your best day ever?
It's a little hot
Oh
I don't think soup is the best thing for him on his best day ever
How about some music on your best day ever?
Music isn't best either
But what is best is what we save for last the one surefire thing to make your best day ever
All right, that's enough. I'm gonna get in trouble. That's enough. What a cliffhanger. Just you go watch that episode if you want to see what happens
But i'll see you guys later
I will be back in a few days
I think we're gonna start next week
with
The gta casino
It came out. I kind of have to play that
How could I not do the gta online casino?
when
So this would be let's say saturday
Sunday monday, but we'll come back on wednesday. We'll do the same thing. We did this last week here
We'll do a like wednesday
I don't have a schedule but wednesday to saturday sounds like
Especially with this new terraria saturday thing
wednesday thursday friday saturday
Same thing we did this week saturday whisper dos. Well, we can't we have to change that up
Why am I gonna say hey star? No, we we're playing uh terraria on fridays now
Uh, it's it says he he invited me
You don't switch that around
You know, you don't go to somebody's house when they invite you to their house and then like change their decorations and move their furniture around
You if you do
Don't do that anymore
But i'll see you guys on wednesday
Thanks for watching
Terraria is actually pretty fun
It's uh, I get to experience this because I never really i've tried to open it up a couple times. I got it on ipad
weirdly enough
And maybe put like 30 minutes into it before I realized I needed to
Put a lot of time into it and I really didn't want to lie in bed
It's like five six seven straight hours
Playing it on ipad
So I was I don't really want to do this and then I never did it
I never really got into it. I didn't
Put the time that is necessary to get something out of it
I don't know. Maybe then maybe we'll see if anybody else wants to along the way jumped in and play it or something
You know, but we we're gonna do the bits
Shouldn't take us too long
Is the stream over? Yeah
I think that's a pretty good. I don't really have anything that i'd want to start
Five and a half hours in
I'd rather just uh start pressure on wednesday
Why can't I play good games?
Isn't terraria one of like the most critically acclaimed
Games like that that exists
What it is, right?
Uh, if you would ask somebody is terraria a good game, I would say probably eight or nine out of ten people would probably say yes
Isn't that as not a good what classifies a good game?
How many people buy it? How many people review it? How many?
I don't know
But let's go back
I'll see you guys on wednesday. Thanks for watching call to personality. Thanks for the two dollars fifty cents
I'm playing shadow run with friends. So i'll have to watch the vod wanted to send bits your way anyway
Enjoy the game with your buds build lots of
uh
Call me for you. Call me block
The calm what does that mean?
the houses
oh
Why why why is that?
That's just what you that's what you you just put people in like
the shoe box
I would just let them roam free
Hey halios. Thanks for 280. Happy birthday germa
You're a little a little off, but uh, thank you so much. Appreciate it. We had a lot of money come in earlier. We
grabbed them all but thank you to uh timmy and chunky baloney for your 50 dollar
Bit donations that came in a few hours ago
It's a lot of fucking money. Thank you
The continued generosity of some of you guys is mind-blowing
No one's under any obligation to pay this stream any money ever yet. Some people do a lot and
I just thank you. I wish there was more I could say
But let's uh do the credits
Throw them up there. Here they come. Here comes those quick
Use all the subs and resubs and get the subs that happened during the course of the stream
Thanks to all of you
as always
we have a few more bits to do but
Get it up there now. All right
Thank you to freudian weapon for the five dollars
Gosh darn it. Germa. You're really making me want to pick terraria back up
But on another note, do you plan on streaming mario maker 2 again? I've got a level in the works. That's sure to knock your socks off
Yeah, i'll do that next week
I'll try to do we'll do the gta casino
We'll do another sam and max episode. We'll do mario maker 2 again
And then I really want to start to
over the next
week or so
Try to get this dumb highlights magazine stream
rules and stuff started so
that'll
pretty
Pribbly
Uh come out shortly
So that's what you can expect the next week when I come back. I think i've had enough break from mario maker 2 to
Come back and lose my mind again
Uh, thank you to you. You follow up
You follow up for the five dollars
I say love the stranger, but you always make my day better but something needs to happen
About the
Trans slur arguments that happen almost every stream. It really hurts seeing such toxic debates spark from such a generous and fantastic streamer like you
Uh, love you lots jerma. Sorry about the chat misbehaving today
Yeah, honestly, I think it's
Everybody kind of just needs to relax
and there's really no reason
to
Get angry or upset about something like that
We're here
To just hang out and have a good time
We're just here to have fun. We're here to relax
It there really shouldn't be
like that kind of fighting like that in the chat and I I I don't really want to
Press too hard on this
But we're here for a very specific reason
i'm not here
to
really
Go over anything else besides us to
Forget the world around us
Enjoy a game and hang out together
Try to be nicer to each other
Now that doesn't mean well, everything has to be everything's positive everything has to be positive all day every day
Everything's positive positive positive
But being like nice to be nice to each other
We fuck around here a lot
We really do
but there's a difference between like fucking around and like being angry with each other and fucking hating each other
Now I don't think that's necessarily been
too far down there, but this stream is
a very very very
I don't really talk about
what I believe in
The things that I care about in politics, maybe the politics joke earlier, right?
But we like that and this is obviously politics and social issues. I don't really do that
If there's ever an avenue for us to really start to discuss those things then that's when it'll happen
But try to be like better to each other and nicer to each other
We don't have to have these big arguments like that in chat
and I try to
Because here's another part right once you start to I don't want to fan
The flames because you know, obviously putting it in sub only is easy to uh
To kind of oh, but let's just like cool it down for a little bit
Yeah, well, that's why I said that's why I separated
Stuff like politics from like social issues and like
You mentioned like human rights issues, right?
You can't like lump everything together
Because they're they're very different
And in the rules there are I have rules here
At the bottom of the stream
It does very clearly say
Don't talk about politics. Don't talk about any
bigot shit
No racist shit
I really feel like I don't have to say that
Just like just relax a little we don't have to do that here
I can't
Tell you
What to think?
I can't tell you what to believe. I can't tell you how to live your life
But
All I can tell you is at least try to respect the people around you
To a point where everybody that everybody deserves
Just for being a person in the first place
That's not the intention of these streams
I'm not a person of multi-billion dollar corporation. Jeremiah 985
Are we allowed to hate you?
Like I said, I can't change somebody's mind. I can't tell you
to like not
Be a certain way. I can want that to be the case
But we all gotta we all gotta exist here
just
Respect your peers here. There's no reason for it
That's not what we're doing here
anyways
I feel like i've made a pretty
Big statement here about I don't really talk. I don't really talk about this kind of stuff
ever really I mean ever
And there's a reason for it. I hopefully I could at least make that point somewhat clear
but
Regardless of any of this
Thank you with five dollars appreciate it. You underestimate how addicted he is to gambling
I'm not that addicted to gambling
It's fun. Sometimes in a fake video game. He moved to vegas
Yeah, but that there are casinos here. Guess what there are casinos in
In the new in new england, too
They just opened up one boston or yeah boston just brought in one of the biggest casinos
In new england, I couldn't have gambled there
You would know
Yeah, I would know because it was one of the biggest construction and
projects the state had ever seen
Wait, what do I live under a rock?
That was happening before I moved
Prove you're not addicted and don't play any gambling games for a year
Playing terraria is a gambling game
You kill monsters and hope they drop the thing that you want
Should I never play a loot based game ever again?
That's that's kind of gamble
You kill the same boss like 20 times to see if
You open the hearthstone packs to try to get the stuff in there to get the
This is the logic that ea used
Ea used the oh, yeah what he didn't use that logic. I'm good. I got it. It is loot box politics
It sadly is to an extent
tf2 is gambling
Hey easy now
Easy now
All right only a couple more we got
Nick just came in with 50 dollars
A few minutes ago. We were in the middle of talking about some things, but thank you nick for the
5,000 bits 50 bucks
That's a huge amount of money right at the very end
They said i'm quitting twitch. Just wanted to thank you from one of my favorite streamers of all time
Thank you for the 50 dollars
nick hopefully um
Quitting twitch the thing is
Let's say that if you know that that's for real
And sometimes you kind of have to unplug a little you know
Social media is great
Streaming stuff is great
I mean sometimes you gotta do something else, you know pull your brain out a little
I barely even I barely participate in social media
Look at my twitter. Look at my facebook
But regardless of your reasons nick. Thank you so much
um
Thank you with the 50 dollars
And uh, maybe uh, we'll see you again another time if not, then good luck with whatever uh, whatever you do
uh back in
Gave two dollars and fifty cents
I already posted this before on discord and on chat, but I made a germ a tier list tier list
Oh my god that you could do
Or not
Maybe at the very end. I would do one of these
Why would I?
Why would I do one of these?
Thank you for the 250 though
For audience thanks to the 250. I would uh not be against terraria saturdays
Neither would I
That's why i'm doing it
Yeah, just keep adding them. I'm gonna do like at least another four or five of those over the next like
Month and with that
Sorry, i'm just clicking over here with that. I will see you guys in a few days
We'll do the gta casino sam and max borrow maker and then terraria saturday
With stern, maybe some other people. I don't know
You should host critical. Uh, it's critical streaming right now. What's it doing? Why?
How am I not following
What is what is critical's name am I not following critical?
Oh, damn, okay. All right, right, right, right, right
I was thinking like wait, why isn't he's here?
All right. Yeah, we'll look we'll just we'll go say uh, hello to critical. It's been a very long time since we've said hello
Right talix talix tug is right there
I don't have to go far to write him. He's right there
Half of you go over there and half of you go here
Oh, but yeah, I can tell you something about tax me and italics are gonna play
um
I'm trying to get swap four
to work
So you might see an italics in uh in germa co-op stream
We were talking about it not like next week. Wait, that's something there's a lot to go into that
Because I think we have to set up a lan and it's gonna take a little bit
We were talking about it though. Oh friendship week. Yeah
All right, guys, uh, go just go say hello to okay. It's been a long time since we've said hello to critical
Queue it up
and stick on I
Was
Are you watching like a john cena video? I have no idea what he's doing
Uh queue it up
I will see you guys in a few days. Uh ferodian weapon. Thank you ferodian for the 250 last minute bits lul. Thank you
I will see you guys
Later. Goodbye. Take care. See you wednesday
Have a great night