What's up? What's up? What's up? What's up? Wow, German985 is playing my favorite game,
Watch Dogs Allegiance. Oh, I can't believe it's out now. It's only $59.99, $99.99, or $119. Why was
there? What's $119? I don't understand. Is this a $120 edition of this game? What do you get?
Hold on, I gotta move my mic. It's low from the auto stream. What do you get with a $120 edition?
A little figurine that's made out of plywood? What do you get? Tell me. Remember your $1080 is
not going to be powerful enough. No, it is. I'm good. I can turn the graphics down if I have to.
It's for skins? Oh, I'm going to be fine. $1080 is fine. Yeah, that's fine. We had 10 community subs
from Aggression Cow. Thank you, Aggression Cow, for the 10 community subs. $1080 Andy. That's me.
I just used the $1080. That's what I do. Make sure you're on DX11. Oh, I just opened the game.
Is that? I don't think I even have DX12. I think I'm going to be fine. So yeah, this is Watch Dogs
Legion. I know it's shocking. I know a lot of you guys are just choking on your grapes or whatever
you're eating right now. Yes, I'm playing a game that came out today. A new game that came out today.
Weird. That shit don't happen. Why am I playing this? Well, go over the German 985 checklist,
please. Okay. Punch people on sidewalk. That's a box that's checked. Drive a car. That's a box
that's checked. Open world. That's a box that's checked. And I can play as old people. That's a
bonus secret menu that you didn't even know about. That box is now checked. And I know, look, I'm
already going to give you my impression of this game. I haven't played it, but I feel like this
is just going to be when I used to play GTA 4 with the pedestrian mod that you could play as
any pedestrian. I feel like it's going to be the same game. I'm going in with an open mind though.
He's going through his daily checklist. It's just a shitty version of that. No, it's the GTA 4
pedestrian mod, but somebody modded in phones like hacking phones. And it looks beautiful on a GTX
1080, I'll tell you. That's a sponsor. It's not a sponsor. All right, let's just go. I'm going to
stall. I don't have to put a VR headset on. We can just go. There's also something interesting
this game has, which, why don't we take a look? This game has permadeath, and I'm assuming that
you can have a bunch of people that are playing in your group, and if they die, they're dead forever.
I'm going to put, why not? My justification of playing on normal is to have permadeath on.
I'm not playing on hard. No, we're playing normal with permadeath. That's your, that's the
compromise here. Please play the game, Mr. Streamer Man. I am. Are you ready? Are you guys ready for
Watch Dogs Legion? It's gonna be a 10 minute stream. Why, you think I'm gonna not like the
game that much? Why do I look like, I sound like, I look loud. Am I, am I really loud?
I look very loud. No? I look loud. All right, let's go. Do you want to start the game with
these settings? Permadeath is on. Permadeath mode can be turned off in the options. Yeah, I'm good.
Let's go. Hacking computers. Files. I'm checking, I'm checking on it. I'm checking on it. Yeah,
just give me a minute. I'm checking on it. Yeah, what these people don't know is it takes like
three months to hack into like some bank account. Oh, you want to get into bank account? Yeah,
let me check on that right now. I got it. Pre-recorded hacking sequences.
All that music, art and multiculturalism and the world's oldest underground, the tube,
the class of cities really top shelf stuff. Raving rabbits. To tear it all down.
Wait, did it say it was 12, London's 12,000 years old? How is that possible when the earth is only
like 3000 years old? What, what are you talking, what do you mean? A light bulb just went like
and broke in my head. Wait, what? Ow. Thoughts. Ow. Critical thinking hurts.
Is that me? Oh, cool. All right. Ubisoft presents not raving rabbits. Resident sleeper. I'm in.
I'm in. I told you. I'm in. Me too.
That's rich, Bagley. The government would sooner arrest us for trying to help,
but actually do something useful. This one on our own. Carefully, Dalton.
Actually, are you detecting a little worry in Sabine's voice? Brilliant. Asking the
computer about feelings. This explains so much. Shut it, you two, and get to work. There she is.
This game is going to suck. Well, you can't say that yet. We haven't even walked around.
Let's check that 1080. Okay. Hey, guys, 1080 seems to be holding up pretty well.
C to crouch. Okay. Press F near an unaware enemy to perform a takedown. If I hit Q,
I vibrate his phone and I can punch him right in the fucking face. Nice. That'll definitely
hurt your hand. Your hand probably broke in four places. I hate that bullshit. It's so stupid. If
you punch somebody in the face, your hand breaks. Why doesn't it cut to this guy in a fucking
hospital bed for a week? Investigate the threat to parliament. That's a weak hand.
If they don't shoot me, I won't shoot them. How's that? Weak bones? All right. Operation
Westminster. Okay, that's vault. Is there a hitman thing where I can see through walls?
Isn't it permadeath on? If I die with the main characters, does the game just end?
Detective vision. Wait, sneak. Hold on a locked door to reveal the link to the closed circuit
terminal to unlock the door. All right, be careful. There's people over here. Okay. Oh,
just like in Half-Life. Hijack. Use to hijack camera and scout the area. Hijack. Nice. Cool.
Press Q when aiming at an explosive device to use the arm trap hack. Okay, that's been armed. What
is it? Wait, no. Arm this one. Wait, what? It didn't say explode. It just said arm. It's really
cool to see that they still think this mechanic is cool like eight years later. Okay, let's go.
Wait, no, don't walk over there. This is going to explode if I go over there. It's permadeath. I
can't die. All right, sneak. Wait, arm trap. Now when he walks into that, he's going to explode.
Is he? Why is all this stuff so dangerous? Why? Why is every single thing we have
surrounding us able to explode? Wait, wait, wait. There's two people here. All right, arm this.
Watch. Hey, guys, watch this. I'm a hacker. I'm going to make the soda machine explode when the
guy walks towards it. Am I not? I mean, what are you doing? Deadsec as fuck. All right, turn off the
power. We've got loads of Deadsec gear down here. And why don't you suppose that is?
What? How did they get their hands on it? I don't know. Oh, hack. Or someone wants to make it look
like Deadsec was here. Shit. What happened? Oh. All right, they think. Oh, I got, by the way,
one really important thing about this story. I don't care. I never did care. I don't give a shit
about anything they're talking about. I played an hour of Watch Dogs 1 and like two hours of
Watch Dogs 2. I don't care about anything they're saying. I have no idea what's happening.
Is that bad that I just played for like three hours total? Is that bad? Does it matter? Oh,
wait. It's OK. I'll get a TLDR. What happens? I only played Watch Dogs enough to like drive
over somebody on the sidewalk, hack a traffic light and have a car crash happen. And then I went,
yeah, I stopped playing. Distract. Wait, where's there a fuck me? The entire place is rigged to
blow. It is? It covered near a wall. I got one right here. AI doesn't swear.
Why would you program AI to swear? All right, we got to reach the House of Commons. I'm just
going to walk around. Oh, fuck. What do I do? I got to distract this guy. All right. Distract.
What? I don't have enough power to hack. OK, I have enough power to go into a webcam and look
at somebody, but not enough to like hack their phone. All right, I get it. Let's just walk.
You're out of hacking mana. The AI is probably stupid. It's stupid. Look.
Look. I'm good. This guy's chasing you like a baton. Unavailable under pursuit? What? I'm
good. I'm just hiding in the trash. They can't see me. Unavailable. Where's my? All right, so go.
Move on. Yeah, I know. The 100 foot radius in a circle around you is clear. You might
want to check somewhere else. Oh, no, I know what they're doing. They will. Oh, OK. No, I'm good.
It's all right. I just screamed. They were just pretending to check and going over the microphone
over the radio like tell the supervisor like, yeah, it was just make believe. Oh, what do I do?
Looks I'm going to have to hack into this. Oh, come on. What about hacking? Why can I hack the
door? This guy dies in the House of Commons in like five minutes. Whoever these men in black
are, they've got blast bollocks to set up in the center of government. I get it. I know. I know.
I'm going to die in like two minutes. And that's what it's like. Oh, you think this is the main
character would have been like kind of a cool reveal if they just didn't spend the last like
full year talking about how cool it was to play as every character in the world.
All right. Reach the detonator. All right. Well, that was unnecessary, but it's OK.
This is a minigame. What do I have to do? Oh, it's a cut scene. And it's definitely live.
Bagley, I'm going to need some help with this. Yes, you are. But sadly, I'm locked out.
Well, we don't have a chance. Bagley. Wait, wait. His name is Bagley. You're full of surprises.
Be quick about it. Not like in portal. I mean, oh, yeah, me too. Bombs have just armed themselves.
Well, that may complicate matters. All right. Hey, those of you that are playing
the drinking game, that's three times vaporizing. So fair warning. Expect this to draw some attention
your way, Dalton. Oh, I'm cancer. Company at our back door. Dalton, we've got some heat here.
Emma, why? What? How long is this going to take Bagley? Depends how often you interrupt me with
questions. All right, everyone faces on guns out faces on. Oh, I can't wait to put I'm going to
pick my favorite mask. All right. I can pick a mask. No, no, no. You're not supposed to save me.
You're supposed to save her. They're on me. I'll try and hold them off.
Okay. Survive the ambush. Oh, shit. Oh, sorry. I didn't do it. Am I supposed to kill these guys?
Okay. So I have to what do I do? Okay. Um, it's still on. This is slow mo effect.
Well, this is a really long slow mo. Turn off the computer. I have to do this. This sucks. Why? What
the hell happened? Press Control Alt Delete. Oh, I'm it. I'm it. Oh, I got booted. I got booted.
I can't believe I have to control. I have to put hard reset this. Watch Dogs Legion end task.
Give me a fucking break. Where's that going to pop up? Where's that? What's that going to do?
Watch Dogs Legion. All right, let's go. That better be an auto save right there.
This is so stupid. Oh, well. Now I can't even open the game. Is it opening? Hello? It says the
game is running. I ended the task. You just got bogged. What is going on? Open. 10 minute stream.
No, no, it's opening. It's just taking a wicked long time. I have all the new driver. I need a
computer. I can't like pretend to play these new AAA games. All right. It only took two minutes
to open. This is what it felt like when you used to have a regular HDD and you turn on windows and
it would take like seven minutes before you got to your desktop. Fuck. I need a new computer.
All right. Here we go. Big bits. Oh shit. There are big bits. All right. This is from tapeworm
corn dog. Holy shit. That's disgusting. Thanks for the that's a hundred bucks. 10,000 bits from
tapeworm corn dog. And they say, thanks for fucking showing everybody my cool username.
Actually, that's not even my username. My username is Royale coming my way. I don't know.
Anyways, they say, hi Jerma. Love you and chat. Been watching for like eight years and today's
my 19th birthday. Happy fucking birthday. Wanted to give it a little back and say thanks for being
the master of comedy. I won't be here for long because I exclusively watch VODs. All right. Also,
can we get some Jerma disgusts for my username? Yeah, I gave you a huge one. Oh fuck. I completely
blew my cover here. I turned it on for a minute to make sure that the 1080 could handle it.
Here we are. No, seriously, tapeworm. That's a ton of money. Thanks for the fucking hundred bucks.
It still couldn't handle it. I swear to God, if it crashes again, I'm going to be very upset.
But the game didn't even crash. We still get an audio. Oh, lower this. All right. I'm going to
lower the settings. That's not a bad idea. Lower the graphics settings. Oh, great. And I get to be
the last person that loads up in League. Everyone has to sit there and fucking watch. Like, holy shit.
Oh my God. Don't even fucking tell me. What a town. History around every corner. God damn it. All
right. Hold on. Turn the graphics down. Video. All right. Yeah. FPS limit. Field of view. I can't
turn that up. Quality. All right. Graphics quality. High. Geometry. High. Environment. High. Texture
medium. Filtering. You can't even tell a difference. OK. Look it. This is like going
to the eye doctor and you have no idea which one looks better. It doesn't even matter.
Low. Shadows. OK. These actually look better. No, they don't. Those look terrible. It looks like
there's a giant spiderweb over New York. Oh, London. Wherever we are. Headlight shadow. Reflections.
But somebody point out the difference. Turn them off. Who cares? Motion blur. Get out of here.
Depth of field. Get out of here. Ambient occlusion. Nobody wants that. Everyone turns it
off. That's the first thing everybody does when they open up any video game. They turn this off.
Uh, subsurface scattering. I feel like this is just a made up word that they can just have
a toggle here. What is it doing? It's scattering the subsurface? It looks all right. I guess it
looks OK. Ray Tracer. I don't have that. I can't do that. Temporal upscaling. All right. I'm good.
Let's go. Dude. Oh, you know, playing a game at launch. Launch bugs. Launch like problems.
It's OK. Whatever, man. This is what happens. Playing at launch. By the way, it is refreshing.
It's just taking a while. Veto it. No, I can't. Are we serious? No, not yet. Go play 3DS. I'm not
playing 3DS. I have to play one AAA game a year. I'm allowed to. OK, here we go. I'm in. Veto.
I'm not vetoing. Let's go. We're here. I have. I've lowered the graphics. I'm ready. I'm just
going to speed run this part. I'm running. I'm just going to run through this part because I
don't care. You're not vetoing. We are. Yeah, but don't you understand? I have like I have the
voting power of like a million of you. I just say we're going and that's what we do. That's a
dictator. I mean, aren't all streams like dictatorships? No, yes. You're a tyrant.
OK, here we go. Welcome to Watch Dogs. I'm your host, Jerma. And thank you. And thank you to
Ubisoft for making such a cool game. And thank you. Big thanks. Thank you. No, no, this is not
sponsored. I just said thank you for making a cool game. Go. All right, I'm in. I'm in. I'm in. I'm
in. Let's go. For real, I'm in. It's time to move. Go. Speed run. I'm not stopping for anything.
Wait, why did I just Medusa that guy? What happened? If they don't shoot me, I won't shoot them.
How's that? I just think spit in that guy's face. Let's go. Oh, look, I don't know. What do I do?
That hurt you more than it hurt me. I feel like I just had a football in my hand.
What the fuck was that Metal Gear Solid bullshit? Good. Turn it on. I've got loads of dead set gear
down here. I don't care. Leave me alone. Who are these men in black anyway? Nothing identifying.
I suspect that's by design. Disrupt. All right, we're good. We're on pace. Okay.
The entire place is rigged to blow.
RDX nitrogen. Enough to level parliament. Analyze. Wait, I didn't do this last time. Let me do this
first. But there's a device streaming a fuck load of encrypted data from the floor above you.
Fuck. Yeah, that fits the bill on my way. Is that not the detonator? No, but it's a transmitter
sending a signal to a device on the floor above us. Safe to assume that would be the detonator
we're looking for. Stage dead set propaganda all around the bombs. This is not how you're
supposed to play. This is going to blow up parliament and hang it on us. Not if you get
to that detonator first. Did you see me? What? No, don't him. Okay, we're good. I did it. It only took
me three seconds. He should have tried to open it, picked up his phone, held it over to it,
and it didn't work. And he should have looked right at the camera and gone like, oh, man.
Yep. Okay, here we go. Save the game. I can't. It's just it's permanently auto saving. All right,
I'm going to arm a trap. Let's make sure this doesn't hurt us. Arm trap. Interact. Here we go.
It's time to shoot. Headshot. Don't. I'm not going to shoot the guy the same way. All right,
here we go. Ready? All right, your way out. Let's go. Why is the guy screaming?
We're good. Three. That's three. Three. Oh, X. Oh, you can. Look at this. 53%. Flashbang.
Flashbang. How do I throw it? Oh, I think it's a recharge.
Why do I feel like I'm playing Left 4 Dead right now? This is payday. Get on. Get on? What?
No crash. We're good. Deactivate. Sick.
On the left, one of them is the receiver. You need to pull the controller wire.
Are you fucking kidding me? No, I'm fucking not. No fucking. Fuck. Which one is this? Fuck. Now,
don't. Dalton, don't. Fuck. Don't pull that one. Oh, fuck.
See, that wasn't so bad, was it? Why'd they all mask up? They didn't even go anywhere.
What was that for? Everybody mask up. We're just gonna stay here. Well, what the fuck am I looking
at?
Should I go get a bomb?
Oh, they knew where our hideout was. It was a mall.
Fuck. It was a mall. It was probably me. To the roof. Wait, pick up ammo?
We're being raided? Oh, well, Sabine, sing the raid song.
I need him for the transmit. Let's press V to scan the area and reveal cameras to hack.
Okay, I'll do it the old-fashioned way. Wipe him. Yes, wipe me. Do it, Sabine,
and get the hell out of there. Okay. Fuck. Hack. Download that. Whatever it is.
Okay. Hack, he's down. You're on your own. Hack, whatever this is, too. What is this?
What are we doing? I promise. Okay. Am I in somebody's iPad? Or did I get it?
I got the code, right? Yeah, I downloaded the code. Hey, hey! What happened? I didn't do
anything. No, no, no. Get down. All right, you stun him and then you shoot him in the head.
Why is that person... That person's like super... What was it? Marshall in World of Warcraft
battleground arena thing? I tried. I forgot what it was. I'm sorry.
Why can I not shoot him? Why is that guy so special?
Why was that guy special? E, toxicity for encroaching 500 percent. Where are you?
Come on. Defuse. What are all these bombs look like underneath your sink?
Have you ever noticed that? Like plumbing in there. There's not even wires. Who is it?
What the fuck are you? Oh, you still think you're here to save London?
I'm afraid that's not going to happen. You're here to help us with some important work.
Important work? Fire! Oh, drones!
Exactly. To save the world. You do know Londoners have died before. The plague,
the great fire, the blitz. There's not much fun. But destruction is always the cure.
And it begins today. Zero day. Did anybody else see this? Did anybody else see this big
projection of Obi-Wan talking? This is like the Emperor. This is like a 10 million decibel
megawatt speaker. It's time for a hard reset. Oh my god. No! Told you he was dead.
A series of explosions devastated three sites in London. Authorities are asking residents to remain
in their homes as the situation continues to develop. I loved that character. I loved that
character. Warners gathered for a series of candle-like vigils that brought closure to
thousands of families and indeed to an entire city. You didn't have a chance.
London is now laser focused. They attend Downing Street where Nigel Cass, CEO of
private military company Albion, received a mandate to secure London. Cass has vowed to
hunt down DedSec. I don't know what's going on. I probably should have played the first two games.
That's not like John Oliver? Oh wait. No, it wouldn't be John Oliver. He didn't go,
I don't think I say that Mr Turfill. I don't want you to do it and I don't think that you're very smart.
So where do we come in here?
What is DedSec bad or is DedSec good?
Willing to expound those theories on camera. Hey attention, were you a follower?
I'm falling for fake news. Wait, but the TV told me that DedSec was not very good.
Oh shit, the fake news is working on me. Who am I? Am I the spider?
Waters and we've been discussing the hacktivist now alleged terrorist group DedSec on this week's
Buccaneer radio. I have Colin calling in. Colin what's your take? Now I'll be the same to start.
We should have round up DedSec and thrown them in jail. Now I say they should all be locked up.
Find it awfully convenient that they've been fingered as the attackers but we've seen no proof.
Say the line. I'd say you have to look at their history of non-violent action.
I thought they just said up there, blame the data center.
The hospital in the past few months and DedSec ever has. I smell a scapegoat.
Now what do we do? How do I shoot lasers?
You're absolutely right Claire. The government's just framing DedSec because they want to make
it seem like they have no clue who was behind the bombings. Put that on their side.
Who better to depend on? Angie, I have you next. What do you make of all this?
I like swallow the last word.
I couldn't even go into the, because I was swallowing.
Do you feel safe for using a pseudonym? Everyone should. Why make it easier for them to track you?
And now we've seen what they're capable of.
What am I doing?
Hold on. Do you mean the government? Are you suggesting the government was responsible for
the bombings?
Fuck. How is it doing that? Why is it just doing that? It's crashed again. Why is it crashing?
No, I haven't even been able to get into, I need to get into a car first.
You don't veto an open world car game without driving the car first.
What if I take down a little bit more graphic quality? Put it on medium.
You drove the car. That's not a car. That was an animal.
Did you update your drivers? I did like a week ago.
What is there like a Watch Dogs Legion launch drivers?
That better not be. Man, that always is.
That better not be. I have a 1080. They don't even make drivers for me anymore.
They don't care about me. They don't want to make drivers for me
because they don't want me to have a, they want me to get the new one.
All right. If it crashes again, I'm going to update my drivers.
What does it say? The crashes that some players are experiencing are due to Windows problems?
It's caused by outdated Windows.
What? What would that have to fucking do with anything?
Dude, is he still alive in this playthrough? He better not be.
Windows user detected. Hold on.
You see it? If I swear to God off this guy, play a silly game.
What is silly game? What does that even mean? Silly game.
This is a silly game.
Crashes are due to outdated. Guys, I did a full fresh install of Windows 10
like two weeks ago, three weeks ago.
This is all brand new operating system as of like two weeks ago.
All fresh, complete updates.
I need to assemble a team, but I can't reboot DedSec alone.
What's going on? Let me break into London CTOS and see
who's available. Did I skip a whole thing?
Oh, okay. Go, go, go, go, go. All right. Get in there.
Alleged terrorist group, DedSec on this week's Buccaneer Radio.
What's your take? We've been saying from the start
we should have ran up DedSec and thrown him in jail.
What were your graphic settings again? You don't find it awfully convenient.
I don't even want to listen to that. I already know.
I can't even, I can't hit escape. We have to do this first.
Say the line. What would it be doing?
Outdated Windows. Why do I feel like that's like weird corporate speak
for holy shit, let's get a day two patch out.
All right, Windows may be outdated, I think.
Check to see if your monitor is plugged in.
Get the patch, get the fucking patch ready by tomorrow, motherfucker.
Check to see if your cable, if you plugged in your cable recently,
like your power cable.
Access the CTOS data clusters. Reinstall Windows again.
What's the graphics card recommended graphics card for this?
It's probably like a 780, 1070. All right, sick. Hack it.
I hacked. I don't know.
Is this a Green Goblin's Tower? What did I just do?
Searching for contacts.
Shit, situation is worse than I thought.
Are they all dead?
There's a candidate. Looks like your dead sex best hope.
Select your first operative.
6G data plan, fast downloads. Wait, hold on.
Animator has a crowbar. Wrench, heavy, melee weapon.
Really fast downloads. I think I like Lindsay Cullen.
Runs hacker forum on the dark web.
Yeah, so he runs a hacker forum on the dark web.
Therefore, he wears a bright purple LED vest and glasses that have emotes on them.
Nancy recently purchased a $200,000 sports car.
Personal sports vehicle. Oh shit, that's kind of cool.
Motorcycle. Okay, but I feel like everybody clicked this because it said internet celebrity.
Nancy Drew. Hold on. Wait, wait, wait. We're not done.
It's podcaster. Ugh.
Grates fake coupons. Dancer.
That's okay. Oh wait, hold on.
What about the old guy that used to sell snake oil back in like the 1800s?
Has a private phone line to the police commissioner.
What? Wrote five star review of the Earl's Fortune Pub.
That's not really that big. That's not like a big thing.
That's not a big deal.
Has private phone line to the police commissioner.
Wrote a Yelp review once.
Why would you... I don't want... What?
Board game designer. I thought it was like he gets a free VR.
SV? Oh shit!
Salary. All right.
I mean, I think it's going to be Nancy. Nancy, the sports car.
Wait, we didn't see the end.
Oh, this guy's a smuggler.
No. No. I'm Nancy.
Nancy Schramm. She's got an awesome car.
All right, Nancy, let's go.
Welcome to the Resi... Resistance. Residence.
Nancy Schramm will be the first member of your DedSec team.
Continue growing your team by recruiting new members.
I was just...
Okay, this guy's a Satanist.
I'm not a Satanist.
What's with this little blue sedan? Where's my sports car?
The game is fucking loud.
Okay, here we go.
Hold on. This game is loud as shit.
Turn it down. There we go.
Okay, locate the safe house entrance.
Press... What the hell is that?
What is that button? What is this way, that way?
What is this way, that way? What button is that?
Tab? It's a waypoint.
Okay, what a waypoint.
Okay, let's go. Locate the safe house.
All right, that's a handbrake.
Brake, drive, toggle music, change music, auto drive.
Wait, there's an auto drive?
This looks like shit.
This looks like Nintendo 64.
Why does it look like Nintendo 64?
Is this the wrong way? It don't matter.
There's no... There's no police in this game, is there?
Don't move!
Watch dogs.
They don't even care? No, apparently not.
Where's this GPS taking me?
Where is this GPS taking me?
What is happening?
I'm supposed to follow the blue arrow, right?
Wrong side of the road.
Oh, that's right. We're in...
We're not in America.
Well, that's going to be horrible.
Hack this guy.
I can... Wait, I can drive his car?
Wait. Oh, that's too bad.
All right, let's go.
Oh, I found it. It's right here.
I don't have a high enough hacker level?
Oh, that's not cool.
All right, get out here.
All right, I made it.
Oh, you blood don'ts.
Manual override.
Okay, access point.
Use to rotate the nodes.
Complete the circuit to solve the puzzle.
Rotate the...
What is going on in 2020
with these fucking rotate puzzles?
This is very, very, very, very, very much
the exact same thing that we did in Alex.
Okay, you're going to have to manual override it
to the painting.
All right, that's unlocked.
That's unlocked. That's good.
Now I have to go like this.
Unlock this one.
Open that fucking door.
Radiator. Open the radiator?
Oh, this is our secret hideout.
Oh, we're up the safe house.
Right, because I'm the only operative ever
that exists.
It's just me.
All right, let's boot it back up.
You drove the car.
Now you can stop playing.
Stop.
My name is Nancy Schwab.
I'm with Sabine.
Who the hell do you think you are?
Who says that?
What cartoon character says that?
What power that you could possibly imagine?
Oh, what's this?
That's how you make a 100-hour game, by the way.
Not me.
I'll be done in about 12 hours.
Probably less than that.
All right, I activated Bagley's servers.
What about the mask?
Oh, there's a mask.
Wait, loot?
Wait, can I drop loot?
Doesn't Ubisoft do stuff like that?
Can I drop a box on the stream?
Can I do that?
All right, let's contact Sabine.
Mask.
Oh, I got a pig mask.
Where's my, do I have an inventory?
Where's inventory?
It's Saw.
Make some pig noises for that mask.
Okay, this is for you.
I don't even know who said that, but sure.
Is your memory intact?
Not even slightly.
The last record I have is of our HQ being raided.
My only lead is a group known as Zero Day.
Ring any bells?
Don't blame me.
Blame the person that told me to do that.
That was pretty good, though, wasn't it?
Just one chance.
They just gunned everyone down.
My god.
How'd you survive?
I managed to escape through the sewers to Camden.
That's pretty good.
What's wrong with it?
A contact snuck up with me out of the city,
and I've been hiding out in the north since.
Prudent.
Your profile is read flagged as a high-priority target
in the city's surveillance system.
Even a partial recognition here would have you
hunted down and shot on sight.
There aren't many DedSec fans in London these days.
Look, I want to help.
I do.
But joining up with you now verges on suicidal.
Listen, if anyone knows anything about risks, it's me.
I lost everything and everyone.
But it comes down to this.
London is in a death spiral.
And if DedSec can't pull it out,
trust me, no one can.
Actually moving so much?
City needs a resistance.
Yeah, I mean, it is kind of like a puppeteer.
It's like moving the head around every word
to make sure you over-enunciate everything.
Fine.
That's how puppeteers do it.
Excellent.
New user registered.
Welcome to DedSec.
I'm not going to skip this.
Guys, I'm allowed to play one, like,
six out of ten AAA release a year, okay?
Now, it would be irresponsible of us to release you
naked and mewling into the wild.
You'll find equipment around the safe house
that are essential items in your DedSec kit.
Pick a better one.
I just came out fucking two hours ago.
It just released.
I don't know.
Tech points can be found throughout London
using the purchase tech upgrades.
Gadgets and weapons.
Cool.
Equipping tech to change an operative's weapon
or gadget use the edit function in the team menu.
Nice.
Spend tech points.
Ooh, tech points.
What's this?
I got ten tech points.
Chase drones can be hijacked.
AR camouflage to render that we're invisible
and break line of sight.
Cool.
This is an LTL-68P DedSec pistol.
These look like Team Fortress weapons.
Ooh, infiltrator spider bot.
A stealth-based spider bot
capable of performing non-lethal takedowns.
Chat.
Should we get that one, chat?
Yeah, sure.
All right, data.
Cool.
All right.
Edit operative.
All right, you have a pistol.
That works.
You've got a nice car.
And we're going to give you the spider robot.
Where is this?
The ultimate sports car.
Speedy and sleek.
It will never be mistaken for another car.
Oh, I can change the paint job.
Is this an Ubisoft box?
This is not an Ubisoft box, right?
Really?
I can only buy gray and black.
I can't do like blue.
Whatever.
It's in-game.
Oh, okay.
A sophisticated system for hiding your identity from facial recognition tech.
It's called a mask.
Hold on a second.
Hold on.
Hold on a minute.
Everyone relax.
Yes, everybody relax.
All right, we don't have to shut the computer off.
We're here.
Perhaps we can talk about updating your wardrobe.
I mean, literally.
All right, nice.
Come on.
Buy a new PC, you fucker.
Look, all the new shit came out.
Like the 3090s.
The new AMD risen shit.
I got to get those.
What, you want me to buy?
If I'm going to buy like a new computer,
I want to buy like old hardware.
I want to get the new shit.
It's got to be available.
No, this is too many ubi bucks.
Facewear.
Okay.
This one's fine.
Okay, hat.
Okay, just turn into a completely different person.
All right, I want this one.
Sure, I'll take it.
Glasses.
Bag.
This is GTA 4 graphics.
It does kind of look like GTA 4.
It really does look like GTA 4.
Oh, why?
This 1080 is not even that bad.
Every setting on low.
No, I don't have...
The 1080 is not even a bad graphics card.
It's not even like four years old.
Okay, I just...
I think I just killed that person.
What happened?
Guard break.
Yes, nice one.
Oh my god.
Put on gloves or something, guys.
Use like fucking rock-em-boppers,
whatever it's called, sock-em-boppers.
Holy shit.
Why are you hitting each other for real?
The face.
Just the hay bakers.
Oh my god.
Throw punch.
Guard break.
Finisher.
Now, thanks for the training.
This person is really hurt.
That's where you're going to take the commercial break?
Okay, let's leave the safe house.
Right, gear in order.
No enough not to punch yourself in the face.
I've got a pistol.
Brilliant.
I'm working at mine zero day and ruin their day,
but I need someone with actual legs to do the leg work.
The 1080 came out in 2016.
It's not even that long ago.
If we want to change the perception
that we're a bunch of violent thugs,
let you be the judge of how best to handle yourself.
But remember, you represent Deadset now.
Yes, it is four years old.
It's not old.
Like if your work's just fine.
Start recruitment.
All right, Sabine, what's our plan?
Wait, I recruit this drunk guy?
Why can I only recruit this guy?
And all our cowering just makes it easier to step on.
Only old people.
I just want to look.
I just want to see.
You look like the sort who might want to take back their city.
Are you Deadset?
If you are, I need help with something.
If I was, I certainly wouldn't say so.
Now, what's the situation?
These Kelly maggots.
Zoomer haircut.
They burned down my cousin's dry cleaning shop
because he said no to pain protection.
How dreadful.
I know who it was that set the fire.
But the cops...
You're wearing a Dedsec hat.
The police won't help you, darling.
But we will.
Yeah, I am.
Rest assured, these gangsters will be put away.
That's not very sneaky.
All right, so we got a new recruit member.
All right.
Dedsec, chapter started.
Squad goals.
Potential recruit right here.
Is he still a recruit?
Okay, he's still...
We're just having a little bit of fun, I guess.
Injured and hospitalized by operative Nancy Schramm.
Well, who cares about that guy anyway?
He's dead.
What about you?
You want to join us?
You look like someone who might want to fight for London.
You look like somebody that was AI-generated.
Oh, I like this guy way better.
He's a crypto guy.
I don't know why.
I thought he was holding a grenade for a second.
I was like, this guy's fucking crazy.
Okay.
Recruit Justin Johansson.
Let's do it.
So let's go.
What do I have to do?
Okay.
Justin Johansson is sympathetic to Dedsec and might be willing to join up.
Talk to them to learn more.
Shoot him.
I'm not going to shoot that guy.
Why am I?
What is it?
What is this weird helmet?
Where's my car?
There's nobody even in this car.
Why was this car just sitting here?
What?
I need a waypoint.
It's like 100 million years away.
All right.
Let's move.
I want that.
But no, it's like a piece of delivery thing.
I don't want that.
GTA 3.
It's not very good.
It isn't.
But it's okay.
Yep.
It's so ugly.
It's okay.
Wait.
Recruit.
Okay.
So I have this watchdog stream.
Anybody else's watchdog stream look like shit?
Is this like a game thing or is this a computer thing?
It's both.
Oops.
An invisible man was just in the road
and just grabbed me by the back of my collar.
Who is?
This person is doing graffiti.
Bye.
What the fuck are you doing?
Why would you do that?
What were you thinking?
What are you doing?
What a fucking idiot.
Hack the world.
Okay.
Let's go.
I caved in that lady's chest.
Okay.
I need to take a second.
Holy shit.
People just walk in front of your car.
Oh, this is a play ball.
Hit the inputs in time to hit the ball.
What is this?
According to an official post on Ubisoft 4,
a watchdog's legion bug was detected
which would cause performance issues on the game.
While releasing the hotfix,
the developer wrote in the post,
we're developing a hotfix to address the performance issues
we're seeing on PS4, Xbox, and PC.
The hotfix has been deployed on PS4 and Xbox.
PC gamers are left away today as the dev...
Yeah.
Okay.
Hit the inputs in time...
My whole body hurts.
Hold on.
Ahem.
Hit the inputs in time to hit the ball.
Okay.
Get a number of perfect hits to do tricks.
Let's go.
Okay.
A, L.
I did it again.
Wrong move!
What are you talking about?
Do it again.
In heels, yeah.
What?
That's a different key.
What the...
These are different keys.
A, S, and K, and L.
I mean, that's...
Whatever.
Wait.
What am I doing?
Oh, I gotta go in here.
Hack.
All right.
I hacked it.
Okay.
We have to steal the crypto.
Wait, these are bad guys?
That guy's a gun.
Wait.
Hold on.
I don't want to kill this guy.
What's going on?
Oh, shit.
Okay.
I steal the crypto key.
All right.
It's down there.
I got it.
Wait.
There's permadeath.
There's actually permadeath.
Hack the drone.
What?
This gun didn't even do anything.
Get back in the car.
Okay.
So this is like a gang hideout.
Evaded.
Do you need a minute?
Ready when you are, my little robot friend.
Why are people screaming?
I just heard somebody go...
What's going on?
Why was we freaking out?
Can't climb this?
Okay.
All right.
Let's sneak in here.
I gotta recruit this guy.
I have to.
Okay.
I gotta go up here.
All right.
I'm gonna...
Let's do it.
Let's do it for real.
For real.
Let's take the hacker spider over there.
All right.
I'm gonna deploy hacker spider.
So I can do a stealth...
Wait.
What's V, right?
Okay.
Hold on.
What do we got?
We got...
Oh, there's a drone right there.
All right.
It's like a Pokemon fight here.
Can I hack that?
Disable.
I can't disable it.
Oh, wait.
I got a camera right there.
All right.
Hack that camera.
I'll use this camera to hack that thing.
Hack it.
Goodbye.
See ya.
Wait.
What?
No.
What happened to the spider?
Oh, shit.
This is bad.
All right.
I just gotta go...
Okay.
Let's distract.
I'm gonna drive this car.
Wait.
He's gonna walk into it.
I can make it go backwards?
All right.
I'm gonna make it...
I'm gonna drive...
I'm gonna run him over.
Say it.
All right.
Enemy.
Just move over there.
And here we go.
Ready?
Go get it.
Hack that.
What is it?
A book?
How do you hack a book?
Oh, shit.
Turn him off.
Disable him.
What?
I have a car in my backpack?
What the fuck?
Here are the frames.
Don't blame me.
Blame Ubisoft.
They're the ones that have a hot fix coming out.
A game came out, but it's not ready.
Who cares?
Put it out anyways.
Those fucking idiots on PC.
See you in a week when it actually works.
I'm getting in here.
This is too hard.
There's too much shit in here that I have to deal with.
The two drones...
There's like four drones here.
I'm not supposed to be over here right now.
There's no way I'm supposed to be over here.
This shit...
There's like four drones.
Wait.
This is my bike.
Steal the van?
Go get it.
What the fuck, man?
Go.
Go get the van.
It's right there.
This gun doesn't...
No shit.
Go.
What are you doing?
Why is toggle on?
That was the worst decision I've made all day.
Go, go, go, go, go.
Get out of the way.
How do I get the fuck out of here?
Okay.
Hack it.
Drive the van to the drop point.
You got it.
It's one kilometer away.
Why can you just make people drive?
All right.
Where's the drop zone?
Oh, this is the first actual mission.
You fucking idiots.
Here's the thing I remember about Watch Dogs.
I remember it was kind of fun to like
make the thing in the ground go up four or five times.
And then it was just like...
You just spam Q wherever you're driving.
That's all I remember.
It's just going like this.
Q, Q, Q, Q, Q, Q, Q, Q, Q, Q, Q, Q, Q, Q, Q, Q, Q, Q, Q.
Oh, the hydrogen exploded.
Two FPS?
It's not going two FPS.
It is?
No, it's not.
It's 30.
Yeah.
I mean, 30 in 2020 looks like two.
All right.
We recruited the AI-generated person.
Wow.
Okay.
Whoa.
What?
You live in the van to...
What the...
What's this gas?
What the fuck is happening?
Survive until the transfer completes.
I just double tapped that guy.
That guy got hit twice in the air.
Dude, why?
Should I just drive away?
Hack everything.
I don't even know what I just did.
Reload.
Are you sure this isn't Far Cry 5?
It's the same damn company.
All right.
Nine seconds.
Four seconds.
Three, two, one.
Transfer completed.
Did I win?
Okay.
Get to safety.
Oh, fuck.
I feel like this mission was very, very hard.
Am I insane for thinking that this is like ridiculous?
Oh my god.
Why would I do that to myself?
Bitcoins in critical condition?
I did it.
Get.
I recruited.
Ha, I found you.
They did find me.
Give me this.
Did the game save after that?
Please tell me the game saved after that.
Oh my god.
Thank goodness.
Point the way.
Fuck is this?
A random fight on this?
Did I get invaded?
Adversary neutralized.
What the fuck is happening in this game?
Give me this pizza vehicle.
Thank you.
I...
Give me...
Give me the vehicle.
Okay, now I've got a new recruit.
Am I supposed to be the good guy?
I have no idea what the fuck is going on, guys.
Can I recruit this person?
How can you tell?
Recruit Ruth.
Hey, Ruth.
I got a mission for you.
Come here.
Recruit Andy.
Dermapress 4.
Don't stop recruiting.
Do a mission.
I...
What is with all the drones?
They're everywhere.
Why won't he blink?
All right, I'll help you.
Can I say, hey, get on the back?
All right, I'm gonna do the mission.
I will.
Can I say, get on the back?
Press 4.
I pressed 4.
All right, I'm gonna do the real mission.
I'll go to music.
No, I turned off music.
It's probably copyright shit.
I gotta be careful with that.
Press 4 when you're off the bike.
4.
I pressed it.
Didn't do anything.
There's mail here or something.
What is this?
Deliver.
Operatives can take parcels from any pickup box and deliver them to the specific donation.
I don't know how that word came out.
Parcels can have up to three properties each with its own difficulty.
This is just...
All right.
No, that's boring.
Give me the real shit.
No, I don't want to.
Why can't you just take armored tanks?
What?
Why am I able just to do this?
If the key's in the ignition...
What is this?
Wait, I can...
Let's turn on auto drive.
Why is it on driving?
Am I in trouble?
Auto drive stops for cars.
Oh, well.
Get away from me.
Don't play...
I didn't do anything wrong.
Don't blame me.
It's a fucking computer.
Look, I'm not...
My hands aren't even on the wheel.
My hands are not even touching the wheel.
The cop is also on auto drive.
All right, I'm gonna get in here to this mission.
I'm gonna lose this guy first.
You murdered somebody?
I did not murder anybody.
All right.
You know what?
Good luck getting through that.
Whoa!
How do they not see us doing this?
Get over here.
Fuck!
What, did you just throw a bottle?
I fucking play Dark Souls a lot.
Like that.
They didn't even look in here.
They just heard people getting the shit kicked out of them.
Sash over.
Nobody fucking here.
Is that a gun?
What?
Fortnite.
How do I get the car?
Okay, so we got to investigate this over here.
Pick this up.
Where is this?
Is it inside the building?
Press 4.
I will.
Okay, I just stole money out of that.
I unlocked that.
Let's go in here.
Oh shit, that's a bad guy.
Shoot him in the head?
Both of them?
Scream.
Okay, so I need to get up top.
Investigate their replacement.
Did I miss something in here?
This isn't your mission.
I mean, it's something very obviously.
What's the green thing up there?
Something's blinking.
I can't literally go up.
Doesn't that green thing mean there's something in here?
Oh shit, look at this.
Give me that.
How do I get that?
It's in the vent?
Oh damn, look at this right here.
Spider.
Spider?
Why can I not use the spider?
Free.
That's going to be a shitload of money, isn't it?
Say the line.
Giant.
Why do you want me to say that?
That's such an old meme.
We're over it, aren't we?
All right, we're banging left.
And then there's going to be a package in here.
Look at it.
Pick it up.
Oh, that's tech.
Oh shit, that's 10 tech points.
Feign excitement.
What the fuck?
I...
Hey, chat.
We got 10 tech points.
Feign excitement.
Got it.
All right, leave the spider in there.
All right, press 4.
So this is not a mission?
Why is it all...
I mean, why is it yellow?
Okay, tech points.
Where's my car?
It's restricted though.
Does it get delivered to me or no?
Is that it on the minimap over there?
Is this it?
Holy shit, this thing's fucking crazy.
Is this mine?
This is my car.
Wow.
Now get in.
You picked colorblind mode.
Oh, I think I did.
Menu.
I did.
Yeah, I did.
Okay.
When I was setting it up, I was like, oh, that looks better.
Okay, that's better.
All right, that makes more sense now.
Okay, well, look, the mission marker is gold.
And I'm in a gold area.
Whatever.
All right, let's pump this.
Let's do it.
Glory.
Oh, I'm so glad we picked this lady.
Her car is sick.
Untracked mission.
Acquire Albion operations data.
No, fuck that.
Two FPS driving.
Come on, guys.
You don't like this demonstration of iPad metal hardware?
Metal graphics processing unit?
It's like eight frames a second, but it sure looks pretty good.
Or an iPad.
Spider-Man 2 graphics.
Is he just trying to make this look bad?
I don't think I have to do that.
I think it just is.
All right, this is it.
Investigate the replacement of Ruth Sen.
And aside from some heavily armed security guards, it's basically a ghost town.
Isn't that interesting?
Okay, let's go.
I don't think this replacement is also-
GTA IV.
Look around and see if you can figure out where-
Put it on the lowest setting.
It's not going to do anything.
We know that's not going to do anything.
Let me pee and figure out what I want to do.
I'll- I'll- I'm going to pee.
All right, let's try this again.
Grandma, please, you didn't update your drivers for the game
and are on the worst possible settings.
And you get annoyed at how bad it looks and how low the FPS is.
I'm going to update my drivers right now.
I'm going to update my driver stream.
Here we go.
No, but you guys told me about the hotfix.
Ubisoft is making a hotfix because the game runs like shit.
Update your drivers, man.
What is this copypasta?
You know, hey, anytime you update drivers, don't you find it really sad
when the default page that it lands on is the new cool one?
And you have to go down three drop-down menus and scroll?
Oh, fuck.
GeForce 10 series.
Oh, man.
All right, here we go.
Update my- the stream's probably going to crash.
Whatever, I'll be back.
Fuck the mods.
Why are you saying that?
Well, how come- why is everybody bullying you?
It's all right.
They don't mean it.
That's what I tell myself every time I lie down and go to sleep.
And then I refresh the page and I see like tons of toxic comments.
I'm kidding.
I really don't.
All right, here we go.
It's time to update my graphics drivers.
Are you guys ready for this?
Fucking POG moment.
Here it comes.
Oh, here it comes.
If the stream turns off, I will be back in 10 seconds.
I don't think it will, though.
Driver stream?
Oh, yeah.
I was here.
I was here for the driver stream.
I was here- I was against my will.
What?
Why- what are you doing here?
Here we go.
All right.
Nvidia graphics driver.
Agree and continue.
Don't ban me.
Don't- don't delete my stream.
I'm coming back if it does.
I'll be right back if the stream turns off.
I promise.
This is the game ready driver.
I'm ready.
I got a six pack of Mountain Dew.
I'm ready to play Legion at the highest caliber 1080p graphics.
Oh, I got what?
Wake me when it's- when it's over.
I will.
I'll scream.
Oh, yeah.
I'm going to yell right in the microphone.
I won't.
All right.
It's installing right now.
Come on.
Let's go.
Vod Watchers.
Skip five minutes.
Actually, that's a pretty good point.
Yeah.
Hey, Vod Watchers.
Just skip like two or three minutes.
Oh, hey, Vod Watchers.
Open up the next Vod that exists.
Because that's- well, it might happen.
See you in episode two.
Stream two.
Is it doing anything?
Why is it taking so long?
Hello?
Everything- everything went- everything just went black.
Am I still live?
I don't know.
I have no idea.
I might be.
Hey, I'm still live.
We're good.
I didn't have to turn the stream off.
It has been installed.
We're ready to go.
All right.
Let's go.
You guys hyped Watch Dogs Legion?
Here it comes.
Fuck, dude.
I'm so excited for this game.
You have no idea.
Hold on.
My Epic Games launcher doesn't work anymore.
Here we go.
I implore you to give this game a chance.
I know you're being a haha funny YouTuber by killing everyone
and complaining about corporate Ubisoft,
which I completely understand.
Please at least play through the first few tutorial missions
and see how social- how the social mechanics of this game are set up.
And that- it's actually a lot like the Nemesis system.
You know, the thing that you in chat absolutely loved.
I implore you.
Well, I'm- I'm not- I'm still going.
I'm still streaming.
I'm just waiting for the game to work.
Here it comes.
I promise this time it is coming.
Is that a coffee pasta or is that somebody's actual real opinion?
I'm going for it.
I'm gonna.
All right.
Stream starts now.
You heard the system booting.
There it is.
We have nude- we have the brand new today graphics drivers.
Why is everyone saying nude?
Continue.
Show it to me.
Loading screen.
Menu.
60 FPS.
Incoming.
This is- this is not internet.
Oh, come on.
Did I download graphics drivers and they like fucking corrupted my system?
I'm gonna- I'm gonna put- I'm gonna load this thing up like they shoot the clay discs.
I'm just gonna pull.
I'm gonna shoot with a rocket launcher.
You downloaded the wrong drivers?
No, I didn't.
It's taking so much longer.
It's taking like three times as long.
Fuck.
Is it updating?
No, it's going.
It's- we're just gonna leave it alone.
You need to restart the computer.
Oh, God.
I just saw it tick.
Hold on.
We- is it- we in?
I'm gonna give this 30 seconds that I'm restarting my fucking computer.
Pain in the ass.
And you guys wonder why like consoles sell so well.
It is moving though.
It is.
And- and everybody else like curious to see what happens when it gets to the end.
Use the talk shit and it's done.
Yes.
We're in.
How did everything go under?
Some fresh meat.
Ready?
What the fuck happened to that guy?
All right.
Game ready driver.
What's going on over here?
Uh, this lady.
That's a lot.
How many times are you gonna do this?
Got him.
Now go, run!
All right, I'm good.
Pad frame rate.
Oh, the FPS is so bad.
It is so bad.
Lower all the- they're already pretty fucking low, man.
I can't- they don't even let you put it on low.
Why is that on?
Fuck it.
We're going- we're going 2001.
Full screen mode?
Are you telling me that's the bullshit that's gonna be a problem?
Better not be.
This better not be the fucking problem.
They're actually running better.
Use DirectX 11?
Trouble- trouble to shoot the streamer's video game so it doesn't look like GTA 3 The Stream.
Put it on DX 11?
How do I do that, though?
How do I put it on DirectX 11?
I don't know how to do that.
I'm not gonna lower the resolution.
Is it in the options?
Options?
Is it in video?
GTX 1080.
It's in the video settings.
Field of view.
F- monitor refresh rate.
Resolution.
Where do you see that?
Look, I got plenty of VRAM.
DirectX 11.
Oh god fucking damn it.
So, how was your day today?
Worst stream 2020.
Contender incoming.
I'll be your host for the evening.
Streamer left.
He walked out after he had to restart his game 15 times and went to crash twice in the tutorial.
He had to download game-ready Legion drivers.
He since has gone out of the room.
I'll be playing now.
I'm a better streamer.
Restart your fucking computer.
If I restart the computer, the stream goes off.
I need like a stream battery that keeps the stream turned on.
Let's go.
DX 11.
Not DX 12.
That's the bad one.
That's the one that sucks.
That's the one that causes problems for every PC.
I remember that.
You're number five in the Watch Dogs category.
Fuck.
Look at how lightning quick that just loaded.
Did you see that?
This is the fastest I've ever seen a loading screen start.
Remember, do you have an SSD?
Yes, I have three of them.
All right.
My computer might be a few years old, but it's not like I have hard drives in here.
He's fuming right now.
Actually, that's kind of entertaining in a way for me.
DX 11 Andy.
You're the second highest English-speaking Watch Dogs streamer.
Who's the first?
Why can't I be number one?
Mechanical Drive Matthew.
Stop.
All right.
This is it.
I'm getting in here and I'm playing.
And if not, I'll hold the power button off on my fucking computer.
I swear to God, if it's still fucked up.
And I'm going to turn it back on to turn and come back in five minutes.
You can't be number one because the other guy's not doing a troubleshooting stream.
Shit.
I need a better computer.
I gotta get a better computer now.
Oh, shit.
And I think it just needed a few minutes to load.
Dude, this looks fine.
This looks pretty.
This looks okay.
This looks all right.
Wait.
Why is it?
What is it doing that?
No, no, no.
Trust me.
Wait, wait, wait, wait.
Wait for it to refresh a little bit.
Bingo.
We got 60 FPS.
Let's go.
Fuck.
What happened?
Skipped frames detected.
What's doing this?
Why is it doing this?
What's going on?
I'll be back.
Give me five minutes.
Fucking turn the computer.
I'm just turning the computer off.
I'm not even going to turn the stream off.
I'm just turning off the computer.
I'm restarting.
I can't even restart my computer.
The Windows button doesn't even work.
I'm back into...
I'm just hitting the power button.
I'll be back in two minutes.
Come back and watch my watchdog streams.
I'm number two.
God damn it.
I'm going to be number one.
Hey, hey, hey.
I'm here.
Number two.
Come on.
I'm the number two guy right here.
Hey, I'm back.
I'm back.
OK.
I restarted the stream.
I restarted.
Watchdog's Legion is now starting.
Here we go.
It's coming.
Somebody said, wow,
Shroud's stream looks great.
I'm sure it does.
I'm sure it looks fantastic.
I'm sure it looks really good.
But mine...
I'm going to get a better computer soon
and then it'll be better.
I left for an hour.
What have I missed?
Not a whole lot.
All right.
Watchdog's Legion.
Here we go.
I'm going to get that 3090.
I'm going to get like a...
I'm going to get like a 35-core PC.
A 3090.
Two of them.
I'm going to have to have
a dedicated energy account
just for this computer.
I swear to God.
You lost 2,000 viewers.
Sorry.
They'll be back in like 10 minutes.
OK.
We have restarted.
I have dropped my stream settings
to be able to handle this.
The game has been restarted.
I'm ready.
It's in DirectX 11.
I have the new driver.
I'm ready to play Watchdog's Legion
on launch day.
We're on V-Sync, you idiot.
Isn't turning on V-Sync
the same thing as like saying Voldemort?
I thought all gamers on PC
weren't allowed to do that.
Here we go.
Let's take a look.
OK.
Continue.
Wait.
I'll do it.
OK.
Let me do that first.
Video.
Full screen.
V-Sync.
Normal.
I guess.
OK.
Normal.
Here we go.
Campaign.
Continue.
Let's go.
Hey.
All right.
It looks just as bad
as it did 20 minutes ago.
Dude, why is it doing this?
Wait, are we good?
No.
My computer can't handle Watchdog's Legion.
I can't.
I just can't do it.
My CPU can't run it.
I can't run it.
I can run it on DX12.
No.
I don't want to do this again.
DX12.
And I'm going to put like
the geometry on high.
Don't restart yet.
Hold on.
Resolution is 1080.
It's the PC patch, not your PC.
What the fuck?
Go to 720.
No, that's too ugly.
I can't.
Turn off V-Sync.
All right.
Here's what I'm going to do.
I'm going to go back to DX Revert.
Let's go back to DX12.
I'm going to put the geometry.
I'm going to keep this here.
Everything.
We're going to put some load on the GPU.
Major load.
No, I don't want major load on the CPU.
Why does my CPU suck?
My CPU doesn't even suck, though.
I have a 6-core, like 6,800.
If this don't work,
if this still looks like shit,
then I'm just going to do tier lists
for like two or three hours.
Get them ready.
Get your favorite tier lists ready
because Watch Dogs Legion
fucking throw it into the trash.
Here we go.
Six cores, not enough in 2020.
That's plenty of cores.
That's a lot of cores.
I just got $50 for like
the worst stream I've done all month.
It's from Phylactery Lich.
Thank you, Phylactery.
5,000 bits.
Remember, please buy a new computer.
I'm begging you.
Yeah, I am.
I just was waiting until like 3090s
and 3080s were back in stock
and the new Risen processors just dropped.
This shit's happening like this weekend.
Like I'm this day.
I'm going to get a supercomputer.
I'm coming back to Watch Dogs Legion
when I get this new computer
and we're going to put everything on Ultra
and I'm just going to run around
and just punch people and laugh
and say, see where we are.
All right, let's try it.
Get your tier lists ready
because I'm about to fucking have a meltdown.
What about AI Dungeon?
Well, maybe.
You made your, uh, put,
went down to 70.
Just try and stop me.
Okay. Well, it runs.
It runs, but not very good.
I fucking swear to God.
Dude, this ain't my computer.
This ain't my computer.
It's not.
This is no way.
That's not my computer.
This is fucking dumb game.
There's no fucking way this is my PC.
He's in denial.
No, it can't be.
No, other streamers are good.
But why?
Why am I not good?
What the heck?
It's not fair.
I was supposed to be number two.
I was the number two guy.
He was supposed to be me.
Put it on XP compatibility mode.
Fuck.
It was supposed to be me, you know?
I was supposed to be that guy.
I was supposed to be the number two spot.
I was going to be able to look over
and see like Shroud right there
and be like, Shroud, Pog.
This stream looks so good too.
And I need like a good stream like his.
All right.
I'm doing this one more time.
I have to try one more time.
Why? Why?
Because it's called, I've, okay.
I lost $99,999.
I have $1 left and I'm putting it on black.
And if it hits, then I get $2.
And at least I got a victory out of this.
You're in denial.
I know.
That's okay though.
But okay, here's the really wacky thing, okay?
My CPU usage right now is like 19%.
What the hell's happening?
This is not like putting a bottleneck on my computer.
This is wacky shit.
My CPU is at 22% right now.
Don't you think?
I want to see what it is.
It's zany.
Oh, Twitch staff is here.
I'm going to be on good behavior.
If you use liquid, what?
Open up a benchmark.
It's because you have a pirated copy of the game.
That's what I was doing.
You guys know how many like subs this channel has
and I'm pirating Watch Dogs Legion.
I don't want to risk too much.
Okay.
Nobody move.
I'm not going to move.
Okay.
By the way, view count rising.
View count rising.
Bye.
Everybody stop buying.
Bye, bye, bye, bye, bye.
View count fucking skyrocketing.
All right.
I can play.
We're good.
Let's go.
It works, right?
We got decent frames.
It just looks like dog shit.
Employer.
And aside from some heavily armed security guards,
it's basically a ghost town.
Decent frames, but at what cost?
All right.
We're good.
Let's go.
I'm ready.
I'm playing.
Okay.
Restricted area.
Investigate the replacement.
Take a look at security cameras.
Time to hack the world.
Hack the world.
Only if you have a graphics card
that's at least in the 2000 generation of Nvidia.
You got anything less than that?
You don't get to hack the world.
Well, you do, but you get to kind of slowly get to hack the world.
Pretty bad frames.
Huge bits.
Hey, Master Fleet, thanks for the $50 for the PC fund.
Don't worry.
I'm going to get one.
I'm going to take this guy down.
Thank you for the $50 of this insane amount of money.
Can I kick this thing when it's on the ground?
Who the fuck is this?
You know when you just get taken out of a groove
because you spent the last 40 minutes trying to get the game to run?
What the hell was that?
Nice trip.
I fucking hate the drones.
The drones are stupid.
What a dumb thing to have in the game.
Sit down!
You too.
Whothis is like a CEO.
Who the fuck is this?
I don't know, battery power?
Dude, I haven't even done the first mission of the game.
I'm realizing.
This is just like hard mode secondary shit.
I need to do the actual mission.
What the fuck?
I can't even do this!
Get out of my face.
You fuckin' tin can?
High disadvantage, what?
Wait, open that back up.
Open that back up.
Go, go, go, get it, get it.
Who needs advanced hacking when you have
idiots that open doors for free?
God damn it.
I'm good.
Like that, where are they?
You can do your corporate espionage from there.
Oh my god, there's a person here.
Shoot him, what?
What's that, what's that, what's it on me?
Hey, what's that on your phone?
Somebody just sent you a funny meme on the internet.
Okay, get out of here.
Hack it, hack this, hack this thing.
Hack it, is it just me, is it just me?
Fuck, what?
Download, all right, downloading it, 5%.
Oh, look at that view count, skyrocketing.
What's wrong with this?
Oh, this thing is sad, this is sad.
I had to put it out of its misery.
It was flying around.
I did it, okay.
Uh-oh, I don't think, I can't leave.
Wait, wait, wait, I'm good, I got it.
Thank god I can do it from inside.
Oh, we're out.
See, this game's not bad.
Look at this, this is a fun, cool thing I just did.
What do we have?
It could maybe replace a few million humans at most.
I suppose from your perspective, that's a lot.
If you like, we can go destroy it
before it puts anyone else out of work.
Very good, forward me the coordinates.
All right, I got it, we're good.
Now, okay, now I'm gonna do a mission.
Let's go do a real mission,
not one of these fake missions, a real one.
Here we go, recruit Seth Den, that's not a real mission.
Here it is, track this, please.
What are my skill points?
Hell yeah, let's go.
Here's my team.
What does he got?
New operative, I can, oh, I can switch to this operative.
This guy dead?
All right, I'm good for now.
You beat his ass and now he wants to be on the team.
What is this, hold on, there's tech points in here.
Let's see, oh, wait, recruitment.
No, no, no, no more recruitments.
Can I get on stage?
Oh, free money, this, this.
Oops, okay, what am I doing?
Okay, mission.
Sir, I'm gonna need you to pull over that car, please.
Somebody, what?
This thing zips, holy shit, look at this thing.
All right, raise it.
What do you mean checkpoint?
All right, I'll be on operations data.
I'll be in propaganda, let's do mission one.
Now this is pod racing.
In here, all right, get me out of this.
Sneak into this place.
You just taking a picture of me?
Taking photos of me?
All right, this is restricted.
Get operations data and get the propaganda.
Restricted areas are dangerous.
Press V to scan the area to reveal scouting opportunities.
I'm glad I got this tutorial now.
Captains will call for reinforcements
if they detect you, eliminate them before they do.
Ammos, drones, traps, got it.
Albion have established an operational base
in the Royal Court of Justice.
Up there.
First they take over the justice system,
then they move in.
So much for rule of law.
Exactly.
Should I download some?
There's information here about how Albion
are targeting dissenters, the who and the why.
I love this PS2 game.
Me too, it's very fun.
All right, what is that?
Is that a GTX 3090?
Is somebody talking to me?
All right, I definitely have to do that.
Let's go up there.
Can I do anything with this?
Can't download that from here.
I can't fuck with this from here.
Oh, I can do that.
Hi Jack, this is a mouse trap?
What else you got?
Got him.
Only one guy left.
Anybody else in here?
This guy.
Got him.
Okay.
I think we're clear.
I can go in now, right?
I don't see anybody else.
All right, there's a guy here.
All right, wait, hold on.
Distract you, go in.
There ain't nobody else, right?
All right, there's the power source.
We're gonna turn the power on.
Everybody's dead, I'm fine.
Play Batman Arkham Asylum.
I beat that game on the hardest difficulty five times
and I was like 20.
No.
And if you believe that, then you're a sucker.
Shit!
You take two headshots?
Nobody, right?
Wait, I got it, it's fine.
Get that data.
Put your head up.
See, first mission done, I got it.
That was a challenge?
What, that was a challenge mode?
No, I wanted to do the mission.
Bagley, what do we have?
A list of what Aldian consider high value targets
that are threats to the peaceful running of London.
See here?
A journalist.
And this one runs a community shelter.
Good God.
What are we gonna do?
Okay.
This is across the whole city.
This is still the tutorial.
Oh.
Gadgets are useful.
I'm sure they are.
Gamers.
Oh, this is one of those games that runs good
when it becomes dusk.
It's one of those games.
Cool.
Press four.
There's essays in chat?
What are they saying?
Are they talking about me?
Are they making fun of me?
It really is GTA four.
This is not good.
It's actually like kind of worse than GTA four.
I need a new computer so bad.
It's not even funny anymore.
Like it was funny like two weeks ago.
Now it's like, get a new computer.
Saints Row three.
You know, I was gonna play Saints Row two like last week.
This runs bad on a 3090.
Why do I feel like that's the norm?
I've lost control of the car.
Okay.
All right.
In here, we have to disrupt the propaganda.
This is not restricted.
This is ATM.
Oh shit.
I just ATM money.
I'm not supposed to take it all.
Can I go in here?
I don't fuck with a gamer.
That's what I said.
Those Albian pricks putting their ugly stamp on everything.
It makes me sick just looking at it.
You're in good hands.
It looks to be that much less once you're done here.
Let's give Camden a break from these eyesores.
On it.
All right, so I've changed the...
So we're gonna hack the thing
to make it look like it's ugly or something?
Propaganda.
We have to disrupt the propaganda.
I didn't even hit you.
I didn't hit you, you're fine.
You did not get hit by that bike.
By the way, how do you feel about the government?
Get up.
I need to recruit you.
Nevermind.
This is it.
If you hijack that scissor lift,
you could use it to access the rooftop.
Okay, hijack.
Wait, don't I need to be in it first?
Get in it first.
Okay, let's go.
Hijack.
And how excited are you guys for Watch Dogs 3?
Wait, I'm not gonna be able to get back in this.
Who cares?
Ooh, tech.
He hates it.
No, I don't.
I don't hate it.
Furu.
No, don't say Furu.
Don't say Furu, they're watching.
What's that puke?
Can I go inside of this?
No, sorry, Nancy, you can't do that.
Nobody can do that.
All right, turn it off.
Congratulations, you've done the first mission
of Watch Dogs.
We shall never surrender.
Hey, it was me.
All right, I did it.
So now what?
I'll get people's attention.
Let them know someone is standing up to Albion.
Light the spark that they can stand up to.
If nothing else, it'll relieve their eye strain.
Where's my car?
There it is.
Mission started.
Clarion call.
We're already seeing results from what you've done.
That list we found.
Taxi.
News journalist in Camden who's been investigating Albion.
We reached out and he's got information that can help us.
Why is it drive?
Forward me the call.
What's wrong with this thing?
It's running over a box?
Oh, come on.
All right, goodbye, it was fun.
Meet with the dead second foreman.
I can do that.
What the shit now?
Why is this up?
Go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go.
Yo, that car looks sick.
Yeah, it does.
This does kind of look like Batman, doesn't it?
Yeah, now that you say that, I can see it.
Okay, meet with the informant.
Don't run him over, don't run him over,
don't run him over, don't run him over.
Who's this guy?
Neil Brown stole Albion weapon schematics.
He knows how to summon drones
and he's got extra faction damage.
All right, he's a summoner?
A little birdie told me you needed help.
Even more money came in.
You can't believe someone else is.
Thought I was alive, right?
Holy shit, guys.
You're not doing much, just putting the word out, are you?
Devil X gave $50.
Someone has to, don't they?
I have Insomnia gave $50, back to back.
Almost got Clip finding this.
All of Albion's operational data for the entire system.
Actually good computer fund, and here's some money,
seed money for a better laptop
because you're playing on one, clearly.
You'll get no argument from me.
Here's a sample.
Albion's closed King's Cross for the public, right?
What people don't know is that-
It's gonna happen.
It's their logistic center, materials.
Dude, when I build this new computer.
A lot of it runs through there.
We're gonna do a super benchmark stream.
Put it out of commission
and you'll severely hamstring Albion's operations
here in Camden.
Hell, everywhere.
Then that's our move.
I'm gonna run this thing through the absolute, through hell.
Okay, no, don't kill him.
I've just seen a car drive out.
Like somebody finally got the car in the mall out.
Oh my God, he got the car out of the mall.
You bastard, I can't believe somebody
actually was able to do that.
And then one of the representatives from the mall is like,
well, I mean, this kind of was the point.
We left the keys in there.
We were just waiting for somebody to drive out of the,
out of the JCPenney.
It's just a free car.
I just went in a circle.
Holy shit.
What did I just run over?
What'd I hit?
That was a camp.
Jesus Christ.
Jesus.
Okay, we can get a drone.
Hijack a news drone.
Okay.
Hijack.
Up, down, flash.
Find the information generator.
I'll go spotlight, turn that off.
Oh, hey.
Oh shit, drone fight.
Drone fight.
Okay, out of here.
Photograph the generator.
What happened?
Just use cover.
All right, there's the schematics.
Photograph it.
How many do I need?
F.
Okay, download the detonation code.
Fuck.
Okay, just wave.
Fuck, wave.
Got it.
Hack, hack, hack, hack, hack, hack, hack, hack.
47%, 50%, 55%, 60%.
We almost loaded the game.
Hack faster.
I'm going as fast as I can.
That's it.
Use the code on the generator
and I can trigger a power surge.
All right, go back to the generator.
Stack King's cross offline and the rail system too.
Is this exhilarating?
Is it?
Wait, should I go flash this guy in the face?
Did I leave?
Oh shit, it exploded.
That was you, oh.
We got a gold mine of information out of St. Pancras.
Albion convoys, informants, gear, you name it.
Everything we need to ignite the people of London,
like we did in Camden.
Derail Albion's operations
and give the people a reason to rise up borough by borough.
The more we do that,
the more we'll get allies flocking to the courts.
City of London.
We'll show London that DedSec is here for them.
London was mine?
What do you mean?
That was off the chain, mate.
I knew DedSec weren't the bad guys Albion was saying.
London was fine.
Thanks.
Now that you've shown the borough
what DedSec is really all about,
there are gonna be folks wanting to join up.
A lot of people have been looking for a way to fight back.
Let me have the title of my stream make sense, finally.
I'll contact you very soon.
I happen to know they're champion at the bit.
At this point, I think we'll take all cover.
DedSec needs people.
Spray, what, what is this, around my hair?
DedSec support complete borough activities
to increase DedSec support.
You get tech points.
Skilled recruits have abilities
or weapons that are valuable to DedSec.
When a borough becomes defiant,
a skilled recruit will be added to the team.
You got it.
All right, let's go find an old lady
and ask her if she wants to join.
Wait, what?
Who did I recruit?
Game doesn't normally look this bad.
Well, it only, it does when you put it
on the lowest settings
because it's the only way you can play it.
There's a lot of potential in you.
I trust you won't disappoint.
I must say, I'm rather looking forward to the experience.
Let's go hunt some baddies.
Recruit a kid.
Me, you're still alive.
I also have been a tenner.
Not only that.
Every time we switch,
the last person has to die.
So now I spy with a vertical eye.
We're just jumping hosts.
What is it?
The Signals Intelligence Response Service or SIRS
or the Earl Grey Gestapo
have developed a surveillance technology
called AR reconstruction.
It's the leading edge of privacy rights violation
and thus it could be very useful
in our attempts to find Zero Day.
It's just a symbiont.
I don't like this human sheath anymore.
All right, we need to find an old lady.
Old lady.
Nope.
Whoa.
It just barely touched.
Yeah.
You're all right, we're fine.
Old lady, old lady, old lady.
Old lady.
Nope.
We'll find the queen.
Or whatever.
We're a new operative now.
I'm just keeping my eye out for old ladies.
Just auto drive and look around.
Auto drive now enabled.
All right.
Nope, don't see any.
Nope.
Looking for old ladies.
The older the better.
Old.
Oh, I saw the gameplay trailer.
I want to do it.
I want to see the gameplay trailer.
There's no old people in London?
It's a rare spawn.
An old lady's a rare spawn?
No.
Auto drive now disabled.
Nope.
I thought that was an old man.
Keep your eyes open.
Hello?
Excuse me.
I have a proposition for you.
I'm from...
Nah, I thought you were old.
Nevermind.
I thought you were somebody else.
Not old enough.
Excuse me.
Jesus, come on, dude.
Get out of the way.
I'm slowly going over to the new mission too, by the way.
Old.
Instruction worker.
No, where are the old ladies?
All right.
I'm here.
In theory, the AR reconstruction
should allow me to use various sources of surveillance data
to rebuild past events.
Access a data...
AR tech.
...scrape all the metadata for...
Can I get in this way?
No, I gotta go the other way.
Around the other side.
Casino.
Go to the casino.
Is there a casino in this game?
You old?
Excuse me, Emma.
I'd like to offer you a contract.
How are you?
How do you feel about the world right now?
Don't you feel like that you would want to become part of
something more?
Emma, I'd like to recruit you.
We have things to talk about.
Don't you think you want to be part of something more,
something bigger than yourself?
She's an activist who's been trying to gather intel
on Albion personnel movements through the city.
Looks like she wants to stay one step ahead of the goons.
Okay.
That is smart, yeah.
Let's help her.
Could turn into a nice little asset.
You're gonna...
A Ponzi scheme?
Look, you just have to sell 400 lipsticks and eye powders
every week and you'll make $40.
I'm telling you, it's the opportunity of a lifetime.
Okay, steal an Albion armored vehicle.
You got it.
Any armored vehicle, right?
Doesn't matter where.
You're blind, am I?
Fucking cartoon.
Tom and Jerry cartoon.
Can I play a game normally for once?
Oh, here's one.
Grandma, I got one.
I got it.
All of a sudden, a little tornado is gonna come pick me up
and I'm gonna get three tubes to pick to skip
a third of each portion of this game.
That's some deep reference right there.
And I feel bad for those who don't understand it.
That's a deep reference.
Wrong way.
It's not deep, it sucked.
But you just got yourself a timeout.
Next stream.
I'll remember your name.
Next stream, you're getting timed out.
You know what?
Who cares, run over.
I've got places to be.
I have an old lady to recruit.
Oh my goodness, thank God you weren't on that other bench.
Get Grandma, I'm getting her.
Distraction.
Yes, you have.
I'm safe.
This is so far away.
It's a very long drive.
I think that person's still under my car.
Are they?
NA driving in EU.
Is that gonna explode?
American streamer, he's on the wrong side of the road.
American streamer, yeah, that's me.
All right, it's time to play as old lady
for the rest of the game
and I don't even care if it's the worst.
Awesome.
Okay, here we go.
Hey, where are you?
Talk to Emma.
Emma, I've returned your car.
It's just, yes, finally.
Excellent, didn't they talk like this?
Aiming often leaves something to be desired
but the hard drive in that vehicle
should more than suit your purposes.
You bet your ass.
Armed with this, I'll be able to dance circles
around those Albion thugs
and shove a boot up their backsides.
If you need anything at all, I'm at your service.
Hey, how about now?
DedSec could always use more people.
Interested?
Right, count me in.
iPad graphics, fucking come on.
All right, recruit complete. Recruit Emma Tan.
Here we go. Team.
There's Emma.
Swap to Emma.
Isn't Emma right here?
Welcome to DedSec, darling.
We are just thrilled to have you.
Brilliant.
I'm not ready to go to pasture yet.
Let's get to it.
Yeah.
How do I, uh, wait, wait, wait.
The new host.
She has a wrench. How do I use the wrench?
It's equipped. Okay.
New host.
Holy shit, she's so slow.
There's no way I'm going to be able to do this.
Slug.
And she can steal keys?
It's all right. All right, let's go. Investigate the AR tech.
No, let's continue to grow our elderly population.
Old.
Old!
Okay, let's go.
How do I, okay, recruit.
What does it, what does it say? What's the bio?
Uh, doesn't like view, doesn't like me?
View the bio?
Has been owed 80 quid by a DedSec member since 2021.
Doesn't like DedSec.
Age 55.
Oh shit.
Never mind.
Wait, it said feet?
Old!
All right, I'll do a mission with the old lady.
Let's go.
The AR tech.
You are so stupid.
Oh my God!
I'm okay.
Oh, no.
No, not old.
Holy shit, this is a million miles away.
This is so far away. Can I fast travel?
Fast travel, where's a fast travel?
Here we go.
Recruit more old people.
I'm gonna.
Don't you think we need new clothes for this person?
Okay, outerwear.
Is there like bathrobe or something?
Oh, this is too, this is too cool.
This is cool.
I don't want cool.
I want casual.
All right, that's all right.
Not cool.
Glasses.
Yeah, all right.
We need glasses.
What about legs?
Drop legwear.
No, it's all this, this is dumb.
I don't want this.
Uh, we need, we got innerwear.
Oh, this is stupid.
What about outerwear?
Okay, this character sucks.
What about bag?
A little backpack?
All right, that's good.
Zoomer boomer.
No, yeah, this isn't every one of those movies where
the 15 year old
switches brains with like the 50 year old.
And then as the
13 year old 50 year old,
they dress like this.
And then they use some crazy teen lingo
when they're ordering a coffee
and everybody looks around they're like
yeah, I'll take a double shot of that
and it's gonna be lit.
And everyone around is like
what the old lady said that?
That's strange.
Wait, isn't this the same guy?
It's the same people from last time.
Wait, play darts.
That's not what I wanted to do.
Let's play darts.
Take the mask off.
I collect, I didn't mean to click.
Let's play darts.
I have no idea how to play darts
and I don't even care to read this.
I'll just get into the middle.
Aim, throw.
Fuck this.
People are pissing their pants?
That's a double bull.
Are they saying that
I have a gun?
I just have a gun in my hand.
I just want to play darts.
I win.
Gun.
Look out, gun.
She's got a gun.
What was that?
Was that Nathan Drake over there?
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
This guy keeps pissing his pants.
Okay, get me the fuck out of here.
Who's talking shit?
Hard mode, I win.
All right.
So now let's go do this mission.
Where's the gambling?
I don't think there's gambling in this game.
That was pretty sick.
Realistic old lady driving.
No, it's not.
Now it is.
That's a broken back.
Holy shit.
That was horrible.
She's fine.
She's all right.
She's still got a little bit of spunk.
What are you doing?
No, what are you doing?
Get on the bike.
She's confused.
Shattered hip.
My stomach.
I can't stop thinking about the darts.
These are GTA 3 tier jokes.
I mean, is it a joke or am I just...
Is this game just fucking...
I was looking at the chat.
Fuck.
Red dead all over again.
What are you doing?
What the fuck?
Get off.
City's fighting back.
Wait.
Oh, I'm getting super deja vu.
This is...
I was here already with a different person.
Okay, let's go in here.
All right.
Rainy's ready to go.
Investigate the AR tech.
Security lasers will alert guards.
Disable them by hacking them.
All right.
What about...
How do I...
I need to hack them.
Is there a camera?
All right.
Mask on.
Power this shit up.
Now what?
Launch AR reconstruction test.
How the fuck do I do that?
Wait, is this a trap door?
Can I like trap somebody in there?
Wait.
Can I...
I can't like pancake throw him or anything.
Can I?
I guess.
All right.
Oh, fuck.
There's a guy right there.
What?
Cool.
Ethereal.
And strange.
Nobody suspects the old lady.
Old diaper.
You're gonna raid?
Oh, this Ludwig.
Ludwig raid.
What's going on everybody?
Thanks Ludwig.
Hope you had a good stream today.
Today we're playing a game that I...
I'm so glad you raided now
and not like three hours ago
when I had to update my graphics drivers
like three times.
This game...
I...
By the way,
I might have made this really clear to everybody.
My game...
My computer sucks
and I can't run this fucking shitty game.
Why?
The game's not shitty.
Maybe it is.
This is a fucking huge raid by the way.
This is a lot of people.
15k.
Holy shit Ludwig.
If you guys don't follow Ludwig,
he's one of the funniest people on Twitch.
He's just...
He's like a content king.
He's got it going on.
Trust me.
Freudian slip.
All right.
Let me get back to what I was doing.
Oh, by the way,
I know that Ludwig says he could beat me in a fight.
It depends.
Are we allowed to bring weapons?
25k.
Oh shit.
Hold on.
There's people here.
Oh no.
No, no, no.
Anybody hear this?
I'm pushing him back into his spawn.
Okay.
What the fuck?
Where am I?
I don't like it in the dark.
Oh shit.
Yeah, this is Mike.
I happen to be...
I think somebody locked me in a freezer.
What?
Wiped his nose?
Get...
Get the fuck out here and let me end this.
What the hell did I...
Okay, we got him.
He's dead.
I fell onto...
Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait.
Escape?
Oh shit.
Okay.
I'm in...
Can I pick up that shotgun?
Give me the shotgun.
I just have to leave.
Minus 10k, Andy.
That's what happens on...
Hey, it's all right.
No, seriously.
Thanks to the raid though, Ludwig.
What do I have to do?
You didn't sing the raid song.
Fuck.
Wait, am I getting locked out of what I want to do?
I can't...
I can't play as grandma anymore?
Oh shit.
...to find your heavy lifter?
I'm for permadeath, grandma.
Wait...
Did we unlock permadeath?
Do I have it?
Is it on now?
I took the box before.
Jesus Christ.
I'm magnetized to other cars. What the fuck? I can't even look at chat for one second
Okay, profile people and see their unique abilities. Oh
construction worker
occupation check drone check I need you
You you and me we're gonna be rich
You look like someone who's sick and tired of the way things are going. You're a dead sack good
I need help with something. We'll do our best. What seems through the matter? I got in some money trouble
Now they have me working off what I owe them 3d. Yes, and it's getting bigger
No, it looks so bad if you can help me settle that I'd appreciate it. All right, no time for chit-chat then
I do do I have the worst-looking
Watchdog stream on twitch right now
How many more things am I gonna add to the list of the worst things for me?
worst fall guy stream worst looking game stream
Okay, find the laptop
Worst twitch stream. I'm just holding W. I don't care at perma death though. Is it still is it active?
All right, is it here? You need to pivot to rat to it
One can exchange. Oh fuck. Okay, but I have to do the construction worker
Erase the blackmail data. How do I get up there? What can I do with the drone saw waiting room instruction worker? Okay
Yeah, okay, oh we got five subs anonymous gifter gave five community subs
Thanks the subs dude, I get the fuck up there and oh no, it actually was an anonymous gifter. Okay, I see
Alright, let's do that. Maybe the spider
Edit the loadout or edit loadout. I'm gonna do I don't she has anything do I have to switch to somebody else three
Hello. No, what the fuck? I don't I'm trying three
three three row
Come on. What the fuck?
Bring on the numpad. That would be so bizarre
I have absolutely no idea where the fuck to go
Terminal or some kind of device. Oh, I think I found it darling
I
Think I've already found it. I need to hide
Fuck. No, god damn it. Get out of here. Run wrong granny. Run run run run run run run run. Hurry. Hurry
Oh, I can hack this. What is it a camera? The doors open? No, no, no, okay back over here to open the door
You dead sec
What the fuck zap him this guy's made of what
No permadeath we're good
Okay, let's let's get a hack where's that news drone this way
That's cool sounds pretty cool out of range I can't
Wait, what I can't hack it. I have to actually be in there. I'm leaving by I'm leaving by I'm leaving by Oh
Don't recruit do a real. This is a real mission. I have to do I have to do this mission. I dropped this or something. Come on
I'm over here. Why do they keep making these? I'm just going to the car
Fuck it. What's just going in? Are you still alive? All right now hide you who?
You who says you who in a situation where people are shooting at you with a gun, I gotta get out just walk you who grillers
We got it. We did it. Hooray sick
Please sir, it's not funny anymore. This game sucks ass right relax relax
Don't true that true don't true that Wow true
Somebody just say bro
Bro you need to dude. Come on. She's still alive
You
You suck at driving. It's that easy to get away from the cops in this game. You just hold W
Where am I wrong side? Of course, let me get in this Zaxi. This game sucks goes zerk off, you know
Not the second part
Mom the streamers told me to suck off
This is for you the tooth. Oh, it's a no idea technically. Yeah, it's a Bluetooth
This is a big decision once I joined that sec. I can't have a normal life anymore. I get it darling
But is it normal Albion can now execute us. I can't believe that Ubisoft was able to make this happen
60 million people that live in London
60 million different voice actors. It's kind of unbelievable
That's crazy. It's definitely not 12 people right paste it over every single person you get. Okay. I'm ready the resistance
No, it's it's just Nolan North. He's every single character. That's funny every single one even the old lady
Oh
Okay, go to the with is a heist what no why I don't want to start this mission bare knuckle league
Prove your physical superiority and they may consider joining
oops
Look at look at my team. I don't care about any of these team members
Do it with granny. Let me just do this first. You can't do it with granny. Ah, that's too bad. Is it illegal?
I guess yeah, pretty illegal
Havoc to wheel and summon the cargo drone
Where it's out of reach so you'll need to use a heavy cargo drone to steal it
Okay, where is it? Let's be out of the car. Oh, right. Well, I'm onto a cargo drone and hijack it
Where is it? Let's get run over it. Oh
Hi, let's go steal the server. I have a question. We're drones in watchdogs to cuz they've really fucking loved this
Losing signal what?
Can I drive can I drive or get on it get on it
Get on it. They say get on it. What the fuck? Oh, you gotta be shitting me
Okay, this is got way cooler than it was ever I ever thought it was gonna be
Can you fall go higher I can't go any higher this is how I go
Green goblin. All right, let's get this attached. Oh
All right, I still it you and me spider-man. This is far away. Okay, cool
I've loaded the server into your vehicle. You can go now careful on the road now throw her in the ocean
We don't we don't need her anymore
I don't be this guy who wants to be?
Justin whatever his name is
Ringo
I need a wider sample of data. So I'm pushing you the coordinates to a new location. That was pretty sick. Okay, let's keep going
Watch dogs three
Not even watch dogs three
This is what this is this is watch dogs to with a different story and different characters to play as not watch dogs three
It was but they didn't number it. Oh, use me
Okay, if the grip the grip if you were watching shrouds stream right now
And the graphics weren't as bad as they are in my stream number two, by the way, we're number two
Would you would the game be better for you?
Jesus don't say that
No, you're number four now what before what?
Fourth place. It's okay. I still get two points in Mario Kart
Hack in more viewers now
What the fuck did I just do what happened
Oh for fuck's sake all right transfer complete
It was a drone
Okay
Let's go. I kind of started like Justin now. What else does he have? He's got loyalty card
Run a face cam. You'll get more views. No, it's alright. It's okay. It's it's fine
I go all the way around when you can just go like this
He's naked. Yes, he is. I do not have a shirt on you're right. I never stream with clothes on you are accurate
It's just been paint. I paint my clothes on
It was an old SNL skit from
25 years ago about shirt in a can
It's pretty funny
They have somebody sprays it on him
It's like a shirt in a can and they spray it all over the body and the guy starts going it's burning my skin
And I thought it was really funny
Boomer humor, so this mission sucks
Do I have to protect this it all right
They love the drones they love drone so much in this game, it's like their favorite thing ever
I know whatever NA aim NA 25 FPS aim. I'm losing DPI on every move
This was better when it didn't work and when you were having trouble
Really? Well now that the game works. It's just the game now true. Oh, come on
Well, you don't want me to watch a loading bar while I shoot drones
Oh CB CBD
Should destroy both the server and the drones. So, you know, yeah
Go, please
Heist made life a bit harder for the tyrants of the world
All right, I did it
Wait, he doesn't put his bare asshole in his computer chair, right? Why why do you think I put my
That to be a thing that was possible. I don't have to do the whole mission, right? No, I don't
You want you talking with me placing my asshole into the gamer chair
Permadeath no, I have to you have to unlock permadeath. No, that's not made up. You actually do. All right, let's teleport
It activates after this mission. All right, sounds cool. All right, let's do. Ooh. Look there. She is
AAA video game stream
On lunch
Build back our arsenal
We just need to show them
Yeah, I just need to kick the shit out of the people who are fucking up London only two of us forget
The fuck is that the city? I won't stand for that. We have another problem on our hands
Did we get a random person because I didn't recruit enough people
They took out dead sex once and it's a good bet. They'll try again
I believe they were responsible for the bombings and the construction worker. Okay
Killed the other two. Oh shit, that's right. We had five and I ran to him over the car. You're right
Permadeath is now active. Okay now if everyone dies the game ends
I only three people what I got permissions. Okay answer the call just digging up the power. All right, let's go with our
our Queen here
There's our Queen
Yes, Queen
Yes
Stop chat stop. All right, let's go aim. We have to recruit a couple more people 13 minutes. Does that mean?
potential recruits bodies people dead, but they dislike dead sick because I
Killed them. All right, let's do it. How do I? Oh gee
weapons
Operatives I would recommend bringing your team back to fighting strength or finding new operatives to replace them. Oh, shut up
Don't tell me what to do
Alright, we got I got we got some new shit here. How many points do I have? I have 30 points
Which we give to was this deep profiler
electro-fist
grenade launcher or a shotgun a
Non-lethal shotgun the grenade launcher. Are you serious? How do I equip these?
Wait, did you say this is a non-lethal grenade launcher? Oh, oh, is it full of fireworks?
All right, find the signal source at the tone attack site is to be do it in the menu. Okay, where is it store data?
team no edit here we go a weapons grenade launcher and
Pistol. Yeah, please. Thank you
Can I not equip this it is equipped? Okay. Okay. I have two slots
I was move his brain. I wouldn't even looking wait was this you just have a keg down here
Take another one Wow granny one beer one beer granny
What do you think can I drink and why does the beer have acid in it?
Why is it a different voice actor? All right, let's go. How do I get the fuck out of here? It's just a filter
Yeah, World of Warcraft did this 30 years ago. Wait, I think this uh, should I buy new clothes?
You can't jump over that and why is it when you get drunk music plays in your head
I'm just teleporting the fuck out of here. I can't can I new clothes?
Teleport to desktop. Damn it. Why?
Why buy clothes from a proper store still drunk? Yeah, I drank like seven beers in 30 seconds
Oh that horrible view game looks better now fuck. It probably does night
If I want to like the can I get in the taxi in the taxi take me somewhere? I don't want to do this
Auto-drive
All right. We're good. Oh
That looks like shit this way that way just wait that way
People saying self. Oh, this is gonna be cool in the future
Hey, I feel like self-driving cars are at the stage right now where VR was 15 years ago
Where the virtual boy was cool, but it hurt and it was not ready people like oh, yeah
That'd be we're gonna have self-driving cars. We're gonna be in those self-driving cars
You're gonna be like going to work. Just like looking at your watch while the car drives you to work
I think that's like a hundred years from now
You know how many roads have to be completely redone in America think about every road that needs to be repainted
That's not how it works. Doesn't it read the lines on the road with like I'm near me like a scanner
What does it just say? There's other cars around me. Be careful. It uses cameras. It's motion sense cameras
That's the already does it. Yeah
but doesn't don't Tesla's only do it if you're going like 60 on the highway and you're like staring straight because
Your destination it uses human brains, but what you guys don't know and what Elon Musk has been
I'm talking be quiet. Well, I must didn't tell you guys is it's just it's just people driving the car with a remote control
When you press the button somebody like bullshit, okay my turn in a giant center like call center
Okay, find the signal source at the attack site. Okay, sure. This is the worst fucking character to be right now
That's just in Guardians of the Galaxies. Thanks for the spoiler. I've never seen that movie
Need a key. All right, find the signal source at the attack site. Let's go who gives a fuck omega low
And when I talked about like season one of Game of Thrones two months ago, we're like, hey, hey
Don't say that. I get what all of a sudden somebody says that Guardians of the Galaxies
This is what happens at the end of the movie and I can't go hey
I don't think this character can do this mission not over the razor wire granny. Oh, there it is
Okay, I'm in. Oh, I need that. I need to hijack that losing signal. What? No, I'm right there. I'm right there
All right. This is the source the power right here granny on it. I don't think granny can granny go on it
I guess so. Okay, permadeath is on you're right. Why did I need to go?
Why did I have to pick her up and I just go in here on the source. Okay, I found it
Source of the power. This is a damaged spider-bot leg. What the fuck? Are you serious guys?
No indication yet who belongs to good god, it's been torn asunder
What is it doing here?
Difficult to say but with an AR reconstruction, we may be able to see what happened to it and if it relates to the attack
70% of people want to see you play a different game
I'll make sure you show up to the screen tomorrow. We're playing the little hope me and it's Alex
I'm gonna do a little help co-op man of a Dan
Anthology series that should be fun. Okay access the surveillance data is not very pog
Right now is it one's down or here? I've ran this guy
Again, alright, cool. Just don't let him up. Just fucking squish him. Oh, no, no, no, no, no, no
No, it's permadeath permadeath permadeath permadeath. Don't fuck around wait get to a vantage point and shoot
Don't who the fuck is behind me who's behind me. What's going on? There's nobody behind me. Who's behind me?
Get out get out granny get out get it. All right, don't matter swap to a new operative
I just did don't worry Jeremy the game will be ending in five minutes
Bring your team back to fighting strength. She fell off a fucking drone
What a way to go
Legal it was just stupid
It's alright, it's alright, but like I don't know I think I'm done
I'm think I'm done with it
Let me try one more time. It's the the missions are kind of boring
Okay, let's go over here. Not even three hours. No, it was like four and a half
I don't I want to I want to like I don't want to drive over that
Every missions I get like a fucking box
Get me in
It's alive. It's okay. He's alive
Missions in a square box surrounded by fucking walls. I know you have to hack and like I don't I'm not strategy guy
Hey, come on here and open up this door for me get a game over. You know what fuck it
This is where it was. I
Okay, don't buy this game. You have PC sucks
That's true. All right, it's true. My PC does suck. What's going on with this ever?
Increasing computer power that you need to play new video games if I computers only four years old. He's actually upset
I am NOT actually upset. I'm not even mad. I'm not mad. That was worst stream 2020. It's not my fault
Don't blame me. That's not it's not my fault the worst than skates pre skates pre actually worked you chose this game
I know I'm like, oh watch Dogs Legion man. They can like be anybody. I got grabbed by the marketing pamphlet
They got me they got me you're an idiot. No, that's a cool concept. You could play as anybody, but I should have known
Let's do a tier list. All right, we'll do one tier list. What do you got?
Maybe maybe more than one German meltdown stream tier list. Wait. All right, I'll do this one. Hold on. What else we got
Let me go pee. I'll come back. We'll do a couple of these the encyclopedia of sandwiches seems interesting. Okay, I'm into this one
Every Pokemon ever I don't I can't I couldn't name you one Pokemon if I tried
Artificial fruit flavors. All right, that sounds interesting. You got me least of the painful party members and never played it
What else you got? All right, well, we'll do these we'll do these will be soft games. There's an Ubisoft games tier list
Okay, I don't think I even need to do this Rayman is s-tier and everything else is D
Oh, wait, hold on. Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait. Oh, I don't know
This is a fair list is this this is not Ubisoft developed games
They pump that no more heroes is on here. They didn't make that game. I'll do it. Sure
All right. Let me just take a quick pee break up here back
We'll do this and I got to put a shirt on too. Give me a sec