This is so dumb. This is the dumbest thing ever. I love it.
Alright, are we ready to play Red Light Green Light?
Yes, yes, yes, yes, stop.
So turn around. Come over here.
And green light. Red light!
This guy right in the-
No! You're not supposed to taunt kill!
Look at all these.
So both of you guys stand over there. Make sure your sentry does not fire.
Make sure-
Be careful you don't fall off.
Look at that guy just did.
Oh man.
It's going to be very difficult to upgrade them because they're just going to start firing.
If you can get it, if you're confident you can get it built to level 3, then try.
But try not to kill anybody.
Oh dear. Oh dear. It's chaos. It's chaos. Somebody died.
Abandoned mission. Abort mission.
Abort mission.
What's happening?
Dude, this is insanity.
Well, okay, so I think we found a problem.
If one person dies, then it all goes to hell.
Everybody point your laser beam.
Let's go with the guy in the green hat first because he's standing up there.
Everybody point your laser. The friendly fire is on.
Everybody point your laser at him.
I want you to uber him and then everybody unload on this guy.
So are we all ready?
Yeah, on the count of three, uber him and then once he's ubered everybody just start annihilating him.
Ready?
Three, two, one, uber.
Get him.
He's getting pushed back.
Is he still alive?
Alright, hold your fire. Hold your fire. Hold your fire.
Hold your fire. Oh no.
Here comes the cottage.
This server is going to break.
Alright, so what we have created here, it looks almost like, it's like a caterpillar.
We've made an NG caterpillar.
This is actually like very, this is like very pretty.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no.
Bang, right there.
Make sure you got that Wrangler on.
Everybody get on top.
Let's hope it works this time.
Our beautiful centipede.
Our wonderfully beautiful engineer centipede that we've made.
And I want, everybody just move your, do a laser light show.
I want to see what it looks like. Just spin around everywhere.
Everybody spread out a lot.
That's good, that's good.
Everyone spread out a lot and then everyone aim at the ear.
And at the same time, count to three, everybody right click.
And let's just see what happens. Ready?
Three, two, one, click.
Alright, let's see what happens. Oh god.
Only one person.
This guy right here is the only guy.
That guy hit by one.
And look at how long he's stunned.
Wow, I did not expect that.
And three, two, one, go.
Yay, it's like fireworks.
Was it the same guy?
Blue pyro.
You should probably get over to the blue pyro side.
This is the red territory.
This is red territory.
Alright, get on, blue pyro's go, blue pyro's go on the blue side.
Red pyro's on red side.
This is not going to work.
This is not going to work. Oh my god.
Holy shit.
You are the scariest person I've ever seen in my life.
That is outrageous.
Okay, you just, you just, I have nightmares.
I'm going to have nightmares tonight because of that face.
Alright, you guys ready?
Only air blast, only air blast.
And whoever wins, wins.
This one blue pyro, get out of here, man.
You gotta get on the blue side.
Ready? Here we go.
In three, two, one.
Charge!
No, no, who used fire?
Somebody used flames.