Hello, what's going on? How are you? Wait, somebody said, you know, it's bad if he's playing Isaac.
What does that mean? Oh man, you know, it's bad if he's playing Isaac.
I'll give you, we'll talk about this for just a quick second.
Oh, let me, let me, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait.
There we go, I had to tweet it. I'm not even here. Just, just watch the fucking...
I'll be, I'll be back in like a minute. So Kristen goes to the grocery store
and she buys 15 apples. She trades those apples to David for 40 bananas. Those 40 bananas are
then turned into a banana puree and put on top of a cake, which is then sold for $100.
What was her first name? Yeah, I got you. I got fucked over from that one like a few hours ago.
I got fucked over from that one. It was like, oh, how about he and times two minus that. It was
like, oh, what, what was their name? Oh fuck. It was Jen. They got you guys too. Yeah, so today
I'm going to play Isaac today. I did say I was going to play it yesterday.
I also said I wanted to play city skylines, but I'll be honest with you,
kind of hurting today. So I figured I would just sit back for a little bit and play
something that I know how to do and just chill for a little bit. So, uh, took some Advil.
Just going to hang out. Oh no, fuck it. For those of you, I'm not like sick. For those of you that
are like, wait, what are you talking about? What? Why are you taking Advil? Uh, no, it's my back and
chest and shit, but I'll be all right for a little while. I just wanted to get that out there. So
city skylines, is it going to be the first thing we do? And I figured let's just do a whole stream
on it rather than try to do like two hours of Isaac, three hours, and then like go through like
four hours of city skylines. I'd rather just do a full stream on it. Maybe a few of them, but
that's the next thing we're going to do. But I do want to stream today and I do want to play Isaac.
So that's what we're going to do because I can't reliably tell you how long I'm going to be able
to sit here for. I'm going to be 1000% honest. I don't think this is going to be an eight hour
stream. No, I don't, not like last time. So without further ado, did I, did I tweet this shit?
I'd be very surprised. I would be very surprised. I'll go as long as I can. I don't know. This,
this whole thing's been like flaring up like crazy. It's like the last like three weeks,
it's just been like, fuck, I've also been doing like physical therapy. Maybe I'm like,
I've aggravated it and it's like, just maybe, I don't know. But anyways, I'm going to do anti-birth.
I'm going to try to actually beat the fucking boss of this game. I mean, I'm going to try to
beat the actual encounter. Oh, he's aggravated. Take it easy. Don't hide. Don't worry. I'm fine.
I am fine. Why I'm telling you already this, if it gets to the point like it already happened this
week, I'll just, I'll just call it, right? And we'll try again. I'm open. So let's go. Binding of
Isaac. Ooh, I just hit you. Where am I going to put my cheat sheet over here? That fits over there.
Watch out for the game cube disks. There we go. All right. Web cams not on, right? No. Okay.
I don't have any fucking clothes on. He doesn't want us to worry. No, don't worry.
Do not worry about me. Don't worry about me. Don't do it. Don't do it. Now, who do I want to play
with? And you guys have to help me here because seriously, I'm going to forget about the fire
shit. I'm going to forget about the puzzle stuff. I'm going to do Judas. What do you want me to
start with? I fucking love this game. I'm obsessed with this game. Just do random. Use mods that,
oh, this is a mod. This is Andy birth. There are other mods for Isaac. Random, random, random.
How do you do random? Oh, there it is. All right. Here we go. Actually spins a wheel. Oh,
god damn it. All right. Fucking Azazel. Really? Okay. Let's go. Do I really want to play as
Azazel right now? No. Azazel. Okay. I need, I need a warmup though. I need one warmup round.
Uh, this, this is not the, the, is how was it pronounced? Yeah. I need a warmup round.
Free lemonade. Yeah. Azazel is not the character you play when you warm it up. Azazel is the
character you play, but you're like, I fucking played like six rounds already. I'm not ready
to go off, like kill everything in one second. How do you pronounce it? It's a steam workshop mods.
What does this lemonade do? Azazel. Azazel. It's Azazel. Well, what did I say? Azazel.
I kind of like mine better. Don't you? Extra lemonade, whatever. All right. This is that.
This is, this is a delete. That's like, I got one heart. I think this is a delete scenario.
Have it your way. Did somebody just say the Burger King jingle? Hey dude, have it your way.
He's dying with Azazel. I'm warming up. It's a warmup round. Don't you know?
Now I gotta, there's a window here that's causing some kind of lag for some reason.
Don't ask me why. What's going on here? All right. My cheat sheets open in an iPad window.
All right. What else, what do I got? I'm going down here. He's already making excuses.
Yeah. That's what I, and I, I can do that. I can make excuses. I can say, nah, it's fucking
things. Fucking doesn't even work. Like I could say anything I want. I could tell you that my
control is broken. Like I could tell you that the analog of my thumb just came off when I died.
Like, oh, I died. Oh, fuck dude. My analog just came off and I have a dummy analog stick here and
I can put it on camera and people be like, oh fuck. I guess his analog fucking came off. That's
fucked up. I've never heard of that before. I don't ever trust anything anyone ever tells you,
especially me. Always, always lying. Fuck what a wash this is. Not yet. Not yet. Not a wash yet.
Okay. I'll just open it. Let's go. Ooh, good. Uh, those of you that have no idea what's going on,
this is, this is anti-birth. This is not the regular mining advisor. Do we have any tinted rocks?
I haven't, nobody's been spamming tinted rocks. I haven't seen a single
tinted rock spam. There's one back to the left because I got five bombs, two stone and one tint.
I don't think there is any. No, somebody would have been like, dude, it's in room A7. Be like,
oh fuck, right. What the fuck does this lemonade even do? I haven't even tried to use it. It just
makes you pee. I'm going to try. I'm using this next room. Nevermind. Wait, lightning. Oh shit.
Fuck it. Throwers. Come on Azazel. No, that's just that. Okay. Rock. Oh fuck. Not a lie. Okay. I
gotta start listening to you guys every day. All right. This is not over yet. The next one is two
bombs, right? You should listen to us. He needs to listen to us more often. I do. You're right.
What are these? Yeah, but I'm Azazel though. Like none of the cool items do anything with Azazel.
That's like the super tier, right? Left, left, left, left.
Mega tiers. Does that work with Azazel? Look at how long this takes to charge. One, two, three.
Oh my god. That's a shitload of damage, but I'm not going to be able to attack anything. All right.
I gotta queue it up before I go into every room. Oh, for the love of... God damn it, man. The hard
counter. Fuck. That sucked. Do I have any hearts? Look at the damage though. It's so good.
Fuck. Oh, it's so long. It's so long. I've melt bosses. I just gotta stay alive.
Yeah, he's right. Just go with a sad face. Damn it. There's no spirit hearts in here. I thought
that was going to be... Just go. Just go. Get the pill? This is going to be like tiers down
and it's going to ruin the whole run. If this is tiers down, I'm going to reset.
Ooh, what's this? Talus. Your feet feels... Oh, I can walk over spikes, right? So this thing does.
Okay, let's go. All right. It's useless. Bomb the left. Going to bomb over here. That could be the
secret room. You're right. You could literally fly. Right. Right. I can literally fly. All right.
Don't use all these bombs when I need this shit. Imagine being able to fly and buying fucking...
God damn it. I'm so dumb. All right. Beasel bub. Okay. Well, that was fun. HP up. That was... Okay.
This could work out pretty well. Get the nail. Get the nail. Get the nail? How much health do I have?
Wait, that's not the nail. That's a different nail. Yes. Get nail. Who cares? Get nail. Should
I get the nail? How many hearts do I have? If I pick this up, is it going to kill me?
You can't get the nail. Don't fall for it. Don't get the nail. Don't fall for it. What about this
thing? Get this for more hearts. Get them both. Do it. Please. Nail. You're a coward. Mask. Definitely.
You cannot get the nail. No, you can get the nail. I'm getting this. I don't want the nail.
I don't know. It's ruined. No, the nail... No, the nail fucked up the last run. You can't get the
nail now. No, the nail fucked up the last run. I don't want it. On principle. I fucked up... No,
I didn't fuck up the last run. Didn't everyone say that I was going to get three hearts for this?
I thought, guys, you guys said if I got gimpy that it was going to give me three hearts.
It gave me one. Oh, man. Who said that? I don't know. Somebody did. I swear to God. I read it.
Like, five times. Don't worry. It's not going to get hit. Fucking hard counter. Come on. Come on,
Ed. It's not going up there again. These things are rocks. The run... No, the run's not over yet.
Not over yet. Should have got the nail. I could have... Oh, my God. Whatever. Whatever's a warmup
anyways. Who gives a shit? Throw the fucking dice. All right. I'm okay with this. I'm okay with this.
This is Judas. Let's go. He's already malding. No, I'm not. You can't... There's no malding in
Isaac unless you die at like 48 minutes of a run at a boss. No, this is nature of the game.
Nature of the game. What is that? Rock blast. Okay. I've seen this before. Five bombs. Just a
reminder that you didn't beat Odama. No, I didn't. And I'm... Go ahead. You can tack that on my
permanent record. I don't... That's fine. I'll look at my streamer report card at the end of the year
or at the end of the semester. And yeah, okay. I'll get like fucking like a C minus in...
Didn't finish a fucking game. You didn't finish as many games as you were supposed to in 2020,
semester one. Because of what? You got an F on Odama. It just brought me down. I got like a
fucking C minus on... What was that one I just beat? Katana Zero. What was the last game that I
beat? What was the last game that I completed? What was it? Super Mario Sunshine. Okay, yeah,
that's fine. I'll take that. None. You're just talking over somebody else's gameplay.
No, I beat a game before that. That hurts me? What? Oh no. What the fuck? My own... That trickle
comes over and hurts me. That's such a good item to get though. I have seven damage. I can't fuck
this up. Oh, I didn't even know. That's so bad. Well, let's go. The run's not over. I got full health
again. He's never played Bomberman. You know, I've played Bomberman, but played Bomberman 64. That
was it. Stay away from me. Stay away from this fucking guy. Oh yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah. Fine. Not
even a single fucking hit. Oops. What's... What's that? Plus one to lowest stat. Oh, that's pretty
cool. At least I can move around fast. I need health. All right, let's go. Oh, beautiful. I need...
Oh my god, where do I stand? Right here. Fuck you, game. He never apologized. Sorry. I'll give you a
quick little tip on... I'll give you a quick little tip on playing games like this. Focus less on
where you're shooting and more just on your immediate surroundings so you don't get hit by
anything. Except for when things blend into the ground. This is a... Oh, I can't walk over here.
Okay, that was like... I don't even know what the fuck those things even did. Like, give me a break.
They just, like, appear next to you. That's a great tip. Yeah. And even... I was paying attention to
my immediate surroundings. Snakes were appearing next to me. Nope. No. App's a fucking loot,
Luna. It's the worst item in the whole game. Jesus. Old R. Right, right, right, right, right.
No rewinds. Well, you're probably wondering why is he doing this? Because I know I'll fucking walk
into it accidentally. You fucking die. Oh my god. How is he not getting hit? Pog. This is, like, not
even... God damn it. Stop making me laugh. Oh, you're fucking making me laugh. That room's, like, not
even hard. It was, like... I mean, it was annoying, but, like, I could have been fine. Oh, dude, how
is he not getting hit? Pog. Oh. Good thing this is a warm-up round. This too-tinted rock. Oh, this is
fucking bad. Game over. Oh, that was fun. Okay, let's do it again. Maybe we'll get a good run.
All right, just blow yourself up. It's just the fifth... It's the nature of the game.
Fight it. Fight it. It's the nature of the game. Mr. Mega blast damage. Okay, that's not bad.
Oh, dude. It's like the enemies are going like this. And it's like, oh my god, holy shit. He's so good.
Pog. That's so funny. That's gonna make me laugh for the rest of the day. So, thank you for that.
Whoever the fuck you were. I didn't see the name. Take that pill. Hold on. I've got these, like,
weird enemies. I gotta fight these flies. Okay, let me give you some insight.
If you play games and talk at the same time, you'll know. You know what I'm talking about?
Where words don't... You can't say them while you're concentrating. Your brain has to focus
on the concentration aspect. And you've been on the phone... I'll give you some... You've been on
the phone talking to somebody while you're playing a game. And they're trying to talk to you, and
you just let them talk. You let them just fucking rifle off a hundred sentences. And you're just
like, yep. Yep. Uh-huh. It's like, what do you think about that? And you have no fucking idea
what the hell they were even saying. Not a clue. And you're trying to reach so desperately to
find out what you could even say to make it sound like you were even remotely paying attention.
Yeah, that's pretty... That's pretty good news. I feel like... I just got in a fucking car accident.
What are you talking about? No, no. I'm saying, like, it wasn't your fault. So, like,
your insurance probably won't go up. So that's like the cerebral aligning, I guess.
Best friend. What is this? Best friend. I'm going to the ice. Cheat sheet.
Okay. Best friend. I've never seen this item. I just clicked on a fucking ad. God damn it.
Best friend. Places a decoy on the floor which attracts enemies and explodes after a period
of time. When it explodes, there's a hundred... Okay. The fuck did I just do? No. Turn that off.
Okay. That sucks. I mean, it might be kind of good, but get an item description mod. No,
it's more fun to look it up because I like to be challenged to use a separate device
to go to a different website to click on a fucking ad. So, no, I like to... I like to challenge.
Hold on. I'm too lazy to do what you're saying to, like, quit the game and go to Steam Workshop
and do that for, like, the next few minutes. Just tell Siri to look it up for me. Does Siri... Does
that work? All right. Do we miss any intended rocks? No, no, no, no. There's no way that works.
Like, hey, Siri, what does the item... I kind of don't want to do that though because it's like,
hey, Siri, what does Mom's tampon do? Well, Jeremy, um, you see... All right, there's nothing
here. Blighted. All right, no more mistakes, man. Oh, he almost touched me. Thank you,
Super Milk. This is the run now. This is the one. It's me. Oh, Super Milk. It's the super frog
voice for those of you that are not paying attention. Curse of the Giant? What does that do?
What's Curse of the Giant? Bike's on the ground. Oh, fuck. Dude, what the fuck?
That was fucking ridiculous. What? That's, like, not even doable. That's not even... You can't even
beat that one. Holy shit. That one... You can't even beat that one. It's the nature of the game.
You know what I mean? It's the nature of the game. Just restart. That was good. I promise I will get
to the third floor tonight. That was insane. People just running around with a bucket. They
were going so fast. What does Curse of the Giant even do? Curse of the Get Fucked is what somebody
said. They sell big rooms, okay. That makes sense. That's insane. They were all champions.
Give me some good... Something good. Oh, don't... I'm so bad at these. I hate these fires. They
really get me every time. Mine. Okay, good. Does the sour please? Yeah, that's a pretty good song.
That's pretty good. I like it. I like the... I like this mods. Hold on. Sorry. Don't... Don't tell me
about anybody. Don't, like, tell me any, like, bad news right now. All right. Now I can focus.
Toxic blood. Bad. Okay. So, what was I saying? I don't even remember. I have no idea what I was
saying. I don't even remember. See, I'm on the phone with myself and I don't even remember what
I just said to me. I have like the... I have a phone upside down next to an ear and right side
up on the other one. I don't even know what I just said to myself. Yes, the gamer brain. Oh,
right. The music. Okay. So, I like... I like this mod's title screen music more than any of the
other. That's going to explode. More than any of the other Isaac expansions or musics or original
game or... I like this one the most. This is kind of a shitty start as well. I like the title
screen of this. That's objectively wrong. What the fuck? Oh, no. Not this one. The, like, hardest
first boss. Don't make excuses. I want to see somebody say, holy shit, how's he not getting hit?
Body blocked him. I did that on purpose. I know I have a heart over there. See? I did that on
fucking purpose. Damage and HP up. That's good. All right. We got hearts over here. We got a heart
over here. I did that on purpose. I body blocked him so he wouldn't be able to get me twice.
If I didn't stand in that spot and get hit by that, he would have hit me twice. Speak words?
What are you talking about? I said body block. What do you think I said? Like, body wash?
What are you talking about? I'm very bad at this game and make excuses for every time I get hit by
an enemy. Oh, by the way, in case you didn't know, I wasn't even looking. I didn't understand,
but plus two anyways. Good effort. All right. I hate these little things. I need a key.
I need bombs too. I hate them. When it turns to the meat chunks, it's the worst
because they come back. This guy had a coin, right? Or a battery. Oh yeah. Don't pick that up unless
I need it. All right. This guy's going to shoot out. Yeah. I know what you do now. I know what
you fucking do now. Not going to trick me a third time. Rock. I'll get the rock. Don't let him come
over here. They all go in a straight line. If I would get hit. I got to get that. Okay. So
you guys, when I get to the point where I need to do a puzzle for the second knife piece,
you got to like, I need to see spam. I need to see like attention, attention, attention. You need
to say the word attention when there's a knife piece that I can get. You have to get my attention.
I'm not doing that. I don't have any keys. You missed a rock. I only have one bomb though and
I need two. Hold on. Come on. Give me a key down here. Well, I, no keys. Yeah. I mean, I could go
here. Should I, should I blow up the heart guy over there or was it secret room left or right?
What do you think? I need two bombs. Tinted rock. I could get a key out of the tinted rock, right?
Attention, attention. Donation guy. Yeah. The rock could give, well, let's see what happens.
Let's take our chance. Well, it, yeah. Well, now what? Now I can't get the item in the second room.
Attention all Fortnite gamers. Ah, go to the sacrifice room. No, I'm going to lose all my
hearts. Let me just kill this guy and see what happens. This is a bad room to fight this guy in.
Hey, all right. Where are you? Wait, what the fuck? Holy shit. I didn't even know that was a
right. You want to push here. You want to push one into your lowest stat. Here you go. Hey,
you're a lucky guy now. Oh shit. Wait a minute. That's not, how was that number? Why is that my
lowest stat? Isn't luck my lowest stat? All right. Now I'm going to sacrifice a bunch of hearts to
this guy. Give me some shit. Give me something. Beggar, the beggar. Yeah. This guy. No, I don't
want the coin beggar. I want this guy. This guy's going to help me out. You can use him twice for
one. Well, I don't know. I don't know the exploit secret room, but I need a bomb. Do I take my
chances? Do I take my chances and give him like the rest of these hearts? The coin beggar. Where's
this coin beggar you're talking about? Is he on the other side? Is he up here? Oh, he's, oh fuck
yeah, he is. No, this is going to be all my money. All right. I'm going to get here. Take it all.
Ray. Take care. Come on. No, not another fucking card. Do it again. Again. Fuck, is this a lighter?
You have to reset now. Just reset now. No, I can't just reset. No, it's the nature of the game, but
just anymore coins lying around. Somebody look under that couch. Any more coins? No, no, I'm not
holding down R. I'm not doing it. I got the world. I'm going. I'm not holding down. I'm not resetting.
Hold R buddy. No, look, there's things I can't do. Whatever. Just I need to do like a fucking run.
I keep getting in trouble. Okay. Well, easy, easy, easy. I need a key. It's salvageable.
This is salvageable as long as key. Take a room. I need two bombs though. Whatever. You gotta make,
you gotta take chance. Okay. So I blow up the, I need two bombs for that. That's not worth it.
If I get a key, I'll be okay. It's salvageable. Where's this guy? What's left? What's left?
I got three bombs now. Go to the left room. Secret room. Key is inside of you.
Blow this up, right? Blow this up. And then I go down and let's hope it's a cool item. No,
it just skips the level. It's not a ladder. Sleep in the bed. Minus one bomb. No, no, don't tell me
to hold down R. Look, I can, I can, I open the door from here. The door's unlocked now, right?
Yeah. I can walk out and unlock it. Hey, well, look at this. I can skip. Just give me a key
and this can be salvageable. What does the fighter do? Oh, fuck these enemies. Oh, fuck you.
Got it. Bomb the beggar. I, I don't want to do that yet. I need two bombs. Remember?
I need two bombs to get the heck out of here. Okay. Set. Run saved, I think. Run saved.
Yeah. Can we, should we, should we get a translation? Yeah. You know the drill.
I don't know what either of these two things do. It hurts. No, it doesn't. Okay. I guess it
doesn't hurt. Bomb into the shop. No, I need two bombs. If I bomb into the shop, I'm going to lose
a bomb. You're playing on keyboard. I'm playing on controller. What do you mean? Eww. This is,
it's a top, it's like a top down shooter game. I'm going to play on. We won't play keyboard? No,
my fingers will hurt. That'll hurt my fingers. I've tried it before. All right. What's this shit?
Not, oh, it's a knife piece. Got it. Okay. This is now, I can't, I can't even use this because I
can't, I don't have any bombs. I know I got the knife. You don't have to do attention. I don't
have any bombs. So this is over. Well, that's fun. If I blow it, maybe if I blow up the beggar,
they'll drop a double bomb. Go into the shop. All right. I have three coins.
Boss could give bombs. All right. We'll try that. If I skip the level, is that going to,
all right. I need some Isaac veterans here to tell me if I skip the level, will it bring me
to the anti-birth level or just go to the normal level? I don't, this is the first time I've ever
seen this boss rainmaker. Not that bad so far. Oh, that is that. Okay. Tears and shots beat up.
That's too bad because look at how good this is now. It goes to the normal level, but you have
the opportunity again on the next one. Really? Fuck. That's just more damage, but I don't think
I have enough hearts for that. I have two. This is just a waste of time. Okay. So we're going to
bomb the beggar and see if he drops two bombs. Oh, wait, wait, wait. I, could I, could I go into
the store? Okay. Go into the store and buy two bombs, buy key and open door. Oh my God.
God, how many keys do I need to open this? Holy shit. I think this, we, okay, we just did a math
problem. We just did long division. What is this? Son to a clubs motherfucker to a club as bombs,
right? Yeah. What does this thing do? Born to rock Tara. What does this do? Born to, born to rock.
This is that. Holy shit. I can't believe it. Wait a minute. Oh man. Okay. Now I got to play like a
champion. No fucking screw ups. I'm going to, I'm going to play like an absolute champion now.
Make sure I need to be, you need to have my attention by the soul heart in the shop.
I don't think there is one in there. There is. Okay. Here we go. Let's go bomb the door.
Keep moving. Make sure you get my attention. Oh, he doesn't work. Doesn't work. Make sure I need
that second piece. Every tinted rock is a free item now. That's a huge deal. Don't blow this.
I'm going to blow this, right? I'm going to like, I'm going to like do like the Kylo Ren voice for
no reason in like 40 minutes and die to the boss or something. Someone's going to be like,
Hey man, I'm driving through McDonald's. I can do the Kylo Ren and McDonald's. And I'll be like,
getting hit by a fucking truck in the game. It's going to happen. No, it's not. I'm ready.
I need two spirit hearts at the end of this. This is XL. So this is it.
XL extra large. He's going to blow this like he blows all of his money. How do you know what I
do with my money? What do you know? Okay, we can. Okay. No, we know where it is. Okay. Yep. All
right. Right. Soul generator. Oh yeah. It's starting to look, this is starting to look up.
Keep the ball rolling. Free. Free. Now just give me damage up and another tier is up. Oh, it's not
free. Free rocks. Nice. Okay. Yeah. Yeah. I can't take that off if I touch it. What does it do?
It's good. I'm not touching it. Chat is mental. What? God damn it. It's all right. I didn't know
that's what that, I didn't know that's what those things did. No tinted rocks. How have there been
no rocks tinted? This is XL. Why are you guys beeping? What's the, what's the, why the, what's
the beep? I don't understand. Stop destroying the rocks. I have to. There could be, there could be,
the rock could be in here. Got one. Oh wait. I sometimes. Hey, what's that alt saying?
Scared money. Don't make money. Oh no. No, hide. Hide. Just hide. I'm safe in here in my fucking
fort. Go the other way. Dig the other way. Dig the other way. Dig the other way. Dig the, dig the
other way. Is that it? Is it, is it over? I don't know. I can't tell. Oh shit. It's just like
Minecraft. Should I dig up? No, don't dig up ever. I'm going to dig into a bomb. I know it. Is it
going to be like going into the lava? Is it open? The door's open. It's over. Okay. Hold on. Let's
just break every rock. What, what, what, what, what, what, what, what's going on? Was it not
supposed to do that? Oh, don't do the attention thing. That's only for when I have to do the
secrets and do the final boss. Oh, okay. Let's go. I'm not fucking around anymore. Don't break.
Yeah, but how do we know if there's any secrets? Don't put that down. What do I do? Okay. It's,
it's the, where the pebbles are. The order with the pebbles. So top. Okay. It's the pebble order.
So this one first. Top right, bottom right, top left, bottom left. Got it. Knife piece number two.
And a tinted rock. Fuck you. Oh, there's a, there's a monster in there. Okay. Good. I've got it. Good.
Good. Okay. I got both pieces. The last piece is with the fire. It's got to get there.
I need a key. Okay. Let's go. You've got jumpscared by a rock through the mushroom. Oh man. I should
have listened to you an hour ago. It's probably a tinted rock in here somewhere. No. Yup. There's
the key. Hey, what's that old saying? Hey, what's that old saying? It's in a BB unit.
No. Go back and get, get Tammy's head. I don't want Tammy's head. I want the book of Belial.
Hey, what's the old saying? You know, it's in a BB unit. Yeah, that's the one. Tammy's head is good.
I know, but is it as good as being able to have like maximum damage? Just use Tammy's head.
You know what? Yeah. I'm going to use Tammy's head temporarily because I can use it every room.
What's with the beep? Stop beeping. Why are you guys beeping? I'm beeping. I'm beeping.
There's the key for the, uh, oh, it's the song. Okay. Any, any tinted rocks? Do you see any?
Attention. Use the head. Go to use the head. Where are I? Hey yo, tinted rocks. I don't see any.
All right. We need, there's another, um, we're going to go to the shop. It's time for the shop.
I also need, all right. Important. I think I'm going to buy the spirit heart. I'm also going
to buy the map. Full visible map. Nice. Is it tinted rock? Okay. I need the other, uh,
I need the other room. Jesus Christ. Okay. They do that. All right. It's just a pattern.
What's the dice guy do? One of these, I think it's just money. And the other one is,
I don't know which one of the, isn't that, isn't that like just a bunch of money?
Right, right, right, right, right, right. All stats up is right. Are you serious? Oh my God. I'm
guaranteed victory, guaranteed to win. And I'm going to beat that fucking bot. Don't forget about
this. Okay. Now I can go down. Let's. Oh yeah. Fucking idiot. This is a bug. This is looking
real good. I just can't fuck up the fire thing. Hushroom. Fire. This is good damage so far. Good,
good tears up. Don't touch that thing. Don't even go. Don't Jeremy. Don't think about it.
We're good. Let's go. Almost just fooled me. Here we go. Wait, attention, attention. I need the,
the book, the book of Belial. That's correct. Yes. That'll go get it. Attention. Attention.
Gamer. Where is it up here? What did I leave it? Two bosses in a row. Yep. And then we'll deposit
two hearts and we get to get to the end game. Where is this fucking thing? Oh, it's down here.
Yeah. I'm not, I'm not going to use the book until the second boss. That's the smart play.
That's the play that gets you into the big leagues. Challenge room. I don't think so. I don't, I don't
think so. I don't think I'm going to do that. I don't think I'm going to do that. That's no,
that's a teeth room. No, I don't want to do it. I don't want to do it. I'm not doing it. No,
it might be good. I don't know. I don't want to do it. I'm a coward. I'm a coward.
This guy, this is a bad place. Fight him. Clear it. Clear it. Clear it. Clear it. Bad item. Very bad
item. Just beat him through. Look at how good this is at this boss. This is, this was built,
was made to kill this boss. What's that? Don't usually have to blow that thing up. That was a
hard counter. Was it soap? Don't pick that up. Tears and shots beat up. Oh my god. Let's go.
Let's go. Any tinder rocks? I don't see any. No, right? Yeah. Okay. Cool. Deposit. What the hell
is this again? Just take it. Don't question it. Okay. Just don't question the run. Yeah. All
right. I'm ready to go. Don't let me fuck this up. The regions after every room. Well, that's
incredible. Don't let me mess this up. When we go down here, when you, if you, I, I, I'm going to
have chat attached to the bottom of my fucking eyelids. So when I blink, I see what you're
writing. So good. Just don't ever shoot a fire. Yep. And no, and no, no Kylo Ren impressions
for the rest of the day. Oh, my kid. Should I get this? It's better than the lighter.
No, it makes chests red. Yeah. Where's that thing? Press forward. Press forward. Rally. Rally. Oh my
goodness. This is that's two. That's double shot. That's double shot. No. Oh, it's not.
That's X ray vision. Oh, it's still good though. It's better than the floating eyeball. Oh, I
thought that was double shot. I was going to say this is over if it was strength. The world. Oh,
um, does that really matter? I guess I'm just, I can know where everything is.
There it is. Okay. All right. We're going to carry around strength for the boss.
We're going to go down here into the item room and yes, um, I'll take another spirit heart,
please. Okay. Here we go. What do I do? This is not, this is not it. Attention. Attention.
Leave. Okay. Well, I'm just gonna clear shit. Attention. I need a key. Okay. 10. I can go
over here though. There's no fires in here. It's free stuff. Oh my God. Jackpot. Oh my God.
Is that item? Is this an item? Oh, okay. No, I thought it was, I thought there's a pedestal.
I was like, Oh wow. Cool. Death. Death. That just scared the shit out of me. Yeah. Dead.
All right. Plus one dead. Dead. Dead. Ooh. Shot speed and full health. I take every pill without
even looking at the, whatever the thing is on the label. Here we go. I'm going to go up.
I've got to find this secret room. I have a lot of bombs and then we get the third piece. I get the
the knife go up. Okay. Uh, attention. Remember there are signs over the map that correspond to
signs on what? On the puzzle? The presses. Attention gamer. Attention. Why did that just
happen? No, I don't want it. I'm good. I do need a key or something, right? Wait a minute.
I've got to get over there. Do the challenge. You're a coward. You have max health. Yeah, but
this is not a point for me to get cocky and do dumb things that I know I'm not capable of.
I'm capable of it. Let's do it. Fuck yeah. Let's go. Ooh, there's a third. No, this is wicked.
Fucking easy. I don't even need that heart. Not a key though. So am I in trouble here because I
can't get over this? Buy a key from the shop. I need to buy a key. Bomb the spikes. Knife pieces
next floor. Break the spikes. Oh, I can just shoot the rocks. Shoot the rocks. Step on them at random.
I need a key though. I'm so paranoid because I don't know what to do. Touch the button. I'm
going to buy a key. This is not a puzzle. This is nothing to do with a piece. Okay. Well,
fucking who cares? I'll go buy a key. I don't have any. Well, I'm going to blow this up.
Stop it. What? I want at least 15 bucks, man. I'm not throwing this run down the toilet. All
right. Let's go do this. Okay. So we're looking for, let's open this. Alrighty. Let's go. Well,
I got plenty of health everywhere. It surrounds me. This motherfucker just spams at you, huh?
Thank God. I just, I can just take hits. Who cares, man? Hit me. Hit me, Mr. Rock. We'll get
it on the way back. Whoa. This brain popped out of his skull. Wasn't there a, uh, wasn't there a game,
an old board game where you pulled boogers out of a person's nose until their brain popped out of
their head? What the fuck is wrong with that? Why? What was the point of that? Yeah. There's a,
there's a board game where you pull boogers. Gooey Louie. You pull boogers out of a guy's nose
until his brain fucking rockets out of his skull and you kill him. I'll play it on stream. Yeah.
No, you know what? Fuck it. Okay. I'll get all the old fucking shitty board games. Play them all.
I'm talking about like slobber and Sam. Posted here. Pound it. What's this? Oh,
it walked into a fucking fire. Two of spades. I'll take some fucking free shit. What's the game
with the ice where you like, and, uh, you don't want to break the ice. I think it's just called
don't break the ice. I think this was called. Play it on stream. I'll do them. I'll do them all.
Don't wake daddy. It's going to be a complete fuck face stream. All right. What's this, uh,
rock you guys talking about? It's rock. Elephant, the elephant. Down. I can't even hold them all.
What was that one? Mr. Bucket. I got the balls in my mouth. Mr. Bucket. Out of my mouth,
I'll go pump. I'll get that one too. How's this? Oh, good thing I don't have very many of those.
Another one of these. I don't want that. They have mainly mouse trap, mouse trap. Okay. I will,
I will play mouse trap, but it's going to be a scenario where I don't even play the game.
I just set the trap up. This is what everybody did. I used to have that game when I was younger,
when I was a kid, but I never, I don't even know how that game works. I've never played it.
I just set the traps up and then just play with them and like put the mouse in it and stuff and
have the, like the Rube Goldberg machine happen. I don't even know how that game works.
I don't know. Has anybody actually even played that game once to the point where they, what is
this? Key? It feels lucky. I mean, this is kind of bad. I think keep the lighter instead. Watch the
world burn. I actually didn't, it fucking sucks. Keep the key. Keep the key. Keep the key. I gotta
look it up on my fucking binding of Isaac. What do I do? Cheat sheet. What's it called? The key.
Key. It looks like it. Rusty. Gives Isaac a higher chance to find keys and chests.
Yeah, that's way better. What does a lighter do? A lighter. No, not laughter. iPad. Lighter.
Chance for enemies to burn when entering a room. Am I going to need keys? Yeah, let's go do it.
I'd rather have that. The enemies burn. Look at my damage. What's wrong with my character?
Why's my character all fucked up? Go into the curse room. Go in the curse room. Fine. It's free.
I'll take it if it's free. Did you do the puzzle? The puzzle is in the next floor. That's what I've
been screamed at. Okay. Is this a, is there a heart? There's one in the regular room.
Puzzle is the next floor. Yeah. All right. Take me back. It's time. Let's go. I'm going to save
the, I'll use the book, but you know, whatever. Who am I fighting? Siren. This is new. Probably
give her a chance. Where am I? That's weird. And that is speed and shot speed up. What do we
got in the devil room? Don't want it. Although I guess I could just take it. It's going to be,
and it's, it's going to end up being just free because I'm going to be at infinite hearts.
I mean, it, I know it's useless. You're right. Blow up her skull. Oh no, I didn't do it.
Oh, too late. As we'll restart the whole thing. Okay. This is important. This place is huge.
I have to be careful. Temperance. Okay. This is just a blood donation machine.
Just blow it up. Lucky toe has appeared in the basement. Okay. Money. And the love is just
hearts. So we're just going to, we're going to put these down on the ground. We'll come back
if we need them for any reason. Nice keys. I can't believe I got hit. I might as well fucking never
stream again. Use the teleporter. I got fucking hit. I may as well eat a shoe on stream. Oh shit.
Hold on. Wait, wait, wait. This is, uh, this is gonna, this is, this is really fucking crazy.
The bottom one, from what I remember, makes your tears fire and they can fucking explode.
It's sad. That might be a little too risky. It hurts me too. Top one is safer. Explode and kill
you. I'm going top. Knockout. Yep. This is the... Whoa. That's cool looking. It actually flies out.
A hand flies out. What do I do? Is this it? No. Wait, what did I do that for? Oh, I can't get that.
I can't get that. That move is so cool. There's a heart there. Ow. Oh, I walked into it. I've
walked into it. I've walked into it. It's okay. Plenty of healing. Ooh, I'll take them both.
Ooh. Answers. Vision. Do it. I have the world. Oh, okay. Well, I know I'm not going this way.
Let's go over here. I want to go into the, uh, the shop. Oh my God. This is the shop. This is
just the shop, but for free, but I already went in there. None of this shit is even necessary.
Just put the money back. All right. 500. Take the pill. Shot speed down. Ban every person that said
to take that pill for at least two to three minutes, at least. Come on. Come on. Come on.
Ah, just a net loss. Great. Thank you. Okay. The stars. That's just the shop. Go donate. No,
I might need this money. What's going on? Why didn't... Hey, it's supposed to blow it out.
Is this it? Is this it? Is this it? Is this it? I see two... I see fires in a room with no enemies.
Don't... I'm not going to put out any fires. Do I have to put out any of these fires?
You know how it looks. Why are you asking? I, I don't know because I'm fucking nervous. I'm
stupid. Mom's pearl. Now I'll keep the pearl. That's more soul hearts. That's more soul hearts.
Yeah. Oh my God. Okay. Good. I'm just, I'm unfucking killable. I don't lose unless I
accidentally blow out a wrong fire, which at that point I'd be very upset with myself.
Remember how this one started where it was like guaranteed. I was not going to be able to do it.
Let's punch through all three of those guys. That was insane. I wish I had more luck.
We punched that guy's brain out. Oh, I didn't even see it. Oh, I didn't even see it. All right. I
gotta be careful here. Attention gamer. There's a rock. Attention rock. Where is there a rock?
What are you guys talking about? Where is there a rock? He's lying. He's lying. He's lying. Okay.
So where is the fire room? Where is it? The big room next to the boss. Zero. So don't touch any
fires. Don't blow out any fires no matter what. I don't care where they are. This one up here.
You motherfucker. Okay. So where is it? All the way to the right. Oh, I gotta do this shit again.
Okay. All right. This way. No, it's probably this one up here. Um, just get it. Can I just take it?
I can just take it. There's no fire puzzle. Just pick it up. There's no fire puzzle. Don't blow out
any fires. Just pick it up. I got it. All right. Let's go. I got the knife. Now, is there anything
special I have to do to get to the last, this last area or no? Just beat this boss and then I get to
go through another door. That's it. Let's go. Shit. Oh my God. It's stumping. We're good. Ah,
okay. I was supposed to do that. Do I pick up anything or just go pick up the Polaroid?
Let's go. Mom's heart. What? Wait, what? Wait a minute. Does this, is this supposed to be
happening? Oh my God. I just took like a fucking million damage. Leave? Jesus. Okay. So here's like
the, here's the real, the real tunnel to the, oh God. I can't leave. I'm going in. This is
rotten heart has appeared in the basement. You're in corpse. Okay. I got to play smart
because I need to fucking get some hearts. Nothing there. Let's get some good shit in here.
Good shit only. That's not good shit. That's not, that's not good shit either. Where am I going?
In Krampus. Of all the assholes I didn't want to see right now, I don't want to see you,
but I'll take the coal. Back to what we were doing. Okay. Good. Very good. Poop wine tears.
I'm gonna say down. Keep your distance. Keep your distance. Just don't let them come near you. Just
knock them the fuck up. Okay. We're good. Oh my God. It's another one. Oh, okay. Can I destroy
those? No. Well, it's obviously not over here. You're doing so badly. I haven't gotten hit since
I came down here. What are you talking about? I haven't taken one point of damage. Um, this is
different. Let's just, how does this thing do? It's like a broken needle. It's trinket, right? Let's
see. Let's cheat. There it is. Broken syringe gives you a random syringe effect to every room.
Well, um, it could be bad. Too random. Too random. Too random. We're not going for, I don't know
what that is. That's like a, uh, like a box tail. We need to work in certainties right now. I got
a lot of money. I don't know. I'll never know what these guys do. Okay. Who's the, who's the boss?
Keep him away. This is it. Oh man. That's going to be even more, isn't it? Holy shit. Oh my God.
Okay. I'm ready. This is un, this is impossible for me to lose, right?
I'm going in. I don't even care. I got full hearts. I got a book and I got strength. Three, two, one,
go. And I was going to hold reset on this shit. All right. Well, there's my evil up. Okay. What
do you got for me, devil? Nothing. It was Krampus. Let's go. Take the deal. What deal? This is it,
right? This is the end. Orbs two. Look at those. Look at those three huge rooms down there. What
the fuck? Holy shit was insane. You see, you know, I do, I can do the way I can do the book of
all hell twice. Yeah. God damn it. That's what I want. There it is right in the middle. You don't
even need that, but I want it. It has nothing to do with needing anything. It has to do with wanting
it. What am I going to spend it on at this point? It's just a thing I want. See, that's why we
collect these things. It's tier delay. It's this is like soy milk. Come on. Yeah. We want the
cosmetic. What just happened? Oh, poop hat or riot. What do you think I'm trying to do?
But what do you think this is? I'm very clearly trying to get the shit hat.
Use the blood bank to get yourself to one heart to have the Polaroid be active.
Did I do that? Did I do that? Did I do that? Like that? You have to be at half a heart. Oh,
well, I can't. If I do that again, I'll die. I'll pick up half a heart and then do it. Okay. Cool.
What does that matter? How often is that going to activate? It doesn't matter. So why did I just do
that? I'll get it. I'll get it. When I get hit, I'll go invincible. Every time you get hit,
you'll be invincible. God, I love this game. Don't you just love this game? Don't you just love
having a 20 of everything? Don't you love getting the poop hat? Is that I'm not leaving till I get
it? Just don't accidentally touch any of that shit. All right. I'll do it here. Here, here, here.
There you go. Hey, nothing. I picked up a fucking stupid heart.
Attention. Okay. I don't care about, I'm leaving. I'm, I don't want to do it anymore. I don't care.
Use the machine when you have a shield. No, that means I'm going to get more money
and I'll have to sit in here for like another 20 minutes. Just scam money with the shield.
I don't want any more money. I don't want any more money.
All right. Okay. Scam. Don't do it. Stop, stop, stop, stop, stop. I'll do it accidentally and die.
Don't do that. Where's my poop hat? Where's the hat? This kills me. Okay. I can get a troll bomb.
I'm leaving. Okay. I'm done. I'm done. I'm done. I'm done. I'm done. No, bye. I'm not going to get it.
What was that? You only get one chance. Wait. You only get one chance. Or somebody just saying
that to like save the stream. It's a hero. Oh, I don't want any more hearts. Come on. I have 10
chances here. Hold down. I'm not going to do that because I'll walk into the fucking enemy.
You should need to hold R to activate your shield. Five chances is it. I'm not going to even get it.
It's not even going to show up again. One more chance. That's it. Yeah. Sorry. You don't get it.
You don't get a poop hat. Sorry, guys. Don't. I don't care. I have 28 keys. Do we think I
give a shit about this? Let's go. Wait. What's that? Why is that hard to have shit on it?
Wait. It's blocking the door. It's blocking the door. It's blocking the door. Okay. I'm fine.
Don't pick it up. It's blocking. Can I move it? I'm going to blow a bomb up next to it.
I'm out. I don't care. I don't care what it does. I don't want it. You owe us a poop hat.
Is that full health? This is not going to give me like health. Oh shit. No. Stop opening chests.
No more opening chests and shit. There's probably hearts in there. Give me a fucking break.
Don't touch anything. No, I'm not. I don't care about the poop hat.
Don't want to make a new username for it. I don't care. Get out of the way. Get out of the way.
Blocking my shot. I heard something. I heard a... Excuse me. Excuse me. Come here. Oh, a bunch of
drugs. Okay. Should I just take this and just forget about the shield? Because I mean, you're
talking about like three or four hits that I can't take. I'm going to carry it with me. I've got an
idea. We're going to do health up again and then I'm going to do full health if I lose these hearts.
You know what I'm saying? If I go down to one spirit heart, I'm going to do...
Am I an idiot? Is that a bad idea? All right. I'm just going to take the health up. But what
about the strength? You'll lose it. Holy shit. Okay. Fuck strength. Just heal and use strength.
Full health just makes you lose health. Just take the health. Who cares? Take strength and leave.
What do you mean take strength? I can't leave? All right. Okay. All right. All right. All right.
Take the full health, not health. Okay. All right. I'm ready. Let's go. Let's go. Let's go.
Let's go. Let's go. Let's go. Let's go. I'm ready. I'm ready. I'm ready. I'm ready. I'm ready.
I'm ready. Use strength now. That's not going to do anything. It's going to disappear.
Use it and take the strength. I'm going to go up my gut. I'm going to go up my gut.
Where's all this stuff? What's that radish thing? Did I get it? What does it do? Delicious. Rotten
tomato. I'm going to witness. And you were concerned. And you were concerned. Oh, is that
not it? Look at the little spider shank. What happened, dad? That was so easy. I killed it.
That was so fucking bad. I was like, what should I do? I got fucking 21 damage and two tier delay.
Pull up skull. Well, that was fun. Why is there a helicopter overhead?
More? Use every bomb. Oh, that was cool. That build was really, really, really powerful.
Kaldama has, you unlocked Jacob and Aesop. You unlock challenge eight awakening. You unlock
challenge nine, seeing double. What did I unlock? What the fuck? Jacob and Aesop. You play two
people? That seems kind of cool. I'm going to see what this looks like. What? Wait, they have their
own health bars. This is some ice climber shit. I don't know if I can handle this.
They get different items each or they use the same item. It's cool. What happens if, all right, can,
can like, can like papa get knocked off the stage? This reminds me of Lilith, but way cooler.
So if one of them dies, do they both die? This is going to be a pain in the ass. Yes. Oh God.
Uh-oh, wait. Uh-oh. Wait, you can't, how do I make them go back together again?
You squish them to the wall. Okay, there we go. They can get stuck. You got desynced.
Oh, yup. This is, this, I know I see where the trickiness of this comes in. The trickiness of
playing this, uh, Ben and Jerry, what are their names? Jacob and, and it's, what is it? Aesop?
I'll get that key. Don't worry. I'm just clearing, but they both have the effects of whatever item
you pick up. Read the Bible. Oh, sorry. Okay. Yeah. Yeah. Sorry. I'm not caught up with my,
with my fucking Bible lore. I, I have to, I, I, sorry. Yeah. Let me, let me, let me read
the Bible real quick to figure out who these two are. This, this isn't like infinity war.
You know what I mean? Like the idea that I haven't read the Bible in a very long time.
Who ha what's going on? Who has that? Where is it? What just happened? It was used. It's used
instantly. They use pickups automatically. What the fuck? Why? Hold on. So I can't use any pickups.
Mr. I don't have anything to blow it up with. I want an item room. They auto use pickups because
they can each have a different active item. That's bizarre. That's weird. I could see this being
really fun though. If you get some, if you get like the Ouroboros tears, whatever the ones that
spin around and like anti-gravity and shit, this could be really, really cool. Oh, that's unfortunate.
That's unfortunate. I mean, just use it. No, they use it automatically. I can't,
oh, this is not, they, that doesn't just fall on the ground. Oh, that's a reset right there.
If I've ever seen one. Recept Randy. You would reset too. You would reset too if you were in my
position. Wait, is it the monk I asked question mark? Is that what we should be doing? The book
of Genesis speaks of the relationship between, I don't know, the book of Genesis, guys, I don't,
the only book of Genesis I've ever read was when, was when like fucking GameStop used to come up
with the cheat code book for the different consoles. No, don't pick it up. Oh, oh, here comes a reaction.
It's pretty fucking good. Oh, oh, looks like we ain't going to the underworld or whatever it's
called. Don't stand over there. It was, yeah, I know I saw it. Genesis, I know you don't have
to, we don't need, this is not like the Bible study class. Who's taking it? Yeah,
we can have item rooms. Where the hell is the item room? Oh, gonna have to start dishing out some time
outs here. Gonna have to start timing people out for their misbehavior. Oh, gonna have to start
timing people out, but they're unbehaving. Wait, they both don't get it. Only one of them gets it?
This is so confusing. Oh, so you have to, you have to plan out how, who's going to be what character.
You have to like play, oh, they get separate stats each. This is so cool. Let's see if I can get that.
Just jack up one character. Yeah. All right. What if I just make one character insane
and just make sure the other one doesn't die? Where's that tinted rock? Give every health item
to one person and give every damage item to another person. And then the one, but the health
just stands in the front. Okay. This is what the, yeah, it's out of here. Fuck. One of them's almost
dead. Who's, who's the bone in the bottom right? Red guy or green guy? Okay. Red guy can't get hit
anymore. Oh shit. Smush. It's Mario and Luigi? Oh God. Yeah. It's too confusing with.
Watch out for that fire. Stop. I can't move. If I move up or if I move down, one was going to get
hit. God. That's okay. Ah, shit. It's okay. Watch out for super frog. Nothing. Just give me an item
room. Damage or something. What? I can't die. I want to bring these two into greed mode. How
come it doesn't exist? Jesus Christ. Does that mean I get more than one key? So if this one key
does that mean it's actually two keys? Can I walk in with one of them and not the other one?
Oh, I can't get that. Wait, I can't like stand on his shoulders? Easy. That's unfortunate.
What's the seed? Here's the seed if you want it. I don't need to restart yet.
I'll be happy if I can kill mom's foot with this. I'll be happy. This internet itself is almost
like a challenge mode. Hey, that was erratic. I don't tell them you need to plug in another
controller. Oh, this is also really bad too. What? What? I can hold. Oh no. That's. I was trying to
tell you that. Well, um, so I can just play the game with this one and just make sure this one
doesn't get hit. Why would I do that? All right. You stay over here. I just like swallowed air
for a second. Relax. Might as well re-roll the enemies. Whoa. That was very, very close.
Something worth taking. It's not re-roll enemies. It's not like the wing thing, whatever it is.
Oh, bad. Oh, this is bad. Oh, this is bad. Oh, I have a wicked itchy head. Okay. There we go.
Dude, these two guys, these two suck. It's not me. It's the, it's them, not me. Oh my God.
Well, refill your health. All right. If it's not a really good item, I'm going to, I'm going to do,
undo character. That doesn't break. Okay. Who's going to take it? Red guy. You take it. Uh, yeah.
All right. Red, red guy is going to, red guy is going to be the drug taker. I think. What? Red guy
is food tester. Here, red guy, eat this. See if it's poisonous. Yeah, it is. Okay. I'll make sure
not to eat that one. Good. What a shitty place for this. Oh, don't get hit by that. It's going to
shoot me again. What? Look at this. Okay. Red guy. That's mine. Damage up. Not bad so far. All right.
Can I make red guy walk into the spikes? So we can, I guess I needed that health. Damn. Red guy,
do you need health? No. Do I? No. Rock. Where is there a rock? Oh, up. I don't see it. Left and up.
Nope. Flies. Whoa. He jumped very far. Okay. What is it? Who's going to get it? Okay. It's lipstick.
Yeah. The fucking way. Red guy. It's mine. You can have the next one. Red guy.
They go through. Now they're going to do that. I want to do regular game. Destroyed on red wine.
Uh, it's pretty good. Remember, if there's a tinted rock, make sure you go. German. I see a tinted
rock. I see one. I don't feel so loud. It annoys me. All right. Red guy. Okay. Good. Very good.
Oh, he leaks. I didn't know he leaked. He leaks. God. I'm all right. I'm gonna. Oh my God. It's the
fucking die. All right. You each get one share. I see a tinted rock. Where? Those dumb enemies. Dumb.
We should take it. So what does this do? It spawns flies. That's pretty cool. Oh, that is pretty
cool. It doesn't really matter. You just take it automatically. From what? What happened? I'm
going to go from both sides. Oh, wait, wait, wait. We're going to move. Oh, I'm so stupid. I didn't
think that through. I had to move. Okay. Hold on. You need the red guy. Go get it. I didn't think
that's through at all. Okay. What is it? Oh, yay. He loves it. He loves it. Let's go frozen in fear.
Hey, oh, come on. What do you have to explode? What's the point in that? What's the point in that?
It's you just make, you're just trolling your audience. You're trolling your gaming audience.
Okay. I died. I actually died. Wait, I have an idea. Okay. Good. Now those, those items were
trashy anyways. You know, like what I got, I got mom's, uh, like tampon thing. Not even worth it.
I didn't get any good items. Red guy got hit like four times. Wait, um, did they both get a familiar
if you pick up a familiar? Oh, what was this game? Not even worth it. All right. Uh, who gets drugs?
I, you red guy, you do it. Speed is good with these two. They both get it. Nice. So they shared
the drugs. I know. I see it too. What was that? Oh, it was the stupid exploding bug. All right.
You know, who's taking it? Why did it hurt me? Wait, he said, did he took the drugs and then
slap me in the face? Well, this is going to be a pain in the ass, huh? Restart.
No, not until I, not until I fight the boss. Oh, we're dead. We're like so thick together.
Oh, okay. We're good. Dog food. Red guy. I don't have any keys. So we have to go down.
No keys. The German hates restarting. Well, not okay. If I don't get any keys, I want to
play as a different character, but the random, you have to go with the random. You got to roll with
and that's the nature of the game. I want to make these two work, but I might not be able to.
Red guys piss. Excuse me. All right. More drugs. Shot speed down. Can I run faster than the shots?
Are you serious? That's so stupid. Bomb, bomb, bomb. It's a bomb. It's not a bomb. Split up.
No. All right. It's not, it's not bad. It's not bad. We just need a key. I got a leap on you.
Grandma, I see a rock. I see a tinted rock. You do? No, you don't. You don't see them. What are
you talking about? See how thick they are? No keys either. Right there. Oh my God. Horrible room.
Who gets the jawbreaker? Why is there not a third, why is there not a third Ed brother?
I get it. I need health. Is there any hearts lying down on the ground somewhere?
There's not. This is bad. This is, might be a reset. This might be a restart. It depends
on what happens here. Holy shit. I was, did I eat it? Okay. Hog food again. Well, we may as well
just have them both be the same, but there's a devil deal. Okay. Holy shit. All right. One,
if you take the kit. All right. One, if you take the collar, why don't you take the tail?
Hold on. Will he die? He'll die. All right. So what if you take the collar and the tail and then I
make sure you stay alive. Okay. Red guy. What are you ruined? Why? Times one. Was that joke funny?
I don't know. Still can't get in the item room. That sucks. Oh, dude. Drinking game. Drink every
time Drew says, this is bad. Sit. This is bad. Oh, no, this is bad. Oh, it's bad. You're drinking
fucking water though. No, not anything else. So there's a water drinking game. You take a shot
of water. This is church. You know what I mean? Like, oh, we're taking shots of water. You don't
have to drink that alcohol. No, we don't. No, no, no, no, no. Place. Come on. Big place. Big place.
Run over. Oh, are you sure about that? Run over, huh? Run over. Run over. Red guy. Get it. Look,
I'm playing every Resident Evil game that had co-op after 2008. Oh my fucking God.
That hurt my whole body. That actually did hurt. It sucks. Fuck.
So does it matter who picks this shit up? I guess you got that one.
Isaac won. Okay. I'll allow it. I'll allow it. Pretty good. Pretty good. Nice work. Okay. So after
we completely fucked that whole thing up. Opening. I see an opening. I see an opening. This guy's
fucking insane at this game. Imagine like you just came in right now and you're like, imagine like
you like it and you like it and you like it. How many times are you going to say fucking like
and the same fucking like? Like, set and select fucking like. Imagine like you. Imagine you come
in right now. Speed up. I don't want speed up. It's kind of sucks with these two because they
run into walls. Jerma, I see it. Tinted rock. It doesn't matter who gets it. I need keys. Have
I found one key in the whole time in like three floors? Oh, there's one. Whoa. That was close.
Blow up. Blow up. Blow up. Key. Okay. Now I need. Should I open a? Hey, scared money don't make money.
Back to Bob's brain. Bob's brain percent. It's over. Okay. Like if you could hit go,
if you could make a bet right now and you had like, let's say it was 500 to one odds
that I wasn't going to die in the next one floor. Would you take those odds now that I have Bob's
brain and one heart? Like, would you take that? Would you do that? Would you be like, you know
what? I think he, you know, it's a huge fucking chance, but I think he might be able to do this.
Would you put like 10 bucks on that? What happened? Oh, wait, why? Where's Bob's brain?
Where's the? Oh, there it is. Okay. I got a little concerned there for a second.
Hold on a second. Just have red guy die every time and I, I'll never lose. Just have him get
killed every time. That's going to kill me. I might as well like just, just play as a different
character at this point. There's no way I'm going to live. These two are cool, but they really are
very difficult to play. Oh yeah. I was going to do a Bethany run. Wasn't I? I'm going to try. Oh
my God. Everything. Watch out for that fucking brain. It's okay. I'm never going to just go in
a different room. Just go in a different room. Oh great. Super wrath. I get this too, with these
two, it's too hard. I'm too concerned about Bob's brain now and I got to move them both around.
They're both super thick. It's triple the hit Bob. Did I even know the item room yet? No,
I don't have the fucking key. Jump Bob. What's still life? Okay. We can continue.
Sorry, I can never lose. I can play as many times as I want. Don't leave me. Don't leave me. Don't
leave me. Oh my God. I almost just killed him with Bob's brain. Back up, back up together.
All right, we're good. No key. This is like the kid that's rented out the arcade and gets as
many coins as he wants. Oh, versus Chad. I could see that. The thing I got Bob's big ass brain.
Dude, I could. No, just do the regular game. Do you think I have no chance? Do it. Do it. Item
room. I can't get into the item room. You're immortal. Literally immortal. Yeah, I'm immortal,
but I can die over and over again. I still have to not get hit. Secret room. Where's the secret room
up here? This is training right here, right? Well, let's just cover all of our bases. It's
like one of these slots right here. No, what the fuck? No, what the fuck? Line up with the door.
What are you guys talking about? No, you can't use brain. Yeah, but I just get to time travel.
I get to just go back in time. I get hit once and I die, but I can do it infinite amount of times.
All right. Who thinks has better luck at the casino? Red guy or other guy? Oh my God. I just
panicked through Bob's brain. We need hearts. No. I can't. Just blow it all up. Fire the brain. Fire
the brain. Fire the brain. Retreat. Retreat. Retreat. What is this one? I just unlocked it.
Isaac's. You get a sword. Wait a minute. Is it an actual melee weapon? Dude, you can. I'm going to
be real good at this. I think I found the thing that I can do very well. I'm going to kill every
boss in less than a second. How much damage does it do? Do I, does it get damage up? Why can I find
this out in the wild? God damn it. Let's go. Guga flies. Oh, that's, that's really interesting.
Really cool. Like a character you are. Um, let me introduce you to a fucking 39.2 mouse clicks a
second. What's this? Still hit. That's fine. If I take one heart, I'll spam and kill them instantly.
Yeah, I don't want to do that. I'm going to item room. I can pick the rocks up. Yeah, that's yep.
There is no item room in these challenges. Is there? No, there's no item room in challenges.
Coins. Fuck. You have the bracelet of strength. Re. Pick up coins. What the fuck?
I'm going to get them. Wait, where? Why did that just not show up on my fucking mini map?
You have the bracelet of, yeah. Okay, let's go. Slow down, MonkaS please. Does the shield block
all projectiles or is only some? This is a really cool item though. Is this added in
anti-birth or is this an item that's in the base game? It's from anti-birth. Oh,
okay. Got a big arc too. Um, let's, let's just go, um, hold on. Uh, let's go kill this boss instantly.
HP up. Not like it matters, but I could maybe try and find a key.
Beep. There we go. Finally. No rocks. What about this? Gonna pick a throw bucket.
Ooh, I have money in it. That's cool. So all of them have money in them. Um, I just got a fucking
item. Blood sucker. That's a little leechy. All right. Item room or just pray. Thank you.
And I have enough for an item in the item room. Look at that. Perfect. Too bad. Too bad. Wait,
what? Hold on. I can, I can hold it out. It's a lance. Deck of cards is good. Yeah,
but I have rock throw. Replace it. I mean, it won't replace it. This is a, oh, it's a passive.
I thought that was the, and there's the sun card. Okay. Well, I thought that was the one
that was the active that you had to activate. Let's keep going. It doesn't get the reference.
He hates Zelda. I don't, I don't play Zelda. I don't play Zelda. I play FPS games. I need money
for this. How do I cycle between the cards? Right? There we go. Yeah. I need money before I summon
him. Throw them, throw them all. The buckets seem to give you good shit. This game is literally
Zelda. It's not. It is literally star tropics. Sorry. It's not Zelda. It's star tropics.
It was inspired by Zelda. It was inspired by star tropics. Hard counter countered. This is really
fun. Get Ed on the line. It was inspired by star tropics. How are we doing? It was inspired by
the Bible. Wait, do I need to collect these? Why do I need these knife pieces? Why do I need these
knife piece of shit? Why do I need this knife piece of shit? I can't even use it. Do I have to get
the knife? This is a challenge. I can't believe that fucking hit me. Wasn't everything inspired
by the Bible? Fuck it. Thanks. Everything was inspired by the Bible. There's no bucket down
here. A lie. The Bible was inspired by the Bible. They made another one. They wrote like three of
them. Yeah, there's like the Old Testament and the New Testament. The Third Testament. I'm not
opening that door. Let's go. Oh, fuck. He's doing another move. Fuck you, man. Nice. HB up, tiers up,
shot speed down. Okay, so let's go. You're a walking cheese grater. Wood chipper. Laugh and
Jerma laughs with you. It worked. Have you ever considered that The Binding of Isaac was inspired
by Zelda? It was inspired by Star Tropic. Fool. All right, look for, uh, yep. March it, Spider Rock.
The Bible. Play it safe here. Just fire at them. You know what? I can't even get over there. There
we go. Stupid. Poked your head up. Coin on the table. There's a coin on the table. Jerma, coin
on table. Someone else will pick it up. I leave stuff behind sometimes so other people can like
have some fun and collect coins. I keep thinking this little leech guy is a bad guy. It should give
him like a big blue outline so I know. This game looks and plays nothing like Star Tropic. Um,
that's spoken like somebody that's never played one second of Star Tropic. Have you? I beat Star
Tropic when I was 11. I think I should know. Look at how much better I am with this melee involved.
Streaming. Star Tropic is grid based. This is not good. Okay, guys. I think it's time to
put this to rest for you once and for all. I think it's time to put this shit to rest.
Once and for all. Sorry. What, what are we watching right now? What's this? What? That little
fucking little maggots on the ground? This is, uh, Zelda. Zelda came before this. Oh, yeah.
No, it's inspired by Star Tropic. And by the way, the song is fucking, this song is an absolute
banger. Uh, uh, Mike, Mike Jones. I think this, that's the main character's name is Mike Jones,
right? He's going to be in the Smash Brothers DLC pack number two. He'll be the fifth person.
Now put on Zelda. When it starts, Zelda NES. I've never played Zelda. All right, let's put on
Zelda NES. Okay. This looks like a fucking wildly different game to me. What's going on here? What's
going on here? I don't want to play your fucking MMO. Get a move. Let's go. Oh my God. I don't
want to play Roblox. Oh, look at this. Just like Isaac, huh? Inspired by fucking Star Tropics.
By the way, Star Tropics came out December 1st, 1990. When the fuck did Zelda come out? 1993?
Yeah, I knew it. Zelda. Legend of Zelda. NES came out on, uh, February 21st, 1996. So sorry,
guys. That's not who copied who. Star Tropics. Fucking sick. You guys only played it. You would
know that it's inspired by, it's inspired the binding of Isaac. Wait, there were games before
Fortnite. Ow. I blocked projectiles. Why am I not using this? How am I not? I have so many keys.
Just go in. Isaac was inspired by GTA 3. I thought you could drive a car in this game. Oh, too bad.
Fucking relax. What the hell am I doing? Oh yeah. I'm done. I can't block those? Oh, that's not good.
See? I told you I could pick up the TNT. I can't. I can't pick up TNT. Fuck. I'm, I'm done. I'm done
for. I can't just use the only thing I'm good at, which is pressing a button very fast. Block every
shield. Oh, this sucks. Oh, fuck. This is bad. I can't get over there. Like, that thing's gotta...
Oh! I didn't block it. Fuck. All right. What? What? What? What? What? What? I made McMillan's
that. What are you? What? What? Let's copy Zelda and Meat Boy to copy Mario. Just make it
your own and be true. I know. Fucking Zelda is one of the inspirations. One of the many inspirations
of Binding of Isaac. Bomb this guy? Does it work? Doesn't work. It's one of the many inspirations
of Binding of Isaac. Star Tropic is one of them. You never mentioned Star Tropic once
ever in any interviews. Oh, come on. Are you sure? Okay. If you type, if you type it, this is where
it gets sad. When you type in Binding of Isaac Star Tropic, there are only four pages of results.
And when you get to page three or page two, you get, you're going back to like 2008 of,
that's almost impossible that there's three pages on Google. Look, I never said that it was the
direct inspiration for Isaac. I said it was one of the many factors in a long line of clearing
enemies in a room and then the door opens and using keys to go in those rooms. A long line of those
games is what I said. Binding of Isaac is directly inspired by Zelda, Star Tropic and viewers like
you. Coming up next is Arthur, episode 380. He gaslit himself. This is what happened.
There's a hot, there's a hot backpedal. What? I don't know. You play Star Tropic?
You'll see. There's items, an item shop in Star Tropic. There's little maggot enemies that go
when they fly over. Look, I know. I've played it. Fuck the technique. Yeah, well, thank you.
Give you some hearts. You know, not yet. Zelda had hearts. You bet they laugh. Yes, Star Tropic
had hearts too. Dermot, if you say the word Star Tropics again, I'm going to lose my mind.
Said like, okay, this is ridiculous. Unbelievable. That's unfucking believable. All right. Bite
them. Eat this guy. Eat them. Eat them. Eat them. Eat them. You're not eating them fast enough.
Eat everybody. Star Tropics had religious imagery and, well, Star Tropics was aliens.
So, I mean, they're fucking aliens in Zelda. Aliens in the Bible.
And then that is when, that is when Peter spoke upon the large alien creature when they landed in
their spaceship. Peter could be heard saying, look at this. You laughed at that. Don't even,
don't even start with me. You laughed at that. I know a couple of you didn't and you feel like
the fucked up. I didn't laugh at that shitty joke, but it's okay because I know for a fact
that at least a hundred thousand of you did. Okay. Can you, don't ever go against technique.
Any tinder rocks? Anybody see any? There's 5,000 people there. What do you mean?
What did I say? Jawbreaker. I see a tinted rock. Do you? Are you making that up or do you really
see one? I don't see one. Oh no. He lost 95,000 viewers. That would be bad. This sucks. This
sucks. All right. Eat them. Look, it's my guy versus your guy. You're a lot bigger and stronger,
but mine has more perseverance. Get him. He is doing the rat emo. Good work. A lot of you guys
over here. All right. You finished the job. Aha. That's two for two. I don't see a tinted rock,
but that's thanks for the input. Full health. I think I'm going to do this shit. I think we're
going to fucking be able to do this. All right, so bite him. Kill that one. Okay. I'll take out
this one. You get this one. Get him. Get him. Get him. Nice. Um, up there at top right. Okay. No
tinted rocks. Name the leech. Um, okay. I'll name the leech. How about, um, I think it's something
that I would be able to remember. Something I can remember. Uh, oh, here's something I could
always remember. Star tropics is a better game than Zelda. That could be that. That could be
his name. Easy to remember. He's never played Zelda. Watch out. What do I do? Oh, I don't know.
Maybe I can't get over there. Oh no. No. Oh, it's okay. I was going to say he's not my friend
anymore. Oh my God. There's a teleporter. What? Blow it up, right? Blow up the head. Wow. You know
what the, you know what the Zelda game was? I'm being honest. I mean, Ocarina of Time's great.
Um, I still play Breath of the Wild, but keep up the pressure. Keep the pressure up. Don't even
let him attack. Just keep the pressure up. Casino. Stream Breath of the Wild, please.
I would probably really like it. Another dumb card that nobody wants. Um, speed up. I'll take it.
All right. Here we go. Give me some stuff. No, I want to blow these up and I don't even want
to do anything. Oh, come on. I want money from these. It's like the game can't even hear me.
You can't hear. Hello. Can you hear me talk? I'm going for it. Come on. Oh, he stepped on his head.
Fuck. Okay. She knew. I can come back with more money. Why can I pick up these rocks?
Pick it up, man. Pick up the rock. Where's my face cam? Sometimes I don't have my face cam on
because I don't want to be on face cam. Sometimes I'm camera shy and I don't want to be on cam.
All right. Finish the job. And yes, I don't have any clothes on. People think that's a joke. They
really do. And that's fine. It's actually probably better that way that you think that that is just
me messing around. But I am sitting here right now. I don't have a shirt on and I'm in pajama
pants. And you'll never know if that's true. No. You know what? No, fuck it. I'm wearing a suit.
I'm in a tuxedo right now. Do I need to do this? Wait. Fires. All right. Fires, right? Holy shit.
No. Who's this going to take me? Oh, interesting. Interesting. That's interesting.
Oh, what the fuck? Why? What the fuck? Oh, they shoot. I forgot the purple ones shoot too. It's
just a net zero. Wink. I don't do winks anymore. I'm not that guy. I don't do that anymore.
You gotta be fucking kidding me. One more for the road. No. Is there a reason why I cannot pick up
rocks anymore with this gauntlet? I can't pick up rocks. They're special rocks. I'm not talking to
you until you wink. Are they going to keep splitting? I'm going to just come on. Do I
actually have to do this? Oh, guess. Good thing I got the bomb back. Oh my god. Oh my god. Omega.
Oh my god. Fucking maca. Omega. Oh, I see what's going on. I see what's going on. Oh, you're not
talking to me anymore. You're not talking to me anymore. I see. I see how it is. Not talking to
me. Now I'm being silent. Dude, I don't want you to... Hold on. Two hearts. Two spades. Just take it.
32. But the Hario cares. The hermit is the... Halgalaz. The lovers explode now. What is this?
Leo Stompy. Nice. Not nice, actually. You guys can give me the silent treatment all you want.
Broken watch or something? Give me that heart. Okay, you gotta kill like one or two more bosses
anyways, right? Remember, you might mute. So is yours. Let's see who cracks first.
Oh, don't these guys look at you and just go like. R.I.P. What do you want me to do? You want
me to wink? No, you gotta, I'm not gonna have you guys be like a defiant unruly baby. Y fell.
I'm not going to do anything until you do this. Oh, don't move. Okay. That's good, I got it.
he's three okay they're all lit except for the okay so it's all the ones in the middle all the
ones in the middle over here and then a smiley face over here that's it all the ones in the
middle over here and then the smiley face and that's it good guys this is we're never gonna
end up we're gonna have to come with some kind of compromise because there ain't no fucking way in
hell i'm putting clothes on right now so wait there ain't a chance to help oh my god i can't
put a good hit you guys are really into this all right is it next floor is it this floor somebody's
gonna crack and tell me it's the next floor right one of you is gonna crack one of you's gonna crack
and tell me next floor right yeah it's the next floor yep thanks for that one person good job
i know i have a bunch of fucking like supporters in here it's wait i don't even need it it's already
open oops i didn't get the
he's being reckless i win the challenge i win the challenge i win the challenge i win
oh fucking great again the game crashed
uh they're starting to crack fuck all right you get let me go back in is that gonna kill my game
this happened last time too what's going on at this point it's bullshit continue isaac
sides with chat um i have to do this all over again really i beat the boss why wouldn't why
wouldn't it shave there i don't even want to do this i like already have everything i need i've
just where was the boss i'm gonna crack i don't remember it was like over here somewhere right
i don't fucking remember it really should shave though it's like unfortunately it doesn't
don't tell him fine i'll just get there quick and quick
still keeping it up that's fine good outcome 50 dollars from chunky baloney 5000 bits
holy shit that they say nothing they say dot dot dot is it thanks to the 50 fucking doll
wiggle worm oh that's too bad where's my validation you will accept if i say speed
no i'm sorry once you once you give into demands i'm not giving into demands that's that's over for
me i'll never be allowed no good i'll have no negotiating power for the rest of the time i
have a live stream i'm not giving into your demands 50 dollars from 5000 bits from goiki
goiki five fifty dollars from two people in a row which is huge amounts of fucking money
goiki says hey germa just really happy that you're playing binding of isaac it's one of my favorite
games ever made and it is very exciting that the new expansions coming out although sad
that it is going to be the last one that's true uh anyways thanks for the content over the years
really appreciate everything you do and chat doing the silent act thing is really really really
childish and i can't wait to at least stop doing it oh thank you goiki appreciate that
thanks the 50 dollars it's a lot of money two diamonds hold on to hold this i need money and
i'll come back all right don't fuck that up chat's cracking i think i can last longer than chat
guys come on you're referring to a group of people that if i spend more than eight
minutes in a tutorial they they freak the fuck out i think i can outlast them piece three where's
piece two tinted rock we've got a cracker we've got a cracker thanks a lot ah more health for me
thank you we've got a chat crack no not what the fuck no like you've cracked you've cracked all
right i gotta kill the boss you cracked you oh fuck wow isaac okay polaroid oh my god my eyes
are wicked itchy and all right moving on i can't believe this is gonna be the last germa stream
what are you talking about all right fine all right we got 50 we got 50 5000 bits from
red planet of mars who says hi chat will you at least say hi to me please that's 50 dollars
hi hi hi no hi oh there you go thanks for the 5000 bits dude it's a lot of fucking money
thanks for 50 fucking bucks and then an anonymous cheer gave 5000 bits as well 200
fucking dolls and bits have come in in the last five minutes i thought you guys supposed to be
being defiant you're paying me tons of money you're getting you're like you're rewarding me
they're pity bits they didn't get a chance fucking idiot fucking idiot fucking idiot fucking idiot
fucking idiot five community subs from arison arison we also had five community subs from
straight puke and uh super bruce both gave five community subs don't tell me what don't tell him
don't tell him don't move people just give him money and doing dot dot dots defiant chat
were you there the day that chat finally was defiant to the streamer were you there and they
didn't crack if a one person cracked they cracked how do i get through this what the fuck
will you dare today will you dare today i'm gonna lose in here what use the suicide king
oh yeah um sure the thing that has suicide in its name is the thing i'm gonna use right now
we're winning there's no competition here all right if i promise i'll give you a a wink
at the end of the stream can we go back to the way it was can we go back to the way that it was
before okay and what if i lie to you and i don't then what happens we'll never trust you ever
again the chance that we are all gonna have to take open your mouth i'm dead i'm dead i don't
think i'm gonna make it through this i've been too distracted with all this nonsense going on in my
chat room i've been very distracted i know how to get you guys to crack you see if there was ever
a thing to make everyone command me to stop it would be hearing the bane impression maybe i'll
do this for the remainder of the screen i'm not bringing out that one i'm not bringing out that
i'm not bringing out the a word sorry hey you know i can do this shit too you know
i'm just turning the camera back on like i'll just cam back on by the way um i ain't ever doing that
ever again all right i want one more one one more one more one more one more i want to try a real
a lazarus want to see the lazarus strategy i'll show you how to play lazarus lazarus is you just
die immediately just die and when you come back to life you get extra stats it's really really
simple okay here we go boom now you play the game i just did range down i took the pills now we
i should restart because it was bad pills i'm gonna restart try it again cursed room is free
because you're lazarus oh here we go that's so much fucking money coming oh my god what are you guys
doing fuck we had 50 dollars from trans scout and 50 dollars from goiki and goiki says actually
best bit we did it chat and then trans scout says hi germa trans rights hi how are you did i already
lose the hearts i i actually just lost the hearts already thank the both of you for the 50 fucking
dollars that's a lot of fucking money there's been like 500 dollars in the last like 16 minutes
i should hold winks back from you more often oh come on really okay i gotta stick with this but
seriously thanks a lot guys that's a lot of fucking money you guys have been giving a shitload
like always and all i can say is thanks and that star tropics is a better game than zelda i mean
it's all i have with me right now that's all i can say don't you dare
no you don't get two that's the thing you don't get two zelda it's better it's okay it's better
you know it's a better game than both of them solitaire i've been around for like 600 years
come on i gotta get one more good run i want to just beat like satan again
or perhaps mega satan if i can get there yeah i want a mega satan run we're going down
when you can play solitaire i actually don't know how to play solitaire i have no idea i just
pretend like i know how to play and then i put like some of those car i have no idea how to play
i know you just you go like up i don't get it like i get it but i don't you go like is that bad i
understand it's like you go okay you have to go in order but i don't understand the rows and i
understand like the the deck at the top you just like you click it and it gives you a bunch of new
cards you take that card but i don't get it i swear to god i don't know i've never i don't play
it first charge shot kind of not good it's kind of not good at all it only works because i have
the penetration this is not a restart yet oh yeah if i didn't have penetration it would be
i'm all right this is not terrible whack whack see it's better it could be really really bad
but it's not it's not it's good oh i see another tinted rock is going off my hair what do i mean
this item is so bad but there's a chance that i'll be able to get like quad tears or something it's
possible a lot of tinted rocks okay it that's pretty good okay and i gotta come on like that's
pretty good i'm gonna investigate a little more kind of pog i guess kind of pog i guess
yeah yeah what did that come from oh that kind of pog i guess i guess
there's been a tinted rock in almost every single room whatever it's not a big deal
not a big deal at all pressed it really slowly that was a kind of pog i guess not a big deal
at all wasn't it i guess what somebody's called hey guys the link dinks hold on wait wait i need
to read this michael comes in and says the worst part isn't that they now have footage of you
winking in a bathrobe but that the wink dinks think their solidarity solidarity action will
get them everything now good luck to him i love you streams that's what i was afraid of but it's
okay remember all i have to do is just wave my magic fucking wand and they'll just i thought
they i could make them disappear what stop what the fuck it's oh it's the cursed charged shot
well this really is the shittiest item in the game isn't it link dinks well here's the thing
you just gave them a nickname that they're going to repeat and love and they're gonna cherish it
and they're gonna say it they're gonna be the it's the link dinks now and i bet you they can't wait
to gather and i yeah now they have now they have a name oh my god i can't even
dink i'm not gonna i can't handle that i'm getting free money uh there we go there we go
hey dinks and chat close it up so yeah city skylines what we would do later on this week
if you were curious this is new it's a new item all stats up super meat boy fan oh that's cool
that's not bad we swear over four it was five damage right at the very beginning
did somebody wink the dinksters i'm glad you guys are having fun glad you're having fun what about
me don't i get to have fun don't i get to have any where's my where's my like where's my dink
winker oh this item is great actually good item wait no it's not hold on this is this is not the
moment you collect the bugs and you can have five oh i thought this is the one where you if you're
going to kill things you collect it and you can release them what does this thing do collects
i see a tinted rock where where do you see one now in the shop oh okay i can't even do anything
about it okay we're good okay not very good wait somebody's asked me if i if they could have my
skype no i who uses skype bugleberry get on skype
scissors lose your head wow that item is very very bad what a bad item doesn't do anything it's not
even as good as the empty jar i don't know what the jar does six room recharge yeah that's
ridiculous is it just me or we've been getting some really really really foul um finding of isaac
seeds i'm getting some pretty foul ones is it just me why did i just use that right there
there was no reason to do that oh i like wait i got to the jar i have one heart in the jar how
many can you put in there bugleberry calling you on skype pick up how much can you put in here
four you guys said this item was bad this thing's actually pretty good what's wrong with this thing
why were we getting so many antipods and i collected this finding of isaac is so fun it
really is just a fun game it really reminds me of another game that i like that's a good game
serious sam three he's so big do you know how many times i've uh thought serious sam and duke
nukem were the same game up until like 2008 or nine or so i thought they were the same game
okay what's in here i got the nail everybody can relax why is it a spirit heart though i
thought it was devil hearts you can't beat mega satan now why not not with that attitude oh man
just can break the fucking rocks you know there's no barriers there are no barriers why do i keep
acting like there's barriers in place i'm not restarting i don't need to i'm acting like i have
i'm constrained you need access to the angel rooms oh right that's true well it's all right start
thinking about what our city skyline name is going to be for the town when i come back later
this week i'm gonna have a efficient awesome town do you have rubyville uh i don't no i don't
know about that one i can't get over there nobody said that that was great
okay wink dink city fighters watch out wink dink city access to the nail there's no um
nothing in here to break that almost just got me that almost just got me tip of that just barely
got me odell tip of that just got me odell tinted rock what are you talking about there's no tinted
rock pay attention boomer where's there a tinted rock in this oh good thing i opened it now i don't
have access to the nail holy fuck i almost hurt myself two bombs oh relax man attention
we got big damage now seven point one eight i want to keep looking around folks right now
we made emergency surgery in the studio why is that on my mind they're all free all the chests
free i love these things these little guys girdies what are they called little girdies
mini girdies tech point five it's still being tested so wait i get to keep my tears but i also
get the lasers that's really good that's really really good oh okay we might have a run in the
bag here good tech let's go learn it another room too we get free doors you flatworm nice
it oh i could still use it wait what happens if you combine tech point five with tech two
what if you do both texts what happens that's too much tech that's tech one this is tech one
they stack do it do it do it do i i lose 0.5 g i wonder what happens if what happens i'm gonna
i get take it moron it's omega tears omega lasers it's worse no they stack why would you lose it
take it and find out at least tell us the seed this one just google it you fool what are you guys doing
let's see a few seconds oh that's unbelievably funny unbelievably fucking funny
okay for a few seconds but that means that it was in the brain at some point during the development
that's it was up there somewhere he's had experience why don't i just walk into this
whoa it's doing triple lasers that's so fun this is so good look at this shit
it's open every door who cares this game is so good do i get the eraser do i get the bra
what does the bra do bogo bombs oh buy one oh that's gonna get annoying
money printer go brr why did i just say that i don't know because somebody wrote it
it's the two plebs what are these guys names the two plebs now i just need tears up thank you
thank you thank you oh that's not very good it's only 0.63 i thought it was tears up carrion queen
term of my queen you guys are fucking crazy yeah i've seen the tweet i've seen tweet and please
but i don't i don't want to have to uh you know obviously this is very very um basic info but
please do not like harass anybody or like spam a developer of a game because we're having a
little fun here okay just let's be let's be real about that just don't like it bad you know i'm
saying he was doing a q a i can't i can't even i can't even say something that's like nice and
good now
guys stop harassing this guy he's like doing an ama at the moment oh my god i'm fucking done
i'm done i'm done i'm just gonna okay okay this is a really good build i gotta play
this is like a guaranteed kill satan run chat just can't stop winning right now where's i
supposed to go running out of steam here i just can't stop winning there it is and there it is
and there it is translator i don't know what this is i'm waiting for other people to be excited
about it so then they'll say what it is in the chat and i'll just pretend that i don't
this is i don't i take less damage block shots okay i don't like these oh it did block it
holy shit that was the mother load chance to not take damage that's pretty good don't run too fast
that's a mega chest what's up what is it i don't know drugs but first skull first i really do need
health though this is bad left hand left hand brief dark rewards drop it drop it drop it
what what oh i i did it it's been five years oh yay fuck i need oh this is really bad i keep
getting like hit by shit use your fucking item oh use your fucking item he's throwing again no
i'm just like hanging out with chat and like listening to you guys and like hanging out with
you right come on i've who cares about i'm hanging out with you guys we're hanging out here we're
having a good time you and i the two of us plus the other 5098 people it's just us here all right
i'm gonna focus don't pick that up pull them please please do it come on oh why every time
i'm gonna record a sneeze for fucking soundboard playback it screws up i psych myself out of being
able having to sneeze oh my god i'm itching my face why is my face so itchy right now all the
times be itchy right now it has to be right now hp and luck good finally making me look like an
asshole nice what we're looking for is we're looking for the uh we're looking for we're
looking for the guppy the guppy cruncher the real good guppy cruncher so what you do is you
put these uh you put these this dog shit down here i like to pretend it's it's my my granddaughter's
wedding so anyways i keep picking up dog shit wonder how many of you guys know that wow we've
got ding ding ding we've got a winner we've got a winner we got a winner easy blow that up
oh secret without even needing to know and it's greed use your fucking item i will
right now not right now right now then it'll charge again and i can use it again
item used lots of these chests i'm gonna get come on push up mate can i get guppy well i
is it there a chance that i could actually get guppy kind of maybe a little small i'm
never going up in that room again use i'll use it don't worry i want tears up tears up would make
this unbeatable it'd be great be amazing well come on but i love when it goes oh fucking item
i'm gonna grab a that's like a word you're trying to give me to say i don't know what the hell it is
here shot no i need tears up please tears up like it's like a double shot it would be
doing it would happen so many times please give it to me a little bit of casino then
he's not grabbing the i'm not gonna say it i don't know what it is i can't even get by this i'm
blowing it up anyways all right i'm in a good spot slot machine go brr i don't think that works
here go up secret room right here guaranteed or i will sit back down in my chair and forget i
talked look at all this damage oh we're killing satan tonight you guys are not gonna be mega
satan just right that way just right yeah fuck left or right left polaroid oh it's just a polaroid
right oh let's take a guess got piece of collar and we need to go deeper fucking worst item in
the game throwing i'm not throwing i'm gonna be can check this out throwing there's no rocks
in this room uh it's pinhead whatever his name is yeah afraid of me pinwheel uh i don't want that
i have the have the um guppy generator the cursed chest thing i want to keep that give me a break
give me a break oh no no no no no yeah no no no are you prepared i was just doing
uh no more heroes enemies my spleen what just hit me all right i gotta pay attention again
no no no i can't get over it what the fuck is wrong with me don't answer that oh tinted
rock hate these things fuck till i get the scratch in my face again i'm still gonna do this don't
worry i refuse to let this fall i refuse to have this be a fall down you know what i mean
if you're a failure i mean what was i supposed to do there i was supposed to do there use your fucking
item there it is yes yes yes coming back coming back coming back we're coming back
game over game over guppy achieved melt melting and a goat head and i don't want it this is good
enough i don't want it i don't want it i don't want it i'm not taking i don't want it this is
a really good room i have guppy guys i'm invincible right i guppy flies right sorry i'm gonna have to
kill you even more flies fill up the room with flies yes guppy guppy guppy guppy guppy guppy
guppy guppy guppy nobody can fucking defeat me oh another guy to explode going on dude
get rid of what he's unstoppable and he's lost it i'm feeling the true power
oh i forgot these explode pill we instantly take every pill in every single run well there you go
boom oh drop left hand it ruins chest drop left hand what the hell do i care i'm guppy
like you can't i can't drop it how do you drop an item drop left hand i can't how do you i can't
throw it what i bought the first g hit control hold control doesn't do anything control that
doesn't do anything you guys what are you talking about you change bindings no i use it i'm gonna
no are you sure this is anti-birth left alt hold the map button triggers for the controller
left trigger left bumper it's a bomb i actually get fucking hit all right we're going down or up
down or up down begotten baby down or up should i go up or down and up or down and up or down
and up or down i don't want that let's go up i tried to move he's throwing i'm not throwing
i'm gonna kill iza can fucking a tenth of a second drop the hand there's no i don't know
kill it kill it kill it oh it's right trigger don't touch that i don't want that right trigger
okay it's right trigger got it why would i i'm not you don't get double guppy i'm already guppy
it's only take it it's only one heart no i don't want to touch that it scares me take me out
double guppy oh platinum his tongue judas's tongue payment received three devil deals
fuck i'm dodging all over the place and i even get hit by it god damn it that's annoying
hmm oh hello you can have every single cent you can have it all take it all from me thanks
the bomb hb up feels so good when you get a build like this and you can just oh don't touch all right
let's go isaac i thought you were isaac what the heck um no i'm not continue too bad i don't have
the no keys or anything hold on that's another technology that's all of them i got all of them
technology too holy shit oh my god it's all the techs and damage them and hp and a piggy bank
this is all the technologies triple triple taser and guppy i don't think i'll have a
cooler build of this ever again and it's fear shot but i feel like i'm doing less damage
am i doing less damage i am that's very un-pogged i think i'm too old to be saying that you know
what i mean i think i you know i think i'm a little too old for like saying the word
pog what do you think is it is it working is it working is it working when i'm like oh pog
you guys like shut up is it like dude he said it you're never too old to pog yeah that's good
to know this is cool to see this all together though rocks don't stand a chance yeah did i
kill the last boss with the germa craft okay that's just a troll room i don't why i even
collect the bombs right now i don't even need them oh the seven deadly sins in the same room
at the same time and it really wants me to grab that huh almost there pinwheel look at that oh
yeah big beautiful fly is this a bob's brain this is a bob's brain that just floats around but thank
god i'm like halfway halfway thank god i'm like done with this playthrough golden touch nothing in
there where is that where is this place oh we're doing a copy pasta now i see
i don't know i don't want to pick i'm not picking it up at this point like i'm playing diablo and
just walking by all the rares and uniques that i know what they are i'm not even gonna pick them
up monster manual all right time for a game over here blue baby all right take take yourself down
to one heart or like or don't take take take it down to one heart okay i can't even the flies are
gonna kill me hooray infinite carry yay i guess i finished another run that music for this cut
scene that's god you hate this game what are you fucking on about store credit has appeared in
the basement i want to look at one more of the challenges i did have a demo man what's this one
seeing double what's this one so what's the this is just wait we both have it
purist is fun um it isn't yours but you you don't get any items at all yeah that's so difficult
it's just i i got no intention of doing that boiled baby
just takes forever to kill bosses two of clubs all right so no items huh
oh there's another secret pocket that i could kill them up before they touch me
i need my memory when he said it was going to be a maximum four hours isaac's stream
that's true i did say that but also remember um if you weren't here earlier this stream is
probably not going to be very much longer i'm trying to take it easy i've had some annoying
pain because you've uh those of you that know the yeah yada yada yada uh i was kind of hurting the
other day and i'm kind of hurting now but i took some advil and i'm like okay now but
this is like i can't sit here i can't do like an eight hour session here it really is the worst
because like like sitting down actually does make it worse after like five plus hours what i'll
probably have to end up doing is i'm probably gonna get a standing desk and see if it helps
so it's on it's on the table tape yourself to the ceiling what because i have noticed that
lying down is all right like i'll wake up in the morning and i'm kind of stiff but and like moving
around if i'm like walking around and moving around you i'm like usually i'm like okay
it's not as bad as it is we're just seated something about the seated position even with
like good posture and with a brace on something about it i don't know it's like somehow it's
compressing my spine and rib cage and um making my issue already it's there worse
oh there's a credit card good thing you just used it for no reason oh that's good luck up
get a hanging from get a hanging roller coaster chair that would actually be pretty cool
well we're gonna fill this room with shit i thought there were no item rooms
in the challenges wait what how is there item room in here get a lumbar roller i have one already
i'm doing physical therapy i have trust me if there's a device to help with like
potential costochondritis like arthritis i've i've probably used it or tried it
i've tried it some of them help some of them make it worse is that a tinted rock fuck it's not
but well marijuana is true uh although here's the issue okay i'm gonna give you guys the real
the we're gonna get real talk time okay so um of course like something like marijuana i mean it's
legal in las vegas it's completely recreationally legal here's the problem um if i smoke weed or if
i do like cbd like if i do if i smoke weed i i can't stream i can't like do anything
i just sit in like a room and just i i'm already so scatterbrained and so fucked up and so adhd
no i can't do anything like imagine if i like smoked and then screamed it'd be like you you
don't want to watch that stream and then but there's also like just oh there we go got it
finally um yeah there's also just cbd oil which you can just have this you can have no thc in it
or anything but yeah i actually have done it before i had a bottle it was like little droplets i would
put under my tongue i had tried it before go to chiropractor well um the theory is do i'm doing
stuff physical therapy first so once physical therapy is like hey this is gonna work or this
is not gonna work that's what we're doing first chiropractors are shit yeah but part of me is also
in that boat right now where i mean it i i gotta get like a clear clear picture of exactly what's
going on and right now it's like okay you might have this like prostagunditis but now you might
have rheumatoid arthritis rheumatoid
apparently i have a high rheumatoid factor i did a blood test for it and i don't know
we're gonna check it out and we're gonna see and here's the thing it's i have autoimmune problems
already like the colitis thing that's autoimmune ra is autoimmune so the doctor was like you know
it's not against the realm of all possibility that it could you could just have ra and like okay but
once there's a clear indicator of what is actually fucking going on that's when you know you if it's
something if i have fucking like arthritis then whatever i have arthritis and you take medicine
for it you manage it and you'll be you're fine you'll be all right you might have good days you
might have bad days but you know you're still doing it see right now the problem is i'm not
being really treated for anything like we're like throwing darts and none of those darts have really
landed it significantly in any area that is like yeah that's definitive that's exactly what's going
on and uh while i uh talk to my friend on the telephone and just walk into every enemy
fuck throwing spaghetti at the ceiling you'll have problems getting into your clown car but
you can still stream yeah i'm not i'm not it i'm trying just to stay it's really easy to get
frustrated at something like this because when i when i have the camera on you probably see me like
lean back and like spread and it's like it's kind of why i'm doing that just do shrooms
i'm not so sure that's going to help me i will do one more one more one more psycho try as hard
as i fucking can as a zelrun i want to do greed mode in an anti-birth but doesn't exist that's
not trying as hard as i can that's getting hit by a spider it's getting hit by a default spider
what happened to bethany yeah that's true but i can't go wicked fast and try as hard as i
fucking can mongo baby famine we got kind of a kind of a shitty start not a pretty bad start
it's a shitty start whatever what do i say wicked because i'm from uh the east coast specifically
massachusetts and it is part of every one of our every citizen that lives in massachusetts part
of their vocabulary i'm talking even like lawyers and doctors and shit well you see uh judge i'm
sorry but the plane to fear has been wicked stupid with the way that he handled this case
doesn't matter oh boy i'm getting hit wow that had much uh well just reset shitty items are what
the fuck are it was passage ooh that's the one that makes the thing underneath you right i don't
see any tinted rocks yes i do i'll have to come back holy water splash oh this thing sucks too
this thing really you get hit and it just puts water on the ground right this thing's so bad
that's not a good first item you don't you gotta get something better than that
he's turning into a randy i want my last one to be at least sufficient but yeah we'll be uh
stopping after this whatever that may be amy's head oh that's a yep that's a really good start
like phenomenal actually see if i can do like the challenge mode right don't you have to go
is that an anti-birth yeah boss rush maybe i'll try it friends till the end best friend okay well
what the fuck did you just do to me what did you just do to me you just supposed to be my best
friend just threw a grenade at me what all right we made it for no reset i don't have to reset
come on no i need passive items i mean i'm gonna win like it you got tammy's head with azazela
you're pretty much there's a 95 chance of victory no matter what and i can go really fast but i have
to get to the boss rush room maybe i shouldn't even do that just go for another victory look at
this this is just deleting time you're the five percent you just threw me off with that now that's
what we're talking about halo all stats up in a room uh what was that time is money i don't want
it i need a key key key key key the bum i don't need it devil bum dude what the fuck i don't need
it it's too i wouldn't it would kill me i would i would die i would die from it you know i would
you know i would kill me from i'm begging you well it's closed now i can't go back in there
thank god there's a key you can survive on non-red health you fool i didn't go in the item room
phd better pills that means it's guaranteed no matter what that the pills will not be bad
range up is really good on azazel as you see it's gone fucked up boss rush let's go
i have no confidence in boss rush because i can only use tammy's head once
better pills i can see forever but new key that's huge range on this too
because of the thing i just got that's good ah the fucking tnt changes every boss wave
really i did not know that really how fucking much range do those things have do it okay we
got need a key you got the item room let's go what's your next game uh city's skylines
city skylines is gonna be the next game that i'm gonna play oh dear which one what's the
candle not one spirit heart uh look them up you cheater i mean i know what the shield does
let's see candle candle it pastel candle gives minus one tier delay for each room completed
without taking damage up to a maximum of minus six so as long as you don't get hit you get tears
up every room but that's not too i mean i'd rather just not take damage sometimes yeah i'd rather
just like not take damage sometimes blow up the angel right right that's tick yeah i didn't have
any more bombs oh we're gonna open the door open open open open go go go go he sucks i i hey come
on feed and that's what i want good find a bomb all right just go down one problem with tammy's
head with as well as when you do that you the whole screen has gone hp up and i'll get it again to
bomb the door no i want to do some because that this current save file does not have
none of these characters have beaten like satan and shit in this save file so i don't want to do
it i can't afford that but if i'm gonna try boss rush i might as well go for it right what is this
myostosis i can't believe they're gonna put this a different seed completely what does this do
i'm gonna have to look this up holy water doesn't up your holy stat yeah that's that's right that's
true that's absolutely right it should i'm not picking that up i know what this thing does
this is actually the worst item in the whole game by far that's the one where if you take damage it
teleports you out of the room that thing sucks item isn't it called item monitor that's not what
this does you're thinking of it's involved in a bunch of game breaking combos oh gives you a
space bar item charge uh right okay speaking with such certainty and knows nothing of what he speaks
is can't get me over here you can't walk in the air like i can because i'm as a cell
spirit of the night scary what is that hey chat what's that do it's useless oh you can double
fly now cool get four wings every time i can't see trying to go too fast that's the issue
trying to speed speed speed tammy's head tammy's head tammy's head tammy said go go go go go go
like that unc turn a light no he's really gonna lose with tammy's head on as a cell huh
no he's not he's not he will complete at least one portion of this game
as a cell who you playing on dude oh you know
i'm saying it the way that i say it which is wrong oh it's it's but it's jupiter though
you guys know that's not the correct way to say it you still say it that way don't you
call the fuck out call the fuck out call the fuck up call the fuck up
the fuck out let's go oh shot speed and damage up i don't know what it is i don't want it did you
just fight a boss yes what is vice from keeping by the room is filling with hearts it's the trinket
oh all right well i got a lot of money but that spawns all the items left on the previous floor
that's really really cool that's really interesting sure to got dark bomb yep i
really should have i was just too scared bombs are key they are now what the fuck does it mean
oh if they splutter loud lump slow effect oh cool is a mega beam you guys are fucking crazy
kind of sucks what do you got mom okay i can bomb use a bomb polaroid polaroid bomb or boss rush
boss rush or polaroid and go bomb polaroid boss rush let's go which one is the best wait oh
i can still get there i can do it wait for you i said what what what one of these is any good
these kind of all suck huh plug is the plug any good 120 volts up why is my uh thing not charged
i get lied to did i oh well there it is i just have to get hit i got pranked sorry i'm only using
what i need to i hate this motherfucker get rid of him i don't like that guy i guess sucks
i wish it wasn't so dark fuck all right there's a lot of people oh he's dead how am i not getting
nip by that shit you gotta be kidding me that was lucky as hell watch out for these fucking guys
what the hell oh stop slowing me down no that's the worst combo to have right now but he's dead
that's fine where is he oh i did it that was pretty cool oh my god don't fucking die
all right that's fun bomb the angel i can't well i'll take some of these it's all right i
have another i have a couple of opportunities don't i i all caps because zero brain cells
what are you doing uh let's go damage and health good okay no room though oh well like i need more
damage right now two hearts uh two hearts better that one felt good i will say that one felt very
good that was very satisfying to do the lightning arcs too that's awesome the other people you know
i hear you play binding of isaac how many of you here and you ever get an item build that you wish
that there was like 10 more stages to the game so you could keep playing with it damn it like a
cocky that's a victory lapis yeah yeah i know but still i missed a rock how do you even see that
from there how would you even see me miss on a rock holy shit your eyes 2020 vision
wait there's another one oh my is it javade right next to the door by the boss door in here
i don't even really damn it sorry damn it it's all right here we go opportunity right can i still do
it damage and hp up i don't have enough this is still time no you get a joker oh well shit
there's a chance there is a chance it's just a chance that's all i need to hear
it's just so much damage it's like it's unbelievable how much damage tamie's head
does with brimstone it's just i'm not even fair oh we're right here already speed the speed
zero percent chance we just go in or explore in case you get a joker oh i didn't get them all
joker or sacrifice room even if you get the joker it might take you to the devil room yeah
worth a shot the game's just playing itself at this point the lovers oh look telepills oh
no i thought that was the temple from shit let's just do it for fun for a second i thought we had
it but then it was like no it doesn't matter because it's not the angel room so i guess i
just didn't remember from a while ago when i played binding of isaac so after the boss rush the game
doesn't end all right i did not know that i thought the game was i thought the game ended
cards joker joker joker joker joker mom's bottle of pills telepills yes here we go keep trying oh
i'm gonna i'm gonna keep trying oh you're still alive well that's pretty much done deal unless i
can find a battery try for super secret rooms uh where are some possibilities up here right
it's only it's only connected to one room right so it could be like right here all the way to left
one near the boss this one here could be same room but the left wall it's within two rooms from
the boss i mean it could be the one on the left right or the north wall above the boss wall i only
have two tries anyways top or right of boss it could not be up here over here east wall like over
here either one and we'll try this one dad's key dad's key in chest dad's key you'll be so upset
if it's actually an angel room here and oh i'm gonna be so sad no angel room don't worry it was
all for nothing don't worry dad's key that's not it that's not it that's not it that's not it
give me the lemonade poison tears triple shot holy fuck what is this thing undefined what i don't
have tammy's head anymore wait will this give me tammy's head forget me not i'm going in recharge
with the fly all right but what why am i doing to leave use it now uh that didn't do anything
what wait what just happened bob's brain pog oh no i don't have tammy's head i have no it doesn't
matter this this shot this just quadruple shot is fucking crazy look at that shit find the timeline
that opens the door just loop it loop again until you get dad's key okay we'll try it
all right here we go yeah i also i need keys too though that's the thing super greed no that's
not who i wanted to see i don't want this daddy's love oh too bad i kill him if i touch him well i
this is throwing what do you mean dad's key is not in the item pool oh well that's unfortunate
yes it is what do you mean it is well which one is it fuck all right here we go why am i taking so
much damage because i'm trying to teleport around i'm trying to teleport to the fucking
i'm taking damage this heart's all in the chest room taking damage charges it because of the thing
i have yeah i'm not just like walking into enemies what if i got drunk all right that's good
don't pick that up yet right i'll pick it up whatever who cares oops turn it up it doesn't
all right well we're here i got like one more chance for this kill this stuff in this room
here we go wait this wait no i need these keys i need the keys holy shit what is all this
what the fuck no i don't want to what is this thing it's that's doctor feet i don't want that
right how many items can you have in the game okay i need to heal i can't just die oh no no no no no
no no wait this is gonna explode if i hit anyone it's all up to bob's brain get me out get me out
i have to kill people with bob's brain or i'm dead right am i good okay okay i gotta i gotta
stop fucking around i gotta go back i gotta go right i gotta get the hell out of here
i need health oh my fuck okay okay i gotta go down down here i want i need these hearts
how the hell did i get over there oh fucking my god oh my god oh my god how do i get back down
i only have to do two more rooms 98 coins take doctor fees i'm not i know what he does
charging with damage is the last resort empty the chest pool holy shit what the fuck
what the fuck is going on oh no empty the chest pool i wanted that okay i emptied the chest pool
i'm gonna do one last chance i gotta go fucking kill the boss no timelines are split what do
you mean no what the hell are you talking about in terms of building it up on my own loop until
you faint you can take more damage you guys are fucking nuts you guys are fucking nuts
but i like it just look at how much damage this shit does this even it's kind of like better
it's a little bit better than what i just had except it goes all over the place and it hurts you
it's got a raid joel just came in with a raid what's going on guys we are currently doing uh
okay this is the room it's half a heart uh we're doing we're doing a binding of isaac and i
fucked up big time i need to find i need to get dad's key which spawns inside of one of these
chests sometimes uh so we're redoing in a time loop over and over again this level because i
have a i have a thing that can make it so we can potentially do that so that's what we're doing
it's really really ridiculous and super fucking crazy i want that heart before i do anything
but thanks a lot for the very welcome guys i don't know what you guys are doing but hopefully it was
fun come on yes all right all right all right all right all right let's take do this tactically
i just i just killed him we do it again look how many people are behind me this is not even
binding advising anymore this is just like what it's like to go to the dmv it's like a disney
world line okay how much we got i gotta get it i gotta get it i gotta how many items in are in
binding of isaac i gotta do it by fighting because i can't take any more damage we lost all the hearts
i have to clear rooms and go from there just half the heart i'll get it this is so fucking
stupid you have a second life yeah i don't want to waste it
oh no i'm gonna be forever i'm never gonna fucking leave i'll never leave i'm i can do this
forever um all right how many more spaces are there jesus christ how many of those am i gonna get
i'm gonna get full hearts 90
keys
is there like a giant key that's 99 keys here we go nope god damn it what is this a magic room
toxic aura tears i can't even hurt myself my own bombs anymore i could just spam i don't like i'm
unkillable with my own bombs this is fucked up when i take damage it does it kills the whole room
yes okay what does this stuff do sweet suffering and um damage up and range up controlled tears
okay more eyes hold on a second you gotta be shitting me
wait i thought i i can't i'm supposed to be able to detonate these on my own
okay i need those keys though i'm gonna run out of keys i can't fucking believe this shit
what is it and all stats up oh hold on give me what is coming out of me do you see that
this shit comes out of my bones it's like raining hell when i ever take damage that's so it's crazy
i don't know what kind of combination of fucking items i have but they're ludicrous oh my god i
can zip i can't hurt myself i need keys okay all right guys
i'm the chaperone taking the school children somewhere
no i can't i couldn't even hurt them what does this do i don't know use it who fucking cares
i have no control over anything i don't have any control i missed a key hold on i'll get it
where's the key i heard another key all right we gotta go this way uh wait why are they getting
stuck on the ground look see that why they do you see what's going on with my shit fuck oh
sulfur temporary demon form common cold the peeper oh my god poison touch another little guy
do i try to go for the joker the world like that fucking really matters does it okay so
use the book too soul protection sure you guys ready for loop number 15 or 20 or so i don't
know which one it is let's go juicy sack gives money spectral buddy and magnetizing tears
so hey i mean this money again i got my little hearts on you i don't even know what i was
trying to do i don't know i don't i don't know what that bit was i'm gone i'm i'm gone i'm
actually gone i don't exist anymore i was like oh maybe it's like an opportunity for like a joke
that what was that i don't oh my fucking god um the plug the plug is gonna be extra take them all
no i can't take them all charge with blood
does this mean if i take damage i charge i'm gonna just teleport oh i'm gonna get every item in the
fucking whole game just press space now what what donate money donate money okay yeah let's
donate this all money candle germa get the candle candle candle what's with the what's the candle
it's broken get it curse immunity and evil up okay i'm ready ready to teleport
wait is it going to do a loop or is it do i just do it get the one plus one equals what okay
go up holy shit guys what the fuck oh my god fire right up the poop hat another friend
and charge cursed child no i didn't do anything i'm never gonna finish anything
oh there's so many keys what is this i have too many friends there's too many people at the party
ow and tear blasts five bombs penetrative shots speed of item snatcher and the bean
uh so i'm ready to go again what's this x-ray fishing where do i see my items it won't even
show them to me no nothing what's this orbiting tier watch out watch out it's the meteors
shot speed up these oh my god this is out fucking this is the most outrageous run of vining visor
i've ever fucking had ever this will never be matched ever again for me is this dude i can't
even pick this up there's too many people around it shot speed up again and just leave me alone
i can't even pick it up i'm full hearts i only have seven keys left though this is a this is bad
brother bobby all stats up then shuffled i can't the screen is more of people farm for keys now
okay that's a good idea just farm for keys i can always teleport this is key farming only
keys bingo five i'm hacking this is what it's like to hack this when you hack in the game
more keys good this is i i downloaded a trainer and this is what the outcome was i put every
item on the whole game what is you feel balanced okay all right i see
i don't even know who's in that room very balanced very balanced i need more keys
by the way when i get to beg of satan you do realize i'm just gonna hold this button down and
it's gonna happen eventually i don't care if this takes another six hours
i'm doing this shit i'm getting dad's key and i'm opening that fucking door
no keys look at all these hearts too all right keys i just got a quarter all right all right
it's time to go what's that was that a god item is that like god a god chalice purifying light
oh my god this is we're doing it again and guys what happens when you do all this
we have to do it again okay working as intended anybody want some health up oh yeah just like
throw it into the trash it's on i what am i gonna do with it just dump it out in the trash what's
happening what's happening right now why am i surrounded by these shits what is happening
bingo oh yeah see you later somebody hurt me hurt me hurt me hurt me somebody hurt me hurt me
hurt me kick my ass beat the shit out of me okay good good we're good good good good good good
good let's go let's heal heal heal damn it okay we've got plenty of room plenty of time good we
got more keys i'm just okay i'm just gonna wait till the rain hits me in the head okay um um
come on come on this we don't got time for this shit i gotta get dad's key thank you all right uh
let me think about how i'm gonna handle this situation oh Jesus bum friend stitches the
eternal life we got a new friend yeah we got a lot of friends now we're the fucking goddamn
pied piper mom's perfume oh five poison bombs yes you wanted them there's a key somewhere i got it
you're playing pikmin no this is not even this is not even pikmin i don't know what this is
secret room keys bombs i have 99 okay good cool um i'm gonna take
keys yep good all right uh get this and then uh and then up okay up that's very very fun very very
cool what's all this stuff what should i grab that i'm not even making sentences anymore no i'm not
take it all okay that's the black lotus hp up times three no i gotta keep this trinket
because this is the thing that's spawning the hearts okay so what are these spore shot
dead bird isaac's tears the shears okay cool let's have a great fun day is that a wallet
not mine dad's key that's dad's key i got it that's dad's key yes glad dad's key that's not
dad's key fuck well okay goodbye the yum heart okay i gotta pick them all up so it registers
that i've collected them yeah it all sucks i can't even take it same one fuck off where did i get
the other one shit luck there we are hey uh i'm gonna buy it all despite it i have 99 fucking
dollars i have a thousand dollars temporary demon form born to rock there's my undefined
um what's this thing spider butt okay cool i got everything i need let's go we might have to do a
key around here frost tears random blast and five bombs reusable fortune and then the thing
all right uh pretty cool anything else oh my fucking god what if i get guppy too from this
office bullshit hp up faith up buy the keys guppy's tail look holy shit you see what this
is doing now this is dangerous this is very very dangerous the game's gonna crash i need to do keys
here there's another friend this mirror boomerang tears tooth shot i gotta get some i gotta get some
keys maybe not maybe not i guys um this split shot i don't know if this is i'm just gonna let
my friends attack why even do anything crazy i have a thousand people on the screen
blood of the martyr damage up i just need keys give me some keys shit quit to save progress
you're you should i exit just in case exit and come back just in case something horrible happens
no no what if it fucks up okay no what if it fucks up you're right did i get a key was that a key
okay no key what is this it's like a multi-colored tears it's a fucking goddamn
skittles party in here oh shit i gotta get out of here i'm gonna get out i'm gonna crash the game
okay all right slow down slow down slow i need how have i not gotten any keys all right minions
kill them shit run out of keys give me a key do you have dad's key unlocked i have to why
wouldn't i you have to unlock it wait i got it i do have it i have it okay judgment wait we might
be able to get a few keys out of this excuse me i don't know what somebody picked it up wouldn't
me good somebody pocketed it what just came out yep good yes i'm looking for keys can everybody
get away from me for a second can you get keys out of this i don't want to take that get rid of
this and i have spiders now i have i'm playing a game of snake but like a toddler set it up
and they color it outside the lines i heard a key where is it
stream ain't fucking ever turning off now boys and girls we are never stopping it's never gonna
turn the fuck off we have we can get every item in the entire fucking video game if we have to
in the 200 fucking items whatever 200 300 items the game's gonna break eventually but you know what
fuck it okay let's go godspeed everybody poop on the ground over here blast damage holy shit
oh my fucking god damage reduction toxic blood and an evil and i'm evil we gotta go go go go go go go
got it you became load of the flies ice cream scoop there it is hooray now
i have a question if i do not pick that up can i do this 900 more times and get it again what
if i no i have to pick it up it won't show up again okay ladies and gentlemen the the it's over
so do the whole floor first seed write that down if you'd like to do this uh how long do you think
it's going to take me to kill mega satan i let's put it this way i'm going to hold down just use
it now i'm gonna hold down a attack button and stand still is right i am three two one get item
there you go satan it's time for you
i didn't think i was even attacking him he had this look on his face like holy shit man
i'm not gonna go near that he was just watching like a whole city burn that was fucking crazy
i can't believe that actually happened that actually worked damn that was fucking cruel that
was cool i'm just i'm just speechless the whole time i don't even know what the hell to say
that was outrageous uh and that that's the one you go out on like i can't i don't think i can
play this game again like this i don't think that's gonna happen it's i i feel like i'm in
slow motion right now that's gonna be it that was supposed to be the last one anyways so
anywho thanks for watching i'll see you again later this week i will be off for the next three days
so you'll see me again on friday friday the 20th we'll do probably friday saturday sunday we are
going to start city's skylines on friday that's the plan a bunch of people have given themselves
a ton of money came in today too we'll make sure to go over it all but uh 25 community subs from
morcus borcus thanks for the subs and a wild barrel thanks for 10 community subs huge sub
drops right at the end thanks both of you that was quite the crack stream it was but i'll see
you guys on friday we'll stick around for a little bit longer like 30 40 minutes we'll do the bits
and hang out for a little bit but see you guys on friday have a wonderful night take care of
yourselves good night just move to the end ow i gotta like put this microphone
i gotta hang this mic from the ceiling seriously like i gotta hang this thing from the fucking
ceiling i just like almost broke my fingers but uh let's do this go back to earlier today
like a boxing announcer exactly you get it the music on and we're gonna go back to earlier this
afternoon to uh lm man thanks with 10 bucks thousand bits herby streams have been helping
me lately my dad is in hong kong so i'm alone during this coronavirus panic i've been uh
discriminated because i'm asian and i've been pretty hopeless due to my college closing down
making this quarter's final stretch even more challenging than it is already
that sucks that's really not cool i mean it none of that matters remember if somebody around here
has it regardless of their race or gender doesn't matter you if you don't practice the
necessary hygiene and you don't do the necessary things you're the one that has spread it and a
lot of people don't even know they have it right you're asymptomatic for like a week or two aren't
you so it's like you can't be you can't be especially not going after because oh it
originated in in china well so what it's here now you just you we got to take the precautions to
try to not have it spread around anywhere else in the world it's all over the world now it's it's
the whole world it doesn't matter what somebody looks like if we're talking about a global
pandemic it's not what but where they're from or we're talking about a global scale but regardless
i'm really sorry to hear you going through that bullshit and hopefully all this blows over really
soon because i know that we're inching closer and closer to now in the united states people
cities are kind of starting to go well we probably need to start locking down shit and nobody can
really be out and who knows what will happen in the next five to ten days but thanks for the
thousand bits and sorry to hear about that bullshit sticks renegade thanks for the 250
as a streamer it's your duty to stream a hundred a thousand percent more during this time of
pandemic many of us are now out of work or had our hours cut and are bored at work without you
please i'm here i'm here the please at the end just for real though thanks to the 250 will the
city skyline stream be modded at least so you have custom buildings and vehicles
probably not initially because i've never played it before so i'd like to figure out how the game
works before i do any of that so initially i'm just probably going to play the game the way it's
intended to be played the first day maybe depending on what it does marv ash mcgalley
thanks for the 250 hi germ i want to thank you for these streams especially for the binding
of isaac content you're one of the only three things that made me forget for a while about
the lockdown ever since i started here in italy i wanted to celebrate my two-year sub by getting
the glue man shirt but i'll have to wait for the lockdown to be lifted because i'm afraid the
package could get stuck somewhere because of it keep planning to make it any more shirts in the
future um not immediately nothing in the immediate future but i do have plans of things i'd like to do
but none of them are really at the tip of the tongue right now they're all in the back of the
mouth someone will figure out what the fuck that meant so they'll i don't know but yeah at some
point in the future i do want to add because that teespring store is just there permanently so i'm
just gonna the idea is just add shit to that store as you know the years go by and they just
are there forever i'd like to put maybe a couple a year one or two a year maybe something like that
there you go lm man thanks for 250 germa do you like to voice act the games you play and do it
and do you do it when you're not streaming no it happens in my head i mean the answer is yes but
i do it upstairs i don't really do it out loud it depends what the game is
silent serenity thanks for the 250 hi mr germa just wanted to say that i totally agree with you
binding of isaac seems more similar to star tropics hey i know that's what i'm saying
that's what i mean lm man thanks for the 250 i'm a true and loyal fan of germa 985 i don't give him
the silent treatment i like the rest of these clowns lol uh larz the dude thanks for the thousand
bits 10 bucks and it's just the dot dot dot dot that's when everyone was but what a weird night
this is a weird one this was a wild one uh thanks for the dot dot dots thanks for the thousand bits
abomination zero thanks for the 250 i'm gonna tell kim you're neglecting us um
fucking do that man inferno thanks for the thousand bits ten dollars germa you didn't have to listen
to these babies there's some people that fighting here hey sarah and fp thanks for the 250 germa
remind me of when i was younger star fox adventures was one of my favorite games as a child
and i disliked zelda even though i hadn't played ocarina or wind waker you need not have bitterness
in your heart just because you didn't play the better game i played ocarina of time i loved
ocarina of time i love i love that game i love ocarina of time what's the one for super nintendo
uh linked to the past that one's fantastic too i mean liar
song of storms
ipona's song
i don't know i remember just doing it i think i fuck you don't think i've played that game before
actual fan it went backwards or fake fan
you're saying hey bitch oh thanks for the five dollars the worst part isn't that they now have
footage of you winky ollie golly cover this one already yeah the mitchell gave you guys the the
the wink dink the wink dinks that was mitchell 256 forever will be infamous
for creating the wink dink moniker uh after smith thanks for the five dollars hey germy boy
haven't caught a stream in a while but i did today after watching one of the second germa vids on a
whim glad to see nothing has changed remember to remind chat to wipe and then here's a meme
my friend playing mario galaxy me collecting all the star bits as player two
but why does people have pringles taped to them nice retit link i'm gonna fucking time that
person out i can't i can't do that stream labs oh yes this is a dumb program anyways uh goiki
thanks for the five dollars let's see what we let's see we got the dru crew the moo crew the
shroom crew the wink dinks did i miss anybody i don't think so i think that's all of them
what is this community the warriors like how many different like fighting groups of people
do we have anyways come out you that's hard to do i have to scream it and i'm not going to
uh green day and cats thanks for the five dollars i'm glad to see you still streaming despite not
feeling the best i've been watching the vods forever now and finally was able to catch
uh them live in regard to your mystery pain i have a friend who has eds and absolutely swears
it by eucalyptus oil i want to get an actual confirmed diagnosis first i have another
appointment here i have to go see a couple other doctors to find out hey because i'm one of those
people i want to get a definitive diagnosis because i've had a couple of doctors already
have wanted to throw darts and do some potentially invasive procedures that i don't want to do unless
i have to you guys talked about the nerve block an intercostal nerve block is what one of the
doctors wants to do and i just don't fucking want to do it unless i have to just i just don't because
it's just not really that good for you i kind of want to know exactly what's going on before i do
it but yeah uh i will give it a look though kim gets that kind of stuff she gets like eucalyptus
oil and lavender oil and stuff she has that stuff i'll ask her about it
hey stripes beast thanks in 250 germa i picked the worst time for a road trip but i was unable to go
to hash house agogo and even eat out in different states it's ridiculous i'm excited for gotcha
force and i hope you have enough toilet paper to pay off the corona goblins love you and the
community yeah vegas is shutting shutting down it's it's sad it really is it's just you know
you look at a place like las vegas's people come here to have fun and to go on vacation and enjoy
themselves and a lot of the casinos now are shutting off you can't even go to them happen
at disney world and it's um yeah it's it's depressing it is but hopefully this shit doesn't
last that much longer and we can get back to normal i'm sorry to hear that you had a trip planned
during this time you'll be back you'll get hash house ago go at the link that's fucking
burger i've ever had let's put on the credits i have a couple more bits to do let's put them on
here if i can do it i should be able to let's swap you out here i'm gonna yeah sorry about that
these are all the subs that were today thanks guys there was a bunch of community subs
that came in right now and earlier thanks a lot thanks for subbing thanks for watching
thanks for continuing to be part of this community appreciate it all of you but there are still some
bits to be done future gamer says this is some monkey paw stuff you asked for 10 extra levels
and you sure got them that's true thanks with 250 this is some monkey paw stuff
gnarly thanks with 250 how do you even play binding of isaac after this
go to fucking run have a good night yeah i might i have to take a break for a while
from binding of isaac binding of isaac is gonna have to take a back seat because you don't come
back to play after that for a while i don't think that's not something that just is oh yeah i'm not
gonna play that right now so yeah it was too good oh futz thanks for the 25 dollars 250 bits
that's way more than 250 it's 2500 thanks for the 25 dollars grown up my father sister and i had a
running joke we would say i'm not talking to you until blank and we would play what we would call
the silent game until someone cracked it sounds so stupid but it's always been one of my favorite
childhood memories i didn't think commenting this that stupid joke would get us anywhere
but that was hilarious sorry for pitting chat against you that made my entire month
thanks for the laughs i mean it was pretty funny it was pretty funny thanks dedicated for the 250
jeremy you've been a great motivating factor to help me and my girlfriend go on while things are
rough i'm so close to getting prescribed estrogen but this lockdown might actually interfere with
the process after i've been in processing for three years thanks for being there to cheer me
up when depression and dysphoria are kicking my ass yeah there's a lot of you know there's a lot
of shit that's just not it's just gonna turn off for a while there's so many places businesses
medical offices i i really hope this is done because it's really gonna start to fuck up
people's lives their day-to-day lives i mean like we talked about yesterday just the fact that you
know you got people going to the grocery stores and buying everything and everybody's just preparing
for this catastrophe and it's just jeez every day there's something new whether it's
the government's trying to intervene and then dump a bunch of money into you know like the markets
and and no there's another case there's a there's another thousand cases it's just it's a lot of
noise it's a it's a lot to take in and i really feel for the people that have shit in their life
that's now getting just detonated because of it workers people that can't go to work
people get laid off because there's they have to close places they have to shut down like we just
talked about um the strip and everything like casinos think about how many people work at
disney world disney land restaurants bars it's not good and each day hopefully we can
soon start to get an idea of just how long this might last hopefully it blows over soon the fourth
this is the fourth time in history that disney is closed yeah we brought it up yesterday
disney world has been closed only a few times ever since it was opened in like 1901 whenever
the fuck it opened like 1960 when was it it's insane but yeah thanks for the 250 take care
of yourself shadows one disciple thanks for the 250 very pog stream king when are you planning
on setting up the germa guild's site can't wait to get together with the poop troop what the
fuck are you talking about what are you talking about it's news and coffee thanks to the 250 hey
jeremy long time no bits since we're talking about corona again let me share my sad story too
i was going to visit my girlfriend in april however thanks to the travel ban we had to
cancel everything and i'm very sad about it at least we can spend some time more time uh because
her break got extended also this last run was insane glad i was here like i always am that's
right i'm always here also play majority's mask maybe but that's uh sorry to hear about the
that's your thing with your girlfriend hopefully that you can do it again that's the thing
it's always another time there's always another time it just sucks that a lot of stuff has to
get delayed and pushed and moved thanks again silence serenity thanks for the 250 why don't
we have a meetup at the hash house of gogo after this whole thing blows over i'm not sure i would
be able to do that i don't think like legally speaking i mean it's a restaurant and i think
they have like code so probably not yeah the cat thanks for five dollars germa i'm sending bits
all the way from korea been your fan since 2013 i love your videos and jokes it always makes me
feel happy it helps me whenever i have a hard time at least can i hear a spi been a while and
it's always been my favorite line oh you got it spi there you go he said it he said it he did it
not only did you get a fucking wink you got a spi too you're gonna dot dot dot dot dot me
again you're gonna dot dot dot dot dot me again next time not you yeah we can't i'm talking about
everybody else uh milla 38 thanks for the 1500 bits incredibly stream germa thanks so much for
all the incredible content thanks for watching thanks for sticking around thanks for being here
thank you i really appreciate it much love to you now we are going to go raid somebody we're
gonna raid kraken because we haven't really raided kraken in a long time in months and months and
months we're going to go say hello to kraken currently playing kenshi which everyone always
is telling me to play although probably not gonna happen a few weeks i haven't i haven't raided
kraken in at least four or five months something like that go say hello hell of the fucking rats
thank you hey yeah i'll see you guys on friday good night take care last minute hits
holy shit blueberry juice thanks for the 250 hey northern lion 985 just want to say that if uh if
that standing desk doesn't work out i suggest a running desk i have one myself and i've been
really enjoying it all you need is a treadmill in front of your computer to really get those steps
in i mean sometimes i fall face first into my keyboard when i'm trying to type and run at the
same time but yeah you know we you know what i've said specifically and then the two and three oh
that's funny all right see you later see them no i'm not tomorrow see you on friday good night guys