Welcome back to Spy Party. In this episode, we're going to return to the game that-
Just making duck noises, that's fine. That's great. Um, we're going to be playing Spy Party again because it was just recently updated.
Oh, that looks fancy.
There's now an option to complete one known mission. We're going to do that.
I only have one-
Only one?
Yeah, I only have one thing I have to do.
That's going to be too easy.
All I have to do is- oh, here we go. So look at these new models.
And there he is, ladies and gentlemen. The new Monopoly guy.
Actually, can I be the old Monopoly guy too? No- what? There's only like four people you can choose from.
I wonder which character Jerma picked. There's a guy with a-
It wasn't the Monopoly guy. It was me. It's just a lady.
This is- that's- there's only five people at this party. What a shitty party.
Oh, I had a- I had a party. Do you want to come to my party? Only four people showed up.
This is a pretty huge house for like five people.
That is so funny. It's like, oh, we have like- look at character model.
Animation's like beautiful than like the Muppet in the room.
No shit!
I was trying to shoot the Monopoly guy.
Contact double agent is your only mission?
So you're going to win, like easily.
I don't know, I just like thought it was him.
Look at this comparison. Look at these two faces.
So hold on. That one guy that just does not belong, he can't be anything.
Literally, I can't make him the ambassador. I can't make him- I can't pick him.
That's the point. That's what I'm saying. You know he is completely irrelevant and you shoot him?
I didn't know he was like that completely irrelevant. I thought you could at least like pick him or something.
So why is he here? Why is this guy here? What is this guy's purpose? Like what purpose does this guy serve?
I love how Morgan Freeman has a cane. Why does Morgan Freeman have a cane?
He's not that old. Is that his wife like standing right next to him? Oh, he's planting the bug on him.
Whoa, look out. This is fucking impossible by the way.
There's only four people in this room. How the hell are you- you're going to see me do this every time?
I don't know. I'm kind of not paying that much attention right now to be honest with you.
What? You're paying attention to like the guy over here?
That's you, isn't it? You know what gave you away?
What?
You tapped your key like once and your character shifted like, and I was like, dude, they don't do that.
Okay, he was the like new Monopoly guy. Big surprise, Jerma.
We're gonna do- we're gonna do something here. Because there's only five people in this room and one of them does not matter at all in the slightest.
I'm going- there's like a 20% chance- no, 25% chance that I'm going to kill you instantly.
Damn it, you're fucking Morgan Freeman again!
You're not catching on to this. This is like the same thing from the first video.
I will keep that in mind, that it's always Morgan Freeman.
Well, no, see, this is where I metagame you.
No, you're not going to metagame me. I already know what you're doing.
You see, oh, it's always Morgan Freeman, but no, no, no. You see, you're not going to pick Morgan Freeman now.
You're going to be like Cruella De Vil from 101 Dalmatians. Game over, I win.
I told you-
Alright, no, no, it's still the old models. It's still the old models when you go back to like the other missions.
Well, it's open bay today. Today's a good day to do it.
Oh yeah, this has been a great experience.
Great experience, Jerma. I'm glad I got to play this game with you again.
I just couldn't wait to do this.
You want to go again? Just do a few more of these?
Yes, I want to do- I want to do another one.
I want to go back to this one again.
One mission.
I want to do-
Alright, let's go.
You and me. Baby, it's on now.
Do you want to just keep doing this?
I don't understand. Why do you think I would know what you're doing here?
Are we done?
Yeah.
Okay, good.
Wait, the guy who doesn't finish is scratching his head on my screen like, what?
Morgan Freeman again.
That was so stupid.