I actually can't even tell I'm hitting them. I guess I'm hitting them. I missed.
This is hard to do. Is there like an aim down sights? Who's saying that? No, that's me saying
that. Am I out of bullets? What's going on here? Something going on in the saloon? Everybody calm
down for a second. Let me get in there. I'm the sheriff around here. What's happening in this bar?
It's a stick up. I'll take care of this. All right. Shh. Shh. Don't say anything. Barkeep.
There's no telling what this crazy maniac will do. I got him. There you go. Yeah, you're safe now.
Don't act like I never did anything for you. Yeah, look who I got guys. Look what I did.
I rescued the town. I rescued everybody. What do you know? Don't put them. No, shit.
Now everybody freaks out. What does he want me to do? What am I doing? Am I holding a piece of bread?
What am I supposed to do with this guy? Do I just blow love potion in his face?
You stay down here. I'm going to take care of these two punks.
Who the fuck was that? Who was that? Why would you run out? I thought that was another bad guy.
You keep quiet. You keep quiet. I'm just going in here to take a look at the prisoner.
Fucking old man. Eat shit. Where is he? Where's that prisoner? There he is. There's that scumbag.
Consider it done. Consider it done. Put this motherfucker in a cell.
Got to make sure I get my story straight for when he wakes up. Sheriff, thank God you're awake.
Those bandits beat both of our asses and locked us in these cells. It's terrible. Sounds like trouble.
They could be east of the Mississippi right now, Sheriff. I'll help you solve this mystery,
whatever it takes. Sheriff, where's the sheriff? What? He ran out and went to the bar? This guy
was just unconscious. He woke up in a cell and that's the first thing he does. He's taking a piss
over here. Very surprised nobody can see me right now. This guy's talking to me. I just had a
conversation with that guy and he doesn't know I'm here. Be quiet. I heard something. Do I have to?
Be quiet. I heard something. Yeah, it was me you heard.
I'm just going to be honest. I can't even make rhyme or reason to anything that's on that mini
map. I have no idea what any of that means. I don't even know what direction I'm facing.
Snipe somebody here. Gonna find my target. What the fuck? Why would you ride the horse around to get
off on the same place you got on? He went like a total of 19 feet on that horse. I have to hit
somebody right in the head when they're on it moving erratically. Just like the ducks at the
old Midway game that go back and forth. This is going to be impossible. Here we go. God damn it.
Say cheese. I got him. Madam, I will have to ask you to follow me. Okay. What do you want?
What do you want us to do? I'm here to follow you. That's what you wanted? That's what you wanted to
tell me? This guy's annoying. How close can I get to these guys without them shooting me?
You know you can shoot at me. You don't have to keep creeping. You know you can shoot me.
I did. I already did this. I already did. This just happened in the last video I made. More
idiots that don't understand dynamite and don't care that I exist. I can't tell if this guy is
sleeping like this or if he's tied up or something, but regardless he's getting punched in the fucking
face. I'm not touching the keyboard. My hands are in the air guys. I swear to God. He's doing
this all by himself. There's nobody. Hold on a second. Hold on just one second.
Will the same thing happen if I stab him? Here we go. I'm going to stab this guy into a portal
in an invisible wall and it's going to kill him. Well boys, looks like this is the end of the road.
Nowhere to go. Nowhere to hide. Unless somebody has a foolproof strategy. Speak now or forever
hold your peace. I got a strategy. All right it worked. I'll go get the horses. I think they're
tied up back. Guys you can put your hands down now. What on earth? What am I doing with this guy?
Why did we turn into a human tumbleweed? This is where I keep the person clothesline.
No you just, I can't trust the driver anymore. You know just you don't get a good clean dry.
Do it the old-fashioned way. That's what I say. It's almost like they're doing their best gorilla
impression. All we need are monkey noises and these guys would make sense.