You can't change anything, dude. Hey! Don't you stab me. Did you just kill that guy and I killed you at the same time?
Yeah, I had to make sure that all- Alright, boo, what are you doing?
I'm being stealthy. There's a cop there. Oh god. Oh boy.
Alright, get all these people out of their cars. We're gonna make a barricade.
Hold on, am I wedged in between these two things?
Okay, never mind, get out of the car and go get another one.
So, hold on, is there already a police barricade right here?
Hold on, what are you-
I'm having a hard time figuring out how this works.
Alright, get out of the car, get out of your cars. We're gonna get behind- Oh my god.
Get behind- Everyone get behind the cars.
We don't have guns, we have pistols.
Attack. I have a saw knife.
I just got the saw knife.
Make a barricade with the cars so the police can't get to us. So, light them up.
Light them up like dominoes.
Okay. See where I am, see on the mini ramp where I am.
I have car. Who's this dead guy?
I just shot that guy in his face, he was being annoying.
Alright, well get out of the way, I'm gonna- You didn't shoot this person.
Dude. Hey!
Alright, so line them up like an army of cars. There we go.
Yeah, alright, we're good, good.
And instant three stars for shooting a cop in the head.
She was head punching.
Alright, we just need- Once we get in the middle here, we can really start to-
This is where it gets crazy.
Oh my god, I just found a fucking striker shotgun. Not even kidding.
Let's keep it, because we're gonna need it.
Alright. It's like a- Oh my god.
Ow.
Alright, alright, everyone get in between. Get in between, so we don't get in trouble here.
What kind of parking was that?
Oh hey, by the way, how do you get next to the car?
Hey, what are you doing? I'm trying to use that.
Q, Q, Q, Q.
I'm trying to use that, you idiot!
Oh my god, there's so many enemies.
Alright, let's do it.
Oh my gosh.
I got shot in the grenade.
What? How did I die?
Wait, the bullets went through the car?
Look at all these freaking cops.
Oh, no, it's this guy with the shotgun.
The guy with the shotgun.
That asshole with the shotgun is dead.
There's like five cops right here.
Are you serious?
They're killing me so quickly.
No, we gotta get like in an alleyway.
Can you auto-aim?
I'm like kicking their ass.
Can you auto-aim? How do you get behind cover?
Pro-sniper.
Hey, baby.
You looking to go for a ride, sweetheart?
Dude, don't shoot the...
Oh my god.
Look at this mess of cops.
Get in. Get in the car.
Get in. Calm down.
Oh, this guy is not happy.
Look at that mess. Oh my god.
Oh, the music. Oh my god.
Hey, thanks for blowing out the tires.
That like really helped.
That really helped our escape.
Alright, boo, get in.
You want me to get...
It's two-seater.
Oh, is it?
No, you get in the back.
How do I turn the radio off?
There's no off.
Alright, let's go.
Oh, so we're gonna do drive-bys in this piece of shit.
Oh, by the way, you can thank MLC Stealth for shooting out the tires for fun.
I can't even drive this damn car.
Hey guys, I have like a story to tell you.
You ever hear the one about the guy that...
Oh my god.
I jumped out too.
Yeah, thanks. Ditch that stupid cop.
That's like playing Battlefield where they just ditch a helicopter mid-air.
We can get six to...
Stealth, did you shoot the damn tire out?
Yeah.
You son of a...
I did that the second you were about to get in that car.
Oh my god.
What is with you? Don't shoot the tires. We need them.
I thought I shot both of them. Only that one.
Alright, new plan.
Can I shoot the tire from right here?
I don't know.
Oh, that poor guy.
Oh, grandma cleaners.
Alright, well Stealth, you brought this on yourself.
Oh no.
Oh, I landed in the water.
It didn't even work.
My guy jumped out the car and landed over the fence.
Why did that not even work? That was stupid.
Oh jeez.
Alright, that's your punishment for shooting the tires out.
That is shotgun.
Alright, what have we learned today?
We've learned that it's impossible to get six stars when you play with MLZ stealth.
Oh fuck, here comes...
The coppers are coming again, I'm sniping them.
Oh, you're back there, alright.
Alright, good, this is actually a great spot.
This is a great spot.
This is a fantastic spot.
This thing's automatic, my god.
I hear a helicopter.
Yeah, that thing shoots really fast.
Oh, there's a lot of them.
That's the SWAT team right there.
Wow, I'm not even near you guys.
I'm running.
This thing's gonna explode.
Run! Get off!
No, why am I jumping on top of the car?
No!
Make a run for it.
Oh, I just barely got away from that.
Holy crap.
I've had a grenade launcher.
There's gonna be plenty of guys for you to snipe here in a second.
Hey, can you see those choppers up there?
I can.
Okay, just wait for me to...
Oh, I just got sniped.
Oh wait, let me get in that SWAT car too.
Oh wait, that's you.
Oh, wrong button.
Let's get in the SWAT car.
Yeah, as you climb in, you get body armor.
I got full body armor.
I can protect you guys.
I can't, there's choppers around me.
I have to shoot them.
This guy's like sandwiched.
This thing's gonna blow.
Hey, that thing right next to it's gonna blow.
That thing's gonna explode.
Run away!
Oh, it's intact.
It's intact.
Oh, my god.
There's so many people here.
Wanna see something cool?
Yeah, I do.
Okay.
Feast your eyes.
In three, two, one.
What did you just do?
Oh, my god!
You just blew them all up.
They're on the left.
Look at that guy flying.
Hold on, German, let me in.
Alright, get in.
I think you have to get in the back, Will.
Oh, is it still intact?
Yeah, this thing's ready to go, I think.
Can you get in?
Oh, yeah, hell yeah.
Now we are unstoppable, baby.
How are we gonna kill those melee godfors above us?
How do you switch weapons while on this thing?
I don't know.
I don't wanna press buttons.
You ram into them head on.
Oh, this guy.
Bad day for you, buddy.
Oh, that was epic.
Oh, you shoot out of the back?
Yeah, you cut right through, and I shot him up, and he kind of flipped the car.
Now he's on his back.
That's unfortunate.
Now, this thing is slow as shit.
I hope we see, like, I hope we railroad somebody straight ahead.
This would be so funny.
Oh, too bad we didn't get that guy.
Alright, so ready?
Here's what we're gonna do.
Break!
He's gonna ram right into the back of us.
Oh, god, he's gonna hit me.
Oh, come on, you can't take all of the tech.
Yeah, I can't shoot these guys.
I can only shoot if they're, like, right to my right.
I wish we had, like, an ice cream truck.
Yee!
Oh, my god.
Um, you have to really piss them off for six stars, don't you?
Uh, yeah, I know, really.
Oh, my god, we've been at five stars lately.
Do you have, like, grenades or any Molotovs or anything?
I don't know how to change guns.
I have, like, a grenade launcher.
Cute.
How do you change guns?
Oh, I have Molotovs.
What?
What just happened?
I got shot out.
You got shot out of the car?
Yeah, they shot me out.
Oh, no.
I've lost my Molotovs.
Oh, I spawned next to you.
I left you for dead.
What?
You left you for dead.
That's what you did.
No, I didn't.
I got this cruiser now.
I'm in the cruiser.
Oh, no, I'm not.
I'm flipping over.
Oh.
All right, so we're good human beings.
What the hell is going on?
Why is this helicopter, like, disembodied?
Oh, my god.
Wow.
Oh, he can't get in there.
Oh, the pilot still is.
Can we get inside and do nothing with it?
Wait, the pilot's still in there?
Yeah.
Oh, the passenger.
Oh, come on.
Um, he's...
I don't think it's glitched out.
Hey, let me on.
Let me on.
Yes.
All right, let's go.
How do you do a wheeling?
Um, I don't know.
Just drive really fast into a car.
Oh, yeah.
Wow.
Everybody's working for the weekend.
Oh.
Broke my back across like one of these telephone spots.
I didn't even get like hurt.