Hello, how's it going? Let me tweet. Isaac late night hogchamp? No, no, no, no, no, no,
it's too late for hogchamp. Is there like a sleepy or like slightly excited hogchamp? Like a ooh,
is there an ooh, ooh? Oh, that one. Yeah, that one's not bad. It was like, oh, the hands up.
Like, here we are. What is that one called? Hypers. Oh, hypers. Okay, okay, okay. All right,
give me a second. I'm gonna tweet. Hello. Yeah, I was going to stream tomorrow, but I felt like
going right now. A new philosophy on the channel is if I feel like streaming, I'm just going to do
it. I could be at energy level of zero or energy level of 10. Whenever I just feel like doing it
is when we're going to do it. I was hoping you were going to play this. I've been trying to find
a way to play this. Oh, also, this is not on switch. I hooked up the switch and I realized,
all right, how many of you? I mean, maybe I'm maybe this is just me. I have the binding of Isaac.
I have bought the binding of Isaac more than I bought GTA 5. Remember when GTA 5 came out
and then it came out again and came out again and came out again. I had it on across like
multiple generations of consoles. I had it on steam. I had it on my switch. I think I even had
it on an Xbox and I thought, oh, the switch one that I have is the one with my save file with all
of my stuff because my steam one does not have a lot of the repentance stuff on blocked because I
didn't really play repentance that much, but I did. I thought I did play it on the switch,
but it turns out I don't even own the game on switch. I own up until rebirth, I think on
switch. So I'm like, what's going on? Oh shit. It's probably on like an Xbox, like an Xbox one.
Oh, I don't know. I don't know where my save file is, but that's the way it is. So what I did
and do not, do not think I am a gamer. I got a save file and it's an unlock for everything. It's
as if I completed the game a million percent. I just wanted to do some runs and I'm probably
going to get destroyed. Cheater, cheater, cheater. Yeah, I know. All right. Let me ask you this.
Let's do this right now. Let's do it right now. But I don't know. Nobody. All right.
I'm going to veto this poll if I don't like it. Do you want me to start from the very beginning
from zero and Isaac, or would you rather let's just go and let's just play and everybody has
already seen this a thousand times, right? Like I've played this game. Binding of Isaac is probably
my second or third most played game ever. It's probably Team Fortress, Diablo two,
Binding of Isaac and maybe Warcraft. I have so much time in this game. Let's just play it. Yeah.
Yeah. Fuck it. Whatever. That's the plan. We're just going to hang out and play. I've never seen
Binding of Isaac gameplay. Really? Wow. Well, the game's fantastic. No, I've definitely played this
more than house flipper for sure. I've played this off stream hundreds and hundreds of times
over the course of the last five, 10 years. Can you wait 10 minutes? I need to take a shower.
No, I'll give you two. That's not enough to take a shower, but don't worry.
We're going to, I'm just going to hang it up. That's pretty windy too. Windy here in Vegas.
You might hear it. Are you going to play with funny mods on? Not right now. I think it's more
play. I had a dream where you were on a tour of black Mesa from Half-Life and on stream and you
got killed by a laser. Stop eating before bed. True. Same. Same. How long am I going to stream
for? I don't know. A couple hours, two, three hours. I don't know. Hey, my dog passed away in
December. Sorry to hear that. Name was Bud. Oh, RIP Bud. Sorry to hear that. Hey, do you know that
you were nominated for streamer of the year? I am aware of that and I, I can't believe it. I'm
shocked. I honestly did not expect that at all. And whatever happens, happens. I think that just
being on that list is a win. So I'm happy just being on that list. A lot of people did a lot
of unbelievable things this year. So yeah, that's, I already see it. That's a win for me already.
And also too, I want to just make sure to say, I know that that's a, that's like a big award.
Um, just be respectful, right? That, that's a very, that's a very hot award. Um, and win or lose,
I'm all right. Don't worry. Just be respectful about it, please. But no, it's, it's, it's,
that's awesome. That's fucking crazy. I don't even know what to say. It's hard to even say
anything about it, but hell yeah. It's 10 PM, dude. Yeah, it is. I'm going to play some Isaac.
Do you, do you call it a cold headache or a brain freeze? Definitely a brain freeze.
100% brain freeze. Brain freeze sounds way worse and it feels way worse than a cold headache.
Cold headache to me is a headache is something that lasts more than an hour.
Brain freeze is instant. It's awful. It's painful. It's a brain freeze. It's a freeze. It's not a
headache. Lasts about 10 to 15 seconds. God, I just got the feeling. Did you just feel it?
Oh, anytime I think of the word brain freeze, my roof of my mouth hurts. You peaked at among us.
Yeah, that's all right. I'm cool with that. That's, that's, I'm all right with that. That's fine.
Hey, you know what? If I've peaked at among us, that means I've peaked, right? And hitting a peak
is kind of cool. Don't you think? That's pretty cool. Peaking implies that you hit some form
of high echelon, doesn't it? Very interesting. Some form of it. He hasn't even begun to peak.
But yeah, I don't want to speak too much about the Streamer Awards stuff. I'm
just happy to participate and obviously good luck to everybody. It's great. I, I remember being,
I was lying in bed when I was looking at the awards and I was like, oh, cool. Like,
look at all these nominees. This is really awesome. Oh, the baseball show got nominated.
Oh, that's so cool. Baseball. Cool. Streamer event. So that's cool. And then I got to the,
and I was like, oh, okay. I won League of their own last year. And I saw the nominees. There's,
oh, okay. Cool. Perfect. All right. Cool. There we go. Stream event. All right. I wonder if maybe,
maybe I got a chance. Although chest boxing was fucking unbelievable. Right. And then I got to
the bottom of the list. I said, oh fuck, I'm on this one. I was like, oh shit. But yeah,
that's all I'm going to say about it. Humble Andy. No, I mean, let's be really, really real
for a second. I, I don't even know how to explain it, describe it. It's, it's really cool,
but it's overwhelming too. Does that make sense? It's incomprehensible. Humble Harry. Oh, I bet
they're done with the shower now. Yeah, that's true. Well, look, it's easy. It's, when you look
at what a lot of people have been doing on this platform, I'm just glad to celebrate as many
people as we can. I think it's really cool. When Cutie decided that this is something that she
wanted to do, it's just like, oh, like an award show. That's not like a, it's fan voted and it's
a bunch of streamers get together and kind of hang out for, for a night. And it's just cool.
It's cool. And being in any of those lists or even being, even being invited to that event is
just like, oh shit. Okay, cool. So yeah, that's, that's how I feel. Are you going to wear the same
suit? Uh, I was, I have a, I had a specific request. I believe it was, uh, it was Jake.
Jake said, wear a different suit this year. I was like, all right, I gotta get, I gotta get like
tailored, right? I don't know. I'm gonna show up in fucking tube socks and like a pair of shorts.
Wear a tuxedo? No, I cannot pull a tux off. No way. I don't, I don't know if I like the way
I look in a tux. I kind of look like a goofball on a tux. All right, let's, uh, let's go.
You guys ready? I know people are going to look, people are going to think that I am an
unbelievable video game player. And you see this shit. I even, it's hard for me to look at this,
right? Ready? Oh, new run. Oh, cool. Yeah. Look at all this. Look, I did all this.
I did all of this. I'm very, I'm so good at this game. Oh, also, I want to talk about this for
just a second. There's going to be, uh, people have a lot of questions about Grotto Beasts.
And as we get closer to being able to really announce the launch, which like I said, is this
end of February, this, it's this end of February into the first week of March,
is this like this target here. You're going to see a lot of stuff. I think, uh, the Grotto Beasts
team is working on an FAQ to help answer a bunch of questions. Obviously I'm going to be talking
about a lot. There's some really, really, really cool shit that you'll see eventually here very
soon. All right. Some of these characters I've never even heard of. Let's, let's see. I've,
I've never played with this character. I don't know who this is. Uh, I'll be honest. I'd say
if I played a thousand games of Binding of Isaac, 900 of them were on Cain. Like R1. What is it?
What does this mean? What is this? I don't like that. Is that like super mode? Is that insane
mode? I don't know what any of this means. Maybe I shouldn't have done this. I don't know what any
of this does. It's alternative characters. Oh, this is crazy. Cain is boring. Well, we got to
just, let me just get back. Let me get back in the swing of things here. We're going to go Cain
in greed mode. Yeah. Cain on greed mode. Just to start. I got to remember how to play the game.
I remember a lot about it. This is like one of my favorite games. You picked the wrong one.
Look, I'm, I'm a Cain player. Oh, by the way, I also have a cheat sheet open here. That's a good
start. Wait, where's my, where is it? There it is. Okay. There you go. I like looking at that.
Is it Cain main? Yeah. It hurts. No, it doesn't. Go ahead and get that started. Now let's go cheat
sheet. It hurts. This is the, okay. Taking damage causes Isaac to fire a circle of 10 tiers around
him dealing 10 damage. Okay. So when you get hurt, you fire tears. What the fuck is going on? Cheater.
If you're playing Isaac without a cheat sheet of what items do, you are an encyclopedia. There's a
good mod that just gives you that cheat sheet info in the game. Oh, that's so perfect. How hard is
it to get? Is it like, is it like, is it a simple, like two second download? It's like, it's simple.
It's a steam download. It's a steam mod. It's super simple. Go to the menus and enable it in
the workshop. Okay. All right. Uh, yeah. I'll do that. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah.
That's fine. Let's let the, yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah.
All right. Give me what I, you know what? Hey, start a stream starting soon. I'll be back in a
second. What is it called by the way? Does it have a name? What is it called? External item
descriptions. Steam workshop. Okay. Workshop. It's called. No, it's not. All right. It is
external item descriptions. Oh, the links like there. How do I open this link in steam? Is it
just like on the front page? Uh, where's like most popular install the POG mod? Oh, I don't want to
do a bunch of mods. I don't know. I don't know what they all do. How do I open this in the
workshop? Okay. It's, it's got like a, here's the name. It's like a, it starts with this.
All right. There we go. What does rep mean? Rep. R.I.P. Oh, repentance. Okay. Does this,
does this work for, um, okay. Yeah, it does. There it is. All right. Subscribe.
It'd be good to go. Right? Right. Mods. External item descriptions. So is it press tab to enable
mods. That's on now. All right. Sick. Let's go. No, it's off. Is it on? All right. So let's, uh,
new game. Read. Kane. I've never heard of this before. Okay. Holy shit. That's so good. Imagine
ever playing this game without this turned on, right? That is life changing. I've had that.
There's a, there's a few websites. There's like wikis. There's that platinum god and it's always
you look for the item. I, I've spent a minute, two, three minutes straight looking for the icon.
Wow. All right. That's unbelievable. Thank you. Appreciate it. POG mod is also fun. Yeah. I
remember looking through and not being able to find that item in the icon list and just being
like, Olly, can you, can you use your, can you help me? Can you use my, can you, I need a second
pair of eyes. All right. Tempers and she's just slowing tears. I wonder if there's a chance. Ooh.
Okay. All right. This is not a bad start. That's a lot of damage. I only have one heart though.
Oh, this might be bad. That's so cool. All right. I just gotta go for it. It's been a while. Just
don't get hit. Just don't get hit. Is it, you know, also I'm going to sit back in my chair
because I really, I feel like Isaac is the kind of game where I need to sit far away.
The closer I am, the worse I do. Just don't get hit. So this is, the greedier mode is way harder,
but we're going to, we're going to start with this first. I remember greedier mode was rage
inducing sometimes. Greedier sucks. They just give you less money and the boss at the end has
a second phase and it's awful. But greed is my favorite mode in the game. If you count all the
hours I've spent in this game, most of them are probably here. Okay. Uh, let's go. It's a horrible
take. That's fine. I'll be the weirdo that likes this more than anything else. How's auto? Auto's
good. All right. Do I, I definitely, I need this unfortunately. Ooh, wait, this is a good one.
That's health and tears up. Oh yeah. Play red dead, undead nightmare. I've been in the middle
of a burp for five straight seconds. No. Okay. I'm good. Pretty good damage so far.
Just burp already. Yeah, but sometimes it takes a little while. Oh, four seconds is bad. Oh my
God. I hate those little things. They, I feel like they take so long to kill. Those things sit at zero
HP for, it seems like an eternity. The rest of the stuff in here is kind of junk, isn't it?
Random stat up, random stat down. Yeah, this thing sucks. I need a bomb. This is, this is bad. Look
at all this money that's left on the table here. That really sucks. This would probably be like
another 10 cents at least spike room. I'm, I only have two hearts. I'm afraid to go in here,
but I'm gonna, I'm gonna, whatever. And that's exactly why you go in. That's why you do that.
Uh, I can't get them both, but I will be able to get them both. Thank you. Is it, is it up? There
you go. Secret room. HP tears up, shot speed down. What kind of bad, you're going to be pissing up a
storm later. Sorry to be the, oh, you're not talking to me. All right. I'm going to be,
is, this is stupid. This is a really bad idea because I would, I should save this for the other
floor, but I'm going for it. I don't care. Not a bad trade. Uh, Kane's, Kane, I fucked up. Uh,
Kane starts with a paper clip, which opens up chests. All right. Whoops. Hey, it's all right.
Worked out. What a fake Kane main. Uh-oh. I got one hit. I haven't played in a while either.
You guys are going to have to help me when eventually we get to the part where, um, you
know, it's like, Oh, go down this hallway to get to this secret area, beat that secret area,
pick up that item and then bring that item to the next area and then go down the hole. And that's
how you get to delirious, whatever his name is. Cause I have no idea. Uh, I think that's actually
pretty good for here because I can use it every single, uh, spawn. Yeah. Every time a new wave
happens, I can do it again. Right? No tinted rocks. Don't miss anything. I have a key. I'm good. I
could check this wall here, but we're not going to do that. Cause it's a waste. All right, let's go.
I mean, I'm doing it here. Oh, what am I doing? Oops. Whatever. I could have done. It could have
been secret room. Just burnt my tongue. Dude. That sucks. Really? Ooh. Ouch. Ouch, man. That sucks.
What five damage up for each enemy killed in the room. Capsa plus. Oh, that's awesome. Especially
if you're green speed. Always good. Hmm. Is it? Well, I'm definitely going to get that.
It's a full day. Look, I have 7.2 damage is actually really good. Am I using a mod? Yep. Uh,
I just heard about this mod 15 minutes ago. So you open the blocks with the paper clip. Oh,
you can't unfortunately, but yes, this mod just tells you what everything does. Well,
I definitely want that first. All right, let's go. Yeah. The whatever Guppy's head is, is pretty
awesome early game. You just do it every single spawn. What do you mean? Shadow is messing me up
with a reflection or whatever. Oh, oh, fuck. I'm fine. I'm actually like freaking out right now.
Oh, all right. We're OK. OK, definitely this. All right. Uh, are the mod friend folio an entire
community expansion of the game? I lost the damage bonus that I had before. How did I have that?
How did I have that damage bonus? It was already a 7.2. Am I seeing things? I always got to left
the room, right? Shit. There we go. I got to I have to be good about that. Well, I had to leave
the room because if I take one hit, I would be dead. We're good. Build it back up. I'm not going
to leave. What? This reflective ground sucks. So I'm no screaming. It's fucking like it's late.
This screwed me up. I didn't die. Somebody said F. No, I didn't. I hate this little thing.
This thing always kills me. Oh, my God. OK, that was a warm up.
OK, that's a warm up. That was just warming up. We're just warming up.
It's all right. Look, we're even going to get the same items. I get the same items.
Die to fire. I thought I put it out. Oh, that's kind of sad. Booster pack. Oh,
booster pack. Is it grotto beast? Not yet. Oh, what was that? What's this? What's this? What's
happening? What is this thing? What does this do? Oh, my God. What does this mean?
Should I stop freaking out? What does this mean? I've never seen this before. Get it fast.
Keep freaking out. That's the golden penny. It's a lot of money. It's just keep. No, no, no, no.
Keep freaking out. Keep freaking out. I'm going to get overwhelmed. I got to kill stuff. Will it
stay there? Oh, shit. It keeps responding until it stops. Oh, OK. I think it stopped. All right.
I think it's tough. I've never seen that before. I've never seen that. I think I think I'm going to
die. You. OK, we're fine. That was crazy. Thirty three coins. Definitely this is the value on this
good. I feel like this is too random, although I could get the one that doubles the coins.
Yeah, let's do it. This is just hearts. This is the devil, which is this is double keys.
Ancient recall, draw three cards. Oh, my God. Death, the sun, the joker. Oh, the hierophant.
I guess I just double the keys and then double the keys. Right. Is this a way? Did I have to?
Now, this is the sun. This is. Should I buy a key and then double the keys? I can't. I'm just
going to do it of speed. It's a free key. And then this is just hearts. So who cares? This is
damage. Right. But who cares? I hold on to the sun. The sun card is the best one.
I'm going to hold on to the sun card. The rest of these. I don't think they really do very much.
Use the joker, the joker. OK, so the joker gives me a free item room. Right. Or is it the secret
room? Wait, let me read it. It reports Isaac to the devil or. Oh, yeah, but I'm going to do that
anyways. Just do it for free so I don't have to fight the nightmare thing. I guess that makes
sense. Yeah, that makes sense. Oh, come on. Oh, come on. Come on. Forgot he did that move.
My range is awful. Why is my range so bad? Cane. Stinks. I mean, it's good. Yeah. All right. Let's
now let's go here. Sun cards, the thing to take. Yeah. Then I'm going to open the door.
Hell is the everything jar. Spawns pickups based on the number of charges. Charge one, two, three,
four, five. This item is based. That's really, really good. It's active. OK, so how many charges
should I really wait for then? Yeah, it's per room. Do it between nine charges. Is it gold?
Depends on what you need. Hold the map button. Oh, that's really cool. OK. Well, there's no reason
to do it for one. Two is a coin. Three is a bomb for. Wait, what is the. I forget what the gold.
What is the gold bomb? Infinite bombs, infinite bombs for the whole floor. Oh, my God. OK.
Do not hold R. Hold the R button to activate POG mod. Oh, good for you. It's too bad you didn't
say that two minutes ago because I don't have the POG mod installed. That was a good attempt,
though. I do appreciate the attempt. Let's just go. I'm going to keep the sun. Oh, man.
You always have to look and see what those are, if it's possible, because if it's the double coins
one, you win automatically in greed mode. I get a bomb. Use the devil one as a different card.
It is. Whoa. So I just use it. Oh, my God. I thought I thought the devil car was just damn well.
That's different. I've never unlocked that. Cool. Good thing I have somebody else's save file.
Nice. Let's go. Oh, it is. It is. Wait, put it down. Put it down. How do I put it down?
Hold. How do I put it down? How do I put it down? How do I put it down? How do I put this down?
You hold a button. It's hold R, isn't it? But I thought I can't. I thought don't hold R,
though. I thought everyone said don't hold R. R is reset. Oh, OK. We're good. That's what I
wanted. All right. So now what? What's this one? Shit. I can't take them both. All right. Well,
I'm keeping it. It was a check. Oh, I thought I could only do it. All right. Sorry. We're good.
I don't need it. I'm going to be going to be dog shit in there anyways.
Oh, pretty good. Very good. Now I get to 40. I get to 50 coins and I get 100 coins and then
we can just go on a complete shopping spree. That's why I love greed mode. Don't buy anything.
Just just I got to make sure I don't lose all matters. I can't even tell how many charges
that is. I wish it was just a number because the amount of real estate that you have to looking
up in the corner of the screen is like death. I pay attention. Just do it when it's over eight.
Nine. Should I do it now? What's that do? Do it nine always then, because that when that removes it,
it gives me health. Right. I mean, it gives me money. All right. I'm only shit. OK. I'm good.
Very cool. Give me some damage up. And this is pretty much a good game.
Could be at least I think he does the bounce. Yep. Does it again. Sometimes you change it together
and it's annoying. Forty one. Try to get the habit so you get a charge every time you get hit.
Take the devil deal. Hold on. I could do it now. Would you be close enough? Right.
Yeah, I'm going to do it now. Here's up to point. I need the range up and it spawns a lucky penny.
Nice. I needed that so badly. I want this for random. I don't like these. Let's just do.
No, it's not as good as I have. I key reroll. Hmm. Oh, what is this? Is that a smore?
I want the smore item. Must be charged. Oh, it must be charged by picking up soul hearts,
then spawns three soul hearts, two angel room items, only spawns two soul hearts and one angel
item if a devil deal was taken previously. I don't think that's good here. Soul hearts.
Where am I going to get so I could make them, but it would take like that's not worth it.
Oh, wait, it doesn't know what this is. Oh, what is this? I know that was dumb,
but we could. But it could have been another double coin. You understand what I'm saying?
Enemies in current room are weakened, slowed and take double damage for one minute. Um, yeah.
What do you mean? No, what do you mean? No, it couldn't have. Yes, it could have.
You can read what it is. No, look in the corner, the question mark. No, you know. All right. All
right. All right. All right. All right. I am ready to move. I've got enough and dominate this.
Quick tip for those of you that are a new dividing of Isaac. If it's two enemies,
they share the same health pool, but focus one. Otherwise you'll have to handle two enemies the
entire health bar. Focus one first. Make sure to get that down. Three broken hearts. This is,
this one's like too confusing to me. Eh, I never liked the orbiting, uh, orbiting items.
The knife is good, but you have to, you have to walk up and I always screw it up and get hurt.
All right. So what does a broke grants? Three broken hearts. So it's 0.75 damage.
Every fatal hit. What is it? Does that mean when I die, it blocks me? I can't die. That seems kind
of unbelievable, but it's going to lower your max HP. That's all right. It's going to be careful.
All right. Cool. I don't think I want anything else. It'd be nice to get these bombs. So why not?
Uh, I'm, it's worth the trade for me. I don't want the bombs. Well, broken hearts kills you.
Yeah, but I'll be, I'm not, I'm not going to get hit. You see how, how much is,
what's happening here? Look at this. Crazy chocolate or honey Teddy grams. Um, I'm going
with straight up original when I haven't eaten any of these. I haven't eaten this in probably 20
years. That's good. Charm tears. 10%. Can't you press buttons really fast? Oh yeah. Fast enough.
Ooh, we got a sale. We got a sale. We got a sale is huge. Look at all this. All right. There's a way
for me to do this with one bomb. Isn't there? Not. What is that? What does it pick up the bed?
Really? Wait, opens the door to the hush floor, regardless of the timer. Uh-huh. It's useless.
Could I go to fight the hush right now? Uh, I want to continue this. Wait, how much more?
I haven't even started to yet. Yeah. I'm just going to do it. I'm not going to use it.
Battery. Shit. That's the good one. Isn't it? Active items can be charged up twice and used
twice in a row. This bar soap, the eraser. Um, these are all active items, aren't they? Just
reroll. I'll reroll. Ooh, this thing is really good. You get items for free with this thing.
Definitely want that. And these are all kind of good. I think this is a win shaping up to be that
you see some more damage. Whoa, shit. Oh my God. My hands. Hold on a second. You ever just like sit
in your chair and like, for no reason, everything is insanely uncomfortable for like 10 straight
seconds. It's just like, wow, like everything. I hate sitting here right now. You know what I
mean? It's like, fuck. And then it goes away and everything's fine. That's so much money.
I want to use it. Just keep rolling. As long as I don't do something stupid. This should be good.
Sure. I got a dentist appointment in the morning and I might have to have my wisdom teeth removed.
Um, I think pretty much everybody has to go through that. So don't worry. I had my wisdom
teeth taken up. Range. Yeah. Those of you that are lucky to not even have wisdom teeth, right?
That can happen. You're lucky. That's good. I was born with no wisdom teeth. That's really good
because you don't have to do any of this shit. Yeah. Giga Chad. Yeah. Skill issue. Having wisdom
teeth is a skill issue. I want the range. Divorce papers plus one bone heart tears up. Spawns the
mysterious paper trinket. What's the paper trinket? Is it any good? Bad. All right. I'm good.
This is, I got a good build right now. I don't mess it up. I couldn't even afford it anyways.
Yeah, that was easy. Oh, that's one of my favorite items. Purgatory. Red cracks spawn on the ground
of hostile rooms. Welcome to the crack. Someone's homing exploding. No. And then this. Oh, this is
the one I lost. Does it take away the bad hearts? Of course not. Still really good. It's worth it.
I didn't go in here, but I'm not going to. All right, let's go. Okay. Well, I keep forgetting.
Speed up. Very good. It's okay. I feel like I have to take this. You missed a coin. Zero out of 10.
Where's there a coin? I didn't miss a coin. What are you talking about? In the Satan room?
There was a coin in the devil room. What? You're lying. You're lying. Hold on. This is important.
Hey, just got word from the boss. If you lose this run, you are contractually obligated to
install the POG mod. Sorry, King. I don't make the rules. And then they're crunching. There's
a cat crunching on a brick and like emote eating a brick or something. Um, all right. I hate doing
this, but I have to. Oh, at least I know what it is. What about that one? Nice. Now what is this?
Bone heart. What just happened? Did it take my bone heart? Wait, my money. Oh fuck. Wait a minute.
What? God damn it. Sorry. I don't need that. All it does is just makes your, uh, familiars
stick in much closer. Here's up range up and spawns three random hearts. Yes, I will take it.
And those are great. Those are great hearts to have. This is, this is really great. I should
absolutely wipe the floor with everything now. What is this? Mucormycosis. I'm terrified of this,
but I'm going to get it. Explode. What the fuck is all this? Oh, I forgot. I didn't do this part.
Don't remind me that this is in here. All right. Pretty good. Very good actually. Whoa. And that
hurt me. No. Okay. Good. Jesus. Yeah. I definitely going to win. There's no way I don't. Well,
I mean, who knows? Who knows? Oh, Vinny. Vinny raid. Vinny raid. What's up? Vinesauce viewers.
Thanks to the Ray Vinny. We're just doing some late night Binding of Isaac. It's been a while
since I walked out of the room, but it's okay. We're good to go. Uh, if you've never played
Binding of Isaac, check it out. Card in the item room. Yeah. I'm not going anywhere yet.
What was that? What was Vinny doing tonight? I made some friends in college
because we all enjoy your streams. That's really cool. That makes me happy. That makes me feel
really great. Hope you guys become pretty good friends. Am I going to get coins if I do this?
No, they have to have coins in their eyes, right? All right. It's time for me to, uh,
activate this and then leave and everybody yelled at me because I missed an item. This actually is
kind of horrible. Hold on. Oh, I was mad and then I was happy. It hurt. It hurt, but I made a bunch
of money. What is this thing? Wow. Okay. Guppy's hairball. Moving swings the hairball around the
ball grows when it kills an enemy. Dude, these are both good because won't it just grow permanently
if I don't leave the room? Piercing tears and they ease this. Okay. All right. I don't want to
go too crazy here because I'm, I don't have that much help. It's deceiving. I feel like I should
probably get this. Okay. And then this too, right? Cause I get a half a soul heart every time a new
floor. Does that count when we're greed mode? D6 D6 rerolls, pedestal items. That's pretty good,
but I, I feel like this thing is so much better. There's only two more floors. Yeah. So I think I
want to keep the money busted, dude. You have to get it. It's too late. It's too late for that.
Maybe next, uh, next fucking round, dude. I don't think I want anything. Yeah. I'm not shopping
anymore. Not about the money. Use the jar right now. This is seven. That's a card, right? Oh no.
Is it seven or eight? Use the jar and then get the D6. It shows what it is. Look in the jar. It has
the item. Late night hangout session. Just chilling. No, we don't, we don't, we're not
like paying that much attention to what's inside of the thing. Nah, no, I'm saving my money. No,
I don't want anything. I got, I still have another floor to go. Two more. Let's go. I'm leaving.
Thank you. Bro. Bro. Bro. Shaking my head. Uh, how do I get rid of the menu on the right?
I don't like that one. I like the one on the left. I like dog food. Nice. Remember
your tea. Oh shit. Thank you. Yes. Ooh, good. That's not so good, but that means I don't die.
Clearing rooms no longer charges active items. Feeling damage to enemy slowly fills up the
charge bar. This one's good. Red stew. What is that? 21 damage up. The damage up wears off over
three minutes. Excuse me. Killing enemies while the effect is at. So will this last through the
next floor? Buy that at the end and speed run the last floor. All right. Yeah. I think that's,
I'm going to buy this at the end and then just rent through the rest of the game. Watch that
be the downfall. Wait, I hate this thing. The Ludovico technique. This thing's awful. This is
the worst item in binding of Isaac, isn't it? I think it actually might be the worst item in
the whole game. Yeah, I'm not taking it. I'm going to do this though. Really? All right. Let's go.
Oh my God. Absolutely. What an ungodly amount of damage. Just absolutely ungodly. I don't even
know what's on the screen. That person just spawned over here. Luckily. Holy shit. Okay.
Don't leave. That's why this game gets so wacky. If you get the right materials, whatever. Shit.
I want an angel room for once. Oh, I thought it was the other way. I thought it was horizontal.
You don't wait. What you have to skip. People were just spamming something. Call is really good.
You're going to one shot breed. Oh, okay. Okay. So I got 57 coins. I want to make sure I do this in
the right order. Ooh, yes. Take reds. Take the 4.5 volt. Okay. I still want money for the end,
right? Pill discount. Yeah, the pill sucks though. Throne keys deal damage. Stew and go? Stew and go.
Stew and leave. All right. All right. All right. Right. I'm taking the stew and I'm fucking running.
Go. Hurry up. Oops. How can I tell how much time I have left? Oh my God. Do I just, who cares? Just
leave? I think I just have to leave. Do I even buy anything? What is it? I don't know what to do.
What's happening? I don't know what's happening. Let's go. Go. Go. Go. Go. Go. Hurry. Hurry. Hurry.
Go. Go. Go. Go. Go. Go. Go. Go. Go. Go. Oh my God. What should I do? Should I use the item?
Holy shit. What the fuck just happened? What just happened? What did I just do?
Oh my God. What the fuck is happening? What is this thing? Ace of diamonds?
I have 70 coins. I should have done greedier. Damn. Greedier would have been simple.
Oh, I already got it. Did I do something wrong? Broke it. Is that bad? It goes, does it go back to
zero? All right. Nice. That was a good first run. You've already unlocked everything. Well, I haven't
unlocked everything. Somebody else did. And I just put the save file onto my computer. All right.
Let's do a real one. Why do I have a million of these? Oh. All right. You guys are going to have
to guide me to some cool, crazy new content. So one of the big problems I have with Isaac. Have
you guys ever jumped on a trampoline before? You ever get off of a trampoline and then jump normally
on the ground and it feels crazy. It almost feels like gravity is times 10. When I finish an Isaac
run and I start over, it's that same feeling of, Oh, I feel like I have just dumbbells attached to
me. We just go, what is that? Is this gold? Money? I've never seen it. Gold rocks. It's gold. Yep.
Gold. Not bad. Playing as Kane. Unfortunately, I have no bombs. Probably the worst character in
the game. As you get a hit on the first floor in Isaac, how many hours do you have in this game?
Over a thousand. Try Tainted Kane. Kane has PhD in repentance. He does? Wait, he does have better
pills, doesn't he? I was wasting $5. Tainted Lost is really fun. Well, I don't need it right now.
I do want to go over here. Secret room may be right here. Yep. Very happy about that. What
does Tainted Lost do? When was the last time you played this game? It was actually not that far
away. It was fairly recent. I want to say five, four months ago, four or five months ago.
And I didn't play for very long though. I come back to this game very frequently, play it for
a few days, play it for a week or two, and then it goes back on the shelf. Another couple of years
go by. I was back out. Maybe another six months goes by. I was back out. Just always there.
Oh, that's good. Have you ever 100% legit? No, no way. The furthest I ever got was
Delirium? I don't think I even beat Delirium. No, I beat Delirium. I think I beat Delirium a couple
times. Whatever expansion that was, that was the end. I want to go, no, let's just go. It was like
10 years ago. Delirium wasn't 10 years ago. Delirium was after birth, right? Or anti-birth?
Anti-birth was the mod that Repentance is based off of, right? I streamed that. I streamed that.
Forget about this. Yeah, you, all right. I remember you need to have spirit hearts,
bombs, right? I forget, I forget what you actually need. Double vision. One key, two bombs? No,
it's key, two bombs, two hearts. All right. My mom thinks you give cool tips and tricks. I don't have
the heart to tell her what you really do. Why are you making this sound so sinister?
I mean, we just like hang out and like crack jokes and play games.
It's not, I don't think it's that sinister. All right, let's go. I'm just going to do it.
Wait, what does the double vision actually do? I didn't read it. 50% chance of adding an extra
blind item in treasure rooms. So I can take two. That's pretty awesome. What about the super secret
room? I always skip the super secret room because I never know like reliably where it is, but it
has to be connected to a singular room. So therefore it could be the one all the way at the bottom.
It could be the boss room. It could be the big room. Wait, why is the big room? What's going on here?
Oh, cause I took the pill. Right, right, right, right. Wow. Well, okay.
What does the bone heart do? I'm filling it. I just filled it up. Oh, it's three hits. That's
really cool. So without a cheat sheet and without the mods to tell you, do you think this game is
more in need of you having a wiki open than Elden Ring? I think, I think actually, yes,
I think so. All right. So, uh, I need two bombs here, right? Or I need two soul hearts.
Okay. Which one of this is, oh my God, stay on the screen, dude, dude, get over here. Oh my God. And
I'm not even doing my own Isaac rule. So my Isaac rule is look, spend at least 60% of the time
playing the game, looking at where, at just you at Isaac only. If you look at Isaac only,
this goes for other bullet hell kind of games too. Don't look at the fucking thing shooting at you.
Look at the area in a circle around Isaac and just move out of the way. Done. Nice ego.
So I get to take both of these, which is one, uh, probably this. Yeah, this one's cool.
This one's more snappy. This one is better. Ah, spectacle tears are better.
Isn't there something weird with the bucket? Isn't there something weird?
Something strange with a bucket, right? I have to like go in one or something
or I need to, I need to blow one up. Something strange. I forget what it was.
It's a mirror. Oh, you throw up in a bucket. Oh yeah. You puke in the bucket. Secret room.
Um, right here. Watch this. So many people just went like, no, no, no. And I was right.
Yikes. That hurt. I don't want to lose the spirit heart. Otherwise the run is over.
The secret roomkeepers. Oh, that's right. This is not greed mode.
That's a volume. Should I turn it up a little or is it a, is it a good, is it a good volume
for like snoozing? What do you think? Good. I already answered that question by saying fuck you.
Oh, man. You're supposed to be snoozing. It's supposed to be like chill string.
Doesn't this mean something? This means something, doesn't it? That means something.
Bomb. Nice shop. Why is this shop so bad if this 999 coins donated? It's better than nothing.
Two of hearts. I lost my spirit heart. What? What? That kinda sucks. That kinda sucks.
Okay. I have a spirit heart. Did someone say, how do you have every unlock? Um, I just got the save.
That's just a save file that unlocks everything. I normally wouldn't have done that. But like I
said, in the beginning of the stream, if you weren't here, I've downloaded this game like
six times across like four generations of consoles and computers. So I just don't have,
I don't know where my real save file is. And it wasn't on the switch though. Oh, well hold down
R like right, like right bumper. What does it do? Hey, what'd you, what'd you do?
I was gonna, I thought I made it all the way out. Those things suck. Uh, tapeworm is,
eh, it's just range. Oh, this fire. Wait, there's something with the fire, right? Now what? Now go
in? Go in where? Find the mirror now. You just ruined the run. I did. I need to go find the
mirror. There it is. Okay. All right. What? I don't, I think I've only done this once ever.
What do I do? Don't get hit. But where do I go? Oh Jesus. These things suck. I'm dead. I lost.
I lose? Why did you tell me to do that? I've never done that before. What? What is it? Robo baby?
You walked in it. Oh, this thing is awesome. All right. I care more about this one anyways.
I can just be a coward. This is perfect. You did that on your own accord. Yeah, but I, I don't know.
I didn't know it was the equivalent of people telling me to hold R. I thought it was like an
item. By the way, I'm playing the game with the other character. I'm just trying to avoid getting
hit. Bro, what are you doing? I'm hiding and playing the game with the robot. I just love when that
happens. Already a better run. Yup. Already a better run. And watch this. I'm not going to
use this because I need two to get down to that place. I will always have two. I was going to
play good. Why are you a Reddit avatar? Kind of weird map. Here's up. You don't need soul hearts.
You just need to survive two hearts worth of damage. Did they change that? Was that different?
I feel like it was two soul hearts before. It was an anti-birth. Oh, okay. It was a change from
repentance. Whoa, they're in the ground. Bro, what are you doing? Is it meat in here? What is this?
I feel like I can blow that up. Yeah. I think I'll roll the dice here. It's pretty good for
my coward gameplay. It's a nice chill stream. I like it. Thanks for streaming. Thanks for hanging
up. Coward strat's not going to work against the mother. Hold on. I think it's going to work
pretty well. Really? I'm standing in the corner and I still got hit by that. That was like the
DVD menu that always hits the edges and never gets in the corner. And it went in the corner first
try. Let's just go from all sides. Hmm. Droid rage. There's two or just one. Go kill it. That's
not worth it. Too spooky is great for cowards. But I have, I'm going to literally one heart. No,
I can't take that. I take too many hits already. Wait, I can open that for free.
Let's see what's in here. Donate. That's cheating though. Just that I want to make sure everyone's
aware. My power might go up. It's very windy here in Vegas. Lights just flickered. So just be aware.
If it does, it was cool. It was really cool hanging out with you for a couple hours,
but that I did. The lights just flickered. So we'll see. If that's the case, a fantastic rest
of your night. Take care of yourselves. I'll see you again soon. But let's just operate on the
fact that it's not going to. All right, let's go. This very high wind gust in Vegas right now.
Yeah, sometimes it can get really wild. The big difference between this was actually kind of an
eye-opening experience for me because I lived in obviously Massachusetts, right? And Massachusetts,
it was snow, snow and rain. I had never really experienced high winds my whole life until moving
out here. And sometimes, I mean, sometimes you'll be sitting there out. We'll just be hanging out
and you hear. And it's as if there is a monster outside trying to knock down everything. It's,
it seriously feels like there's somebody like outside trying to like, like a gigantic monster
trying to like attack. It's fucking terrifying sometimes. Especially when you get those like
50 mile per hour gusts that the room kind of shakes the windows. You'll hear it. It's like
with this huge, scary gust behind it. And that's this is new. I've never experienced that before.
I remember there was a windstorm so bad that you could lean into it and not fall over. Whoa,
what's this thing? Spawn six random book of virtues wisps. I just take them. I don't know
what this does. Just use it. Use it when somebody did a troll face. What love crafty in hell do you
live in? Oh, Viva Las Vegas. I don't know what this does, but I'm gonna, I'm gonna keep it for
like an hour. I'm not doing that shit again. This is a rock. Vegas is a modern above ground hell.
Maybe I'm just like a contrarian or something, but I like it out here a lot. Talked about it
the other day. I really, I like it out here. Anytime you ever hear somebody talk about Vegas,
it's like, Oh, what a fucking P what a dumb place is a piece of shit. And I'm just like, I like it
here. I like enjoy it here. I think when people think of Vegas, they just think of slot machines
and drugs and fighting. So I'm not supposed to be screaming. It's late, but it's not really just that
it's 11 AM. What do you mean? It's so late for the North American audience late night.
Ooh, well, I don't want to do that because I don't want to touch the donation machine.
This is not bad so far. I could really use some better tears though. These tears are kind of
plain and boring. Oh wow. How do I tell my dog? He's a dog. Your dog does not understand English.
He understands the phonetic way that you pronounce his name and he hears that and he
locks that into memory. He knows like probably four words. Your dog knows probably 10 words total.
So if you tell your dog like your thesis statement or like a paper or something,
if he's going to be, he's going to hear if someone you talk to your dog, this is what he hears.
Mm hmm. Food. Good boy.
Your dog can process the language that you're saying by associating it with things.
They can, well, how many words can a dog know? It's like 20, right? Like 15. Dogs can like
understand like up to like 10 to 20 words or something, right? Like it's like, it's a little
low. It's 20. It's like 200. It's 400. It's 150. 60 to 180. 60. Yeah. Yeah. So they're,
and the thing is, here's the great thing about a dog. Dogs are so unbelievable because they so
badly want to understand. You know what I mean? They so badly want to understand what you are
trying to tell them. 180. Yeah. So basically 10. Yeah. But I was, I mean, I was very wrong,
but I was making a very clear point. If you try to tell your dog that they're a dog,
they're going to just hear the words that they understand, which is probably like treat.
Like, oh God, the light's flickered again. Oh, going down with the ship, boys and girls.
I'm going to keep this. You know, you got to think of a really funny cutoff word.
Cool. That was a big one. That was, I don't know if you heard that probably not over the game,
but that was, that one was chunky. That still has spikes on it. Worth it. You're going to be
in the wizard of Oz soon. Uh, reusable fortune. Question authority. What does that do? Is that
just the fortune telling machine? It's only 27 miles per hour. You'll be fine. Well, the powers
to well, gusts probably could be potentially more than that. Oh my God. I want that. That's, um,
that is amazing. Uh, should I just take all the money? I don't care. Give it, give me all the
money. Cheats, cheats, cheats, cheats, cheats, cheats, cheats. What does this thing do again?
I don't know. Friends from beyond. Just gives you from friends. Is it friends for the floor?
Friends for the room. I imagine it's probably just for the room. I don't need this anymore.
As long as they stay alive. Okay. Cool. Dude, get out, get away from me. I thought it was
going to bounce off the wall. Actually, probably the best three stats to get upgraded. Oh, I need
another bomb. That's the fire and then go in the mirror. I, that's how I died last time. I better
get this. I have to try as hard as I can. Where is the mirror? Is there a way I can make sure I
don't die or just play very well? Just be good and don't get hit. I already got, I mean, it's
already over. What did I do this? I'm leaving. You have light floating attack. Why? It seems kind of
good. What? Oh, did I just lose a heart by doing this in here? I did. I was on autopilot. I just
lost a heart. I think I have three bombs now. All right. Don't mess around. Where's my buddy?
Get up here and do stuff. Nice. Okay. Give me the item. Use the soul. Use the soul. Use the soul.
Oh, cool. I keep going. Should I fight the boss? I have a question. If I use this right now, will
it give me another hit? That's too risky. I'm going to go for it. Whatever. What's the worst
that happens? I lose. I think I'll be all right. Whoa. Oh, it's the same boss. That's fine. Yeah,
we're good. Here's up exactly what I wanted. All right. So now do I just go back through the
mirror? Cool. Good. That's not so bad. Yeah, that's all I really want to do anyways. Tinted rock.
Where is he? Yep. You're right. God damn it. Cheater. No, I did. I cheated to get that money.
You're absolutely right. Look at this speed. Secret room. There's a lot of places where it
could be. I don't really know which one. Hey, is it true that you bought a toilet plunger? 15 pounds
of brown beef and a... No, I can already tell you that's not true because of the second one.
Okay. Is that really worth two bombs? I don't think so. He's vegan. I'm not vegan. I'm not vegan.
He hates animals then. Come on. Oh, I ate red meat. Oh, you must be a fucking monster.
No, I... But I'm not vegan. Wow. What are you? Dumb? No, but I... Come on, man. Oh, this little guy
with a little rock. I will tell you that I have really tried to, I don't know, be a little more
aware of... Just like what I'm eating. Trying to cut back on... Trying to be better about what I'm
eating. Trying to eat more fish, right? Less meat overall. Just because, you know, I'm getting older.
Why don't I just do that? Re-stock. Never-ending stores. Oh my god. This is ridiculous. Okay.
So let's do this. Let's do this. Oh, it's not a full heart. Well, now it is. And now it is again.
That is actual bullshit. Why did I even buy that? Rip deals? You've wasted... What do you mean rip
deals? I got... Dude, I've got an end-game Zelda heart container over there. I'm fine. I could get
hit a hundred times and be alive. I'm good. No, this is not even end-game Zelda. I don't think I
have a... This is 100% completionist Andy Zelda. I think I fought Ganon with like seven hearts.
Stop saying Andy. It's not gonna happen. I'm sorry. Clutch. I've never fought this boss before.
Oh, I get it. This is kind of fucked up. How could I have all these hearts? Jesus. Oh my god. He like
glues to you. Okay. Well, that's the first time I've ever seen that guy. I do need more damage.
Well, that's amazing to have. I think I still want to keep the hostile fly. That's a full heal.
It's incredible. I still want the... Don't... Thought I went in an accidently. Oh, the item room.
My power went out. LMAO. Be careful. God damn windy out there. But yeah, I'm trying to eat a
little bit better. And hey, however you eat, it's up to you. Are you vegetarian? All right.
Let's go. Up to you. You eat a bunch of meat. It's up to you. Ooh, angel room. Although I...
I do think that just for me personally, trying to cut back on just meat, meat like meat and cheese
is... It's just better. Just better for my slow 40-year-old fucking man metabolism. Man-sized
meals. Is there even enough time to do this still? Well, it's probably better at this point.
Re-rolls and restarts the floor. I think I might just do that. Why not?
What a McDonald's Andy. But I don't eat McDonald's every day. Neither should you.
This is the worst item in the game. I mean, whatever. Oh, thanks. Wait, you're 40? What am
I doing here? I don't know. You tell me. This dude is fucking ancient. I think I'm just going to do
it. Yeah, let's do it. Free stuff. I got tons of money. Not tons of money. I got tons of hearts.
Jesus. Well, now I do have tons of money. My God. How many pills?
Nah. That's a cool item, but I've obviously got way too much money.
Tammy's head is all right. Well, let's gamble. Candy heart. Pure love. Holy shit. Picking up
red hearts gives permanent stat upgrades. Seems really good. What is... Okay. Oh, that's cool.
Let's just do it. Oh, I turned it off. Shit. Oh, I didn't turn it off. It's kind of fun to do.
How do I already have 70 coins again? Break rocks and secret room entrances and damage enemies.
Landing a hit with the axe reduces its charge. Better than the cookbook, but this is probably
better overall. I can't even do it. Oh, I mean, no, I can't even do it. Stop buying pills. Well,
Kane has better pills. I'm trying to get stat increases with that. I'm not trying to get health.
Look at Amara. I'm already doing an ungodly amount of damage. Okay. Yeah, let's go. I fucking hate.
I hate this item. Who's shooting the boogers? Oh, it's a random baby, right? Oh my God.
That's great. No one's forcing you to use the book. Well, how am I supposed to do the use the
cookbook challenge? Is there everybody voted for a couple hours ago? I don't want to do that.
I already found the secret room. That's a lot of minus twos. Geez. That's an ungodly amount of
minus twos. I'm getting my ass kicked. Wait, what's going on? One makes you larger? Why is
it showing me that? Oh, okay. I want to be bigger. I want them to be able to hit me with incredible
ease. What does that do? I need to get all three of them. Oh, cool. Okay. I'll do it. Who's this
little guy I have here? I like it. Wait, what is it? Oh shit. Okay. Sorry, I'm reading mod chat.
Um, hold on. I need to write something. No, no, everything's good. No, I'm not. Wait, why is
this still happening? Oh, okay. I already have good pills. What does it do? Wait, should I just
get free pills? Does it make them even better? I don't think I need any items. Yeah, I was just
reading something in my chat. We're talking about something. It's really, really cool. Really nice.
It's a really, really cool, really, really nice thing. All right. Okay. And let me pay attention
now. Touch every button. All right. So buy hearts. Uh, I could buy hearts. You're right. As well.
Stock up. I'm going to say it's right. All right. There's the third one. Should I not press it yet?
Maybe I shouldn't. I think I've realistically only done this route three times. Maybe ever.
What's this? Press it and get in the mine cart. Where am I going? Why do they lose stats? Where's
all my stuff? What is this? Why is there nothing in here? Okay. No, didn't I? Have I never done
this? Is this? When did they add this? I piece too. That's fantastic. Um, how do I get out of here?
Oh God. Thank God. I have so much help. You. What do I do with that? I think I just figured that out.
Hurry up. I did it. Okay. Cool. Now what's the price of electricity? All right. That was pretty
cool. So what's the, what's the, what's the protocol now? Where do I go? Just keep going.
Just get more health. I have the sun. So that's good. Thankfully this baby is amazing. I could
go buy. Oh, there we go. I could go buy hearts though. There's a lot of damage. That's that.
It's better. That's just way better than the, uh, in the book. Please.
Hmm. The sacrifice room always seemed like just a waste to me. You have to step on it like seven
times for it to do anything good, right? Is that better than the laser? I could go in there and
get hit a bunch of times and use the sun card. Ooh, that's just amazing. This thing finds to the,
I wish I had this permanently turned on. This thing finds tinted rocks and secret rooms is
awesome. I don't have to, I don't even have to look, do the sacrifice room. I don't,
I really don't want to, I want all heal, use it 13 times. Exactly. No, it's not worth it.
The sun card is a full heal. Whatever this last boss is of repentance. Do you really think I'm
going to do this with only being able to take like eight hits? No way. Although
worth it. Don't do it this run. No, yeah. I, I don't even know what the boss is.
Whatever the final boss is with the knife or whatever, or whatever, whatever I get,
I don't know. Is it delirium? Nice. Strength, sun, get out of jail free card. Open all doors in the
current room. Uh, I'm just going to do this. I feel like it's the sun though. Use strength and
just keep. Yeah. Like I'll see it, but I feel like I want the full heal. You want to do the
true final boss. I'd like to see it. I'm going to hold onto it. I'm going to keep the heel. I think
it's way more important. All right. Now we're talking. This is some pretty, this is, this is
damage that can carry. I think the end of the run, maybe if I get one more good damage weapon, maybe
Ooh, awesome. Okay. That's pretty good. Finally locked enemy shots coming from the direct.
I think that's it, right? Salvation. It's probably that and just standing in the corner and look
right. It's the shield. It always is. Just go like this and just always make sure you're on the same
plane. Bomb the angel. This is for a key piece, right? Why did I not block it? I was standing
right there. Hey, why is it not blocking it? Is there anything else I can do before I leave
changes to pee pee poo poo? I mean, that's fine. People are going to ask what the fuck
that even means. Yeah, that's, that's all right. That works. Yeah. Funny. I think I'm just going
to go. Let's get out of here. Tired. I got to get up early. Get some sleep. Mausoleum. What's that?
I've never seen this before. It's five cents. I got it. I got it. Marbles. Oh, that kind of stinks.
I mean, I have, I have the fly. I don't think I'm going to keep the things. Still pretty good.
Yeah. A little late for that. Geez. Wait, that, I don't know if I want to touch that. That could be
the nine lives thing. That could be guppy. I don't want to touch that. That's going to bring me down
to one heart. I'm not touching that. I don't know what it is. Do it. Do it. Touch it anyway. No,
it's going to be Guppy's body. And I'm going to go down to one heart. Okay. I did it. I'm,
it doesn't matter. I don't even want it. So, all right. That was very scary actually again.
But what, why is this thing going? What's going on? Where am I? I don't know what I just did.
What happened? Where am I? It was a golden pill. I thought it was a money pill. I got to make my way
back to that room. I wasn't done. Is that a blade? Shit. I can't pick it up. No, it's going to be,
I can't touch it guys. What was that? Nice. IV bag. More prizes. Nightlight? Scared of the dark.
Oh, oh, it slows them if you look at them, right? This thing's kind of, yeah. You drink coffee every
day. Usually. Yes. Usually. It's a big part of my morning routine. What was it? What are you looking
at? That was weird. Sometimes it's damage up. I completely forgot about the active item. Oh,
shut up. Ow. All right. I got to clean it up a little bit. I'm, this is pretty sloppy.
This is pretty sloppy. Hold on. Actually perfect. Exactly what I wanted. Perfect. All right. Give
me hearts out of here. How would you use your trinket? Trinket. Flying. You need flight. Flight
is the, you are, get a trinket from the arcade. Scared the absolute shit out of me. Forgot that's
what that did. All right. Where's the flying trinket? You swallowed the, wait, there is not
one. You have no trinket. Wait, why did you guys tell me to come back here? Your fly ate it. Shiny
rock? What are you guys talking about? You need the trinket for something else. You ate it. Take
it. You swallowed your old trinket to get a new one. Oh, whatever. We're fine. Oh, you're good.
Thank you. I'm looking for hearts. Don't get hurt. God awful room. No, not spirit hearts. Regular
hearts. Spirit hearts. Whatever. This is cheap. One plus one free forever. Jar of flies. Pretty
cool. Coupon. Now you can fly. Ooh. Jumper cables. School bag. Extra active item. And that thing.
Give me a regular heart, dude. Come on. Oops. How do you switch between them? How do you switch
between active items? R2? Oh, okay. Right. I think this is fine. Stop giving me this shit.
Give me something else. Use the coupon in the shop. I already did, didn't I? Yeah, I did.
Isaac's dream. Bat chest. Wait, this is like a red empress. Plus two health up. Ears up. That
glass. All right. I'm just going to use it right now. Isaac. I feel like bat chesting Isaac is
that makes me feel a hundred years old. It's not accurate, right? No, it's not at all. Isaac
bat chest. No, that's no way. I actually do not believe you. That would be a shock. All right.
Let me go get the other thing that was over here. I think I got a pretty good build to try to finish
this. I've been on this run for an hour. I do play this game so slowly though, because I'm so
afraid of getting hit and like hitting spikes on the ground. Where was it? Using a pill car to ruin
is a 25% chance to drop a copy. Oh man. That would be amazing if I could, if that actually worked
with this. Well, let's hope so. 25% is really not, that's a place to bomb. It's not? What is that?
That is very clearly an X on the ground. All right. Let's go. This is the siren hatch book.
Now I definitely want to keep this cool. Bomb the skull. We keep going. Is there anything I need to
know on this floor? Oh, is that quad shot? No, it's not. What is this? I was going to say that's
game over if it is. I mean, it kind of, it is shoots four shots sometimes. Yeah. Oh, it is cool.
Nice. All right. As long as I play pretty well, I might be able to see the final, final boss.
And then I want to do another greed mode. I love greed mode. Ow. Give me a good card. Hmm. Who
Nintendo? No. 5% is really low, but if you get hit all the time, it's going to be okay. I would love
some more area. I feel like my tears are really small. Range up. Nice. You want to fight the final
repentance final boss or the true final boss of the game? Which one is more interesting? What would
you say is the more, Oh yeah, that's cool. You should see that the beast. It's too late to do
the beast. You're locked into the repentance boss right now. Oh, that's all right. Whatever.
It's cool. If you have the knife, it's the repentance boss. Okay. Might as well have 7.5
luck. Do I have anything that is spawning off of luck or works off of luck? I don't think so.
Jesus. Oh, he popped out of my head. Do I just don't control them anymore? He's awesome. He's
awesome. I should just get hit. You like old book smells. Um, probably. I mean, I, yeah,
I would say so. I like the smell of, uh, like a seller, like a basement. There's this really
specific basement smell. It's really, it's, it's great. It's such a nice smell. What is that by
the way, that smell, what is it? No, it's not mold. It's a very specific thing. It's like musty.
No, not asbestos, asbestos, damp concrete. Yeah. I like the smell of wood too. All right. It's time
for all of you to judge me. They make these dog toys that are wood, dog, chewy toy things.
And I love the way these things smell. These things are for dogs and they're so, they smell
so good. They have this unbelievable, unbelievably wonderful wood scent on them.
This dude is huffing his dog's toys. You know, I don't, some of you that don't, if you know,
you know, right? If you know, you know, should I make it harder? This is gonna, this is stupid,
but I get more damage, right? I could also do this and just spam it at the boss. Just hold onto coins
and then just go, bub, bub, bub, bub, bub, bub, bub, bub, bub, the red thing. I need more damage.
Oh, that's how you do it. This range is ridiculous. Why is this pill so huge?
What just happened? This is the fastest I can go. I'm capped out for speed. Okay. Cool. You've got
max stats. Feels good. What the hell is that thing? I can pick that up yet. Dog toys. Otto has so many
dog toys and I can't get rid of them because he likes all of them. Sometimes he'll just go in.
He's got a little toy, little toy chest thingy and he'll just pick out a different one every few
days. And sometimes one, a toy will be unused for months and months and months. And then randomly
one day you'll see him go over there and he'll pull out Mr. Flamingo. And he's like, Oh, Mr.
Flamingo today. And he's throwing it around and he's having a bunch of fun with it. He has not
played with this for weeks. What is this clip? This clip looks like old. Wait, I did this already?
Hold on. Turn this down for a second. You've already seen me do this. Hold on. I'm not going
to chew on this on stream, right? This is what I'm talking about. It's this weird tree trunk
and I'm not going to smell it because it smells like my dog's mouth. But when this is out of the
package, brand new, it smells fantastic. He's right. Right out of the package. It smells like
this awesome wood smell. This has been in my dog's mouth. Here it is. I'm not going to put it in my
mouth. Somebody said, dude, why is David Spade on your stream? This is when I was growing the
mustache out for the baseball stream. Or was it after the baseball stream? This is two years ago.
Wait, what? Why did I have a fucking mustache two years ago? What was this for? Why did I do this?
What was the point of this? Was I doing a bit or something? I must have thought it was funny.
I had to have thought it was funny. Why did I do this? You did this after shaving one night
and thought it was funny, as Holly says. I just thought it was funny to do this. I guess so.
All right. Well, I thought this was like a few months ago. Anyways, yeah, true. It's good.
I'm not sitting there huffing dog bones, but it's got this great cedar smell. I think they put it
on there specifically. You look 45. Yeah. I ain't getting any younger, man. I'm, you know,
whatever. But people age. You get older. The way it is. All right. So if I walk through this door
is a time to fight this super boss. That's really cool, dude. Smell whatever you want. I don't care.
Play the game. Oh, this is different. What did I get hit by? That was almost perfect. Okay. What?
It's the left, right? I'm doing a lot of damage. So much more damage. All right. And then to the
left. Let's go. Mom's heart. Okay. I'm used to this. Shit. My God. They're everywhere.
What is hitting me? Did I win? Oh, room dumb ass. Hey, it's don't you think it's too late
for insult? It's too late for insult. Corpse one zombie, which coin friend should I give it to?
He'll never read this. It just did. None of them. First one only. I don't know what the other one
does in the end. Okay. It gives rotten hearts. That doesn't fill up the regular hearts though,
does it? Also, I need to activate the flies. Let's just do that in the next room. Fuck. I had it.
Should have wharfed it. Oh my God. So much money. Really? What am I going to do with all this?
Did I just get that? Did I have that floating fly before? Rot hearts take double damage. That's
fine. Better than nothing. If I had resident sleeper to a positive message, would you read it?
Resident sleeper is not necessarily a negative emote. The context of resident sleeper. For
instance, you could say, I'm getting really sleepy right now, but this is like a really chilled
night. Resident sleeper. Like, oh, I've got so many exams I have to study for a resident sleeper.
Like it's, you know, I'm tired. So now if you said this stream sucks, resident sleeper,
I'd ban you. That's the context. Have you, I don't think you've ever banned anyone ever.
Um, I don't, I don't know. Maybe a long, maybe a long time ago. I mean, it's a lot of mods.
The mods, I'll take care of it. Mods act 100% on my behalf. So you know what they're doing.
Electric key. You know, you did, you banned someone for posting a video that had a jumpscare
noise in one of the VR streams. You banned them for three days. I remember it vividly.
Well, all right. So it's been, it's been at least one. Hey, just, just relax and you won't get
fucking banned. It's that simple. Ooh, I'm small. Glass eye. All right. The tears are huge now.
All right. We got damage. I just gotta get, keep my health up. What is going on?
Come on, dude. It's turning into a real annoyance. Roll. All right. Well, I might as well just go
spend the money, right? Cause this is, is this it? One more after this. This is getting close.
Probably nothing worth buying. Light is overpowered. Another run after this. Yeah.
I'll do another greed run after this. Whatever happens here. That's cool, but not a big deal.
What the, oh my God. I didn't know they get, I thought they shot the beams.
I gotta find the secret rooms. Yeah. Yes. I can't pick that up. Power pill is cool, but no.
On the skulls. Yeah. Might as well. Let's go. Turns out it was worth it. Oh, lovers again.
I wish I could pick that up. Take some damage and come back. Um, wasn't I, I already was hurt.
I couldn't pick it up. You'll get stat buffs. Wait, when I pick up red hearts, that's right.
Yeah, you're right. Let me just go get hurt. Oh, I can't get hurt by the spikes.
Somebody hurt me. I'll just do it myself. I've got 40 bombs. Um, it's all right. Nice. All right.
Let's go. All right. I got old jar. Everything good. All right. Let's do it. This is almost
instant kill. Good because I don't, I am taking a lot of damage. Okay. Good. Good thing. I do a ton
of damage. Are there any more hearts? I don't think so. I could stand across the whole game
at this point. All right, let's do it. Uh, wish me luck. Oops. I'll just bring it up.
I'll come back in here. Use it right now. Oh, it's time to make the devil mad.
No, it doesn't. It just makes the devil mad. You're cranky. Am I? I think so. I'm not,
how am I cranky? I'm not even, I, let's go. Uh, oh, what do these do? What do these do?
He's actually saying you're in a really good mood. What is this thing? Open shops for free.
Really? These things, my friend though? Weird. I'm just so fast. When you get to like 2.0 speed in
Isaac, it's actually kind of a detriment. You move so quickly and you run into shit all the time.
Your son card? No, I'll get it. I will not lose it. Let's play everything first. Where are my
glasses? Where are my glasses? You swallowed it. Why is that happening? Why is that happening?
Where are my glasses? The marbles. Oh shit. That's, that's actually pretty unfortunate.
You keep the effect. Oh, there's so much. Okay. Let me go get my thingy. Where's my thingy?
Get pink eye instead. Pink eye is probably better than this. Yeah. Poison damage would be.
Yeah, for sure. I would nine, almost 9.0 luck. Are you kidding me? Where's the card?
Geez, that scared me. Get the fuck out of here. Wish I could sell some of these keys for hearts.
Something's wrong. Bombs are key. Who cares? Even more range. So much range. Can you please
play my favorite game? Oh, this is Ball Fondler. I'm reading Ball Fondler's comment and I didn't
think it was Ball Fondler. I just started reading a message and it just happened to be Ball Fondler.
Hi Ball Fondler. How are you? How are you doing? Well, and let me, let me just answer Ball Fondler
directly. Um, no Ball Fondler. I'm not going, I, I'm not going to buy all the flying carpets you
made on the auction house. I don't play that game. Stop asking me to do that. I can't, whatever.
Let's go. Hey man, can you please play my favorite game? I'm like, Oh, I'm going to read. What's this
person have to say? He's just everywhere. He's everywhere. Come on, do it. Skyrim is, I don't
know. Is it weird that I really just kind of like don't want to play Skyrim? I already ruined
everything for myself playing it. I put on a bunch of stupid dog shit mods and I've ruined the whole
game. I can never play it normally. All right. Am I ready? Skyrim fucking sucks without mods, dude.
Are we good? I'm going to go for it. Hope I don't lose. Mother. Oh my God. Holy shit. Whoa. Jesus.
Oh my God. Oh, can't even see. Did I do it? Did it? Nice. That was crazy. I mean, 11.7 damage.
I have a lot. I, that took, good thing I had the sun card. Otherwise I was dead.
Sun carry. Yeah. I don't think I've ever seen this cut scene.
I'll show you a monster.
I can't even look at you. Isaac has a voice song.
Did they give Isaac a voice in repentance? I don't remember in the other ones. I'm talking
for some of the final cut scenes. Yeah. Oh, what did that say? I didn't see it. I liked over chat.
That's really cool. All right. I'll try. Greedier might as well. Who's good for a Greedier. So I do
Greedier with one of the characters. Try the beast to a beast and trending. Who's a good character
to play with? I love Samson. Wait, painted Samson. This is good. It's fun. That's right.
Cause it looks like this. So is it worth the same as regular Samson? If you get hurt or do you have
to, how does it work with this one? Hey, it does not work that way. Wrong difficulty notes. It's
not hard. Yeah. It's hard. You're Greedier. You were supposed to play Greedier. Yeah. Then somebody
said, kill the beast. And I was like, you know what? Maybe I'll try that. I'm going to give it
like one solid attempt and then I'm going to play the other one. He's just more fun. So how does
this work? I'm turning red, but I'm not in my damage isn't going up. You'll see like, look,
I'm about to explode. Okay. So that you turn into that and it lasts for a few seconds,
the more you kill, the longer it lasts. It doesn't have a charge bar. He doesn't have charge bars on
Omega Lul. If they're distracting. So it's probably better just to do melee then, right? And not throw
it. There really are zero coins in here now. That's so funny. Um, give me one second. I want
to get some water. Actually, you know, I might make a tea. Oh, Northern lion, Northern lion. What
about it? Northern lion's awesome. I'll be right back. I'm going to get a tea. Okay. Hello. Hey,
I need to make my tea. It takes about four minutes to steep. That scared me. I'm trying to do,
I told you, like when I come back from breaks now, especially when it's this late,
I try to do a little like, I'll be like, I only got the clown makeup on here. What's the music
playing? It's just the Isaac music. Do I put anything in my tea? Not usually. And it's not
because of flavor. It's more so laziness, but there's a peach tea and put the bags in it's
steeps. And then I just drink it, take the bags out, drink it. Like getting the honey, getting
sugar, get it, taking it out, squeezing it in, stirring it up. I'd rather just drink it. Uh,
but no, I like putting that stuff in my tea. I've been pretty basic about it though. Same with
coffee too. I've been drinking a lot of black coffee, a lot of just regular ass tea. Manuka
honey is superior. Yes, it is. Manuka honey is unbelievable. It's thick though. Manuka honey is,
it's a paste. You get a big chunk of it, stir it in. Manuka honey is really good for you too.
It's like a superfood, isn't it? I'm just getting into tea. This is helpful. You know, I go through
phases. Sometimes I'll drink tea for months and then I won't drink it for a year. It's weird how
you body and your brain decide to do that. Weird. What is the baseball stream? Um, it's the California
circus versus the Maryland magicians. A very, very tough game. Very close game. All right, let's go.
Uh, we're, this is where we left off, right? Tea tier list. I used to drink a rooibos red tea,
which is actually not really tea at all. It's not like a tea leaf. It's actually
like a bush or something, right? But I did that because of my digestive problems. It's good. I
think it tastes really good. It's pronounced cannabis, not rooibos. No, it is rooibos. It's
like Roy. Yeah, it's Roy does constipated. No, I'm not going to have colitis. Oh, here we go.
Oh, nevermind. I'm standing here. I've been diagnosed like three times and I've been told
two or three, two or three different things, but we don't need to get into the details of my IBD
because no, just know that I have it. Okay. Thumbs up. Sure thing, dude. Why can't I pick this up?
Fake money. I need a bomb. It's too heavy. Uh, IBS and IBD are different. IBS is irritable bowel
syndrome. IBD is irritable bowel disease. Uh, IBD is something that you have typically for life
and it's usually in the like Crohn's disease, colitis, fructitis. Uh, I believe IBS is a series
of symptoms. I can't get that nickel. I have IBD and I initially got diagnosed with colitis.
This is a long time ago. And then I had another sigmoidoscopy and the doctor was like, Hmm,
no, it still might be colitis, but we're going to treat you for this. Now we're going to treat you
for ulcerative proctitis. I was like, Oh, okay. I went to the doctor again and had a full
colonoscopy. This is back a couple of years ago. Uh, when I took that big break in 2020,
was it 2019? No, no, this was before the break. Uh, how do I do the beast? The same path that I
took before. Just go do a regular run. Okay. Uh, but yeah, during that, during that colonoscopy
that I had, it was kind of, you probably have colitis again. Well, not again, but the way that
colitis and Crohn's disease work is Crohn's disease can affect anywhere all up and down your whole
like gut, all your digestive tract, everything. But colitis and ulcerative colitis and proctitis,
they affect very specific parts of your colon. This is, we're having a while. I haven't talked
about any of my medical problems in a while, but it's time to let's talk about my medical problems.
How much time do you have? All right. Hey, I got all night. Weird to talk about this during Isaac.
What time like the present, right? Keep it going, keep it going, keep it going.
Okay. Now I see why people think this is cool. So the idea is you just do this and clear as
many rooms as you can. Okay. That's really good. Wait, wait, there was ASCII art that got into the
channel. It was there really? That's been a long time since that's happened. Oh, nightbot got it.
Oh, okay. Hey, I, by the way, I'm not encouraging that you're going to get probably timed out or
banned if you do that. It's just, it's been a long time. I've not seen ASCII art in a long time.
Really? That's surprising. So during the Christmas stream, that other channel,
that other channel was just, that was a, that was a fucking mess out of it here. I got enough
money, right? Nope. What about auto ASCII art? I think the problem with ASCII art is not the fact
that it's ASCII art, but the fact that it just blows up. It's the fact that it blows up the whole
chat room. It just takes up the whole thing. And trust me, when I say this, you think I'm going to
actually sit here and tell you, you really think I'm going to sit here and go, why did that thing,
that thing just die? But do you really think I'm going to sit here and tell you that I've never
laughed at ASCII art? You're out of your mind if you think that. You've laughed at ASCII art. Of
course I have. Every single one of you here has. I don't want to, I don't want to hear anybody
pretending in here that they have not chuckled at some form of ASCII art at some point. Well,
I'm not talking about like, no, I'm talking about you just get like, that's kind of funny for a
second. Go, go, go, go. Hurry up. Oh, it's all right. I have something I want to test. Josh,
what do you want to do? You want to test something? Okay. Let's see it. You have the floor, Josh.
Uh oh. Didn't really work. Why did it show up twice? Yeah, it showed up two times. No,
let me scroll up. Where is it? Yeah, it showed up for me two times. I think it was doubled.
It worked on mobile. Probably the size of the chat, right? And whatever your font size is,
size of the window. Uh, Josh, time yourself up for five minutes, by the way. No homing bombs.
See, when I get to the depths too, is when I have to do a different thing. If I even make it there.
Oh, come on. I got it. I did it. Pretty sloppy so far. What's your favorite way to prepare a
chicken? You were saying something about the Christmas stream. Oh, just saying the other
channel had a ton of ASCII art in it. Cause we didn't, I don't, I think the whole thing with
that second channel, we had a couple of meetings about it, like what to do with it. And it was
just like, you know what? Fuck it. Just, just let them do whatever they want. But to an extent,
right? It was like, how much moderating tools do we actually put on there? And it was like,
you know what? Just who cares? Let them have some fun for like 20 minutes. You know, I get you.
This person wrote, dude, can you please talk louder? I'm eating corn nuts. You cannot do
anything while on corn nuts. It is nothing you can do besides sit quietly in a chair and eat them.
There's no activity. There was nothing you can do. It is one of the only foods on earth that
requires total isolation. And I like corn nuts, but that's, that's a really big factor when I'm
like, I don't really want to eat them. Dude. Okay. I got a corn nut story for you. I swear
I was in a hotel room one time and they were corn nuts. Oh yeah. I guess like usually when you,
when you go to a hotel and I do this, I, all right, I'm going to get, I'm going to make sure
I have a couple of waters. Cause I don't, you know, obviously you don't want to, oh, the water
that's on the table is nine dollars. Like, no, no, no, I'm going to get water. I'm going to get a
couple of snacks just to have them in the hotel room. And then one of them was corn nuts. And I
swear, I swear to God at about two o'clock in the morning, I was eating these corn nuts just in the
hotel room. And I was actually scared that I was going to wake up somebody else next to me in the
hotel room next to me. I'm serious. It was like, boom, boom, boom. And I, I, sometimes I felt like
I heard like movement in the other room and I'm like, this is so, am I loud? Like I, it would not
have surprised me if like the 2 a.m. dead silent hotel crunching, somebody heard it.
Somebody said, those are prey instincts. Like, I don't want to hear that. Like the wolves are
going to hear me crunching. Oh my God. That's so funny. Oh, that's wow. That's actually
unbelievably funny. Ray instinct. I'm going to be thinking about that all night.
Shit. I don't want to die. Dude, would tears up make this just disgusting? Well, there it is.
No. Okay. So just go down, right? Not going through there. Did you end up trying ceremonial
matcha yet? I've had it before, but I have not bought it in a long time. I remember having it
like once. Did I, I had like a really good one. I don't know if it was like ceremonial grade. I
don't remember. It may have been. What about mochi? Uh, you're talking about the little
ice cream balls that have the dough on the outside, like the soft dough with the ice cream in the
middle. Okay. I have, I do have opinions on them. My opinions on those are if they are very small
and I mean the size of, you know, the little ones that are like, it's because silver dollar.
Oh, no, no, no, no. That's mochi ice cream. Okay. Okay. Well, I like the mochi ice cream better than
the regular mochi then something about that contrast of that dough and it's not freezing
cold and you bite in and it's like, wow, this is cold. Um, it has to be little though. I don't
like the big mochi balls. It's kind of too much, but mochi ice cream is unbelievably. It's
unbelievably good. Mochi ice cream balls are one of those snacks that it's a multi-layered experience
is a visual. The visual is when you bite into it, like you get to see that cold,
like dry ice foam. You know what I mean? That, like that, that mist that when you breathe out
on a freezing cold day, it's like fucking ice breath. Oh, that's a visual. That's what that
adds to it. It only happens for like one second. Sometimes it's just like a little rough and then
it tastes really good. It's got texture for two different kinds of texture flavors. Strawberry
mochi ice cream. I would put up there as probably as high as I could for desserts. I don't, I don't
love the green tea ice cream, green tea mochi. Not a huge fan, but strawberry is holy shit.
Doesn't get better than that. Mango. Oh, I'm not sure I've ever had mango. So I have a question.
Can we, are we ever going to be able to have a conversation about any singular item
without somebody saying that I'm going to put that singular item up my ass? I think we've gone,
I think we've gone too far. The fondler effect. Kill the meme. Kill the meme friend. Kill the meme.
Let the man be born. You brought it up though. Yeah, I told you when I talked about kill the
meme stream too that I'm going to die. Is that I'm a fault of this too? Mike, did I lose? What
happened? Oh, damn it. All right. Well, now that I understand how the character works, I'll do it
again. Restart. Well, my voice sucks. Now I want to do Greedier. There we go. Good start.
Greedier is going to be amazing with this character. Nice. You revive as Lazarus. Oh,
I like that. Oh, this is unbelievable in Greed mode. Sprinkler is a god tier item here. How come
you don't play on keyboard? Every other game you insist on playing keyboard. I do. I feel like I'm
playing on a controller way more than half the time. I prefer controller. Yeah, I usually play
on controller, don't I? Maybe not for like an FPS or something, but most action games I'm on a
controller. Okay. Well, this is good. This is a good start. I'm going to walk through here.
This game's hard on keyboard. Um, anytime where I need to use my right, my WASD is fine, but I don't
know, using like the arrow keys to shoot. I feel like my hand would, my hand kind of hurts after
doing it for a while because you play this game with the right hand on the arrow keys, right?
Yeah. All right, let's do it. I forgot how much Greedier just gives you nothing. All right,
let's go. This is so good here. Wow. I mean, I'm getting, I'm getting hurt, but
only 11 coins. Holy shit. That's bad. Uh, I feel like that's going to kill me. I will die
from this thing. I think that's all good. Pick up. Not, not a troll bomb. Oh, it's regular bombs.
Damn. Okay. That sounds pretty good. I can buy a key. Also pretty good here.
Have you ever had a Ramune? Ramune? Japanese soda. I have not. Ramune. Ramune. Ramune. Okay.
Oh, this might end poorly. Oh God. I'm gonna end poorly. Don't. Oh shit. Damn it. I kind of
got in trouble there. The timer is shorter on Greedier too, right? By a lot, isn't it?
Well, that's good. Good start. Now give me Duffy. Uh, the only Japanese soda that I've ever,
I've wanted to try. It was a, it was a green bottle and it was, what, what was it? It was like a,
like a mango cream soda or something. What was it? It was a, no, yeah, it was a melon soda.
Mango cream soda. Cream melon. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. It was a cream melon cream soda. Is that correct?
Yeah. It was like a milk melon soda. That's like the best one. Is that a good one?
So good. What type of melon? It was, I think green. It was like a green melon.
All right. Let me, uh, I gotta, I gotta focus up here. Okay. 30% fire rate for the left eye only.
Sure. And a key. You said you don't like honeydew or cantaloupe and that they're the same.
Well, not that you put melon in F tier. I need to correct the record. I don't like the melon
fruit. The flavor, the melon flavor is all right. But every time I have melon,
it's the texture is, it's sort of like chewy and hard. It always is the shittiest quality thing
in the fruit cup. It's always like somehow just not good. It's like, I don't know. I feel like
I get a lot of rind pieces or something. It's just not, it's cause it's not ripe enough.
Yeah. But I don't know. But I've had bananas that are not quite all the way ripe and they're
perfect. I like the flavor of a melon, but I just don't like the texture is not like my favorite.
What the hell is this thing? They hated him because he spoke the truth. Hey, whatever fruits you like,
that's up to you. My ideal fruit combinations. If you're talking about your ideal fruit,
what is your ideal fruit scenario? It's fresh strawberries, fresh pineapple, grapes, blueberries.
And that's it. Like if we're talking about mango, mango. Yeah. Apples are right. I like apples alone
though. If I'm talking about like a, cause usually melon is with a bunch of other fruits. You see
melon part of a fruit cup. You see melon on a board with here's a bunch of like cheeses and
crackers and melon and straw. Usually it's not alone. Melon is the best part of the fruit cups.
That pineapple is my favorite part. A good fresh strawberry that doesn't taste like nothing.
Sometimes a lot of strawberries can kind of taste like nothing. Thanks for letting me farm that.
Appreciate it. I was risky, but whatever. I did it. Yeah. Strawberry experience can be really,
really bad. It can be really, really good or really bad. I've been to a strawberry that was
really chewy and had almost no flavor. And then I've been to like a succulent strawberry.
It's like a T it's a commercial. It's like a television commercial eating it.
Homegrown and the most flavorful. Ludwig ate a $500 strawberry on stream. Really? Was it,
was it fucking good? Holy shit. Don't go in that. Okay. Yeah. Cause I want the angel room.
It was mid it was mid. It wasn't, it was not very good. It was just normal. It wasn't worth the
price. Honestly, 500 bucks to me is, I just don't, I don't think there's like a fresh fruit or I
don't think there's, I don't know if there's a food item that I think is like individually singly
worth $500 to me. I think you can get pretty much any high quality food is I mean, it's talking
about like at a restaurant at least like even like a place that's like a couple hundred bucks
a plate. I don't know if you go very much higher than that. After that, it just becomes, well,
we missed it with a, a candied mist spray. It's like, let me just eat the fucking strawberry,
dude. Like, I don't, who cares. It's coated in a thin layer of, of mango film. It's like,
is that really worth 700 bucks? Not really. 500 bucks. That's crazy. That sounds pretty good
though. Yeah. You spend 500 bucks on more important stuff like family guy. That's right. I'm way
better at this than you. I, I bet you are count on it actually. Uh, that's the thing. No. Okay. So
wait, somebody said family guy 30 season box set. Is it 500 bucks? Think about all the laughs you
could have one strawberry for the family guy, entire box set collection is that's talking about
the value on that one. None of you are taking the strawberry. Get out of here. I guarantee none of
you would take the strawberry. Whoa. Oh my God. I don't know how much heart, how many hearts I have.
This is actually kind of scary. Stop. Stop. Stop. I hate these enemies. Here we go. HP and luck up.
Your size up. You need some more range. That's pretty abysmal. Isn't it? You could look back
on eating a $500 strawberry and laugh. Yeah, you could. There's value there. I'm buying this. Eh,
I thought it was going to, it could have been the diamond. It could have been the one that doubles.
It was dumb. It was five bucks. I didn't, it wasn't 500 die. If I do that anymore. Well,
here's range. I'm scared to do the nightmare mode because I feel like I'm going to lose. I feel like
I'm going to die. Oh, fuck. I didn't get a key. I'm dead. I'm alive. Bowl mapping effect
spawns a random wisp, spawns one additional wisp with each use up to 12. And this one is worthless,
right? Your faith grows. I don't, wait, I don't get it. A random wisp on one wisp with each use.
So will this just refill every time I, the button is pressed? I think so, right? I wish I had more
money because that's very needed right now. Oh, let's be dumb and cool, but I don't want it.
I mean, that's nice. That's pretty good. I don't have any more money. Oh, no. Oh, this is the,
wait a minute. Oh my God. I can, everything's fine. Oh my goodness. Wait, should I open this
or should I buy? Hold on. I'm doing it. Nice. Um, all right. I'm going to buy a key. I forgot
I even had that. Oh, it's the lard, right? That's what it is. God, don't flex an enemy or projectile
right before Isaac would take damage from it. It needs to deflect projectiles near it. It needs
to be touched after deflecting to be reactivated. Holy shit. Nah, I think this thing is better.
Wait a minute. Like a dollar. You can use ace on enemies. Oh, I thought it was an
item on the ground. All right. So if I use this right now, what happens before I do it?
Poker chip. 50% chance for chest to spawn extra pickups or to contain a single fly.
Money. I know what that does. I know what that does. Good. Inexpensive keys. Very good. Very
good. It will spawn a wisp. But will it refill? Nice. Okay. Let's try it. This thing has already
protected me twice. Why is this thing so little? Where'd he go? Where's my friend? Where's my
friend? Geez. Oh my goodness. These things just spam. Oh my disaster. Actually a disaster. All
right. Damn. That's it in a locked gold chest. You gotta be kidding me. What are you saying?
Seven bombs. Removes the delay between bomb placements. You can just spam it.
It's kind of terrifying. Oh, so it keeps leveling up. I get it. Well, hopefully I can make it to
probably probable. Oh, I'm dead. Oh, I'm not very good with this character.
Two up close and personal. You get that speed and you sprint around. It's like, no, no, no, no, no.
I was never very good with melee in this game. I like range. Let me use original Samsung. Tainted
Lost. I'll try it after this. This is actually my favorite character. When I said it was came,
it was alive. I made it up. That was an unbelievable room. Oh, should I do that?
Should I do that right now? Should I hold this for a little longer? I made the whole thing up.
Do it now. It's a lot of money. We're getting to use the head. Oh, that's great. 25 coins on
the ground. This is how you make greedier actually reliably doable because now I'm essentially the
coins that are on the ground are the coins that I would have had in regular greed mode throughout
the course of the whole playthrough. So let's go. Like these are the amount of coins that I would
have had throughout the whole playthrough. Get lucky with a card. It's not really reliable.
Multiple Isaac's damage, tears, range and speed stats, which multiplies Isaac's damage.
What's the recharge on this? It's bad. The range. What? Did I already go in there?
No, I didn't. Did I? I don't remember going in there. I went in there already. I went in there.
I'm thinking about the last playthrough. They blend together sometimes. All right. I'm gonna
this is dumb, but it might be brilliant. Let's find out. Here's bad. It was a bad idea. Hey,
never going to, you're never going to get the cool crazy thing. You don't try the cool crazy thing.
You could have dropped something unbelievable and everybody here would have been going home.
Holy shit, dude. You're so fucking cool, man. Just do you put the cool, man. You see, hey,
like, Hey, did you see what item he just found? I was called an idiot, but like, I mean, I don't
know. I think he's just, I don't know. He's like the coolest guy I've ever seen. I do not go in
there. Ego boosted over a kid's game. I think I would probably not want a kid to play this game.
I think that would be very bad. I don't think that would be a great thing. And that's the reason why
I opened that up with the key. Don't have a key anymore. Got the pill that opened the fucking
secret that has, look what's in here. A crazy door. What is that? Does this go anywhere different?
Nothing. It just goes down. It's the exact same one. Really? I think it just goes to the next
floor. Oh, if it has the ladder, that means it's like an item room, right? That's okay.
Yeah. Chairman, dude, that was so cool. Oh, it's up to my throat. Not good, but better than nothing.
I think, I think my body wants to sneeze probably what's about to happen. Yep.
One heart container while held was one coin container for keeper.
Thank you. Which one of these is better? It's just a health up.
Ooh, another tier is up right there. Nice. Come on. Good block. I hate how the elite
champions do a full heart. You'd be patched out of the game. That's like a really interesting
mechanic where it's, it's like, it should be the way that it is. The weird glitch. Yeah. It's like,
I don't know, glitched out. They should just remove taking damage. You know, I like, I was
going to say that, but I, yeah, I, I think I agree. Like I shouldn't be able to get hurt.
Like the top left should be nothing there. Like shit should just bounce off of me.
God, get in there. Will you stay still for a second? Get over here. You know,
I have a question for you all to be honest. This is a very, very interesting discussion
because I'm telling you, I would love it. Hear me out. This is really, really interesting to me.
So Polly and I are sitting on the couch and I was playing a game. So that's not the whole story.
So during this game, what do you mean I wasn't? Wait, let me tell my story. Okay. So that we,
we got food and I was playing and it's like, okay, so I'm playing this game. I'm controlling
my character running around. I'm doing stuff, but I want to eat. I want to eat. We want to eat food
and hang out on the couch. I wish I could press a button to have a bot take over and play the game
for me. Just like AI plays while I just sit there and eat. Don't you think that would be so cool?
Like I'm talking about, yeah, I'm talking about like a left for dead two bot mode where for
instance, like, like a wild hearts. I've been playing wild hearts. I have a fucking hilarious
clip that you guys need to see too, by the way. It's unbelievably funny. It's the funniest thing
I've seen all month and I'm not kidding. Um, so I just want to press a button and just have my
characters kind of walk around and like pick up stuff and like attack enemies and stuff. That's
just a movie, but it's temporary. Just pause it. No, but I want to like, I want, I want to continue
the, I want to continue. Just hold down select for five seconds and we'll, okay. We're in left for
dead two bot mode. It's just a bot takes over your character and you can sit there and eat your
cheeseburger, have your fries and like, okay, yeah, yeah, yeah. That's the way I wanted to go.
And essentially the game plays for you for a little bit temporary. Just let Holly play while you eat.
She's eating too. That's stupid. I don't think, I think it's actually an interesting thing.
You don't think it would be kind of cool just to be like, all right, you play temporarily and it
would have, look, why not? I think that would be a really cool feature. This is why you have a child.
Hey, hey son, come here. Hey, uh, your mom and your dear old dad over here want to eat our, uh,
look at McDonald's. Can you play, uh, wild hearts? What's even the point of the game? Well, I'm not,
I'm not, not going to play. I just, while I'm eating, it's just in food mode. It's food mode.
Like, Oh, like start right bumper, right bumper, right bumper settings down, down, down, down, down,
down, food mode off, food mode on big thing pops up on screen. You have activated food mode. Food
mode is a feature in wild hearts that tells you, well, it's the bot will take over. Uh, it can't
do certain things. And then I can press like, uh, like a combination of buttons to turn it on.
Chat is, chat is over here watching you play a game, probably eating and then calling you stupid
for doing, wanting to do the same thing. Luigi mode, but it wouldn't be Luigi mode. It would be
a, like a voluntary Luigi mode, but that's good marbles. Oh wait. Oh yeah. I'm laying in bed. I'm
drawing, but you could cheese with it. Well, no, the AI would be very bad at the game. I'm talking
like, I think about this just, hold on. I know everyone's kind of, you know, going, what the
fuck? Okay. I'm going to press on the map. This is where I want to walk to. This is my, like an
open world game, right? This is my destination. It don't go there and like walk there and on the way
pick up some fucking herbs on the ground. Right. And maybe pick up a side quest along the way.
And I'm just sitting there eating and just watching it. Okay. Yeah. Yeah. This is exactly
what I would have done if I didn't have grease all over my hands. What about it? Could food mode be
millennia? I don't know. No, no. Cause all exactly. That's exactly what I mean. Food mode would not
be good enough to do very much of anything at all. It would only be good enough to traverse
terrain, to pick up items, to, to like attack and you know, move to like the area of like a quest
or something. Right. It wouldn't really be able to do, be able to do very much. That is a slothful
idea. It's not that bad. It's an auto farm tool. No, it would, but what if we had like a five,
no, how long does it take to eat? Okay. It was, you could only activate it 30 minutes a day total.
Food mode would not activate. It would say, sorry, you've already used food mode for 30 minutes.
Please come back in 24 hours when food mode is reactivated. I think I don't want any of these.
I think it's a good idea. You know, how many times I've just sat there where I was in the middle of
something, a middle of, I don't want to stop really necessarily playing the game. I would like to have
it play it for me while I just sit here for 15 to 20 minutes, not long. And maybe have it like kill
a couple of monsters or something and then like, oh cool. Oh yeah. Oh, what dropped? Oh, nice.
And then I turned to Holly and we high five each other with these greasy ass fucking hands.
Nice. Blade and soul kind of has that in some areas. It's a shit game though.
All right. Okay. Nobody likes my food mode idea. Take the file. I ate it. Take the heart.
Taking damage depletes red hearts before soul hearts. The red heart damage can lower your
devil angel room chance. Why would I want to do that? What if it was a special code from
takeout places? Like in the box, you get a QR code that gives you one hour of food mode.
That sounds pretty hype. Yeah. Like super Mario, super Mario Odyssey two.
It's with its, it's cross promotion with pizza hut. If you get a large three topping pizza,
Mario will play the game for you when you want to just sit there and have your garlic sauce
and dip it. Yeah. Fucking perfect. This is dystopia dude. Yeah. Oh,
you are encouraging the fall of Western civilization.
All because I want to be able to eat a fucking steak on the couch and have a bot play a game
for me for five minutes. I disagree. All of a Western civilization. I think it's a good idea.
Oh, I've got to hold on. Can we evolve this idea? So what if instead of the thing you all hate,
what if you press the button and the it's food mode turns on and the character sits down and
a cut scene plays and it's a, it's a long, like 10 to 15 minute long cut scene where they're
just a two or three of the characters in the game are eating at a table. And we're all eating.
We're all hanging out and eating together. I'm done. I'm done. I swear I'm done.
Oh man. It's Mar. Yeah. It's Mario and Luigi are like eating pizza and like spinach and
spaghetti and stuff. And like Mario's like, Ooh, Luigi, the sauce is phenomenal. Oh Mario,
have some of the garlic bread. Oh, what are you eating? And he looks up into the camera,
looks right at you. And then he sits there and waits for you to tell him. Oh, that sounds
Mama Mia, that sounds delicious. Oh
Pilk
Mama Mia
How do you love still?
Just to be careful. You might to get a diarrhea
But that's horrifying. That's so sad. Yeah, but you don't think that that would be funny or like interesting
I feel like I would be if I that was in a Mario game. I feel like this is so funny
This is so like cute. It's just like there's like an eating we could just like watch them
Games need food mode. I want this these are free to go in now
What is that holding the item causes non-ghost enemies to spawn small red ghosts on
death this
Like more enemies
There's a lot here. So hold on. So when I kill something it turns into a ghost the ghost hangs out
Using the item causes the ghosts over there. You blow them all up using the item also kills any ghost enemies
Wait including bosses. Wait, okay. I'm curious. I want to try it. Is it a one time?
Is it and I use it many times I want I had to take that because I wouldn't have an opportunity to
It's infinite. So how often should I use this thing? Whoa, don't wait. It's just okay. So I don't have to oh
Interesting kind of fucked. I'm not gonna lie especially in a little space like this
Okay, I'm like paying almost more attention to that than the actual game
Okay, they don't all they don't hurt you for some reason I was assuming they did the explosions hurt it might
I'm not taking this because I want to hey
I want to help you want to get a bunch of them on screen and blow them up. They don't alright
That's good to know that the explosion doesn't hurt you. They don't hurt you. I thought that they did good to know
Yeah, well, we'll wrap it up after this too. Whatever happens here. This would be the last run. They already went in there. Anyways, thank you for the speed
Oh, that's right. I turned off all spikes. I'm gonna check the secret room
Having a bomb doesn't this do something you can blow this up and it goes down or it heals fully heal. All right, good
Chaos all items are chosen from random item pulls spawns one to six random pickups wacky
Yeah, the wind has died yet. I'm glad that the card didn't come up
It's eight the other thing the other trinket. I think I'm just gonna hold it for until like a boss
It's probably the best thing to do, right? I need more
My tears are kind of bad. All right, stop talking. I'm sorry. I had to those things are awful
I feel like I'm not killing anything. Look at how slow I'm that my damage is so high too. What's going on here?
I oh
I'm a stupid person over here get over here bro turned on food mode and didn't think we'd notice
Is it chaos or is it I need heels chaos?
Ooh job breakers good and then soul of the loss turns the player into the loss allows taking one devil room item for free
That's bad humor the strutting that ass guy. Yeah strutting that ass strutting that ass
You get you walk to gutters. You're gonna be so fucking tired. You wouldn't be strutting that ass
Why don't you walk to good? Why don't you walk to good? I don't want to walk to go
Oh, why don't you walk to good? Of course, I've seen it before who is he?
What are you talking about? What? All right, if you don't know what that is, then I do sound
Ridiculous right now. It's a it's a video. It's like an old meme video. I go in it's a boomer meme
Somebody asked and I answered that sounds cool
Things pretty cool, right? You gave a whole performance. I
Mean, I've just ever I remembered the video could have had it for free
But when I turned to the loss doesn't it mess up my whole character gives me like three soul hearts
No, I can I die in one hit or something right it's one room it was temporary. Oh, well then I'll take it
Holy shit that item is really good. Oh
Come on that item is unbelievable. Stop doing that to me. Oh
Thank you worst item in the game. I'll take this though. This is really good. This is pretty good, too
I really don't want to do this but I'm gonna okay. There's a thing. Oh, yeah
Does that button ever do anything good? I feel like every time I press that bad things happen in this room
I've never had a good thing happen when I press one of those in the breed shop. It's like almost never
Mmm, I think I'm good to go by the $5 one. Why would you buy this 50% chance to explode? No, thank you
Salvation almost just walked into the
Bad technique. All right, let's go. What happened to my item. What's going on? I'm fucking confused. What happened? What happened? What's going on?
This is rerolling enemies. Wait this stupid thing that I picked up who told me to pick this up
Who told me to pick this up? It's this is on you. This is on you. Why did you tell me to pick this up?
I thought that was it. Oh, no. Oh
No, this would be this was that was gonna be so good for super greed
Because of all the shit that he spawns. Oh, no
Why did I listen you?
You've rerolled it I don't know I just let me read it this is not an okay active item is top-left
Consumable is bottom right? I might as well just reroll it but I can't use it anymore, right?
You'd only listen to me. I have 600 hours in this game. You need a key. I need a key
All right, I need a key. I need a key name somebody on this fucking website that can do a barbarian like that
Uh, I think it's okay little neff. Yeah. Yeah, that's fair. I agree
Let's do it again. Can that in this stack if I stand right next somebody can it be like
It's really good you do that again and hit me again. I'm gonna scream
Internally, okay. So here we go. So you're telling me that if I use this I get this for free
You have chaos. Yeah, don't use it
Oh, but what if I go I'm I don't all right get this shit out of here
So if I do this now
Well, will I actually can I still do it?
No, is it because chaos really mess everything up the flush thing would be kind of good for the next room or two
Just wait for everything to spawn and turn everything to shit and flush it these items suck
Chaos made all the items. Oh, that's right. I'm doing it
That's free
Yeah, okay. I have flight now too. I want this shield of tears. It just really good
I'm gonna buy another heart too. Are you gonna see the Mario movie? Oh, yeah, absolutely
another judgment
Judgment god damn it fine
What? Oh, it's an item from the current rooms item pool
So I go into the stop the store and do that. It's one heart container. Okay, that's fine
Okay shit. Okay, robo, baby
All right shit. I've I got to greedy. It's all right. I have the toilet thing. I can plunge
Why would I do that? I don't know. What about secret room? I could probably find it the right the left
Bottom. Hey the runs over do just drink some Ramune on stream and call it a night
You might be right. All right, we're good arts arts in here
Her new room
You're gonna single use a dice consumable item. The dice disappears when leaving the dice does not take up a pill slot
Okay, blow up the reroll machine, I don't think I want to do that now that that's not gonna do anything for me
All right. Let's go
Let's go quietly. It's late. What's the d12? It's the eternal d6. Holy shit
Give me that do the d6 in the shop like right now. Whoa
Okay
What is the eternal d6 online? I'm a little good. I need to look at my whole loadout. How do I drop everything?
I'm holding down right trigger the curse room
Yeah, I just what the fuck I want that person timed out for a hundred hours
How did I get hurt you immediately do everything one guy tells you not true. What is my item? What's going on?
Would my item go what happened to the thing that I just did just turned into it. Did it explode read it read what?
Damn it. It's
Fuck man, that's like I don't I'll be alright. We're good. We're good. We're good. Everybody relax watch this
Why they're not all flushed? Why is it not everybody's still here? Oh
No, it didn't work the way I thought it was gonna work that jump was fucking stupid this game
I just got I don't know. I'm tired. I fucked it up. I'm tired
God damn it one more one more and I'm gonna try as hard as I can
It all went to shit when I picked up that stupid bag of whatever it is
What is this enemy kill drop red half hearts that despair after two seconds? I don't know if you gamble on greedier
That's probably a bad idea. All right, this is actually the one I'm going to really try and I'm gonna pay attention
We're not gonna have a food mode notice when we started talking about food mode
The gaming skill dropped by like 70% its game. I'm here. That's better. There we go clean dish
Oh what no, it was such a bad placement
Stop talking me. I can't play and talk at the same time
What we got sometimes burst out of the ground and grabs an enemy levitates in front of Isaac deals damage
Isaac's damage six times per second. This is good, too. Well, let's find out what's in here ghost bombs
How do we know you're not eating right now?
Now I was thinking about just queuing up a bunch of crunching sounds on YouTube or something and just playing and being quiet
But it's too much for me right now. I kind of this is kind of cool. This is way more practical
I'm gonna do it. I know it's the I'm doing the lame thing, but I want to stay alive. Does this hurt me?
Plus the two kids that's ten cents that I'm not gonna have to spend. That's good
I'm not going in it. What's this game about? It's about killing things attacking upgrading
Random die do it again win do it again
Okay, let's go and I'm gonna activate that
Magdalene thing or a boros worm. Nope panic button. No, that's bad, too
Taking damage uses the active item if it's charged. Why would I want that? How many seconds behind him? I read this
Well, here's the good way to do it so
That's an interesting experiment. I like the experiment you want to do
You do this experiment is I clap and then you say clap the second that you hear clap and I'll tell you
I'll give you the exact time ready. Don't do it yet
No, no, no, don't do it yet. I didn't do it yet. Don't do it yet
dog five seconds
So I said dog and then five seconds went by and it was over in chat. So if you're ever wondering
Like wow, I can't believe how does he not we told him to go left, but he went right
Because when I went right it took five seconds for you to tell me to go left
So you like we we were always miscommunicating by five seconds. What does this tell it? Wow, that's pretty good for three seconds
It's a lot my favorite thing here. Is this working greed mode? That's amazing
All right, I actually have to really I don't I don't want to lose this looks like this great items here low latency
I I think I have low latency turned on the second that that feature was available. I turned it on
I think it really depends on distance as well for a lot of people
Some people I think have it pretty low
It actually is like three or four seconds for you, but it might be like eight seconds for somebody else, right?
Probably not even playing is probably going through a whole bag of corn nuts
These things are annoying
Thankfully, I will probably never get hit by a projectile ever again. Oh
I'm sorry. I freaked out cuz I forgot that the
I'm sorry. I let me let me let me just get my sparrings here for a second
The hearts are disappearing and I forgot that that was part of that item and I just like was like what the fuck's happening
What he leads her in this room?
Get out of my I'm so mad. We'll get out of the fucking way. What the hell?
It's like every enemy that spawns was an elite and that those two big fat guys just blocking my way
It was like seven it was six elites in the room
Last one. I forgot how much greedier was just like a fucking painful
You can't kill those mother. Oh
All right, last one nice my question mark. I'm trying to build up my damage lucky. Okay, that's it Max, right?
Yeah, Northern Lion collab when I mean, I don't know. I wasn't lines really cool, dude
The way that I feel about collabs like you guys know just whatever like sometimes it just like happens. Sometimes it doesn't sometimes it does I
Would play something with no in line hundred percent. All right
Remember do you have an agent? I do have an agency. Yes, I am under evolved. I have an agent
I have a manager. I don't really talk too much about them or about it. But yes, I do do that damage. No
All right. Let's try really hard. I just absolutely
Dissolve that person. All right, don't go in it. What do we got the stew is it's just gonna make me lose
I think what about an army of lawyers? I do have lawyers. I do I take the stew just go fast
Okay, but let me get everything else. I need to heart or a key. I'll be full health, right?
I think it's full health because I'll be able to get when I steamroll everybody
I freaked out cuz I saw the chest this worst thing to start with. Come on, man
Only I had tears up so much better timers going up though. This is a good thing. Okay. Oh nice. Nice. Nice
What is this picking up soul heart grants a random permanent stat? Oh, yep hurry I
What is that? What is this? What is this? I'm gonna pause it. What is that on the corner that thing? What is that?
I've never seen that before. It does nothing for you. Okay, it's a holy version of the devil, baby
Okay, it's not worth it. Okay
I'm gonna just go buy stuff very fast
Key, this is a
Wait, there's a free key. Let's not buy one. Um, what do I buy? What do I buy?
What do I buy? What do I buy? What do I buy? Go quick. Hurry. What is that? I don't know all stats up. Oh
Don't shit the Sun two flubs
The Joker. Um, take a couple of hearts. It's mommy something good. Alright, fuck off
Joker no, I didn't mean to cool nice panic equals power. I don't know what that just does. Does it do oops
I didn't I honestly did not press that fucking button. I swear to God
Why would you why would I have right like why would I have pressed it?
They said there's no reason why you would have it was it I leaned it against my fucking thigh
And it hold on go tinted fucking rock. I can build it up. I can build it back up. Look shit
Forest fucking enemies to have right now
Get out of here open open
Free soul hearts. Oh, yeah, this is awesome. I'm gonna get permanent stat upgrades for this. Oh, yeah
Um
Okay, good. I think it's over. Yeah firing a coin tier costs one coin
Every 20 tears you shoot a coin tear and he's hit with the coin turn into gold
I'm gonna miss this a lot. I imagine it could be good, but it could be bad. I'll try it
Why not every 20 shots does it keep track? 1 2 3 4 5
6 7 8 9 10 11 12 13 14 15
That wasn't 20. It was 15
Okay, um
That soul of Eve
14 dead bird familiars fly in and attack enemies
Take that for the greed fight
Good for final boss. Yeah
Bad I have to lose the card
All right, let's go. I have a key still. Yeah. All right, let's go by a soul heart
Mmm, I want to save the money
Random coin every two rooms. That's great. Oh
God damn it
Go hearts. Oh
Um, whatever god damn it I I worked there's no way anyone's gonna count that I just hope it hits somebody
Geez, I might I might be at a net negative right now with that. I'm just losing money
What's hitting me? Stop? I have the coins to collect of my relationships been fantastic
You mean like all like all around everything's great. Why are you shooting cuz it's I just do it weird question
Yeah, whatever. Okay, this is important
Re-rolls pedestal items, which already already already bought them, but I'll use the soul of Eve though. Oh, no, is it?
Oh, okay. I don't really want the book but on the random trinket while hell doubles the trinket effect
Oh, I'm gonna do that. Yeah, nice. Okay has be completely uncharged active item. Stop shooting
Duplicates one pickup in the room d100. No, I don't want that
Doesn't this double while hell doubles trinket effects shouldn't this be I shouldn't have more
On the bulb, right? Yeah, but d6 to be honest d100
Let's gamble this shit use the d100 in this room. That's so bad
D100 will give you infinite coins. Yeah, it restarts the room time to break the game use it in the shop
I'll see you guys later. This is nice hanging out with you
To
Bismol this is a
Bismol I don't want that. Okay, so we got the backpack
extra active item two trinkets worm
Trap door and then this thing extension cord. I have way I have familiars. Whoa
This is actually pretty cool. Is it worth it to have this and just kind of run around and hope I kill stuff
I mean the stat increases much more important. He will literally do anything you tell him
Well, I mean it is like three o'clock in the morning here, I think I'm a little more I'd say relaxed
I'll keep them both. Well, might as well do it again, but doesn't really roll the room with some damage up
This is actually not terrible, but I need damage up before it's over. I mean it might even be over right now
Yeah, hey EU. Good morning EU. We're having a good breakfast. What are you got? What's it? What's a European breakfast like cigarettes and toast?
Did I just read that wrong?
Soy milk is so bad. I don't think is this even soy milk?
I think so milk is even faster than soy milk is great too, isn't it?
Sad. Oh, it's not like the build I had before was really fantastic. It was okay. I'm gonna lose I'm gonna lose
To the fucking Larry whatever Larry jr. 2.0
God really? Thank God. What can I do to save this divorce papers?
No, this stuff is even worse. That's the red poop with half a heart to get full HP. Oh, yeah
I forgot about that bomb reroll use the d100 again
Um, there's no battery pack reroll for a battery and then
The whole thing. All right, fine. That's actually a smart idea. Damn it. No batteries damage up
Wait on the machine. Well now I can't reroll it again. Well, I was gonna run out of money. What just happened to me
All right. I have an idea. Here's my idea
I'm gonna get to greed and I'm gonna use I'm gonna get to greed and I'm gonna use the
Shit on the ground and just teleport out put that in the war spot. What is he doing? What are they doing?
Use the shovel now. Um shovel doesn't do anything at greed. Uh
You shovel on gems. Yeah, it'll spawn if I put it. Okay, let's see what happens. Nice
Only friend this may have just saved everything because I can just go like this and fucking move up and down and just scan
I'm like a goddamn fax machine. You know what i'm saying? Just go like this and just go
I hate this i'm gonna heal. I didn't realize that that was stem cells. Well, might as well go all in holy shit
This is cracked out. This is actually insane. This could have actually saved everything. I'm okay. Relax
Is it cracked out? Why was it doing? No, never mind. Yeah, never mind. What was doing that much damage this thing here then?
Yeah contact damage from this. It's amazing
Hmm out of my way
Not bad. Yeah, not that great. Whatever. It's all right. I'm just i'm just playing for fun
Anyways, it's not like a cure that that that that that that that that much random direction
And then one bone heart three red hearts
Oh
Back in action. Do I have anything that does this?
homing shots to all familiars do the d100 again, I will after this
I'll let me i'll do this. This is such a mess
I don't even I I don't even know where i'm shooting. It seems to be working
Not bad. Actually, i'm not rerolling this. This actually is kind of good. This could be going way worse and you all know it
Fuck up range down. Who cares?
Tower wait, what's this? What's the improved tower do?
It spawns six clusters of random rocks and obstacles
That's pretty cool
Holy shit
Um, no tinted rocks though, right?
none
uh
How is he still alive?
Do these stupid floating heads?
Why are they still here?
This build sucks
Well, I didn't make this build on my own
I listened to one person that told me to reroll every single object. Wait, this is gonna is it? Hold on
But this it's kind of working
What the fuck was that?
What just came out of my eyes?
Ow, dude, I the text on the screen is making it hard to see
What the fuck is happening? Oh my god
Dude, can we please charge bar? Hold on a minute. What is going on? Is that 1.8 damage or is it good?
I don't want to do that. I mean i'm rerolling this shit. I'll take that give me all stats up
So confused right now, but whatever it's all good. I'm going to use this right now
Nice 2.6. Oh the knife the knife hurts a lot. Not really. Yeah, this thing's stinging and anything save this
I imagine not really dude. Do you know what actually could actually save this?
The just the dead birds and just avoiding greed the whole time just running away and dodging and they'll just kill them
That's the plan. Let's go. I can't take two. Wait, I can do this though one guy. That's a good item
But it's how is it gonna not gonna shoot at anything?
Okay, cool. I'm ready
I've got my soul of eve. I just have to make it through the next area which good
That's not bad either. But what is it gonna poison?
Whatever. Let's go
That's kind of funny because I get I I might just will I be able to reroll during greed like end time
All right. Wish me luck. I have no damage. I literally do nothing. It's gonna be impossible, but whatever
22 damage. I have 22 damage now. Oh, everybody relax everybody relax. I have a shitload of damage now
22 damage
All right. All right. All right. I think I did it. I think i'm good
I don't even know what I have what items these are but this could be this could be legit
The shot speed is so slow. Look at this
My tears are so low
What else is alive?
Something else alive?
Get out of my way. My goodness
I think it's spectral tears
Oh my goodness gracious. Nice lot. Oh
I already have one of these don't I here size up might as well give me that give me this give me this
This is huge. This is actually huge. What should I do now bomb reset? Good idea
Rainworm, okay
This might actually work. Oh two trinkets. All right. Yeah, I I think i'm good
I just have to be careful during ultra greed just hope that the birds can help kill him too and it should be good to go
Please shit. Thanks
Jesus stop spawning shit. Fuck off. Come on. This is like this jerk
Come on, do the 90 degree turn thing that you're supposed to be doing
How come you're not showing your items? Uh, because strange snipers. I wanted to see what I have
So this is like kind of crazy, right? Bones of random pickup
This is a pogged item damage and tears up. Holy shit. All right, i'm ready. So let's go i'm buying
I'm filling up my slots. I want to get the purse, right? So
First in the poison. Wait, is this should I get this? What does a mom's?
Stuff do or just go to blue hearts knife and damage take it blue hearts or
I need the range. Look at look at how bad this is i'm doing it. That's much better
I feel so much more confident. All right, this is it i'm ready
It's time and just use this thing every single time every second whenever I can use it just just use it
Oh shit, wait that with soul of eve. Could I have potentially 30 birds?
There's a 25 chance that i'll have 30 birds. Let's go. It's time. This is it. This is the this is the one right here
Take both of them. Oh, no, I don't want that. Let's go drink it in the shop
All right. I already have two trinkets is poison and um, maybe 30 birds better than this thing
No, i'm gonna keep the worm. All right, let's go. I'm going what is this?
Why is there a ladder in here? There's an angel room up here. It costs money. Why does it cost money? Okay
What is this? Wait, this thing is fucking cracked you shoot
Okay, I only have three luck bomb the angel for more money does that work you liar you liar
You lied you're a liar. Okay. Well, let's go. Here we go. Let's go
I got it. I actually happened it happened happened. I got it. I got it. Look at this. I just used it again
Where are they a bunch of birds odd mushroom? Holy shit, dude
All right, i'm gonna play well, let's go
Nice hooray
Wow, that run was thrown away
Brought out of the trash thrown away again, and then I got like 40 items. I don't even know what I was getting
Let's see there's an extra hud like I don't even know carried by d 100
Well, the d 100 ruined it and then made it better again. Look at all this shit that's around me too
23 damage, it's pretty good. Very cool. Very cool four coins in ultra grade. Oh my god a moment
Yeah, that's fun. I think when I played grittier all the time
I want to say it was like a probably like a 20 or 30 percent win rate
Grittier actually is a huge pain in the ass unless you something like that happens, honestly, and that's it
I guess i'm asleep. Oh my god. I had a moment. That was really fun. Thanks for chilling out and dave
Tell us a bedtime story. No
Hello eu hope you're doing well. How many people are still up in na?
I have to imagine that pacific na is probably very tired
and central and east coast na
Are already asleep right now
8 a.m. Na
Where in na?
Where is it 8 a.m. In north america?
6 30 a.m. On the east coast. What did you say six and i read it is eight isaac's a lot of fun
Thanks for watching. Thanks for hanging out
I'll see you guys. I'm not streaming tomorrow. I mean, well technically it is tomorrow
Let's see what it looks like on thursday friday
I have a couple of things
Very important to take care of for grotto beasts
Because grotto beasts is very very close
There are a lot of things that still have to be kind of situated
Because obviously the launch of grotto beasts is
Very very soon when I made that I made talked about it on the discord
Talked about a little bit a couple weeks ago three weeks ago or so
Still trying to shoot for that end of february
And if it's not
The end of february then it'll be literally like within a day or two later
We'll get you a hard date
Tons of info is going to come out tons of things that we can talk about
Should be really really fun a lot of time a lot of work went into it
Um, it's kind of the project that took the place of a
I guess like an event stream
No way already. Yeah, but what is the end of february? Well, it's still about six or seven more days
six more days
What I also told you guys do that this year
This year's a lot of
more of this
Way more of this
And this new philosophy that I have for the channel
I think i've streamed way more
By just being like, you know what?
It's eight o'clock at night. Let's go. I'm gonna just do anything. It doesn't matter what it is
And this is the stuff that makes me happy
So i'm gonna keep doing it
That's how gamers should be
But yeah, thanks for sticking around kind of an impromptu late night stream
I'll see you guys in a couple days
Maybe a day or two. I don't know. We'll see. I who knows over the next two days
If I just might just turn it on again
Breath of the wild is something I really actually do want to do
Imagine you'll see that frog detective has to happen before the end of february
What did I say? I was gonna like delete my twitch channel or something if I don't
it's like hooper, uh
Will probably be played within the next six to 12 months
So yeah, I mean there's lots of things to do
All right, everybody
I will see you later
Take care of yourselves get some sleep if you are still up
Or you know what do whatever do whatever you want
You do whatever you feel like it's your life. It's not mine
I'm not going to tell you what to do with yours exactly how I expect you not to tell me what to do with mine
Just take care of yourself
Have a great one
And definitely look out for grotto beast info. It's gonna be a big deal. That's all i'm saying
Some of the stuff we got cooking
Just it's I cannot wait for you to see it. That's all i'm gonna say
We're never gonna see him again. I just I told you i'll be back in like two days
Hey, my mother wants more info. When can we expect sorcery?
Uh, she said she has no faith in your wait a little longer excuse
Yeah
No, that's a mother. All right. Yep
That's a mother
After breath of the wild, I think I want to finish that first
Yeah, I still want to do the hitman stuff
I finished sorcery three times in a row after seeing you play it. That's awesome because it's
One of the best games ever made
Any new weird dreams?
um
Not that I can really recall that were that interesting
Hold on. Let me just manually turn this down
There we go. Nice and slow. There it is. Good night guys. Be good
Be well
See you soon
Have a great morning
Good morning, not good night
I got it wrong
See you later
Call your mother
Not right now
In a more reasonable hour
See you later