What's up everybody? We are live, yes we are.
Sorry, I have to move over here to my battle station.
I had to set my microphone and cameras up for this stream.
And we're all set. Go back offline.
That's the second day in a row. Okay, that's the second day in a row that I have read.
Within 30 seconds of the stream starting, somebody say,
Get the fuck out of here. Turn off your stream. And I go, turn off my stream.
What are you talking about, man? What?
I don't know why. I have no idea.
Anyways, today is going to be sort of a fun stream, I hope.
It depends on how good Joel and I are at communicating instructions.
We're going to play keep talking and nobody explodes.
I have, well, I'll just show you.
Well, hold on, hold on.
Joel just started the stream too, so let's let people trickle in for a little bit.
Make sure I got my copy in the right place.
Give me one second.
Alright, so take a look at my setup here.
Well, the stream is not over, don't worry.
So I've got for you here my battle station.
I printed this shit out. I'm ready to go.
I'm not messing around.
I've got my guide.
As you see, bomb defusal manual.
I've just got to lean over a little.
I am ready.
I told you I was taking this fucking dead serious.
Dead serious today.
And you can see, look at this. Take a look at this.
You can actually read along with me if you want to.
That's good. Looks like it's not blocking the way.
There's my bomb defusal manual.
Joel has one of these too.
So wait, you can't even hear the music.
We did a trial run before the stream turned on.
And we did alright.
We did okay.
Shave. Get out of here.
How can you even tell?
I have like a spooky ghost light on me.
How can you tell that I need to shave?
It just looks like a little bit of scrub.
How can you tell?
It looked like Jesus.
If Jesus was around today,
he'd have the most followed Twitter account.
That's okay with me. He's a pretty fucking big deal.
Alright, so let's see. Is Joel ready?
Is his stream on?
He just went BRB.
Wait, hold on. His stream is not on?
Yes it is.
What are you talking about?
His stream's not turned on?
No, he's on. He's on. He's on.
See?
We have to do the squad stream thing because
we're going to have two different...
When I'm doing the bomb stuff,
our screens are going to be completely different.
Why did he leave the call?
Important question.
Who is a better music producer?
I don't know who any of...
Neither of those people are. I have no idea.
Alright, what's he doing?
Joel, what are you up to?
See, this is my own... Alright, let me tell you something.
This is my own damn fault.
When I start a stream,
I'm just like...
I have an intro screen, and the intro screen plays.
Right?
And then, I sit there for one minute, and then I go...
Okay, it's time to start streaming now.
I'm like, I've got time to go. Let's go.
I don't give any fucking time.
And some... I always just...
Not even two minutes will go by.
I just sit there because...
Yeah, ADHD.
It just takes over my whole body.
Because I'm looking at... I'm here. I'm just here.
And I'm seeing the screen. I'm seeing people chatting.
I'm just going like...
I want to... Let's go.
Fucking five year old. What is that thing in your camera?
What are you talking about? The thing in my camera.
What? What thing?
Five, six thing.
Five, seven. Don't fucking get it wrong.
That thing.
Oh, this thing.
This is this camera.
I have like a...
I have like a periscope.
This is one of those scenarios where
I'm going to fall down on this stream,
and this is going to go through my fucking eye.
It's like...
Everyone's now going,
oh, please don't do that.
Oh, okay, he's almost ready.
He's almost ready.
We spoiled the joke.
Me putting my head through
is... What do you mean a joke?
That would be a disaster. That would be a horrible thing that would happen to me.
Alright, look.
Alright, here you go.
Alright, hold on.
I'm going to be...
You know when you wait for the bus
and you got there way too early
and you realize
that the next bus is coming in like
30 minutes,
and you go, fuck.
I mean...
This is the way that I am when the bus
is coming.
Walking around, just looking at stuff.
You look at the same ad on the side of the bus stop
like a thousand times.
You just pace around.
You're like, alright, that bus will be here in 30 minutes.
My phone...
My phone is not even interesting.
I hate that shit.
When your phone is not interesting,
that's when it's the worst waiting.
You can't even open up your phone
and do anything because
nothing on this phone is interesting.
I've already seen these tweets a thousand times.
I've been to Reddit twice.
I wrote 25 comments.
I hate waiting.
Hey Jervis, so don't we when you're late
all the fucking time.
Oh, shit.
Oh.
I got myself. I fell in my own trap there.
I stepped on a rake
in the backyard and it hit me right in the fucking face.
I don't have front teeth anymore.
Alright.
Let's fucking go.
And then, when the bus
actually shows up...
When the bus shows up... Oh, hold on. I'm sorry. I'm going over something.
Alright. When the bus
actually shows up and you look at the top
text on the bus and it's not
for where you're fucking going.
It's the complete opposite side of town.
And you're like, god damn it. I have to wait for another
20 minutes. I thought it was 30. Alright.
How you doing? You ready? Yeah.
I'm good. I'm good. Go.
You ready to defuse some bombs?
I hope so.
Yeah, me too.
So you want to go first?
How do you want to do this? You fucking read.
I'll read first. Alright. Listen.
I'm not self-deprecating but I'm saying
if I start fucking reading manuals right
now
I might as well be reading a fucking Arby's menu.
Alright. I'm not going to get shit done.
You have to read. I have to do this.
Okay. I think I can handle it.
Alright.
We did do this once.
And god damn it. This is gonna
hurt me. Alright.
Now it's all like this is a gun pointing at me.
Ugh. This is a gun pointing at me.
Listen. The core principle
of defusing bombs are like
handling stuff under pressure.
I've come to learn that
you can always rely on chat.
Chat always knows how to handle these situations.
Chat should really be
the bomb experts in this case.
So what we're going to do in case this gets a little
hard, you guys are going to have to spit
instructions at us and I'm sure that
with your expertise and
our lack of, we're going to have
an excellent stream that's not going to be going down
as the worst stream of 2020 already.
So
you ready to do this?
Hey. Look. Joel.
We're starting all the way at the bottom.
We're starting at the bottom.
So there's no way this could be the worst
stream of 2020. Like as
long as this is even 5% better
than the Halo. Jeremy this is already the worst stream
that we've ever done.
Alright. Are you ready?
I'm fucking ready. Wait. Wait.
We have to squad stream. Oh yeah.
Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. We gotta
you know. Cause guys people are only going to see
the manual on mine.
Let's see here. Somebody
just goes worst stream of the 21st
century.
Alright. I invited you to a
squad stream. Squad up.
So what will happen is you're going to get
two Twitch
screens on both channels and you're going to get
to choose which one you want. Screens or screams.
Alright. You get it?
I'm ready to go.
Alright. It says invite send.
Are we even in squads?
Are we squading up? Are we let's going?
I don't know if I see it but are
you guys seeing it? Do you guys see?
No. No. That one
that one ain't going where I want to go.
It just drove by. Fuck.
No? What do you mean no?
Listen guys. We're trying to diffuse bombs here.
Alright. Alright. You send me
an invite. Okay.
You know what's the funniest thing? Sometimes when I try to like
I just want to like
send you tweets or whatever stuff.
I forget what your name is.
I know your name is like Bob or whatever but
the thing is like you have these
three last numbers. I'm just like Jerma 900.
Jerma 800 like
Alright. Let's fucking
go Joel. I'm ready. Alright.
We're squatted up.
Alright. I'm going to turn off this monitor.
You got control right? Yeah.
Yeah. Alright. Monitor off.
I'm ready. Are you
fucking ready for the stream
2020 to define
the 20s. The roaring
20s. Alright. If you don't know how this game
works. We have
five minutes to diffuse a bomb where I can't
see what he's doing. I have to give him
instructions on what he has to do.
And he can't see anything.
Just open the fucking game.
Alright. Hold on. Should I
mute this? No. Does that
matter? No. No. No. No.
Alright.
I was taking control of the game.
Alright. Listen. Listen. I
I'm on Jerma's computer. I get to see all
the desktop porn. Alright. Listen.
Feel sorry for me. I didn't give you
access to the fucking keyboard. So
Sure about that?
Listen. Do not look at the screen.
I will. I got
like my last like six years of
tax returns on my desktop. Don't fucking show
it. Alright. Maybe
fucking tell me instructions and we won't have to fucking show
that on stream. Alright. Here we go. Let's kick some ass.
Alright. Jerma. You
ready to read? Yes.
Alright. Okay. What do you got?
Okay. So. We got a yellow wire.
A white wire. A red wire. And a blue
wire. Wait. Wait. Wait. Wait. Wait. Modules.
Okay. On the subject of wires.
How many wires are there? There are
four wires. Four wires. Okay.
Is there
any red wires? There's one red
wire. Okay. Is there more than
is there two red wires? There's
just one color. There's
one yellow, one white, one red, one blue.
Wait. Wait. Wait. Wait. Okay. Hold on.
Nope. Don't argue.
Don't argue. I can hear the noise and it's freaking
me out. Alright. If there how many
Wait. Is the last wire yellow?
No. I need to talk to you.
Alright. Hold on.
There's no red wires.
There's one red. I fucking said that.
There's only one red
wire. There's one red wire. Okay.
Alright. Is the last wire
yellow? No. It's blue.
Okay. Is there one blue wire?
There's
Is there one blue wire? I'm gonna fucking come over to Boston
and I'm gonna fucking. I don't even live there anymore
man. Alright. I'm fucking
Alright. Is there one?
Yes or no? Is there one blue wire?
Third fucking time
blue wire. Say it. Is it one blue?
Okay. Then cut. There's one blue wire.
Cut the first wire. Cut the first wire.
Did you cut it? Yeah. Yeah.
I don't know how to.
Okay. What's next? What else? What else?
Okay. Then we have a
second module. It's a keypad
looking thing, right? Keypad looking thing.
With the symbols?
The first one is like an X with a little schadoodle
underneath it. Okay.
X with a little. Just go. Okay.
It's like a
really badly looking K
or an X. Okay. It's a bad K.
With a schadoodle underneath it. It's a bad K with a schadoodle
underneath. It's like a
cursive kind of looking K. It's not an X.
Is it an H? Is it an H?
Does it look like an H? Yeah. You can
say that. Yeah. Sure. Okay. So
it's. Okay. What else?
Then you have an upside down question mark.
Upside down question mark. Okay.
Then you have a drooling O. Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait.
Could that also be an upside down
9-2?
Uh, no.
I don't see any upside down question marks here.
Yes, I do. Okay. What else? What else? What else?
Rifle. Rifle. Rifle. A drooling O.
An O that's drooling. Okay. Yep. What else?
Okay. Then you have
a backwards E with two dots.
It's like a swede
rodent E. Okay. Alright.
Press the backwards E first.
Okay. Then the drooling O.
And then the H with the
squiggly. And then the upside down question mark.
We got it. Got it.
Alright. Is that it? What else?
That's pretty much it. What do you mean that's it?
Why is it still ticking?
You got the big old button. Big old button.
Alright.
Follow these rules in the order that they are listed. Perform
the first action that applies. Alright.
What color is the button?
White. It's a white button. Okay.
We don't have less than a
Just a minute now. Alright. If the button
is white and there is a lit
indicator with a lit. What does it say on it?
Abort. It says abort. Okay.
If there's
If the button is yellow, if the button is red, and the button says hold.
If none of the apply, hold the button and refer to releasing.
Wait. So where's the board?
Does it say abort anywhere?
How much time do I have? On the fucking button.
Bright fucking Las Vegas letters
blinking at me. Why? Why? It's like
stuff coming. Okay. Hold the button down.
Okay. And then
If you start holding the button down, a colored strip
will light up on the right side of the module.
Based on its color, you must release the button
at a specific point in time. What color?
Blue. Release when the countdown
timer has any four in any position.
Any four?
Yeah. Four in any position. Let it go
when it's at four. In any position. Okay.
Okay. We did it!
We did it! You didn't think we were going to get one.
You didn't think we were going to get one.
You didn't think we were going to get one. You didn't think
we were going to get one. Listen. Listen.
Here's the thing about being a
miracle man, right? You have to like
underperform. You have to tell
people that it's going to be awful.
And then you have to do a slight effort.
And then people are like, wow, they are geniuses.
I couldn't believe that. I doubted them.
You know. That's the power.
That's the power of lying. Alright?
Okay. That's being a
gamer. That's what being a gamer is all about.
You guys doubted us.
You guys said, oh, colossal
brain. You said dumb and
dumper. Alright. Uh-uh. Listen.
Mario and Luigi. Listen.
We can do this.
Joel, that was level one. This is one of many.
I don't want to
step on your, uh, I don't want to
rain on your parade here. That was level one.
Are you ready to do level two?
That doesn't, that doesn't matter.
We got this, man. Alright. There's so much in here
too. This is like a thick ass book. Alright.
Here's the thing though. Here's the thing though.
I noticed there's a problem already.
You're yelling at me.
You were yelling at me.
You're yelling at me. You're being
unnecessarily
aggressive. How
Listen, next time you start yelling at
me, there's going to be consequences.
Oh, consequences. Oh no.
Consequences.
Are you ready for the second one?
Excuse me? Are you ready for the second one?
I'm ready. I'm ready.
Okay.
Where is, uh,
where's the second bomb at?
I kind of feel fucking like shit right now. Alright.
Uh, second bomb should be the next one.
Uh,
free play? No, this is, is it all
like level two?
I can't find level two. Let me turn on my monitor.
That's the first bomb. Alright, first, that was the first
bomb. So let me turn on my monitor and help you out here.
Oh, no, no, no. Okay. Never mind.
Never mind. Never mind. I, I, we can do
this. Okay. Sorry. Sorry guys.
Listen, listen, listen.
Maybe you guys are the bomb. I guess you guys are fucking
yelling at me now. What are you looking at?
You see, you see, you are the challenge.
You are the challenge right now. Alright.
Listen, I'm all blind.
I'm being gamer.
You see, I'm inviting you in. I said
that when I just won. The thing about this
is I underperform.
You guys don't expect this, but when we actually get into this
we're gonna soup through everything.
Alright. Okay.
Let's fucking soup
through everything. What do you, I don't know what that means.
Alright, let me turn on my monitor. Sometimes I say
I don't mean anything. They just like phonetically like imply
things. Like, you know, soup is like
you know.
I still have ink on my hands. This is fresh print.
You have ink on your hands?
Yeah. I printed this like 40 minutes
ago and like the ink is coming off my hands.
Taste it.
No. Why did I give that one second
of thought? Why would I give that even one second
thought? But listen,
listen, it might like sharpen you out. Like
tell you, here's an added challenge.
Try the ink. Get poisoned.
If we can do this in time, you can make it
to the hospital. You want to up the stakes gamer?
I'm going, I'm going, I'm
running to my destination.
What did you say?
When is some, seeing something familiar bomb become
comforting? No matter. This bomb will only be half comforting.
You ready to do this? Same thing.
Five minutes, three modules, three strikes.
I just spit on myself.
Alright. Are you going?
Alright. Yeah, I'm ready.
I'm ready.
Hang on, hang on. We're not done yet.
Alright, we're starting now.
Alright, gamer, you welcome? You welcome to
help? I'm ready.
Alright, first module is,
well, we actually have two wires now.
Why am I doing this so slow? Two wires?
What do you mean two wires? Okay, yeah. We're going to look at the first
one. It's going to be two yellow wires.
There's three wires in total. There's one red,
two yellow. Two yellow.
Okay.
As you said, there's a red wire. Thank you. I'm going.
Okay. Is the last wire white?
No, red. Last wire is what?
Is there, is there, is it, there's no more than one blue
wire? There's no,
there's three wires, two yellow,
one red. Cut the last wire.
Alright. Okay, what's the next one?
Second one, you have one
blue, one black, one red.
What do you mean, what do you mean? There's another, there's two wire modules?
There's two, there's, we just saw
one module of wires, now that's a whole
new salad of wires.
Fuck! Alright, what is it?
There's one blue, one black, one red. One blue,
one black, one red. What are you doing?
Cut the last wire again. You think you're funny? Cut the last wire again.
We got it.
Alright, and then we have a whole new problem.
Alright, listen.
Listen, we have a new problem now. We have a new model I've never seen
before. It's a giant two,
and it says one, three, two, four
in four different key buttons.
Wait, what does it look like?
Okay, you have a giant
like big screen with four
buttons underneath that says one, three,
two, four.
Okay, alright, it's a memory problem.
It's a memory problem. Alright.
Press the, alright, memory is a fragile
thing, but so is everything else when a bomb
goes off, so pay attention. Okay, so press
the correct button to progress the module to the next
stage. Complete all stages. Okay, press the correct
button, progress. Pressing an incorrect button
will reset the bomb. Button positions
are ordered from left to right. Alright.
It's stage one.
If the display, what number
is on the top? What number is it?
Two, two, two. Okay.
If the display is two,
what do these different stages mean?
Alright, there's five
stages.
Stop stressing out. Just read and tell me.
Alright, if it's stage one.
What are you doing?
I don't understand.
Yeah, you don't understand.
If the number is two, press the button in the second
position. Oh,
right, right, right. We go, go, go, go. Alright, so
I pressed
the third one. It's showing a green one now.
Now press the button in the same
position as you pressed,
you just did. Do it again. Okay.
It's still two, right?
Yeah, okay, okay.
It's saying a three now. Okay, three.
Press the button in the third
position. Got it.
Two left now.
What's my number?
Three. Press the button in the same position
that you just pressed in stage two. Wait, don't press
anything. What did you press two times ago?
That
would be the first one.
Okay, last one, last one.
Okay, what's the number?
Two. Two. Press the button
with the same label you pressed in stage
two. That would be the same.
Oh, no, no, no, no, it isn't.
Oh, Jesus, I'm sorry.
Did you fuck me? Did you fuck me?
No, I didn't. Did you fuck me?
You said two, right? No.
What did you say the number was? No, no, no, no.
No, no, no, no. Wait, we have to do this
all over again. Alright, come on, come on, come on.
What's the number?
The number is one, press the button in the second
position. Okay.
Got it. What's the next number?
What's the next number? Two, two. Okay.
Press the button in the same position you pressed in stage one.
So, press the same one. Okay, I got it.
Okay, remember what you just did.
Yeah. Go on.
The same one?
What's the number? Two!
Okay, two. Press the button with the…
Ouch! Press the button with the same label you pressed in stage one.
Press the same one you just pressed.
Okay, you did Joel Joel Joel. He's dead. All right. Where is he?
He didn't like turn his stream off. Did he? I'm dead. What the fuck was that shit?
What was the what was that cartoon stuff? That was her life's German. All right. Well, we know what that all right
You're ready start over. Yeah. Oh my god. Okay, so
Listen, listen that was that that was what was called a fake move. That was a fake out
Sometimes you do fake as a test the waters. All right
Now we have conquered this
Alright, it's probably gonna be same modules. You ready? Yeah. Yeah. No, no, it isn't. Oh god. It isn't
Okay. Well, whatever the point. Okay. Listen, listen first. First module. We got is wires first models wires three wires one red one black
One yellow is a no white
No, cut the last one. Got it
We have a keypad at the last one
Keep that. All right. Give me two symbols. What are they? First one is is mr. Smiley, man
Okay, smiling man with we got a back. We got a backwards P
What do you mean smiling man? Like like that like mr. Like like one one guy bullshit. Okay, okay smile the guy backwards P
Yeah, all right. All right. All right. Then you got like a three with a snake squid Leah
All right, yep
Yeah, and then you got a TV
What's it was a TV with a tea inside? All right. I got it. You ready smiley face TV backwards P weird three
Got it. Now we got Simon says Simon says I would this is new
Okay, one of the four colored buttons will flash
losing
Using the correct table below press the button with the corresponding color
The original button will flash followed by another repeat this sequence in order using the color mapping
Okay, so
Blue is blue at top up top. Yes blue stone top
Okay, so it flashed blue button to press the red button the red one press red
Got it. Okay. Now what then I went blue yellow red
Green no blue yellow. What?
But you need to press wait, it does a serial number have a vowel in it
I
Detect the serial number to the serum above a vowel in it. Just anything around the serial numbers
Okay, do you have a look for the serial numbers of have a vowel?
Hang on. Hang on. It's gonna
Yeah, it's like it's like a sequence of numbers. It's it's like a little time. Yeah, is there a vowel?
Right, so we got so it's blue it's a blue yellow, right? Yeah, press red green red green
Okay, then I went blue yellow green blue yellow. Okay. I want you to press red
green
What was the third color?
Jerma, what was the third color? Just say it again?
It was green. Okay, so you need to do red green yellow. Okay
No, it's not you said blue
Okay
Green red. Okay, red green red. Okay. Good quicker
Okay, press press green red blue, okay got it blue yellow green blue
Okay, red green
Oh my god
What are they they're new what are they blue yellow green press red
blue
Yellow red blue red blue yellow red blue yellow
Yellow the colors fucking change. It's like reading the color and seeing the fucking thing
We got this man, hey, that's the first time we even seen that without now what now we know what happens
Listen here's what's gonna happen
This is unbelievably stressful and
You might say like listen here gamer. Are you colorblind? No
You you fucking try having having this amount of stress on you. All right, listen. Listen, here's what we're gonna do
We're gonna do we're gonna try again now that we try the waters
Okay, it says cause of explosion Simon says all right Simon says might be a horrible decrement to the gameplay
It might be the killer. I
Get how it works now. Okay. Okay. Okay. Good. Okay. You ready? I'm ready. I'm focusing here
Unfortunately, we have another Simon says immediately. So let's look let's do that last. Let's look first. Fuck. Fuck it Simon says first
Where do you have a
Do you have a bee anywhere? Where's a bee? No, this is fucking making a table. God. Damn it. I
Must've got stapled in here. All right
Simon says what? Okay, what first color first color first color? Okay
I wasn't paying attention. I was too confused by bees red red red red red red. All right, press blue. Wait
What's serial number vowels? Oh
Hang on. Uh, Jesus Jesus Jesus. We have any we have any we have all right, so it's flash red press blue
Okay, go on lose pressed red yellow blue green blue greens been pressed now red yellow blue
Blue green red. Okay now red yellow blue yellow
Yellow blue green red green red yellow blue yellow blue
Red yellow blue yellow blue red. Yeah, don't do these
I'm just saying I'm over red yellow blue yellow blue red yellow blue yellow blue red yellow blue yellow blue
Okay, okay. I'm gonna say these out loud and you press them as I do it ready. Okay blue green. Hey red
All right reset you gotta do it faster man. Oh god, okay red yellow blue yellow blue red red
You hold on red yellow blue yellow blue. Okay. Okay. Yep. Yellow red red green
Green red red green green
Okay, what's next? Okay. Okay. Yeah, keep that keep head symbols
Okay, uh TV TV is the first one then you got an upside down nine
Then you got a squiggle fucker at the bottom at left like you got it you got a triangle upside-down triangle
you got like a like a
Japanese toll what fuck you don't read Japanese, whatever then you got a upside down
Bowel with a line in it upside down basically spider think spider. Okay, so you got you got you got upside down nine
you've got the
Spider and then you got an upside down question mark. Okay, I got it. I got it
I got it press not press upside down nine. Okay, then
The was there TV in this one. Yes, there was TV at the first one TV
Did you press it with that one? Okay. Yeah, okay, and then the weird spider thing you were talking about
No, wait, wait, wait, like the Japanese thing you were saying. Yeah
Okay, and then then the then the question mark already got it man. Okay, what's not?
Okay. Now we just need to press the you got a big red button figure about okay. Okay. What does it say on it?
Just put this press it's a red you said 55 seconds that how many batteries on the bum
None, I can't see any spin it around. Just look. Okay
They are two they are two batteries four in total, but but two batteries one, two, three four actually
All right, wait, there's four batteries. Yeah four batteries
There are more than two batteries on the bomb and there is a lit indicator with the label FRK
Press it immediately release the button
Ah
What I'm just gonna hold it I'm gonna hold it
What do you mean it's blue it's just blue FRK fuck it fuck it don't do that. Okay, press press and hold it
What happened? What happened?
Somebody said Joel is fucking dumb laughing my ass off
Listen, what? No, he's not
I'm not I'm a gamer. He's a gamer
What I don't understand?
That's so fucking I don't know what happened
Let's listen, what's the ratio of dumbness here? All right. Listen, listen, what's the ratio of dumbness?
Like all right. All right
If we're on a seesaw thing, right? What where's the dumbness our way a
seesaw
You don't know what a seesaw is. I know what a seesaw is, but like that's not there's only two
Let's let's say we have animals for heads, right? That represents dumbness
All right, we both sing at each side of the the seesaw which dumbness like outweighs the other so tips over you know
I mean, oh
I see what you're saying. Like you're talking a scale a scale
We both sit there like our brains are both being weighed on a scale, which who has the heavier brain? Okay. Um, I
Don't know that's for the audience to decide. No, I mean they balance each other
It's just even at zero
All right, we're gonna get this one because it's all right
embarrassed
his thing though is the thing what you don't understand is like
German I are what is commonly referred to as liars
it's a bit of an incorrect term here really but
we've been putting on a show for you guys because we know that you know if we breeze through everything here and we didn't
You know entertain you guys with with
Fail attempts we would essentially be beating this and there will be no comedy to it
So but we're gonna we're gonna do this thing now where we're gonna drop the facade and I know you guys are doing
Kappa and stuff like that, but but you could tell
That I'm not smiling when I'm saying this
That means that this this is the one
This is gonna be the one speaking of facade. Do you know that button shit just fucks me up?
Jerma, I gotta ask you something. Oh, I already saw it. Yeah, somebody linked it. Yeah, somebody linked it last night
See it I did
The image of I don't know I'm just saying it's the same face
Yeah, listen. So it listen. Ah, do you have any do you have any?
You know anything to say about it
What am I supposed to say? I look like I mean, I mean the source apologize
Why do I have to apologize for looking like somebody? Well, you know apologize for looking like somebody Jesus
That's unbelievable. Well, maybe to the audience, you know, maybe they feel offended by it
by the fact that
You've been like, you know
Going around dinner parties and stuff. I don't know
Yeah, I just go out of dinner parties and I introduced myself
Listen, it's I'm sorry better than us trying to defuse bombs. Are you ready to do this?
I'm sorry, and I'm gonna give you the best instructions I can all right you better
There's the apology. Maybe said the word I allowed Joe
Listen, we don't have time for your bullshit. No, I'm serious
We don't have we we can't we can't do German talk, right? All right, right, right, right
First one we got a keypad thing module. All right, we got a backwards P
Star a
Three with a squiggly underneath it
Okay, what's the last one? And the last one is one?
It's like I with a you inside of it
Okay. Yeah. All right press I with a you
Then backwards P then weird three then start got it. What's the next module?
Sorry, I was just I was just thinking about you looking like trip. Anyway, we got this big three with four keypads underneath it
Okay
What's it? He said three?
Yeah, press the button in the third position. All right. Okay, we then have four
Press the button in the same position you just pressed in stage one. So press the third position again. Got it. Okay
We've got four again
Press the button labeled for okay. We have a four
Press the button in the same position you pressed in stage two, which was
Guys, what's that? Too? Was that too? Was that too? Was that too? No, no, no, no. No, I don't know
I don't know. I can't see your screen
It's a third. We're good. We're good. We're good. Okay, last one. We got one press the button with the same label
You pressed in stage one
That was to again right no
Number it's gonna match the number the label the number not the position the number. All right, where are we? Oh
Fuck. Okay. We're back to one back to one. We're back to one. Yeah, we're back to one. Oh my god
All right, what's the number?
One, okay, press the button in the second position
Got it
Never got one again. That's the next number. Okay
Press the number labels for we got number one again
Okay, press the button with the same label you pressed in stage two, which was labeled for got it. Okay, keep on
number three
Press the button in the same position that you pressed in stage two, which was
It was whatever it was. It was whatever was like
Guys, what the fuck was that?
People think three I'm gonna go go with your your choice yet
All right, and now we have number two press the button in the first position
And that was in the first press the button just in the first visit the first number
German we're fucked one
second position
Three press the button in the first position and remember what these are. Yes. Okay
For press the button labeled for okay three
Press the button in the same positions you pressed in stage two
guys first position I
Got you covered. All right. Okay. I got you covered
Press the button with the same label you pressed in stage four. I
can't help
Thanks guys
Listen listen that was the one that was the one
Listen, you know what? That means chapped. I can't trust you guys
You can't listen to chat chat is gonna it's gonna it's gonna chat
Unbelievable they're gonna say press two and you're gonna go to you got it and then the big explodes we have to do it again
Want you to look at the screen right now, I want you to read the cost of death memory
Okay, listen last one if we can't figure this out listen
That means it's impossible for me to do this. All right, we can switch roles and I could take the bomb
Well, you read the instructions we could do that too after this you want it you want to do that?
I think I can it's gonna help us. I think I can I will be very clear with you
Okay, okay. Oh my god. Okay. Here we go. I'm gonna retry this one
All right, listen no more bullshit no more no more for real this time for real this time for real this time
All right, we got we got a wire module at the first one. All right, we got a blue one
We've got three black another blue and a white how many how many words just slow down so many wires
They are currently
Five wires five wires. Okay
What's the serial number?
What do you got for sale into cereal? What's the serial number? Okay. Sorry
Is it by the way is the last wire black?
Let's see here. No, it's white. Okay
Forget that if there is exact is there one red wire and and no more is there one
Serial, no, no fuck that forget all that. All right. Is there one red wire and one yellow wire? No, there's nothing like that
How many what? Okay, so is it more than one yellow wire?
No, there is two blue three black and one white
Are there any black wires at all?
Did you not hear me? I said I did but are there any black wires at all? There's three. There's three black wires
Cut the first wire. Okay
You fucked up. No
Fuck that's my fault. That was my fault. I fucked it up. All right, what do we got?
What we got at this point, I mean we fucked it up fucking we're gonna keep that instead
We're gonna be back with see you with the two dots
Okay, keep going
We got a we got an H with a without you over it and it's got a bit of a squiggle at the bottom
Okay. Yep
We got the fuck I keep thinking in Japanese we got
I can't say this what that's like saying the the kind of for key
Fuck, you know Japanese. I don't know any Japanese fuck
Okay, we got like a little figure a railroad track. Like it's a it's a line with two like staples on it
What like a puzzle piece?
Okay. Okay. Okay. Yes. Yes. Yes. Yes. Okay. I see I see
Okay, and then we got I
like the letter I a
I know what you mean by that and like I could use a little clearer instructions. Okay, what else and that's it
Okay, so we got you said there's a
Even two dots even two dots. Yep. Okay and go over that. What's it? What's it? The other one the
You alright you ready? Okay backwards backwards e train track
I and then the H the H got it. Okay. All right. Now we go back to the the fucker again
alright, so
We really got a rumor this time. We cannot fuck up this time. Okay, we got a two
The fucker
Don't second position. Okay one
Labeled for press the button labeled for got it to press the button with the same label you pressed in stage one
What was the first one or like like number the same number in stage one?
Got it. Okay now two
Press the button in the first position got it for press the button with the same label. You pressed in stage three
Yeah, I think it was whatever was in the third position I think yes, I did it I did it I did it
Yes, yes. Yes. Yes. Yes. I
Think so
Level two. I see I'm still going though. It's still fucking going. So what is there anything else?
It's been a little bit wrong
Shit, we got we got a serial port inside. Oh the wires the wires the wires
Blue black blue black blue six wires. Yeah, do we have an odd serial number?
And they took a random one and I swear to God if we would have won that way fuck it, but here's the thing
I thought if you fail a module, that's it, right?
So we were just sitting there and you're just spinning the thing around like all right, we win we did it
More time I'm gonna get you through this one. I'm getting you through this. I'm gonna do it. I'm gonna get you through it
I'm gonna get you through this one. I
Far to be fair. I did fuck up the wire one. I fucked up that first one
Here's the thing is like I wanted to like try you and see like ha ha ha ha
But I realized that's fucking utterly stupid of an idea that is to like fuck around with now
So I said no, no, no, let's not do that
And I thought you didn't hear me
So I thought like okay now now you're going on the tangent where like you didn't hear my joke
So it just became this this this smear of like let's let's not fuck around
All right
All right for real this time listen, this is it this is the one
Tips to help me help you. Okay. Okay. When the when a module when you got the modules, right? Mm-hmm
Immediately immediately tell me the number of like for wires number of wires immediately. Okay. All right. Okay four wires got it
Then go right. Okay. Okay
But then I can go bang right there
Right there and I'll be ready for it. But what if you fuck up? Well, I did fuck up last time
I've fucked the whole thing up last time
That was on me that was on me man
Listen, this is the one. This is the one right up. Listen. I can only play so much half-life in my head
Eventually, there's too little space and I get a little dumb, you know, I mean I'm saying
It does say you put you're playing half-life every single day on steam
Okay, at least on that that doesn't that okay just for clarification here
I've been playing half-life for like 35 days on steam and I don't know how to shut it down
Just says he's playing half-life and I can't like a control out the late in the in the
Panel whatever still there. I don't know what's going on
All right, listen
Task manager. Listen, listen, you think you think I'm a native English speaker? I barely understand half the shit
I'm saying right now
Incomprehensibly difficult it is to communicate with somebody
Not graphs the words that are coming out of your mouth
No, no, no, don't move the fucking mouse. I can't move the mouse. I can't click that link. I'm sorry
All right
Jeremiah I swear I will go on the desktop and I'll reveal all the stolen tax documents you got
Don't show my fucking taxes. Don't show my tax friends. All right, you've let's go. We're doing this. All right level two. Yes
Okay, I believe we can't do level two. This is fucking embarrassing. All right. Okay. Here we go. We've got three wires
Well, I didn't even know where we're going
Okay, three wires
Yes, what red blue white red blue and white? Okay. Yes is
The last wire white. Yes cut the last wire
Gotcha
Next we got a whole new problem. We got a whole new model. I'm not familiar unfamiliar with we have essentially pac-man
It looks like pac-man
Okay, all right. All right. All right. It's like a maze. Okay. Yeah
Okay, this is a find the maze with the matching circular markings
the diffuser must
Hold on the diffuser circles
The diffuser must navigate the white light to the red triangle using the arrow buttons warning. Oh fuck
I have you I have your keyboard disabled
German
Hold on. Hold on a second. Hold on. All right, I'll press the buttons. You just tell me what they are. Okay, but you not cross the lines
Do not cross the lines
In the maze. Okay, so I have no fucking idea what this wants us to do
This battle that battleship find the maze with the matching markings. Okay
All right. So where are the circles?
There's two circles at
The second row and the third row. Okay second. All right, are they on opposite ends?
Yes, they are. Okay, they're on opposite ends. So now
So that's the correct this one here, but what how am I so you have to navigate
You must navigate the white light to the red triangle. Where's the red triangle? It's
left of the the right third column
Okay, so so like one two three down and then one over from from the right. Sure
So now you have to
Navigate the white light to the red triangle. Don't cross the lines. These lines are invisible on the bond
We're fucked. We're fucked
You want to restart this? Wait, don't move. It's over Anakin. I have to hide rounds. I fucked it up
I fucked it up. You need to have you need to be able to press the keys
Just a bunch of buttons and explode and I'll give it to you. Okay
You don't need a key you use the mouse you can use the mouse what you can use the mouse to like navigate to the keys
You don't need a fucking numb
It says well, you have to use it
The keys, okay
It's not keys on the keyboard. It says the arrow buttons that the arrow
Shit, okay
You you have to that one's the right one. Hey, don't give me that tone fine
You must navigate the white light to the red triangle using the arrow buttons
You have to navigate to you have to navigate the white light to the red triangle. Don't cross the lines shown in the maze
These are invisible to the bomb. Okay, you let are you ready? Yeah, you want to go up?
Ops, not an option. What do you mean? No, it's what do you mean on an option?
Are you starting right here? Did you spit out red at me? You can't go up
No, I can't go up. You have to be able to go up. No
Light the light you must navigate the white light to the red triangle. Tell them why the white dot is okay
it's at the bottom at
bottom at
The
Dude, this is fucked. It's like the sixth spot the sixth spot. No, sorry. I'm stressed out. Okay
So alright, we're down all the way at the bottom. You're in the last one. Okay, go you can't go up
No, I can't go up. Are we do we are we correct?
You all the way at the bottom in the sixth spot like a second last one. Oh the second the left
Okay, one, two, three, four five six. So you're second the last
Just second the last spot. Are you okay? Go left
The fuck are you
I'm gonna go right that worked. Hey, we're dead. By the way, I'm cheating. I don't even know where I get this now
I understand this. Are you understand this?
Okay, chat chat chat was that Jerma's fault or my fault
Both
Let me get new modules we got it as you got to figure out what to do. I don't even know what it wanted us to do
All right
It's gonna be fucking Simon says or it's gonna be the fucker
All right, we do not beat the first three levels of this game. I am going to scream. Okay?
Okay. Okay. We got some assess some assess it. Okay some assess and it's gonna be blue
Okay, press red
You motherfucker
All right, okay, okay serial number is
It definitely had it definitely doesn't have about okay, let's go what was it you said it was blue
Press yellow, I just I know what you said it flashed blue. Oh, we have
Now we have two strikes, oh boy press green
Jerma Jerma press green quick so we can move on. Come on, please. We have to be green green
blue blue green green
Okay
Blue blue green. Okay, green green blue green green blue blue blue green blue
Green green blue green green green blue green. Mm-hmm. Yeah, we got it. We got it. Got a keypad keypad
Backward C with two dots. Yep
We got an Omega symbol, I don't know that is
No Omega symbol for real, I don't know that I have no idea that is I've no I know you know
You know, you know, I'm gonna make a simple
No, it's like an old with with thick ultramarines Warhammer. I don't I didn't play I didn't play that game
But I just don't know you did you did what's the next? What's the third? What's the third? What's the third?
So it's like
It's the the the you with the eye in it
I
Didn't I played like the first four hours
I played that wasn't in the God of War game
I don't know what all the video game
Okay, fuck the okay. Listen back was the east first
Okay, Omega Simmons a big all with two like spinies underneath it that goes like a toilet seat toilet seat
Did you leave so I'm here what's the
Okay, you
It's like it's like a trident. All right, try okay, and then an AI
Okay
backwards II
Trident Omega
Okay, good. We got we got a key the red key. We'll say this whole hold it red key on hold
Wouldn't mean like the button. It's a button. Okay. Yeah, it's a red button. Okay. Yeah
This is hold on it. Yeah
How many batteries on the bump there is three there? Okay. No, that's what it's for. Sorry. Okay. Okay
Okay, is there a lit indicator with the label FRK?
It's not late. It's not lit. Press and hold press and hold the button. Hold on and then release the button
Drama if the button is red in the bar
It didn't say I'm gonna eat this fucking paper
What was this was there a strip I checked all the fuck wait wait, there was a switch on the bottom
What do you mean? There's a switch. There's a switch on the bottom. Okay, that was my fault
That was my fault. Was there a switch on the bottom? It's my fault. Whose fault was that?
We can take the blame for that one
Who takes the blame who takes the blame? All right, that was German's fault
This is not level 2 this is level 3 we have to be level 3 do again. Oh good
Okay, okay, you ready? I'm ready. What's the first module? Let's go
The first module is Simon Says
Okay, hang on. Okay. I'm looking at it
Number and what is there a vowel in the serial number serial number says you want the serial number?
No, just is there a vowel insert. Is there a vowel in the serial number? Is W a vowel?
No, no
A E I O U
Okay, what did it happen?
No, it's not fucking vowels. I'm just kidding. Come on. It's green green on green on Simon Says. Come on
I'm okay
Then press green
Green on green green on green
Green is proposed
Green green green green green green green blue
Green green yellow. Okay. We got it. Okay. Keep that keep that time
We got we got a smiley face
Okay. Yep
spider
Uh backwards bp. Okay tb. Okay. You ready backwards p tb spider smiley
Okay, say like slower slower backwards p tb. Yep spider smiley got it
Okay. Now we got a big red button says detonate on it
Is it red? Okay. Hold on
How many batteries are in that bump?
Okay, i'm i'm checking i'm checking we have uh
There is uh, two batteries two batteries and it says detonate. Yes press and immediately release the button
You see jerma if you listen to me that was quick
Okay
If you listen to me
Everything will be fine. It only took an hour and 10 minutes to beat level three if you start screaming at me
You screamed at me first. You screamed at me first. You know, I yelled at me first. Did I yell at jerma?
You've been yelling at me the whole time. I haven't yelled at you. No, I I have not yelled once. I have not yelled at you one time
Look at chat. Look at what chat's saying. I haven't yelled at you once. I have not yelled. They're saying they're saying no joe
You did not scream at jerma. No, I didn't yell once
Jerma, you don't know what an omega symbol is. You're you're invalid to say anything
Anything you say is null and void
How can you not look what listen? I might be a dumb motherfucker. Listen, I might be drinking like toilet water
But at least I know what a fucking omega symbol is. You're american like don't you read it's greek. It's greek and i'm american
but you know
I don't know greek language. So what you fucking live in boston. You guys speak a whole other language
I can't understand what you're saying. I don't know greek what?
I live in fucking america. I live in boston. I don't even live in boston. Listen you you eat like
Oh, don't your pizzas are aren't they baked wrong?
pizzas
Yeah, yeah, isn't like boston pizza like
something wrong with it
No, wait, no, sorry. I'm being i'm being an insensitive asshole. I'm thinking of chicago deep style. Sorry
No, boston pizza is ranked number seven in the world by the way in the world for pizza. Wait, wait, you guys have your own pizza
Boston pizza is ranked at number seven in the world what the most delicious pizza
It's what it's it's uh, it's like thin
Crispy you get fucking pepperoni on it. You can get i'm I don't know. I don't know. It's just so that's how your brain looks, huh?
I can't talk about I can't talk about pizza. I'll have to stop this really
All right. I can't talk about that. It's crispy and thin. Let's get pepperoni. I can't talk about move on
Let's press the next button
I'll leave I will even buy you get a pepperoni pizza right now. I swear to god this happens every fucking stream
All right, what we got? Okay. Uh
We uh finished two levels
Can we finish this third one? Jesus?
The fuck did we not do this?
What do you mean? You gotta stop the string because you talk about pizza
Stop saying that word
why
Stop saying that word because it's I if I if I hear it enough times
I start thinking about a fucking thin crispy crust. How about with tomato crusty slice?
Yeah, that's not doing it for me
Nah
Yeah, you fixed it. Yeah, you fixed it. Stop
All right. What's what's the first module?
What's the first module?
Is this a weakness?
No, no, no, no. Listen, we'll get through this. I mean, i'm just wondering like
Like a tomato blood flesh slice. No, no, it makes you horny
What are you talking about? Oh, i'm just asking like like i'm not
I'll tell you what I I I have a big pee pee problem, right if people say waterfall for me
I get really like in the mood for peeing
So if I say I like the word jizza
You get really horny for pizza
You're on thin ice young man. We're gonna we're gonna do this. We're gonna do this next one. All right
i'm ready
Double your money the task is clear, but the timer doesn't work, but doesn't care about your workload
Wait, the timer doesn't work in this one. No, no, no, it's being descriptive
But I don't think it's quite literally the task is clear, but the timer doesn't care about your workload
So the it there's no timer. Okay, let's try it. Here's what we're gonna do
Let me see what it says
Double your money the task is clear, but the timer doesn't care about your work. Yeah, it's the sick. That's a lot of modules
That's the six modules. That's six modules. This is the first real test jerma. What are you doing?
I'm I let go of the mouse man
Like let go of the mat. What are you doing? I'm not touching anything
What?
Jerma i'm not touching anything jerma what?
I'm not touching anything. I don't worry about it
Six fucking modules six fucking modules
The mouse is right there. All right, six modules. Let's get it done. Let's get it done
Listen, what do you got? This is gonna be the last try. We'll continue this at some point
This is gonna be my last one. All right
He's ready to make this count brain is is on fire
All right. Are you ready?
Yes
First one is our wire module. How many wires?
We've got we've got four we've got blue red two white two white. Okay, uh blue red two white. Yep. Okay
They said there's one blue wire. There's one blue wire first one cut the first wire
Gotcha. Okay. What's what number two? What's it?
It's a bunch of uh keypad modules whatever. Okay. Yep
Okay, we've got a three that's kind of like squiggling off in the distance
It's not quite a three. It's like half a three and then it goes like on a ski ski path. Got it. I got you
we've got a
uh
An at symbol, but it's kind of like wrong
um
Okay, like you understand I think I think so I think so
Okay
Like I think infogrames
Okay, holo star not black one got it and then copyright. Okay copyright
weird at symbol
Weird three and then star
Gotcha. All right. We've got another we've got another uh module
We've got an upside down question mark here. Oh, it's another one. Okay. Yeah. Yep. Yep
Yep, then we've got infogrames again. Okay, we've got a grueling. Oh, yep
And the h with the little uh thing at the bottom. You got it. Okay drooling. Oh
Uh messed up at symbol the weird h and then
Hey upside. Yeah. Yeah, we got it. Okay. Now we got we got uh, we got six wires
Okay, hold on. Wait, wait, wait six wires. Okay, six wires
Okay, two red one yellow two blue one white you said one yellow. Yeah
Uh, and there is only one white wire, right? Yes
Okay
There are no are there any red wires?
There's two red wires at the start. Okay, cut the fourth wire
You sure you sure?
Yes, we got it. What's next? Come on. Keep going
uh
There's nothing spin spin the box around spin. You gotta spin the box around. I think there's this stuff
There could be stuff on the other side. Oh, there's stuff on the fuck. Hang on. Oh god. The game is lagging
That's so laggy. It's so laggy right now. Okay, we got two detonate buttons
Two detonate buttons. Okay. Yes, what what is the what color is the first one?
They are both white. They're both white. Okay. What is what is on the text of the first button?
Detonate. Okay. It says hold on. Okay. How many batteries are on it? Are they more than one battery on the bomb?
uh, there is uh
Three batteries in total on this whole thing. Okay, and that button says detonate. Yes, press and immediately release it. You sure? Yes
Yes, what is the text of the other of the other one detonate? Okay
Do it again press and release it again
Unbelievable unbelievable
It's almost like you said if if i'm just pretending here and I said they will be the last one just to make sure that uh
We do this all night. Anyway, uh
Unbelievable guys, you see
That's what happens when you think jerma. So are you done?
No, no, no, I can go all night. I can go all night
Because I mean I took I took a multivitamin like four hours ago. Just just specifically make sure I took
Multivitamin I took like b complex like vitamin c and
Why why are you taking like drugs on stream man, I took a multivitamin because I want to be trying to focus
Well now you're horny
What are you talking? All right. Do you want do you want to do the reading for a little bit or do you listen?
Listen, it's what I propose. Here's what I propose in order for us to maintain this amount of
Quality, uh, I propose that we do one more
And then i'm gonna do some other stupid shit tonight, but next next saturday
If you guys want to chat would you want us to resume this game?
And next stream would do I do the reading
It's fucking it's it's harder than it looks
What are they what are they saying on your chat? Are they all saying no?
I'm saying yes
Okay. Well, they're saying yes at mine too. So uh
We did that one pretty good too
You know, I gotta say though
Once you stop like taking super mario boner pills, you're pretty good at this
But you keep you keep you you keep doing this to me
You keep doing this to me where you can't read like omega symbols and it's it's
It you're you're being real silly. You're being just don't just don't play. Uh halo is what they said
so
All right, that works
All right. All right. Well, you ready for the next one?
All right, let's do the next one. Let's go
Listen as long as it's not simon says
Simon says it's hard because when you say I could explain it. It's fucking hard. All right, you're right
All right. Here we go. Next one is called one step up
It's for those who I made it this far and want something tougher, but not too tough
Not to which for us means fucking impossible
I can't believe we spent that much time on the second fucking this level is the equivalent of like licking your elbow
Are you face caming right now?
Yeah
Can you can you lick your elbow?
Do it now prove it
Did it you did it?
Yeah
Did you do it?
I don't understand. Why is that hard?
He did it
Okay. Well if you can do that then then uh
Then i'm sure we can do this
Yeah, I did it. I did it both ways just to prove I could do it
You ready?
All right. Let's get it done
All right. First of all, let's go
Here we go
Ultra rack. What what does that mean? All right. You ready? All right. Here we go. Here we go. First one is uh,
We got the fucker. We got the oh my god. We got the
Super fucker. Are we got a three?
It's over it's over it's over it's over then the super fucker. I don't know what that is
We've got four four things. I don't remember when I press got six
What's the number
Three, okay, press the button in the third position
Okay, by the way, what number what did you just press?
What number did you press? That was the number three. Okay. Remember that first position was three. Okay
Two two
Okay, press the button in the same position you pressed a second ago
Okay
That was a four by the way. Okay. Now we got a one
All right, press the button with the same label you pressed in stage two, which was a four if i'm not mistaken
How dare you be so condescending?
Number three
Is it stage three?
This is the third. This is the third time we've done this right there. This is number three, right?
In a row. This is like the third. This is number three like stage three, right?
Uh, this is the fourth one. Okay. What's the number? What's the number?
The number three press the button in the same position. You pressed in stage two, which was a four
Condescending asshole here. I am. All right, I didn't say that I did three
Same label you pressed in stage four, which was a four
Is that your final answer jerma? I don't know. Yeah
Pretty smart. All right. Is it right?
Yeah, okay. Uh
All right. Now we got the uh battleship pac-man thing going on. Okay. So fuck what do you need to know?
All right, where where are these circles?
circles us at the uh
second position top and bottom
What?
Okay, give me like six across row. What like two across row? What you don't even okay?
So in total you got you got six dots on each right? Yeah, six and six, right?
Yes, so the top one the the circle is at the the top at the second one
Oh, okay
I think I got it and is the one directly below that on the last line like is it matching directly below it?
like
Yeah at the bottom. Yes, sir. Okay, so you have to take the white light
Yes, and you have to get to the red triangle
Right. Okay. Do not cross these lines. I'm about okay
Where is the red triangle?
The red triangle is at the second row at the first position second row first. Okay. Are you ready that top position?
The top one go left and then down. That's it
That did not work. What do you mean? Okay. People are saying where's the light?
Do you need a light? Yeah
Yeah, I said you must navigate the white light to the red triangle fifth top are we talking about the same thing?
Yeah, okay. All right. Listen. Listen. Listen. Listen down
Down down up left up left left left
Oh, I fucked you up. I fucked you up. Hey, go ahead. Just run run to the wall. I fucked you up
No, no, no, I'm gonna do this. No, no, we can't we can't trust me
We can't we can't get into the wall. What's the point of the two circles? I don't understand
All right, no, no, just run into a wall run into a walk. Seriously. Yeah
Uh, where is the red triangle again? I don't know. I solved it. I solved it anyway
Fuck it. Whatever. Let's do the keypad keypad. We got we got a butt. We got a giant ass
Giant ass. I don't see an ass
Giant giant badonkadonk. Okay. Okay. Okay. I gotta see the giant ass. All right test these test these. Okay, holo star
Yep
We got a we got a three that will squeak us off. Yep
Got it. What's what's the what's the last one?
Half-life, okay got it. So uh big ass three squiggly half-life start
Okay, okay last one I want a keypad that says abort blue
Okay, it's it's a blue button and it says abort on it. Okay. Yes hold the button down
Okay, what happened?
Uh, it's showing a blue one. Okay blue line release when the countdown timer has a four in any position
Okay, we got it. We got it. We're getting better at this. We're going better. We got it
We're getting better at this shit
We got this man. Yeah, we're getting much better at this shit
For gamers
Let's do a high five. Okay, you ready?
Yeah
Yeah, it's because we're from across the world. So the latency the sound latency was bad. Yeah, dude
The lag is really messing up. Uh, or uh
Cerebral power together, you know
All right. So are you are you you are you done for today with this? Okay, tell what?
Let's do one more because we're on a roll here. We really tapped into our potential here, you know
All right, then I i'm gonna move on to something else. So what am I gonna what am I gonna play?
I'm gonna go how about how about this? How about how about how about this? You look up basic greek for idiots
All right, you ready to do this last one? All right
What do you got here? No, i'm not gonna play jump king. No way
What jump king?
Oh, wait, you're supposed to play that and like beat it weren't you?
What you were supposed to play that and beat it you didn't beat it though. I'll beat your ass
Okay
Pick up pick your nose whatever this is
All right
Okay, reading this only uses up time. So you don't have chop chop. All right, you ready?
Yeah, guys, do you think germa scared on me?
All right. Anyway, uh, oh fuck we're not at the end of time. Okay
Okay, we have a whole new module right now. We have a whole new model right now. What's it look like?
It's saying six things saying no middle, uh, nothing blank ready first first word is no
Okay using the label from step one push the first button that appears in its course. Okay, you said the first one was no
Yes, okay
um
What hit blank?
I don't know that didn't work here using the label from step one push the first button that appears in its corresponding list
German, what are you doing? I don't oh, oh, oh, okay. Okay
So wait, there there's like okay
Read the display english i'm trying to do it's the new module just speak english. I can't understand you brian
Bring them out bostonian bring them out
all right, so
Read the display and use step one to determine what buttons label to read
Using this button label. Fuck me. Okay based on the display read the label of the word
No, we'll see about that. All right, you said no, right? Okay. Can you click like in the bottom right corner?
Yes
Greg, you're fucking you fucked me. You fucked me. You said it was no, right?
No, no, you said bottom right? No, no, no, but but but the word was no, right? The word is no
uh
German you're about to witness. I don't understand how gamers do it. Watch this
I don't know what wants to do. I'm trying to figure out what it wants us to do
What did you just did you just throw the bomb on the ground and step on it?
Listen, I I just took a chance. I took a chance and I pressed something random
Sometimes that shit works, you know, it's a leap of faith text text text text
Read the display. I can have to look at that
I have to look at that
Okay. Um, tell you what this shit is. This is the first time we've ever seen in this module. Is it a new module?
All right. What do you want? What's that?
What's up?
Yeah, what you said tell you what this guy
He said fuck you talking at you said tell you talking at
You're gonna fight
You want to kiss?
Kiss my gut
You why is it so impossible to do anything with you? Why do you have to be so difficult always?
Look at my we're all here rooting for you. We're all here rooting for you. I want you to look at me
I'll believe in you. Jeremiah. Why do you have to do this every time?
I want you to look at my screen. I open up my stream. Look
Look at this. This is what I had to work with
You want me to go over to your stream
You can look over can't you?
I don't know. Do I want to like
Put myself down there. It's I don't even I what what was on your screen?
Okay, hang on
Joel you are so argumentative. I'm not argumentative. I i'm being fair
I don't think he's being very fair
Okay. Okay. Okay. Okay. You want me to look at what you've prepared in the printout or whatever? No, just look see
That's like you said the word was no
There's no so then there's this eyeball in the bottom right and I figured you had to press that
Okay, hang on. Hang on. Hang on. We got this we got
Don't stop fucking screaming at me. Oh, wait a minute
uh
I don't understand
the list but
No, but what the fuck does this even mean?
Jeremy you got really tiny hands
My hands are fucking actually huge like i'm sorry. Did you have the tiniest hands i've ever seen i've got like monster hands
You're looking right now
These things are fucking monstrous
Look at this shit
Yeah, but
Maybe there's kind of like normal sized and you know, the rest of you kind of you know
That was uh, that was joel that was playing. Uh, keep talking. I know what he exposed the joel. I have been apparently
He's gotta go. He's got something else going on today
So he's got something else to do
Uh, it was good playing with him
uh, it was
uh, it was uh
It was something and I look forward to the next time. Uh, we are trying to diffuse blow. Listen, we're gonna beat this game together
I don't matter no matter how no matter no matter how tough this is gonna get
So the power of of the mind
and with patience
I I thought we could get it done
We are getting it done. I'm just saying next time you're gonna realize when I read these instructions
that's
When you understand I feel like if I had the bomb in my hand and we flipped it around
It would be sad. I could probably get it
You could probably feed the info better and I could do the actual clicking and moving around better
We did it wrong. We should have been the other way
All right. All right. Well, we'll check back, uh next week
Saturday
And then uh, yeah, whatever you do for the rest of your stream. Have a good stream
All right. Well, uh, well i'll tell you what
Uh, uh, let's uh, I was I was talking I was talking to jerma about this before we started streaming. Uh, I was talking about the uh,
Keyfabe you guys know what keyfabe is in chat. What the fuck were you talking about?
keyfabe
Uh, do you know what that is? No, it's like it's like the terms are wrestlers use
kefabi kefabi kefabi mama de prosciutto listen, uh,
It's a term wrestlers use to like not break character and i'm gonna break characters
like mute the fucking stream or uh unmute it because uh,
it's been so terrible listen beside the point listen i'm saying that
German I
Uh, if you think if you think that we're we're we're we hate each other. Don't worry about it. We do does it beside the point?
Uh, it was really fun coming on the stream. Uh,
Listen, um
Uh
It was fun. It was a lot of fun. I know I I look forward to uh,
To more streams and uh, hopefully this stream was just a little bit better than halo reach. Uh, just a little like no
This was a thousand times better than halo reach like without a doubt in my mind
Yeah, but still still the worst of 2020 though, but no it was not. No it wasn't
No, what could someone be like through i've only streamed like three times in 2020. No twice this is the second time. Oh shit
Well, i'll tell you what i'll tell you what incompatible friends
What incompatible friends somebody just said
Uh, all right
All right. Well, thanks for having me man, and uh, I look forward to uh, uh the next time we uh, we uh,
you know, uh
Work it out. Yeah, that'd be fun
All right. Well, uh, i'll see you later and i'll uh, i'll see your tiny little baby hands
I just left
All right. He said hand. I thought he was going somewhere else. That's why it is immediately left
All right, let's uh, let's move on and do something else
We'll do that again
And this time we will reverse the roles next time
Uh, i'm gonna be right back
Oh now I can click on that. I I have my monitors all set up wrong. Give me like a few minutes
I uh, i'm gonna switch over to something else. Have a great day