Hey, pay no attention to all the drop frames right now. Don't worry about that. It's because
I had to re-download all of the DLC again. Remember I came in here and I was like,
hey no, it looks like that wasn't the problem. I was too embarrassed to come back and tell you
that that's what was happening. So I had to re-download the DLC. And I was like,
no, it's all good. I didn't have to do that. I restarted Steam and the download started again.
So we have about two minutes before I can open Hitman 2. I was like, should I come in there?
Are people going to laugh at me when I tell them this? Probably. Why am I using so much CPU right
now? Hitman's not even open. Why am I dropping so many? What? Hold on. What's going on with my
computer? I'm at 50% CPU. I'm not doing anything. Hold on a second. Oh, this is not... Watch me
burn out my CPU. No, and now I'm going to have Hitman open when I'm already at 50%.
Is it... Am I installing a Windows update? Oh, it's because it's installing Hitman. That takes CPU?
No, it doesn't. That uses HDD. That uses hard disk drive. That doesn't use that much CPU, does it?
HDD in 2019. You think I got any moving parts in this thing? I got all SD. That's how you know
that was a funny lie. HDD. But I'll give you... I'm going to refill this. I'm going to get some
good stalling content here. You know, I got to refill this water. So, you know, let me just stall
for like another 45 seconds. All right. I've got to tweet it too. Didn't tweet. We're going to do
the Hitman 2 DLC. No, no. Wait, wait, wait. Let's talk for a minute before I go do that.
So today is the day before TwitchCon. And some might say that TwitchCon actually starts today.
So this is the last stream you're going to see from me until I am back from TwitchCon. A lot
of moving around here the last week, the last two weeks of September. So this stream is only going
to be a few hours long. We're going to do the Hitman 2 DLC campaigns. I have not done the last
one. So we'll see how long that takes. After that, I got to go. There's still a few things
that I have to take care of before getting on another plane and leaving for four days.
Technically three, right? Whatever it is. But give me one second. I'm going to fill this drink up
and then we'll play Hitman 2. Be right back. And I'm going to tweet that. See you in a minute.
Yeah, yes, I've seen the new Twitch. I made this reference earlier, but I'm going to make it again.
It is the World of Warcraft chat. Especially when you go into all caps. I don't know what
the wow chat is. Whatever. I'm of the opinion. Why on earth would you ever under any circumstance?
And I'm not talking about Twitch. I'm just saying ever in general. Why are there so many fonts?
12 to 14 point Helvetica is the only thing there should be. Why would there ever be another font?
Do we need 16, 17, 1800? How many fonts are there? 1800? How many fonts exist?
It's probably thousands of them. What's the point? There are millions of fonts. Why is it?
There are only three fonts that should exist. Reading things clearly. Birthday card.
You can be fun with that one. Birthday card. That's it. I can't think of another reason to
ever have another font. There's no other reason for other fonts besides those two.
Alright, rip Times New Roman. No, that one doesn't even have to exist either.
This should not be more fonts than there are serial brands. Something about that is not correct.
They can't even figure out how to make cornflakes fucking 500 times. They've only made it like 30
times. How can you? How do you make the letter H look six million times different than the last
time you made it? You can't. It's just three lines. It's one, two, three lines. Anyways,
before I get all worked up, I'm going to play Hitman now. I have the audio muted so you
shouldn't be able to hear it. It shouldn't hurt your ears. Make my own font. It would just be,
it would be just a few lines. Wait, you shouldn't be able to hear this.
Hold on, not yet. Hold on. Not yet. Now I have to do this fun thing where, oh god, where's my mouse?
Why is the window staying open? Close that, please. Don't turn off my computer. Okay, we'll go
starting, starting strong here. Okay, here we go. Get that off. Just give me one moment. Nice
transition there. I have to get this captured. Let's get it. Do not capture Goose Game. I want
Hitman 2 done. There we are. You thought it was going to take me longer. It may have.
All right, I got the DLC installed. Hopefully it works. Otherwise, I'm going to be very sad.
Stop sweating and turn on face cam. Though, cut my nails though. I did do that. Those of you that
were yelling at me last night at the end of that stream, I appreciate it. So this two DLC
campaigns, those two missions that I haven't done, right? Campaign, Hitman 2. I did all these
already. So golden handshake and the last resort. All right. Remember to shave? Already did. You
don't think I was already on top of that? I had to shave to the minute that the Twitch party is
going to start on Saturday. I shaved at exactly 7 30 p.m. last night. That's a lie because I was
still live. When did the stream end? Like 8 30 p.m. Pacific? That's when the Twitch party starts.
It's going to grow out. When I'm in like the Uber to get there, it is going to be perfectly
grown out. The last second when I step out of that cab, perfectly grown. So this one is brand new.
This one is not. This one is probably like a few months old. By the way, those of you that are
going to laugh at me for this, I have not played Hitman since the last time I streamed it. I don't
even remember how to play. So that's going to be a thing. Bad, bad. I haven't played it in like a
year. I forget what happened. This is a whole game here.
Yeah, I'll turn the volume up in a second.
I have to pay attention to this, though.
That's Troy Baker. That's Troy Baker, right?
You can always tell when it's Troy Baker because he elongates words.
I'm not nearly as talented as Troy Baker. I'm just telling you.
All right, let's go.
You don't need to tell us. I'm just telling you.
I'm going to pay. Look, I got to pay attention. I can go through the basement, right?
Right. So I've got to get three flash drives.
And then they combine. I'm going into the basement.
Okay, give it to me clear. Break into the vault, get the hard drive rack, and get rid of the director.
Okay, break into the hard drive, steal the bank, break into the... All right, break the director,
steal the bank, eliminate Athena Savalas. Mission is now active. How do you swing?
I think it's a Q. Sound is too low. I got it. I got it. I got it. Hold on.
QRS. Okay, objective. Target Athena Savalas, retrieve the data, and exit the bank.
I got to get the data. Difficulty professional. That has to change. Wait, no,
that's what I played on before, right? Okay, I'm going to be the New Yorker.
Don't I have any DLC suits? Why is this taking so long? Should I just go for... All right,
I'm going to go into the winter sports suit, I think. I won't look out of place at all.
Okay, coin. That's good. My concealed weapon is my ICA-19. That looks all right. Starting location
bank entrance. I think I'm ready to go. Pray for my CPU, because the last time I played this game,
it was all fucked up. Difficulty master. No, wait, wait, wait, wait.
Professional. Okay, here we go. And I'm going to turn it up a little bit louder.
That should do it. Hey, now you can hear. Let's go. I forget. What's the plan?
Welcome to New York, 47. I'll get it again. Milton Fitzpatrick Bank is open for business,
but it seems there's some sort of investigation underway. Expect increased security.
Your target, Director Athena Savalas, can be found in her top floor office,
overlooking the iconic... Stop chugging. What are you talking about?
Head of security, Mateo Perez, is roaming between the vault area and the teller hall.
What are you talking about? What? And head of accounts, Fabian Mann,
can be found on the investment banker floor... What, am I dropping a shitload of frames?
...driving the internal investigation. That shouldn't be happening.
Remember, we need to secure the data from the bank's reinforced vault.
This is a lie. Or, alternatively, acquire three hard drives...
I'm supposed to pay attention to this. ...and two lieutenants, Mann and Perez.
Now I lost everything. Good luck, 47.
Hold on. Are you guys actually fucking with me? Oh no. Oh no. You weren't. Were you?
I have to keep this out. They didn't see this. Oh shit. All right. God damn it.
Why does my computer have to suck so bad? All right. What do I... Let me save it.
Manual save slot. How about... None of these matter. This one right here.
Okay. Eliminate Athena Savalas and obtain the data. You got it. I need to... I don't remember how to
play. That's Q. Retrieve vault data core. Three of them. Okay.
Those of you that are wondering why I did this, I'm making sure my CPU can handle it.
Okay. I can handle it. Maybe... No, it can't. It can't handle it? It wasn't silky smooth?
Wait. That wasn't silky smooth? What? God damn it. No! I have to...
Hold on. Hold on a second. I might have to restart the stream.
Can I do that during the stream? Hold on a minute. Shit. Shit. Shit. Shit. Shit. Damn it. No.
It's because... I have to restart the stream. All right. I'll be right... I'll be right back.
It's because when I... Last time I played a console game, I turned my CPU preset down and shit. I'll
be right back. Like in 10 seconds. All right. We're good. We're good, right? I think we're good.
Hey. How's everybody doing? Did it work? Confirm with me that this worked. Yes, it did it. Yeah.
I have my CPU preset so fucking high. So low, I mean. All right. Okay. Hopefully not a thousand
of you left. You probably did. But now we're silky smooth. We should be. I left. All right.
Hold on. I got to do this too. Like, I'm sorry guys, but like this is... My computer sucks.
It really shouldn't suck this much. Do I have to take tech... All right. I'm going to take this
down to two. I just got this computer. I got a 1080 in here. That's not good anymore, is it?
Shit. That's not good anymore. That's like not good at all anymore. I have a 4770K. That's good,
right? No, I don't. What do I have? Somebody do hash... Somebody turn on exclamation point.
Whatever the... Hold on. The 60... I know what it is. Quiet!
I'm sorry. Why is this stuttering so much? Have a good day. Okay. Hold on a minute here. Ruby Red,
famous month-breaking investigative journalist, is in the bank. Known for her fierce skills at
digging up dirt and her excellent nose for scandal. She's definitely up to something.
She's up to something. Might be worth following her around the bank, 47. Okay. Let's see where she
goes. Investigate Ruby Red. All right. Why is that happening now? Teddy, it's me. I'm at the bank now.
This game fucking hates my computer. Somebody called it too. Don't you dare dump this story,
Ted. I will find that report. Oh, she's listening. I'm sorry. I'm not interrupting your phone call.
I'm testing my stream settings. Don't you dare dump this story, Ted. I'm the story of the year.
Director Ceballos has been at extreme recklessness and the public deserve to know that. My informant
will come through. Just make sure... I look like such a fucking idiot right now.
I'm doing v-sync. That's right.
Okay. Stocks are gonna plummet. They actually fixed everything.
I'm so out of place. All right. Email the documents. Investigate. I gotta investigate
the whistleblower. Wait, was that the person she was on the phone with?
Why were you talking on the phone? I can't get in there. All right. Hold on. I gotta get a suit.
Yeah, I can't let you pass. I'm sorry, sir. All right. Let me...
All right. You got a good cop, bad cop routine going. Appreciate it. Wait, I don't want to get on
camera. All right. Let me see the map. We got a bathroom. Lost and found. All right. Let me...
I don't know what to do with the bat. I don't know what to do. I need a new... I can't be a guy in...
I got the corner of my foot touched that. What? Oh, because I picked this up. I picked up...
How do I put it down? I didn't do that. I had nothing to do with that.
Look, it's obviously a wet floor. I didn't kill anybody. How do I put this down?
Hold on. Wait. I can go over here now. This is the security check. I just got it.
Let's go. Wait. Do I have the door lock on? Unlocker. All right. There's another cop up there,
though. I got to get the janitor. I got to find somebody. Somebody over there. Where am I? Okay.
Why do I care more about this in the game? Wait. How do I get to my...
How do I get to my... I don't know how to get to my inventory. How do I get to the inventory?
What the fuck was that? Did somebody puke? Who just puked? There's a Q. It's not Q. You want me
to punch somebody. Which mouse button is it? E. Space. Middle mouse. No, that's gun. R. S.
I. No, but how do I get the fast one? Tab? V. It's not V. Scroll wheel. It's not scroll wheel.
Hold on. Mouse and keyboard. Key bindings. Interact. Agility actions. Pick up. Use items G.
Aim. Shoot. Reload. Instinct. Camera. Shoulder. Crouch. Holster. Precision aim. Zoom in. Zoom out.
Holster. Inventory. I. Isn't there a spinner? Font change. Am I thinking of a different hitman?
Okay. So, all right. That's a different hitman. All right. I need to go investigate. I need a
different clothes. How long does it take for a janitor to come in here? You? Thank you. No.
It's I too. All right. Just investigating distraction. Who is? I forgot. How stupid this
game is. Okay. I need to investigate the whistle. I need somebody's outfit. Can I put my back against
the wall and do like the knock knock solid snake thing? All right. Hold on. Wait. I got an idea.
Somebody just get the fuck in here. See? I told you. Janitor. Janitor. Janitor. Janitor. Janitor.
Good to go. Damn. Janitor. Okay. Fresh disguise. What else you got? Coin. Come here. Can I fit
two people in here? Yeah. We got a raid? Tyler Vic Vicker. Thanks for the raid. Welcome guys.
Playing Hitman. DLC. I'm trying to relearn how to play the game because I don't know how to play it.
I do this thing where I don't ever put me on a bicycle because you know like oh once you
learn how to ride a bike you'll know how to do it forever. No, I won't. If I got on a bike right
now I learned how to ride a bike when I was like 10. If I got on a bike right now I would fall over.
All right. So I'm good. I'm the janitor. So now I have to end. What's going on?
Why is it illegal for the janitor to be up here? God damn it. Why is it? What's wrong with this guy?
Why does he hate me so much? All right. Wait. There's something else going on.
What's this story?
Nerves maybe? Oh wait. Hold on. So the job interview.
Final applicant was seen going into the bathroom. Yeah. Okay. Where is it?
Thanks. I want to do that instead. Wait. Can I blend in with a mop? What's this thing?
There's earphones on this desk. Save. Save it. Save it right here. Manual save. Hey stop this
ridiculous behavior at once. I'm sorry. I just want the earphones. I got them. Free earphones.
All right. Let's go back to the guy that's thrown up here.
Where is this? Wait. He was in here? Oh I have to. The door is locked. Oh I get it. Okay.
How do I knock on the door? Is he going to come out? I got to be ready for him when he comes out.
When he comes out. Should I? Is this the exit? How do I get in there?
Oh this is still flooding. Is there a way to? Wait.
I need to get in this bathroom. Oh this is bad. I don't want to do that.
I'm fucking ruining this bathroom. Is anybody in here? Knock knock.
I need to unlock this door. Doesn't the janitor have every single key?
I thought that was the thing. Shoot him through the door and then I would never get in.
No. I need a I need a key. Like a security. I need a security key. I'm kind of just collecting
stuff. All right. Wait. Hold on. Soda can. Nice. Okay. This is not Skyrim. I don't know why I'm
picking up all this useless shit. Could I take this guy's coffee when he puts it down?
I'm waiting. All right. I need that guy right there. I need a new outfit. I have to get in that
room. Can I open the door with the crowbar? I'll try it. Don't you dare.
I have too much stuff. I got to disguise as the applicant. Does he have a key card?
I'm gonna get um. Is there enough room in here? Put his face in the toilet. You guys are fucked
up. Look at the toilet. T.O.S. I'm just gonna turn this off. I don't need it anymore.
All right. I now approach the reception. I'm the applicant for the work for the job.
That's the target up there. I'm like to the interview. Feeling better I hope.
Should I let HR know you're ready for the final interview? Yes. I feel like a new man. I'm ready.
Wonderful. Follow me please. It's right down here. Best of luck in your interview 47.
I thought that was her. All right. Follow you. I hate when they do this shit in MMOs.
I don't want to walk faster than the NPC. I want to walk with the NPC.
Like why is there no match speed? This is the interview.
I bring my lucky wrench to interviews apparently. Mr. Thomas. Okay. Let's sit down.
Cool.
I'm sorry. I'm sorry. Can we do the interview still?
Did I get the job? Did I get the job? Oh shit. Okay. Oh my god.
I'm just doing my job. That's all. How is somebody not figuring this out?
Wait. Let's go. Like you'll ever get me. These games are fucking so funny.
Best of luck in your interview 47. Let's see where this will lead you to.
All right. I'm going to get stuck here I think. I don't want to get seen by the camera.
Shh. God damn it. I got seen. Press alt. Why? Alt?
Okay. I'm ready for the interview.
Oh.
Personality test.
Kick this off. Okay. I'm ready. Okay. So this is a very simple test.
All you do is pick a card and tell us what you see there.
Now it's important to point out that there are no right or wrong answers.
Clearly me. It's just to give us a better impression of who you are on a psychological level.
Does that make sense? Why would they be doing this?
All right. Mr. Thomas. Did you see my resume? If you will please pick the card.
I want the brown university. God damn it. Opportunity. Opportunity.
Now here's the fucking 500 IQ play. You know, the Forbes magazine over there.
They're going to be like, wait a minute. That wasn't part of the plan.
Oh, I understand. He went completely out of the box. Opportunity. I don't know. This one.
No, this one. This one. All right. Now look at it closely. Take a few moments.
Then tell me, do you see an animal or an object? It's clearly a bird. I see. What kind of animal? An eagle bird.
An eagle perhaps. Eagle. Very interesting. A forceful animal. Anything else? It's
feeding on something. Feeding on what? A carcass. The scene is reflected in a pool of blood
flowing from the body. Okay. It's a vulture feeding on someone else's kill.
This is for a bank clerk job? Mr. Thomas. Yes. Brutal even. Right. Very interesting observation,
Mr. Thomas. Not what we expected, but that's perfectly fine. Let's take the next one, shall
we? The next one. Pick any of the remaining cards that make you think of execution, please.
I mean, it obviously is going to be the one with the Hitman 47 with his two pistols,
but this could also be one. I'm not going to go for the easy one.
Oh, very good. This is an interesting one. What do you see here? Take in the whole image, please.
And in as much detail as possible. It's a river. It's a river with rocks all around it. Or it's
a stone head. I see a big pile of money earned performing questionable actions.
And how do you feel about that? I'm trying to just completely bomb this interview.
Very good, Mr. Thomas. Well, that's a very creative interpretation, Mr. Thomas.
I think we've just got time for the last card. Please proceed.
This last card should hopefully make you think of prosperity.
So my experience in the banking world, I was a teller at Bank of America for four years.
I've handled money for a lot. You don't care about that?
Whenever you're ready. Okay, sure. I'll pick the card. I'll pick this one.
Good choice. Tell me, what is the first thing you've seen?
I've also been I've handled gold before and figure in a large coat. Perspective skewed
as if I'm looking at him from the ground. He's got something in his hands. I go on. He's on
dual firearms, large caliber pistols. I see. What else do you see? He's just finished a job
perfectly executed. And who is this man? It's me. Very, very interesting, Mr. Thomas.
Well, that was certainly unexpected. I think the results are pretty clear. Did I get it?
We don't have the perfect match for the investment banker position. However, you're just the man we
need for our accounting department. I have to agree with Kevin here. We need someone a little
more cutthroat for the top tier here. This is when they lean in and wink. It's really dive into
character as it were. But on a positive note, I want you to wink wink. I want you to beat the
shit out of people I don't like. Great point, Melissa. There's no need to turn this little
setback into a complete failure. Someone with your particular set of skills would be perfect.
I'll take it. When do I start? Well, aren't you an eager beaver?
Well, we expect you to come in tomorrow at eight. Welcome on board, Mr. Thomas.
Oh, I got it. Oh, I did it all correct. I didn't even mean to. I did it. Now what? They're both
just leaving their office? Okay, bye. Time to rifle through your desk. Okay, cool. Close this
shit. Turn the lights off too. Let's make it atmospheric. No, close. Okay, quickly. What do
I got? Coffee. We got something in your desk. Your computer. Hack his computer. Take his pen.
What should I do here? What should I do? It's a bust of his head, I think. Okay.
Nothing else. Well, I got the job. What are you talking about? I got the job.
Restart. What? I got the... Didn't I get the job? They gave me the wrong job. That's a win, man.
It was me. It was me.
Wait, hold on. Are they... I thought they were going to...
All right, so I did it wrong? That's too... That's too... I saved over it. No? Okay, right here.
There's an auto save that saved me. Tell me what this reminds you of.
Okay. No, wait. I can't... I screwed it up, guys. I saved over. I thought I got the job. I thought
I got a job. I thought I got a job. I didn't get the job. I got a job. Go further back? But then I
look at how far back this is. I'm gonna get distracted. All right, I'll try. I'll try. I'm
gonna try it. I'm gonna go very... I'm gonna go very, very fast. Oh, god. I need another... Okay,
I need the bathroom. I need crowbar. I need bathroom. I don't even... I don't remember... I
don't remember how I got in there. I gotta watch out, though. All right. Well, let's go down here.
Make the guy fall again. I can't just relive the whole thing. What is this? No. I'm too stressed.
I'm not stressed. What are you talking about? These guys have guns. I'm getting inside my own...
Where's the bathroom here? All right. This guy right here. Bathroom. You're not allowed to go
in there, right? You're allowed to go... Is this like public space? No. Okay. What? It's a zoo?
All right. This way. I need to find the... There we go. Wet floor sign. This is the part I remember.
It's gonna happen. Here it comes. She absorbed all the water. She absorbed the water.
She must be so... She's just like... She's soaking.
Not why they're looking for me. I told you this wasn't gonna work.
Create a water leak. All right. What about over here?
There's the janitor. Money out of the ATM? Hold on. Is this like free money?
Why is it a slot machine? You just gotta know what you're doing. That's all.
Yes. That guy said yes. It is a slot machine. Okay. Here we go. What's up? Shit. Get out of here.
It's in the house. Come on. I need this guy's costume.
If she's here, we are all in big trouble. You sink? I mean... No. No. You.
I peeked out. That was me. All right. Janitor key. Holy shit. I got the janitor key.
All right. I'm good. That guy left. Have a great day.
Okay. I need to save the game here. No. Didn't wash hands. Okay. So now
I'm going up here. That guy can see. Can I walk into this? I have the janitor key. This is fine.
No, it's not. I'm not allowed in there. I'm a security guard. Why would I not be allowed
over there? All right. Hold on. There's like a wardrobe this way. I'm going a completely
different way than I went last time. All right. Hold on. What is that? I want that. Whatever it
is. Give it to me. Propane flask. I don't want this actually. No. I have to put this down.
I just showed it to him. I just showed it to him.
All right. I have to reload.
That activates it? Wait. What? I forgot how much fun this game was.
All right. Let's go. I got to go this way. Up the stairs. Just avoid the random police
officers that are going to be staring at me. Just run by. Made it. Kind of. What's with this cube?
Hold on. What's the cube? I need to know what's in the cube. What? Okay. All right. I'm not going
to fail the interview this time. Wait. This is something new. Wait. This is the whistleblower.
I hit a bit of an obstacle here. No. Nobody's discovered anything, but for some reason,
the security is super high. So that's why he's fired? I don't think I can get to the documents
safely. There's some sort of investigation going on. We kind of want to be left alone.
Okay. Fine. Do you mind? Fine. He's discovered anything, but for some reason, the security is
super high today. I don't think I can get to the documents safely. There's some sort of investigation
going on, and they're specifically looking for the file. I hit the file in a safety deposit box in
the basement. Keys were on the desk. This whistleblowing thing sounds great on paper,
but I am telling you, it's pretty damn terrifying. Let me save it here. Locate the deposit box key.
All right. Where is that? That way. All right. Can I scan my ass? I'm sorry. Don't mind me.
Do you have anything on you? Nothing? Apple. All right. I got to go to... Wait. Rat poison. Get it.
All right. Locate the safety deposit box key, which is this way. I'm not allowed in there though.
Hmm. That's the head of security here. Mateo Perez. Who? He'll be holding one of the three
backup data disks. Who? This guy right here? This person right here? That's the only person
that's here. That's the first backup data disk secured. Two more to locate. Shit.
Somebody has to come help. I have to make my escape. My fingerprints are all over that, right?
Yeah. Look at it. I don't even wear gloves. My fingerprints are... Oh, no. I don't even
not have fingerprints. Nobody comes over here, right? Okay. I'm good. Let's go. Can I get the
knife? Oh, that's disgusting. Okay. Give me the apple. I was never here. Wait. Can I dress as
this person? Nope. Okay. Hold on. I got the safety deposit box key. I got to go
up here. I'm freaking out. Okay. Save the game in a different spot. Okay. Wait. I have bloody
footprints? No, I don't. Who is looking at me? What is this? Turn on frosted glass?
Oh, nice. This is a little safe area. All right. I gotta keep that. I gotta remind myself to come
in here. So, I gotta get in there and get the key. I'm allowed in here. There's only one person's
person at the desk over there. I can get it. Shit. Is anybody else in here? No. Don't poison the
water bottle. What am I doing? Okay. The key is... Where is it? Nothing. All right. Looking for the
desk. Looking for the key. Wait. Is it in there? It's not one of these desks. Got it. Holding
ear pods. I'm gonna save it here. No. A new one. Can I take a bite out of this? All right. Time to
go to the... I gotta go down to the basement. Now, how am I gonna get down to the basement?
I have to go all the way down here, I think. But will these guys try to stop me? No one's found
this yet. That's good. I gotta get down here. These guys will let me through, right? Good afternoon,
sir. All right. It's in there. This is the vault, 47. The data core should be behind that large
steel door. Looking for the data core. All right. Incriminating evidence. Well, at least it's not as
bad as that time in Queens. Remember that? The 6,000 semi-incinerated files we had to tape together?
Don't remind me. I'm just saying, maybe this isn't so terrible after all. There are always worse
cases out there. I guess I mostly... Got it. ...to staff or ask around if people have seen a folder
full of secrets. We could be here weeks and not find anything. Any money in here? You don't have
to love it. Yeah, I guess you're right. Oh, shit. There is money. There's a money key. All right. I
got the money key. Now I have to fuck with this guy for a minute. He was gonna call something in,
but he just got embarrassed. I think he thought he fell off the chair. Hey, this is... Oh, wait a
minute. I was just sleeping. Never mind. Everything's fine. Right before he dozes off. All right. He's
just dozed off. There it is. You know when you're right about to fall asleep, you get ripped out of
it. He's gonna go back to bed in front of these guys.
How could you go back to sleep? Ready? He hit his head pretty hard. I got plenty of shit to throw at
you. Wait, I think the net... No. Whatevs. If his mouth opens, can I get it right in his mouth?
Ah, there we go. Now he wants to investigate. What did he just take? Ready? One, two, three.
Aha. Okay. This is where we end up. There's some kind of fracas down here. I'm having a look around.
This is gonna be so horrible. Hey. Right when he goes to bed. Oh. He's up. Let's put him up.
Okay. Hold on. Will he remember this? I'm trying to sit him back in the chair. This is not even
that bad. Everybody knows this guy sleeps on the job anyways. All right. I need to pick up all the
things I threw. Okay. That's everything I had, right? Unconscious witness. I'm gonna be an
unconscious witness. Wait. He saw my face. I can't, like, dump rat poison down his throat.
All right. That's fucked up. I can't. I just said that out loud. All right. He'll be fine.
I was trying to, like, plant the ear pods on him. All right. Whatever. He'll be up for a while.
I gotta go to Ruby Red. How has nobody found you yet? Reload. Oh, that's right. I did. I saved it
right before I did all that. You're right. The blood has been cleaned up. All right. Let's go.
Should I be actually working with Ruby Red? I'm gonna get double crossed here. That's what
happens in these games. Now the blood is there this time. All right. I got files. What are you?
What's in it for me? How are you? Hmm. It is.
Sounds like Miss Red has quite a scoop on her hands. Yeah. My guess is this will cause a major
market upset. No, no, no. No photos of me. All right. We need the other data disks. Got it.
Data disk objective is there's one down here. There's a data core. All right. Let me go down
here. What was the other thing that I had? I had some more intel. No, it was objectives.
No, it was intel, wasn't it? I already got this one. The whistleblower got that one.
Okay. I got, I need one more. There's another one down this way. Let's go here.
I need to get the job. All right. I'll get the job. Where's the guy that's puking?
Insider trading. What? Oh, God. No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
No, drop, drop, drop, drop down, drop down, drop down. How do I drop down? How do I drop?
How do you drop down? I can't just let go. Stock is crashing. Wait, what? Where? I need to,
where's the stock? Where are the stocks crashing? Where's the puke? Where's the guy that's throwing
up in the bathroom? I don't see him anywhere. Wasn't he supposed to be in here? Oh, the other
side. Oh, fuck. Second floor. Right. Oh, God damn it. The guy with the machine gun. All right. All
right. I'm surrendering. I'm surrendering. You gotta be kidding. Just a little bit closer.
What? It's not, it's not a wet floor. Somebody. All right. Well, what was it over here? Second
floor in the second bathroom. Kind of, I gotta be a gamer. I can handle it. Don't worry. I can
handle it. I didn't save after this, but it's all right. I'm just going to run up there.
Straight, left, right, up, skip. Don't step in the blood and get it all over me.
There you go. I got something for you. Is that, is that what I think it is? Uh-huh. Yes.
Just make sure the information will be put to good use. Oh, you can bank on that for you. What's
your role in this? I'm not important. Good luck. It sounds like Miss Red has quite a scoop on her
hands. My guess is this will cause a major market upset, which is sure to bring the director out
from her fortified office. Oh, it's as if she comes out. All right. Here we go.
Going through bathroom time. Look if a guy in the bathroom.
Save game. Go get, go play the stock market before everything crashes. All right. So then where was
the bathroom? Am I in the wrong fucking place? I thought I was supposed to go up and then right.
Isn't that like where I am? Go by. I'm up, I think I'm up way too high. All right. I gotta be careful
here. He's not in here. It's the other side. Oh, fuck. What? What are you up to? Who are you?
You, you're starting to piss me off. Hey, I know you can hear me. I'm talking. Who the fuck is this
guy? Oh man. No, no, no, no, not the gun. Um, fuck. Jesus. Thank Christ. How did you get up?
God, come on. It's a fucking three stooges episode. Oh, it was the other side. Shit. All right. I'm
back. Everybody has the little dollop on their head here. It's not this bathroom this way. Wait a
minute. I don't have a crowbar. Whatever. All right. I'm gonna save right here. You very clearly don't
work here. Oh, this is the stock area. Trespassing. Get a note. I'm trespassing. It's okay. I got the
note. What is it? Intel. Notice from the bank's head of security mentions that recent issues with
the building's wireless internet have gotten director Sal Vallas so high strung that fixing
the wifi in her office always takes priority. If the wifi in the director's office breaks down,
IT is allowed full and immediate access to the area. No questions asked. Okay. I gotta get,
I gotta be an IT guy. Don't see me. Don't see me. Don't see me. Don't see me. Is this an IT guy?
I don't know. Don't they, they wait to highs and shit, right? Investment banker.
You have anything else? Holy shit. Wait a minute. The guy's doing coke. Wait, what? Hold on a second.
I want him to wake up and then do coke naked and die.
Can you, how do you wake somebody up?
Get up. If I make a loud noise, will he get up? Can I give his clothes back?
The guards wake him up. Okay. Reload and poison coke. How am I going to do that? He's just going
to be staring at me. Hold on. Just dump poison on it while he smokes. Okay. It's this way.
He comes into this bathroom. Is it just here? He just, who just has coke just sitting here?
What? This is just community coke. Hey, uh, who are you? I'm sorry. It's all yours.
Answer me when I'm talking to you. Identify yourself. Oh, the veins are popping. Some
psycho's trying to kill people. He's got his hands around someone's neck. Hey, please, I need help.
I was behind the door. How would you see that? All right. I gotta go faster. Okay. Then I'm
going to go in behind him. Wait, can I hide in this? Yes. God damn it. I just want to watch you do
coke and die. What happened? He didn't do anything. Is he just sick because he's sick? He's still sick
though. He's ready to fight. Jesus Christ. That guy was the problem. I thought it was me. That
guy was the problem. That's so funny. I'm sitting here so concerned that they're chasing me.
Okay. I'm only doing this one more time and then I have to, I have to do something else.
Can you do the coke? No. You got to get him sick and then high and then him running around outside.
Right. Okay. I'll go for it. I don't feel so good. Where are the bathrooms?
He doesn't know where the bathroom is.
Why would you puke in there?
Wait, wait, wait. Give me that wristwatch. Don't mind me. I'm just going to turn on the water.
Help me out a little bit. Wait, hold on. He's not going to slip in that, is he?
I'm just making it worse. All right. Here. Now. I just broke his watch.
Give me the watch back. I have to bring people over here. What? What was he doing?
Is he wiping? Is he washing his hands in the water on the ground? This guy is fucking high.
Look at this guy. He's doing something wrong. He's not. He's not going to go back. No, is he?
It's high. All right. I've had my fun. Is he the only one that comes in here? I have to get him
high and then hit him with muffins. Give me that watch. All right. Time for objective. I don't. Oh
God. Here he comes again. Oh shit. Don't turn. Is it still poisoned? He's not going to do it again,
right? He just did it. All right. Muffin time. And then I'm going to fucking just let him run out.
Okay. Get out there. Run out there and cause a problem. Oh my God. He doesn't. I don't know you.
Is this real or are you just high? Imagine opening the door and the security guy would
fucking apples at a guy who is lying on the ground. Holy shit. He's looking at the blood.
This is bad. This is really bad. Holy shit, man. Okay. I'm ready. I still got the tie in the same
spot that he had his tie. Hold on. Wait a minute. Wait a minute. Wait a minute. Wait a minute. Wait
a minute. Wait a minute. Oh, they're above. I have the Coke tie on right now. Okay. So I'm safe. I'm
going to save it by the way. Right here. I got to get to the IT room. Key card. Do I have, can I do
card reader? Okay. I don't know. I don't know where I'm going. I've got, I'm going up restricted
area, unauthorized accesses. Okay. So I'm guessing going up. I'm going up here. Okay. I love that.
You can, you can save scum in this game. It's so wonderful. Milton Fitzpatrick,
IT. Oh, I'm supposed to be up here. Right. I'm an investment banker. Ooh, coffee. I don't have any
poison in the office in plain sight. I'm sorry. There's a guy that can see through my disguise
here. Mr. Man, we've been reviewing for just a few hours. It's not quite enough to get through
the substantial amount of documentation here. You're supposed to be the best. I was told
Mr. Man Kruger and Schultz has won best internal auditing awards. Nine years in a row. We are the
best, but we cannot buy low, sell high. I'll put my hand down now. Don't worry. You're pretty
little head of shit. This guy's got a disc. I'm feeling pretty salty here, lady. Pizza. All right.
I swear those people in IT need to get off their asses. You used all the right software on my laptop.
All right. Where's IT? Oh, that is Athena Savalas, billionaire banker,
Providence Herald, and Bane of the middle class. Push her out the window quick. Get her out the
window. Do it. I died with an apple in my hand. I need that guy's disc. He's got like, he's a,
he used to go do like a colonic. No, I'm sorry. She can't take any calls right now. I suggest
you call back later. Sir, are you with the... What the fuck is this? An iron, I guess.
I gotta, I gotta stick with it. I haven't killed anybody. Last ditch. Where is she going?
What the fuck was that? Oh, she's got, she's, she's got like a bunch of like
people watching the stream. She's got four pocket medics. Take the principal to the safe location.
No! Close the door on me. All right. I'm getting in there. No more fucking around. Distract guy at
desk. Easy. Stay here and try not to get in my way. Okay, but be careful. No, you need to both be
over there. Oh, come on. The alarm. Say what? Don't have a fuck with Coke tie. What's this? Oh, I need
that. Apple we got. Okay. So now I gotta get in there. I gotta get to IT.
Do they labeled? Conference room, director's office. I need IT. Level two, level one,
level zero, teller hall, level minus one. Where's the IT office? Security hub, interview, VIP,
waiting lounge. Where's, there's no IT. Deposit boxes all the way down in the basement.
All right. I got a, I got all the way up here though. I have the key. I need to get a different
disguise. This is going to beep and all right. This is good. This shit in here that I can do.
All right. Apricot. That's a smaller, more dense, compact apple. So that's good. That's good for me.
Create water leak now. Clothes, iron. It's like a net gear. Does she just come and try to unplug it
and plug it back in? Nope. She's going to figure it out. What'd she do though? She demands an IT
person. Where'd he go? Somebody get IT up. Yeah. All right. Where's the IT guy? Get IT. We need Tim,
the IT guy. All right. I gotta get the hell out of here. Tim, the IT guy. Gotta go down. Have you
tried turning it on and turning it off again? She's asked for her assistant to get someone from IT
to come up and look at it. This would be an excellent way to get close to the director.
I have to get down to IT and get a costume. Where am I now? Down. I gotta go down from here.
Is he already up there? A guy on a computer up there. So which way does he have to go? No,
that's not a guy on a computer. Is he gonna come up these stairs? He has to come up these stairs.
All right. So where is he? Fix the router. Let's go. It's gonna take a while to get up here.
Are you guys sure somebody's gonna come up into this room? I think they were on the way up and
I think they just found the body. That's the IT guy that's on the way up.
I have to get back down there. Oh no, the IT guy found him. That's great. Oh my god.
Why is the IT guy? It's always the IT department. They just do everything.
They figure everything out. They don't get enough credit. I wonder how long I have to sit here for
though. At what point does unplugging and plugging back in the router take precedence over dead guy
with knife and head on the stairs? I don't know. We're gonna find out. Still searching. What is
that down there? I have to go meet him down there. I do. Where did I save at last? I think I have to
just run down to where that guy's dead and intercept him and leave two dead bodies there.
You know what I'm saying? That's the play. Okay. I've got to get down to where that is.
All right. Get down there quick. Where is it? Where is it? Oh shit. Where is it? Is that?
Get out of my way. Fuck. God damn it. It's that guy. No, I can't. You gotta get ready. What a
fucking idiot. Where is he? All right. Out into the right. Down the stairs. Go. Go. Okay. Okay.
Okay. Okay. Okay. Okay. Okay. Where is it? Where is it? Where is it? Where is it? Down here.
Okay. All right. All right. All right. All right. IT guy. Where is he? That's him I think. Right there.
Who? What? What? Who found it? Oh, fuck. There he is. I gotta save right now. Over,
over here. It's Ruby Red. Get out of here. Ruby Red. We're on the same team.
Ruby Red. Get out of the way. Ruby. I'm sorry. No, Ruby. God damn it. I'm sorry. I have to.
Ruby's gonna have to get hit in the head with an apple. She'll be fine. No, no. Why are you
not knocked out? No. I'm like a fucking clown. I don't have anything else to throw.
All right. We're on the same team. We're not on the same team. Don't make me do it. Don't. Don't.
Shit. Why? Okay. I need to sit here for a second. Ruby, I'm sorry.
Over here. I need some assistance. What the? You didn't even fucking. We need help, please.
Why would you come investigate? He investigated last time. All right. No fucking around. They're
both going down instantly. I have to. Here's the play. Person now. Oh, she just. She did a
lemmings move. It's too gruesome to get my head around. Okay. She comes down. Go investigate.
Both of you do it. I got to make this very clean. We're doing iron. They both are going to come up.
Don't hit me, buddy. Watch this. Here we go. Someone help me.
Okay. New plan. New plan. I have to get it. You have to go down now. Okay. You don't look.
Hello. Got it. What are you firing? All right. I. We have to. I have to do something else. I have to.
I have to throw. This is going to be hard. Okay. This is the one. I'm going to try it this time.
This is going to be the one right now. Promise. Check this out. Ready? Without even a second
thought, it's going to be hit her. Get body. Iron. Wait. He's going to come up. What a shock.
Come on up. Take a look. Get a closer look. I need some help over here. No, you don't.
You need to take care of this. Oh my God. I'm trying to put the bodies higher.
Fucking God. All right. I got to move on. I have to. This is the last time I'm going to try this.
Guys, I need some backup. Nothing at my position.
Yeah. Still looking. Please. Why? Why did I do that? Oh, I'm so mad at myself. Why? I thought I
could drop down all the way. All right. That's the play. Here's the play. Oh, okay. This is the play.
So far. No. Okay. I have to run. I'm just going to hide in the box.
Hide in the box. Turn on the panic room. Quick. Turn it on. Turn it. Go, go, go, turn it on.
It's done. Ruby saw your face. It doesn't matter. Don't clap for that. Okay. So IT guy.
IT guy is dead, right? Ruby can get up. That's fine. Compromised. No, that ain't going to work.
Okay. I'm not going to be like, I can't leave my panic room. I have to get somebody to come in here.
Okay. I got coins. Who's around that I can get to come in here?
I need like a security guard, another outfit, something. Here we go. Right there. Get in here.
Get in here. Come on into the wall. Are you serious? They're bringing the body up. They're
bringing the body up. They're taking the body out. They're taking the guy out. Not good. Very bad.
We're good. We're good. We're good. We're good. I need that body. I need that body.
No. Hold on. Oh, I need this. I need. Look at this. I can't play. I need this body.
Oh my god. They take the body up. No, this is bad. All right. I know what to do.
Did we see it? Who saw it? Okay. I have to sneak. She's going to see me every time. This is horrible.
I've soft locked myself. Why do I need the body? Because I need his outfit. Who's around here?
You're right there. You're back there. Is there? I got to get to the bathroom. All right. I'm
sneaking to the bathroom. Nobody is going to see. There it is. No, Ruby. No. He's got the body right
there. All right. I need to. I need a coin right here or an apricot. Doesn't matter what it is.
You got to be fucking kidding me. They frisk you. They frisk you. How do I throw everything away?
What's the what's the drop button? How do you drop? How do you drop? How do you drop? How do I drop?
G? How do I drop? F? How do you drop something? What the fucked up shit do I have in here? Illegal.
Okay. I'm good. If you want to come through this way, I'm going to have to do it.
I got to pat you down. Sorry about that. Okay. You're all fine. Off you go. How are you today,
sir? I'm doing well. Thank you. What? What are you talking about? Okay. I think I did it. No,
they're going to see me do this. All right. Save. Throw apple. Okay. Throw apple through doors. I
could you know what I could do. I got three apples. Check it out. Let's see if I can get this done.
Distracted him. He's in the sky. Throw the apple up. I wonder if I can do this without anybody
caring. Wait, what? Oh, it's right here. As long as I don't do anything. I mean, that is weird to
take somebody's clothes out of a body bag. That is that's weird. But how weird is it? Is it weird
enough for me to get seen? Yes, it is apparently. What the fuck am I going to do about this?
I'm going to have to throw a coin down the hall somehow. What's going on in here? Unlock. No,
they're going to take that body out if I'm not. I got to let's see. You go. No, go look for it.
You got a problem, sir? You move around like somebody just kicked your ass real bad.
You motherfucker. This is fucking way louder. What do you think that noise was? Go have a look.
You go look too. Both of you. I got the key, right? I did. Let's go. No illegal items, right? Sir,
if you want to come through, I'm going to have to pat you down. That's fine. Okay. Thank you, sir.
This will be over in no time. Who says apples don't come in handy? That's right. That is exactly
what I said. Good job, sir. Thank you. That was verbatim what I said. Always carry a few apples
with you. You never know when you're going to need to throw it against a wall. Don't get on the camera
or whatever. Okay. Up. We got to go up one more. I'm supposed to be here. I'm supposed to be here.
Save it. It's time. All right. I heard you had a problem with your computer.
Good problem solving skills. I'm known to be the best. Let's take a look. All right. I'm going to
put like rat poison coke on her computer. Make the most of it. All right. I'm in. I'm in. Move
meeting. All right. I moved scanning through director's daily calendar. It became clear that
she has a meeting planned with Fabian Mann and Mateo Perez. It's scheduled around end of business,
but should be possible to advance it if needed. Okay. What's this? Newspaper? Is the meeting going
to be in here? Sabotage the clock. Yeah. Not playing anything. Commemorative token. Oh, nice.
What else is in here? She's right in there too. All right. Wait. Oh, wait a minute. There's poison.
Poison. Poisonable shit in here. Okay. Now? When's that meeting? I'm going to go in here.
Private chambers discovered. It's a hostile area. Okay. I'm not supposed to be in here.
All right. Wait. I got to wait for that meeting to happen. I got to tamper with the clock too.
How do I get you guys out of here? Come on. There's got to be something I can throw.
There we go. Perfect. Just like throw it over here.
And then you come investigate an apple. Go see what that was.
Got it. Always carry around a few apples. All right. So now I got to fix the computer. I got
to fix the internet and then they're going to have a meeting and someone's going to fall out the window.
I don't know how to fix the router apparently. I don't know how to fix a router. I'm not a real
IT guy. What the fuck am I supposed to do? Can I even do this? Wait, hold on. Looks like she's
coming out. Shoot it. No, that'll alert everybody. What else do I got here? Okay. I advanced the
meeting. Is there anything else I can do to advance this? Because I can't, the internet is not fixable
now. It was here a minute ago. There she is. Okay. Investigating distraction. What do you mean?
What distraction? Oh fucking God. What distraction? Where is she going? Oh God, no. Go to the meeting.
Meeting.
You're on your own. Run. If your bodyguard or security guard ever says you're on your own, run.
Okay. Go to the meeting. How do I get them to go to the meeting?
There aren't anything else I have to do. I have the gramophone. There's no meaning because I killed
him. Oh, I killed the person that she's talking about. How did I do that? Wait. That's me.
Now listen to me, Ken. Yeah. I don't want to hear any excuses or answer any questions.
Just fix my computer and get out. All right. I already did. Everything's good to go.
I'm going to body block her so she can't leave. Ben, come here. Get up. You did it.
I'm going to take you. Somebody fucking help me. I got the other key card.
My computer sucks. So she has one. Who has the other one?
How are these idiots ever going to find anything?
You know what? I think it's time. It's time just to make this happen.
Director Savalas eliminated. Good work, 47. Second backup data disk is secured.
Just one to go, 47. What is this? Credit card? Oh, wow. I disabled surveillance systems.
Can they hear me through the glass? Is it going to break? What was that?
What was that explosion? I'm firing through the glass somehow.
I need to get the last data disk, but I have no idea where that is.
The mirror is shooting at you. Okay. Can I store this? I can. Can I take this? I can.
All right. I'm ready. I need one more data disk. It's out here. Wait, I have to get rid of you.
This guy's as the agent. Oh, yeah. High security guard. Good to go. Last.
I think I can see right through me. All right. Let's get out of here.
Straight out this way. The IT guy was way more secure than this. Everybody can see through this.
Go fix the router. That's unfixable. I broke it. All right. Down. We have to go into the bank vault.
Oh, my God. Everybody can see through this. Except for you. Shit. This is a horrible disguise.
Okay. Down one more level. I'm going to go get all my weapons. They should still be over here.
Save it. Down one more time. So I should be a high security officer. I'm the bodyguard
of the objective of the game. Don't get restless. Nothing to report. Yeah, me neither.
These are perfectly good apples. How could you let these go to waste? I can unlock this.
I think I have the key card. Yep. I don't even need it. Let's just go into the vault.
Break open. Security lock enabled. All right. I got to go find the security room.
I thought the doors were closed. Area discovered. Wait a minute. Hold on.
Poison. I can put poison into the vents? Car battery?
I'm trying to shock him. I don't like that. I'm going to get less points for that.
I have to live with it though. I have no save. Yes, I do. I'm not losing points.
You already killed four non-targets. So? I'm an assassin. Sometimes you have to do dirty work
with the bad guys. Turn on the air conditioner. Okay. What about this? Unlock the cabinet.
What is in here? A chloroform? Okay. I'm allowed in here.
Okay. Where's the device? Where is it? It's not in here? You're doing easy mode.
The more people you kill, the more frames drop.
So what do I need in here? I got to poison this, but they're going to kill them anyways.
Let's turn this on. So this guy comes out here. And then what? This guy's pissed off. We choke
him out. I take his outfit because he's... I'm already wearing this disguise. Well,
that didn't do anything. Okay. What do you mean distraction? They all just want to turn the AC
off? That's so stupid. I got the key card. They all come out to try to turn the AC off. What about
you? Yup. I taught him here. Oh my God. I had to let him have a victory here. I got what I needed.
There's nobody else even down here. Wait, there's another AC person? Oh no, not good. Did he get it
off? He got his radio. I don't think that mattered. Missing key card. I picked up like four of them.
None of those were it. Oh shit. Really? All right. Well, it looks like I'm going over here.
I wonder if I should go up. Where does this lead out? I need a key card to get in there.
Apparently when I don't have. Are we dropping frames? Oh, that sucks. I wonder why this is
happening. It's been pretty good for a while, but it doesn't matter. Cox always sucks. Well,
I have rat poison though. He's just figuring this out now. God damn it. Really? All right. I don't
want to mess this up. Did I drop one of the other cards? Come on, stop dropping frames. What the
fuck? What's your deal, Cox? What's your deal? Sorry, I don't. Do I have to open it with something
else? There's got to be something in this room, right? Got it. Bingo. Let's go. Vault security
system has been unlocked. Let's do it. And then I beat the level. Should I push the big red button?
That's a deal. What's in the vault? Trespassing. What do you mean trespassing?
Uh, I'm going to save it here. That's not good.
Let's go. What's with the frames? Give me more frames. What the hell? This is horseshit. Oh,
I'm so glad this is going to be over real soon. I'm going to be on fiber in less than two or three
months. It's going to be fantastic. I got it. The expose. A lot of things to do, apparently.
Did he say fiber? No fiber, like fiber optic internet. Fiber to the house. So it's not going
to be through cable internet, which sucks ass. Oh, am I dead? Stream it. Stream dead. All right.
Are we good? Oh, this is bad. This just started right now too. It's struggling. One star though.
How would I get the points? 30,000? Uh, I wonder if I should change. Um, I wonder if I should do
this. This would probably kill the stream though. No, that's not going to work. Let's see if it'll
ride itself out. Damn it. Come on. I was having fun too. I knew this was going to be a short
stream today, but not this short. Uh, I'm going to go take a break. I'm just going to pee. Come
back, see if we can ride it out. I will be right back. Let's see if this actually, uh, stays live.
We'll find out. How are we doing? Have we, has it been bad since I left? It's been bad. Shit.
Even the BRB is getting fucked up. No, I don't want this. I didn't want this to be the last
thing I do before TwitchCon. Come on. I wanted to go for at least like three, four, five hours.
Ah, just do a comb stream. I really wanted to get these two DLCs done today though,
but I obviously don't want to stream if it's going to be shitty. Um, yeah, I don't want to stream
this. I did say that I was only going to stream for like three hours or so, three to four today,
because I have to get ready to go and put TwitchCon, but I'm not going to leave yet.
Well, um, we'll just hang out for a little bit. See if I'm going to, I'm hoping now it's still
dropping. Damn it. You might get a random vlog from TwitchCon, just like an hour long stream.
I don't know if I'm going to do that though. So don't hold me to that. I might not have an
opportunity to, cause I'm not going to be there for very long, but, uh, I don't want to continue
to do this if it's going to be unwatchable for people. So those of you that are just going to
take off, uh, I guess you can consider this like the end of the stream. I will see you guys later.
If you're going to TwitchCon, make sure you say hello. I'm going to have a toothpick in my mouth,
find the guy with the toothpick. That's me. But for the next like hour or so,
we're just going to painfully deal with this until I, uh, take off. So you'll see me again.
I'm so salty about this right now. Damn it. It's going to zero and shit. Ah, day before fucking
Twitch. Whatever. It's all right. I can't, I'm not going to sit here and be, uh, pissed off by this.
Uh, I'm going to go like this. At least we got to go through one full hitman mission.
I would like to do both of them. Sometimes you can't do what you want, I guess.
Do talk to transformer. Uh, we'll see. I'll show you guys my, let's just get out of this,
but thanks for watching. Regardless, a nice, a nice quick two hour and 22 minutes stream.
It's like the old days. This reminds me of back when I first started on Twitch,
I would stream for like two to three hours. Remember when I did that? Yeah. Just remember this,
pretend like this dream happened like six years ago. This over here, this should switch over to
here again. We can hang out and do the bits too. Just chill again. If you're going to Twitch con,
please say hello. Hopefully we even stay up long enough to do this. Ouch. All right. Change the
category. Yeah. I've been looking, I'm looking at my stream health on the, on my dashboard.
It's just zero up, zero up, zero up, not healthy stream. Apparently I know Twitch I'm trying.
All right. Let's head over here. Uh, let's turn on. Let's move. I wonder if this is going to work.
Is this still taking it from yesterday? I think this is taking it from yesterday.
Why is it not working? See you later. I didn't take a stream. It was the same, same people. Yeah.
I'll be back on Tuesday, most likely. And I'll probably just end up starting with Hitman 2,
just to try to finish that. And then we'll move on to something else. Unfortunately, I'm sorry.
This is not the way that I wanted this to end. You got to do what you got to do. Uh, I'm going to put
on the wonderful music. I still don't, I don't know why this shit is. I got to figure this out
when I come back, but let's do the bits. Let me put the camera on. We'll just sit here and talk.
Let's do that. How do I, where is it? Oh, it's this one here. Let's see. I'll prove to you guys that
I shaved. If you want to see, is that going to work? Wrong one. This one's cool too though.
Where's my, where's the camera? Oh, there's the camera. It just buttoned on. Oh,
that's what I wanted to do. I shaved, see? Hey, there we go. I got a shaved face. I can actually
make this smaller. All right. Streamlabs OBS. I kind of don't like you at all because it's hard
to move shit around in the scenes. You know what I'm talking about? It's like it locks shit around.
I haven't figured out how to turn it off. It's like, it's like almost harder to use.
All right, there we go. Let's move this over here. So if you're at TwitchCon, say hello. If you're
not at TwitchCon, then whatever, maybe we'll see you on Tuesday. Check the nails too. Did those look
cut to you? Told you. Told you I was going to do it. All right, now I got to go over here.
So I should do this. The music's getting louder, I know. Let's do the bits. It shouldn't take us
very long. We had, I'm not going to yell over it. Zake, thanks for the 250, Zake. You're going to
do a nail painting stream. I don't think, I don't think so. But thank you Zake for the 250. So I
translated the Minecraft copy pasta through every other language in Google Translate and back to
English. And this is what came out. In the game, it's awesome. Yes, there are peas, peanuts, beans,
and various products. We hope you enjoy the place. Black sauce, pour it back. But drinking
apple pie might not be so good. So that is the, that's the intro to the, to Minecraft.
Well, that's, that's good, I guess. Actually sounds pretty fun. Sounds like a fun game.
Drinking apple pie. That, yeah, that's called half the items at Starbucks.
I wouldn't order them if I were you. You come up, I would get, get like an ice coffee. Don't
get anything else. Uh, OC, oh, OcRolo, thanks for the thousand bits. Please use these measly pennies
to buy an eighth of a gigabyte of RAM. You need it. I need it. I'm probably going to get a new
computer. It's been about like three or four years, so I'm probably going to do new PC soon.
Within 12 months. I got, I want to get like a new RTX 2080. Get a new, um, right, 2090. Is
that coming out soon? I know there's one coming out. Should I do AMD? Should I do AMD instead?
Don't need fully new. Yeah, but I have, I have a 6800 or think, uh, CPU. I could do for, I could
do for an upgrade. I want to do like a supercomputer. What's the equivalent of the latest Intel
processors? Are they good? AMD CPU, Nvidia GPU. That's what I was thinking. AMD CPU. I, you know,
I actually heard that AMD really is starting to sincerely give Intel a run for their money.
Just like their processors are just better now. It used to be the complete opposite.
AMD was always like, oh, you have AMD. I've got Intel, Intel inside. And it was always like,
okay, yeah, that's, yeah, that's right. Intel's way better. They're kind of flipping, aren't they?
They're caught. Yeah. They, they, they're way cheaper too. AMD has gotten considered a bit. Yeah,
you know, I probably will. I'll probably do like one of those, what, thread rippers,
just get something crazy and water cool it. But then you can't bring it anywhere. That's the thing.
All right. The thing about having a huge, insane supercomputer PC is yeah, man, this thing's got
like liquified, hydrogenized oil that's cooled to negative five degrees Celsius. It goes through
all these tubes. The tubes are made out of glass, by the way. So never move this computer.
Don't ever pick it up. Don't even fucking pick it up and put it somewhere else.
When you put that 112 pound machine somewhere, that's a full tower. You ain't moving it ever
again. I would be so scared to, to like bring that computer anywhere to ever move. I would
think I would break everything, everything. All the hydrogenized oil would come out. It'd be
terrifying. Yeah. Even with this one now, it was scary. It's kind of heavy and I feel like I'm
going to drop it. I'm just going to hire somebody to take care of it. It's like having somebody
watch your dog, you know, like, Oh, I'm going away for the week. Somebody watch my dog for me. I'm
going away for the week. Somebody watch my computer, please. And make them and let them out,
let them out a few times and like open up the thing at the bottom. And it like pisses out stream
you building it. I would, I would never build a PC like that. That's so much money that I would
literally just be deleting because I would break something. Having like the GPU have the tubes on
it that you have to take off the GPU fan case, put on the your own heat sink. No, no, no. Somebody
else has to do that for me. I can put memory into a slot and I can put video card into slot.
That's about all I'm comfortable doing. I used to be a PC computer doctor, but I lost a lot of
business. I had like 1.4 stars on Yelp because I did a stream and I did a thing where I was like
showing people how to build and I got a lot of flack for it. So I was at like a 3.8 and then
it went down to 1.4. So I decided I was going to kind of just give it up. I guess it's what I was
doing for a long time. So, and the thing is, most of my customers were old ladies. So I don't know
how it was weird how that happened, but they'd come in and I would give them the computer back.
I would fix it. I'd do everything I needed to. I'd build them a computer and I never, they never,
I never got like a call. I never got like a mean phone call or anything. They seemed pretty happy
about it. But anyways, thank you. Thank you to, that's, that was oh, Acrolo, Acrolo. Mini clips,
thanks with thousand bits. Here's some bits for a new computer. Keep having a good stream.
It was until I started to drop a bunch of frames and it was happening for long enough where I
decided I was just going to call it. So you'll see Hitman again. And right when I start talking
about it, there it goes. It's almost like it can fucking hear me. It can fucking hear me talking.
It can hear me. I said that and then it turned off. What the fuck is happening? Who was listening
to this shit and doing this? Somebody just sitting there with like a dial from zero to 10 and they're
just turning it. We even had a problem with this in like at least three or four weeks either.
It's been like a month or so since it was a real issue kind of like this. Oh well, I'll make a call
see if they can do something about it when I'm gone for TwitchCon. So we'll see. But thank you.
Mini clips for the thousand bits. Appreciate it. Acrolo again gave 500 bits. Wait, never mind.
You'll just spend it on a clown costume. Clown costumes are way more expensive than you think.
It's, it's like 80 to a hundred dollars plus for a nice, maybe even like $200 for a nice clown
costume. We're not talking just like a t-shirt. No, no, we're talking a silk, fully complete
overalls. It's way more expensive. I'll be in one for during the entirety of TwitchCon. That's how
you'll find me. I'll be the clown with the toothpick. But thank you for the 10 bucks. Appreciate it.
We also had sad Vega gave $2.50 a belated birthday to you, Jerma. How's it feel to be 34?
Feels, it doesn't feel that bad actually. It feels okay. It doesn't, I don't, it's all right.
It doesn't bother me. When I turned 31, it bothered me. When I turned 32, it didn't.
So I hope that answers your question. But thank you for the $2.50. Thank you fat
Sanic for the 500 bits. No message. They just say, uh, cheer 500. Thank you, uh, fat Sonic.
I really appreciate it. Also thank you to Gnarly for the $2.50. Is this a stealth game week or
something? First the goose game, now Hitman. Then Jerma tries not to be seen at TwitchCon.
I mean it, it, it is whatever you want to call it. What if I really just tried to just not have
anybody see me? I should tweet out a place that I am and I'm just not there at all. Hey, I gotta
be standing in front of this statue of the guy from Borderlands. And I just, I'm not there.
And I'm just sitting somewhere else within distance, within like visual line of sight
distance of that place and just like counting who comes over. Three, two hours, four. Okay.
I got four fans. I got four people that like me here. And then the next day I know I got four
people. So I'm just like, Hey, uh, the four of you. And people are like, wait, okay, so how did he
know that? Come visit me at the coffee station. I'll be there. It's Saturday morning is when I'm
going to be there the most time. Saturday morning into Saturday early afternoon. That's the window
that I'm going to be at TwitchCon. And then I will probably show up at that party for a little while
because I gotta, you know, be the toothpick guy. And, uh, I try to wink with this eye, but I can't,
I can't, I can't wink with my left eye. It's too hard for me to do. I can only go like this and I
have to turn my whole face upside down when I do it. I can't wink with my other eye. It pulls my
mouth over. It's weird. Uh, it's like there's a fishing line here attached to this eye tight
to here. It's odd, but, uh, thank you. I appreciate that. Thank you. Also to, uh,
Final Fantasy 12 Penelo. FF12 Penelo. I don't know why I just said Final Fantasy. Botox.
Not getting Botox. Once you get Botox, that's what you admit that you're old. That's my opinion. The
second that you get Botox injected somewhere, I am admitting that I am old. Maybe that'll happen
when I'm 45. I don't know. Maybe it'll never happen. Maybe I'll never feel old. Maybe I,
and then you, and then if you do it too much, you end up looking, it looks too much. You know,
it looks like you did it too much. No, not gonna happen. Just try to age. I'm gonna try to age
like a nice red blend. Should be all right. What do you think about the shave job? See you in two
days when it looks real good. But we only got a few more. We got, uh, that was, uh, FF12 Penelo.
They said, I turned your stream on at work, promptly forgot I did. So when I put my headphones back in,
I was like, who the fuck is talking and realized. Anyways, genuinely thanks for what you do for
real. It always cheers me up when I need it. I think I would probably be, I was, and that's weird,
audio to hear too. Playing Hitman and talking about like strangling people and poisoning people.
I don't understand. Like I poisoned him. Why is he getting up? I poisoned that guy.
Oh my God. What the fuck, dude? Why is he waking up? I'm gonna throw an apple in his head. You'd be
like, I need to get like a new computer. Oh my God. Mugga ass. But, uh, if you can let me be on
at work, hopefully you have it in a situation where it's okay. And it's not going to be bad
that if you accidentally unplug your headphones and all of a sudden you, your boss hears me saying
fuck. Uh, they're not going to think you said it and then you're going to get in trouble.
So hopefully you got a situation there where it's okay. You got to like a system. You always have to
have like a good system. Uh, and make, and, and make sure you get your work done too. As I don't
want to just burn all your time there. Cause then they're going to blame me. And what if I get the
call from HR? What if my stream gets banned from your company? That's at least like six or seven
followers that I'm going to lose. I can't, I can't have that six or 7,000. No, but thank you. Uh,
thank you to not, not Hugsy. Uh, they said fix your internet. It's sad because I've fixed,
I've fixed this internet probably 15 to 16 times and it'll all be done soon. It's all going to be
over soon. Fiber to the home. I'm going to be on a direct thousand thousand connection,
true fiber. And then we can fucking forget that any of this shit ever happened.
I'm going to have like the best internet you can possibly purchase.
That is consumer grade internet at least I'm going on the fiber diet. That's right.
I can't wait. I can't wait to boot it up and have it be worse than this, which is that's not
possible. If you got direct fiber to the house, no fucking way. All these issues are because coax
sucks ass. Coax cable sucks total asshole. It is a fiber optic line. So all the dropping the frames,
the packet loss, the fucking dropouts, that's all because the cable companies suck and they have
laid this fucking groundwork that's been there for like 40 years and they're all dog shit.
All these lines of trash. So now that fiber is being laid out and they have to have it now,
you have, you, you'll be on a, if you can get on an actual to the home fiber,
all these issues disappear. They don't exist anymore. There's no noise. There's no like
ingress noise and packet problems when you're dealing with a fiber, a true fiber to the home.
You can have internet problems, but not like you do with coax. I fucking hate coax. Coax sucks.
I don't even want it plugged into the back of my fucking TV anymore. I'm going saddle.
Oops. Oops. Looks like somebody may have cut the bike. By the way, I just realized that there's
stuff going on in the background here. Is that an I? Is that a G? Is that a J? What is that?
It says there's like a monster on the left. I didn't even see that. Coax has less latency.
I would rather have stability than care about a few milliseconds of latency.
Coax has so many fucking problems. It doesn't matter where I am. I've, I've used three or four
different coax lines and they would just dog shit. So we'll see. Maybe I'll have my, maybe
fiber is worse, but there's no way it is. I've been told by every person that works in like
internet infrastructure that if you can get on fiber, get on it because it's a thousand times
more stable and better and more consistent than coax. So I'm like, thanks. I appreciate that.
And I'm going to be on it in a couple of months, but I think it's time to see if I set this up
correctly. If fiber is worse, what are you going to do? Um, shit my pants because at that point,
what the fuck am I going to do? I'm going to make my own. I'm going to have to like make my own
internet. Uh, let's see if this works. I want to see, can it work? I just need to know. Never
mind. It's not going to work. Oh, he blew it. He really blew it. I think. Yeah, he did. It's all
right. I didn't, I didn't set up correctly, but thank you to Mark Alter, Mark Alter. Thanks for
the $3. Enjoyed the stream. Good luck with the internet. And I, oh, I hit you in the eye. Now
you can't see. Sorry. Yeah. I'm going to, I'll make a few calls and see what's going on. Hopefully
they can get somebody out here and just turn the nozzle. Like apparently they do every time. And
then it's fine for like a month and a half. I don't understand, but, uh, I will see everybody
at TwitchCon, whoever's going. If you go into the show floor, I'll be there on Saturday. If not,
if you go into the party, if you make it there, I'll be there somewhere dancing with a toothpick.
Thank you guys. Here come the credits. Uh, door cube though, two 50 from door cube. I knew you
were going to shave your face in preparation to TwitchCon. That's what I told you guys that last
night, but I didn't realize you were going to get a haircut too, but I guess you needed one since you
played cosplaying as Daniel clamp from gremlins two. Is that the guy, the tie guy? That's the guy
with the tire, right? Oh, I know. Here come the credits by the way. Thank you everybody. Whoever
subbed in this kind of what did less than two hour period. It's still a lot of people leaving those
streams are going to only be a two or three hours long. Hope you enjoyed hitman for how, as long as
we got to play it before I had to stop. When I come back on Tuesday, we will do the second hitman
mission, clean it up, do the DLC, finish it up and move on from there. I thought there was something
wrong, but that's a person's username. I was like something, the spacing is incorrect on that.
This is really slow compared to yesterday. Yeah. Well, well yesterday was also eight hours and that
was also the first time I'd really come back, um, at my desk in about eight or nine days.
This is still a lot of people do not get me wrong there. This is still a shitload of people that
will sub in the two hours. Hey, cut tack. Thanks for the 500 bits stream extension. Oh, I see what
you know. Right. Yeah. Okay. Zake. Thanks for the 250. You are in the Minecraft copy pasta again for
Google translate. This time all languages. He is the creator of the first chapter of creation.
All other games are important games. You can have a cup of tea. I want to be a magician. At least I
got the last part right. Oh, this last one, this is a Siroc. Thank you Siroc for the 250. They say
goat hog champ German Venus. It's them watching the stream with a goat. Are they at the anti-mark
goats still available? Can we confirm? I don't think there's probably a very many left. Let's see.
Got one. You got one. Is it over? It is over. I had to stop because of the internet, but it's okay
though, because I do have a lot of shit that I still need to take care of before leaving stuff
that is not even Twitch con related stuff. That is my real life related that I have not been able
to do because I've not been here for four or five straight days after I got back. So I will see you
guys soon. Take care. So you have to Twitch con. I might turn the stream on at Twitch con. I don't
know why I would though. Maybe like eating spaghetti for like 30 minutes. It's only going to be like a
20 minute stream. If I do at least show this to you guys because it's funny. Take a look at that
link, get your anti-mark goat. If they're still available, which I don't think they are. Thanks
for hanging out everybody. See you real soon. Take care of yourselves and have a great weekend,
regardless if you're going to be a Twitch con or not. See you soon guys. Now there's no audio on
this. I broke something. I broke something. I don't, you know, it's just a lot of technical
things going on today. But before I leave, BorealBeast gave a thousand bits. Hey German,
this is my first time cheering. It's my birthday today and I wanted to give you something back to
one of my absolute favorite people as well. Love you and your content. Thank you so much for always
making me laugh and get me through tough times. I know you hear this a lot, but I really mean it.
Happy fucking birthday. Hope you have a great one. That was BorealBeast. Anytime I hear about the
stream people like and people have a great time here, it makes me, don't, don't worry if you,
you know, I know you hear this a lot kind of scenario. Every time somebody says that,
it doesn't matter how many times I hear it. It makes me happy every single time. Thank you.
And thanks for the thousand bits. And then HeatLegend thanks for 250. While I can't attend
TwitchCon, I hope you have a great time in San Diego. It rained for the first time today in
over a month, so I hope the weather isn't shitty for you when you get here. This would be the first
time I've been to San Diego as well. Well, not as well. You live there, I think, as it sounds.
But yeah, this is the first time being there. I will see you guys later. Take care. Good night.
I gotta go get ready. See you soon.