What is extreme content? What does that mean? It's not blood or gore. Usually the blood or gore is a checkbox.
Watch the first scene of this game. There's gonna be tits everywhere.
I asked you a question.
I don't know.
Yokiken?
That's this person's name, Yokiken.
That's something that like Chung Lee would scream when she shoots a fireball.
Yokiken! Yokiken!
Holy shit!
This is so loud! This is the loudest thing I've ever experienced.
Yokiken!
There's only one enemy down here.
Does it seriously have to be this loud?
I told you he was gonna die.
Is he gonna get run over by a motorcycle too? That's been the best.
What?
What an awful shot.
How are you not shooting him? How are you missing that? How did you miss those three shots?
Shoot him! Shoot him! He's already gone!
Ster?
Yes?
I didn't want to be the first one to say this, but I truly think...
I truly think this weird agency is poisoning the water supply.
Oh no!
Where is he? Breakfast is almost served.
Honey! I have your favorite Pop-Tarts!
Pop-Tarts!
This is the one window in the whole game!
No! You broke it!
Did you see me trying to jump through it?
You fucking broke it and you messed up the joke!
Honey, I've got your favorite breakfast snack here waiting for you.
It's Pop-Tart!
Pop-Tart!
Honey! You know there's Pop-Tarts down here!
Huh? What? Pop-Tarts?
You fucking idiot. Get in there!
You know, I've got all these breakfast toaster strudel things here. They remind me of...
Toaster strudel? Toaster strudel?
I got it in. Oh no, I didn't. It's close.
Alright, it's in. I got it in. I got it in the house.
I got it in the house. Help me.
I don't know what to do. I'm stuck.
Well, get off of it.
Get off of it so we can do this joke.
I kinda can't, dude.
Alright, I'm gonna get off. I'm gonna get off.
You got this on the second floor?
Honey, I have your favorite breakfast food.
Pop-Tart?
Yeah, that was so cool.
This is lagging so bad.
This game just got so much better.
I was riding on the walls. This is so...
Oh my god.
No, don't go. Don't go.
I'm dead.
I was dead.
I'm gonna burgably throw up right now.
Oh my god.
What is extreme content? What does that mean?
This was such a boring game. And then they added this to it.
Oh, you landed on the roof.
Watch out for this guy. I'm gonna die.
No, dude. What?
I'm dead. I'm dead.
Alright, here's your last chance, honey.
They're nice and piping hot. Pop-Tarts!
Please give me the Pop-Tarts.
Wait, mom. Mom, I need the Pop-Tarts.
I'm gonna use my superpowers to see where he is.
I'm not climbing up.
This is like on all those movies you watch with like the school bus is just hanging by a thread.
Do you see my tires spinning how much it's going?
I'm stuck perfectly. Like, I have no traction.
You cannot move at all?
No.
You cannot move this at all. This is like penis motorcycles.
Oh, yeah. Sure you can't.
No, no. Hitting the jet booster on the back kind of helps.
Alright, I'm done. I'm out of this fucking game.