I'm so sudden, somebody said. So sudden. What do you mean sudden? I've got a time frame.
And I'm here. I could show up at one o'clock. I could show up at 1.59. Or two. Or 2.15. Carrying
a bunch of fucking grocery bags. I might, yeah, I may have been late, but I've got groceries. I was
at the grocery store and I have all the groceries. Six or seven bags on each hand. Because I don't
know about you guys. I don't do multiple trips going back and forth from the car. You do all of
it. So you only have to do it once. Sure, it hurts a little and it's a little bit of pain,
but you get everything done. I'm so proud of that. One and done. Yeah, exactly. 700,000 bags of milk.
But hello, I've returned. I was back from TwitchCon a day or two ago, but didn't stream.
Had some other stuff to take care of. But we're back. For good. Not that we were gone for good
either. I saw people in the pre-stream chat. They said, you've got to tell us some stories.
Okay. You ready for some wild TwitchCon stories? How about this one? Whoa. So at the TwitchCon party.
Wow. Huge concert. People fucking partying in the front on the field. It was at Petco parks. It was
a huge thing. I sat behind home plate where there was nobody there. Me and like five or six people.
We just watched from like a mile away. Just kind of sitting there enjoying the concert.
No, somebody said people watching. No, we essentially were doing a helicopter tour.
That's how far away we were. Just sitting there. It was kind of nice. Did I have a toothpick? Yes,
I did. At some point. And I'm sure there's going to be lots of pictures that people have.
Yeah. This one in the chat. Yeah. That's what people are saying. How do you react to,
how you can react to in gigantic quotes? Look, I squished Jerma in Photoshop.
Let me see. How do we react to this? What the fuck? The fuck did you do to me? I'm not that small.
Is that what you wanted? This one isn't even trying. Look at the, look at the ceiling. They
actually just took the crop tool, grabbed from the top of the picture and then squished it down and
then stretched it. That was not even trying. What about the stain on my pants? Yeah. I saw the one
with somebody. I saw the piss one, the, the way somebody made it look like I pissed my pants.
You got, you guys are some, there's just so, there's so many fake pictures out there.
I don't even know which one is the real one. You know what I mean? When you, when you, okay,
when you take a picture and it gets circulated a million times and it's edited a million times
and you show one of those, you show them edit number 600,241, that person probably thinks
that edit is real. A case of point, somebody put a text on my shirt in one of those posts.
I didn't have text on my shirt and somebody said, why the fuck is he wearing that shirt?
It's like, I, I wasn't wearing that shirt is exactly what happened. Dude, what the, what,
what happened? Why did he piss his pants? No. No. How do we combat fake data is what I want to know
because it's all fun and games. It's all fun and games until it starts like world war three.
This is the future. Yeah. But no, TwitchCon was awesome. I had a great time. Met a lot
of people. It was fantastic. Lots of new stuff coming out of TwitchCon. Uh, the next projects
project is already being worked on and it always isn't going to be good this time.
I ain't going to give you any details, but just know that somewhere in, um,
somewhere in December, January ish, uh, you're going to get something else. And it's going to
be pretty fucking cool. That's all I've got to say. Cool. All right. Today we are going to play
Hitman Tuesday. I'll say we got caught off last time last week, so I'm going to play it.
We have to finish one of the missions. Uh, there's one more area and then I kind of,
I want to go back and do the first area again. It's untitled goose game. Community stream when
right? Okay. I said I was going to talk about that too. I will probably do the community stream.
I'm going to go three days in a row. So we're going to do today is going to be hitman tomorrow.
Something weird. Uh, something that I don't, I might, I might have to change games within
10 seconds or I'll be addicted for 10 hours. I don't know. I just know that it exists and I'm
going to try it. Uh, and then Friday, I'm going to try to compile all those images and all those
things for the community night on Friday. So the end of this week, that sounds like plan to me.
Oh, should I go to work? Well, I did say that I was going to do it right. Like kind of right
after TwitchCon, I was going to, we were going to do it. So I mean, TwitchCon was this last weekend,
but let's get started. Don't waste any more time. Let's play the second area and hitman two and
let's just enjoy hitman too. I mean, let's enjoy it because this is, this is probably going to be
the last time that I play this game. I can't imagine going back to doing more hitman too.
So let's get all we want out of it today. How's that sound? This one's called the last resort.
Why is everybody doing the D phase? I don't get it. Oh, it's because it's the, by the way,
all my other monitor is just that image of me. Like, and here's the thing about like,
here's the thing about like the fake. I can't even talk about a problem. I will in a minute.
I'm like spouting off about fake media, but it's true though. It's
actual fake media that's supposed to be presented as real.
out of the Maldives. It's true. It's fake. To the public, they specialize in reputation management
for the rich and famous. The real money, however, comes from the covert reconstruction of identities
for wealthy criminals. They make people disappear. The partners are using Haven to acquire new
identities. Yes, it's true that it's fake. This is going to get real weird in 10 years.
The access keys every 10 hours. That unfortunately makes them targets. It's called Haven is a true
tropical paradise owned by the company's founder, Tyson Williams. The island is used by Haven as
a combined headquarters and client entertainment center. Current and potential clients are ferried
to the island and treated to the very best. Do I get to drive a boat? I hope I can drive a boat.
That's the first thing I'm going to try. I don't care about anything else.
Boat client. You want a boat.
And he loves the water. He loves boats.
CEO of Haven. This guy, a former confidence artist hired by Williams to serve as a client
recruiter in hand. Okay. And Stephen Bradley, technical wizard and the brains behind Haven's
proprietary software. The owner's gone. Olivia will be able to penetrate the Haven servers long
enough for her to secure the new part. I've uploaded all the information we have on the
island and the three targets. Best of luck, gentlemen. Well, good luck. I don't do shit.
I just send you off and stand over here till you're done. But I'm a very, very,
I'm very good at assassinating people too. Where's the multiplayer? Come on,
with co-op for this mission. DLC co-op with that guy. All right. So we've got Jesus. Okay. So we
got Tyson Williams, Stephen Bradley, and Ludmila Vitrova. Let's go to the planning stage. Resort.
Okay. Coins. I was going to take a few coins. I would prefer apples, but I don't know. They're
not available. They better be available in this mission or I'll be very upset.
This guy's wearing welding glasses. Okay. Good to know. I think we're good. No, wait, wait, wait,
wait, wait. I got something better than this, right? Yeah. Looks good. All right. I'm ready.
And play unprofessional. We just got big bits just came in. Freddie Dredd just gave 5,000 bits.
Thank you, Freddie Dredd. I don't know how to use Twitch, but I love you,
Jerma. Made this account for you. Well, thank you, Freddie Dredd, that you figured it out.
I think you got it working. Welcome to the Maldives.
Appreciate that though. That's a lot of money. Thank you, Freddie Dredd. Made this account from
me. It's ready to receive you under your assumed identity as Tobias Reaper,
a professional thief looking to retire from a life of crime. Freddie Dredd watches Jerma.
Ludmilla Vetrova can be found in the public section of the island, primarily tending to
client needs. Is this some kind of currency thing? Steven Bradley alternates between looking after
a strict training regimen. I also made this account for you. How many of you guys made your
account last night? While Tyson Williams roams his large villa estate at the back of the island.
Why did you just put on extra glasses? Eliminating the three owners of Haven
should buy Miss Hall the time needed to do a full penetration and retrieval
of the Providence partner. Providence partner data is what I need.
I told I get to drive a boat. I knew it. I didn't, but he did. Jealous. Jealous.
Damn it. Okay. Did I take the bag? All right. I got to, okay, hold on. God damn it. I wish I
could fly one of those. All right. So we just get up here. This is a nice place. A little chunky.
It's a little chunky right now because my computer sucks. I need like a 2080.
I thought that guy was pissing. All right. So we have to look for some intel.
Let me look at the map. So we write what there's one right here.
Easy. I need to get a better computer. I know I do.
Is this open? No. Anything in there? I don't know. All right. Let's go to the welcome center.
I think the welcome center is over here. Let's go through the front door.
My shadow is messed up. Yeah. Well, that's what a 1080 gets you.
Okay. Key to the private hut. Welcome to Haven. Let's do it. What do you guys got for me?
Personal message. All right. Can I get a candy? No, I can't take a peppermint.
So the key to your personal hut. Where the hell is my, where is it? I hate when hotels do this
shit. They just hand you your key. They don't even tell you where the elevator is. Here you go, Mr.
Albertson. Have a nice day. You're on like the 54th floor. You don't know. I don't know where the
fuck to go. Did she tell me? She told me. What did she say? Hold on. She said it?
Hut on the left? Hold on. Wait. Did she actually say it? He just wanted to talk shit. Wait. I don't
care about that. We don't go right to your hotel room. Anyway, you go to the bar first. This is
water. This is cool. I was too invested in the candy. Oh my God. Are these pretzels? Okay.
Selling off. Wait. Oh, you two aren't talking.
I'm just eavesdropping on the wrong people. Okay, you're selling it. All right.
It seems Ms. Ventrova is trying to get Jason Portman out of his hut and she has ordered a
member of staff to watch him. According to his entourage, he's planning on selling his shares in
his company, Much Talk to Haven. Can I? I want to get on this. Maybe she'll think it's a real alligator.
Look out behind you. Holy shit. I don't know what that was. What she made out of. What are you made
out of? No, it was intel.
Okay.
I keep thinking of the alligator. That's not cool. All right. Okay. I need to go to my hut.
Can I go back to the front desk? Excuse me. Where did you say it was again?
I just, I forget. I know you had candy up here and that was a mistake. Get that out of here.
You're distracting all of us squirrel people. Was it this way or to the right?
Behind you on the right. Right over here. Okay. Do I have to get searched?
Listen to me. You will get that whole fucking container of peppermint candies
and you bring that fucking whole container over here. Okay. You do that. There's a $50 bill
with your name on it. I want that. I want that whole fucking container. Make something up. I
don't care. All right. There's a message for me in here. Intel. A pamphlet describing the various
activities available to clients visiting Haven Island. The island offers massage facilities,
a full gym, yoga lessons, private huts, a fully stocked cocktail bar and a five-star restaurant.
Pretty cool. Can I just like, can I just do this? Can I just enjoy the resort? What if I don't want
to do anything? This is awesome. I wonder how much this is a night. This is probably like
2,500 bucks a night. Oh, there we go. All right. Call this number. A note from Ludmilla Vitrova.
I wonder what she wants from you 47. Regardless, it would be a shame to keep her waiting.
All right. So I have to call Vitrova. All right. Let's call her. Don't ever fucking leave without
one of these. You didn't think there was going to be apples in this trip, did you?
Well, there are. I wish there was three. Come on. Come on. Yeah, I thought about it. Wait,
can I get that? No, get down. Oh my God. You idiot. Hold on. Save the game. I got to have a
point where a nice save slot. Okay, there's that one. I don't remember what any of these do.
I'm going to go over here. No, I can't ride it. Wait a minute. Was that the guy? I think that was
the actual guy. Is this the guy that I need to get rid of? All right. Let's go call Vitrova on
phone. What's with all the water everywhere? Well, the point, it's the ocean. What are you talking
about? What is this? Is this a shaver? You got to be careful with these things. I talked a lot about
these things are dangerous. All right. Overflow the sink in my own apartment.
No, no. Turn that off. Turn that off. I don't want to do that. This is a nice place. Shit. It's okay.
Can I take a bath? No. Where did that go? Okay. It's fine. There's a big dent in it, but it's
all right. Let's make the call. I can't do it. I'm going to practice this. Hey, Vitrova. I met you
at the bar and I want to say, I think we hit it off. No, I can't do it. Okay, good. I can do it.
What's going on? Vitrova, it's Tobias Reaper. I really wasn't nervous. I reviewed your file prior
to your arrival and it's very intriguing. An offer. If you're interested, you can find me over at the
restaurant. I'll keep it in line. Go to the restaurant and she has an offer. Meet Vitrova
at the restaurant as Mr. Reaper. Do I get new clothes? No, I don't have any new clothes. Why
did I do this stupid outfit? Two big butterflies. That's a nice touch. Okay. Nothing else in here.
All right. Let's meet. What? What do you mean remove safety pin for the trap door?
Oh, am I going to 1980s cartoon villain somebody down here? All right. Should I? I just want to
see what it does. Oh shit. All right. It's ice fishing. Stand on it. I can't stand on it. Get
in there. Hold on. Can I be like a trap door spider and just pull somebody in? No, I don't think I
want to do that. I think that's just a, I think I don't know. Maybe I dropped somebody. All right.
I gotta go to the restaurant. Let's go. Let's keep it moving. Restaurants this way. That's the toilet.
You know, I, for a tenth of a second, I believed. What do you mean trespassing? Trespassing?
We don't share this whole thing. Let's get this private hut. Yeah. The inside. This is,
I'm not allowed to be over here. Jeremy, this is a hotel. Yeah. But it's an outdoor hotel. I've never
been in one of these before. Sorry guys. I don't have any experiences in a fucking $4,000 a night
outdoor cabana place. Quick. I gotta get in there and dance. I had fun too.
How do you dance? No, not subdue. Dance. Let's go right here. No. Order a drink?
Why would you poison something in front of everybody? All right. I don't think I can do
anything here. All right. Let's go to the restaurant. Guys playing chess. Can I play chess?
Playing chess by yourself. Isn't that how you learn? That's how you get to be like next level,
right? You try to beat yourself. Okay. Yeah. You play chess against yourself. So then you
always have a move because you know you made it. And then you just gridlock yourself until you win,
until one of your brains wins. All right. Let's have the meeting.
Mr. Reaper. So good to see you. Good to see you too. What do you want to talk about? Should I sit
down? No. Let's talk. You mentioned an offer. Yes. It's a little embarrassing, but we've had an
incident. A theft. A thief is an employee here. A person working in Mr. Williams's villa at the
other end of the island. What was stolen? A USB drive containing some sensitive information.
Personal information, which I would rather not fall into the hands of others.
Okay. So my offer is this. Obtain the USB drive from the thief without alerting anyone
at the villa. The thief is likely still there. I can't get you inside, so you'll have to use
that particular skill set of yours. Two targets remaining. The trover has been permanently
detained. What the hell was that? Oh, it's another one of these.
She said particular skill set and I had to do it. I don't even talk. What do you mean whiny?
I love this game so much. These games are so fucking good. They really are. Just like so.
This is so ridiculous. I love it. Sometimes you forget just how much fun you're gonna have in
just being a dickhead in these games. Well, now we have to listen to that again. All right,
so I have to infiltrate. Mr. Reaper. It's very good to meet you. I'm not gonna do it again.
You mentioned an offer. Yes. It's a little embarrassing, but we've had an incident. A theft.
A thief is an employee here. A person working in Mr. Williams's villa at the other end of the
island. What was stolen? A USB drive containing... Get the USB drive. Personal information,
which I would rather not fall into the hands of others. So my offer is this. Obtain the USB
drive from the thief without alerting anyone at the villa. The thief is likely still there.
I can't get you inside, so you'll have to use that particular skill set of yours to gain...
No! I wanted to do the apple! I thought I was gonna do the apple.
Why would I have a melee item equipped? I was gonna hit apples in the face,
now I just punched her in the face. What do you mean try again? No. You want me to be stuck here
for like 45 minutes? Uh-uh. Did it break the game? The next four hours of the stream is gonna be
this. This is what we pay you for. What about that plan again? Tell me more about that plan.
Command? Yeah. It was nothing. It's very personal. Please call me as soon as you've recovered it.
I'm sorry. I just was hit in the face by an apple.
It's taken me months to prepare this, and I've been very careful.
We're gonna watch everybody here get fired. I'm really looking through my computer right now.
Okay. Do I have to walk with her? All right. Infiltrate the villa.
Good afternoon, sir. I think this is fucked up.
The accounts are in place.
To be fair, that hit her square in the face. It was not like in the back of the head.
That was just right in the face. How come I can't pick up these?
Yeah. I wonder how many teeth I knocked out. And I got it back. Just gotta rub it off a little.
No big deal. Oh, I just pressed the DPI button. All right. So let's infiltrate the villa.
So that puts us... Okay. Look at how menacing this thumbnail is.
Eat the apple? No, I need this. This is important. All right. Let's see.
So I got to infiltrate the villa, which is down here. I can't vault over this?
All right. We've got to go down this way. Wait, there might be more apples in here.
Kazzy, thanks for the five community subs and Clown Daddy. Both of you.
Thanks for the five community subs from each of you. Oh, soda can. Perfect.
What is this? ATM? Ice machine? No. Oh, actually, I probably...
Am I gonna stab himself in the face? All right. I think I'm gonna turn on...
I'm gonna get the chef outfit. I think that'll help. All right. Let me get out the...
No, I'm just gonna knock him out. Turn this off! Turn it off! Turn it off! Turn it off! Turn it off!
Turn it off! Oh, shit. Oh, no. Oh, no. That's bad.
No, god damn it.
Fuck. It's too condensed. It's... All right. It's way too condensed.
Where was it? 1340. I can do it. It's gonna be quieter than that.
Lead pipe. The game is quiet. I'll fix that. Just give me one sec.
There you go. That should be better. All right. I gotta become a chef.
I think it's... The apple is not silent, by the way. It's very loud.
Everything is loud. So I need... Where's my iPod? All right. The iPod will work.
Let's get the chef to come in here. He'll figure it out.
I'm gonna get behind him. I'm gonna close the door.
This doesn't kill him, right? Oh, I killed him. I killed him with the fucking iPod.
All right. Well, that's unfortunate because I really did not want to kill that guy.
By the way, I feel like the iPod would break. I feel like these earphones would just
snap and it wouldn't kill the guy. Whatever. Does he know? Does he know that I'm not him?
Oh, meat bone. Nice.
What's going on? Well, I'm turning the stoves on. I'm a chef.
I turned on the stove. Damn it. And I didn't fucking save it. Oh my God. I'm too... I'm too
ADD in this game. I was there. I turned the stove on. Why is that so out of the ordinary?
Wait a minute. The chef just turned on the stove. Let's all fucking run. What? Oh, I don't want to
kill him. I just want to knock him out. Whatever. I don't know about this. I don't know about this
guy. Well, I turned on all the stoves, but who cares? What if I had a big dinner service? I love
how turning a stove on as a chef is more suspicious than hiding and throwing an apple at the target
in plain sight. Save the game. Let's do this one here. This guy was destined to die. No. All right.
Don't turn the stove on, but I do want the meaty bone. Plate this up. I'll make it unforgettable,
chef. I need poison. Oh, this is awesome. Poison. Poison. Poison. What do we got? Poison.
I need poison first. Where's poison?
Anyway, we also need to find a good way. I had some in Copenhagen a few months back and they're
just perfectly tangy in the city. A real treat. Like mighty down on an overripe orange. We go
great with the sauteed chinoise and soy garlic. I'm trying to put it up there.
All right. Just put it. Okay. I'm done with that. Where's the pot? Wait. Hey,
hey, Mike. Where's the poison? Where do we keep it? Start a gas leak. Cheeseburger. Oh, yeah.
Cheeseburger. Nice. All right. Blend in as a waiter. Why do I need to do that?
I must remember to grab one. Okay. I gotta put this down. What is it? J? How do you drop something?
G? Z. Okay. Hey, mister. I think you dropped that. Yeah, I know. I did. All right. I need to get
poison. Perfect. Where can I get poison? Don't touch that. Leave that there.
What about over here? No, no, no, no. Don't. Don't. Don't. Is he taking it out?
Mr. Trova. No shit. Okay. It's perfect. Perfect. Come on. Christ sakes. All right. Poison. Quick.
Where can I get some poison? Some hut or some? Where's like the basement? I need like a chemical
basement. Is this poison factory? Staff key. Got it. Save it. Poison. No. I'm gonna shoot myself.
I had to just walk away and I swear he didn't even notice. He just kept on talking.
On a different sub. Let me take this off of him. A little too strong,
mister. Let me get. Let me take this off your hands. Let me help you. Let me help you. Get out
of the way. I'm trying to help you. Get away from me, you creep. It's my turn to do the dishes. When
have you ever heard something like this? Check up on stock with the key back. Whatever. Yeah. I got
the key. Oh, am I allowed to be back here? Oh, that's right. I'm a chef now. Okay. What about
the old man? Poison. Poison. No, it's just soda. It could be poison though. It is poison. If we're
talking real life. Am I right, guys? That's funny. All right. I'm getting too distracted.
I really am. There's so many things to do here. There's so many places to be.
I'm too distracted. I gotta, I gotta focus hard. Is it ready yet? Please don't tell me you're trying
to put ants back on the menu. Nobody liked the ants. It's not ready. So here we are. I really hope
you like this one because yeah, that would be nice. I missed it. Wait, she's coming in. Sir,
your breath stinks. Back off. Okay. I'm rather speechless here. Um, let's pretend I didn't taste
it. I'll come back. You try again. You didn't even get it. That was a garnish.
You didn't touch the cheeseburger. Okay, here we go again. All right. Looks good.
Oh, that reminds me, I did some experimentation. Your breath stinks. Wait, revolt.
Once that's done, we skin them, slice them thin and ferment them with poison.
But I stopped getting distracted. I need poison. Why would you be upset about extra food there?
Well, go, go, go, go. Yeah, I kind of do.
Imagine waking up to this. Why me? Why me? Free drinks. Poison. Where was the poison?
Somebody said poison. No, it was an accident. I need poison quickly. That was insane.
Oh, that's just mean. Hold on. That was mean. I'm going back. Where was it? You know how hard it is
for me to play these games. Some of you guys can be very, very tactical and very precise.
That's awesome. But if there's an interaction, like for instance, like I'm just going to pick
this up. I kind of have to. I have to pick this up. There was an internal struggle in my head
right there. Don't pick that up. It doesn't matter. I had to pick this up. I had to.
I'm watching the stream right now. I'm not participating. You and I are in the same boat.
My hands have taken over. I don't know what the fuck is going on.
I don't know what he's going to do next. What? That wasn't that big of a deal.
Is this over here of a trash can? If I'm this person, that's... Get rid of it. I'll take care
of it. I'm going to save everybody. Hold on. I'm going to rescue us. What? You've all been
rescued. Congratulations. How did nobody give a shit about that? Wait, sand castle.
Wait, can I... What? Let me help. This is a beautiful sand castle.
Does anyone know this dickhead? Has anyone seen him before? Oh, sorry.
What do you think you're doing, buddy? I'm done with you. I'm getting out right now.
I'm never going to get to the end of this mission. I'm sorry. Some guy walks over to
you sand castle and just ruins it with... He puts a big chunk of meat in there.
Did you just get threatened by a gun over a sand castle? Yes. Don't do too much. Hey, good to see
you. Good to see you. Okay. What was I doing? Right. I need to get poison. We have to poison
the thing. Right? What the hell was I doing? Yeah. Poison. I'm walking by. Don't... Why? I'm
walking by. I'm just walking by. What the fuck are you doing? Okay. Don't walk by that guy.
I can't cover. I know. I know. I didn't think. Okay. Don't. Easy. There's a guy right there.
Just let me look at the... Let me look at the menu. So I need to go. We need to go over here. So I
just got to turn around. Just make my way this way through here. If I come across poison, I can
bring it back. That sounds like a plan. All right. Good. Down this way. Watch out for the guys that
know who I am. So I have a couple of choices here. Go infiltrate the villa or find poison. I think
find poison is number one. I may actually be able to get poisoned there. All right. I might be able
to just get in as the chef. Okay. We're good. I can go through here. Right. They're not going to
search me, are they? No, I can't. I'm not going over there. I know I'm not supposed to be over
there. That's fine. What about in here? What the hell is this?
All right. So I got to do that. Okay. All right. All right. All right. All right. All right. I need
to... Well, I can't poison her then. Don't poison her. Go to... Oh, fuck. I'm trespassing.
Poison. Oh, no. I'm in trouble. Oh, God. Oh, my God. What the hell happened? Oh, fuck. I'm in
trouble. Okay. Okay. Okay. Okay. Okay. Okay. I got it. Say, why? Oh, Mr. You're currently
trespassing in a residence. I'm not going to be bothering you. No more, sir. Thank you.
How do I get over there then? I need a security outfit or poison. Either one will work. Oh,
there's the gym. Personal trainer. I gotta be a personal trainer. There's too many things to do
here. There's too many things to do. I got to be, okay. Personal trainer. Is that a personal
trainer which one of these guys was which one is a personal trainer
i've got some clothes in here personal trainer clothes come on nothing
oh i can't get anything out of the bag okay where i don't it's just somebody's
room wait security guard i can't drop down
wait somebody say what are you doing save
uh this one's 1349 this one here right yeah
i love parkour i don't even know if i got in all right i have the kettleball
oh god don't give me a kettleball i need to blend in
no no no no no this is a personal trainer though but uh how do i
no i can't i can't do it
oh shit it kills him i need your clothes what
wait oh hold on i need that outfit that's like a super security guard
walk this way walk this way walk that way walk that way walk that way
you know what go ahead walk that way no
fuck who how do i get down i can't get down i thought that that guy was going
to be a personal trainer who's seeing me hey don't fool around
you all right oh shit any description on the possible suspect
oh shit oh shit okay well uh that guy was just here
yeah and we know what he looks like i didn't really see what he was wearing
eat it huh what you can see through walls
okay when did i oh okay this is a good save
i know karate if you got hit in the face by a kettleball
i mean that's there's no way you're coming out of that one
uh freddy dread gave 10 000 bits a little bit earlier
thank you so much freddy dread i missed it from 10 10 minutes ago but thank you
10 000 bits so they're not personal trained
are you personal trainer is that a person trainer i don't think it is
no
everybody here personal trainer is that a person is this personal trainer
where's this going this is like a laundry room he's dead i fucking killed
somebody personal trainer wait oh no i'm like an
old-fashioned like burger it's roller skate chef you know what i'm
saying hey man did you do this
all right let's rock uh they need to leave can i hold the bars for somebody
someone's coming over here holy shit wait a minute save it
i can actually can i drop those bars on somebody's head or something
this is gonna be crazy somebody new spot one of the security guys
come on give it a go no no no the guy is coming up here now that i need to do
this too hey let me see how much is steven bread
notorious hacker chief programmer at haven
and rumored to be quite reckless in his behavior
there he is he's gonna put on too much weight it's gonna kill him
wait no no no no no i want the other guy although i did
how much weight do you want wait but he's gonna be here
i don't know what happened man he just took too much weight
all right that's what i need to do to him germa horse
no it all right i gotta wait i gotta be the personal trainer over here
any any of these other things do anything crazy poison
damn it nope i'm gonna be like giving out pamphlets
i want to see you do a lot of box steps now okay
100 box steps go oh no let me buck box steps lots of box steps
all of you do everybody get in there do box steps
all right can i like distract people to come up here and then make them do box
steps i want to see you do a lot of box steps
now what if there's no more room in there
get in there i can do this i can help you i can show you how to really bulk up
looks like you could use a little more muscle tone
you can do it steps lots of box steps no freaking way
i gotta okay go build your strength give me 30 pull-ups
playing diner dash need a spotter in the zone
let's go hey let me see how much you can bench
let's go come on get over here still distracted
all right let's get him what about this guy over here go do box steps
is this guy gonna hear the guy getting killed oh Jesus
okay hold on so that's steven bradley taken care of
well done got it so he's disappeared two targets
remaining wait what did he land on somebody
did you hear that it was like all right i just want to see what happened
box steps now do 200 box steps now back to box steps two targets
remaining okay i guess i'll do box steps
is this guy all right he'll be fine he's having a
he's having a protein headache
the body's out 100 box steps go okay understood what takes precedence your
guy you were bodyguarding is dead or go do 100 box steps let's find out
steps lots of box steps you taking it i want to see you do a lock step
okay now looks like box step doesn't take over
you need to weaponize your body give me 50 pull-ups
absolutely see this you see this this is what your femur is going to
look like in six weeks under my program i always bring in
raw meat to show my clients just what they're fucking capable of
i'm gonna get up we're gonna make them do it again won't you fall off
get back up there go for a run that's what i was gonna tell you to do
i'm trying to get it to come on can i
i need the id of the perp can you tell me what it looks like
what do you look like i don't have that information
i want to see you sweat pull ups lots of them
i hear you man build your strength only 30 pull-ups that's understood
is this working sir i'm talking to you sir
i'm excuse me i'm working here i'm not moving
i'm not i'm not moving i ain't moving now that i just can't do
now that i just can't do sir now that i just can't do
say it anymore i was trying to tell him i want to see those box steps
all right oh but it's too much fun one more thing how many shots was that
way too many can i do them too just down here like some village idiot
not again no i'm not doing it again i'm not doing it again
yeah they were your gunshots why is there screwdriver on the ground
all right i gotta move on i can't do it anymore i would sit here all day i
really would i would be here for the next two hours
i swear to god that's not a joke people wonder like hey man what do you
like what kind of like what kind of games do you like to do
off-stream i wouldn't leave here until i had to eat food that's the only
reason why i would leave okay so uh one target down now i've
got i gotta get poison still looking for poison
i'm still a personal trainer so i can go in the back personal trainer room
god damn it on don't don't do this to me
hands over your head are you stupid put your hands up no more warnings you got
that what are you waiting for fire will
like a basketball coach who the fuck is this guy that just freaked me out
all right stop it i stop running into interesting distractions
stop having fun all right that's it that's it i'm out i'm out i'm out okay
one more one more thing just one more thing and that's it
no i'm out go out out got one done never leave home without a fucking apple
that's what i gotta say about that one let's get out of here all right i gotta
infiltrate that way already got one of three
done so i'm a personal trainer does that mean i have
i mean that's higher than security guard right listen here pal
i'm sorry but you are not getting through all right fine
still needs poison damn it there's so many things to poison
oh i just like took that guy's tip i'm really sorry
but what's that i thought okay that's i thought this was food
it's like who look at that looks pretty good doesn't it
steaming nice delicious like hot dogs or whatever the hell it is no
cigarettes safe no i hold on i feel like i should follow this guy
this is this guy's alone he's a security guard
no too risky it's too risky i'm not gonna do it looking fine today sir
okay what wait like the poison in here oh there's absolutely poison this is
like a tool shed poison there's gotta be poison in the
tool shed sure i saw something i guess i'm just tired
there's no poison in the tool shed how is that possible
oh no this is bad they got me in a pickle i'm between second and third base
right now which way do i go okay out this door okay what about
upstairs i gotta save oh we're good what is this
looney tune shit all right this is where i was before
trespassing right now but that's all right i remember this is the ice
oh right okay okay i remember don't do it all right i gotta go back to
down that area that was before straight through this way all right i
have not been this way at all any intel potential intel then i would
suggest you simply stay in the shade but i promise you the sun is not as strong
here as it seems my cat also had a rare skin disease
i'm sorry to hear that but seriously i wouldn't
worry just use plenty of sun tan i never married
somehow all i did was focus on the money and my sick cat
pims we both hated the sunlight but your skin looks fine i don't think you
need to worry i had an assistant karen karen she had one
simple job karen job ointments into pims's boiled
infested body gotta find an oint kin not kim karen's ointment
oh i'm sorry i i have no opinion about oh
pims was my love and that stupid karen suggested that i put her down
isn't that disgraceful fine karen well if
our cat was sick so i had her put down
what karen i mean pims lived another six years
so you're a murderer pain but she only existed to make me happy
what as all do just kind of said that well
um i suggest you stay in the shade don't you get it
give me help we'll do i think it's five o'clock somewhere on the planet
cocktail hour have a lovely day you too i know man
seriously okay yes right enjoy the game tonight
why are you all up in my face mr we're really rooting for you this year the
championship so i guess that was just kind of a
thing to have there all right what's what's this beach ball
can i go in the water i guess i can just kind of go in the water too
i'm gonna play the part guy fishing guy fishing guy fishing guy fishing guy
fishing nothing else matters guy fishing who cares about anything else
push guy push guy fishing push the guy fishing push him over
okay i'm giving you something to fish i scared the shit out of this guy this
guy was sleeping standing up at least he has another one oh no wait
can i get the fishing rod hold on where'd that come from i can't not
pursuing a career in sports are you don't do it don't do it as much there's
nobody looking and i mean like there's nobody looking
i'm a personal trainer god damn it you want to talk shit now
yeah okay fuck this guy watch this hey wait a minute you but you can't throw
it shit that far wait i probably should have kept the
hammer okay now let's do the the true timeline not
this one let's do the true timeline that's no that's a gun
he was alive
did you see the thing over his head he was still alive
and then he just kind of i don't know he just died i guess
no this is not the true timeline i didn't mean to take the gun out
oh you know what who cares wait dump him wait what i can't even take his hat or
anything ouch well okay it is the true timeline
nothing happened he'll make excellent bait he just wanted to fish on vacation i
know i'm awful every guys we're chaotic
add that's how this game is played no no no it's
neutral add neutral adhd so this is a restricted area
idiot get out of here yeah idiot all right i can take out that camera
wait what's over hold on who cares about money camera it doesn't matter
there's something over here there's gonna be some secret weirdo over here i
know it come on give me a secret weirdo npc
no too bad okay okay it's a real life right that's what i said back to the
true timeline this is the real one i can't save it ever again
all right that's the grill master i get down there it's nice
i just want to get him huh shit
goes in the green bin we okay is he gonna use it use it come on
i was trying to get to land on the grill i can get that on the grill i know i can
wait a minute no yeah this is it i need to spray tan
no saving i didn't save i loaded what are you talking about
i like it down there stop attaching to his head
stop attaching to his head stop attaching to his head stop
stop doing that there it is huh fuck i'm gonna try this one more time then i
don't care just bear with me for a second back it
up a little like right right there i i don't i don't think this is
particularly funny i just want to see if i can do it
no i can't do our you doing the carnival stream
no well the carnival stream would be if there was 10 people in here and we all
were like ouija boarding their hands on my mice
and we're all trying to pull in different directions at the same time
all right let's do it can i knock it up there from here
drink besides the sea scares me you never know what's down there in the
deep depths oh lighten up a bit enjoy the food i just
want to get back okay what's that what's that
someone to push someone to someone to push off
okay this is wait this is sorry
i did it yeah i don't all right oh fuck that was a great pencil dive too
i like it down there it's nice and cool shoot the fingers no don't you don't
even need to shoot in that scenario just run up and stomp on my hand all
right here we go this is gonna cause a spray which is
in turn gonna get this guy over here i'm gonna drag him over
i'm gonna pull him over it and steal his like expensive ski suit
why why are you coming over here all right i gotta pull this guy down or
something why are they in these outfits oh wait
investigating distraction can i take these clothes i was gonna hear this
right i don't think so let's do an apple just to be safe
somebody know what i can't take these clothes
where's the guy that was just over here where'd the grill guy go
i gotta use the apple i have to i mean you break it you bite
get over here oh my god what are you doing okay
i think it's just time to get up there okay we're good
what is it disguise search for the thief in the facet
what the hell am i wearing what is this okay we're good
let's go it's so hot out for this turn stove off
no i'm just gonna leave it on whatever start gas leak no don't need it
all right what's over here hot dog buns people were waiting and then they got
out of line you got some all right you got three
different diets here very interesting stuff and then you got
this person don't care no do you leave the i gotta save it
because i see propane tanks those are mcdonald's fries
all right looking for the thief in the facility
and there's a target up there you're not funny
is this are you talking that's a very uncomfortable way to go in this pool
shove guy off plank no that's good today sir
that's way way low hanging fruit for me hey guys i already got a low hanging
fruit in my hand right here looking for the thief you wait a
minute i'm gonna steal that book motherfucker i
can see you he's gonna shove that book down the front of his pants and try to
walk out speak okay speedboat key
a key to a speedboat there's one docked at the pier
nice escape route
i want i just needed to know if it could work come in i just needed to know
i'm just gonna surrender all right that was just uncalled for completely
that came from a crime he dug himself into a hole the stupid bastard
pirate will
let him fight let him fight let him fight
they're kicking the shit out of each other
npc random dialogue is a blessing on all of us it really is why why is
probably going this way all right i gotta find a thief i'm looking for a guy
that's stealing stuff let me try to get upstairs
thief talk about something have a conversation about stealing
anything wait a minute was what how do i get
how do i get down there how do i get down there wait there's a thief down
there how do i get downstairs all right i need where's the map not for
at least a month she goes off to one of the other islands on the last boat
all right i need staircase staircase staircase staircase goes down
over here i've heard mr williams is a bit of a handful but i thought she was
really in love with him i guess that explains why
there's birds oh what what did i do i just like walked over here oh my god
um how do i get down let me see the map right there on the other side
maybe i can go from here through here it's on the other side of the building
give me that it's like in here have a nice day
wait what this is a door is there a secret pull the book thing
there's a secret door right here oh shit all right
um where's the oh i can't i need to make a distraction in here so i
can do the evil lair all right what about the tv
yeah turn tv on say what oh i didn't know you were here
what the fuck man this sucks
okay uh right here do i know you okay i can't it's not gonna work like
that i have to distract the this lady somehow
i'm thinking i'm thinking apple right in the corner over here or
uh no hamburger i have to keep to the end of the game it's my left for dead
gnome coin excuse me
got it all right how do i close the door
good now what's this all right new clothes or something i need clothes
i need something anything oh fuck oh no get out of here get
out shut out it's four fps he died with a super gun oh get
i don't know close hurry up okay the camera the camera's gotta go
i need i'm gonna shoot this with a one bullet let's see what happens if i do
this will anybody hear this they don't know
how to get in here fuck it they don't know do you think the you think
the maid knows how to get in here investigate surveillance footage let's
go is this my room who's that that's the guy
reading the book that i told you about that guy
yep it's something to that guy i knew it fresh food though that's nice
it's delivered here i have no way to get into the safe
all right this is where i have to be careful so what do we got here a scanner
all right this is i i'm trespassing right now is this camera
i made it through all right here we go obtain the usb from the thief the thief
is even further down there's a whole aquarium down here
all right should i turn should i take this no i need a wrench i don't know i
can't do it what about in the boxes nothing okay even further down
numbers check out there's the giant jellyfish whatever it is
we haven't had to do this subdued the chair remember how long it took
is the chair alive never seen this patrol was so freaked out i think she was
getting claustrophobic or something give me it
whoa back up buddy i'm married computer stop being so bad
i just wanted the muffin what the fuck is this guy talking about
sure it is all right i gotta keep going further down what do we got
poison turn off ventilation system okay get a water wait create a water
distraction i don't need it what oh did you do this what did i do
this i couldn't go down from here yes i could
you're in big trouble now mister hey yeah just you drop
the whole everything came out in his mouth and he
just spit it all out one by one
oh shoot no some scooby-doo shit right there
all right stop we need this you're the area no don't do that
okay here's this one right here you didn't listen he said
don't do that i don't know why down here is making my it's
i'm dropping a lot of my computer is having a lot of problems down here
weird because up there it's a gigantic open
huge beach and i'm surrounded by four walls and my computer is dying
all right was that wrench i just saw one shovel
sure there's any legal item no where am i going i gotta go
where's the thief down maybe it's on the water
keep going that's as far as i can go now i gotta go through here
and then down again this way and further down all right that guy
can see through my disguise all right easy here we go
shoot the glass no i'm not gonna shoot the glass
i need the usb from the thief it's very important
security break room if mr williams discovers that i've stolen
there we go that's the thief found the thief
good afternoon sir what what what do you mean what wait wait wait wait where is
it where is it where is it where is it where is it
what do you body find that's gonna hurt
this wasn't the thief why did it say to come in here
command anybody there come in fresh disguise
oh fuck hey hey i need you to get your shit together where's the thief
we got a possible situation we need you to stand up and fight the aliens
you were knocked out by any description on the possible suspect
he's in some type of uh costume yeah i know exactly who you're talking about
i don't get a mask on now though well he knows
he didn't go down he didn't even go down
still looking we gotta use the big stuff for this guy
didn't even go down no sign of the perp go with that person
my fucking computer sucks
he's gone hey i could use some backup over here boys
come in do you copy we got bodies all over some assholes on a killing spree
try running anybody copy no sign of any perp
moving on john wick come on flood it flood it
sorry lady my computer sucks shoot glass i just shot the glass a thousand times
what do you mean shoot i was just shooting glass what do you mean shoot
glass all right i just shot glass this guy's not the thief that's the thief
yes hello miss vitro just leaving a message
hey sweetie we're in the middle of something
oh no got it i got the intel where is it what tyson secure
i told you it was the guy with the book i told you it was the guy with the book
upstairs the guy with the book i knew it remember i said that guy with the book
he's gonna stuff it in his pants he's gonna get out here it's a guy with the
book upstairs check this out watch this let's
fuck the whole thing up i can't get out i don't know how to get out
shoot glass shoot glass shoot glass shoot glass and shoot glass and shoot glass
see can i stop with this now i forgot i fucked it up sorry
voicemail again yes hello miss vitrova just leaving a message
it's me i well i have the item you asked for
i have i mean it's not on me of course it's in my locker
anyways please come by the villa and pick it up
this if mr williams discovers that i've stolen
well please just come and get it hey sir i fucking can't help it wake up
my computer sucks it's the key the clocker key
right i had the first time shit my computer's having problems
it's hard to focus lower the settings don't matter i'm running on a fucking
four-year-old hardware yeah four-year-old hardware matches your
four-year-old brain for not upgrading it
don't throw this at her wait i need to now this guy's gotta go
right now quickly apple break his neck close it stand up we're good get the
shovel no put the shovel down apple break neck
same thing cheeseburger let's see how you react to the cheeseburger scenario
where'd you go where'd you go uh go in why are you not going in there what are
you doing what why would you know i think i just found
some sort of weapon over there all right stay put what weapon i found a
weapon what's a weapon there's a shovel
what you don't this shovel on the ground what a weapon
left the weapon oh it's a fucking gun god damn it
okay we're good we're good anything else
get cheeseburger let's get the new disguise on
all right i now am in complete and total access
unlock the door get me out of this fps dungeon i'm in
bingo got the usb stick the usb stick supposed to continue to spread the stone
from one of the human orders okay i got what i needed check this other
locker too might be some secrets in here nope damn it there is probably a
secret in there that i can't get now let's get the apple contact miss
vitrova it's gonna get out save it just gotta get out of here
and who might you be get ready to laugh get ready to laugh get ready to laugh
here it comes get ready to laugh
that was the funniest thing i've seen all day i think it's funnier every time i
see it every single time it pops up on the screen it makes me laugh
harder oh wait no it don't work please get me out of this
down here sucks get me back to the open world
and my computer's fps can all right where's she
should i get a gun is this illegal like with it but should i
i mean does this make sense to make me to use this
what did i i mean i am a security guard i'm trespassing but i'm a security
guard yeah that's me no wait that is me
everybody in here knows this is bullshit i all right what is it is there any
disguise in here oh this is not good um i have too many
items all right just get rid of like the like
the soda can to get rid of the soda can okay
uh actually it's gonna work out i think in my favor a little bit here
i think we're good yeah we're good all right on my way back
uh okay we're cool all right have a nice day gentlemen
it's that easy all right good you're ready for war
i i mean all right i'm ready to call hey what's up
what's up the eagle has landed miss vertrover
i've acquired the item you wanted wonderful should we meet
yes we should oh i get to go to the spa yes i get to go to the spa i gotta get
like a massage hello no that's a sacred thumbnail i can't
get rid of it so is this one shit there's too many
sacred thumbnails which one uh i guess this one
wait it's me that's her it's me hi i'm mr reaper
yes mr reaper you can go right in miss vertrova is waiting for you inside
thank you have a good time oh nice outfit mr reaper
i see you're already doing what you can't fit in tactical like gear
follow me i'm ready for my massage let's see where this ends shall we
hey pal put it in the holster you leave us hello there sir hello
which one should i take this one you have the item with you
can i have it please here you are oh thank you so much mr reaper i can't
tell you how much this means to me mr reaper
i'm afraid things aren't quite as serene here
as they may seem hope is a double cross you don't double cross the guy that's
standing here like this and it was my plan all along to have
you eliminated god he's not well hasn't been for some time
we used to be together but his illness i couldn't take it anymore
i don't know why i'm telling you this he monitors my every move
i think he asked that girl to steal my information because he wants to
i don't know punish me kill me who knows anymore
just one more target to go
good work 47 lord miller vitrova has been permanently
uh but hold on there's more to do there right it's not just i can't that's
that's too simple that's the simplest possible way
i shoot you in the back with a shotgun guns and hitman no you don't use guns
and hitman hitman's like batman if you use a gun you're doing it wrong
that's therefore all my guns are now on the ground i'm mr reaper
i have an appointment yes mr reaper you can go right in miss vitrova is waiting
for you inside have a good time thank you oh nice outfit mr reaper
i see you're already doing what you can't fit in
follow me i love how it's a storm let's see where this ends shall we
thunder and lightning shows up what happens if i just let her
kind of go just monologue to me watch she's ready watch this guy
i want to see how quickly this changes i'm gonna stand in the spot that she
wants to monologue and she's gonna be pissed
take it here you are i'll tell you how much this means
i'm slowly beginning to understand that your monologue spot
oh shit she got him he's not where hasn't been for some time we used to be
together but his illness i couldn't take it
anymore i don't know why i'm telling you this
no too too much comedy i'm trying to think the perfect thing scissors
no i think he asked that bell to steal my
information hammer apple he wants to i don't know
punish me kill me who knows anymore sounds hard you wouldn't even die from
this i sometimes wish oh disappear you know
she just stepped on a cigarette with her foot
then i'd be free anyway i shouldn't bore you with my personal
problem let's get a massage you've been very helpful
and i will honor my promise and make sure that you get the discount
perhaps we'll see each other at dinner
we're gonna get a massage sounds ideal excellent
well if you'll excuse me i have a few more target to go
good work 47 lord miller vetrova has been permanently
retired wait can i get a massage
give me a massage can i have one how do i get one
i want to get one how do i get a massage i want one how do i do this
i gotta change my change clothes okay um change i need to be in uh
robes or something right and changing room come on i need to change clothes
who the fuck's calling me this storm is insane
and there's no god knows any clothes i can take i'll get out
okay here's the plan i have to find somebody who's on vacation
knock them out and then steal their clothes right
you're looking a bit tense mate yeah i know nice fps storm
there's nobody on vacation here come on i want to get a massage
this sucks i want a massage i think someone's in trouble
command you can't be here i just wanted a fucking massage like
what the hell messed up that guy
well all right fuck it well at least we get to do this again
why does a worker have a flashbang that's a great question
i can't get a massage oh well i'm gonna eliminate
immediately if she gets more than two words out then i lose
more target to go good work 47 lord miller vetrova has been
a key grants access to the haven villa on haven island
what oh shit all right haven island let's go hammer get up there what are you
doing i can't get up here can we stop the
thunderstorm please all right so now i get the key
this should take me in here i gotta go up there eliminate titan williams and
then i have completed the mission he's upstairs i'm dressed as a security
guard so i should be all right hey how are you what
what i can't go that way all right we'll go out this way
all right hold on we got a machine up here missing poison missing poison
i'm supposed to poison the poison medical cabinet
right oh that's down all the way back there was that cabinet i couldn't open
before all right this should get me out here
we're gonna play it really really safe here
got guy right here save it check this out guys going over no he's not got yeah
he's going over the edge fuck him you know what i mean
that is tyson williams ceo of haven a reputed paranoid tyrant williams is
known for his bad temper and heavy handedness
hey who the hell i i can't push him what why couldn't i push him don't even
think about it buddy do the right thing and show me those
hands i will fucking shoot you if you don't
listen to me and put those goddamn hands up
you have been warned i will open fire i'm gonna fill your head
feel good this is giant bathtub holy shit all right but my cpu right now is at
like 22 percent what the fuck is doing this for okay
here we go nobody in here just knock them out
that's all i need got it okay who cares now
that guy's out nobody knows nobody has seen it
it's now an opportunity what do you have on the ground anything
nothing no nothing i'm already wearing that disguise
what is that cool thing in the middle
whoa there's a huge there's a big spiral thing here that's cool
all right not allowed in here good day to you sir
shoot it i'm not we're not right not right now
i gotta observe what this guy does stay here
shoot it or riot i don't need to do it just wait
okay wait he's gonna disease what on earth is she oh i thought she
was leaning all the way back oh my god i have to make a distraction
through this window she saw it she saw it oh fuck it's
mr williams i understand you were looking for this
what i'll give him the usb stick wait get usb stick
hold on turn around turn around this way i can't be in here
i'm currently being the turn turn turn turn turn here
okay you want this i like you come with me
i'd like to personally reward you for your good work
oh so now i everyone doesn't care that i'm with them
and that's right i took you a place i pulled into second place now
i'm like i'm like putting my arms up and like making like like what are you
doing and i turn real quick oh nice job i got first place before
not anymore fucking idiot what's that sir yeah coming in here
yeah keep it real i can't by yourself come on seriously
this guy huh why aren't you listening to me
are you dead okay you're playing with fire now
i'm sorry i just wanted to be what's in here
poison onto you you idiot hey everybody wanted me coffee
boys
fuck how far back is the same
why did i do that it's so far back uh it was right there i just had to
press the button again it's all right wait there's an autosave right there
oh shit it really is saved by 2019 video gaming
we just closed it that's not very secure then sir
uh if i may say if all it takes is a little bit of body weight
let me just put this thing back in the safe
change the pin code should i be letting him do this right
that's that i'll wire a handsome reward to your personal account
my friend you know what i have a better idea
what's the better idea well huh i found a weapon
i'll deal with this you just hang back what the fuck are you talking about
what are you talking about criminal on the loose
he really did a number on someone here shoot the gun
47 excellent work you just live in it tyson williams eliminated
excellent work 47 that's all we need to do from here
miss hall should be able to extract the information needed from the haven
servers good work
i'd hate to be his neighbor my neighbor you just put this thing back in the safe
i want to see what's supposed to happen here change the pin code
huh i found a weapon calm down calm down i'll check it out right
all right gary lost it sing back in the safe
then he just changed the pin code he did it you already
changed the pin code that's that i'll wire a handsome reward to your
personal account my friend wait is the guy he was supposed to
the guy that he wanted to have kill me just left the room
i guess you just got promoted a personal bodyguard
thank you mr williams now mike's been getting on my nerves
for months now the man's got no sense of personal space
you know this promotion is a once in a lifetime opportunity
what's it called what's it called but what's the thing that that auto locks
onto their heads is it just called headlock aim assist
is it in gameplay weapon aim no mission timer difficulty
hud aim assist off it's not doing it
it's not in subtitles it's called fast target
there's no option for it the most of it rest assured
mr williams i will no your new outfit's in that locker behind you
i'm just gonna do some work in here for a while make sure nobody comes in good
fucking
actually kind of comfortable
wait he changed the pin code though how many does it take to kill him
why is he still alive why is he still alive i'm just trying to make this quick
is it gonna wake him up are they cold oh i just want someone to come in and find
him like this it's like i need help in here i don't know
what happened to him he's acting like a real weirdo i'll get the outfit was the
outfit outfit nice tyson williams eliminated excellent
work 47 that's all we need to do from here
miss hall should be able to extract the information needed from the haven
servers good work 47
fingerprints on every item she's dead no i all my stuff is on the ground hold on
is that a camera guy in the diving board just
i i all right that's it and then i'm taking off the plane
um no i i can't i gotta get out of this
um block hole no i'm out i'm out i'm out i'm done
like honey mustard can i'll do it another time i'm done i'm done i'm
there's the i can take off the plane
i don't know gun i'm feeling uh so you uh how do you not have a gun
he does i did it na aim what do you mean na aim that's like
3000 meters away what are you talking about
a lucrative opportunity got it let's see what out what i unlocked here
the bad boy the tyrant the confidence artist usb
there's so much cool stuff great supposed to potassium
no pain no gain 32 000 experience points looking good that's probably good enough
for like a two three star rating it's a 40 41
it's a lot of experience all right worker for rating
zero now that that doesn't work like that that only happens when a restaurant
doesn't have the restaurant needs like three ratings
on yelp to get a star i haven't played three levels yet that's
the problem reached haven island level six i can
stash in the laundry room restaurant storage room
i can get a pirate saber can start at the shark hut
shark hut remote gas device mission stories completing a mission is just
the beginning they're meant to be played more than once
multiple plots to uncover characters known unlocked during once you get the
over story the last result you complete the following missions
the water horse oh let's do this one right now
the water horse uh concealed we'll just do the uh
the chrome one take the pirate sword what is this just screw explosive pen
all the duck frag let's take okay grenade
concealed weapon that's fine take the duck
explosive remote concussion collect the pale duck
all right let's do it duck all right i got it
i got the duck welcome to the moldives so what is this this is another mission in
the same area the haven island staff is ready to
receive you under your assumed identity as tobias reaper
yeah a professional thief looking to retire from a life of crime
it's the same mission but ludmila vetrova can be found in the public sections of
the island primarily tending to client needs
all right so what what about that uh didn't what about that other guy
when they're it's a snowball it's not gonna knock anybody out
did i have it in the freezer hey psycho holy fuck that thing's
crazy
all right exit him hold on a second what's um i thought i had like another
mission to do campaign sniper is at the okay hold on
yeah right right right this is the campaign
briefing the last resort no no no no challenges mission stories here we go
take a deep breath follow this one the shape changer follow
and the water horse follow okay so i'm following the water horse i can only
follow okay take a deep breath this is like a doctor
oh it's just a different path with different lore i see okay
let's try to do the doctor or the um or the jet ski
horse horse okay let me see what it does there's also stuff to do in this one too
aren't there like other little things to try like yeah there's a contracts too
this is the last time i'm gonna play this game all right let me get my weapons
back that way they were but hitman is done what the
shortcut will start there this was the final dlc right
they're not doing any more app for hitman 2 right that's what i kind of
took out of that whole thing all right uh i'm gonna take this thing
this just looks dangerous and then i will take
a um i'll take the duck everyone take duck
let's go for duck i fucked it up already he already screwed it up so
is there one more expansion i was under the assumption that this is the last
one all right let's go hitman 3 is coming
welcome to the moldy all right let's do it new mission story i'm going to do the
doctor blood money's good too yeah they're all
good absolution is the only real it was all right it was kind of a
different game doctor
the pool bar later on i'm sure mr williams
mr reaper is it not welcome to thank you
are you one of the owners yes indeed i'm ludmila vertrova co-owner of haven
and your gracious host for this day i suspect we'll be seeing more of each
other today i suspected too sure of that miss vertrova
hey buddy this area is off limits your late booking has me intrigued
what the fuck are you talking about in the meantime our staff will take good
care of your knees don't let the grass grow under your feet get moving
come find me when you're ready mr reaper i'm talking to somebody we have lots to
talk about if you don't move now we're gonna have a
problem okay um we'll see you i'll see you around
giving me no choice face the ground i'm taking you in
vertrova can you do something can you please do something about this
what the fuck good work 47 rudmila vertrova has been permanently
retired i needed to talk to you apparently
i don't want to do it how do i put how do i stop
what's the no she's dead okay i where's the doctor i want to know why
i was too i was talking
put the duck in the bath what the hell is going on up there
help me basketball coach coach i need help over here
there's a psycho we need help
i thought you ran all right you're fine i think there's a fire over there
a lot of it there's a fire there's a fire
why did that happen there was no reason for any of that to happen
the guy freaked out and started talking shit talking shit
all right was i trespassing so i'm trespassing i'm having a conversation
with somebody owns the entire resort and i'm trespassing you know it's there
needs to be an insanity meter on the right side of the screen
that was probably like a two-thirds full insanity meter
oh the doctor right so i gotta get in there and
let's listen in he did i'm here now it's amazing he's a pair to meet up with
some patient called tyson williams over at this big
i didn't even get the intel
yeah what are you what are you made out of gremlins what happened there
okay here we go thank you doctor fantastic work i'm my brain is insane i
thought those are cars on the minimap he did i mean it's amazing he's apparently
gotta do his doctor thing here meet up with some patient called tyson
williams over at this big villa on the other end of the island
on the other end of the island i can't believe i'm saying that
it's tyson williams has summoned a doctor to the island
you must be feeling under the weather you have some experience with
pain relief 47 maybe you could be of assistance
okay so nice here me oh i'm just gonna chill in the sun drinking mimosas until
i pass out oh the person on the other line is like
yeah um did are you in the middle of doing it
did you shit i couldn't grab him you know
okay watch this no i need to make it who the fuck is looking at me what
oh my god and this and this he was pretending
to shoot me with the gun yes anyone copy the plan still stays the same plus two
percent insanity that was not insanity that was me being
seen by the guy from behind here we go i had an opportunity there
i got here i'm gonna make this really really easy
we're gonna guess where i am yes he did i'm here now it's i fucking didn't even
let them do the fucking story to give you the intel to progress it
my other fucking name is somebody said you're worse than the new twitch font
az those are fighting words okay you're never gonna guess where i am
i don't know where are you you're here it's great it's amazing doctor
meet up with the patient tyson williams there he is somewhere
on the other end of the head what are you doing here guys i i'm really you know
what i listen this is i swear to god what happened was
i fucking pressed x instead of space because i'm just rushing through it
i pressed x i climb up instead of like just fall down
god damn it i'm so sorry this is the last time this is gonna happen
oh i'm getting texted i'm getting texts who is it
i'm sure everything is all set to go you can get levels from the first hitman
what do you mean don't fuck this up he did do not fuck it up stay right
here don't touch anything he's apparently gotta do his doctor
and i'm saying it with some patient called tyson williams over at this big
villa on the other end of the island on the other end of the island i can't
believe i'm saying tyson williams has summoned a doctor
it's so we never have to see that again
this is a hard crash too the whole thing turns oh shit god damn it okay um
i want to play this mission please wait it's this a there's a patch i'm
downloading a patch right now for hitman 2 i think i just got
crash booted out to download a hotfix or is this a cloud this is my yeah this
is the cloud sync oh okay well that makes sense then hitman
three oh by the way i've had that germa
985 is squashed into like four feet tall image on the right monitor the whole
time i just can't i have an alt tab and close
it it's still over there was i just destined to not play this
mission this kind of story here i think it's
possible show it i don't need to show it you guys
know the one i'm talking about i could be describing 500 different
pictures by the way no we don't no we don't no we don't yes you do
yes you do do the challenge instead of the story mission
yeah that's a good idea so let's go to uh we have escalation is it game modes
no no this is wait no destinations okay let's go to
uh heaven island and then challenges the last made the last resort so i just
i pick one of these aren't there other missions inside of
these though or is this the i remember the other ones had
um other stuff is it escalations the hell is this sniper assassin new
content haven island no i already have it is that it's just
different targets yeah i've thought there was
i remember from the base game contracts trending elusive target the captain
should we go for the captain let's try it good morning 47 target is
ruthaford a captain who works at haven resort the owner tyson williams has
contracted us that he wants ruthaford dead for causing many accidents at the
resort including sinking boats okay just yeah why does
why can't you just fire him that doesn't i don't understand
flash phone what does this do oh that sounds cool
all right let's get him captain ruthaford ruthaford ruthaford all right
eliminate captain ruthaford so you can make a contract for this guy mr reaper
that's pretty cool eliminate the captain all right the captain's in here
upstairs i wonder how difficult this is going to be
go just go in there and just poison them this is not going to be this easy is it
i think i just did it i went i think right
hey so i just i just have to dump the guy and listen to the story okay
is there an actual story they're all easy to do it like this
all right let's go so i'm gonna say i'm gonna tail him for a little while
so he does he's up here drinking comes out here this way and then
we're gonna listen to what he has to say
soon as i find the rest of this here treasure map treasure
will be mine that means it's probably a treasure easter egg on the island
right i would think so back off a little buddy
you're starting to freak me out does he only stay up here
hey buddy how you doing well it's poison is the easiest thing
well at least the one that's the most i'm trespassing i know
does he go anywhere else okay guys quit screwing around here okay he doesn't
he doesn't look like a person he looks doesn't look a person to me
he looks like you know gordon ramsay's show when he puts on a bunch of
masks and makeup and stuff and pretends to be somebody in the restaurant that's
what it looks like
this guy's doing undercover boss right now all right so very easy
we found out here but can i be like come here
come sit with me i don't think so uh all right so i need to make a
distraction this guy only does this so we have to
make a huge distraction call i can use the phone what
it's tobias reaper i read your note excellent
i reviewed your file
we're not doing that looking sharp okay what about rubber duck
and all right here's my plan no i don't have the rub duck anymore
so what if i just what if i just flash me in the eyes
shit young man god damn it
you're all what am i thinking i could easily well the phone's
probably ruined no can i throw it that high i don't want
to be in the view of this guy got him here we go let's get up
there
like a little men in black thing just like right in his eyes
oh my god that was a fucking
nuclear bomb
holy shit that was too i was like just unexpected completely
what the fuck i never like there was no reason why that was gonna happen in my
mind you thought that scared you holy fuck is
that what that thing's supposed to do no way what is that thing supposed to
do he wasn't even knocked down that guy is a real
a real fucking wait a minute hold on i can't uh okay so there actually is a
treasure map just in case anyone i want to find the
treasure so i'm just gonna say i don't care i mean
all right pick it up pick it up it's not gonna do it again right
i want to see this from a distance i'm very far away
that was not that was not as ridiculous
i think it was some kind of device yeah some kind of device
i want that i want that treasure map i guess it's everyone's kind of uh
all that everyone ran away i think i'm gonna get him over here now
this guy looks what are you doing awesome what what's doing that's the way
to do it i like it what is he doing are you all right
yeah i'm awesome yes i think he's grabbing
i think he's losing his mind that's the way to do it i like it that's the way
i'm not sure what your what the way is i'm awesome are you trying to shake with
shaking hands i'm awesome yes i don't think he's gonna move
that's the way to do oh my god don't we weren't gonna get out of that
i just want to i just want to know all right that's it
um that's it that's it game over check it
that just about enough of this oh yeah we aren't gonna do anything we're gonna
go right we're just going right for the kill
who's looking at me what oh okay you kill somebody to starfish
now let's go
i killed him with a starfish wait seriously you can actually do that why
is it a knife what this makes no sense
okay i i got the treasure map no stop oh my god i can't it's my treasure not
yours damn it fuck explosion i'm gonna
you woke my parents up twice i'm sorry all right just do the plan that i had
originally for the love of god watch this i'm just going all the way out
what's going on over here oh god damn it nobody does
no i shouldn't ask but mr fokker boy who just checked out
looked please i need help it's horrible
all right i got where's treasure map part part of an old pirate map
looks like a palm tree what do you mean part of a map
this guy's out of the way i didn't looking for me nice try
and area is all clear please advise over okay hold back
but it's not over yet okay palm tree that's palm tree right here
trash is probably right here all right treasure palm tree
yeah
tree holy shit lady wow wow hi there looking for a treasure map
treasure treasure wait nothing over here
well that doesn't do anything for me though i don't want blisters i'm very
prone to blisters when i'm out of time so please
good job it's gonna be loud it's gonna be loud it's gonna be loud
it's gonna be loud you're gonna turn what are you doing
did you turn it on what are you doing what
somebody come pick it up
no no
all right i did it i did it i don't have to do this one anymore
is there any more sniper missions to do what about the treasure who cares
three new unique targets new gameplay 20 new mastery levels okay
i care uh what about this one is there anything else that i could do here
this one was crazy you know that's probably
um let me look at this just once more
we're probably pretty close to the end here i just want to make sure i do the
thing is wait what is this objective wait this is in new york
eliminate using electrocution what what the hell am i dressed as
what i don't want to be in this costume i have to
eliminate erna seamans by electrocution i don't have any items so it's just it's
a game of sneaking around all right you got it
sure you don't even need to sneak around i tried to throw it
come on snap out of it get on your feet this is a restricted area
do i have to stay in this disguise all right this time i'm not going to be the
fucking idiot electrocute the guy grab some stuff i have
to stay here so people are going to see through everything
what i'm gonna go car to car here go wait battery
i need that battery you can't save it oh no
this is gonna be hard shit okay everybody can see through
so i'm gonna oh god somebody's coming i can't yeah no i can't save scum
that's a disaster here we go i'm gonna have to do this
bingo let's go the camera holy shit this is really really hard
so i have to avoid everything shit i don't think i'm gonna do this one
this is too escalated for me i need to get a carrot
go pick it up yeah this might be too escalated for me
no safes coming oh don't know if i'll be able to do this
i can get to here can't go this way so i have to go up this way
all right slow down i got that person does not see through my disguise
or is it just trying to load what i need uh
put this down all right i can turn that box off
and then god damn it what oh fuck i can't go i can't leave
where is he how many people coming out okay
yeah bang left go here who's in here oh my oh my god uh can i can i do this
it's weird that a guy's a rabbit right now right is it weird
that's a little weird right that's a little weird coin
that's a little weird it's it's it's it's it's it's it i
i um
but i can't go over here how the hell am i supposed to get this way
to the left i think and then to the oh there's the manager
i don't know i have no idea i don't know this is there everywhere there's nowhere
to go i have to throw a coin for this guy
all right i'm gonna try it i'm gonna throw a coin we go one two three
what are you doing throwing this stuff around you stay here
oh fuck okay then
maintenance have a look at the deposit box room oh my fucking god
oh my fucking god oh my god oh my god what do i do
what do i do about this i don't have a good i don't have anything what do i do
what do i do what do i do what do i do what do i do somebody help me what do i
do what do i do vault i can't drop no this is
wrong throw something i only have the car
battery i don't have anything else to throw
there's nothing else to throw throw this at him no i have to electrocute the guy
downstairs i have to electrocute the i'm right
there should i punch him in the face and then run downstairs
punch and run punch and run punch and run punch him and then run
punch him and run i'm gonna punch him and run i'm gonna think that's what i'm
gonna try to do throw battery to space can i use the
wait important can i use the battery again
try going right after i vault i'll try it this shit out
i need that battery i need the battery oh
right out of the camera's view get the fuck out of here
battery save there is no saving i can't save it
all right so if i just overhand throw this at the guy will it electrocute him
no how do i do this just throw it in the water
okay i'm gonna throw it into the water that's water right
that's hitting the water currently correct
is it a shadow that's because you're i have to leave now
where's there an exit oh come on don't even
i have to get to the exit i only have one exit
wait how do i get out of here i'm taking the gun where's this gun
where is it let's have to run out the door okay all right easy
easy easy all right right there right there right there right there right there
right there right there right there right there right there right there right
there oh clean i did it clean very clean
see you later that was hard that was fun though
come on give me two three stars come on someone could hurt them so there's even
more to do here i guess technically not you did it
start with the standard loadout electrician with the bank rubber disguise
very cool three stars i'll take it so you just do
it faster is that how you get higher stars
so what's the next one yeah you just gotta go faster what about let's look at
the details fresh disguise silent takedown
unnoticed never spotted no notice kills no recordings at all non-target kill
how would you get the cop away without making them both get up
you know what i mean seems hard to do that with a coin but wouldn't they both
stand up all right we got another one if any
non-targets are eliminated you will immediately fail the mission
i have to retrieve the burial dagger i have to
kill these two with the burial dagger oh no and electrocution
holy shit yeah that's not possible i don't think i can do that one
so here's elusive target this is interesting good afternoon 47
your target is etta davis also known as the angel of death the target is a
retired nurse believed to have killed dozens of
patients in retirement homes and hospitals across great britain
okay her preferred technique is poison though in later years
she's begun to prefer blunt weapons and violent accidents such as falls
ongoing intercepts have tracked her to marrakech well i can only one chance
predictions that she's expanding her hunting grounds
i can only do this one time oh no that's not good while the target may look like
a harmless old lady it is certain that she will kill again
repeatedly given the opportunity the clock is
ticking 47 good luck one chance planning do i get to plan
anything i do all right let's do the let's take
the silver baller i'm gonna stay in the regular suit
fiber wire i never use small gold bar interesting i'll try it coins
okay i'm gonna pee before this because i only get one chance
yeah it's piss time it's been like almost four hours and it's time to pee
see you guys in a minute howdy so this is going to go very very poorly i assume
because it's been it's been like six months or so or four or
five months since i've been even on this map
so no idea we'll find out all right let's go this contract is an elusive
target when playing an elusive target the following rules apply
you must begin the contract before the countdown expires
if you die you can't retry if you completed the contract and successfully
exited you may not retry it okay you can't
restart the contract you cannot save your game
the contract briefing may contain additional fail conditions
start the timer now because i think it's a win for me
if i last five minutes five minutes from right now if i'm still in this mission
then i win good afternoon 47 we have been unable
to determine the target specific location
now it's too loud it's like it's like way too loud
it's super loud now i can't even imagine
what that explosion was like sent her a few hours ago
whatever you do don't accept a cup of tea from her 47
no tea good hunting it must have been so awful
all right so we've got where is she in regards to the map itself uh
let's find out my god where are you i don't even know where she is
oh my god this is gonna be hard all right we need intel
she's right there huh okay area discovered brick don't pick up the brick
sorry man but you're just making me feel a little uncomfortable now okay
what is this is him okay i can get up there
not allowed up there guaranteed hello i definitely can't go this way right
they're gonna be like stop listen here yeah sorry but you're not coming all
right let's go this way i'm assuming i could probably break
somebody in an alleyway oh screwdriver that takes care of
that and a wrench good to have cause an oil
leak here and i approached germa anyway really germa
something about germa didn't submit a twitch con
all right
nothing to wait kitchen no i gotta let's go i need to bring somebody
in the alley here and then i'm so paranoid because if i
do anything wrong it's over how you been there's so many people
that could just get an accidental wrench markets where the hell are you
now put that down i gotta get a military costume
oh yeah this isn't their film crew is there no intel on this either
i don't get any intel no intel or anything
that talk we had about blood sugar yeah this is one of those i don't know
where the hell she's gonna be because i can go in here she's not up
there i remember there's a guy up there he's a different person though
hmm she's not over here maybe i have to do something to get around
i don't know where is this lady is she blending into
she's not showing up red if crystal don't get involved should we take action
all right here's military costume right here let's see if i can get it
all right i want you to come over here okay examine the printing schedule
intel no intel we got a raid we got a raid from robots
just came in thanks a lot robots welcome everybody
we're currently doing hitman 2 dlc although this is not
relevant i don't think this is even dlc we're just kind of cleaning up hitman 2
uh hope you had a good stream i don't know what you're playing but
what were you playing was it a good game all right i'm gonna throw something
over here noita okay is that game for people
a lot of people playing that game looked interesting all right here's my
chance brick
fuck how did you guys hear that from beyond the wall
they don't even see him over here damn it killed
they're gonna wake him up i have an opportunity i have to take it i'm going
for it i'm going for an opportunity and i'm going for three
two one go for it here we go check it out watch this one three two one
i'm fucking bad i'm bad at the game i had it i'm fine
what is that noise somebody's running a generator over here what
who is that guy that guy was making a lot of noise
all right i know oh god damn it man will you please
all right any more actors like to come out of stage left
any more actors how many hey what happened over here
god damn it i lost there's no way i'm gonna do this
i don't even know what she is she's not even in the game
she didn't even logged in yet this is ridiculous what that's a real one
i can restart holy shit i thought i could i thought i could only do this once
so where is this lady then i i'm so confused
good afternoon 47 we have been unable to determine the target specific
we can't we don't know what she is sighted in the city center
all right the city center right yeah don't accept a cup of tea from her 47
wasn't it just in the city center just don't die
all right easy all right city center market square consulate square
so is she just in here what does she look like
i'm looking for an like an old lady
electronic street so where's the city center
i'm just waiting for her to cross paths this
is probably the city center right like right in here market square
consulate square i mean i would say that would be the city center
this is city center take a look at this shit
this is the center of the city if i've ever seen the city center of anything
my life this is the market so is this the city center
she's not like sitting up here or something right
you're just sitting up on the roof somewhere
that's enough i ended up in the same exact place i was last time
okay so she was in the city center a few hours ago but good luck
where the fuck is she good afternoon 47 we have been unable to determine the
target specific location but she was sighted in the city center a
few hours ago now then help me whatever you do don't accept a cup of
tea from why the hell wouldn't you say she's in the market i remember this
i'm just gonna go in this in the middle of the market and just literally walk
around in a circle
this is this is where's waldo is that what the whole point of this
this is where's waldo but i don't get to see every single person at once on a
piece of paper i have to walk around in the image what
the hell did you say stop talking stop talking somebody said
something here what did she say though i heard
rooftops okay there she is that's her right there isn't it
no get the fuck away from me how do i get on the roof and just like
in where's waldo instead of a guy with a white and red
stripe shirt and the hat on there's somebody with like a red and
white pinstripe shirt on not the horizontal it ain't waldo how do i get
on the roof from here all right roof how do i get on the roof
just fly there
roof access i need roof access it's not up there it's like where
up can i climb this the stairs over here but that just leads
i got like this stairs here okay distraction time
where's this on the map so i can remember where this is and okay so it's
right by the vase street here we go distraction time soda
stupid motherfucker guys very clearly i am
sir this is sir you hey what is she doing up here okay i can get her
vase street you got it vase street just banging she's right here we have
been unable to determine the target specific location
but she was sighted in the city center a few hours ago
whatever you do don't accept a cup of tea from her 47
no i won't good hunting what time did he give us again
sorry sir i can't let you through sir you are not authorized
he's gone do something
target eliminated the money has been wired to your account
oh fuck guys i can't restart the mission i have to leave oh no this is very bad
oh no this is very bad
no i did it it's okay if i didn't miss the first i panicked
there's nobody up there with her i went like left right
oh god that feels so i feel so drained i feel so unaccomplished right now
it's grayed out too and i did i did it but it's
i didn't do it i thought they were gonna be like three or four people up there
with her but there wasn't there were downstairs and they followed me up that
last time i thought they were already up there
i'm sorry that was still fun anything else going on
sniper assassin did i already do this did i do this i did this one
what's this one this is new this is a multiplayer
all right this is a sniper mission hitman multiplayer rage i remember that
i was so angry i was having such a good time on that stream too and it just
i i just i'm so upset that sword
former kandanyang national poet has been kidnapped
from his suburban home ladong defected to the u.s during a meeting at the united
nation some years ago and has been living under witness
protection ever since her targets are jin nu
long kwai and re thak three key members of sun po's military elite known as the
three targets the three are in singapore to secure mr and mrs ladong who've been
smuggled from the u.s in a shipping container the ladongs are expected to be
transported back to kandanyang for a public execution to celebrate the
birthday of the country's dictator sun po the targets are preparing to
transfer ladong and his wife to an awaiting car i have no idea how to use
the sniper i three are under orders not to allow han ladong to escape again
so keep this one quiet should the alarm be raised we expect one or more of the
targets to try to eliminate they're gonna run over there and try to
kill the hostages to be a success good luck is this
counter-strike 1.6 am i playing with a griefer i don't
understand okay one two three hostages must survive
and get rid of all the bodyguards this is gonna be impossible for me
come on i don't know about that i've got the level i don't have any upgrades
i have the default rifle i don't have anything else cool
all right fuck it let's go how do you zoom in
47 this is uh no diana this is 47 how do you zoom in the sniper rifle i
haven't used this one before that was a civilian all right we're
looking for i get right here that is captain ree thak aka spider
gifted recruiter and intelligence officer in the heavenly guard
okay and here that is colonel gin new aka the blade
vicious and fanatical colonel new has orders to eliminate ladong in case of
an emergency okay and then we've also got up here
it's coming down the stairs that is captain long kway
aka dragon eye and his nickname after taking a bullet for the heavenly leader
okay get rid of as many bodyguards as i can so where's the the action is here
all right i gotta make it i gotta make a plan here shift is breathe
i'm gonna wait till they all get down in the same area i can go for it right now
that's moving that's hard now now she's moving just take the shot take it take
it 47 the situation is about to get out of
hand 47 an alarm went off they're evacuating i did it i win
no god damn it shit oh come on are they still this they're
alive right oh he's going oh no no no no no he's gonna
go kill them oh my god i need i need a toggle
i'm a toggle guy right now holding down right mouse button is hurting me
oh that was pretty damn good that guy's on the toilet no refrain refrain
refrain you can't felt pretty damn good to me get
his face oh how many people do i have to shoot
i had all of them you bastard get over heavenly guard has been taken care of
got it i'll get an extraction team to secure the hostages excellent work
that was fun running in circles yeah is the only way to avoid it
yeah you just have that's it i didn't do anything fun
i did nothing fun i just shot people with sniper rifle i didn't get anything
that was just a tablet gamer i like the sniper rifle it's cool
how is that a tablet gamer there we go it's because see i needed to unlock
this stuff i got an extended mag flared mag well reduces reload time see what
i'm saying all right let's go back to um replaying
mission actually you know what yeah go back to the menu i want to do the next
one there is an iphone game that's made for this
now i know i've played it i also three-starred every single
level and hitman go kind of a good achievement i think if you ask me
and then this siberia i just want to see them first and replay them
so these two are dlc so my uh stream is not alive welcome to siberia 47
i could do something cool in this one instead of just headshot people
your destination is the privately owned perm 14 prison facility
located near the freezing siberian tundra here you're tasked with the
elimination of vitale reznikov try to kill somebody with an apple
and roman kabko renowned russian mobster with suspected political ties
roman kabko has been a prisoner might be possible for the past decade
but his function more is a second in command than a prisoner
now he wants out and has offered warden reznikov a bribe to facilitate an early
release scheduled to take place today kabko's offer comes at an opportune time
for reznikov it's like a swole golem united nations human rights kind of does
a string of recent news articles has exposed violence and even murder
as everyday occurrences in perm 14 our client suspects that kabko's release
could cause serious diplomatic issues both targets must be eliminated along
with reznikov's mercenary does the cold mess with how i shoot the gun
note that the prison's regular guards are not sanctioned targets now the riot is brewing in
the prison which could be used to our advantage since our client has asked we eliminate the
targets clandestine you will need to find a way to set the riot off and use it as a
so i can't just shoot people eliminate the warden roman and then the siberian tigers
mission is now active nice extended magazine nice it's already on there right yeah okay cause
a riot and then eliminate as many members of the mercenary death squad as possible so these are
the two targets see what i can do so i have to start a riot too so i can't just shoot guy so there
is that is the fucking window he went through the window he went through the window oh i'm damn good
47 code red everyone is evacuating i can't even i can't i'm gonna do it for real everybody relax
did that even kill that guy oh that range okay all right all right restart i have to start a riot
so he's right there oh that'd be so easy roman cadco high ranking member of the russian mafia
and about to be released from prison he's about to be releasing and up here is the warden
that is vitale resnikov corrupt warden here at the perm 14 prison facility okay
so if there needs to be a riot in here how do i cause a riot in here probably shoot one of these
things not yet though hold on he's just hanging out in there the warden stays up there i'm thinking
just shoot drop one of these what about on the other side anything interesting over here i think
i can just get this guy i'm i think i'm just i'm just gonna get this guy no one no one's around
right nobody else around here everybody's gonna be see that okay i'm gonna get it
all the way down there he's gonna see somebody right where is this dude coming up from the bottom
will he see this roman cadco looks to be violently punishing another prisoner
where it's not pretty oh fuck wait a minute what's that what does this thing do
shoot the faucet i'm gonna shoot the faucet about to be spotted
i didn't want to see that i didn't want to see that i was gonna be horrible
my stomach too late
last try last try and i'm gonna go i'm gonna start the ride immediately save the guy you killed an
old man with a starfish that was different circumstances though all right when he starts
to do that i wait i hold on a second here wait a minute when he he's gonna he'll let you he'll
let you get himself he'll die this is gonna spray water over here and he's gonna slam this down and
he's gonna die right i would assume that would happen so i shoot this
during the the craziness and then just let him do it i'm gonna try it let's just keep an eye on it
why is there another prisoner over here i could just get him right in the shoulder
imagine this guy pushes down and starts choking him walks out it's a guy with a bald head
i can shoot that i'm gonna i'm waiting for it because that's interesting here we go all right
that is roman cadco high ranking member of the russian mafia and about to be released from prison
press x to change bullet type wall piercing ammo shockwave ammo it's not pretty
boom okay here we go here we go uh-huh it didn't do what we thought it was gonna do
wait wait a minute that's impressive 47 47 they're about to raise the alarm oh
wait wait where is he where is he wait wait whoa oh is he he's on the move huh
i did it i did it where are wait there's people oh fuck no shoot this guy what oh come on is he
gone where's he going where they're going what the fuck was that what's going on they're over here
i'm getting shot at i'm getting shot up where are they shit damn it that's kind of collateral
where's his head what the fuck oh i got him god
shut up i don't see you down here that's the last target
it should cover our tracks perfectly
why the money as per usual i thought that i don't know the water barrel may have sprayed him
just wait till i get those points for the electrocution really there's an animal in
this somewhere oh shoot shoot it when it's in his hands oh extended magazine let's do it again
let's try okay i'm gonna try i gotta cause a riot too let's see what happens when i do this
i mean this is a riot right here right i mean just open the door perfect 47
that seems to have started the riot it should help cover our tracks
and hide any bodies in the rioting crowd 47 the situation is about to become critical
47 targets are evacuating secure any remaining primaries now
47 the warden is on the move he's heading for an exit i did not see that coming 47 well done
oh yeah it feels good i dropped it on his head wait where's the other guy
i gotta get him the head where's he going where is he going straight to hell all right no more
slow motion we're doing it straight up check this out straight up my dpi is so bad i have to move
my hand like 10 times when i zoom in that far what i just i just dropped icicles on somebody
all right i could do something cool for this guy something cool we got electrocution right here
he's gonna turn and no he didn't he went the other way i'm gonna
how did he die from that okay that was odd open the door what's behind the door something else
something else cool something else cool to do two more got it didn't even need to zoom in
last one right here i'm gonna make it cool something interesting something funny something funny
something fun he's going all the way up i guess i could do that no it's not gonna do anything
i'm just now there's nothing in the way i just have to shoot them that's the last target
the riot should cover our tracks perfectly that was really funny that last one so what is the
animal one is a duck all right let's go back i want to do what's the first one actual where
is waldo yeah but that's not where's waldo because it just tells you where they are
oh this is that is this the i remember this one all right i'm gonna do something cool for this one
i believe last time i did this as well it was i just shot at everybody and that was it like
all the other game modes good afternoon 47 i don't use weapons in regular hitman ceremony is about
to begin with lang and his daughter arriving shortly very rarely do i shoot off around proceed
directly to the open area where the groom and priest is waiting along with all the wedding
guests okay this is the demo level here preparing the wedding details and entertaining guests
i expect he will also attend the ceremony doris lee is on route via helicopter
this one released a year and a half ago my intel suggests she will not be watching
i know how it works no one's gonna be concerned about this 47 the situation is about to get out
of hand just like i did last time nothing changed since the last time i played wow he's trying to
stop him nice work 47 doris lee is making a break for it stop her now or it's over
lee has been eliminated you can get out of that you're in a helicopter the helicopter you could
just leave why would you get out and run something funny who cares about comedy gamer mode gamer mode
got him i love the shock waves they're fun what what why did he explode i don't know why that
happened ah that was so close it would have been sick here we go right now get it right in the
fucking face wait that's a bride no i i'm not shooting the bride she's in the maze
oh no what have i done i went into the maze this is the worst possible place i could have gone
she's stuck in the fucking maze she made it out okay you did it congratulations run get out get
out of here get out there's dangerous people up there wait don't you know these people she wants
to go to the maze again it was fun uh thank you tyler mcvicker for the uh raid a few minutes ago
thanks a lot welcome everybody okay i gotta wait i gotta get this one i want this one again but uh
yeah welcome guys this is technically the last of the hitman 2 the hitman 2 good afternoon 47
how much is this game and is it worth it uh hitman and hitman 2 respectively are some of the most
fun video games you could ever buy absolutely there's a never-ending amount of content in both
of these games how much is it though um i think it's 60 agent and the owner of the mansion and
its grounds is it ad no it's not an ad there's an opinion all opinions are not ads i mean that's
i didn't know that was over there all right we're gonna wait for something to happen i need to it's
got to be right at the you know when they're dancing i gotta get it during the dance that
is dorian lang the red robin former military engineer and father of the bride
mm-hmm and then up here we've got this person that is doris lee aka the gold finch
former hollywood stunt woman of Cheyenne descent interesting that i want to destroy the cake so bad
i just want to destroy the cake for right now it's the cake is a perfect it's just a target
for me to shoot at i just want to destroy the cake shooting cakes now 47 47 they're about to
raise the alarm confirmed kill on maison 47 47 wait that killed you must act now oh
shit attention 47 doris lee is heading for an exit lang has been eliminated doris lee confirmed
killed the cake exploded he died from an exploding cake i have to see it through now because that's
definitely uh that's that's gonna be an achievement it has to be but that was sneaky
got him i'm so bad come on right i gotta try to hit him in the bun wait that's not even a bad guy
okay that's all right i need more ammo in these each round oh these guys are wearing the same
coat so i'll make sure it's dead and head three two one god no got it that's a long way
can't running outside in a sniper fight well it's not wait there's a computer that went that hit
him somebody got away this guy's gonna get away this guy's gonna get away i need a toggle to aim
before i throw up on camera he's gone he's gone he's up he made it no he didn't money will be
wired to your account in a moment i saw i wanted i have to let it happen i i didn't get anything for
the cake how did i not get this for the cake that cake exploding cake is not an achievement
all right i'm gonna do it the way i'm gonna dirt it's he's dancing and you gotta get it right when
he's dancing last one all right we just hit here i'm not gonna zoom in zooming in is admitting that
it's time for you to fire that is dorian lang the red robin former military engineer and father of
the bride i've never seen what this ceremony looks like i just want to watch the ceremony
from a distance they take a while it's usually at about this point right now where i
lose patience and just start firing at the targets hasn't happened yet so that's a good sign
run out the 15 minute timer and don't do anything i get nervous that is guillaume maison the king
fisher former interpol agent and the owner of the mansion and its grounds okay i'm good i'm good i'm
good okay all right i'm fine everything's good to go it was i was a lot of resisting there
is that jim carrey in the dumb and dumber suit all right everybody they're over there so here
comes the ceremony you don't even that's a really really long walk the daughter down the hall they
went from the car that was almost a full five straight minutes and people would they're just
gonna go all right i does anybody even know the wedding's happening congratulations okay you nice
job i was fired that just like that just that was an immediate response it was like duck hunt fly
the issue thing in there that was almost seriously a like just a almost like an animalistic response
like think get thing okay here comes the tiny guy during the dance they're all going up to the
reception that's a really short ceremony so where is he going that way inside where's the bride
don't you take pictures all right here we go time for the toast and then uh the father daughter dance
and like the guy the butler whatever he's got to go over the railing nope
10 minutes remaining sure whatever there's an achievement to do this during all right wait are
they all going to stand in the same place can i just do a shockwave right into the ground
it's like i'm playing quake is the dad also the priest i'm confused that was a pretty great wait
hey hey hey hey you're about to be spotted lang is down nice work 47 47 an alarm went off
they're evacuating 47 is attempting an evacuation stop him doris lee is confirmed killed well done
like i see the guy can see me it's the only guy your only hope is about to get eliminated
oh no not the face we're stuck in the maze terrible bodyguard like i was standing still
asshole stop doing that toggle you idiot i'm trying i've shot that guy every single time i've
replayed this mission four or five times that guy dies every single attempt what like i fell i didn't
shoot that guy that guy fell down god damn it who the fuck are you what who is this guy he was
holding binoculars that means he he was a threat he could see me and he could tell everybody where
i am i didn't get to see the dance i didn't get to see the dance uh i just want to see this
i'm impatient well the guy had the binoculars and he freaked me out i thought he's gonna see me
this game is so much fun i can't do it again am i actually gonna do this another time
i'm not even gonna zoom in i'm just gonna sit here read a book for six minutes to distract
yourself i i don't have a book i don't have any book or anything here to do that with
uh what's this all right i'm gonna read the guy theory minute to win it for the connect uh guide
book okay so now here we go play as if you were a minute to win it contestant you will play 10
games and succeed at each challenge in less than one minute cool interesting stuff the goal is to
win 10 games in order to earn one million dollars when you do not succeed in a challenge you lose a
life that's not good if you have no more lives you fail you only have three lives so be careful
if you succeed in the challenge you will earn money and will be able to choose between continuing
to the next level or stopping and keeping the money nice pretty cool if you decide to continue
you will play the next level and be able to earn more money but be careful if you fail you lose all
the money you have earned during the tv program unless you have reached some bank stages a thousand
fifty thousand or two hundred and fifty thousand dollars for example if you fail after having
reached the fifty thousand dollar stage you will earn fifty thousand dollars that's interesting
the player has in the supermarket aspect of the game the play no this is terrible that's just not
an interesting thing to read at the same time this doesn't make any sense i don't have any books
i don't own a book truly keep reading it no i don't own a book
where we at almost halfway there i missed the dance no i did not miss the dance
the dance happens way way later just read chat yeah i mean that's kind of what i'm doing
what was the last book that i purchased uh probably a song of ice and fire a dance of dragons
it might be the last book that i purchased who would win in a fight you or a drunk you
me face cam your mouse for this no i'm not gonna face cam my mouse a song of ice and fire is now
normie tier uh i'm gonna put my hand up and get called on in the class i read that book 10 years
ago so i read that before the show even was like a fucking thing you understand i read that book
i read i read those books before the show even aired what are you gonna say now it's my favorite
tv show right now i don't really have a favorite tv show i sporadically watch random shit like um
hold on oh no we're good i don't know i've seen i've seen like three or four episodes of mr robot
i watched the last season of attack on titan it's my one anime per year that's the one it's
gonna be i i've watched the gordon ramsay's kitchen nightmares like for six or seven episodes
um what else oh uh uh peter pop-off miracle springwater infomercials i watched them at
least once every other night add that to the list uh what else have i been watching lately
that's pretty much it are they dancing that is dorian lang the red robin former military
what is he looking at the bride there's no reason to have binoculars out right now
what are you looking at you this wall you're looking at the wall you were just standing next
to that wall looking for me no we i got that that happened last time all right when's the dance
that is guillaume oh they're gonna be near the cake oh they're near they're right next to the
cake this is hard to do they're right next to the cake they're standing next to the cake
that looks like a good cake you know what i really like and i didn't even realize until i
had it very recently banana cream pie holy shit what an unbelievable s tier dessert if i could
redo my desserts banana cream pie would be at s plus there ain't anything better hold my i couldn't
believe how on the velvety texture of that banana custard and banana filling with that cool whip
whipped cream on top crunchy crust i hate pie pie sucks but banana cream pie is like the best
i'll eat it every time are they gonna dance yet or what chocolate cream pie i thought was my
favorite pie is the only pie i ever really ever wanted to eat that's till i had banana cream pie
and you just don't know until you eat it imagine not liking key lime pie banana cream pie sits
if key lime pie and banana cream pie are next to each other
banana cream pie is on a ladder that is 3000 feet tall key lime pie is not even close it's good
it's not close and then i thought now remember i said this first anybody any other streamers
that want to try to tell you that they came up with this they didn't i did a banana cream pie
filled donut i came up with that and another streamer wants to tell you that they did they
didn't i did where can i get one of those how are you gonna fit a pie into a donut no i'm saying
like the banana cream filling in a donut like a chocolate cream but it's a banana cream filling
that is doris lee no no no no i need the dance to happen five minutes what are they gonna dance
when is the dance trying to shoot the piano no stop aiming at objects does this actually
happen or does it was that just thumbnail now i want a banana cream pie what have i done
the bride left 47 there are just five minutes left of our window wait the bride left nice try
this has to be it right here that why are they all going upstairs i'm looking for the dance but
they're all going up here oh shit wait a minute hold on i can get them all i can get them off right
now i'm gonna get them all right now holy shit but there's no dance but why is it not falling
why is it not falling i waited so long for this why is it not falling 47 someone's onto you
hang is confirmed killed that's maison taken care of nice work 47 47 targets are evacuating
secure any remaining primaries now lee has been eliminated i got everybody
that was everybody no not that guy watch it watch it there's so many people there just
we ain't ever gonna see this dance i almost just shot the bride what a mistake that would have been
who's shooting funny funny oh you blew the funny thing you've disappointed everybody in the chat
room now i want to banana cream pie so bad why does this always have to happen bad here whoa
well i think i'll go down these stairs i wonder what's going on at the wedding i've been up here
for about an hour and a half just thinking about stuff contemplating i wonder if it's free drinks
what why are they going up here what are you doing up here you walked you went all the way up and
now you're going are you going all the way up this is not how you leave this is the top floor
like i was running over there to get hit by that there was no other reason and i don't know why
that was there yeah that was so far up in the top left away from everybody that i mean i feel like
people were like doing it like a drug up there they're like breathing in the fumes from the
air conditioner oh the the fire extinguisher i'm never gonna see this dance am i i can't i can't
do it again it did so many times let's i want to see this one i haven't seen this one
this one this could be they could be interesting things to do in this one too reward yourself with
banana cream pie i will oh tomorrow if you guys want to know what we're doing tomorrow
um i don't know i don't know what i'm thinking with this one but a game came out recently that's
been around for a long time from my understanding uh it's called numbers go up idle game yeah and
i just saw it and there's a million upgrades it's like cookie clicker but not it's like a it's a
cookie clicker 5.0 you play i'm playing that right now laugh out loud how the husband it's
been on a website for a while came out on steam recently that is captain rethak aka spider lily
gifted recruiter and intelligence officer in the heavenly guard you really phone it in tomorrow
what no i just saw it and it's a coloring book game too that i wanted to play look
tomorrow's stream is going to be different and then friday we're going to do the first community
night i also have code vain i want to play code vain too i don't know we might do this all tomorrow
i also have the floor as i'm not even gonna tell you i'm gonna keep everything when i'm
showing you my whole poker hand all right let's take a look around lots of weird generators and
stuff looks like colonel new and captain thack are having a meeting of some sort 47 meeting up here
was that meeting right here that is colonel gin new aka the blade
47 one of the hostages died right is over right i quaked them all
no no no no wait just wait wait a minute god i love this game oh just hitman just keep making
hitmans do i have to wait for like another five minutes i do but yeah so tomorrow we're going to
try some random there's an achievement to get one of these i know because i saw it okay i gotta wait
i need what's down here there's a car oh yeah i'm gonna drop a car on somebody absolutely guy in
the toilet rubber ducky right there's a rubber ducky scenario do it now why would i do it now
when the guy this guy's just a mechanic i'm not gonna do what else is over here a lot of
little random spots i'm not gonna kill this guy he's drinking on the job back to work
wait a minute what that was actually an achievement okay yeah no more happy hour
oh that's so funny all right what are they doing over here is captain long kway aka dragon eye
and his nickname after taking a bullet for the heavenly leader yeah i also have the floor is lava
that's a parkour game where the floor is actually lava they have to avoid it seem interesting
that looked interesting yeah it did it really did he showed his whole poker deck
oh no i did not that's the best thing about playing poker i've got two hands up my sleeves
you guys don't even know you guys aren't even gonna see them i think do they move them i think
they move them where are they moving them to are they not moving them not moving them
47 i'm seeing movement yeah spider lily is escorting the hostages towards the ship
so this is a good this is an opportunity what about i want to drop the car on somebody
that has to happen you already played goose game yeah i did we did that uh before twitchcon
this has something there's a lock is he fighting careful careful stop i got you don't worry
i mean i could just go do a double right there but that's not interesting hold was he just
seriously down here at the car did i miss that no he's gonna go to the toilet now i think
is he no he's going to this like weird office he's gonna drink out of the glass should i shoot the
glass out of his hand 47 the hostages are being transported to the ship you need to act now
i just tried to donkey kong that guy and it didn't do anything i thought i was gonna hit the stairs
and roll down hey hey hey hey hey look at this look at this look at this oh he didn't do it
somebody go under that car will you go down go down the stairs 47 they're beginning to suspect
where the hostages running guys don't just run did they not know
47 targets are evacuating secure any remaining primaries now
47 the blade is on the move i think he's running for the hostages wait let him get to ladon
he's running for the hot wait wait wait wait wait wait wait hold on
how does he know where they are we're good 47 what
has managed to escape the mission is oh i forgot i forgot about that all right all right all right
this is actually the last one this is it we're doing this lightning fast by the way i'm gonna
it's gonna be like insane how good this is here we go let's take a perimeter scan bingo 47 someone's
onto you no who could be fucking on to me 47 code red everyone is evacuating why do you take
this sword up he takes the sword out dragon eye is heading for an exit i can't
please just wait where did he go hold on hold on where's it
where's he 47 where'd he go where is he where's the guy's sword oh he's dead no i'm done i'm done
i'm done i'm done i'm done i'm done i'm gonna shoot the handcuffs off can you do that this
probably i'd bet you there's an achievement to shoot off the handcuffs them actually might be
i wouldn't be surprised if okay if shooting guys glass his booze bottle is an achievement then
47 one of the hostages died the mission is over you have to shoot the bag off their head
no i don't want to go here all right i think that's probably gonna be it for hitman here
unless i want to do one more thing all right this is gonna be an absolute dickhead run
you ready this is we call this one a shit for brains run that's every run no it is not i don't
think you know what that means every run it's not everybody i don't do this every run i don't do
what you're about to watch right now didn't work out the way that i thought it was gonna work out
didn't work out the way that i thought it was gonna that's not what i do normally i don't even
use a gun normally i don't use a gun two targets remaining good work 47
ludmila vitrova has been permanently retired good jeez should have brought the snowball
one more target to go so that's stephen bradley taken care of
why are they aiming at the tv they're aiming at the television who the fuck are you all clear
let's go wait iron good get some more weapons give me the gun that's a shotgun give me the
shotgun give me the shotgun give me the shotgun where is he he's all the way down he's so far
away you're playing this like hotline miami wait i remember this part i just i triggered the event
to have it be thunder and lightning out shoot him through the window who i i just get out of here
move whoa i'm almost there uh i um oh shit i'm dead i'm dead what what do you say a drink for
why was he dot i don't know i have no idea that's over no not one more time that
no not that's it not one more time one more time fine except i'm gonna do differently i'm gonna go
from i'm gonna do from behind i'm gonna go all the way to the back and then all the way forward
go get the job at the bank oh yeah i'll do that too two targets remaining good work 47
ludmila vitrova has been permanently retired all right now we're at this way right over there
there he is that door is not open how what is this a machine whoa that's awesome
i've rescued twice didn't work i have no time for this all right we're gonna go around the back
whoa bros what's this a machine like if you think it is sub if you think it's not
that's so stupid get up here i'm done i'm out i gotta get out of here i have to leave i'm out
i'm out i'm out i'm out i'm out i have to stop that's it i'm done you can't just sprint through
the mission i've already beaten it like three times that's it i'm done game over that's it
this is it that's it didn't even get the person i didn't even get the lady
all right that's it that's actually it that's for real that's it that's the end that's it that's it
that's it that's it i'm done thanks for watching hitman 2 guys i had a lot of fun games fucking
amazing wait there's one more thing i have to do i have to get the job because i knew i wanted to
do that i'm gonna go get the job this is the new york bank level i need to go get the job the job
there's a guy puking in a toilet over here somewhere i don't remember where but he's
somewhere over here remember this joke from last time we gotta see it one more time
fall i'm losing my fucking mind guys
i'm losing my mind okay to make the speed this up direct me left or right or straight
to get to the interview left this way am i going the correct way no okay i'm gonna go back there's
a mission story to guide you through it is there really okay all right mission story
the job interview all right now i'm ready yeah let's do it the job interview
disguise yourself as a job applicant so i wasn't going the right way
excuse me if you're coming through i have to sure go ahead like where did you just go
won't take a second sir you're good to go sir thank you i don't know that is i saw it on the
ground what if you want to get through i'm gonna have you down you just did you just did it thank
you please proceed fine all right this is it time to get the job for me you creep you're standing
in the doorway just blocking the door where'd you get that jacket i like it we got the similar
taste okay here we go have you forgotten how to open the door yeah yes why can i not save the game
climb in through the hole what's your problem this person has a key this person doesn't have
the key i need like a security guard to come in here i don't know where that guy's going but
i need a crowbar figured it out crowbar where's the crowbar here we go he's still a few approach
the reception this is it why the feathers come out of there all right it's time wait
yeah right i'm gonna play the part come on man it's me you're talking to me
oh please go away you're so not in my league i'm the person that's supposed to be here
it's me what the fuck are you guys doing they just made fun of me to my face
doesn't sound promising we'll give him the benefit of the doubt let me know when he comes out
we'll do thanks there you are feeling better i hope should i let hr know you're ready for the
final interview what the fuck don't do that toxic working environment what the fuck man all right
let's go i feel like a new man follow me please it's right down here best of luck in your interview
let's see where this will lead you to i think start grabbing trash cans like puking in them
i gotta keep the character going come on man hi i'm here for the interview good to meet you
i'm kevin and this is melissa we're both with hr and we will be guiding you through this last
test it's important to stress that there's no pass or fail here it's merely a standard
personality test meant to gauge how you'll put into our corporate culture all right if
you're ready let's kick this off okay i'm ready okay so this is a very simple test all you do is
pick a card and tell us what you see there now it's important to point out that there are no
right or wrong answers the right answers are about behind them spoiler for everybody watching
we already did this this is just cleaning it up yes i'm ready all right mr thomas let's proceed
then if you will please pick the card that most conjures up the word opportunity that one okay
this is an interesting one what do you see here take in the whole image please and in as much
detail as possible tell me what this reminds you of what the hell are you talking about
uh you i thought you guys told you guys said that it's the ones that are just right behind them
fucking really really stupid like i i i i have no there's no defense on that one
so i got plenty of offense it's nearly a standard personality test i can't defend that one
no way i can't all right i can say anything to you guys and it would this i'm ready what do i say
about that so this is a very simple test all you do is pick a card and tell us what you see there
there ain't nothing i can do about that that there are no right or wrong answers here it's just to
give us a better impression of who you are on a psychological level does that make sense yes
i'm ready all right mr thomas let's proceed then you'd be digging a deeper grave please pick the
card yeah there's no dude condors up the word okay let opportunity i know sometimes uh when i'm
wrong that's one of those times this one all right now look at it closely completely then tell me
do you see an animal or an object animal i see what kind of animal a bird an eagle perhaps very
interesting a forceful animal anything else it's feeding on something feeding on what a carcass
the scene is reflected in a pool of blood flowing from the body and do they not know
it's a vulture feeding on someone else's kill that's very graphic mr thomas yes brutal even
right very interesting observation mr thomas not what we expected but that's perfectly fine
let's take the next one shall we pick any of the remaining cards that make you think of
execution please this one the one all the way to the left this one good choice tell me what
is the first thing you see here just the very first thing that comes to mind i see a figure in
a large coat perspective skewed as if i'm looking at him from the ground he's got something in his
hand he's got something in his hand go on he's on he has dual fire fire caliber pistols i see what
else do you see he's just finished a job i see perfectly executed and who is this man it's me
very very interesting mr thomas i think it's this one very good this is an interesting one
what i like to do an interview is that i like to put my hands on my mouth and just go
please and tell me what this reminds you of well i just put my hand up arm up and just go
money earned performing and i go sorry i'm gonna shake those out i'm gonna check those nerves out
and shake fucking wildly back and forth and blink blink blink blink blink and then put my hand on
shake the hand again with whoever wants to shake it was very impressive mr thomas for instinct i
think you'll fit right in with milton fitzpatrick wouldn't you say so melissa i couldn't agree more
mr thomas allow me to congratulate you on your new position as an investment banker here at
milton fitzpatrick thank you when do i start well aren't you an eager beaver well we expect you to
come in tomorrow at eight tomorrow board mr thomas you know what i want to start today to have a look
around the bank you've got clearance all the way to the top i want to start today just don't go into
the ceo's office we don't want to lose you on your first day thank you i'm sure you can see
yourself out mr thomas have a nice day got the job poof everybody i got the job that's right this
guy your new colleague hey carol frag hopefully my desk will be next to you did i save it i didn't
save it it doesn't matter we i did the interview that's all i i already been up there we already
did this i already did the ceo i did everything already get off the fucking wall
oh god this shit's all messed up do something please
i have to get out of this game now i have to get out of the game i have to leave this game come on
in let's go i'll sit here until 50 people come in here and slip
up
wait that can only happen once holy fuck that's a lot of people
thanks for watching everybody that was it more more more no no i can't i can't i can't do anymore
i'll do one more thing no that's it that's it all right i'll throw one more object at one more
person okay that's it one object is getting thrown at one person that's all i'm gonna do
that's all i'm setting out to do there's no other goal that's it it's the first item i see it's
gonna get thrown into the nearest person what item is it that whatever's the club there it is
closest item what is it it's a of course it's a coconut perfect who's the closest person by
proximity it's you i'm sorry uh i fucking missed there's no there's no other objects around i've
might as well finish the mission then let's eliminate sierra nox sorry i remember playing
this mission i'm trying to drop somebody onto the tracks took it out of the way i go first
i go first how do i get over there oh i'm an illegal item
that guy was pulling a pretend gun i got dropped what even happened with the coconut
she's trying to dodge stop dodging i didn't do anything
there's no objects guys i can't there it is wait did i no you can have this back i didn't
come on pick that up yes you are the man that's the perfect con that's the perfect con
i distracted him gave it back my accomplice picked it up what a dick you deserve this
there it is i take one person give me that coin back asshole here take this back i got your money
back what the fuck was that oh cars they're not really searching very well are they
one clip is down i hope this guy runs out of ammo two three four does he have infinite ammo
look at how many he's gonna have he's gonna have so many no you'll ruin everything
you can ruin everything i would have sat there for as long as it took for them to drop like a
hundred to two hundred clips on the ground all right that's it we've been going for us six hours
i think that's a good place to call it for tonight we could still do one last one
sir i'm sorry i can't let you you can't be here okay
i see him right there
are you kidding me you're kidding me who's gonna activate the alarm
he's hit real good one two three instant headshot game was laggy that's it i have to leave
that was the germa green screen
okay good night everybody i'll see you guys tomorrow this has been we did all the dlc for
hitman i'm stuck in between he's doing one shot kills okay is it safe to leave not done yet
jesus christ it's jason born i knew i was gonna hear it at some point what no i didn't want to
shoot him in the back i wanted to knock him out i want to like pistol whip the spock the karate
chop vulcan neck hit thing we got a thing to do over here who is this
yeah get him steve what i have to all talk for no that's it that's it i'm done i'm out of here
i'll see you guys tomorrow this has been a really really fun couple of streams with hitman i
recommend the game it's very fun dlc is pretty substantial it seems like a lot to do that's it
i will see you guys tomorrow by the way i still haven't figured this out this has been the same
for a week and a half it's supposed to be the session why is it doing this but see tomorrow
we're gonna with this at least three or four games we're gonna jump in tomorrow it's gonna
be a weird one i feel and then i think i want to try to do the first community night on friday
but let's get the bits out here from earlier this afternoon any plans for horror games this month
yeah i think so i would say yes a few things have come out anything major or not necessarily
i'll take a look but let's go back we had uh two fifty two dollars fifty cents from devakitty
did i have fun at twitchcon i like this picture that shows your compactness clear as day
this is the this is the jeremy pissed his pants picture don't guys let me tell you something
don't ever under any circumstances don't ever uh like have like water or oil or something
don't ever touch anything and then touch your pants apparently because then this will happen
let me get it on here i need to do this yeah you guys were so quick too i take like a couple
dozen pictures of twitchcon and all of a sudden this shit happens if you didn't know any better
that this is real you know what i mean there are people on this earth right now that really
truly think that i pissed my pants at twitchcon and it doesn't matter what i say i could be like
no well that it doesn't it don't matter i have to just embrace it i pissed my pants at twitchcon
it was really embarrassing it's a good picture though i like this picture regardless of the
piss pants imagine if like there was actual piss on like shippy or talc's leg see that's like the
500 iq play there is like you put a little bit over here too and it's like wait a minute
i know you did that one but did you do this one where is the original i'm not even sure
the original is online it's been re-edited 50 times thank you for that picture appreciate it
yeah i've seen them all i've seen it you're not gonna show you're not gonna show me
ones i haven't seen yet i know all of them yeah the original that is the written but that's not
piss i don't even whatever it is fine who cares so uh that was uh i believe that was definitely
thank you for the 250 yeah and i wore a blue shirt with like a white front and all of a sudden
it was like oh let's let what about let's make him look like he wore this thing uh thank you to
germa's stinky feet thanks for the five dollars chat germa has not washed us since the carnival
what do you mean washed us the bacteria in the dunk tank has allowed us to achieve sentience
we have a telepathically possessed one of germa's fans just so we can beg all of you to tell germa
to take a shower what oh right okay like your username right god all right whatever
what why do i why do i feed talk this is freaking me out
thank you for the five dollars really appreciate it we have the bacteria no you're not all right
thank you to gnarly for the 250 dude you were at twitchcon right did you see that
fucking asshole with a toothpick in his mouth he was so fucking annoying i wish security forced
that guy out he easily ruined the whole event hope your experience wasn't ruined by him too
heard about him heard he was really really annoying but what can you do
main he's mean spirited person thank you gnarly appreciate it peaceful hailey thanks for the 250
bits hey jeremy hope all is well and you had a good time at twitchcon i did it was very very
productive very very good i recently made a youtube channel and uploaded my first video
it's kind of cringy not gonna lie but who cares it's my cringe and i've been getting nothing but
support anyway see you around go watch the first hundred videos i ever made you know what are you
linking now yes i've seen this one too this is what i'm talking about like there's just no escape
i've seen it yes the one with my head is like the size of a grape next to these two people here how
do you meticulously cut somebody out and just like shrink them by like 25 like it's so i want the
original and i want this back to back so she can see the the efforts that go into this where's the
original okay so here's this one and like very very clearly that's a lot of work look at how much
work that is what the hell is this it isn't really though that's the original no this is the original
i'm gonna go right to the twitter where it came from the background is plain it's easier to do
all right so let's this is the original i'll put it next to the other one just so you can see i gotta
defend myself here otherwise come on what we're gonna do that's not that it where is it okay here
it is this is the original like look at this see what i'm saying it's so it's so slight like you
you you've made him larger and you've shrunk it's just it's deceiving you made them like huge you
made these two 20 bigger and you made me like 10 smaller what can i do though i can't tell it's
an optical illusion now i just saw them both up close and i was like what the fuck they're both
fake they're not this is what happens when there's so many fake things out there nobody knows what
the real one is that's by design it's by design so the truth gets muddy anyways now thank you
peaceful haley good luck on your youtube channel and you kind of learn a lot about yourself the
first i'd say 50 videos or so maybe even less than that but thank you thank you also to the
wombat from hell for the 250 bits hi germ i want to make a game recommendation the game is called
the hex it's by the developer of pony island it's about six hours long what is pony island
it's one of the coolest games i've ever played and if you did want to play it i wouldn't advise
knowing too much about the game as it could spoil the experience is this is it good the hex is
this a stream game toss it in the recommended i'll take a look at it hey pigeon thank you for
the 500 bits i remember meeting you at twitchcon finally got the chance to meet you and i didn't
think i'd be so nervous and i i certainly didn't think you'd be just as energetic in person as on
stream makes me happy to know that you're not playing a character and you're genuinely an
amazing person anyway proof that you're actually five eight and a video proof of it as well i've
seen this circulating with the uh the tape measure this has this has 25 000 views it's been
viewed 25 000 times show it show it show it show i just linked it i look there's some things
there's some things in life that i don't want to show on my stream and one of them is me being
measured for the tape measure you know you know what fuck it let's go all right let's do it fine
let's just show it how do i just like pull out the video can i even do that i think i have to do
this is there way just to go right to a video yeah twitter video uh i'm just gonna do it i'm
just gonna have to capture the browser oh hold on give me one second maybe i can do it like this
can i do it like this browser source here we go add source uh add a new source there we go
does this work see if it works i guess it works did it work can you see it oh here you go you can
see it can you hear it all right listen listen listen listen up can you hear it yeah three
people were there to take a look at it i thought for a second i really thought that it was a
doctored photo like i thought that it was going to be like they made their own tape measure
and okay i've seen a lot of people say why do you look so weird here it's i don't know
it's the it's the camera like this camera was like strange it was it was like i was
you know what i'm saying i don't know why i look like my legs look so strange here
standing on my toes what are you talking about these are just i'm wearing a pair of sneakers
see no it's i'm telling you it's the camera it's the camera it's one of these new like
samsung galaxy 10s it's got like a fisheye lens on it see let me prove anything else all right
we're getting derailed here i gotta we gotta go back to the bits but that was some pigeon thank
you pigeon uh it was a pleasure thank you for the 500 bits and hope you had a good twitchcon
afterwards as well it was ten dollars from uh anonymous i think can you even do that i don't
see there's nothing here just says a thousand bits came in uh from nobody i guess that's
interesting that's new uh at my starfish thanks for the five community subs appreciate it
zake thanks for the 250 bits they say uh they they say you have uh you uh i think it's different
language i'm not sure what that means i don't know how to say it but they say when cooking stream
just wait maybe someday maybe someday i'll do a cooking stream i don't know just wait it might
happen i don't know you've been asking for it yeah it's possible someday someday confirmed in
the future he'll look into it that's right hey sad vega thanks for the two dollars and 50 cents
250 bits i need to see you do 250 box steps right now uh that would probably take 20 minutes i don't
have a box to step on unfortunately but thank you thank you apple shift for the 250 bits hey yo do
you have a set date for the community art stream uh friday i'm gonna try to get everything compiled
on friday if not friday then probably no there's no reason why it wouldn't be friday yeah it's
i mean that that channel has been active for just about a full month now so we'll see what's there
if i don't think there's enough there for a whole couple hours or two three hours at least then
i'll do it another time but this should be enough there this is going to be a one-time thing or
monthly or something it is going to be every time i think there is enough content there to do one
whether that's once a month or once every other month once there's enough to do a full at least
couple hours that's when they'll happen and i will announce them at least three four days to at least
two or three days in advance that they're going to happen usually like a week the last the last
thing i said about it was before twitchcon i said we would do it after twitchcon at some point so
friday seems like it's the good day to do it thank you fiti for the 250 bits i forgot you only read
messages with at least 250 so i'm going to copy and paste from before when i give 100 this message
has been brought to you by the i pay extra money to add disclaimer for the off chance that the
streamer reads both copies of the message for some reason gang thank you fiti for the six dollars
here and they say literally everything you do is funny to me jeremy thank you for always being
there for me throughout the years you always manage to distract me from the bad things in life
for years i've been struggling to fall asleep as my mind would always wander to some really
terrible fucked up stuff that left me anxious and unable to calm down whenever i have one of
your streams of vods on in the background i can sleep like a baby thank you from the bottom of
my heart thank you fiti if these streams are a nice little wind down for anybody yeah however
you however you consume this stream wherever you can get any enjoyment from it i'm glad you do
thank you so much for your six dollars your 600 bits you just called your streams boring i don't
think no i don't but but whatever you know if people i get it i get it i understand like you
just kind of need something just to have on the background or people some people guys a lot of
people do twitch while they're at work working on a project they just have a tab on another random
tab just open with almost like a radio station that's all right that doesn't bother me i don't
know why it would it didn't just kind of however you are consuming what the stream is that's fine
to me as long as you're getting something out of it that's cool hey thank you maris or maris for
the thousand bits appreciate it hey germa i met you twice at twitchcon and i wanted to say thank
you for being an amazing person it made my weekend being able to meet my favorite streamer much love
the tall girl in the overalls with no sharpie i remember you i did come prepared that next day
though i was like you know i i want this because i think i might need it it was an absolute pleasure
thank you for even flagging me down in the first place to anybody that said hello at twitchcon it
was great every conversation was pleasant what's probably gonna happen next year at twitchcon is
i'm gonna do an official meetup because as the channel has grown i was actually told that i
couldn't do a hey meet me under this sign i i explicitly asked and i was told that you can't
do that so next year at twitchcon i'm gonna do an official meet and greet at a booth somewhere just
because i know there's a lot of people that probably wanted to say hello i know i saw at
least a few messages afterwards that were like oh i didn't get a chance to see you i didn't get a
chance to say hello so i'm just gonna do an official one next time and of course besides
that if you see me walking around and grab me and say hello germa rumble at twitchcon i don't know
about that but thank you for the thousand bits maris pleasure was all mine thank you uh colu
cia thanks for the 500 bits hi germa meeting you at twitchcon was awesome you were so energetic
and fun to talk to thanks for hanging out for a bit even though i was so nervous hope you had
a good rest of the con i'm glad you're back no it was it was awesome talking to everybody
nobody let me tell you this nobody really came off as nervous or not comfortable or it was
whatever you were feeling i didn't see we were just having a good conversation i did have a
great rest of my con a lot of productive shit went down a lot of stuff behind the scenes guys
is starting to move i cannot wait for you to see the stuff that's gonna happen later lot of cool
stuff i'll leave it at that thank you to c4g for the 250 bits it's a bunch of emojis it's a hey
little piss uh baby you think you're so fucking cool huh you think you're tough you talk a lot
a big game for someone with such a a small truck and it's a bunch of emojis thank you for the
250 appreciate gnarly thanks for those 250 bits you should enable some of the bt tv emotes some
chat members have made except gerbil louis i still have nightmares yeah i am i'm just i'm just a
shit streamer when it comes to getting new things added to the channel i really have to get on top
of that i say it every time but you know it's true it's just true you know we're gonna run the
credits right now here they come because we are now at the end of the stream thank you everybody
for watching the theater is now closing in another five minutes or so i like this screen a lot but
that's it now that's it see you guys tomorrow we're gonna run the credits those of you that
stick around if you'd want to see oh wait wait wait wait wait wait i ripped this whole thing up
still learning stream labs obs although i'm probably just gonna go back to regular obs
because they've added a few great features that i really want to use and it's annoying because i
just went back i just went to stream labs obs and then found out that they added an insanely
helpful feature on the new obs that released last week so i'll be back to them unfortunately
because i really liked stream labs obs's layout but the regular obs is just probably way better
for me at this point so shit but um where the hell is my credits why are they not here
where are the credits hello credits where the fuck did they go how come where are my credits
i lost them how what the fuck is going on they're here somewhere hold on i'll find them they're not
here anymore how is that possible i don't understand okay um i need to add this then
all right give me a sec i'm doing this on the fly trying to figure this out
but wait a minute this should be it here found it all right hey here come those credits it wasn't
enabled it was down here sorry i keep bumping into you i'm sorry i'm sorry thank you everybody for
subscribing to the channel a shitload of new subs have come in very recently that's supposed to be
behind but you know that's okay it's supposed to be on the screen but we do what we can thank you
everybody let's finish up the last of the bits thank you amazing sponge for the 250 hey jeremy
lots of stuff is changing my life right now i'm getting pulled out of school for some psychiatric
stuff but you're always there at the end of a long weird and new day thank you so much and love from
wood island uh i wish you luck hopefully whatever it is that's happening you can get on top of that
getting pulled out of school i wonder um i don't really know the context as to why but that can
always be very jarring so hopefully you get through whatever that is thank you so much
for the 250 bits hopefully your life changes for the better and red island is a great state that's
one of the new england states it's one of my favorites i miss new england sometimes but it's
not like i'll never go back thank you amazing sponge for the 250 and good luck spooky spitfire
thanks for the 500 bits so germa this bit donation is a serious one sorry for ruining the vibes
but if you remember me from about six months ago with dbd ask me in chat if you want to know
what i mean by that and my mental health has been deteriorating for about a year and a half
i'm really sorry to hear that i was in kind of a mood and about to get fired from the only job
i had one of the only reasons i didn't is because the carnival stream so you are a literal lifesaver
thank you well here's the thing i really truly hope that whatever it is you're going through
you can really figure it out going through problems going through mental health issues
it's rough and it's hard to do everybody has their own way of getting through it
but i really really hope that you can find the right way forward things can get better but it
may i mean it's not you're saying i don't want to ruin the vibes or anything but
no it's it's just we're all people man i might be on a live stream platform but
i felt like shit before let me tell you oh yeah everybody has their own path forward
and my path forward might not be the same for you everybody's very different but i really truly hope
you find it and i'm really glad that you like the carnival stream because uh i made the thing for
all of you that's the only reason why i did it and if i'm able to do something like that again
i'm gonna do it again take care of yourself i wish you the best for real hopefully you can go through
either the professional or uh therapy or any of the methods that are available to you
and try to get it figured out good luck much love to you take care of yourself we're also now getting
right now i think well actually a minute or two ago alamitos thank you for the 269 bits
you ever wonder what people are saying when you leave to go to the bathroom do you wonder if
chad is talking shit about you behind your back i don't worry about that at all guys i just got
linked like a half dozen pictures of me with piss on my pants i thought it's all right it's gonna
be fine whatever anybody says okay it's not gonna bother me very much you should talk my face yeah i
don't you don't need to do it behind my back it's all in good fun though i know don't worry
hey alistair h2o thanks for the 250 bits i think you missed the epilogue cut scene from the heaven
island mission it's got good hitman 3 teasers oh i don't want to see it i don't want to see it i
don't want to see it i don't want to see it i wouldn't be surprised when hitman 3 comes out
i'm one of those people i don't look at anything i just wait till it comes up you want his tuba
and finally at the very end sorry bumping you again we had spooky spitfire for another 250 bits
germ i'm doing a soulsborne i die twice more than twice where i play the games in chronological
chronological order dark souls 1 dark souls 2 bloodborne dark souls 3 sd2 what's sd2 dark
souls 1 dark souls 2 bloodborne dark souls 3 sd2 sakiro excluding demon souls because it
isn't on the ps4 where i have to use a katana or blades of mercy in bloodborne dlc optional
it's pretty fun shadows die twice oh okay that's an interesting way to do it okay that's
sd2 shadows die twice oh all right that's cool yeah because it's like ds1 ds2 bb ds3
s well s sd2 nice i like that ssd2 yeah i would play through all the souls born games again all
the way through but i have played them all even on stream out of order too if you're gonna see me
play one of these games again on stream i did dark souls remastered i did dark souls 3 very
much out of order i've never done dark souls 2 on stream except for that one time when some
fucking guy climbed in my window and boy was that annoying and it ruined the rest of my playthrough
i never played it again after that something with things just sour your playthrough you can't go
back to them you know what i mean and then bloodborne i've beaten a hundred times already so
kind of gonna wait for the next one you will definitely see elden ring on this stream
whenever the launch day but i'll see you guys tomorrow i have a fantastic rest of your evening
we're gonna do just we're gonna do random easy shit tomorrow we're gonna do an idle game tomorrow
it's gonna be my it's either the biggest mistake i've ever made or like a a 12 hour stream where
i can't stop we'll see it's the phone in stream no it's not gonna be phoned in i'm just i want
to see what it's like if it sucks we can play something else play jackbox the new jackbox is
coming out soon isn't it like next month or something it's gonna be a rant stream no it's
gonna be a mouth open lean back in the chair stream i think
all right i'll see you tomorrow good night guys have a great rest of your evening take care