Hello, good afternoon. I didn't put this on, so give me a second. I don't know why my profile's
not here, but while we set up, just give me a moment. I need to be able to see you guys,
which I gotta get this in the right spot. Looks all right, okay. There you guys are,
in all your glory. Let's see here. Oh, that's wrong. Why is my, what happened to my profile?
I gotta like put the headset on for this. Red text, red text. Sorry, I had to, I had to do
phone calls. I get, the headset's gotta be on. Fuck, because I can't tell. Why did my profile
not get saved? All right, we're not even close. All right, so I gotta bring you guys forward.
So you're gonna come forward. Is there a way I can just grab this in here? I don't think I can.
You're not supposed to be seeing this. You're like actually not supposed to be seeing this.
Uh, just pretend the intro's still going. Okay, that looks better. Hey, there we go. Sort of,
right? Yeah, okay. Hello, how are you? You know, let's put this back up. You guys are too big.
All right, how do we look? Hey, there you are. All right, back to the intro. So we are going
to be doing more VR. Uh, not drunk today. Not today. We're sober today. We did go over,
I was in the chat earlier. We were talking about it. Not today. Yeah, not today. Hung over. No,
that was yesterday. That's why I wasn't live yesterday, because I felt fucking like dog shit.
Nah, it was a lot of fun. You get a drunk stream maybe like once every few months here.
What we're gonna play, we're gonna start with Disassembly VR, which is interesting from the
trailer. We might go back to Mind Show. I might also try to beat Jet Island. I don't know. Months,
you mean days. Wait, you guys think that's just a drink? Hey, why am I not on camera?
I'm an actor. I should be on camera. Uh, depends. We'll just kind of go where the day takes us. Hey,
here we go. Uh, you felt like dog shit because you were eaten by the dog. Still didn't shave. I'm not
going to. I think I was gonna let it just be, I'm gonna look terrible, but it's fine.
Kim check. All right. I'll do a Kim check. There is nobody in there. Right. Okay.
I didn't get you though. You got to give me some credit on that one. All right. Let me, uh,
make sure everything is right. Let me drink my sewer water. Well, you got a relatable superhero,
huh? I'm going to go over some adult things with you guys. Okay. First of all, I, my wardrobe,
you've talked about it before. You, I have, you have too. I have a ton of like star wars and
superhero and shirts from like the last 10 years and I don't want to get rid of them. They still
fit. Eventually I'm going to have to get some adult person clothes, but I, why the, this is
fabric. This is like a hundred percent cotton. It's, it protects me from the sun. It protects
me from the weather. If it's raining, it protects my skin. What else do I, it covers my like chest
and belly button. What else do I need? Do I have to go buy new clothes? This is fine. Yeah. I need
to get a suit. I'm not, I can't wear suits. Suits make me uncomfortable. I don't know how people
wear those every day with the tie and the button up and the blazer and the pants and like the cigar.
I couldn't do that. I would melt inside of that thing. I would need, okay, for me, a suit is the
same thing as wearing a mascot costume for like a high school football team. Okay. They have air
conditioning units that sit right here. If I was going to get a full suit, I would need one of
those. They have to make them for weirdos like me. A cigar. Yeah. Like a cigar. They just like
businessman. They just smoke cigars in the office. You've been inside of an office. It's like, it's
like worse than a casino. It's full of fucking thick cigar smoke. All right. Let's get in here.
I'm not going to fuck around anymore. Welcome. Hope you're having a good day. I'm doing all right.
I'm having a good day. Germa's stuck in the 1950s. I saw that show, Mad Men. They just drink
scotch and smoke cigars. Nobody goes, nobody works. They just have competitions with who can like
smell like more wine to each other. There's no, that's what you do at work. Let me get in here.
Make better jokes so the stock goes up. I ain't talking about stocks today.
I'm talking about taking things apart in VR. This is Disassembly. The ultimate reality
destruction game. This looks kind of fun. This might be your new favorite. I untangled everything.
Weirdly enough, I don't even do this shit when I'm sober. I cleaned up everything. I plugged in both
the controllers, which I don't do that so sober. I wiped down the lenses. Like I drunk cleaned up
this room. I don't know how, but thankfully these things are at a hundred percent. All right. Let's
go. Give me the other one. Welcome to VR. No drinking tonight. I didn't know what my tools are.
They are. This is left hand? Yes. We talked about this already in the chat before the stream,
but you know when you drink and maybe you drink like you drink a little too much, you have,
you get a little drunk and you open up your phone and oh, did I text anybody? No. Let me check.
Just check for five seconds. Okay. No, I didn't text anybody last night. No, whatever. I was fine.
I didn't call anybody, right? Okay. No. Seven and a half hours of VODs. That was my, did I text
anybody last night? Like, oh, Josh. A fucking eight hours of on camera. What did I do? Did I
do anything fucked up? No, I kid. I was completely with it the whole time, but yeah. Oh, let me just
check my phone. I don't think I did anything bad. I was fine. It's almost 2 AM in Australia. This
stream better be worth it. Oh my God. Way to put the pressure on. What? This better be worth it.
Oh my God. Now you got me all fucked up. Can you guys hear this? I think I need to unmute this.
Yeah, I do. It's a pretty good royalty free soundtrack. All right. Disassembly. Welcome
to Disassembly VR. Feel free to try out the tools. Feel free to try out the tools and weapons on
your right to get used to the controls. Close this message by aiming your right hand and pressing
the trigger button below. Okay. You can show this help again in settings. All right. Here we go.
So wait, I can, this is a game about taking things apart. How do I walk?
Uh, probably need the info here. Uh, okay. How do I move? Touch pad movement mode.
Press. All right. So I can grip to use. Is it going to explode? No, that's a prop. It's not
going to do anything. Tools. Grip to, oh, okay. I see. I don't know. How do I use it though?
God, this is fucking loud. Turn it down.
Wait, how do I turn loudness down? I don't want to hear this music. I'm sorry. That's just the way
it is. Where's the audio? Is there no audio settings? Okay. So how do I, ah, all right.
Let's go over here. Ah, what am I, what is this? Is this a bomb? I don't know what this is. Oh shit,
the battery. All right. What am I, is this the tutorial? If I can get this open, then I win.
It's just a parrot fucking screams at you. How do I get this off? This is, I could take,
can I take it off? Oh, what the fuck? Okay. Do I have to put something in here?
I think I'm ready to play. Oh, side table. Well, I am fucking like 15 feet tall.
Side table, lamp, speaker, side table. Let's just do something easy.
Well, it was a bomb. I just took the bomb apart. I think it deserves a couple of claps.
I might have to turn this all down completely. Hold on. Let me just turn this all down. It's
fucking loud. That like, all right. How's it, is it good for you guys? Is it loud for you guys?
What do you think? What kind of fucked up studio am I in? All right. I think we're good. All right.
So, uh, parts, there's 40, I'm timed. There's 42 parts. All right. How do I get rid of this?
Okay. So what I have to take this apart. All right. Wait, I've got to unscrew these. What
have I tools? Do I have to do it with my hands? I have to undo this with my hands. Okay. Uh,
is there any more parts? I think this one's done. Is it? What? Oh, they're okay. Get this off.
Okay. Can I fall out there? Can I actually go out the window? I gotta, I gotta get this clean.
Hold on. What is my hand? What am I, like Inspector Gadget? Go, go Gadget. Finger drill.
What? I can't even pick this up. Do I need to hold on to these? All right. Why am I trying to
hit my knee? Oh my God. It's a lot. All right. I need a tool. Where are my tools? Tools? Do I not,
are they inside? No, there are no tools in here. I cannot, I have to redo the whole thing now.
Why am I like floating around? Wait. Go, go. This just became another game. Where is this house?
Uh, whose house is this? It's just a floating cube. It's not, it's just a floating room. This
is like a Black Mirror episode. All right. How do I, where are my tools? Movement, turn the movement
speed up. All right. There we go. That's better. Don't I get tools? Maybe I don't, maybe I don't
get tools. Get in there. I'm here to save you. How do I get down? I'm just flying. Do I float down?
Go down here. Stop flying. Why do I stop flying? What am I going to do again?
I don't know what the fuck I did there. I have to swim? All right. I don't get tools. I have to
take out 42 parts. Oh, stop it. Come on. All right. Are we good? No, I'm still too big.
Okay. Let's get the, I'm going to get this for real now. Okay. How about I get parts?
40, 38. Okay. Here we go. This is where I glue I think maybe. Okay. Cool. Let's get them in a pile.
Why do you think they can broken glass out? Can I not pull this off? What's that say? Tool required.
I don't have any tools. All right. Let's get, let's, I think it's all right. Let's get this all off.
What do I get for doing this? Oh, cool. All right. Can I take the top off? How do I get a screwdriver?
Why would you put me in this room without a screwdriver? You understand? You have to build
a tool. What do you mean build a tool? Smash it. I, that's not working. I, no, I don't want to save
the screenshot. Maybe I can't do this one. The door behind me? That doesn't know a door here.
I, I need like access to a tool. What did I just do? What is this thing? Check your pants. Tool belt.
No, I don't, I just have two floating like magician hands. This is just the Smash Brothers boss. Hold
on. There has to be a way to get this off. Come on. Grip button. Press. There has to be a way to
get off to this. Why? Why? Why would that even be possible? Look, I can see it. I can do it with my
teeth. I swear to God, I'll get it. Tool required. I can't open it. Use a shard of glass. Holy shit,
that person's correct. Wow. Are you kidding me? I'm gonna get hurt. Give me a piece of glass. Okay.
Here we go. I'm just gonna use the pointed end right here. Can I get this smaller? That's not
gonna work. The panels? This is exactly what it's like when you build your own Ikea desk.
Seriously. What do you mean the panel? Help me. Glass on the panel. What about this thing?
What is this? Can I use this? Just get out in the middle here. Do it to me. There's a point right
here. Be careful with this. Be careful with this one. One false move and say goodbye. Oh my God.
This is too hard. Oh no. What? Right menu button?
Left right to choose. Grip to use. Oh my God. I can't fucking believe it. That would not break
the glass behind me. You fucking caveman. These weigh like a quarter of an ounce. Did I get it?
All right. Oh. Mission complete. It's hard to see where the lines are right now. Where am I?
Got it. What other tools do I have? I got a wrench. I got a hex wrench, crowbar, precision driver,
test pen, finder? No, part finder. What is it? What are these? Precision driver, pliers?
Get it off. Get it off. This is the tutorial. Just give me where the screwdriver goes.
Okay. Let's go. Guys. So this is what it looks like inside. Interesting. I thought it was like
a bunch of wires and computer parts and stuff because for a desk to open those doors to open,
I'm surprised it's this simple. All right. Now I can. Oh, the support's going down.
All right. Stop breaking the glass. It's going to give me a headache. All right. Now what?
Oh, top is off. Now can I pull these? I think I can pull the sides off now. Let's get in a good
position. Okay. Now I can pull this off. How do I get this off? What's down there? What is this?
Coin? This is mine. I got it. I win. There's nine more parts. Side table. I did it.
I did it. I win. Now what? Did I do it? Wait. There's another one. Wait. Parts six.
There's two more of these somewhere. It's right there, right? Where's the other one?
How do I take that? What are the other parts? Parts. There's six more parts. I don't think I
can do anything with this. The base can't be pulled apart. Take out the park finder.
Oh, Jesus Christ. Oh, they're coming in. The invasion. Sir, they're coming in 44 knots a second.
All right. It's right. What? How can? There's three parts left. What are they? One, two, three.
That's it. Disassemble. Best time. Two hours and 42 minutes. Two minutes and 42 seconds?
I've been live for 31 minutes. Two minutes? I don't understand that. Hold on. Can you guys
not hear the sound effect? Well, that's odd. But this game, I kind of like this game. That was the
side table. What's next? Show it to me. So that's it. Let's go to the next one. All right. Main menu.
So we did that. Side table complete. All right. We did lamp. Oh, we're in this fucking room again.
All right. Now I know how to play. Let's see. Is it connected? Not connected to anything. Let's
get a good look at it. Anything on the bottom? No, there's this wire here.
Just stand here. Oh my fuck. Whatever. Just leave it. All right. So what do we got? How many parts?
39. All right. Let's go. Screwdriver. We got, what do we got? We got a couple of screwdriver points.
No. Is this screwed on? No, I don't get it. I'm done. Take the bulb out, right?
Oh, that actually like hurt me in real life. No, just call me shaky hands, Elbertson.
All right. Let me try to get in here with the precision game. God. All right. I gotta get the
wire cutters. These are wires, right? Why? Oh, I've got a complete item pack 10 to unlock.
What? How do I get this? How do I undo this? Come on, get in there. Nice. Okay. We're getting there.
What's holding this in? Stand up. I wish you could just stand up. Stand up. Stay. No, stay. What tool?
Electric pliers. Test pen. I can't, I can't like push it in there. Precision driver. Hex wrench.
Screwdriver. Mannequin. Gravity gun. Rocket launcher. C4. Grenade. Classic assault rifle.
X-ray glasses. Magnifying glass. I need the tweezers, I think. Shoot it. I can't buy it.
Gamer glasses. It's the precision driver. Is it though? Wait, I need like a tiny screwdriver.
See what I mean? Will the screwdriver get that? Okay. How many parts are left? 24?
Nothing. I gotta get in here. I gotta get in there. Okay. And the, the puncher. I need the puncher.
What about, how? Oh, what happened? Oh, God. That was like taking out an ingrown hair. That was,
you know what? DLC. DLC. Whoever made this game. Ingrown hair removal. Right? No? No. Yeah,
like little tweezers pulling it. Ah, whatever. You guys don't get it. We got 21 more parts.
They're all connected to here. Get a screwdriver again. This is kind of fun. You know what? I'm
getting like a house flipper vibes. Because you can't do this with stuff in your house.
You won't work anymore. If you wanted to do this, you wouldn't be able to do it.
Your mother would yell at you. This gives you an outlet. Okay, now just pull it apart. You know?
This is what it looks like inside. Ooh. Whoa. Well, that's, that's the worm that's inside.
It's a skeleton. This is what it looks like inside. Nice. We got four more.
Six minutes for a lamp. Record time. Praise the sun. All right. What's the next one? Speaker.
What else do we have? A house. You have to take apart a house with like a screwdriver.
Um, the Titanic, a screwdriver, a rice cooker, a car, an airplane, a toaster,
a skyscraper, a tank. Oh, they, okay. This is, they're not fucking around. You thought this game
was like a little joke. Just wait till we get to the fucking plane, the car. We have to start small
though. We're, I got to work my way up. This is fun. Uh, it's basic. This is a real basic game,
but I honestly, this is what I would recommend for VR. Like your father or your grandfather.
They love this shit. You know, they like to go into the garage and just like fucking put
things together and take them apart and put it back together again. My grandfather took apart
clocks and put the clocks back together. That's a lie. I don't know anyone that's ever done that.
I think I actually stole that from like a Disney made for TV movie. Well, I don't know where I'm
getting that from. That happens in a movie and it was like, it's my pretending that was my
grandfather. That's my pretend grandfather. All right, here we go. Speaker. Had to do it once.
No, go back, go back, go back. That was a waste of time. That was in Star Wars. Put some tunes on.
I don't know. I don't know if like, I mean, the music in this game is like default music.
What we got? Q R S. If you go back and watch, somebody mentioned this and we talked about it
before the spring. Every single character does this with their hands during that.
I don't know what the fuck is wrong with me. I didn't tweet the fight either. No.
All right, let's go. What do we got? Speaker. It just feels cool to do this. How many parts?
My father was, oh God, 43 parts. This is a big one. I can't wait to get the power drill.
That's for winners though. Okay, that's that. Let's put this down carefully. A lot of glare.
This is what the inside of a speaker looks like. Interesting. All right, how do I get that?
Dude, what? I thought it was full of liquid. I thought it was kinetic liquid. All right,
no more of those. So that's that. Let's turn it back around.
Okay. Ah, I got to take those out. Have we done the base? Dude. All right. No, nothing else here.
I don't think because it's just the charcoal. Wow. That's it. Huh?
Oops. Well, I need that. Don't make a mess. Can, is this just one part or can I pull this part
completely? I think this is just one piece. This on the other hand, I've got to work with.
What do we got left? 20 parts. Raspberry P. Do I have to get in there and take all those off?
What about the wires? There's 13 more parts. What are the other 13 parts? I need to get tool
pliers, right? No. How do I get these out? These? Oh, I think it's, no. Are you serious?
I get to get them with a crowbar? No, that's not right. Maybe I can't. Shouldn't I be? Wait,
they wouldn't. No. How do I get this out? Just a regular screwdriver? No. Flip the table. I can't.
I'm not strong enough. You used to see, I don't have the C4 unlocked yet. How do I get this? Do
I have to grab it from this side? No. Tool required. None of these worked. Hmm. You'd think
it would be pliers. Apparently not. Yeah, like that's what I thought too. But look,
tool, I don't think I can do that. Try to take the, well, I know these probably have some stuff in
them like this right here, right? Well, this is going to be tricky. Like a fucking dentist.
Dentist game. Dentist DLC. You can like pull teeth out and stuff and like correct. You got the,
you already have the engine here now. What? How do I do that on the other one? I don't even know
what I'm pulling out. Okay. These, I need to get that out, right? Apparently not. I don't get it.
Still 10 pieces. Use the other pliers? They're unlocked. I can't even, I have to beat item pack
four to get these. Why is that person here? Hmm, nothing. This is the wires that fell from down
here. I can't go out the window. Guys, can you use the, yeah, the park finder maybe.
It's probably not a bad idea. Is it right here? Hold on. Like, is it this thing? What? Oh no,
he's going for a tombstone. So what is this thing? Is it? All right. So I don't get, what the hell is
in here? Ah, look at that. Okay. Six, one, two, three, four. All right. Three now. It's this stupid
thing right here. This is one, two. All right. Give me this. Turn it on. How do I get you open?
How do I get this open? Just take it out. Put it, I'm not going to put it there.
Test pen. Oh, I can delete that. That's good. Test pen. Why did I try that?
There's one more part. What is it? All right. Open up. It's time for your cleaning.
Nine minutes. Not a big deal. Best time. All right. I was not expecting that.
Sticker. All right. Item pack one complete. Item pack two. Pocket knife, microscope, and antique
car. This wasn't going to be fun. All right. 23 parts. All right. All right. Is it alive or what?
Okay. Let me see if I can identify all these. So we have, wait, there's one more.
See if I can identify everything. So we've got baby scissors to cut literally nothing because
there's no reason to have those. They don't do anything. They're just there for you to pretend
that on a Swiss army knife, that's there for you to pretend it's a monster and you could like make
a voice. My grandfather used to do that. Knife. That is dull enough for you to spread cream cheese
on a bagel. So I mean not really that useful. Spring. Well, I don't know what you'd use a spring
for to like pretend to bounce it. What use does that have? Then you have like the assassin's creed
assassin dagger. You know, you like that. Here is your can opener, which is pretty useful if you're
camping. There's the fish knife to collate the fish. And then here is the hind leg to prop it
up like a bike. Oh, and the key chain. So there you go. That's pretty much how this works.
Is he talking shit about Swiss army knives? No, look at how useful this is.
That's useful. That's useful. That's useful. That's useful. Not useful. Don't, not useful.
That's useful. So, all right. So like 75% of this is useful. The rest is just there for fun.
Fucking rabbit. Scissors are dead weight. All right. I don't like that noise. You replace the scissors
with, okay, you want to know how you make that cool? Instead of scissors, have it pull up a
little roll, a little mini roll of tape, like scotch tape, even if it was like two slabs. How
is that useful? You do the math. Oh, I gotta get this one off. Whoa. Get out. Get out of here.
That's how it, that's it? Oh, they're, these are all gonna fall down. Cool. There's the spring.
All right. I want everyone in chat to be real with me here. What does this, what do you use this for?
What is this for in this? It's a corkscrew? No, for what? For wine? Why is half this shit to open
bottle of alcohol? But what do you do with this? Is this essential to survival? To like open a
wine bottle? No. Replace this with like pez. Have like three pez here instead of this.
See, let me show you the use for this thing. Ready? Like, hey, it's me. I'm a scummy monster.
That's what my fucking grandfather did in the middle of his spare time when he was building
and taking apart clocks. What is this? Oh, the shaver. That's useful. Look at this. Look at
it. Look at the precision here. There that goes. Okay. Is that it? Four more parts.
On the back of this maybe? What? Oh, right here. Oh, okay. Is somebody breaking in? What?
Somebody just threw a baseball. God damn kids, that's why my study. I wanted to have it against
the other side. Away from the neighbor's backyard. I'm taking apart shit and putting it back together.
Fucking rotten little shits. But we want to play baseball. Get out of here. Get out of there for
me. Shit. Where did it go? Fuck. No. God damn it. Where is it? Does anybody see it?
Damn it. That's the second ball this week. Hello. Yes, this is the police. I've got a few rotten
kids that have been hitting baseballs into my window. Yeah. Thank you. Send two squad cars.
It looks like they're having a good time out there. Andrew, put them away. Okay, give me this back.
It's this thing right here. Just shut it out. Oh, fuck. I can't move. No. No, wait, wait, wait.
This is going to be fun finding this part. This is going to take like $400 million in like the
entire state of Washington to find this. Oh, god damn it.
Just reset. What? No, I'm already done. Hold on. Did anybody see it? Where is it?
It's apparently right in front of my face. Look, snorkeling in my own house. Is it still forward?
Wait, did you see it? I think I saw it. Wait, what do you mean? It's the...
Oh, nice. Very good. Very good. Amen. All right, we got a microscope and then an antique car.
This one's probably going to be a lot. This is 43 parts. How are we going to get a car in here?
Oh, Jesus. Okay. Well, what can I look at it first? Don't lose anything. Oh, wait, you guys can't see
that. Now you can. I have put my hand under here. You can't see anything? No, well, I'm probably
going to take those apart. Okay. No, no. Okay. Going good. Some of these might have to be
completely taken apart. Oh, that felt good. Oops. This game's really cool, but I'll tell you.
Being able just to go like this means somebody didn't put this together correctly.
They didn't use any glue, tape, screws. It was, they just jenged this thing together.
Whoa. Why is there like smoke here? Oh, turn it off. Rotten motherfuckers.
Yes, me again. I don't know. Somebody's driving by and going loud and honking and shit. Yes. Yes,
I'm aware, but I'm a part of my neighborhood watch. I'm like, yes. Yes, I know I call six
times a week. You've already got with it, but you haven't. I'm a preferred member of my community.
Give me my other phone. I got two cell phones for this reason. Hey, no, no, it's going to be
forever. No, it's not. Get it both off, right? Oh, we got just too wild and crazy guys. Oh,
my God. I'm going to break something. Oh, who cares? It's not going to turn on. Get me back down
here. Any of our other cell phones. Oh no. Charlie. Charlie. Oh, this is ridiculous. Charlie. Oh,
the fan. Wait, wait, Charlie. Charlie. Charlie, work. Charlie, it's working. Charlie, get me down.
Okay. Why is it so complicated to move? Jesus Christ. Oh no, it's not going to stop.
I got to do this quick. How many parts are left? 25. Okay, we're going to get silent now. Oh,
God damn it. Whatever. Why did I fucking do that? It's stuck onto this one. Charlie. Drink it again
quick. Nice and quiet. That's the way I like it. That's the way I like it. I'm going to need that
later. There's the light. Very bright. How do I turn this off? No, I just made it brighter. I want
to turn this off. The light is so bright, I can't even focus. Turn it around. Okay, any more parts
here? Okay, little ploppers. Okay, can I take the back off? You can. All right. Oh my goodness,
the whole thing comes off, right? Is there anything else in here? Because I kind of want to just get
rid of this. I think this is just one big piece. So get this away from me because the light is too
much. All right, what do we got? 15 parts. The little ones, right? Maybe this? Can I get inside
here? No. No. Okay, there's that one. Done. All right, a couple more of these clickers.
Click. No. Come on. How many more? Nine. No. Take these apart maybe? The glass inside? No,
there we go. Any more? How many more? Four. Where are they? Anything else on here? That's
two? Where are the last two? No. No. Not this, right? No. I'm like eating my lip. I had it?
That's one more part. Where is it? Where is it? Stop chewing on your lip. I'm like concentrating
like, that's not it. Huh? Cute. All right, I'm gonna drink some water. Let's back it up for a
second. This game's fucking fun. This is just relaxing. All right. Clean the lens a little.
My greasy face. There's like water in here. That's how disgusting I am as a human being.
All right. Let's get back in. Just want to get some water. Stay hydrated. All right. Good to go.
Car coming up. Old-fashioned car. Antique car. Oh wow. Oh, there's like a smudge on the lens.
God damn it. Hold on. That's gonna bother me. That's better. So, I am supposed to take this
thing apart with a wrench. Is that what I understand here? There's 52 parts. Brutal. No,
no. Get in the car. No. Get back. Come here. How do I move reliably? Seriously. Okay. Well,
that's a start. Does it still work? Hold on. I'm gonna drive this thing around. Wait, you mean I
could teleport this whole time? How the hell did I just do that? What? I could teleport this whole
time? You mean I've been swimming around for no reason? What the fuck? Yeah. Brutal. What did I
just do before? All right. The controls changed. I pressed the same button I pressed last time.
I swear to God. I was pressing up. What happened? Use the D pad? That's what I did last time. Now
I'm teleporting. Okay. It's not that. It's not left or right. This is now teleporting. No. See,
look. Look at this. Okay. Slow down. Turn it. Turn. Slow, slow, slow, slow. It only works when it's
highlighted. All right. Now let's actually do it. All right. What is this? A headlight? Doesn't do
anything. Engine. Why? No, this is the air filter that brings in cool, clean air. Comes out. That's
how your air conditioning works. Make sure there's nothing else in here. Okay. This. I just want to
show you guys how this shit works. Turn it on. Was it the engine? I can't turn the engine on now.
Why? I was gonna do it manually. I can take that off. Easy. What is that? This is the wing.
What is this? It's a weight. Nothing. I don't have to take anything up far here, right?
Okay. Another piece of glass. This is the second headlight. I don't think they're going to do
anything else with that. It's the wheels. I don't want to fuck with the wheels yet. Test it first.
What? Okay. Well, I was trying to punch through it. All right. Spare wheel. I can take the inside out
as well. I do. They thought of everything, didn't they? They thought of everything, didn't they?
Well, let's go ahead and get the tools out. We'll deal with that later. Put all the tires
over here. This is the danger cone. Oh, this is this bike seat for somebody else in the back.
What's in here? You are very strong in this game. All right. This might. I'm going to have to take
a look at that later. This is this. This is the. I can just pick these up. Those are the. I don't
even know if that was holding up that thing. All right. Here's the other wing. Oh shit. I have to
take it off that wing. Wow. This car is. These things are really basic, huh?
Get that one. It just hit me right in the mouth and knocked all of my teeth out.
All right. This is the back. Let's go like this. Can I get this off? Oh, no, no, no, no, no. Don't
do that yet. This thing's going to freak the fuck out and flip over. What's going on? What's
happening? That was weird. Okay. Oh shit. All right. The weight. I got to get some weight
distribution. The whole thing is going to come down. Can I take this? All right. This is going
to. The whole car will fall. Not yet. I'm going to get the doors and the other crap that's over here.
Now I need a tool. Can I open this? I'm just like breaking these things. All right. It's fine.
Take the top off. That leaves us with the engine. Now get the doors off. How much more parts? 27.
Use the hammer. I don't have access to the hammer. I haven't unlocked the hammer. I have like a bunch
of tools I still need to unlock. I can't take this off yet because it's buried in here. All right.
Hold on. Can I take off the roof? Okay. I can get the roof. All right. It's starting to look
a little skeleton here. Get the seat out. All right. Now let me get the tire. How do I get this off?
I can't rip this off. Do I need another tool for this? Pop the tire. How the fuck do I get this off?
How do I get this off? Behind you. I don't even say that. Use the wrench. Oh, okay. Oh shit. Okay.
We're almost. How many more parts? 22. Not even close. No, no. Stop hitting the wall.
Oh. Yes. My plan worked. Who needs a wrench? How many more parts?
15. There's the engine. Get that over there. What's this part? Okay. Can't get that off yet.
Can I get the wheel? Yep. Oh, yes. This is where it all just falls apart. You just look at it. It's
just so tender. It falls off the bump. Look at that. Look at that. All it took was 12 minutes
in the new wave oven and it's just so. The bone, the meat just is. Do you see that?
Take a look at this. The meat just falls off the bump. Watch out though because it can
fucking spray up at you. All right. There's still things I need to do here. Shit. Is it the engine?
Nothing else on the engine? Uh oh. I need to get the part thing out. Oh, it's the wheels.
The wheels, right? Come on. The wheels, these things, look it. The middle has to come out of
them, right? Whoa. Oh, never mind. Coral bar. Get out of there. What's left? It's the tires.
He's done it again. Perfect. How many more? Two more tires? Three more? What was the other one?
Right there. That's it. There's one more. Is there one more tire? Let's get a bird's eye view here.
Tire. Tire. Tire. Shit. Over here? Whoa. It's this. What do you mean this? What is this?
Oh, I got 13 minutes. Classic bomb unlocked. I got a bomb. Got a bomb. Robot. Safe bicycle.
Robot. How big is it? Oh my god. I was thinking it was going to be a little toy. Well, they just
gave it to us. We have to see how it works. All right. Grip. Left, right. Okay. Grip either hand
to use. Well, how do I? Is it just lit right now? What determines how this explodes?
Whoa. It goes into slow motion. Holy shit. Oh my god. Are you kidding me? Is this going to fly at
me? What happened to slow motion last? Wow. It's still in slow motion. Can I touch it? It's still
in slow motion. It's super hot. Super hot. I think I can hold on. Movement speed. Interface.
Graphics quality. Bomb slow motion speed. Should we just do like 80%? 60, 70%? 60, 58, whatever?
It was still in slow motion. It is really cool, but you kind of have to sit here. How long does
this last clock on the main menu time? Is it done? Let's throw another one. Okay. How many
This is crazy. All right. Let me. Let's start over. How many parts are there? There's only 24
parts. That's nothing. Maybe I can just do it all with this. Get it. Get it. Get it. Get it. Throw it.
Get it and throw it. Okay. No. Here. Eat this scumbag. I think I did it. That's it.
So, uh, I think using the bombs is cheating because you don't get a time.
So, no, that's just for fun. That doesn't count. Did it actually count though? See? That didn't
count. We're going to do it legit. See, look at this. Ready? I had no timer. See? Look at that.
All right. Let's just get, let's get this done the right way. Is he going to fall on me?
No. Watch it. Okay. Come on. Get the other side.
This is a real lip biter. Take his heart out. Oh man. What am I doing with them? Oh, shit.
Let's get the head off. Anything else with the head? No. What do I need? 21 more parts. Shoulders
come off. Oh my God. That's so cool. No, no, no. How dare you? I was using this as a weapon.
What? None of that came off?
I don't know. This is like his other shoulder.
Oh, Jesus. I have his whole body. All right. We're going for a breakup here.
I can't see. No, don't open the window. Oh, give me this. Ah, this is what it's like to be Superman.
I could go with some more sound effects besides.
Yeah. We got 16 more parts. It's like a little. No, what the hell would it be? Here? Is this all
one piece? I think that's all one piece. That's the torso. I don't think these come off.
I don't think so. I think that's one piece. The arms on the other hand. Yeah. Okay. Looking good.
Any more pieces that are attached here? I think it's just the knuckle. Maybe the fingers.
I think that's the way. Did these come off? See if I can get a hand off. Yeah, of course.
Yeah, the whole hand comes apart.
That's that. Okay. Get it on this one. How many more? Eight. That's it. Okay. Six. What am I
missing here? Maybe something with these. Oh, definitely. This wheel comes off. Absolutely.
The other arm up there. Maybe. Yeah, I think that thing comes off.
I'm getting too into it. I think I broke it. Are we good? We're good. I'm getting too immersed.
How many more? Three pieces. There's only two more pieces. Where are they? Bring out the tool.
You know the one. Straight ahead. Where was it? Oh, shit. Okay. It's this thing? What is connected
to here? Ah, all right. Then there's one more piece on the main body. This little piece? This
little chest piece? No. Where is it? I have no idea. It's not it. Thank you. I've been biting
my lip more. I do the shit. I like, I just have chew on my mouth when I'm just concentrating on
something. That's interesting. Why do I get guns? All right, so we got it. Crack is safe.
What if I just know the code? Let's try code. This is probably a code. Crack is safe. It's not,
and let's just paint it on there. 7331. I would probably advise against putting the code of your
safe on the safe. Otherwise, somebody can just do that. Does it open? Gold bars in here. What is it?
Gold. 999. One kilogram. This is like 50 grand. A kilogram of gold is like 50 to 60 thousand dollars.
Is it not? All right. Okay. I got the gold. Wait, that's it. Oh, no, it's not. Can I get out now?
Am I locked in forever? All right. All right. I got a piece out.
All right. Let's see systematically how we take this out. There's a lot of parts, apparently.
Yeah. All right. I've ripped it off. Can I get the sides? What about the top? It's 39 parts.
39? How much more is in here? Flip this around, maybe. Oh, Jesus. All right. Well,
oh, God damn it. I hate my rooms. I rent out an ice skating rink and pave over it and have to be
my personal VR room. Where do I put this? Hole in the wall. All right. So now I get to, this is
where all the parts come from. Let's go ahead and get something, some finesse here. Let's go with a
wrench. No. Take out all the slugs. Nice. There that goes. Is it still plugged in? They're disappearing.
No, no, no, no. Leave it. Leave it. Leave it. Ruined. Can someone tell me if this
streamer is popular? What? What do you mean? Can somebody tell me if he's popular? I don't know.
That's kind of an odd question. Oh, that felt good. That felt really good.
Okay. I think, wait. Nice. This is just satisfying the video game. What do we got? 11 parts.
I wonder if it's part 11. I can't pick this up. It's got to have to do with this, right?
Cares if he is funny and nice. That's it. Well, thank you. That's really, really nice thing to say.
Thank you. Oh, it's every individual button. It looks like fuck with our roommate. You know what
I mean? W A S D. W A S D, huh? Now it says like dickhead. What do you call that? Did I win? Oh,
I won. All right. I won. That was fun. What's coming up next? Bicycle chair. Okay. I don't,
this one, I don't know about that one. That one seems like it's a train, an elevator,
a real car, the Titanic. How am I supposed to take apart the Titanic with a screwdriver?
Cool. Do the, I mean, I'm gonna do, I'm, this is disassembly stream guys. This is, I'm having a
blast. This is just fun to play. Can I sit on it? I can't do it. Oh, that's so much fun. All right,
set it back up. The need training with, oh, you can actually do it. Hold on. Oh shit. No, don't do
it. The bully from the Disney movie. Come on. Get out of my way, Walt. I gotta do this. No,
it won't stand up. I can't do it. You know what I'm doing though. Dude, you know, you know,
anybody ever turn their bike upside down like this and try to like make like soup and shit and
fuck with your candy? I used to take my candy bars and like grind them. So I have like chocolate
wheels. Somebody would just be there going, and you would just hold something there and like,
like a sander. You won't put your face on it. You won't put your face on it. I'm not gonna put
my face on it, stupid. You know, I'll do it. And then they like kept like a fat lip for the next
like three or four days. Nobody did that. Nobody like did this and then put their face on it.
Don't do that. It's a bad thing. All right, let's take this part. Now I want to stand it back up
again. Nobody. No, I'm talking, look, I'm talking about setting it up like this and spinning this
and like going like this. And some, one of your weirdo neighborhood friends does that and like,
it was a dumb thing to do and you should never do it. I do not condone it. I did it. It sucked.
Don't do it. All right, how do I get this apart? How do I get, let's go here. What? Oh, I just got
a five controller. A wrench? All right, wrench. Come here. Come here. Come here. Ah, shit. Pliers.
I don't have pliers. Fuck. Oh, come on. Really? Come on. Come on. Thank you. Oh, that's not it.
Except for that one. Oh, I got like a hair all over my face. Let's get back in. Oh, let me take this
off so nobody have like a drink of water. Come on. You won't do it. Kim check. All right. There ain't
anybody in here. I want to get some more water in a second after I do this level. Is this the right
side? Yes, it is. Ceiling? I have to tape bells to the door. That's fucking hilarious. Wait. Oh,
come on. Why is it, there's like a stain on here now. Fucking bird box. Turn on music. Ah, but,
however, I'm gonna have to take this. Let me take my first break. Let me go refill my water
and I'll come back. We'll put it on like a playlist or something. I'll be right back.
Okay. Hello. Let's go back in this and take apart bike. You want to sip my fresh water?
She's, she's not in there. All right. Let's get a, let's get like a, I don't know, like a Monster
Rancher. Somebody's Monster Rancher 2 OST. Hopefully I can actually play through these speakers.
Um, Monster Rancher 2 OST. I think it's like eight minutes. Put on doom again. How, how it's made.
Like, how it's made theme song for one hour. No, no, how it's made background music. Hold on. How
loud is this going to be in my headset? This is an hour long. This is going to drive me insane.
How it's unmade. Then he takes the wrench and moves it down over the hole. Two workers come out
and hold either side of the glass. An assembly line and hard workers. That's what it takes to
undo a bicycle. Two tires are replaced with air filled tires. This is so loud though. Hold on.
Uh, this is too, this is too, the OST is banger. I love this show too. I'm not shitting on it.
That show's amazing. Okay. How do I get this to play softer in my ears? Probably like that.
Yeah. Okay. Here we go. Where are my hands? The person grabs the bike with their bare hands.
A skilled worker undoes the handlebars with an Allen wrench. Two workers then hold the bike
upside down and a third worker presses his face into the tire to make sure for a perfect face burn.
Did we get like frame rate here? What's going on with this?
God damn it. Got it. No, no, no. I get it. Is it getting faster? I feel like it's getting pitched
up. My game's breaking. I don't know how to take apart a bike. Got it. Pick it up.
Uh, other side. All right. Get in there. This is going to come out. Okay. Hold on. Wait, wait,
wait. This song is going to fucking drive me crazy. It is getting faster. The pitch is going up.
What? Shit. I'm going to hit you back. I'm going to lose my mind.
No. All right. I'm almost done. I got to get that off.
No way. Almost got it. Get it. Take it off. No, don't do that Joe. That's not going to lock.
Is it over? Of course not. I got it. I got it. I got it. All right. Get that out. Oh yeah. Why?
How many more pieces? 45. I can't take that anymore. That's too much. Uranium is a metallic
element that was discovered by a German chemist in 1789. The significance of this discovery
wasn't understood for a century and a half. In 1938, scientists figured out that uranium atoms
could be split to produce energy. The size of a fireplace log, this nuclear fuel bundle
generates a lot more heat. It's packed with enough uranium to power 100 homes for a year.
To obtain the uranium, they tunnel 1,640 feet underground at this site in northern Saskatchewan.
This mine is the largest source of high-grade uranium in the world.
Lies beneath a bed of water-saturated sandstone.
To reach it, they use drill bits studded with tungsten carbide buttons.
Like knuckles on a fist, the button bits punch into the rock face.
Burst holes are for pipes that will hold heat out of the ground and squeeze it around the ore.
It transfers a new piece of pipe to the end of the drill roughly every five feet.
To penetrate 426 feet into the sandstone bed,
it takes up to eight days to install just one length of pipe. There are 200 of them.
Workers configure the pipes so they surround the ore deposit. These freeze pipes will stabilize
the ground and also turn high pressure groundwater to ice so it won't interfere with the actual mining.
Freeze plant above ground chills calcium fluoride brine to minus 22 degrees Fahrenheit
and sends it through the freeze pipes. It absorbs heat as it freezes the ground
and loops back to be chilled. All right. All right. I'm done.
Let's get something relaxing for crying out loud.
We're learning. Don't do that. We're learning.
Oh, listen to the fox and screams. No, no, no, I'm not doing that. I was learning.
Well, not learning today. Earthbound OST. That's not bad. Okay. That's the first
too loud. Okay. That's at a reasonable level. Earthbound.
I'm going to get this fucking bike disassembled. Oh my God.
We've got a house coming up too. We'll put on some heavy fucking metal.
I'm going to tear that house down with a sledgehammer. This is better. Okay. This
is relaxing. It's good. High quality sound. Yeah, that's good. Good. Allen wrench screwdriver.
We'll get it. What? Get it. Huh? I back to one. Okay. Oh, why? I've done every tool.
Every tool. Oh, all right. That's good. Oh my God. I've hit more walls today. Jesus. I need a bigger
fucking room or I have to do like seated play. How do I disconnect that? Here we go. Please dad.
Can we learn again? No. Everything you need to know, I can tell you. You don't need all fancy
books. I can tell you what you need to know. Here goes the chain. Whoa. All right. Now we get it.
It's done. What's left? What do we got left? The bike, this part of the bike, right? It has to be.
Crowbar. There it is. Perfect. How do I get that off? Can I even get in there? I just barely
could get in there. All right. 14 more pieces. Jesus. Okay. This part of the bike. You know,
this is all fucked up. Okay. This right here. Can I stay still? Stay still. Stop moving.
All right. Now what else is there? I've done so much. 11 pieces. This thing. Okay. That works.
Good. Does this come off? I don't think so. This comes off, right? Yep. Dive to bike wheel. I did
not die to bike wheel. Four pieces left. I don't know. Something got a loose screw in it somewhere.
No. Fuck. These things. I don't think so. Big wow. Well, we're gonna have to pull this out.
Oh, this thing. Oh, fuck. It is this thing. All right. Is there another one? There's another
one of these somewhere, right? Got it. Last thing is this has to be this. No. 33 minutes.
Handgun has been unlocked. Handgun is unlocked. That's right. Finally. Safe. Bicycle. Chair.
Water heater. And then house. We're almost there. This is gonna be easy. I don't know. It's not 62
pieces. 62 pieces? Are you kidding me? Let's go up on top. I gotta be more careful about this stuff.
All right. I'm ready. Let's go with handles. I think I can take this. This is the pillow.
Everything that's not naked goes over there. Anything else loose? So we gotta get under here.
All right. This is not. I don't want. I want. I don't. I got the other one. I want to keep standing.
You know what I mean? Look at this. I already got you. I'm already fucking halfway in front of you.
Hell yeah. We can't do it like that. It's illegal. It's against the law.
It's against the laws of the video game. Scarily effective. No, I'm just. The fucking door.
I just door knocked the streamer meme to myself. Jesus Christ. No, don't break.
Hold on. Do it one at a time. These are elaborate. Get them all in front of me.
Do it smart. You know what I mean? Why fuck the whole thing up? God damn it. I did it again. He
did it again. He did it again. He did it again. Move out of the way for a minute. Where am I?
Where am I? He's going mental. I got a I got a booger inside my nose and I can't get it.
You know, you know, seriously, like valve or the HTC. Cut this up a little bit so I can like put
my hand in my nose. I can't do it right now. Am I in a decent spot? I think. All right. Keep it going.
This is the way you're supposed to do this shit. All right. You ready? Check it out. Wrong tool.
Wrong tool. He's just he's just surgical with this. Turn around. You got a good sear on one side.
You don't want to cook them too long. If you cook them too long, you want to go to a medium well.
You don't want to go over a medium well. I think these are done. I'm cleaning my workstation.
Come to me. What do we got? What's next? Looks like this guy right here. This is the spring.
Nothing in there. There goes the spring. All right. Easy. All right. Hold on.
Can take that up. Turn around to the other side. Nothing else on this side. Are you sure?
Get the other side too. Oh shit. Okay. That worked. How am I going to take apart a whole house?
That's going to be impossible. Oh shit. Okay. We got it. Good. Great. Get the paper out of here.
Now what's next? These. I really got to get under here, don't I? Look at this shit. One arm.
This whole thing's going to hit me in the head, isn't it? This is some America's Funniest Home
Video shit. Okay. What's left? It's the only sound. I'm getting good at this.
This is still connected by something. What is it connected by? What is this connected to?
A crowbar? I don't see anything that's connected to. Oh fuck. Give me the pliers. There it goes.
All right. What do we got here? This should come off cleanly now. Got it. The bike took a long time.
I don't know why. Well, I'm from. I'm hyping myself up. We've got one more and then we have
the house to do. So I got to be ready. I got to do my stretches. What do we got?
Yeah. Water heater and then house. Does it work? Can I actually turn it on?
That's so huge. 104. What? Oh fuck. You might as well take care of this first.
All right. How do I get the panel off? Just with my hands? No, no, no, no. I didn't want this.
I don't want this. I don't want this. Oh my God. Why? Just stay over there. I don't. All right.
Turn this off. Thank you. How do I get the panel off? Shut up over there. Will you?
Can I wedge the panel off? I don't know how to get this off. No, no gun. No gun. Look at that.
Right there. What the fuck? There we go. There we go. This is cool. All right. Leave that there
for now. So this is what a water pump looks like. Hold on. Can I turn it on? I want to see
where the water comes from. Press this button. I can see right here. This is cool. This is the
circuit breaker. Such precision. Just get all the screws out. All right. Hold on. Screw hanging
on up here. Tool. Okay. I got that. Hold on. Anymore? Right here. I can take it off a wall.
Oh fuck. You're right. Look at you. Look at how smart you are. Actually, no. I don't think I can
do that right this second. Really? It's right there. Oh, all right. I'm going down here. I'll
see you guys in a minute. I feel like this is the kind of shit that's on Sesame Street
with the song playing here. Don't you? This is like, this was an episode. I got to cut wires.
What was that? The grill. The circuit board was an Xbox 360 heatsink. Look at these tiny little
things. My goodness. It's so tiny. Oh my God. I got to turn it around. Look at down here. I'm
going to get the screwdriver out. Easy. Whoa. That's the reactor. That's the nuclear reactor.
Look at this. Whoa. Whoa. Are you kidding me? Look at this detail. How many more parts? 40 still.
Hmm. Pliers? I'm going to say pliers. What is the other part? All right. Got it.
There's the band. Come on. Come on. Very interesting. Okay. Now I think I can get rid of this.
Yep. Nothing holding this together. I feel like there's another thing getting held down here.
Yes. Yes. Nothing in that one. This is where the water comes from. What is that? Is that a bug?
What is this? Oh, that was weird. Come on. Get it open. Come on. What? What tool do I need to get
that off? You think it was pliers? Is it not pliers? Time to fight. Oh, shit. Missed. Minus 20 HP.
Hector uses PK dart. Not effective. Oh, Hector uses dart again. PK dart. Very effective. He's
almost dead. PK up. PK dart. I don't know. PK. PK call the police. Didn't work. PK crowbar. That's
a win. PK. PK gun. PK gun. No, no, no. That'll fuck this up. That'll, yeah. No, no. Let's get
back to what we were doing. Stop distracting me. You're distracting me. Wait, am I looking the
right way? It's this one. It's PK dart. Sorry. He's lost it. He's lost his mind. Oh, my God. I got
to get in so close. Look at this. What? Ah, nice. Looks like just shake it out. Same deal over here.
Here it is. So then I can pick this up again and shake it out. Now what? I can't get this one off.
You know what I mean? I can't get this one off. How do I get this off? Ah, there's a screw there.
Now I can get this all off. Bingo. Bingo. Done. Two more parts. There's so much shit on the ground.
The button on the front? Oh, right. Over here. Done. That was cool. There's a lot of little
intricate parts. All right. Uh, the time has come to see what the house is. And you know what that
means? It's time to put on like the hardest fucking song I could find. But I want to bring the house
down. What is like an extreme like blast your eardrums out song? Not the full house theme.
So I'm thinking something different through the fire and flames. This is pretty hard play.
Just keep using this one. No, not this one. I'll get fine. We're going to do we're going to pull
this back. I'm going to do doom OST 2016 because I mean it's been a while. This is loud and fucking
crazy. So here we go. See you guys soon. I'm going to I'm going to thrash the fuck around right now.
Get ready. It's going to be loud.
That was so easy. You didn't even try to have this host in. They built an entire house without any
cement, without any brick, without anything. Nothing to hold it together. They just stuck it
together like a house of cards. Yeah. The precision. What's left, huh? Get the fuck out of here.
Oh, I don't think I can do it anymore. I really hurt myself here. I haven't broken the thousand
back. I am the champion. No, no spill. I'm going to go take, I'm going to be right back.
I just use like six days or the energy. I'm going to get my water refill.
That was fucking intense. Why would a house fall down that easily? This game is fucking mental. I
love it. I'll be right back. All right. Hi. Let me uh, I've got to untangle this cord. It's
kind of all over the place. Kim, check Kim's downstairs. I just saw, just said hello.
Let me untangle you. Is my hand okay? It's all right. It's a little red, but it'll be fine.
It was the controller took the brunt of that below. Let's put this back in. What do I have
left to destroy? I need to moisturize. I'm going to do more than that. I got to shave tonight.
The Titanic, that's going to take all day. What a fun game though. Holy shit. I did not expect this
to be this fun. I feel like this is kind of an overlooked VR gem. If I'm going to be honest
with you, it looks pretty, I'd give it a solid, uh, they give it a solid B plus right now.
All right. Let's get back in. Thanks for being honest. Yeah. It's an, I can't pretend you guys
have seen me try. I'm not going to give you bullshit. Games is 79. I mean, it wasn't B plus.
That's an 80, 88. Oh, my head's gonna fall. Stop wearing it. Like it's a fun hat. I,
okay. This is how greasy my head is right now. Is this the right? Let's get this back on.
Use the neck strap. If there was such a thing, just use your grease to moisturize. Uh, you want
me to have like, you want me to break out tomorrow? Here we go. Let's finish this one.
No more doom. No more music. I got to focus. Okay. It doesn't. Get that in there. I've been
playing this game for three hours. Holy shit. Oh, it's been worth it. It's been fun. All right.
What's the, what do I, what's the final count here? There's 27 more parts. How the fuck am I
going to find that? I mean, like this, does this count? What? Am I frozen? Am I frozen in time?
Is this like a Quicksilver moment? Should I run around and feed the dog pizza? I think it's the
foundation. It's down here. If I could have time in a bar room, the first thing that I would do
is run around and feed it on pizza. This is a lot of the doom. I have to slide it all the way down.
Is it the floor? No, it's not the floor. It's all the windows. Let's check. 12.
And I didn't even use a gun. You understand? I didn't even use a gun. I did this all with my
bare hands and a little, a little help with one of my friends, you know? A little help with a couple
of my friends. Okay. Nine. Well, this is eight. Seven. Seven. Six. Something's going to be buried
underneath. Oh boy. This is bad. I need the tool. Oh God. Right here. Right here. Four more parts.
And I did with my bare hands. Right here. This is where the stove was. Right here. I'm surprised
that this is not dropping down to like 10 frames a second. That's even in a game, a game that has
this much physics and shit in it, random pieces. Don't, wouldn't you expect this to be running at
10 frames a second right now? Two more. So one. That's it. One more. Where is it? Is it the thing
in the sky? I think it's floating in the sky right here, but can I not grab it? That time is inflated
because I had to take a break. How is this going? Okay. I want to, I want to, I just want to go
inside the house if I can. We need to go inside. That's too interesting to not just look at it at
least once. All right. Here we go. Let's like walk in. All right. It's an actual house.
All right. As you can see, no, no, no. Back it up. Back it up. Realtor. Realtor bit. Here we go. Three, two.
So as you see, property is very, very well maintained. Very well taken care of.
Sort of has that colonial vibe to it. A little bit of a step up. You just get the foundation
happens here. The foundation goes up a little bit. You get your second floor, which is your master.
Yeah. Your master and your master bathroom is up there. And in here we've got the bathroom.
A little kid's playroom over here, as you can see. Pretty, you know, that's standard carpet,
nothing. You can take it up if you want. This is all marble, by the way. A little walk-in closet
for, you know, for you guys to store your jackets. And in here is one of my favorite parts of the
house. In here is the backdrop out of the backyard. Yep. You don't have a huge backyard, but look,
you got a place for a grill and entertaining and having your friends come over.
Oh yeah, it's beautiful. You want to see upstairs? Yeah, we can see upstairs. I just kind of,
it's a big house. Yeah, let's take a look up here, as you see. Neighborhood's great. Schools are
great. Watch your step, though. It's a little slippery, but it's just clean. Yeah. Really?
Wow. I'm surprised they have that work here. That's a great job. Balcony out here, as you see.
As you see, beautiful, beautiful landscape out here in front of you. You've got a lot of plotted
land. This is not owned by anything. You could take your dog and your kid out there and your
kids can all just run around out there. You can get a whole baseball team out there.
Yeah. So, price, right? We're talking about price. As you know, property like this is not
necessarily cheap. We are in, like I said, a very beautiful area. Watch out coming down.
So, I mean, the thing is, they're looking, what they're looking for
is they're looking, look, they're looking for, they're looking for $29,000. Oh, Jesus Christ.
What? Get down! Why? Get out, quick!
It's driving!
And scene. Cap that one. Cap that one right there. Cap it. $29,000. I wonder why.
There it is. Share that one with your friends and title it,
Hilarious Realtor Moment. All right, let's go. God, that's going to happen in my own place.
All right, what's next? A hard drive. This would be easy. I'm tangling up again. God damn it.
Damn it. Whatever. This one will be fun. You guys like computers. Let me show you how to
destroy a hard drive, guys. It's pretty simple. I didn't even destroy it. I didn't get the most
important part. Never mind. This is actually interesting. I don't know what it looks like
in here. The only thing I know about a hard drive is it's a brick. It's just a cube that
stores data. I don't know how. I think there's another computer in here, right? I know how a
hard drive works. It's a hard disk. It's magnetic. I'm not stupid. I'm not going to let you use that
one to fucking hurt me. You know what I mean? Can't get it with that one. Why not? What the
fuck are you talking about? All right, you got to use the pen tool. Wow. So it's a record player.
That's what it looks like in there. It's a record player. It's so tiny.
What did I get? That's it? What? What's up?
Gas tank. How do you think it operates, guys? Oh, whoa. I need to get some. Let's just like
put you guys over here. Sit down and relax for these. I got to get them. You know what?
You're right. I can check on them. I'm like standing too much. Whoa. It's made out of gold.
See you guys in the next video.
Flip it around. Well, that's the part right here. What is that? Ah, screwdriver. No,
not screwdriver. What? I had the right tool. The little baby screwdriver. The little baby one.
Oh, cool. That's what it was though. The vane.
Come on. I got to get that off. Got it? Let's hold this on.
Can you just break stuff? Yeah, I could like probably whip it against the wall,
but then I'll lose the parts and I won't know where to go. What do I need here? A wrench or
something? How do I get this off? I don't think it's the crowbar. Whoa. Holy shit. It was the
crowbar. No, it wasn't. I can't grab that. Come on. Get in there. What? Oh, screws. Three more
parts left. Well, this obviously. What's this being held on by? Someone's still grabbing this
right here. No, it was still holding on to that. There's something. Ah, there's still a screw in
here. Don't drop this. Don't drop this. It's fucking. One more part. This cord is going all
the way up. You know the word. This thing right here. Bring out the beeper.
Oh, right there. I did it. That's it. Okay. Nice. All right. Well, I think we're coming up on a
blender, I think. I have to. I gotta. This is so tangled up. Hold on. I gotta undo this.
I'm gonna make it so you don't see this because it'll hurt your eyes.
So let me just. I wish that was like a detangler profile. See, it ends up bunched up like this.
No, you can't see me. Never mind. Wait, I. Sorry. You see, it goes like this and gets
taut around so much. It's hard to take care of. I need to stand up on my table.
Really wring it out. All right, let's wring it out here. Get the suspension wires off Amazon.
Yeah, but I don't know if I can put the. I don't have like a drop ceiling. Don't you need a drop
ceiling to do that? Or does it? Can you actually get something to stick on the ceiling? I think
we could fall off and get hurt. That's better. Bring it back. Cable sleeves. I wonder if the
cable sleeves would have just bunched up too. Let's see. Did I stream this in VR for like six
to seven hours two days ago drunk? I did that. I don't know what. That's insane to me. And I
did a backflip. I did. And you weren't here. Somebody link it. It was a full backflip. Not
baby sister falls down because she's like four and a half months. You know, not like baby brother
falls. It's a backflip, man. Let's get in that. I think Blender's coming up next.
All right. Ultimate reality destruction. Coffee machine sink. Lego van. Hellfire missile.
Ice cooker. A saw. Let's go to the blender. I gotta be careful. I feel like can you,
can I blend my stuff? Oh, you can blend. Wow. Wow. That was fucking terrifying, actually.
Um, hold on. I'm not done. Blended gun. Was that, that was loud as fuck. Should I blend a grenade?
I feel like I have to try. What about one of the little things, right? Like the little,
Allen wrench here. Get in. The whole purpose of this is to be able to feed things.
What the fuck? I didn't do anything. It's from fat guy's neck. No. Let's try and restart.
Coffee maker too. Okay. Here we go. Last thing I want to try. That's not.
This thing's still spinning. I don't want to. Let's do it for real. For real. Pop the top off
the lid and as fast as you can say, bop's your uncle, bop is your aunt. You've got a delicious
strawberry smoothie in the magic bullet. How many parts? 62. Give me a break.
I can't even pick the fucking thing up. What a hazard. KCH brand. Unbelievable. Imagine you
picked up a glass pitcher and it exploded in your head. Let's get a good look at this. So we've got
screws down here. Sit it on. Come on. You fucking Darth Vader mask. Stay here. Look at how tiny
this is. Ready for this? You got one sound. Let's get in there. Look at that. Now look at this.
Need the little one. Are you fucking kidding me? Are you? Are you kidding me? No. No. No. No. No.
No. No. I don't have it. No. How am I supposed to get it? Look at how precise that had to be.
These are the later levels you can tell. Do this one step at a time. Are you shitting me?
I'm like sweating so much. My gross disgusting beard. I can feel it like water on it.
That's just gross. I can't wait to shave and take a bath. Anything else on these? Yeah. Yep.
I have to shower every day. If I don't shower every single day, it's a nightmare. It's bad.
Can you guys even see me? Come to it. I cannot go more than a day. I just feel terrible.
All right. What do we got? We need some clippers.
Can these sides come off? Okay. Anything else inside of here? Is this thing?
Ah. Got it. Now what? The tiny little beer cans. How the fuck? Get in there. It requires patience.
And a steady arm that I don't have. Okay. Let's get clippers. I want the tweezers so bad.
Don't worry. You're probably saying like, oh, your cable management just sucks. Let's just
cable it. I'm going to shake it up. I need that in a minute. I'm feeling it. I'm feeling it. All
right. See? Now we shake it up. Perfect. Perfect. Let's put that there. How do I get this off?
I have to go from the other side. Oh yeah. Oh yeah. Is it a screw or Allen wrench?
Oh yeah. I thought I had it. I thought that was the one. I thought this was the one.
Now I actually might be able to get in there. No, it's too big. It's too big.
Yeah. That shit's too big. Oh wow. Well, that wasn't supposed to happen.
Come on. I can get the fan. Ah. Holy shit. There's a lot. This is the motor.
Nothing's too big if you try hard enough. Can you hold the whole blender in one hand and the
screwdriver in the other? Yeah, you can. It's kind of hard though because your eyes, you guys are
seeing only the right eye. So this is what you guys get to see. But my left eye is in play and
the left eye is, you guys don't see the left eye. So when I pull it close like this, I get that weird,
like when you put something too close to your face, you start to see like double.
Like, oh, I can't, it's just hard to see right now because I see it. I don't have like a full
resolution one eye. So it's actually sometimes easier to see it from like here rather than like
go like this or like that, you know? What am I missing? The pliers? No. What? Is it screwed in?
What am I missing here? Not the wrench. How do I get that off? Dumb. Dumb. Why am I dumb?
Try to just close one eye. Jupiter? Is he dumb? I was thinking this, but apparently that's not it.
What is it then? What? Ah. I'm gonna have to take that apart. Look at that. I want to get a good look
at that one. Same with this. And I think that's all. It's your road on here. Oh yeah, that's it.
I don't think this is a piece. I think that's it. I'm just gonna take apart these.
These little ones. Out of the window? Sure. That's it. Yep. This, where this guy.
This is where all the meat comes from. Is that it? I feel like that's not it. Whoa. Holy shit.
This, I got five more parts. Maybe something on here? This shit? It's gotta be this thing.
Let's go with the wrench maybe. Just like pry it off. What am I missing? Might as well take out
the tool. What? Oh. No, it is this thing. What of it though? The little pieces? It's not the little
tiny pieces, right? Whoa. Okay, it was that. Now what? Something over here. Oh, it's the motor.
Oh, the, not the motor. The blade. You know what I'm trying to say. Cool. Coffee maker. And then
sink. I'm gonna try the missile. I feel like I should jump to one of these. There's so much
interesting shit. No, no jumping. No jumping. Yeah, you know what? This game's great.
I think this is fun as hell. Coffee maker. Can I use it? Oh shit, I can. Give me coffee.
I don't like it. All right, well, this is where the water goes. Oh, ice cream. Can't break it.
Can I take this apart? Oh, that's a filter. I feel like I'm gonna have to come back to this one
because it's a little twisty here, right? There are 93 parts. You got to be kidding me. I'm gonna
do this slowly and steady. Nothing here. If there's nothing there, get rid of it.
Nothing, right? This might be, I might need to use that later. Nothing, right? Smash it. That's a,
I would, I would, where'd you buy those? Because I would love to have them.
I might need to restart the game. I'm getting a little frame ready.
Is this, I might need that later. Don't need this. Get out of there. Can I, I can't turn it?
Now, there's the water tank. Jesus. Can I open this up? I have to be able to, right?
All right, let's put some sea monkeys in here. Nothing? Don't think so. That bottom,
I feel like I can take it up, right? That I can, we'll get back to that later.
Screws? These are thick. I'm still holding on to it. What is still holding on?
Ah, so this whole, all these guts are gonna fall out here. Still attached.
I can't get that ring. What is it? Ah, don't fall. What? How you, this is, no, there's two more
screws. Nothing else on there? I don't think so. You need to do this in real life. I don't think
that's gonna be, I would never be able to do this. Let's lie on this back. Guys, I have trouble
replacing the rubber stopper in the toilet bank. You think I'm gonna be able to do something like
this? Oh shoot, it still works. Whoa! I don't know why I think that's funny. Like, I'm gonna put it
down my pants. I don't, I don't know, I don't understand. I don't know why that's something
I'm doing, but that's the second time I got it. Whoa, holy shit. The buttons might have to come
off on here. Yeah, the buttons definitely have to come off. Really? Apparently not.
That's what it looks like. This is what it looks like inside your computer. Damn.
All right, let's do, let's take this slow. Can't do that. Yeah, let's just get the screws.
There's a couple of big ones. Whoa, what am I doing? No, no, no, no, no, no. Pick it up. Spin it.
Okay, let's hold on to the brackets here, but I don't think I can move the brackets.
Not yet. Still more screws. There's a ton of screws. I can't move this. I can't move that.
Oh, I can get this. Wait, don't. Hold on. I gotta slide this shit off. What? How do I get that off?
The screw? Screw? Undo the clamps. Yeah, but I, how the fuck can I do that? I don't know if
I can do that. Hold on to it. All right, so now, get these off. Nice. So what, what, okay,
this, this tank is being held on by exactly sure. You can get rid of that. Does this have to come
off? I don't think so, but I'm scared. So I'm gonna hold on to it. Lego piece. Give me the little,
no, give me this. Can't like rip this shit off now. That's still attached. Ah, fuck, right here.
All right, this is still screwed in. God damn, am I getting sick again? Like my, my throat,
I'm getting that, like, I have a cold feeling in my throat. I just got over being sick. Not again.
You know, you know what I'm talking about? You just feel it in the back of your mouth and throat.
I just got over being sick. I want to unscrew more things.
What? I gotta get the pliers and snip this. Apparently not. Is it the, which one is it?
All right, let's shake it. Get those loose pliers out of here. All right, fuck, get,
this is my workstation. Get the fuck away from me. Clean workstation. Where they plugged into over here.
That should be able to shake them all out now. There's a couple more that go down. I can't move
them. All right, now that leaves. What is holding this down? There goes that. There goes that one.
Anything else? Can I pull these off? I don't think so. I think that's it. All right, now I got some
more freedom here. Does that help? How do I get this off? This thing is still screwed in here.
Hmm. Whoa, whoa, when did I get this? I got needle nose pliers now? I didn't even know I had these.
Holy shit. Well, that's a major paw jam. I need to get these unscrewed. All right, well somehow that
worked. Magically, I got that to work. How do I get you off? Screwed on? There's nothing holding
this. Whoa, okay. What is holding this down? There's nothing holding this down.
Hover to find out what tool to use. I feel like that'll just stop. Okay, wait a minute. Slow down.
All right. Okay, I got another work area here. I need to pull this out? I guess not. Itchy nose.
Uh, 21 more parts. I'm assuming they're all here.
All right, let's get the pliers. The good ones.
Oh, shit. Can't get rid of that yet. Spin this around. All right, shake that.
A couple more screws. Can I move that yet? Not yet. Why? One more. Oh, that last screw always feels
the best. Out comes that. Oh, we get to see the brain. Ain't nothing in there. All right,
four more pieces. What's this? This? There's gonna be this shit in here. Two pieces.
Well, there's nothing in there. It's this right here, isn't it? One, two. Give me that piece.
One piece. What's in here? All right, bring it out. Let's see. Is it the ice cream scoop? It is.
That was a lot longer than seven minutes. I thought that was under money. That glass just
is fucking killing me. All right, let me see. I'm starting to think that the tank is getting
empty here. No, not that, not that. I think I'm just going to play this tomorrow.
I love this. Sink. Missile. Titanic. Car. Plane. Train. Space station.
Oh, this. All right. Guys, I'm gonna. Why do I have to be so tired? Only four hours?
Come on, I can do more than four. Usually I can do like four and a half to five. All right,
we're gonna do like one or two more. No, that's too early. I'll do one more. So drained. No skipping.
I'm just gonna beat this whole damn game. You know what? It was the rage in the house.
It was the house rage. This one's gonna be quick. I can do two more.
If this shit is too fragile. All right, I get it. Hold on.
Clean it up. That's a nice water sound though. All right, that's fine. Let's get it out of the way.
All right. Turn this off. Can I even turn this off? All right. Can I pull it out of the wall?
Oh, Jesus. I can't turn it off anymore. My batarangs out of the way. All right.
You see what your problem is, is you hulked through the sink. I think that's probably what
the issue is here. But I've been wrong. Can you fix it? I can't. I fixed it. No, I don't think so.
You're gonna have to call a real bummer. I'm just gonna steal all these parts.
Know what copper is worth? God, no. Is there anything I can do about that?
All right. Look, I gotta get under here. Oh, that was that was the water. Would you look at that?
And we can pop this. No, we can't. Now you can pop this. Ah, screws in there.
Come on. That's how I get in here. Oh, my God. How am I supposed to get this?
Maybe I'm not supposed to get it. I don't know. I pull this up. Oh, shit. Okay. Okay.
It's kind of just floating. How much is left? Six more. Oh, shit. There's something else.
Uh, oh, it's hard to get in here because I can't. Do you see? No, it's like a gorilla trying to open
up a fucking twist off coke. You know what I mean? It's not gonna happen. These little wrench things?
I don't think so. I can't get them off.
Fuck. Four? How do I get these off? I can't get them off. Knock plier.
We don't have any clue. We don't have any clue. Stop looking at chat is what somebody said.
Why do I have two of these? This thing? What the fuck? Okay, so with three. God damn it. No.
Okay, it was that. Guys, how the fuck am I gonna do this? I can't get these off. It's the screw.
Yeah, I can't get these off. Not the wires. Hold on, I'm gonna move these out of the way. Okay,
I'll bring up the ghost finder. What? Shit. Where's the other one? I can't get in here.
Is that it? God damn it, it is. How do I get in there? I can't get my screwdriver in there.
No, we already talked about the gorilla with the coke. What? What am I doing wrong? Two? It's one
thing. I don't think I'm doing this right. I'm like a ghost in this person's house. Screw it.
The little silver thing is copper. That's not what you meant. That's not the right way. It's
not the right way. Way. I'm so tired right now. I'm just like slugging on the ground. Imagine you
walked in. You walked in. There's a guy preparing your sink and he's crouching lying on the ground
just going, hey, there's no way. I don't know where it is. I don't understand. Do you? And you
see a little thing? You'd be like, holy shit, you get out of my fucking house. Imagine his
germs on his tiptoes. That's funny. I'm looking for one of these. I honestly got no fucking idea
what's going on. All right. So mouse plumber. It's this thing. See? Not that thing. This thing.
No, don't use the gun. I can't get in here. I did it. Oh, I fixed your sink.
That'll be $400. You can write me a check. That's B-A-C. Reverse plumbing and heating.
God. Time for the Lego van. I don't know. I'm out of fucking juice. Let's see. What do I got?
Let's at least look at it. Okay. Let's look at it.
It's so small. All right. Oh my God. Can I pick the whole thing?
This is tiny. Oh my God. I want to put it on the ground and lie down.
I can't put it on the ground and lie down. I have an idea.
I'm still lying on the table. All right. That's how we do this. All right.
I think I'm going to eat grapes from a vine. Oh, yeah. Come on. Come on in, sweetheart.
Yeah. Do you think this is sexy, what I'm doing here? That's right. Seriously. I can't throw it.
This one's actually going to take not that long. Ready? Watch this.
Yep. Yep. Yep. Yep. Okay. Yep. This is what a cat feels like. This is what it's like to be a cat.
This is life as a cat. This one. Get off the counter.
Weird cat can fucking slowly fall off the table. Yeah. They always land on their
fore front feet. You know why that is? Because when they fall, they fall in slow motion.
All right. One more. I don't know. Whoops. All right. Give her some juice.
Ah, I can't. I don't know. Same on the gas. Well, the engine's running. Let's try something.
Give it a little more gas. Yeah. That's a car fixing. I'm invincible. I didn't tell you. I'm
invincible. All right. We have to dissect a missile. Hellfire missile. I can't throw the missile.
I always thought you had to be careful with this shit.
All right. Why inside of a missile there's a bunch of Christmas decorations?
That was a part. That was a pinata. That was a novelty pinata.
Uh, that was going to be scary. No, apparently not. Will it, does it explode? Maybe it's because
I took off the on button. Hold on. Maybe I should give it a starter.
There was clearly a second exploded, but the little cartoon grenade was more powerful than the,
whatever this is, like this missile. Here it goes. Look at how, I just want to,
just look at how many parts are everywhere. I want to see how many parts this is.
This is going to be like probably 200 parts. 102. Damn. All right. I think that's going to be it.
Four and a half, like just about four and a half hours. We'll do bits about five hours.
I got to take a break. Gravity gun. Well, I'm going to play this tomorrow.
So I, this is what we're doing tomorrow. Cause that was fun as hell. That was great.
You'll forget about tomorrow. I'm not going to forget tomorrow.
No, I'm not taking tomorrow off. I took yesterday off. I'm not. No, we're doing,
we'll do it tomorrow. Get in Minecraft VR. I did expect that I was going to play the four and a
half hours. You're always going to forget. No, I'll be, I'll be like tomorrow. At least throw the
missile out the window. Okay. I'm going to try to get the missile out the window. No, it won't go
out the window. Watch. Just watch. Yeah. Typically two nights ago was not an indicator of a VR
stream. Usually my VR streams are only like four to five hours because I can't, I can't be in here
for that long. I just can't, I don't know how the fuck I did it for like seven hours, two nights ago.
It was a shit face. All right. I'm going to try to get out of here. I need to break this precisely.
Wait, I have this now? I didn't know I had this. This is why you guys were saying that. How do I
use it? Is this all it does? Trigger pressure adjusts grab force. Okay. I see. It's actually
kind of useful. All right. Let's, let's get out of here. See if I can actually get this out the window.
Okay. Come with me. That ain't going out there. I'll try to get it. There's a wall here. I can't
get it. Christmas gold thing. Have any gun from the outside? Move the window. Shoot the Lego van.
Why do I recognize the sound effect? Cause it's a stock sound effect. Don't look down.
The Christmas gold thing. That's how you know I'm at a gas. Ah, the Christmas gold thing.
All right. I'll turn it off. Can't hurt it anymore. All right. Let's just chill for a little bit.
If you're going to take off, you take off. But I'm not going to turn the stream off completely.
I'm going to get the chair back in here. We'll hang out, do the bits, chill for like 30, 40 minutes.
Yeah. I'll post that on Twitter. We're going, yeah, we're going to go on low power mode.
Sometimes it just does it to me. You looking at the sun? Sorry about that.
All right. I'll be right back. We'll go for like another 30, 40 plus minutes.
Got to go over five hours. All right. We don't have to, but we will. Ah, that's another thing.
It is like a thousand degrees in here. Just adds to it. I think VR Josh was talking about it. I
need to get like a fan to just go, but then it kind of makes noise from outside in the hall to
this room. It's like at least 20 degrees difference. That's an on top of it too. That's
another reason why I got to get some like circulation, but I'm happy with going four
hours in VR. That's kind of typical last time before shit faced Saturday. I didn't want it to
be less than four hours though. That's, that's too small, too short, but let's just go like this.
Let's just hang out for a little bit. Move this over here.
Uh, can I not do that? I shouldn't be able to. Hey, look, full camera needs to be brought down
a little though. This is what it looked like without glasses. See people are going, well,
that's what it looks like without glasses. Yeah. I don't want to get stretched. Why's this camera
doing this? No, it's cause it's up too high. All right. Here's the portion of the stream. We're
just going to sit around and hang out for a little while. Maybe like 30, 40 minutes. We'll
do the bits while we chill. Let me get the chat over here too. Just cause you know, I need to
be able to see what you guys are saying. Did I X out of it? Like an idiot. All right. So see,
okay, everyone, okay, the drunk stream two nights ago, when I took that headset off and I was sitting
here, everyone's like, look at how red he is. He's fucked up. Look at his hair. This is a normal
human, not drunk guy. And it's the same shit. So see, he's drunk again. Look at how flushed and
fucking sloppy he is. No Labo VR. I'm going to do Labo VR. You already know that. Only a drunk
person would say something like that. All right. Let me, uh, let's get the bits on here. Let's go
like this. If you take it off, we'll see tomorrow. More, uh, take stuff apart. I can't wait to take
apart the plane. I think, I think I found my new house flipper. I'm for real. What's on my face?
Uh, a dirty beard that I haven't shaved yet. And I probably won't do it until like tomorrow night.
Is that game of the year? Don't say that yet. We've still got like another few months or like
seven. Yes, I'm going to do the, I will do the new Labo sets. I promise. All right. So let's go back
a little while ago. We had, uh, Icy Youpi gave $10 earlier. They say cool stream kiddo. Thank you.
Thanks for coming up. Hope you enjoyed it. Can we collab? Can we collab? Can we collab?
What are you talking about? Why is everybody saying that? Can we collab? That was happening
before the stream started. Well, the answer is no. No, I don't do collabs. I, I do organic
accidental. We, if somebody's a friend and we do something, I don't, I don't do collabs.
Well, these faces that I, you know, I couldn't, I always, I never thought,
I never knew what that was until, um, I had better Twitch TV. I thought you guys are just
always at that. I didn't know that was an actual emote face. Played Toribash. I did play,
me and Star played Toribash like a couple of years ago, about like six years ago actually.
That was a long time. It was like 2012. If you want to watch Toribash, me play Toribash with a
friend, that video is still there. What's in here? You think that's still all right? I don't think
so. Plus it's like nine o'clock at night. Why would I do that? But thank you to, uh, Icy Youpi
for the 10 bucks. Smelly boy, thanks for the 250. Please, please, please tell us where Shido is.
I heard he's going to prison for trying to 3D print. What are you talking about? He,
Shido is in the other room. So what you guys didn't know is I can actually do these noises
with my mouth. You know what I mean? So I'm sorry that Shido is no longer here. Show us. Yeah,
this is in the cartoon when the, uh, when the, the big giant monster eats the person or eats,
eats the character that is in the show or something, or like a squeaky toy. And every time they try to
talk, they're just, they usually have a booming voice like this. And then when they open their
mouth, they like swallow it and they eat it. Oh no, the character's dead. I did that.
And then it becomes like a joke. There, Shido's right here. You're fine. See,
everybody thought I like threw it away. Why'd I throw this away? Somebody says you're a joke,
Jeremy. I got nothing to say about that. You're probably right. You're a joke. It's all right.
There's worse things I could be. Anyways, let's keep going. Uh, that was smelly boy. We proved it.
So Number Guts, 10 bucks from Number Guts. Thank you, Number Guts. Uh, consider my wig snatched
bald. I don't know what that means. My wig? I mean, I know this looks bad, but I don't know.
Might not even be what you're referring to, but thank you. Also, uh, uh, Zach said, Zach SD,
Zach East. I hope I'm saying that right. 10 dollars. Uh, hey man, I genuinely appreciate
your content and the effort you put into it. Your videos and streams got me through some
tough times. Cheers from Finland. Cheers back to you. Thank you. Thank you for the 10 bucks.
Thanks for sticking around the community. Kim check. Kim is not in there. I did, I was just
downstairs, but, uh, thanks for the 10 dollars. I appreciate every one of you guys that comes
out and watches this channel. So I couldn't do it without you. It wouldn't be possible.
So thank you, Kim. I almost just ran over my VR headset. I just crushed it and I would have blamed
all of you. I would have put the blame on you guys. That's like 500 bucks. I would have just
crushed it. I'll prove it again. Nobody in here. Well, okay. The boy who cried wolf. I'm going to
do that so many times. That one time someone's going to be actually in there. It's messy. It
is messy and it's very messy. It's an incredibly messy closet, but it's okay. But thank you, Zach.
Appreciate it. Superintendent Chalmers, two dollars, 66 cents. What do I think about the Star
Wars episode nine trailer? If you haven't seen it, do a YouTuber reaction on stream. I already saw it.
There's not enough info to go on, but there are some characters. Seems pretty cool.
If people are trying to avoid spoilers, I don't really want to talk about it because a lot of
people don't want to read or see spoilers. And there are a few things in that trailer that could
be, wow, I wish I didn't know that, right? So there are a few characters. I'm not going to tell you
who they are, but they're in it. You have an Ant-Man shirt on because you can relate to being
incredibly talented and very handsome and soaring like an eagle and be very, really cool.
And like Paul Rudd's really cool. And he's, he's like 50 years old and he looks like he's
fucking 28. What a person to be compared to. Thanks for comparing me to Paul Rudd. I appreciate that.
It means a lot. Stormy Chu. I missed this. I missed this. Stormy Chu gave 50 dollars,
5,000 bits from Stormy Chu. Thank you so much for the 50 fucking dollars. Wanted to remind you that
you're the best streamer. Whenever I'm in a bad mood, you can always manage to make me laugh.
You're doing great things and I hope you and Chad have a wonderful evening. Thank you. I'm sure other
people in chat are happy to hear that as well. You wishing everybody a wonderful evening.
For as much as people give me credit, right? Like so many people here are so funny and I see so
many people write like, oh, like, hey, have a good evening, Chad. Or like, oh, Chad, I met some
friends in chat or it, there's so much fucking going on here that you guys are so nice. Look,
we fucking around a lot. We do, but everyone's so nice to each other. It's refreshing. So many
people are just fun here and there's a huge difference. I know, like I said, that this,
we say shit, we make fun of stuff. We, I mean, like I said, like 80% of the stuff we say is
just bullshit. You guys all know that, but I'm so shocked and surprised every day at just how
like fun of a community this is. I'm very fortunate. So 100% of what I say is bullshit.
Well, there you go. At least you've made it clear now, but still make sure that thank you for the
$50. That's more money than I could ever ask anyone to ever hand me through a stream. So
thank you. That means a shitload. 50 bucks. Make sure to floss too, as Grub Club says. Yes.
Chunky Baloney, 10 bucks, $10 from Chunky Baloney. Thank you. In summer camp one year,
I was messing around with a bicycle tire just like that and accidentally busted somebody's
lip open. They had to go to the hospital and get multiple stitches. Don't do that. Be careful.
You can actually get fucked up like that. Don't do it. Accidentally, in quotes. Guys, it's not,
it's not like you're going to spin the wheel and like go after somebody with it.
They do that on Malcolm in the Middle. Is that where, is that what that's from? I thought it
was from Pee Wee Herman. Doesn't that happen in Pee Wee? That happens in Pee Wee Herman's
movie, right? That definitely happens in a Pee Wee Herman bit. I think so. What happens? The
bike thing when you spin the bike upside down so the wheels are pointing up and then somebody
goes like this with the wheel and then somebody else's face gets like burnt on the, that's from
a Pee Wee Herman. He's still on this. I'm not. Somebody just brought it up and I'm explaining.
Supposed to be end screen music. Uh, I don't have the end screen up. We're just chilling out.
I'm almost done. There's not very many more left to go. So he's going to go until someone says,
yes. What do you mean? But thank you, Chunky Ballona. And that sounds like a horrible fucking
story. Hopefully everyone's all right. Number Guts, Five Dolls from Number Guts. Hey, German,
me and my partners have watched you for a long time and you've been an incredible and consistent
source of joy. I've been going through a lot over the past few years and your content's helped me
make some of the real bad days a little easier. Thank you. Thank you for being here. And I say it
a lot, but I have to say it a lot because I really only fucking care about us having a good time.
If you are having fun, that's fucking awesome. I'm glad because that's all I give a shit about.
All this, this, this, all this, this room, this room, the whole room is just, I want to have fun
and I want you to do too. The whole thing. I'll rip, I'll rip that closet door off if it means
you're going to have fun. I will rip it off with my bare hands and I'll snap it off my fucking knee
like twig in a dream, in fake reality. Not real. Dude, why would I, I can't do that. That's a
95% of everything I say is not true. Use a screwdriver for, yeah, I'm just going to go in
there and like rip it off the hinges. You don't, you won't do that for us. I'm not going to, no.
Oh, rum fun. Rum. Rum. My rump. My room. Jeremy, you look defeated. No, I look like I was in VR for
four and a half hours. This is why the drunk, I told you the drunk stream was so much worse.
I said this in the chat in the beginning of the stream, but I want to make it clear again.
When you drink and do VR, you save state yourself outside of the headset. So when I was like drinking
the wine and going into the headset, I, reality was different. It wasn't, I was like getting
drunker because like in the headset, I wasn't drunk. When the headset would come off, it'd be
like, I mean, it was, I was saved stating my drunkenness. It was crazy. And VR Josh was
talking about how, because in the headset, it's, he's right. You don't see blurry vision in VR.
It's everything so crystal clear that you don't even realize. So you take the headset off and
all of a sudden you're like, take another sip and you're like, holy fuck. It's just, it makes
you five times drunker. Be careful. Don't, don't drink and do VR for too long. Like I did. Although
I was fine, but just, you know, your health is important. I would puke if I drank and put on my
headset. Why do you think I needed to take yesterday off? I drank an entire bottle of wine two days ago
and did VR for seven hours. Like that was energy levels. What's going on here? I'm going to leave
it. I'm going to leave it to scare away all the new people. Where's the mouth vomit clip? I don't
know, but I forgot that I did that. I did that. I did the fake insta puke. Somebody has to have it.
I went back and I looked at the VOD. No, nobody laughed at this. They were concerned. I thought
people were going to think it was funny because I've done it a couple of times before, but I did
like the fake insta puke swallow it. Nobody thought it was funny. It was like so realistic
because I was so drunk. People were like, stop, stop, are you all right? I don't think anybody has
a clip of it. I didn't even acknowledge that I did it either. Is this channel bits only? What are you
talking about? We're almost done. It's been like 15 minutes. Nobody wants to see it again. I kind
of wanted to see it though. You were retroactively saying it was a joke. I've done that like three or
four times before. I've gotten that down real well that people can fucking be confused by it.
That's that's the snort clip of my click on that. If there's one thing that I know how to do really
well, it's fake insta puke and insta swallow it and make it look like it actually happened.
It's one of my talents. One of the things I can do. But let's move on. We're almost done.
Soul Harry, thanks for the 260. Hey Jerma, could you please do us a favor and save the
Mind Show Dread Hall stream from last time to your channel's highlights before it's deleted?
Why would it be deleted? Chat was fantastic that whole stream and also an integral part of
understanding the Kim scare. We wouldn't want it to be lost in time. Oh you talk about after 60 days.
Yeah well it's deleted after two months. Well that means that like the drunk stream is forever
etched in my Twitch bibliography. I don't know if I want to do that. That's the thing that's
number one on my highlights. That would be the only one I have. Oh yeah man like come on to
Jerma985. What have you got for highlights? Let's see. From 2011, testing to see if the
highlight feature works with a hand of fate clip where he accidentally clicks on something
and dies from a boulder. And he never deleted that for some reason. I don't know why he didn't.
And an entire stream of him embarrassingly drunk. Sounds great. YouTube. Yeah the YouTube
archive is fine. Maybe I'll maybe I'll just get see if we can pull the chat. Maybe I can pull that
chat. There's no chat. I can pull that chat. I can pull that chat. We'll get a way to pull that chat
out. Embarrassingly drunk. We'll get that chat. Don't worry. But thank you for the 260. Appreciate
it. Ethan Ricks. Thanks for 10 dollars here. Long time viewer. First time subber and donator. You're
the funniest person in the world. That's a that's a lot. That means thank you. In my opinion you
always make my day so this is my way to repay you for your content you rat bastard. That's a that's
a heavy load to hold. I'm shocked. I can't believe you think I'm that funny or entertaining. Thank
you. I hope it can stay that way. I hope you still have fun. There it is. Is this it? Oh this is it.
I need to watch this on stream. I can't wait to see this. I get this like shit eating grit on my
face. Hold on. Give me a second. I gotta change my audio here. Speakers. Okay. Can you guys hear
that? You should be able to hear that now. No shit you can't. Hey there we go. Okay. All right let's
get this on screen. Wait I do it again? I don't I don't remember doing that again.
Holy shit I did it like four times. Always doing something different.
Wait wait wait wait wait. The whole vines. Hold on. Are you talking about the talent? Are you talking
about like who I think is the funniest and most interesting? What do you think? Who? Everyone
fucking was freaking out. Second one was no none of them are real. None of them are real.
Uh the chat is the best. The chat is so fucking funny. Can I get it? Oh. Are you talking about
who I think is the funniest? People usually people weren't laughing. Stop. See stop.
Sad face. Who? Oh fuck. What what the fuck? Vinny. Joel. What the fuck? MonkaS. They always do.
What the fuck? Ew. What? What the fuck was that noise? Stop it. The whole Vinesauce team
always doing something. God damn it man. I don't know. I've got something fucking wrong with me.
Uh but thank you EthanRix for the 10 bucks. Thank you JermaWide about Fruity Loops.
Damn this streamer is kind of cringy. Why the fuck would you say something like that? Okay.
I can't get it to play again. So this streamer is like this stream is kind of cringy huh?
That's interesting. Like never mind. It's all fucked up. I can't even do it. It's fucked up.
Well thank you for the 250. Whatever. That don't matter. Uh thank you for the 250. JermaWide
lied about Fruity Loops. Not yet. Is it a lie if it eventually happens? That's not a lie. If it
happens it happens. Thank you for the 250. Thank you Novaz for the 250. Is the green screen parts
do still have? I could have pat my face. Yes. Oh there's been so many though. I have to.
Yes. Yes. Yes. There's so many. I could have. Yes. So I have an Instagram. I do not have an
Instagram account. I don't have any social media accounts besides Twitter. And I haven't tweeted a
real tweet this since like February. So I don't do social media. I'm disconnected from social media.
This is the only social media that I have. YouTube channels. Twitch. My Twitter. My official
Jerma985 Twitter. And that's it. I had a Facebook at one point. I haven't said anything on that
Facebook in probably four and a half years. Nothing. I don't do the social media thing.
Except for here. Right now. It's my entire. My entire career is social media. But I don't
do the social media thing. I don't tweet that. I don't like Facebook that.
How do I keep up with the new memes? You guys. I see what it is. Somebody writes it and then I type
it into Google and I find out what it is. And then I make references to it and I look like I'm in
with a hip crop. You know. Yes it will happen. I'm just. I know. I know. I'm bad. Mostly lost.
Thanks for 250. Jerma, you ever heard of a razor? It's a nice modern invention that can help with
that shit all over your face. And that's the show. And that's the show. Thank you TV. That's
thank you TY Towns for the five dollars. Had to give some bits for the doom house slayer.
You're funny Jerma. I think that was more fun than funny. But it was still fun. Maybe you thought
it was fun. Glad you did. Thank you for the five dollars. Freudian Weapon 250. Happy Friday. Can't
wait for more Disassembly Shunen against tomorrow night. We will go live tomorrow night. Probably
on the same time. And we will keep it. Keep it going. I will see you tomorrow. But thank you.
Something or other. Thanks for the 250. Heard about the sweet deal with Nintendo for the new
game on the SNES. Looking forward to it. Jerma Quest. Sometimes big things come in compact
packages. Thank you for that. Fender McBender. Thanks for the three dollars. Did you hear about
that comedian who died from a heart attack on stage? And no one realized it because they
thought it was a bit. That's horrifying. Yeah that's fucking horrifying. That's terrible.
Um that sucks. I can't even imagine how fucked up that would be. You think it might be like part
of a joke or a bit? Damn. Yeah that's. That just makes you feel terrible. But how long
ago did it happen? When was it? Was it recently? Jesus. Yeah that's scary shit. But yeah you just
gotta. You just gotta be careful. At some point maybe um. Did I call level up plunge? No not yet.
That's kind of on the plan though for the summer. It was years ago. Not yesterday. Oh well regardless
still that still sucks. But thank you for the three dollar spender. Uh Peek-A-Banana 250. Hey
Jerma my friend wants to know what the paint color of your walls are because he wants to paint.
He wants that paint color for his place. Um Sand 3 I think. Thank you. Hey Flugboy. 250 from Flugboy.
They say toro-roo-roo-roo. Hello boss Jeremy. Does want to know you do great things for my guy.
You do great things my guy. My mood is always automatically switched to cheerful when you start
streaming. Mosh moshi. Have a good night. Well thank you. I'm glad that you feel that way.
Thanks for the 250. Stick around there's more to see. Uh Mark Shinobi. Thanks for the five dollars.
Hey Jerma where is Sekiro on your top from software games and can you list your top five
from software games? I'm about to play all of them because I hate myself. Uh love you bro never missed
a stream. Thank you. That's that's a I can't believe that you've never missed a stream. That
there's a lot of times a lot of hours. But uh Sekiro is underneath Bloodborne and it's underneath
Demon's Souls. So I think the total list from least favorite to most favorite is
Dark Souls 2, um Dark Souls 3, Dark Souls 1, Demon's Souls, Sekiro, Bloodborne. That's where they
stand. No no no no no no no. I yes yeah Sekiro is above. I think Sekiro might be like tied.
Yeah let me I gotta do it again. I gotta like think about it. Okay Dark Souls 2 is my I still
liked it but it was not as fun as the other ones I think. Dark Souls 2 is the bottom. Uh Dark Souls
3 mainly because I just had gotten over the Bloodborne craze and it was like oh I want more
Bloodborne and this was kind of like fast like Bloodborne but it wasn't um I wasn't like a big
fan of the areas in Dark Souls 3. Something about them there was only a few areas that I really
really liked. Then Dark Souls 1 and Sekiro are probably tied just because Dark Souls 1 was just
you know it's it was so interesting. I would still probably put Sekiro over Dark Souls 1
because this there's a lot of shit in Dark Souls 1 that kind of like is unfinished.
Rushed a little. There's two of those areas felt very I think they even by the admission of From
Software were kind of thrown out as fast as they could but I would probably put Sekiro a hair above
Dark Souls 1 and then Demon's Souls and then Bloodborne. Bloodborne is if Demon's Souls is
here and Sekiro is here like oh and like Dark's Demon's Souls, Sekiro, Dark Souls 1 are all like
right here. Dark Souls 3 is like down here. Dark Souls 2 is down here. Bloodborne is all the way
up here. You can't even see it. It's off the fucking chart. Somebody said Jello arm. I'm fucking 33.
Okay I'm not like 20. I'm not like I'm not 20. Okay I'm 33. I'm not 20. God damn it. That's why
I never have a camera ever because I would look over and I'll see Jello arm and it'll throw off
my entire night. I'll be like, you don't look a day over four. Thank you. That means a lot.
Tweet the fight. I have to like link it to my Twitter which drunk me was not going to figure
that out so I'll figure it out. But thank you to Mark Shidobi. Hopefully that answers your question.
Bloodborne's number one. Garfield the Monday killer. Two dollars and fifty cents.
Gig Garfity goo. Here comes Garferoni with a load of funny bits for you in a wheelbarrow.
Just gonna dump it right over here for you. Do you like me yet? Garp craves approval. Are you
looking forward to Shrek 2 remake? Why would they remake Shrek 2 before Shrek 1? Do you think
Garfield will be a part of it? I'll be voicing Shrek and Donkey. Tell Lord director of 21 Jump
Street is working on the same project as Garfield since we agreed to do a scene. Would Jerm be
interested in doing a part in the film? Maybe a three second camera. My favorite part about
all the Garfield bits is in like a full two like almost full paragraph of just word soup.
There's a there's like three lines of a question you know. Okay so we have like a paragraph of
word soup and then are you excited for Shrek 2 remake? There's always something there. There's
always like substance there. So I don't I didn't even know that existed Garfield. Thank you for
the 250. He's got a yeah he's got a world of lore that he has. The Garfograph sandwich technique
is just it's passed on for generations of Garfields. Guys I hate to tell you this and people are gonna
maybe maybe this is a sad thing to say. Gar Garfield's cat he's been around for like 60 years.
Cats don't live 60 years. There's been like five or six Garfields. I don't cats only live like
15, 16, 20 plus maybe years. It's been like three or four of them. Are you insinuating that Garfield
can die? I'm insinuating that an animal a cat which is what Garfield is does not live on record.
I don't think there's never been a cat on record that has lived past 28 years old or 30. Even if
that cat even if Garfield was the most highly living cat in the history of the world he still
has been from two or three. Oh what about SpongeBob? SpongeBob is a sponge that's they live forever.
Oh no my my my cup oh it's only got like 15, 20, 30. No no what are you talking about?
Like Turtle? There's a couple of Turtle characters. Who's a popular Turtle character? Did that? He'll
be around for 150 years. Franklin the Turtle. Yeah Franklin the Turtle is like 40. He's got like 60
or 70 to 80 more years left to go. The Ninja Turtles. Oh that's right the Teenage Mutant Ninja
Turtles. They're gonna be eating pizza and cracking some skulls for like another 100 years.
That's why they got bought out by Disney. Viacom. So they got bought out by Viacom.
He's checking his Twitch stocks. I don't even fucking want to look at those.
But only a few more bits to go. Thank you Garfield. We're just poking fun at you. We're
just kidding around. Don't worry. We all love you. Don't worry. We're just we're just playing.
We're just playing around with the idea that you probably died six times. But thank you. Thank you
Jack. Jack you jacked the Mac for the five dollars. Jeremy my grandma passed away today
due to a banana experiment. I don't know what that means. I don't know if it's serious.
I'm sorry to hear that. Sorry to hear that. If that's sorry for your loss. If that's you know
thank you for the five dollars. Wow. Why the fuck do you look like that? You know what I've got to
fucking put this up here because I'm gonna hold this because like this is like this is my proof
that like I've got a headset here. Okay you ready? So here I'm like I just got out you know.
Hey man you uh having some trouble with your VR headset? So then if you come to the stream and
you didn't you didn't mean you weren't here before you're just like oh okay just um all right where
were we? Mostly lost. Oh I got some like mouth problems. Don't bite your lips. Uh thanks for the
250 mostly lost. On the subject of paint colors I've always said the one guaranteed job for
English majors is coming up with names for paints. Yeah like there's like a light green and it's like
springtime sea cucumber or something. That's true. Sand free. I'm not an English major though.
That's I mean you can make fun of me all you want but I that's I'm not an English major.
Are you an angry guy? I don't I don't think so. Uh but thank you mostly lost. Thank you to all
Mew for the three bucks. I cannot believe that so many people come out to watch you take apart
things in a virtual reality. I mean to think technologies come this far. Next thing you know
everyone and their grandma are going to have a oma. I'm not going to do that. I I know all the
tricks. I know all the tricks. I'm not going to say it. Thank you for the uh three dollars.
Hey bop beep thanks for three bucks. Appreciate it. It's uh oh he's going to puke. It's a youtube
link. Faith of the heart? Enterprise team? What is this? There's a song? I've got faith of the heart.
I don't I don't know what this is. I've never heard it. Uh thanks for the link. It's not another
Garfa graph. Yes there is. Hey uh gibbler thanks for the five dollars. Any plans to check out
outward? It's like Kenshi mixed with breath of the wild just came out on steam. Probably not.
Not in the immediate future here. There's so many other things that are going to come
first. Uh italics played it already and he was telling me about it. I'm not sure it's something
that I don't know if it's something I want to do. But yeah I'm not going to 100% rule it out,
but I'm not going to 100% rule it in either. So when's the next emote contest? I don't I don't
know. I don't have a plan in the moment for it, but that's my stance. Uh sticks renegade thanks
for the two dollars 55 cents. Thank you sticks. You've heard of the comb stream. Now this spring
get ready for the shave stream. Seriously shave on stream. No no I'm not going to shave on stream.
I'm not no no way. Hey pika banana thanks for the 250 german. You might have thought I was joking,
but my friend is actually now going to paint his room sand free. Thanks for answering the question.
I hope that's the correct color because I made that up. So here look look look I'll get look.
Let me give you a hand here. I'm gonna help you. Let me give you a hand. Just bring this into
Home Depot. Take a screenshot and just like bring that into Home Depot. Yeah ask him for this. You
got it? Wait I'll make it smaller. So get like a good shot of that and then get that in. Pretty
good poster. Bring that in and just ask him what he thinks. Ask him what he thinks about that. Hey
what do you think about this? I'm just gonna keep it like this. We're almost done. I can't fix it.
It's too hard. Ask him what he thinks about this. Wait hold on. All right um we had uh Garfy the
Monday killer 250. You've you're mistaken Jerm. I died seven times. How have you died seven times?
Garf is currently on his eighth life. I was a cave cat and got crushed by an odysseus rex frozen in
ice as a viking garf. Shot on the chest as a private eye garf. Stretched apart by a taffy
puller as three stooges routine garf. Transformed into a dog in the lab and then died shortly after
with problems of the mutation. Died a peaceful death in a rainbow fun land and the seventh one
was an immortal cat demon that got bored and died. He's eight. Thank you. Jerma lied about
Minecraft VR with five WDD subs. Thank you the five subs. I'm looking right at you. I'm looking
right at you. Take this shit into Home Depot and say what do you think about this? You're a creep.
Yeah that's sand three. You got it. You're doing great. You figure it out. All right we're at the
end of the bits. Mostly lost cup work just came in. Three uh 250 from mostly lost. Well if you're
not going to shave on stream you better damn well shave off stream. I will not. I'm going to look
like this tomorrow. I don't want to. Maybe tomorrow. Hey the mad god thanks for three bucks. Any chance
you'll bring back some of the winners of previous rumbles like the pencil captain crunch. It'd be
cool to see these legends return and also a match between Dr. Oetker and Gabe Newell clash
of titans. Not sure if this sent twice or not. Good night chat. I would. It's just in the new.
I don't. Let's just fucking get this fixed. I look like a sicko. What am I doing? That's okay.
That's better. That's just too weird. I look like a fucking weirdo. I look like a weirdo.
Okay I would but the problem is uh wwe all the ones after 2k14
not very good. They weren't good with the creative characters. They you can't do as much crazy shit.
You can't really make captain crunch in those games now. The pencil is impossible to make in
any of the new ones and going back and making them on the old ones they're so hard to make.
When you get more than 10 20 30 wrestlers and you do like more than 10 layers some of those
characters took hours to make just because of the loading times so I would not go back.
It would be it's so hard to do that and it would make it even worse because I don't have the
PlayStation 3. I don't have that PlayStation 3 so the like 40 of 50 characters I made on that
2k14 they don't exist anymore. They're gone forever. That place I don't I'm not in possession of it so
I don't have to save file so I would have to remake everybody. It would take me like it would
take me a month to do that so making like 75 characters in a thing that takes like an hour
and a half to make a character with more than 10 20 layers unfortunately we're gonna have to just
let it let it uh I was gonna say rise we have to let it rise and I'll go get it I'll go get it
tomorrow no do you think we'll ever see another goofy wrestling game ever again probably not
because apparently simulations are more important than making weird characters and maybe that's just
maybe that's just we have to kind of fade out here and and let the default guy in underwear first
name last name versus default guy in underwear first name last name is more important than a
guy in a clown suit so I don't think they care anymore because I we need glue man you can still
make glue man still you can make glue man still just I've seen it a couple times in the chat
fix your camera before I fix my camera there's nothing wrong with it you didn't like those edges
yeah are we good are you good uh get a ps3 get to get him I don't know where it is I gave it to
somebody is it okay is this a parrot or is this me proving why I look so bad I feel like I'm holding
the dog like okay here's my dog guys yeah it's cute huh uh peek a banana five community subs
speaking of the subs let's get them on uh camera here let's put them up all the community subs
and all the new subs and old ones here they come right here three four five at least six
at least six thank you guys though for real thank you thank you thank you uh there are
still one or two more bits to do thank you jack the mac for the five dollars have you ever
been noticed in public before other than for charities or events happy friday I have been
noticed in public like twice very random occurrences they I don't think it'll ever happen again
but now it's happened usually happens at a convention but if I'm not at a convention
it's only happened like two or three times in almost 10 years so it doesn't really happen
that often it's still really interesting what it does though and then zulaski thanks for the 250
and they say they say check this out cream puff the cat was a domestic cat she was the oldest cat
ever recorded according to the guinness book world records when she died she was 38 years old
and then the same family had another cat that was 34 years old from the same family you got to figure
yeah I would that point I'd be like what what what were they eating you know that's insane
38 years old and then 34 that's that is impressive but thank you for the little fact there
and then we had the five community subs and peek banana and then finally at the very end
mass shinobi three dollars thanks for answering my question but in my humble opinion of course
without offending anyone who thinks differently from my point of view but also by looking into
this matter in a different perspective and without being condemning of one's views and trying to make
it objectified and by considering each and every one's valid opinion I honestly believe
that I completely forget what I was going to say that's it thank you for the three bucks
yes you got it 250 I purchased the ingredients for lemon basil ice cream wish me luck you're
gonna love it let me get over here so you can see me you're gonna love it you're gonna love it update
us I want to know but let's get this off let the credits play out here in the very end thank you
everybody see you tomorrow take care stream legends you got it of course how could I forget
I forget every time so that is how see you guys tomorrow we're gonna take some more things apart
I love this game so I'm gonna play it again you know it's pretty rare that you sit down you go
holy shit I love this so that's what we're gonna do let me get my okay extensions here you go you
ready in three two one here comes the free gift there it goes all right guys that's my time I'll
see you soon I gotta go uh bathe I'm gonna try to go longer tomorrow I mean five and a half hours
this is a typical VR stream but I'll I'm gonna try to go like at least five hours in the headset
tomorrow I will give it a real attempt I'll see you soon any idea what you're gonna play we're
gonna play more of the disassembly and if we get sick of that then there are plenty of options
uh go for a raid who's streaming right now let's see who's streaming a list of people
who have I not like rated or like said hello to in a while Nova cry again yeah maybe we'll
raid Nova it's been a while critical yeah critical is yeah let me see what are they playing that's
important italics yeah we played we played with italics last week though
gta 5 world war z what the hell is world war z isn't that out the game isn't that game already
out isn't that critical is playing apex
yeah let's go say hi to uh the Nova let's go raid Nova it's been a while since we've said hello
no I'm kind of interested in what this game is so I'm gonna watch for a minute too
all right cue it up here we go thanks I'll see you tomorrow have a wonderful rest of your night
see you soon guys and load it up good night