Hello everyone, my name is Bacon and welcome to the German Stream Archive.
Today I have a long overdue update video for you all where we'll be talking about some important
things. It's been a long time since the last update video and because of that there's a lot
that needs to be talked about. There are timestamps in the description and the comments for each
section you might find important. You can also make use of the YouTube chapter feature to skip
around to find the info you're looking for. There's this section which is the introduction.
Here we'll be talking a little bit about who we are, what we do in the channel, and where we came
from. After that we need to talk about the channel being officially partnered with Germa
and monetization. Next we'll be talking about changes and improvements to how we archive
streams. After that we'll be talking about chat replay which is a new way to watch back chat on
our uploads. If that interests you then you don't want to miss that section. Finally I'll be ending
with a Q&A answering some questions that we keep getting asked. As I mentioned before it's been a
long time since the last update video. Between the last update video and now both Germa and this
channel have grown tenfold so I felt it's worth reintroducing Starkiller and I. My name is Bacon.
I own and run this channel alongside Starkiller. I started the Sturr Stream Archive more than five
years ago around late 2016 and added Germa to the archive shortly after to make it the Sturr
slash Germa Stream Archive. In late 2018 we split the channel into two, the Sturr Stream Archive
and the Germa Stream Archive. Since then Germa has only grown exponentially in popularity until
we get where we are today. My role in this channel is to download the video from Twitch
and re-upload them to YouTube. I also handle most of the business management and community
affairs of this channel like this update video. Starkiller is my friend who's been helping me
run this channel since near the start. Starkiller has his own channel where he used to archive
Germa streams until he noticed my channel getting more views and having the official name
Sturr slash Germa Stream Archive so he messaged me one day asking if he should stop uploading on
his channel. Instead of telling him to stop I actually decided to invite him to work on
the archive channel with me and he's been helping me since. His role in the channel is making the
thumbnail, putting the title, the description, end cards, and the rest of what makes a video a video.
He used to handle the downloading and uploading of VODs as well before I got my fiber internet.
If for some reason I can't download a VOD he's usually my backup and he comes in the clutch
because of that. Now that you know this a little bit better let's talk more about the partnership
and monetization I mentioned before. You guys heard me right, partnership. I've been talking
to Community Jake and Germa and they've asked us to come work for them officially and make the
channel an official archive channel as well as be a part of Germa's umbrella of channels.
For the most part things will be run the same except for a few changes we'll talk about later
in this video. It's just that now we're official and we'll be getting paid for it. After the last
time I mentioned monetization or donations I've decided to be careful about money on this channel.
The last time still giving me nightmares for even daring to mention monetization.
Before I felt it wasn't fair to enable ads without Germa's permission or without working
something out with him first. Now since we're officially working for Germa we'll be enabling
monetization on streams. I know people don't like ads so Community Jake and I decided on a decent
spacing of ads that won't be too intrusive for you guys. I really hope you guys don't get too
angry at us this time because honestly this opportunity Community Jake and Germa have given
us is like a ray of light in the dark for us here at the archive. If you feel this monetization is
unfair towards Germa then don't worry. Part of this ad revenue will go straight back to Germa
and funding his big shows. As for the money that is coming to us at the archive we will do our
best to earn our keep which leads us to the next section I want to talk about upcoming changes
and improvements we plan on making to the channel. A while back I made a survey about the volume of
Germa streams. In that survey I asked if there were any changes that you wanted to see made to
the channel. I wanted to thank everyone who left a suggestion even if you made a suggestion for a
change that was denied. I really appreciate all the comments. The suggestions have been read
through and considered. Changes that are rejected will be explained as to why afterwards.
It's important to understand that we're trying to balance the channel being an archive and the
channel being viewer friendly. For example splitting the streams up by game versus not
splitting up the streams up at all versus splitting an eight hour stream into shorter sections of four
hours each. Inevitably I can't make everyone happy but I can do my best by making a few improvements.
With that being said let's first start with changes not to be made. Many of these stem from
not having enough time or just not being very feasible. The first thing is having playlists for
many different types of streams or even just a playlist for different periods and arcs of
Germa's life and the reason I don't want to do this is because having too many playlists makes
it hard to sort through and also it's just too many playlists to kind of sort things into so
that'll be a little bit too much. The next one is more detailed timestamps and chapters.
For example timestamping highlights or skipping to a specific point in the VOD or timestamping
the beginning of him playing. For this one I'd say just have a little bit more patience. It takes
too much time to timestamp everything. We do like however seeing some people timestamp different
bits in the video and we may occasionally heart some of those comments if you timestamp the video
so thank you if you do that. The next one is kind of similar in that it's editing out BRB sections
and trimming streams down. This one takes a little bit too much work for not much return.
If you don't like the BRB sections try watching some long edits of the streams like Skye's
long edits or Chelsea's stream recaps or if those are too long watch the second Germa videos which
are also very very good with some talented editors. On top of all that we're a stream
archive so it doesn't make much sense to edit the streams down. The next one on the list is
having the date in the title. Now this one kind of clutches the title too much. In the past we
used to put the title in the the date in the title but we decided to take it off. It's nicer and
cleaner not having the date and the date is already in the description. This next one is speeding up
VOD uploads. This one I kind of don't really understand because usually I like to have the
videos uploaded the night of the stream and have it go up the next morning. It takes a little bit
of extra time to get all the bits ready especially if it's closer to midnight when he ends the stream
or if it's a bigger stream like the latest Elden Ring streams. So if it takes any longer it's
usually due to copyright or having to edit the video for some other reason or it's a big stream
that I'm waiting for Community Jake to send a copy of the studio recording. If for some reason
it takes a little longer than I expect I usually try to announce it in the archive discord so if
you want some more news about when a video is going to come out late go ahead and join the
archive discord. This next one is kind of similar to what we talked about before splitting the videos
up into parts for example splitting Elden Ring part one into two four-hour videos. This one's not
really feasible for the same reason as not trimming it down. It takes more time to do for not much
return more time to upload and it wouldn't be a very good viewing experience for the majority of
people. YouTube does a really good job of saving your place or you can just leave a comment with
the timestamp that you left off. I prefer to have one eight-hour video than two four-hour videos
and this also means less ads in general. This next one is on the other spectrum of splitting
streams and that is not splitting streams that have two games in it. This one we like to do at
the archive because it makes it easier for a couple reasons. One if a stream gets blocked or a game
gets blocked for whatever reason the audio the music in the game it makes it easier to split the
game up so that the other game that he streams doesn't get blocked. Another reason we like doing
this is because it helps people find the game they want to see Jerma playing without having
them skim through a bunch of different streams to try to find it. It also makes things easier to
place them in the playlist for organization's sake and also for people wanting to binge watch
a specific game. This next one relates to what we talked about earlier with monetization and that
is to reduce the amount of ads in videos. Now I want to make clear that if any video gets any
amount of copyright claims more times than not there tends to be an insane amount of ads and we
can't do anything about it to reduce the amount of ads. For example the Laugh You Lose video got
claimed and has so many ads in such a short amount of time. I've heard reports of about one every 10
seconds. For the videos that we can control ads on I do my best to make sure to minimize ads while
still keeping him there. When I talked to community Jake about it I told him that I like to keep ads
to a relative minimum and he agreed so we agreed on a good ad spacing for us both. This next one
asks us to put the hour a stream starts into the description. Now for this one I kind of want to
ask why. Also I don't really know how to find that without keeping track of the time he starts
because oftentimes he starts at different times and he's just late. This one asks us to announce
when VODs will come out. Now for this one as I mentioned before VODs usually come out within
the next day or two of the original stream. If it takes any longer I'll announce it in the community
tab or I'll announce it in our discord. A few of you have asked us to place VODs into a non-youtube
place for example mega, dropbox, google drive, etc. This is something that I've actually kind of
wanted to do but I'm not even sure how to do it without an insane additional cost for the amount
of streams and data that are going to be archived the extra time it'll take to upload them. It's
something I'm interested in but it's just not very feasible at the moment. This next one is one that
gets requested fairly often and that is to put the twitch VOD link in the description. After a couple
months the original VOD gets deleted meaning the link is only valid for those 60 days that the VOD
is available. While I could delete the link after 60 days I'm not really looking to track every VOD
for 60 days for the rest of the time German streams so yeah sorry about that. After around
germans resident evil village streams this is one that gets requested fairly often and that is to
upscale the videos into 1080p uploads instead of letting youtube downscale to 720p. Now there's
a little bit of technicality stuff going on here but to kind of put it simply it's a little bit
more work to put into 1080p. This is something that I actually kind of want to see and look into
and experiment but if it ends up being too hard to do too much overhead we might not end up doing
it so there's a chance that we'll do this but don't really count on it too much at the moment.
This next one is one that gets requested very often and that is to put chat on screen. The
reason I don't want to do this is because I don't want chat to become mandatory for people who
dislike chat. I know a good portion actually a majority of people don't like having chat on
screen. In the past I did a poll and a majority of the people said that they didn't like chat and
didn't want chat on screen so because of this I don't want to make it mandatory for people who
don't want it. Now I understand that having chat is what makes a stream well a stream but I can't
admit that chat can be distracting at times and sometimes you just want to see a full screen of
germa focus on germa. Now this last denied change I want to talk about is anything that relates to
changes on germa's side for example putting chat on stream or having more facecam time or doing
specific kind of stream because for the simple fact that I am not germa. Well that was a little
bit long and I hope you guys weren't getting too bored but now it's time for the exciting part
which is talking about the upcoming changes and improvements that I want to implement.
Starting off we'll be talking about one change that's on germa's side. The main purpose of the
VOD volume survey was to determine if it was a minority a majority of people who were experiencing
audio issues with germa streams. I showed the results of the VOD volume survey to Community
Jake and both Germa and Community Jake agreed that something needs to be changed so they'll be
looking into making some changes soon. Frankly I'm actually really happy that I was able to do
something that helps improve the stream for everyone else. Now for the first change that
we'll be making on the channel is we'll be starting to mark the start and end of the BRB
segments to make it its own BRB segment in the chapters. Additionally we'll also be time stamping
where we pull the thumbnail from. Big streams are important for Germa right now so I want to make
sure that his archive of that stream is as good a quality as we can get it. So because of that
Community Jake will be sending us recordings of those big production streams to upload.
If for whatever reason he can't send it then we'll be uploading the twitch version instead.
This next one is something that's been requested fairly often and that is having community made
subtitles. We'll be looking a little bit into having these community made subtitles. Now
obviously this change relies more on the community so it's not for sure if this change will be made
for certain but if anybody's interested in helping write eight hour long subtitles for
fans of hard hearing please let me know message me on discord my discord will be in the description.
At the very least if anybody's interested in helping subtitle some of Germa's bigger streams
I'd be very grateful for that. This next change and the change after that are some changes that
we've already made to the archive channel. The first change slash improvement being uploading
and recovering older lost vods or blocked streams that have been blocked worldwide or for
certain people. As some of you keen-eyed viewers may have seen we've already re-uploaded Germa's
Jump King part 2 stream which is uploaded with some parts muted while keeping Germa's voice intact.
Big thanks to Sky for helping out with the audio for that stream. If you guys haven't already please
go to his channel and give him some love. He's been very kind and helpful to me. I wanted to
start bringing back more of those long lost blocked streams or even some of the very old
streams that were thought to be lost to time if possible. I'll be making a community post in the
near future asking for suggestions on what videos you want to see returned next for the next change
we've already made. For streams that we have separated by game like a recent stream where he
streamed Mario Golf, Picross, Big Brand Academy, and Elden Ring we'll be linking the other games
within that same stream but you'll be able to click the link to it in the comments of the video
to other parts within that same stream. Getting down to the last couple changes the next one is
having detailed thumbnails for example part numbers within the thumbnail. We're going to
start trying to put a little bit more detail into the thumbnails mostly just putting part
numbers on the thumbnail if applicable but we'll see what else we can do. Finally the last thing
I want to talk about is something that has been requested over and over again. In the past I've
said I wanted a way to add chat to these VODs while at the same time making them optional for
people that don't want them or don't like having the chat alongside the video. I'm pleased to
announce that I finally have a solution that's available for you guys. What I have for you guys
is a website called Chat Replay. Well what is it you may be asking? This website will allow you to
watch archived drama streams with a replay of twitch chat alongside the video. This means you
get to see your favorite one guy moments live in chat or see twitch chat say hi to the VOD watchers.
That's you guys. Chat Replay will not only let you watch archived drama streams with chat but also
many other participating channels. That's not all though. If you prefer to stay on YouTube to watch
streams then you can take advantage of the Chat Replay extension to have chat embedded right on
the YouTube page right next to the video. The extension will add a button below the YouTube
player that will allow you to embed chat into the YouTube page, pop chat out to put wherever you
please, or open a twitch-like theater mode for you to view just like you're on Twitch.
The extension is available now on Chrome and Firefox. If you're on a browser that doesn't
support the extension or you're on mobile, you can still make use of the Chat Replay website.
If you guys know a YouTube channel that uploads a copy of Twitch streams to YouTube
and you want to see Chat Replay on that channel, ask them to message me or Restorn on Discord.
My Discord will be in the description and Restorn's Discord can be found on the top
of the Chat Replay website if you click the Join button. I just want to remind you guys that when
you're asking your favorite channels to implement Chat Replay, please do so politely. Don't spam them
asking them to join your Chat Replay and keep it civilized, please. You can link them to this video
with a timestamp to the start of this section or just link them to the Chat Replay website.
The link to the website and the download pages for the extension will be in the description.
Bringing you guys Chat wouldn't be possible without the help of community member Restorn.
He's the one who created and maintains Chat Replay in the background, so please give him
some of your guys' thanks. In addition, if you guys run into any problems, please let him know
directly. Please don't leave any comments somewhere else and expect a problem to be fixed.
If you guys like Chat Replay, please feel free to toss Restorn a couple dollars using the Donate
button on the top right of the website. You guys have been asking for Chat for a long time. It's
a question that has been asked for years. Can you please add Chat to the videos? So I'm glad to have
finally gotten a good solution to that question. There are more things you guys have been asking,
so I feel like it's time to move into the Q&A section of this video. These questions are picked
out from the Bod Volume Survey, as well as a couple from the community post I made recently.
Again, big thank you for your questions, even if I didn't pick yours to be answered. If you have a
question that you'd like to have answered but isn't in this section of the video, you can go
ahead and ask in the comments and I'll do my best to answer as many as I can. The questions can be
about anything like Chat Replay, the partner slash monetization, the channel, or anything else.
Just please try to keep the questions somewhat related to Germa or this channel. This section
might be fairly long, so I'll try to get through it as quick as possible. But if you're not interested
in listening to me answer some questions, feel free to skip to the timestamp on screen. Or you
can exit the video now because this is the last section of the update video. If you decide to
leave, thanks for stopping by and listening. I hope you had a great day. For those of you still
here, let's get into those questions. Question one asks us how much work goes into uploading
a video from Twitch to YouTube. Generally, the stream takes about two hours for me to download
the VOD, make sure it's ready for upload, and upload it. I'm able to upload it quickly with
gigabit fiber internet. While it uploads, I link chat using Chat Replay so it'll be available as
soon as it's live. Once it's uploaded and processed, it's in Starkiller's hands where
he skims through the video to find a suitable thumbnail, writes the title, description, puts
playlists, end cards, and finally sets up the video to go up at 7am PST. On to question two,
what's our relationship to Germa and did we have to get special permission to upload VODs?
Up until about the time Germa moved to Vegas, we didn't have direct contact with him. I think he
was a little cautious of us up until then, but since then he's been talking to us more,
and I even got a chance to show him the sunflowers that I was growing while not knowing at all that
he was also growing some too. While we didn't have to get special permission, I made sure early on
in the channel's life to get explicit permission from both Stirr and Germa before I continued
archiving for the public. I still uploaded streams for my personal use though. Question three,
how long do you plan on doing this channel? Currently, the plan is to upload as long as
Germa is streaming. If for some reason we have to stop uploading, I'll do my absolute best
to find a replacement so that the archive stays updated. Question four asks, do we edit any VODs
or they re-upload from Twitch? We tend to try to keep the VODs as close to a source as possible.
The only edits we do are cutting the empty spaces of not talking at the beginning of the streams,
or when we split up the streams by games he plays, or in the rare instances of copyright blocking a
stream, we try to edit out any of the copyrighted content. On the topic of copyright content,
question five asks, how do you deal with copyright claims that block streams? If he's playing a
random, somewhat unimportant game like House Flipper or Fart Simulator 2023, then it's easier to just
mute the section that gets claimed. But for big streams like Dollhouse, Game Awards, or other
streams where sound is important, we determine if we have a case to file a dispute against that
It has to be almost clear that we'll win the dispute, because with too many strikes,
the channel will get deleted and that's no good. Question six asks, what would you do if a seagull
crashed into your room? Question seven asks, what are your favorite content creators aside from
Jerma? At the cost of my pride, I'll reveal some of the people I've been watching lately. I have
been watching a lot of VTubers lately, but more specifically, I've been watching some Nijisanji
members like Salen, Pomu, or Finana. It's only a few streams here and there from a few members
of Nijien, depending on if they play a game I want to watch. Aside from that, I've been
enjoying many of True Nerd's Fallout YOLO runs, Ray Navey's Jr. streams, and very occasionally
Soviet Womble and Russian Badger whenever they upload. Starkiller, on the other hand, enjoys
watching Vinny Vinesauce, Kitboga, SimpleFlips, Many True Nerd as well, Windigoon, and JimmyIsHere.
There's a few more that he likes to watch, but those are the ones he's been watching lately.
Since I had out myself watching VTubers, I'll hint at Starkiller's favorite VTuber.
You'll see it on screen now. Now that I look at it, most of the questions that are left are about us,
so if you guys aren't interested in that, then also you can skip to the timestamp. Question eight
asks, what is our favorite Jerma stream? Mine is Chibi-Robo because it was my favorite GameCube game,
but no one else seems to like it for some reason. Either that or Rhythm Heaven Fever.
Starkiller's favorite Jerma stream is either the Long Drive or Talk to Transformers since
he's seen the highlights for many times. That or the Sorcery streams. Question nine asks,
pineapple on pizza or no? If I have a choice, no, but I'll eat it if that's what gets ordered
because I prefer not starving. Still on the topic of foods, what is our favorite food?
Quesadillas. I love Quesadillas so much, but mostly only the ones that I make myself. That's mostly
because the ones from the fast food chains taste like fake cheese. Starkiller, on the other hand,
had a hard time deciding, but settled on pizza and Chinese food. Question 11 asks, how many
Burger King burgers have you eaten? Wouldn't you like to know McDonald's spy? Now on to the last
question, question 12. Is this channel a labor of love? A lot of time and effort goes into this
channel that there's worried of us getting burned out. Years ago when I first started this channel,
it started off as a personal storage of VODs that I wanted to watch later that I didn't want to
save before Twitch deleted them. As I started to see more people make use of the Archive channel
and as I got better internet and storage space, the channel started becoming a better way to
serve the community and for me to personally give back to Jerma since at the time I didn't have
money to sub or give bits. Nowadays, as Starkiller and I become busy in our personal lives,
update the channel each Jerma stream is something we have less time for, but seeing how many people
we help just by uploading this funny man makes it all worth it for us. So with that last question,
that brings this video to a close. There was a lot that was talked about here with the partnership,
upcoming changes, and chat replay, so I hope it wasn't too boring to watch.
Like I mentioned at the beginning of the Q&A section, if you have a question about anything
I talked about here today, please feel free to leave it at the comment section below and I'll
try to answer as many as I can. In addition to that, if you want more news about the Archive,
want to stay updated with why Abad might be out later than usual, or just want a place to hang out,
come join our Discord. In there, it's always time for some juicy franks.
One final thing before I end the video, I wanted to thank you all for your support from the bottom
of my heart. If you excuse a quick tangent for me to share a little more about myself,
I had always dreamed to be a YouTube star as many kids do. Growing older, I realized I don't exactly
have the personality or the voice to make good content. Even while doing this line, I had to
retake it several times. However, this channel has allowed me to live vicariously, feeling the
support of the community. I know most of you guys' support goes to Jerma, but I read every comment
that you guys leave thanking us for the Archive, and it always makes me glad that I get to be a
part of something so cool and useful to so many people, including Jerma himself. We here at the
Archive want to thank you once again for your support, and we will do our best to keep providing
the Jerma content you know and love. Thank you all, and see you next time.