Too many of you guys bet on this sure thing and it works until it doesn't.
There were millions of channel points that said I would not be live
in the next 15 minutes. That was about seven minutes ago.
I know that 98% of the time that's accurate, but not this time.
Kind of pay it out. Big payday.
6.1 million goes to MeowMix and 341 other people.
Nice job. Make sure I tweet this out.
Hi guys, welcome to a late night edition of the live stream.
We're going to play a chill game today, but I know I say that every time.
And it ends up not being that.
Well, it's a late night version of the stream.
We're going to play, I saw it pop up the other day, or today to be more specific,
Such Art Creative Space.
This is going to be a painting stream.
I'm going to paint pictures.
You can get commissions.
You can sell your paintings and shit.
It looks really fun.
This is not the full game though.
I think the full game comes out in like a month or two.
This is a free starter edition of the game, I guess.
I don't know.
It looks like there's a lot of content there for it being just a random starter edition.
It's kind of like a demo, but it's more than a demo.
EA. This is not an EA game.
What are you talking about?
You already played this game.
I did not.
I played a passive, passive pout, passive pout, the artist game.
This one's different.
I think this one's a little more involved than that one is.
What was it called?
Passpart, passpartout, passpartout.
No, not pat upon.
Passpartout.
Right.
There it is.
CVD brain.
No, not tonight.
I don't know what happened two, three nights ago, man.
I have no idea.
I walked in a circle in the third Hitman level.
25 straight minutes and just was yelling at myself.
Didn't I talk shit about parking garages?
I don't know what happened.
Everything was going so well.
And then I just started talking shit about parking garages.
And I walked in a circle for 20 minutes and I turned the stream on.
What the fuck happened?
He fucking hates concrete.
Yeah, I was talking about how concrete sucks and stuff.
I don't know.
Well, we'll just pretend that last 20 minutes of the last stream didn't happen.
You're not supposed to drink the bong water.
Well, you're not supposed to tell me how to live my life.
Hey, thank you.
Unionize your workplace with the 10 community subs.
Appreciate it.
Thank you.
This game has Twitch integration and I think it's on,
but I don't have any idea what it is.
So it's on right now, but I don't know what that means.
I guess we'll find out.
EasyCache and InkCat.
Thanks for the subs, too.
10 from EasyCache and 5 from InkCat.
Thanks, guys.
What are your opinions on cheese?
I love cheese.
That stuff's awesome.
Dogchompers.
Thanks for the 5 community subs.
Gooey.
It's just ooey gooey cheesy.
Name 10 cheeses.
Brie.
Gouda.
Swiss.
Havarti.
American.
Cheddar.
Gruyere.
Oh, Gruyere.
Three more and I'm done with this.
Jack.
Jack cheese.
Two more and I win.
Provolone.
And the final one.
Feta.
Thank you.
Just named 10 cheeses.
25 community, but this is this 35 community subs are EasyCache.
Giving too much money.
Thanks for the 35 community subs.
That's EasyCache.
MintyFox.
Thanks for 5 subs.
Let's just, what are you?
Let's get started.
Let's do it.
Jack cheese.
Havarti is not a cheese.
What the hell is it then?
What is Havarti?
I love Havarti.
Havarti is awesome.
Havarti is kind of like, it's a cheese that just sort of sits there.
And the flavor of Havarti is sort of just like you,
it doesn't even really taste like much, but you know it's cheese.
So you just put it on your sandwich.
It's just like a square that has cheese texture
and it kind of has like a hint of cheese flavor.
Realistically, like Havarti on your sandwich is just like an extra 140 calories.
But I like it though, and it melts really well.
So it's nice melty, ooey, cheesy, gooey.
You know what I mean?
You're stalling.
Look, this is a late night stream, all right?
This is a late night stream.
Stalling.
I'm about to paint paintings.
All right, that's enough out of you guys.
All right, let's go.
We're going to move on to here.
This is, I guess it's turned on.
This is called Such Art Creative Space.
He's stalling.
I'm not stalling.
What are you talking about?
Okay, I am now.
Like, I'm definitely stalling right now
because I just looked at my phone.
All right, let's go.
There's a story mode.
Let's take a look at what it's going to look like.
Add this to your wish list.
Oh man, I can't wait for this to come out.
A bigger, nicer, well-equipped studio?
Full creative mode?
A virtual gallery?
A story?
I almost burped.
A full story involving robots, aliens,
and the very fate of the solar system.
What is money if there is no fame?
Let the whole solar system know about you
as you become more famous.
Cool.
All right, so let's go.
I'm just going to paint.
How's the audio?
Should we turn it up?
There's music.
Is Twitch enabled?
You're connected.
Jerma985.
I don't even know what this means.
I guess we'll find out right now.
Here we go.
A, B, C, D, E, B.
What's your artist's name?
How about Jeremy?
Jeremy the Great.
Jerry.
I'm your uncle Jerry.
You're my uncle Gary.
I am my uncle Jerry.
Jerry.
The year is 2130
and you have just received the result
of your professional compatibility DNA test.
Huh?
Your genome indicates
that you have rare artistic talent.
For decades, art has been...
I feel like that would be way too stressful.
That would put a ton of pressure on you
your whole life.
Can you imagine having you be like
50, 12, 13, 14, 15 years old?
It's like, hey, you know,
you have the rare artistic gene.
You should be so good at art.
Are you?
And you haven't like explored it yet.
That would be so much pressure.
What if you like didn't think
you did a good enough job?
That would freak me out.
For decades, art has been largely dominated
by robots and other artificial intelligence.
But in these times of artistic perfection
and homogeneity,
the world of art has become stale
and in need of renewal.
It is time for you to act.
As on earth, the threat of a robot revolt is rising.
What the fuck is going on?
An alien species, the Crabucks,
covet the planet's saltwater.
Only you can decide what to paint
on your next canvas.
What does this have to do with painting?
We're being harvested by aliens?
But so far you have yet to be granted a studio
aboard the International Space City.
In order to get ready to revolutionize the world of art
and while waiting for your real studio,
you have been provided with a virtual space
of artistic simulation.
You activate your hollow headset
and connect to your virtual studio.
This isn't a VR game, right?
This looks like you're about to go into a VR portion.
Is this VR?
I hope it's not.
I didn't look.
I didn't even look.
Is it?
Streamer menu.
Oh no, hold on.
I don't want to look.
Wait, wait, wait.
Did I lose connection?
Nobody look.
I don't want to spoil anything.
Oh no, a red connection error.
Hold on.
All right.
There's no spoilers here.
I thought that might be spoilers.
It kind of is.
There's my-
What happened to my cursor?
Okay.
Challenge my skills.
Challenge my style.
Boo me.
Rate my painting.
Have you just completed a painting or a challenge?
Time to get booed.
Did that do anything?
I don't think the streamer menu works.
I have a red connection error.
Maybe it's not working right now.
Oh well.
Did I just turn it off?
Connect.
You're not connected.
Well, why not?
It doesn't-
You're connected.
Oh, shit.
Here we go.
All right.
What do you guys think?
Boo me.
Boo or applaud.
Only five of you have voted?
Is it actually boo?
All right.
This is acting like half the time that I have diarrhea.
I just want to be clear.
Can I stop and poll?
All right.
Let's see what you guys say.
This is too long to boo.
Is that too-
Was that gross?
That was kind of gross what I just said, isn't it?
I have zero dollars.
All right.
Let's see.
Okay.
Thanks.
Paint.
To paint with a brush you have in hand, press right.
Whoa.
Hold on.
Select another object present in your inventory.
Use mouse wheel.
Oh, shit.
I shouldn't-
This is my house.
Is that a distinct paint on the wall?
All right.
What else do I have?
Oh, shit.
Throw an object.
Press E.
Okay.
This game is going to be fun.
You pick up the object you threw, aim at it, and keep pressing without moving.
Ah.
Thanks to the wonders of artificial gravity, you can also press space and jump.
Cool.
Press left control to crouch and paint the ugly floor.
This is-
It's like a toddler.
Okay.
Wait, do we have a canvas?
You don't have any commissions.
After you flush what?
Place a finished painting on the support to send it to a customer.
After you flush a painting down the toilet.
After you finish a small painting, place it here and send it to your client.
Okay.
Those are my emails.
Hold on.
Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait.
I'm excited.
Hold on.
Was-
I have a paint roller?
No, don't fuck this up already.
Press F to do a-
Oh, wait.
I can go like this?
Okay.
So I can go vertical or horizontal.
I just testing.
Holy shit.
There's so many slots.
This is my canvas.
Take a photo.
What?
Holy shit.
This is awesome.
What is this?
It's like ice cream station.
Choose a color and tone to get the paint you want.
You can access your photos from the main menu or in-game using the computer.
Oh, cool.
How do I put this down?
Is there a hairdryer?
By the way, why is there a hairdryer?
Is this drying the paint?
Okay.
This is so-
Why is there a broom too?
I'm gonna prime this canvas.
Access your photos.
Cool.
From the main menu.
From the-
Oh, and the computer.
Photos.
Whoa!
That's not that exciting.
Whatever.
Emails.
Painting order.
Welcome to your-
Hold on.
Dear Jerry.
Welcome to your virtual art simulation space.
Following the results of your latest DNA test
and a view of your immense artistic potential,
you've been registered in the Talent Development Program,
a United Earth program.
Until a real studio is assigned to your name,
this simplified virtual studio will allow you to familiarize yourself with all this stuff.
Cool.
All right.
That's all I send back.
Order.
What I want?
Something very powerful.
Use a small canvas, please.
Would 220 dollars be enough?
I mean powerful.
Small canvas.
That's enough?
Sure.
How long do you-
How long do I have?
Okay.
Small canvas or something powerful?
I need a canvas.
All right.
Change canvas.
Small.
Good.
Can I make the FOV bigger?
Where's like FOV?
There's no FOV, is there?
No FOV?
That's all right.
What is it?
It looks like it's 90.
All right.
Small canvas.
Here we go.
That's not a small canvas.
This is huge.
This is fucking-
He's like an entire wall.
And this?
Well, how do I make this small?
After you finish painting,
use the terminal to send it to your client.
Change canvas.
Wait.
Smaller.
How do I make a small canvas?
Small canvas is already on the wall.
Where?
Oh shit.
It's right here.
Oh fuck.
Okay.
Let's go.
All right.
Something powerful.
Okay guys.
Why don't you challenge my style?
No.
We're not doing any of this right now.
Yeah.
Fuck all this.
I'm not doing any of this.
All right.
Something powerful.
I need paints.
All right.
What should I get?
Raspberry sauce?
Yep.
Give me this.
Raspberry?
Wait.
These are spray paints.
What?
Oh my God.
I love spray paint.
This is cool.
All right.
I love this.
This game is a lot.
Wait.
Is this a sponge too?
You can clean?
Uh-oh guys.
I may have found.
Uh-oh.
I think I may have found
a game of the year 2021.
It's possible.
Let's not get too excited here.
I don't want to get too excited
but I may have found it.
And this shit is just free right now.
This game doesn't cost any money.
The one that costs money
is coming out like in a month or two.
That's a lie.
I don't know.
It says coming soon.
Oh, it feels so good.
Okay.
Just get rid of this for a second.
I need to have a station set up.
I want this first.
What do I want this for?
I'm going to dump paint on this
and spray paint it.
Yeah.
Hold on.
Wait.
Powerful.
Power.
I'll give you.
I'll give you power.
What does this do?
No, no, no, no, no.
That's too high.
You can flip it.
Ooh.
You can rotate it.
You can tilt it back.
Tilt it forward.
All right.
Cool.
I'm excited.
What should I do?
How do I spin this?
Oh, man.
That's a good start.
Let's get the sculpting tool.
What?
Dude.
Holy fuck.
This is cool.
Dip it in the blue.
I got to make sure before anything happens.
I got to fucking sign this.
All right.
Now let's do...
Give me the brush.
How do I wash this?
Does it combine?
I think it combined.
It is combining.
Dude, this is fucking crazy.
It's combining.
It's combining the colors.
Let's get some red in there.
What's this?
Salt?
Oh, it's like a little pounder.
Wait.
Hold on.
What is this thing?
This is like the pitcher's bag.
This has got to be powerful.
I did my first painting.
Spread that around.
We'll make it like kind of dusty.
I need some green down here.
Get a little bit more red.
Layering sucks.
It's not...
What do you mean this sucks?
Did you see the title of this frame?
This is the background, guys.
This is nothing but a painting.
Plus, this art, you can't say art sucks.
Somebody sold a banana for $150,000 taped to the wall.
You can't say that.
I just go.
I'm an abstract painter.
What does a spoon do?
Let me try.
Eat the paint.
Wait, you can just...
Really?
Hold on.
What?
I can just like drip it on there?
I need to hold on.
I need to tilt.
Throw paint.
Wait, how do I throw it?
Hold on a second.
Back up.
Holy shit.
Okay, this looks pretty good so far.
All right, we got a background.
Let's get this little one up and just be like...
What do we do?
Okay, now we're gonna have...
Let's see.
I think it's ready.
Is everything is ready?
This looks fucking cool.
I squeeze some on there.
All right, let me get the teal.
Dude, can I just squeeze the paint out?
Holy shit, you can.
No, you can't.
There's nothing left in here.
No, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait.
Where's that other tool?
The thing you can spread it with.
Wait, should I dust it?
Shit.
No, it's okay.
It's a big fist coming out.
Wait, hold on.
Actually, I kind of like it.
I'm gonna call this one Tornado.
I guess with Tasmanian devil in there.
Okay, where's my painting tools?
Why is there Nerf gun in here?
Is there stencils?
Are you kidding me?
What?
Okay, I have to give the Tasmanian devil like a Victory Royale.
Okay, hold on.
I need...
Where are my paint brushes?
I throw them on the ground.
This isn't doing anything.
Where are my brushes?
I kind of like this so far.
What do I do with my brushes?
Where are my paint brushes?
Oh, they're in my inventory.
Is this cleaning?
Oh, you clean your tools.
Okay.
Let's test the porridge.
I sprayed this?
Wait.
All right, now I'm gonna...
I'm gonna...
Let's...
I have minus $30 right now for what?
Minus 30 bucks.
What?
Okay, I need this.
I want it to be...
Let's have little fine lines just like...
Make them blue.
I want it like a teal.
That looks good.
Okay, now let's go like this.
The same color?
No.
How about punching someone in the face over here?
How do you...
What does the fist look like?
And the thumb is up here, right?
Okay.
Is this a sniffing nose?
Should it just be a nose?
Maybe just like a guy...
Like 3D is nose.
Cartoon style is like...
He's like sniffing in something.
Looks like boogers.
Hold on.
Wait.
Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait.
I think I messed this up.
I messed this up.
I have to have like eyes back here bugging out.
Like, whoa!
Because it looks 3D.
It's not a snail.
No, it's a big sniff.
This is one of the eyes.
You know what I mean?
Is there an undo?
How do you undo?
Can I do Ctrl Z?
No, you can't.
Oh, they should be white.
Okay, that's better.
Okay, good.
Is this too thick of a brush?
Yes.
Way too thick of a brush.
It's paint.
You can't undo.
Well, it's a video game.
You should...
Yeah, you can.
I can fix it.
Here we go.
Ready?
This is so cool.
I've been like waiting for a million years for a game like this.
And I know they already exist.
But this one's better.
This is a crocodile doing a big sniff.
What do eyes like attach?
I don't know.
It's called painting.
Or like what?
Like an elephant?
Or just a guy?
Like a green guy?
Should I make like a big mouth here?
Like, whoa!
What do eyes look like?
Like this?
This is a hair.
That can stick.
Okay, now we need like a mouth going like, what?
I need teal, right?
A little bit, a little bit more.
That's it, right?
Yeah.
Wait, did I accidentally touch the purple?
Is this the same color?
No, it's not.
Old and brash.
Make a pog crocodile.
All right.
There it is.
That's the right one, right?
I can't tell if it's the same color.
Okay, he has to be like, whoa!
I can't mess this up.
I can...
No, it's not ruined.
It's not ruined.
It's fine.
Is this the right color?
Not the right color.
Wrong color.
I need to undo button.
Fuck!
No!
It's okay.
You can't.
I know.
You...
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
I can fix it.
I think.
Hold on.
This one has the right paint on it.
This one does, right?
No, it doesn't.
How do I get that fucking color?
How did I get this color?
It's that color.
It's that one.
Wait, hold on.
No!
What the...
Get the gun?
There's nothing in here.
Holy shit.
Are you kidding me?
I want this.
Somebody wants this.
I don't care about anything.
Who wants it?
I want this.
I like the power of your paintings.
I think you have great potential.
Here's what I'd like you to paint.
Abundance in a gothic style would be great.
Then...
All right.
Take it.
He wants this.
He wants this one.
Give it to me.
Send this painting to Jay's.
Take it.
Send the painting.
Your painting will be sent to the customer.
There's no virtual gallery in this training program.
Consider taking a photo.
Take it.
He said, I want this.
I got a text saying, I want this.
Okay.
Did I do it?
Did I get the money?
It's not done yet, but what do you think about it so far?
Oh, come on.
I have to fix it first.
That's way too many.
I'm not counting any zeros or any tens.
Thank you for the 80 bucks.
You guys thought he did...
He said he gave me an email that he wants this.
How do we...
Does he have like binoculars in my house?
Is he like over here looking through my window?
What is it?
Did they take the average or just the...
That's fair.
That is actually kind of fair.
Oh, I'll take it.
That's fair.
Four, five, fucking three.
What is this?
Is this like a soft serve ice cream machine?
Oh, shit.
Soft serve.
Oh, whoa.
It's kind of sour.
I don't taste any vanilla.
The credit card?
What is this?
What color is this?
Oh, my God.
I got it.
All right.
I got the color reader.
Okay.
Now give me that color.
Now what do I do?
Oh, I did it already.
Oh, no.
Fuck you.
Do it again.
Give me another one.
No.
Put it in.
Stop it.
What's the range on this?
All right.
It's pretty fucking far.
Nice.
Yes.
Finally, I have the right color.
I need new water.
Okay.
Where do I get water?
Where's the water?
Place to finish painting on the support.
I don't even need to do that.
Canvas printer.
Oh, shit.
That's cool.
What do I get water?
What if I need a lot more of that?
Does this cost money?
I feel like I'm going to need a lot of this paint
because I'm going to make a couple.
I like this teal.
Take my favorite color.
Teal addict.
I like teal.
I love teal.
I need water.
I have another bucket.
I have two buckets.
I'm fine.
Trust me when I say that I will use this.
This is going to be used in every single painting, guys.
This is a bucket filler.
If it isn't that, this is water.
How do I put it down?
Put it down the drain.
This shit's stuck there forever.
Why is this water so cloudy?
This is cloudy ass water.
Look at this.
This is the cloudiest water I've ever seen.
This is water.
We'll pick the damn thing up.
Okay.
This is just permanently going to be teal.
It's paint thinner.
Where's the paint bucket filler that you got?
Oh, dude.
There it is.
Cotton candy ice cream.
Let me leave my mouth under it.
Cotton candy.
Fill it.
Fill the bucket.
What are you doing?
Nice.
I just fucking throw it over there.
All right.
How do I put this down without dumping it?
I don't know.
How do you put it down?
Okay.
So I have the right color now.
I'm ready.
I'm taking my paintbrush.
I'm going to wait.
I need water.
Give me this.
You're fucking crazy, dude.
What are you?
Why?
This is an art studio.
I don't understand.
Go find me an art studio that doesn't have paint
all over every fucking wall and all over the ground.
All right.
Here we go.
I don't want to use this.
I want my finesse.
Where's my finesse brush?
What happened to it?
What did I throw?
I just had it on the floor.
Yeah.
Where?
Where is it?
Left.
Where?
How did I get over here?
Okay.
Rinse.
Here we go.
Time to go.
Let's do it.
Let's touch this up a little.
Thank you.
All right.
This is not the right color.
How?
Is this the wrong color?
How is this the wrong color?
Is it dry?
Is that what it is?
It's a work in progress.
Just wait.
It's not drying.
You guys fucking annihilated.
I'm not.
Okay.
When it dries, then I have to put
like a big open mouth right here.
D face.
I mean, it's kind of, but this is happy.
Dude, I'm an artist.
Turn off the music.
Kind of is the same loop, isn't it?
Need more paint.
Wrong one.
Put on an OST.
I kind of don't want to nuke this VOD though.
Doesn't that happen every time you do OSTs?
Okay.
This is actually, this is starting to be.
I got to make sure this doesn't turn into like
a like big green penis.
I'm trying.
It'll just wait till it's done.
Hold off your reservations here.
Those are clean lines.
Ah, you guys are relaxed.
I am so relaxed.
Okay.
There it is.
He's like, whoa.
Okay.
Um, now we need teeth.
He's got like teeth and a big tongue.
I need white.
Well, I'll get teeth as he has.
Too much?
No, that's all right.
It's orange.
Wrong.
This is like fucked up.
Okay.
He's, uh, this is just like, this looks
really fucking wrong.
He's like boogers into his own mouth.
Is that what is happening?
Get the vote menu.
No, it's not done yet.
I'm not taking the menu up.
I need to see what it looks like.
And then I got to change it.
Well, they wanted something powerful.
They're going to get it.
And by the way, I'm sorry.
You don't just commission somebody like
a famous artist like me.
Hey, uh, do whatever you want.
Just make sure it's powerful.
You have to be ready for anything.
You might get, you might get human shit in the mail.
Be careful with what you ask for here.
Be, you got to be very clear.
I want it, uh, I want it powerful.
But, um, use paint and make it look like
I could show it to my grandmother.
There you go.
Powerful, but grandmother.
Okay.
Tongues have like a line, right?
Do tongues have like a line down the middle?
This looks like it could be,
I like on the commercial for like an old
soft drink in the 90s or something.
In fact, I get an order for you.
Hold on.
I think there's like a Nickelodeon ad
with this exact thing is happening.
Some of you guys forget this.
Nickelodeon used to be about like eating boogers
and like pooping and shitting your pants and stuff.
Nickelodeon from like the late 80s into the mid 90s
was about like boogers all over your face
and like boogies and boogers.
It was every single thing they did.
All right.
I'm selling this one.
This one's ready.
Let's start over.
No, it isn't.
Yes, it was.
Actually, this would go on the grid on the bottom
of a skateboard.
Don't you think?
Let's get a picture of this.
Why am I trying to paint the lens?
Like that's stupid.
All right.
This one's completed.
I'm going to call this one
a skateboard t-shirt
ponyhawk menu t-shirt menu.
Create a character t-shirt number like 32.
That's what I'm calling it.
Okay.
This is for Solman.
Solman.
Here you go.
Let me know what you think.
How do I send it to you?
How do I pick it up?
It's okay.
It was dry.
Paint side down.
Okay, Solman.
Hope you like it.
Let me know what you guys think.
Finish painting.
Rate my painting.
By the way, 40 seconds is way too long.
You have like 15 seconds.
Come on.
What do you think?
Okay.
6.5 out of 10.
That's not bad.
That's pretty good, actually.
I'm happy with that.
6.5 out of 10.
That's good.
I can sell this on a marketplace?
Wait.
No, I have a commission.
Hold on.
How much are you going to give me?
This is like how much money is this for?
Can I sell it for more?
I can only do one painting.
220 bucks.
I'm going to get like 500 for this?
Oh, I forgot to sign it.
I forgot to sign it.
No, I did sign it.
I just painted over it.
Hold on.
Uh, yeah, I got to sign it.
Okay.
I'm not doing my real signature.
That guy freaks me out.
I'm not going to sign my actual like real signature
in front of fucking 14,000 people.
It's kind of sounds dangerous.
Doesn't it?
Hey, I don't know if I'm going to do that.
All right.
Let's just let's do it.
I want something very powerful.
Small canvas.
Let's go.
Do you like it?
How is it?
Make your signature the channel icon.
I don't think I can do that.
Into the shredder it goes.
All right.
We're going to go wild for the next one.
I'm talking just I'm going to just do whatever the fuck I want.
I'm not going to think about it.
Did you pay me?
Target tube.
Where's my money?
My name is Dumari.
I would like to.
I would have liked to be an artist myself.
Here's what I'd like you to do.
Something steampunk.
No, that's fucking boring.
My name is Asher.
I think you can change the world through your artwork.
Can you paint something for me?
A skull.
The size of the canvas is up to you.
Okay.
I'll do that one.
All right.
I need a big.
I'm going to do a huge skull.
I'm going to paint it with this gun too.
It's going to be like in red paint like a red blood skull.
There's going to be so much meaning behind it.
I can't wait.
And I just like.
All right.
Load it up.
Give me that canvas.
Change canvas.
I want a big one.
This one.
One by one free.
Where's my money for the last commission?
All right.
I'm going to do it.
Wait.
I need a back.
I need a background to be gray.
Gray background.
There's a roller.
I'm a little tall enough.
Where did my money for the other one go?
Oh, shit.
This whole thing moves.
I need more paint.
It's all right if it's a little washed out on the left here.
It's just it's the background.
All right.
Hey, let's go.
Let's go to the McDonald's and let's get every fucking soda.
We got sprite.
We got Powerade.
We got Powerade blue.
We've got like Mountain Dew.
Do the whole thing.
Yeah.
There it is.
Oh, yeah.
Okay.
They go.
220 bucks.
Let's go.
All right.
That's a pretty good start.
Not a bad start.
All right.
Let's go.
Give me the gun.
I told you guys this one was going to be.
I'm just going to go for it.
All right.
We got red in here, right?
Okay.
Fill it up with red.
There it is.
Let's make this fucking skull.
What does the skull look like?
It's got like a big head like.
Oh, okay.
Now I need this might give me that paint brush.
I need white.
I'm a big T like this looks like one of the enemies from Mario.
This guy's from Mario 64.
Oops.
Who's the Mario enemy that looks like this?
The swamp?
Maybe.
All right.
Now let's that looks all right.
It's a skull.
Um, hold on.
Let me hothead.
Yes, that's the one.
Thank you.
Hothead.
Wait, there's a thing in the middle too, right?
I need red.
That's kind of like a clown.
Wait, give me the smear tool.
That's what I want to use.
Perfect.
Sell it.
Send it quick.
Skull.
I need to take a picture of it.
Oh, well.
How do I clean up?
I need to.
Okay.
Time to clean up the station here.
Station cleanup time.
We didn't even vote for it.
Oh, vote for that one.
All right.
You guys remember what it looked like?
What was it?
Well, I clean up.
A package has arrived.
Package has arrived?
Just dump the bucket.
A two?
A 2.8?
Two?
That was a two.
That was not a two.
How was that a two?
It was zero effort.
No, it wasn't.
That was me just going just visceral.
Not everything has to have a plan.
Why does everything have to have a plan?
Everything has to have a plan, Arthur.
Not everything has to have a plan.
But it does.
Doesn't it, Arthur?
Yeah, doesn't it, Goku?
I'm not going to do it.
Some people hate that, by the way.
I've seen at least half a dozen comments saying,
I really fucking hate it when he just adds a Goku
to the end of everything when he does a low voice.
I've read that.
I've seen that.
All right.
No more just throwing shit on the ground.
This game is sick, though.
I love this game.
This shit's free.
You don't have to buy it if you don't want to.
What's the story mode going to be like?
There's more to this game?
How did you make this free?
This is free.
This is a free game.
This is 100% for free.
There's actually no strings attached to this.
You just go.
You can play exactly what I'm doing right now for free on Steam.
This game's called Such Art.
It's a fucking free game.
I love the water effects, too.
A lot of time went into it.
You can tell time went into this.
I like this.
I have an incredible offer for you.
What is it?
I'm Arly.
You're in my top 30 favorite artists.
I'm so glad a friend told me about you.
What I want?
Boredom.
With your personal touch.
The size of the canvas is up to you.
155 bucks.
You're in my top 30.
Excellent link.
Hold on.
I'll be the judge of that.
250 million off the debt if you choose a random Bob Ross video and follow along.
All right.
Hold on to that one.
Why is 1 billion scratched off?
All right.
Hold on to that one.
We'll do it.
That sounds like fun.
Can I do that?
Can I watch a Bob Ross painting on Twitch?
Am I allowed to do that?
No, that's not like a problem, right?
All right.
So anyways, I have spoken.
So this is what he wants.
They want boredom with my personal touch.
Sure.
Boredom with my personal touch.
I'm just getting the I'm getting the spot ready.
No, I don't want the big canvas.
It's too much for me.
I want a little canvas.
This one's perfect.
This is perfect.
Spin this around.
Boredom.
That's too much.
You're going.
You know what?
Wait a minute.
Holy shit.
Whoa.
No shit.
Cool.
I like.
All right.
I like that.
This is a rainbow from every two-year-old
you've ever seen in your life.
I need Sprite cans.
All right.
We got green on there.
We're doing a little bit this green right here.
Let's test it.
It looks all right.
I'm going to stay far away.
Dude, this is like rotisserie chickening gas.
How's that?
You hear it?
Cool.
I like it.
This is like outside with some grubs outside.
I need a leaf.
Is there a leaf stencil?
Not really.
That's a leaf.
Can I make this small?
Stop spinning.
I need a leaf right here.
Grubhub gives you.
What the fuck are you talking about?
Okay.
I need a leaf.
Yeah.
Somebody's to turn the music off.
Right.
Sorry.
It's just way too loud.
It can be in the background.
That's fine.
All right.
I need a leaf.
What color should it be?
Should it be like maroon?
Like fall?
This looks spring to me.
I think it has to be green.
Inspiration.
Okay.
Or what if I just like...
All right.
So it goes like wham, wham, wham.
Droplet.
Wham, wham.
Okay.
I'm just going to go for it.
I'm going to go fall colors.
All right.
I need one of these things.
Okay.
Let's mix these together.
What?
I put that on my pants.
Dude, that's a good one already.
That's a good one.
It's like a little guy.
Okay.
Here we go.
Let's see if I can get this to happen.
Is this clean?
Okay.
That's a perfect leaf.
That's right.
Okay.
So it's...
I don't have to be perfect.
This is too big of a...
No, that's not water.
This is paint.
Okay.
All right.
Here we go.
Looks like it's a one, two.
It's like a fucking shitty palm tree.
No, it's okay.
It's okay.
Shit.
Hold on.
I need a spray can.
Oops.
Okay.
Give it to me.
This would be such a good VR game.
That's right.
Okay.
Hold on.
I should just did it like this already.
This is way better.
I shrink that.
I need to blend.
Blend it in a little bit.
Hold on.
I need like a blender.
This thing.
Or did I?
Wait a minute.
No, I didn't.
Holy shit.
This is awesome.
This is in the background.
This is like a beach.
This is a beach.
This is a fucking palm tree.
That's a palm tree.
The beach.
This is perfect.
That's a background.
That's a tree.
The beach.
That's like an animal crossing tree.
Okay.
No, that's perfect.
I'm all right.
If I go all the way up.
These guys need eyes.
Why did you smush caterpillars on the canvas?
I didn't.
Hey.
Hey, hey, hey, hey.
Grow up.
Hey.
I didn't want to shrink his head.
I want to paint.
I can't paint on top of that
because it's technically paint.
Get over here.
I killed him.
I didn't want that.
Shit.
Is that like bat?
Is that like a squished head?
Here we go.
This is just part of their bodies.
It's pickle Rick.
I don't hate this so far.
I actually really...
What was this one?
Boredom?
What should I add?
Maybe...
I don't know.
I kind of like this.
How's that?
Awful.
Looks fine.
Is it bored?
I actually like...
I like this one.
What's the...
Look, and we'll go like this too.
I like this one.
It's cute.
I think I want to dress this up a little more.
Or is it ready?
What do you think?
All right.
Let's see what you guys think.
It's ready.
I have a package to get too.
I love it.
You guys can give me inspiration.
6.0.
Give me a break.
That's better than the 6.0.
Oh, it got squished.
Flip it around.
Oh, they got squished in.
Oh, well.
It's still wet.
Wait, I can fix it before it goes.
Let's give a check mark on it.
Okay.
Where's my...
I got a new package.
Where did I get a package?
Important.
Nothing.
Where's the package?
What the fuck is this?
What the hell?
Small...
Ready for delivery.
What's ready for delivery?
Oh, shit.
What's going on out here?
Okay.
For a second, I thought we were in a moving truck.
I was like, we're going...
We're on the highway right now.
What the hell is going on?
What's in here?
Is there anything fragile in this?
How do I open it?
Dude.
This is the best game ever.
What's this one?
Hearts?
You can drag it too?
What's the last one?
Oh, god damn it.
Are you kidding me?
I could have just done this in the middle of the last one.
Whatever.
All right.
Let's get you guys involved.
Pick three random challenges to make your life harder.
The chat will then vote for one of them.
Don't cheat.
They're watching you.
Okay.
Pick three random art styles for your next painting.
The chat will then vote for one of them.
You will fail.
Perhaps your viewers are merciful.
Okay.
How about...
What do you guys think?
We aren't merciful?
Yes, you are.
Thank you.
Thank you very much.
All right.
Challenge my style.
As real...
Oh, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait.
I canceled this.
I need more time.
It's gonna be longer than 15 seconds.
30 seconds.
All right.
Challenge my style.
Expressionist, Cubist, or Art Nouveau.
I don't know what the third one is.
So I have no idea.
What is a Cubist?
I'm just gonna interpret that as draw cubes.
Cubist.
Okay.
So it looks like we're gonna go Cubist.
Sounds good.
Analyze and cut your subject from different angles.
Now make those cuts more abstract
and reassemble them on your painting.
Okay.
I'm gonna draw some cubes.
I don't know.
Whatever.
All right.
Canvas size.
I want a normal one.
Oops.
Throw that one away.
How do you throw a painting away?
Thank you.
What?
Okay.
One by...
Let's do this.
Let's just small one.
Perfect.
There you go.
Cubist.
Cube painting.
A cube painting.
Interesting.
Very interesting.
Very interesting indeed.
Where's my sponge?
That was very loud.
Sorry.
All right.
Where's the leaf blower?
Aim this right here.
Clean that up.
Aim it directly down.
I'm getting rid of the play like paintball.
All right.
Where is my...
Where's my leaf blower?
What is this thing?
What is this?
Whoa.
Holy shit.
This is...
Let me...
Hold on.
Wait.
What the fuck?
This is awesome.
All right.
This is like I got like eight brushes on it.
I want to...
This is a mop.
It's a mop.
It's just a regular mop.
I thought it was going to be like a bunch of paint brushes.
For a second, I thought it was clay.
I could like squeeze clay out of here.
All right.
I'll do the satisfying thing when you go like this.
Keep going.
Oh.
This cleaning up the paint.
I want to do that later.
I'm not...
Let's do that later.
Where's the leaf blower?
There it is.
Here we go.
You ready?
There.
Here's Cubist for you.
Let's go.
I'm just waiting for the mom to open the door and go,
Jerry, what are you doing?
And I turn.
I've got like lipstick all over my face.
I've got all of her clothes on.
I got like a pair of dad's shoes on that are way too big for me.
They're like eight sizes too big.
Jerry.
What is she, mom?
Cool.
It made a really cool pattern.
Look at the pattern it made.
We need more.
We need more paint.
Give me...
Spin it.
No.
I'm not going to spin it because this symbolizes like the insanity.
And this is me trying to be as stoic and normal as possible
while the sanity just flows over me.
Insanity, I mean.
In a true Cubism fashion, I stand strong while society just goes nuts.
I try as hard as I can to stay cool and stay strong and stay locked.
But getting hit by all the crazy shit going on.
I kind of like what it did to the floor.
Okay, I got it right when it...
I got it.
No, I didn't.
Fuck.
It's okay.
That's the Joker.
That was just for the Joker.
I want a bucket of paint.
I want to spray it everywhere.
Isn't it fun to make a mess when it doesn't even matter?
You're pretending this is some profound statement
when you just don't actually know what Cubism is.
Oh, it's full.
Okay.
Hell yeah.
It was like, I know what Cubism is.
We call that an accident.
That's not a happy accident.
That is, you've ruined the whole painting.
Looks like it's red now.
Okay.
What do you think?
Cubism.
Okay.
How do I wash the...
Can I just press a button and have the sprinkler system come on?
Because that's the only way this is getting clean.
Zero and ten.
Therefore, it's a five rate.
I'm going to put this on the marketplace.
Let me sign it first.
It's a Spider-Man popsicle.
I win.
Spider-Man popsicle.
I won.
It's a Spider-Man popsicle.
It's okay.
It's fixed.
Marketplace.
Sell it for 250 hours.
No, 100 bucks.
New vote.
All right, all right, all right.
Challenge my skills.
One minute to paint.
Paint with your eyes closed or one single stroke.
How am I going to do any of these?
How am I going to do one minute?
One single stroke?
Paint with your eyes closed.
I don't even...
I can't...
How am I supposed to do that without somebody being in the room here?
I need to put a pair of...
I need to put clothes on for this.
Fuck.
The only reason why you guys are clicking on that is because you want the webcam.
All right.
Fine.
Let me set this up.
Can I clean the area up first?
Let me clean up first.
I got to do a full cleanup.
This is disgusting.
I got to...
It's disgusting.
Give me a minute.
I got to organize.
This is just absolutely fucking revolting.
Where's the trash?
Where's the trash can?
Is this trash?
Over here?
I guess so.
All right.
Trash.
He's stalling.
Yeah, well, whatever.
Oh, I'm sorry.
Ow, my face.
I'm really sorry.
I didn't mean to.
Don't do that again.
Okay, I won't.
Come with me.
I'm going to put you on the shelf.
You want your favorite delicious nutrition paste?
Okay.
Clean.
Oh, this looks nice.
Clean, clean, clean, clean.
Give me that bucket.
Move this stuff out of the way.
Okay, that's what those are.
I thought there were bugs everywhere.
All right, give me my trash.
There's a gift above the water tap.
How do I get up there?
What is this?
Is everyone saying compact?
Do you understand that this is like 14 feet tall ceilings?
Okay, open.
What is it?
A ball?
Whoa.
Can I put paint on it and throw it around?
Can I cover it in paint?
Hold on.
Dip it in a bucket.
Hold on, let me.
All right, dip it in a bucket of paint.
Sure, fill this.
I'll roll it around here.
Stalling, stalling.
I'm playing.
I'm not stalling.
This whole game is painting.
Just chill, okay?
Chill.
Don't make me take a break and go eat a piece of beef jerky.
But I will.
All right, let's dunk it in the paint.
Where'd it go?
Whoa, it rolls down.
Wow.
Is there any more fun toys?
Put a canvas on the floor.
Yeah, but it's the biggest one I can get.
One, three.
One, two.
One, one.
No, this is tiny.
Sell it back.
Right here.
One, 13.
Oh, yeah, yeah, yeah.
Yes.
Give it to me.
How do I move this?
Can I not pick this up?
Five minutes ago, he said you were going to clean this place up.
What am I?
You know, strong enough.
Hurry and turn the cam on.
All right, we'll just wait a minute.
What is this?
I thought that was my doorbell.
I was about to freak out.
I was like, somebody here.
That's a dick.
I have to change that.
I don't know, like this one.
Whatever.
Better.
Okay, good.
Who?
Okay, what do we have for customers?
Offer.
I'm Scarleth.
Always stay strong in the face of adversity.
I'd like a painting from you.
Something warm.
Big canvas.
Thank you.
This is pure art.
I'm amazed.
You're my favorite human artist.
Stay free.
I need a painting for you.
The portrait of a demon.
In Dada style.
Don't know what that is.
Got it.
Incredible offer.
Yep.
All right, well, hold on.
End of the simulation.
This is the end of your simulated training program.
While you can spend more time training your skills here,
no more virtual clients will try to contact you.
Hope your natural talent for the art has been further simulated.
Yet another disappointment.
Can't wait to have a real studio.
Equipped with liquid art runs through my veins.
End of the trial.
No.
Let me end it.
That's not.
Your painting is on its way to the marketplace.
Offer.
You want a...
Do you want something warm?
Hey, this kind of looks good.
Turn the camera on.
I'm gonna do a camera one.
Just hold on.
I have to like...
Let me take a break and put on a t-shirt.
Jump into the laser now.
No, it's probably gonna kill me.
It's fine.
Hey, hey, hey.
Seize get degrees, guys.
Oops, I just ruined it.
Whatever.
I don't care.
End it.
Oh, this is not big enough.
Sell it on the marketplace.
For 50 bucks.
SD5 added to the marketplace.
This looks funny.
Okay.
All right.
Let me...
I need this.
I'll do the...
I closed one on like a decent size canvas over here.
Well, this is...
This is fine.
Right there.
A little bit higher.
Close your darn eyeballs.
I will.
I'm not gonna...
I'm just setting it up.
What's this link?
It says...
I don't know.
I don't know what the hell you just linked me.
I don't...
What is this?
This is from Ferris Bueller's Day Off?
I don't remember this.
I don't...
I don't remember.
I've seen this movie a few times,
but it's been a very long time.
100 million off the debt if you clean the studio
and keep it clean for the rest of the stream.
I don't think I can do that.
Clean the studio.
Wait, what is this?
It says 100 million off the debt
if you clean the studio
and keep it clean the rest of the stream.
I can...
That's not gonna happen.
All right.
Let's take a break.
I'm gonna go pee.
I'm gonna grab a...
I'm gonna grab a beef stick.
And I'll be right back.
And then I'll make sure I have clothes on.
I'll turn the face cam on.
And I will do a...
I closed one.
All right.
I'll be right back.
Here we go.
How many catboys?
I left...
I left like four or five minutes ago
with a catboy on camera.
And I came back and there's a catboy on camera.
It's like...
It's just all catboys.
All catboys.
It was 90 plus percent catboys.
Oh my fucking god.
That's so funny.
It's only catboy.
They're holding a gun?
What is that?
Oops.
All catboys.
Why is...
Why is this...
Why is he holding a gun?
All right.
Let me get my camera set up.
One of us.
What the fuck?
All right.
Hold on.
Let me get my camera set up.
Out of the way.
Get this out of the way.
And I'll close my goddamn eyes.
Okay.
Make sure this looks fine.
I've got a drink here too, by the way.
Don't...
Don't get mad at me.
How am I gonna do this?
Can you see me?
Anybody see me?
Why is my camera fucked up?
Wait.
What is this?
Fuck that.
Why is it...
Get out of the way.
You see?
Hello?
You down there?
Why am I...
Oh.
Hold on.
Oops.
Oh.
Gotta get the good side in too.
We can't...
We can't just have the bad side.
Gotta get the good side in there too.
We can't just have just the bad side.
I have to keep my eyes closed.
I'll try it.
Raid song.
Family guy raid.
We got a family guy raid?
Donkey just came in with a raid?
What's going on, Donkey?
What's going on, everybody?
Welcome.
I'm just setting up a chat challenge video.
Family guy?
Should I sing family guy?
I'm not gonna do that.
There's 6,000 new people.
No way.
What's up?
Thanks for the raid.
This is fucking crazy.
I've been a fan of Donkey's for years.
He was one of the YouTubers.
I'll tell you, the capture video,
that's one of the best videos on YouTube.
Like, hands down.
The capture Donkey video
is one of the best YouTube videos on YouTube.
I'm gonna be gushing here for a little bit.
Sorry.
So what we're doing right now...
Thank you again, Donkey.
Welcome, guys.
We're doing a art stream.
And part of it is, as you'll see...
Hold on.
Whoa!
You just...
Now you can see what I look like with the white.
Turn that back off!
Shit!
With like a real camera?
Why do I not know how to drink?
This is not even alcohol.
I just lied to you.
Ew!
He's like ugly now.
Okay, so the goal here was...
I got challenged.
I'm connected.
Look, look, look.
Here you go.
So this is connected to Twitch right now.
And it's a cool game.
It's called Art...
What's the name of the game?
Such Art.
It's a game where you just kind of can do whatever you want.
There's spray cans.
There's paint brushes.
It's really fucking cool.
So we'll see what they do.
Oh, the challenge, right.
I have to keep my eyes closed in the next painting.
But let me get...
Okay, while you guys do, let me set this up.
Because this is not ready at all.
I want...
What color should I do?
Let me get this...
Hold on.
Right.
And you can go like this.
You get this cleaning in the game.
If you like viscera cleanup detail, you're gonna love it.
It's free.
Make sure I say that.
Get it out of here.
Free game.
This is free.
You want to see the amount of content that's here for free?
Okay, I need this brush.
This brush here.
I need to have a palette.
Okay, let me get this back over here.
I need to clean this.
So if my eyes are gonna be closed, I have to be...
I gotta be really close.
So this is gonna go up here.
I'm gonna clean it like this.
So if I...
It's right there.
So it's...
How many degrees is that?
That is burp puked.
How many degrees is this?
One, two.
I took one sip of this.
It's a ginger beer.
Oh, you're urinating.
No, I'm not.
Okay, so let me clean this.
Do it. Vomit.
Shut up.
Fuck.
Fuck up.
What are you writing?
Mr. Jeremy, sir.
I'm gonna read it until it gets fucking deleted from the mod.
I've been to ask this for almost four months now.
I cannot sleep.
I stayed for nights going through this thought process
in my head over and over again.
My wife cannot even look at me in the eyes anymore
and she's moved to her mother's house.
I need to know if you urinate standing up or sitting down.
I know this is somewhat off limits,
but this morbid curiosity is ruining my life.
That's an easy...
I can answer that.
If you just go number one, you stand.
If you go number two, you go number one
after you go number two while you're sitting.
Easy.
That's correct.
You go number two and you're still sitting there.
So it's like, all right, might as well do number one too.
I'm right here.
That's like a fact.
If you don't do that, you're a liar.
So wait, let me get this straight.
You go shit and then after you shit, you go,
if you have to pee, you stand up and turn around
and pee into the toilet.
Can I understand that one?
I'm confused.
You go before, but what if you have to go?
What if you have to go afterwards?
What, you're just going to hold it?
Is that such a big deal to pee while you're sitting down
for a lot of you guys?
You just don't go.
What?
Why?
Toilet humor stream.
No, this is not toilet.
I'm actually curious if you guys are gaslighting or not.
God, I'm so sick of being gaslit every day.
What is this?
Oh, I need that.
Okay, so what colors do I want?
I want to do, we'll do like a gray.
We'll do a yellow.
Yellow and other yellow.
Mustard, pink and purple.
Good.
Okay, so let's go here.
I got to remember where these are.
Okay, so that's purple and pink are on the left side.
Mustard and yellow are in the middle and blacks on the right.
Okay, so paintbrush one is here.
I need paint.
And this is another slot.
What just happened?
Yeah, I don't like the slots these are in.
I know this is a lot of setup, but bear with me.
I need water.
Shirt your pants right now.
Had to do it.
The person gave like 500 community subs.
So this is going to be to my left.
Oh, come on, dude.
Really?
What the fuck?
Actually did it.
So this is in.
That's correct.
Okay, so if I close my eyes, it's not close enough.
It's got to be closer.
Okay, there's the canvas.
Okay, there it is.
And then I've got my paints over here.
Here we go.
All right, I'm going to start.
Are you ready?
I'm going to do...
Let's just go for it.
See if I can do something here.
When do I close my eyes?
Now?
Wait, should I close my eyes like...
Can I open them at all during the whole process?
How long do I do this for?
I don't have a time limit.
I guess until I'm ready.
Set a timer.
All right, what's the timer for?
Five minutes?
I was at a time for five minutes.
I just...
Okay, I almost just...
I almost just locked out my phone.
I just did the password wrong like five times.
I just deleted my whole phone.
Jesus Christ.
Okay, let's do...
Timer.
My alarms are so fucked up.
My alarms right now, I have one for 7 a.m., 8.30 a.m.,
and then 1.30 p.m.
After 8.30, it's kind of just like...
Apparently, it's just like...
I guess fuck it.
I'm just going to stay asleep.
Okay, timer.
Five minutes on the clock.
Ready?
Three, two, one, go!
Oh, wait.
I want the thick...
Okay, one and two.
Is this one?
Do I have paint on?
I don't even know if I have paint on.
I think there's paint on this.
I don't even know where I'm standing.
I don't know where I'm standing.
I heard something.
Where's the paint?
I don't know where I am.
I gotta find the water bucket.
I think I'm on the...
I hear it.
I don't know where the bucket is.
I really have no idea where the bucket is.
Did I move?
Fuck it.
On the bucket.
That means here's the canvas, which means here's the paint.
I have no idea what's happening.
Is this the bucket of water?
I don't know what the you grabbed paint sound is.
Where's escape?
Okay, this tilde is one.
I hear like the...
How long is it?
It's been five minutes yet.
I think I did something wrong.
I think I just clicked something.
I don't know where the bucket is.
I gotta find the bucket again.
That's the bucket.
That's the water bucket.
So then this is the canvas.
So then this is the fucking palette.
Is this the palette to the right?
Why is it making painting sounds?
How much time is left?
Is my phone on silent?
Can I...
Wait, hold on.
Can I look at the phone to make sure it's not on silent?
If I go like this, hold on.
How long has it been?
Can I look?
Can I look at the phone?
Please?
I don't even know what you're saying.
I'm painting something.
It could be the ground.
It could be a wall.
I don't know.
Where's my drink?
This is the stupidest thing ever.
Why would I like just blindly reach for a drink?
Why is that so hard to do that with my eyes closed?
It's not like that my muscle memory changes.
Do I need to see?
Holy shit, I did it.
Stop.
Shut the fuck up.
I actually did it.
What happened over here?
How long has it been like that?
I haven't had paint for like probably a long time.
The whole time.
Well, how did I get this?
All right, here you go.
What do you think?
I disconnected.
I'm in.
Let's see what's going on here.
Game's not centered.
It really isn't.
How long has that been like that for?
I think this is broken.
Yeah, this is fucked up.
I'm going to disconnect and try to reconnect.
Where's my mouse?
What the fuck is going on?
Where's the mouse?
All right, disconnect.
Disconnect.
Try it again.
Connect.
This has just worked.
Well, I'm going to say it was a 10.
I'm going to restart it.
Can I save the game like this?
Do a straw poll instead.
It's probably for the best that we can't rate this one.
All right, now let me do that.
All right, here we go.
I want to do the Bob Ross thing.
I'm going to take a picture of this.
It was a pog out of 10.
All right, what's a good one to do?
What's a good one that's not going to get me DMCA claimed?
Does he have like a YouTube channel?
I need a new canvas, first of all, and I'm going to sell this.
I'm selling this for 200, 150.
He's on Twitch right now.
Just co-stream the one on Twitch.
But I have to catch up, don't I?
There's a Bob Ross right now on Twitch.
I have to catch up.
I'm not prepared for that.
He just started.
Did he just start?
What happened to the top?
Where's the top?
Wasn't there a top to this?
Where'd it go?
Wasn't this sitting on top of this?
Yikes.
Jesus.
Holy shit, that was bad.
Okay, I got to get a Bob Ross.
I'm going to co-stream Bob Ross.
I'm going to do what he's doing on Twitch.
What's the link?
Bob Ross, there it is.
I can do this, right?
I can do this.
I think so.
All right, let's go.
I'm going to turn the music down here.
I got to hurry up because he's going already.
I got to catch up if I can.
If it's streaming, then yeah.
Isn't that the whole point of Bob Ross?
I guess.
I guess, I mean, this is like cool, I guess.
Hopefully.
Disney Plus, Hulu, and ESPN.
Okay, what do we got?
Disney, Hulu, and ESPN.
I think the sketchy website I bought this turtle from.
I didn't buy a turtle.
Get that up here.
Make this full screen.
Give me one sec.
Okay, can you see it?
Shit, okay.
Wait, I can't hear it.
I can't hear it.
He's already has a full fucking mountain.
I'm not going to be able to catch up to this.
He's got a beautiful mountain.
He just started this.
That's it.
What is it, blue?
I'm going, I'm going, I'm going, I'm going.
Blue, white, and this thing too.
White.
Where's white?
Blue, white, and gray.
Go.
Doesn't matter.
I just need it.
YouTube link.
You need a brown too.
Just YouTube it.
Fuck.
Give me, give me.
Wait, wait, wait, wait.
Stop that.
All right, give me.
Where's the better one?
Please, please, please.
Hold on, hold on, hold on.
Use YouTube, use YouTube.
This better not be a fucking screamer.
I swear to God.
I will let it stream if it is.
Not a screamer, but like, fuck you regardless still.
Did you just link me like your channel?
All right, how about this?
How about this?
We'll do the next one.
We'll do the next one here.
I don't want, I want to catch it.
This is Otto's Big Adventure 2.
Great.
Do you understand how hard this is going to be
to get somebody to give me a real video?
We have to wait for the next one.
I guess I could just find it myself.
Bob Ross.
Okay, Bob Ross follow along painting.
This one is called
in the midst of winter.
In the midst of winter.
This is the right one.
No, I'm going to do in the midst of winter.
I really hope I can do this.
In the middle of winter is this one.
Good grammar and spelling are important.
Not anymore.
You can just type it into this grammar thing
and just it corrects literally every mistake
you've ever made.
You can just fucking just who cares.
Just mash your goddamn keyboard like a fucking piano.
Doesn't matter.
Send your emails will all get fixed.
Okay, let's get this in the same spot.
It undermines the writer's message
and the word choice is bland.
Okay, here we go.
Glad to see you today.
Tell you what, let's get right on today
and have them run all the colors across the screen
that you need to paint along with us at home.
While they're doing that, as usual,
let me show you what I have.
What do I need?
Today I have my standard old pre-stretched
double primed canvas
and I've just covered it with a very thin coat
of liquid white.
That's all.
It's wet and ready to go.
So I thought today maybe we would do
let's do a little winter scene.
Something that's let's just see what happens.
Let's start with with black.
Potato blue.
Or blue and black.
What?
Just sort of mixing together.
Black and blue and blue and black.
I thought we'd just play a little bit today.
I don't even have my paints here
and I hope it is wherever you're at.
Just have a good time with this.
We're just we'll just pop in a little sky here and there.
Something about like so.
I'm leaving some spots open intentionally.
Just little spots.
I don't want this to be a flat old dead sky.
I wanted to have some life.
Some action to it.
Shoot.
Maybe we can get a little crazy here.
I've got several of these brushes.
Mine just doesn't do that.
Another one.
Put a little touch.
Not much.
Little touch.
What color?
Of alizarin crimson.
I think that's on the ground.
Just so it's not too bleak.
Sometimes winter scenes can be very very depressing.
Put just a little pink in there.
Just to give it a little warmth in the background.
This looks like shit.
I need my masher.
I still want to have a distinct winter taste to it.
Play some of that right down to the edge of that pink.
And that's basically all it takes.
Is it?
I did it.
There a little bit and that's good enough.
That'll give us the sky that as I say it has a little life in it.
Some actions happening.
It's not just a flat old dead sky.
You can see light areas and I like that in the sky.
Shoot that's working pretty good.
Maybe we'll do the same thing down here.
Shit.
Anything that we don't use.
I should have done this in the beginning.
If this is a winter scene maybe we'll have some snow.
You've got to have shadows in the snow.
Or maybe it'll turn out to be water.
Who knows?
It doesn't matter.
I'm doing pretty well.
We can fix anything that can happen here.
We don't concern ourselves with mistakes.
We just have happier mistakes.
What a fucking unbelievable person.
I love this guy.
Bob Ross is incredible.
What a fucking joy of a human.
You know what I mean?
Seriously.
I should have done this more often.
I should do this like every fucking week.
This feels good.
It looks okay.
I don't know.
It's a little too much in the middle.
Oh wait.
Black, Prussian blue, a little patch of crimson.
A patch of crimson.
Blue.
Crimson.
A little crimson and I'm going to get some white.
White.
Just take a little bit of white.
Okay.
Mix up.
Put a little more blue in there.
A little more blue.
Yeah.
I want it to have sort of a blue cast to it.
That's good.
Oh, I like it.
That's a good looking color.
Okay.
Yeah.
You just mix it until it gets to the flavor you like.
My flavor is...
It's sort of a drab.
Real bright.
Too much white?
Please old fanbrush today!
Yo look still...
See this color is not...
Wrong.
Wrong!
Where's my paintbrush?
Wrong.
Wrong!
Where's the paintbrush?
Wrong.
Where's the brush?
Where is it?
Where's my paintbrush?
Where is my paintbrush?
Where's my fucking paintbrush?
Pretty close.
I'm going to pause this.
Maybe it has a nice winter color.
Okay.
Pursed.
Where's my paintbrush?
Okay.
All right.
Good.
so that needs to be this a little more crimson a little more blue a little more gray a little more
white i think we're there i think we're there here we go on pause i need black okay yeah black too
squish this down here black okay how's that look that's very wintery i think i got it a little
more there we go that's it that's the one right there that's it i got it that's the one i'm good
let's go let's grab an old brush an old brush full of color where's it going
maybe in our world back here i don't know where it's going somewhere see this color is not
but it's already on the canvas let's push upward today and make us a little tree it's pretty close
to the color it's on the canvas and that's what we're looking for i don't want it too much right
there and you decide how many trees live in your world it's up to you totally well i only did one
as you've probably heard me say before to me that's what's so fantastic about painting
is that each and every person will paint differently and that's what makes it special
if we all painted the same way what a boring time it would be see yeah that's right you would know
what the finished painting was going to be before you start that's right he's right because people
are different paintings are different it's the beauty of it it really is makes it very special
allows you to to show your individuality the trees do we want here it's up to you you decide
you decide maybe like five you just want a few maybe just a little baby one right there
he's not so big yet make up little stories you know people look at you like you're a little
strange but that's all right painters are expected to be different i love bob ross
it's trees i thought i don't have a real paintbrush
what the fuck is that thing i've missed down here at the base of this
yes so just by tapping we're just going to softly softly disappear over here
we used to just sort of look like we're just sitting in a little misty area
just breathing in the cold air i fixed it very misty cold looking and already you had the
impression of winter mine looks like a forest of burnt down this doesn't look like clean
now the paint snow with a two inch brush very easy loaded full of color which is white and we have
we already have this gray color on the canvas we put on and talked about it being shadow now
it's gonna pick that up see there we just let it sort of disappear over here we don't care
fuck wrong way that easy fantastic why are you doing that snow is one of the easier things to
paint in this technique okay you ready for a little a little fun today maybe tell you what
we filmed the show in indiana and there's a there's a lot of old barns here that just
let's paint an old barn today barn in there one of the easiest ways is to take
scrapes out of basic shape just where's my scraping tool where's my scraper exact and
you're not where's the fucking scraper committed here i'm actually using this the whole time
decide what comes down like yeah it has a place over here for the cow to sleep you decide barns
come in all kinds of shapes where's the scraper farmers are like painters they they do it their
way wait stop stop stop stop pause it that's so great about being a fantastic
that looks so good okay pause it where's the scraper can somebody help me out here where's
the scraper behind you on the table where is it this is a dora moment i don't know where it is i
threw it a long time ago i've whipped it across the room a very long time ago and this place is
filthy so i have no idea where the scraper is here is it you're throwing for views i don't know
where the scraping tool is does anybody see the scraping tool does this work it's under the
elevator wait see what do you mean under the elevator what the fuck am i going to do this
little scraping tool it's near the spoon i just saw it big canvas left corner i don't think it's
even still here can i get another one i looked right at it did i under the lift you mean under
this there it is all right i got my scraping tool i'm good all right bob what are we doing
let's do it snow is one of the easier things to paint in this technique okay you ready for a
little a little fun today let's go tell you what we filmed the show in indiana and there's a
there's a lot of old barns here that just fascinate me let's paint an old barn today one of the
easiest ways is to take a scrape out a basic shape just sort of scrape it out it doesn't have to be
and you're not committed you're not committed here so let's just decide what kind of old barn
we want maybe it comes down like that maybe it has a place over here for the cow to sleep
it doesn't matter you decide this is just a figured tree all right i made it a perspective
their way great about being a fantastic country sorry the other side about the same distance here
but just scrape out i hope you can see there's just a basic basic that thing sucks and as i
mentioned earlier you are not committed bandak brown dark sienna you can change your mind at
this point a little roll of paint now let's begin picking out the little thing there's the the back
i didn't paint it
me too i do that i do i got that's take let's take let's take some white arc sienna
uh a little band i can i wasn't done a little crimson too what the heck uh give it a little
warm feeling don't over mix the paint off a little roll of paint then we can go up in here
shit and just barely touch just let it graze see let it graze looks like old old wood
if you painted barns and cabins and stuff what happened here what happened to mine
antique glass for example when you get my age you have a tendency to like
you can relate to them i need a thinner brush it's this it's not going to work it's not going to
work let's take a little bandage whether it's darker on the side because maybe not as much
light is going to hit over here see that's much darker now that some boards in there for that
we'll just take some bandag brown i need a thicker brush but i need a thinner brush it's too thin but
it's too thick raid song what what happened who raided another fucking monster raid who raided
i came to see what's up coney thanks for the raid welcome everybody shit low to you what's
going on coney coney am i saying this wrong i'm saying this wrong oh my god i'm such a shithead
i got it i got it i got it well thank you welcome guys today we're uh we you get a nice straight
edge i guess i don't even do i have to explain what's happening i mean i think this is very
clear that i'm just this is just a complete bogus this is not working well uh but thanks
to the very welcome guys hope you had a good stream if what happened there's no paint on this
this actually looks not this just looks off this it's very bad this is very bad happy accidents
well what happens when they're all accidents what happens if you only have accidents so you have a
nice straight edge i need purple there and i need white up here straight edge this looks like an old
book this is like an old shitty tomb that you found in like your grandfather's attic
there's like a bunch of spells in this i i don't know what to do about this
but you can just move it anyway that you i fucked up this angle i don't know how all right we need
a door oh cal's gotta have a way to get in and out there let's take some bandage decide where
your door lives and once again don't worry about the bottom we're gonna do we're gonna do a barn
as i mentioned earlier okay uh wherever we wanted to be i need a door which is about time to do now
let's say the old barn take too much cutting on that but sometimes i paint that's that's that's
salad fingers house that's who that's who lives there okay um what do i do now wait he's little
like uh speckles down here on it on the snow you know what they say about it i gotta pat it over
here on the other side we'll just bring it when in doubt just like mush this fucking thing down
and it looks kind of like you did it on purpose snow is so easy to paint i actually don't like
this so this actually i don't this doesn't look that bad actually now i look at it gotta have a
big big what's he doing very very helpful most is important is having what is having easel that
holds your paint you're okay you're painting you're gonna cough your sneeze you really need
you all right okay you're okay you're just going like he's supposed to like sneeze or cough
you're good he's okay missed it what happened little crimson little crimson in there what he
just do maybe right here when you paint just a little bit pretty soon you begin to get a feel
for it when it touches if it don't want to pull just right then you can add a little that's not
lightning i just knew the paint wasn't going to cover us unless i did i guess it got be darker
have a happy little tree he lives right there darker little guy darker on the side the barn
go the other side over here you know me here we go bigger tree big old tree so much fun to make
they're very simple very simple takes a little practice like everything else everything in your
life takes a little practice and mine looks pretty good this technique faster than any painting
technique that i have ever seen fuck out of the way i think i've tried just about all of them wells
are so forgiving what am i what am i painting with acrylic i know what that is i think that's
why the old masters painted mostly in oils they just have a richness mediums to me are very flat
when they're dry and they're harder this is the easiest because it's very forgiving you can't
make a mistake here all right let's take let's take some of that nice gray color we had
this don't look half bad now there's a bunch of trees that covering all the shitty things i did
maybe there's a little just work way out here oh shit when in doubt mash it on our little ever
drink titanium white i changed the blue i've been using titanium white liquid white and titanium
blue whatever that was this is a blue spruce i just made a decision command level decision
right here that looks really really good not mine but his omega l command focus on your face what
to decide which trees in the foreground make the small one here is so you do the one
what oh my god what actually good what is good and did a little tree over here
somebody just made this this is this is good that's pretty good that's really good nice job
is the other you need to click then click this link what the fuck not edited oh my fucking god
hmm okay let's go keep going i only got like five minutes left oh it's like saw it don't take it
off it's nice and frosty titanium white this is gonna ruin it yep winter seems a lot it
might be the easiest ones to do fucking hell yeah what do you got here and we just blend that a
little bit until it looks nice and soft all right let's go in this little tree over here
i'm intentionally grabbing some of that dark color see we'll put him up on a little hill
that easy that's not gonna be white right he sort of sits up high isn't that neat but just
by pulling some of that color that you can create that illusion believable to have this kind of
power it's a blustery day you just decide like that i like it right there right there my path
is fine you can just go back and this until it gets just what we consider perfect for the roof
and sometimes it's nice to just pop in a little duder here what do you say open in one
you decide you decide where they are but you have little patches of bushes and sticks and wigs
limbs and twigs that go everywhere what is the same brush ready to get crazy let's take some
van dyke brown and i brown mostly van dyke brown mostly van dyke brown do i have van dyke brown
i don't have brown brown does not a color here what is this we're gonna make it
all right we're gonna make van dyke brown is that van dyke brown is this van dyke brown okay let's
give him a friend let's give him a friend maybe this is an old birch tree it lives out here it's
up to you oh why did that fucking happen i got actually visibly mad about that this is the 31st
series of the joy of painting good gosh holy shit that looks so good for this long been doing this
now for years i need white i need white i need white white white white white
and you've made me feel special to enlighten into your home and to let me be part of your family
i could do it if you hadn't got to see all the shows in your area you would like to
give your station a call they're available to them they're available to them or if you want to see
some of them over again it's the only way they know the brown but paint them here i'm just gonna
put on some little lambs it's too cold for there to be any leaves on here they went they went to
florida oh shit this leaf there's a good thing i didn't hold it over there i need to add limbs
where's the what i do with my paintbrush where's the fucking paintbrush where's the
fucking paintbrush where's the fucking paintbrush where's the paintbrush paint it no no the other
paintbrush i'm not holding it no no reposit where the white paint is hear me why i i don't
i'm sorry i have the paint says where's it this is fucking hidden object game that was a hidden
object game give a break that was a hidden object game okay let's go back he wants to do limbs on
here with the titanium uh titanium brown wherever it is oh just rascal a little stick right in there
maybe let's go right over in here maybe over in here we can put the indication of just
a few little twigs and sticks and things that are living everywhere i can shoot i think with
that we've done haven't finished painting let's take a little bread and we'll sign this rascal
i really hope you've enjoyed this little painting i hope you'll try it it'll give you a lot of
experience using the equipment and with experience comes confidence with confidence you know you can
do anything that you believe you can do there it is from all of us here until next time that did it
bless my friend i did it what do you think it's not bad too bad i could have uh i can't do the poll
i wish i could do the vote let me start let me try to connect it again you are connected
shit i'm not connected though oh well actually good it's it's all right let's sell it on the
marketplace sell it too wait what do you want sell it for as much as i can possibly get
four hundred dollars don't keep it what why st no it's all it's all messed up it got disconnected
and reconnected and it's all fucked up put it on the fridge i have one to do here what i want to
do here i'm just gonna go wild with this one all right all right the first thing i see in chat
is what we're doing first thing i see i'm looking for a inspiration i'm gonna say three things okay
we got green pickle okay good i might did green already no the next one a bear okay bear where's
the bear where is the bear at a waterfall all right bear at a waterfall what time is it time of day
night or day morning okay morning bear at a waterfall in the morning i have to clean this
is a this is a joke i it's time i gotta clean up this is ridiculous i i wanted give me a moment
this is absurd you know throw all the shit in the corner okay let's i'm gonna i'm gonna go i'm
gonna clean up draw do peter griffin no i'm doing a bear at a waterfall in the morning that's what i
did we just did a come on it's improv painting improv throw it in the trash chute this there's
no trash chute here we go make the bear peter just give like a white shirt and the green pants and
glasses i think they already did that guys this is something that has already happened
they remember that time when i was a bear i don't know maybe it was remember that time i was attacked
by a bear no no remember that time i was he got attacked by a bear at one point right it was a
chicken no it would he look he's been attacked by every animal what yeah what what this is different
mediums this is different mediums guys i don't understand this is a different medium i'm on the
it's not this computer game i thought if it was the same game it was the wrong link there is no
meme or anything you just look particularly handsome today that hairstyle really suits you
that's chat said that hey thanks really really through thanks guys this is big look at this
confidence boost you're giving me thanks for the confidence boost i was about to just put my finger
in my nose and fucking like suck on it i don't know just trying to make myself like uglier
i'm thinking about doing it i really am i'm seriously considering it everyone that like
thinks i'm like handsome if i like eat boogers on stream you're not going to think that anymore
you know what i mean you can be like holy shit that's fucking disgusting never mind
maybe i should do it more handsome if i do that all right what where what am i doing what was
happening oh i was cleaning right i was cleaning up all right i look so zoomed in why bear in the
morning at a waterfall that's what it was i have a booger eating stream i don't i don't think so
how did this get up here well i don't remember even this how did this even happen how did they
get up there oh the blow dryer right i let me state this one more time for the people that
might have just trickled in here i have paid for games that had like way less shit in it than this
one and this is just like a free demo you can just like just you just load this up and just draw
and paint and just fuck around and throw stuff around i'm gonna have to give this a full 100
recommended download pretty rare to get that from me that's pretty rare you know i hope myself to
set like a much higher standard than everybody else put on music yeah this is kind of doesn't
be scratching it like this is just me scratching my ass all right guys take a quick little break
i'm coming in poisoned sumac it sucks you have no fucking idea how itchy this is
no more crack there's no crack today this is i'm just chilling out this is a relaxing stream
i told you this is a late night stream this is a late night relaxed paint stream
i told you what you're gonna get from this today it is today it's 10 o'clock pacific what time is
it where you are i thought this was a green wall i really thought this was a green wall it was not
a green wall this is like a gray wall 1 a.m well it's because it's because of west coast of best
coast he's an east coast trader i did used to live on the east coast you're right nobody even said
that i just made that person up coming along absolute cringe what's the cringiest thing i've
no never mind fuck that we're not doing that not doing that never mind i'm gonna stop that one
before it right in its tracks do a cringe or it's pre-recorded i already did like two minutes ago
people playing battleship yet no oh nice and clean it's drunken
i'm just making a trash corner right i have to clean up it's making me it's freaking me out i
need to clean nice germ of reference poser am i a poser if it's me what about i'm the one saying it
yes you're a poser i'm gonna miss a spot and someone's gonna be really really upset this
visit background is ridiculous we are absolutely gonna play this again when it comes out i'm gonna
actually launches with like a story mode you will see this again for sure games where i get to look
games where i get to clean stuff and i can make a mess this has got both i can make a mess and
clean up wow that's pretty solid for me this has creation and destruction that's pretty high up
there i think okay good let's fix this oh fuck this is the new house flipper no this is called
such art creative genius something like that it's something like that i love that water oh
a wet brush the wetness don't you just love it don't you love the streaks
i just want to dump the shit all over the ground and then clean it up i hope there's a power
washer unlockable make power wash the dlc and then make it so i can power wash the people's
driveways and stuff please paint the clearing oh it's looking so fresh you need a clean
environment to work oh i love that somebody make that make make like a you know what make like a
like a like what's the paving of the driveway i want to pave a driveway with like the tar and
shit don't you i want to like just drop the tar and like spread spread spread spread spread
make a clean thin wet shiny i want to do that you know what i mean like just like put like tar
driveway power wash somebody's house the drive i just want to do that that's a fetish i don't care
i don't care if me talking about power washing a driveway is doing it for you i'm gonna not i'm
not gonna not talk about power washing a driveway you germa don't put your finger up like that that's
a fetish oh sorry germa don't make eye contact that's a fetish okay i guess i'll take a sip out
of my drink germa swallowing liquid meat is a fetish swallowing germa standing still with no
emotion that's like i like it i get off to that then it just i won't exist i'll turn the cam off
and i'll be quiet thank you okay good it didn't it didn't uh make a paint splatter i really do feel
like this is kind of like if somebody ever was uh let's put it this way right if somebody would
ever hit me up and be like oh hey man can ah i really like love what you did with your kitchen
could you like take a picture of your like of like your kitchen yeah i love what you did with it
yeah no no no shove every fucking dirty disgusting thing in the corner just stuff it in there just
anytime someone wants a photo of like any part of my room or any part of like a place
it's just make the take all the dirty shit throw it in the corner clean one corner up wipe it make
it look really nice like wash like a window and make it look beautiful so then like you can take
that picture and like send it to mom so then she doesn't think that like that you're like living
like a fucking goddamn mess you need one corner oh like hey what do you think what do you think of
my place oh wow that looks really really good yeah it does these are all like fucking mcdonald's
bags we have an insane link now okay holy shit oh my god fucking jeez power wash simulator is on
steam what the fuck ready to read cleanup time is this what you guys are spamming so intently
this is the thing you were spamming so intently no no this is the one we were spamming this is
like is that i don't know if that's i can't tell this is me this is freaking me out this is actually
like a scary picture is this supposed is it now my face who is that wrong again but is that me
it's like really freaking me out okay uh wrong again apparently so give me the right one our
wash simulator that's the one it's this one please this is the real one all right power wash
simulator look let the soothing sounds of high pressure water wash away your worries fire up
your power washer blast away every speck of dirt and grime you can find release the pressure with
power wash simulator when is this out this comes out this comes out this year q1 2021 is what it
says which means like probably like three years no way this is oh my fucking god this is the best
thing ever i need to like i can't this is the fucking this is the best thing ever
release the pressure you power wash the video game this q1 2021 is when this comes out guys
guys have it like can i just have it how do i get this i want this right now q1 2021 means
the game's done the game is done how do i get it i need this game there's a demo okay there's a demo
i did you add pave driveway in this one and there's another link uh gas gas gas i don't
even want to click this one i'll give this one second of my time all right let's go i'm gonna
play a game let's go i'll watch simulator you're gonna see it on this channel second it releases
and i mean literally the second that it comes out i don't care if it comes out at two o'clock
in the morning i'm playing it when it comes up okay play the gas video i just did let me uh get
rid of some of the trash please please demo here demo here all right yeah yeah well i want to i
want to play the real thing i don't want to play a demo demo is out i want to play the real thing
i don't play demo i want to play the real video game i don't want to play a demo this is a demo
no this is not a demo this is not a demo this is a free version of the game that is this is
not a demo of the game this is a free version of the game that's releasing at some point in
the next month or two or three or four i don't know whenever it releases this is not a demo
this is a standalone free version of the game if it was a demo super mario at some point would
pop on the screen and go thank you for playing next person in line and i'd have to get out of
the way it's not what this is it's an old bit still relevant still works how many episodes of
johnny carson i've gone back and watched none i've never seen a full episode of this night
show with johnny carson not once not even one not even probably not even five minutes of a single
portion of his streams or whatever the video whatever it is the show why would you i don't
sometimes it's fun to go watch like just weird old well not weird but you know old stuff recently
i watched all the like video game and snack food 90s commercials and 80s commercials i don't know
i kind of like it i don't know about it's like real comfy and very cozy it's nostalgia that's
right that's right like the raid song now i i got rated like an hour and a half ago
if you didn't get the raid song an hour and a half ago you're not gonna get it now all right we're
almost done with the i'm gonna dump this in the trash ah this is footprints whose footprints are
these was it oh uh i almost said johnny carson solid snake and now wow we're gonna who's who
hey ed whose footprints are these
you know you know wow wow wild absolutely wild that game was wild ed goodbye oh there's still
a red thing in there i just dunked this yeah i'll just dunk that in the in the water it was owen
wilson no it was johnny carson nothing happens when you jump in it doesn't they were right bad
end okay give me the uh trash uh heap thing throw a bunch of this shit away not the paint brushes i
need those god i just love picking up stuff and putting it over here it's so fun just pick up
things chores in real life suck chores in video games good oh jesus this is bad hold on you're
lazy yeah i don't know why you know what it's because you don't have to go anywhere the reason
why chores are so good because chores are fun they are they can be fun but you have to move around
if i could put a vr helmet on right now and have a mannequin of me walking around the house well i
had vr connected to the mannequin the android me and just sat here at the desk and just like
cleaned the house i would do it that would be awesome you know how much shit i would get done
if i could just put a vr headset on and let and just go with the android guy of me i would do i
would go to the bank i would i would fold all my laundry i would do everything it would be so
awesome i would get so much done what chores do you want to do at the bank just go i don't go to
the bank and make a deposit or withdrawal i don't know this is errands yeah no not not like you
not robbing the bank robbing the bank with the headset on as the as me android me how many people
would just like not know what they were doing if that was the case you like get in there and you
like getting think about how you see people move around in vr people would just get like run up by
cars like oh i'm gonna go i'm gonna go out and do some errands i'm gonna go to target and they
were like they wouldn't be able to get out of the front door it was like bumping into the walls they
would like trip over they would like open the they would open the door to the front door to their
house and like hit themselves in the fucking face and the android would break and we would be and
no one would be able to even do this you would just look around and there'd be people just all
around your neighborhood just like throwing glass bottles into the ground and you'd hear laughter
in all the houses like in all the windows you'd hear like it's like all right okay you would hear
like oh and like you'd look over the guys like bumped into these stops like that what like bill
your neighbor's android just like stops stopped moving for a second i followed along oh you did
nice job let's take a look let's let's go over it not that one look that's pretty damn good what
program is this is this paint what mine look like some of you guys have fucking heavy critics
this looks great this is like very good this looks excellent it's too brown what he means
too brown what are you talking about that's exactly what he put bob ross did why this is
like fantastic you guys are fucking out of your minds all right can i can i clean please it was
a real voice yeah it was that's just me saying can i clean please loudly yes that's how i talk
all right we're getting close to whoa no we're not why there's so many teals why are there this
many teals this is way too many teal isn't it it's way too many you did to fill the ball right to
fill the bucket all right i forgot how's that look a little bit there's a little little mark
over there a little scuff mark perfect okay cool let's clean up the paint can i get in there and
i can good check the shop on the computer what the baba zone i wish i had all these
large sponge adjustable easel next gen movement easel water gun give me the water gun i don't
care you already have these one oh no cancel that cancel cancel cancel i already have this
cancel cancel well i can't i'll get the water gun at least i'll get a water gun can i like
clean my feet or something what's going on here i bring this back boomer ipad omega low boomer ipad
i don't i'm trying to figure out how to do this just return it i'm hitting it with a mop package
has arrived oh my god wrong champ no germaphenous germaphenous do i have a good pogchamp emote
what do you think facing the wrong way right people probably gonna hate it because it's
facing the wrong way it should be official i don't think it should hog champ slug pog is better
bug pog is is slug pog is better but i don't talk about that anymore not at that even it's
not supposed to exist anymore blood everywhere hey it's late for a lot of you guys i'm surprised
there are this many people still here this is late night for a lot of you this is 10 11 12 1
this is almost to almost 132 am for you guys a lot of you eastern time and don't even talk about
eu eu you just had some fucking tea you woke up you just had some fucking eggs it was like 7 a.m
eu 8 a.m 6 a.m i'm losing sleep for this well i'm really happy you stopped by maybe you stop by
again on the next one probably tomorrow we'll see you tomorrow what should we do tomorrow you know
i'm terrified to go play hitman 3 again because of how that stream ended i was literally walking
around in a circle for 25 minutes and i just i was just zonked out of my mind i'm actually
terrified to open that game again on stream because i feel like it's gonna happen again i
don't know why it's like that that's that that level just is fucking with my head um oh hey wiggly
joe thanks for 20 community subs thank you wiggly joe that's a lot of fucking money thanks for the
subs you you can skip it i know but can you really there's only six levels in hitman you're really
gonna skip one of them that's skipping what 15 of all the content of the whole game 15 30 45 60
75 100 got it i got it i could just skip it but i got 400 bucks with that painting that i just
put up for 400 should i go back to hitman 3 tomorrow and do a couple more levels or something
what should we do tomorrow it is available it is there all right all right we'll do that we'll do
that tomorrow i i'm i'm gonna try to not be like a fucking weirdo tomorrow i don't be high maybe
what have i counteracted so i wasn't high last time what if i get high and i counteract it and
i can do it very well interesting this room's gonna be 15 minutes long it's gonna be like a
12 minute stream but uh seriously though no i will do hitman 3 tomorrow i know we've been
started we started later today and that's gonna happen tomorrow too uh tomorrow would not this
late but we'll be starting tomorrow probably around are we like four pacific or 4 30 something
like that i'm just gonna let's just say 4 30 4 30 pacific tomorrow i want to start at like
seven or eight like i did tonight we'll pull it back all right where's my trash you lied about
yakuza i know i didn't we'll do that just not tomorrow and not the day after that and probably
not like until like at least like another four weeks from now in fact it might be like july all
right we are clean very clean actually clean completely clean the only thing is a few more
paint drops over here that's fine and i got a bunch of packages let's see what came in
dump this get the packages and i'm gonna paint that painting what we got oh sick of water gun
give me this how do i use it it's a water gun can i is a paint gun suck it up it is paint
whoa i'm sorry i freaked out all right clean it up clean up clean up clean up everybody clean up
put them up cubrics there does it hurt my eyes this is quick this will be quick look look look
look this is quick it's quick it's quick quick whack this is quick whack why did you just you
just did that to everything you cleaned i added water i added sprayed water with clean this is
water this is blue water with cleaner quick quick it's quick blue water yeah water is blue in every
piece of media you've ever consumed i was water not blue and like every art piece what do you mean
what are you talking about blue is water water is blue that's just the standard default way to show
water on any really anything is it's blue see i told you that was gonna be quack i told you that
was gonna be quack all right what do i do with this i can't erase all right i'm thinking i want
to just spray the hell out of this with spray paint what do you think oh the bear the how long
that was like 45 fucking minutes ago the bear in the waterfall on the morning time
i don't you guys feel like that was yesterday that we talked about that there's a water on me
all right let's say the bear waterfall here we go i want to roll for this one i'm gonna set
let's set that let's set it up here we go get this on here i'm looking for we need to well i need
brown for the rocks blue two types of blue fuck did i just say two kinds of blue
turquoise and blue and royal blue i want green for the grace i want green grace
i want a yellow sky this morning i want a big sun i'm ready green gosh all right that's good
let's get this set up so i want i want i want the bucket i want i need uh i want i want do you ever
have do you ever want you ever have a dream where you where you where you want where you have do
you ever want you ever have it where you get where you have a dream where you i just joined
the stream what the fuck is he doing oh holy shit the reason why chats freaking out so much i just
ate like three boogers on stream it was fucking disgusting go check the vod dude it's fucked up
okay i got water let me bring on my new tools over here this is a new tool look at this thing
let's put you right there okay whatever let's put them on the ground fucking it doesn't matter
i want the little brush right here well vod washers you know what to do i want a ton of
paint in here and i'm just gonna dump this not into my own mouth in here because that's dirty
water now let's fill this up with what color i'm gonna need a lot of blue because it's a big
waterfall big froth at the top i want like a bunch of foam at the top so let's go with i'm gonna say
this blue here maybe like that like that maybe a competent yeah that one right there look at how
fucking beautiful that looks that's robin's egg royal blue and i'm gonna start i need brown i need
a couple of palettes that was just the mario dinnin dinnin dinnin it happened it was like
that's weird it was the first one let me take a look here we go all right i gotta be easy here
waterfall froth up here boom all the way down let's start let's go for it froth check this out
want less paint this one i'm doing working on something all right what do you want me to say
hey look at this look at me look at this thing look at that thing look at this thing oh
i'm working i'm working we told you to hush don't you said to hurry up
get on with it do you know how long it takes to make some of these famous paintings you've ever
seen you know how long the mona lisa took it took like six years for him to finish that
he didn't finish this is what the mona lisa looked like in the first two hours it took
seven years to paint that just you wait till the end of this and you're gonna fucking rate it
this is gonna look sick i can't wait oh come on it looks like shit you don't even know this is you
don't even know what's happening right now you don't even know what's happening right now you
don't even know what's happening they don't they don't they don't get it god none of you here are
artists oops it was a mop again it was like a little charlie brown hair over there i had to
fix that you lost a thousand plus viewers like two o'clock in the morning good i hope you go to
go to sleep it's fucking late as hell it's a lot of paint in this can by the way fuck out of the
way is it present all right drop me drop me look at this froth i'm not even done not even close to
being done this is literally like part zero out of like 200 parts yep yeah yes yes what do you have
to say now let's go straight up yellow i need it to be like that give that to me let's go i want to
use my new brush that we're doing with the sun we're doing the sky bang right up there we're
gonna have tons of rays coming out all right uh what does this look like how does how does this
thing used i like it i love it already get me back up there look at that really got to work it in
work the painting holy shit that looks fucking unbelievably good i'm gonna go like this i like
it oh it's so fucking pretty oh i forgot i didn't make the sun i fucked it up hold on give me that
give me this one give me a deep orange give me this one this is morning time this is uh this is
dawn he's trying start banning people that make fun of my shit i made it i want instant permanent
mans i don't actually ban anybody though it's just me being like a goofy guy all right uh give me this
check this shit out is it gonna be dawn dude this shit kind of looks better than this okay where's
my where's my smasher there it is why is there no water in this bring me up it's dry this is
cheeto dust stop saying that because it's funny oh it looks like shit it looks terrible yeah yeah
whatever i could look making a fucking painting that's 15 feet tall and now we're gonna get to
check this out right boom this is regular cheeto this is flaming hot cheeto now or or oh look at
that color blend this looks like just above watercolors look at that blend this looks like
fucking cave painting this is just this is part zero guys just wait this is gonna be fucking great
looking and i'm getting a lot of i'm getting a lot of art criticism in here getting a lot of
art criticism in here interesting stuff oh don't you think that's quite a redditor thing to do
and i thought you guys hated that place talking about how bad or how much you know about this
about this art you don't think that's a little bit redditor of you but no but we hate that place
right guys interesting fuck come on more blending more blending need to be blending the froth
there we go into the froth there it is there it is see the layering see the texturing i'm doing
you see the layering here do you see the layering here are you paying attention are you paying
attention tap back over tab back over stop looking at porn what do you see the blending over here
oh it looks good wait i just want to make sure i freaked out like one person that forgot they
had this open a little too far we can do some touch-up work later all right give me the yellow
wham oh that's the wrong tool that's the wrong tool i thought it was this one i can fix it
oh yeah fucking hell yeah go to bed why hey mom all right we almost found with part one
part zero i need some rocks i'm gonna paint these rocks i need brown oh how thick is this
that's good we need some brown rocks up there where's the bear this is the background this is
the background the bear goes on top of the background playing music oh shit all right
this is the first thing that i had open somebody did it to me um how about classic music classical
music can you get dmca for like bethoven who owns the rights to bethoven oh nobody does right
does somebody own the rights to this song i don't think so right that's public domain isn't this
oh
somebody owns the performance of this song performance and recording oh quick i you
record yourself doing it grizzly hills from world of warcraft home on oh yeah this song's
fucking awesome all right yeah grizzly hills it's gonna be that's probably gonna be inspiration
now i need uh brown brown and blue hell yeah brown and blue check this shit out so no this is
no this is like a this is like a uh a cobalt kind of blue with a cobalt brown all right let's make
some rocks is the froth over the rocks or under the rocks over it right make sure they're nice and
fucking bumpy and shit i got a bit more froth in here oh they're going up way too high i'm sorry
that was really fucking loud because i kind of like it look at these look at how good these rocks
look to me look at that froth just like bam over the top i'm gonna add a little froth and watch this
gotta get some like different like little formations this might be coal this could be
some type of graphite or coal or stone please add a bird oh well hold on you can be set up on the
rock no we're gonna get the froth is gonna come over the rocks and then everybody can and then
everybody can just can literally sit back and say i fucking was talking shit to this guy
froth what's the froth gun what color was the froth the waterfall behind the rocks
i'm doing this right all right now how does a fucking waterfall work
you just have way too much froth all right let's continue all right bear is gonna be right here we
need a big tree or something here or we need like another set of rocks you don't have to clean a
spray can i need a blue i need give me this blue you know fuck it just go i don't care yeah i do
all right sorry we can fix it we can fix it we can fix it we just had a little bit of froth
all right okay okay all right all right all right all right all right all right all right
there right here i need to finish the background though maybe just a layer of froth layer of grass
down here green down here blend in some green no rocks rocks rocks rocks more of this cobalt
yeah more cobalt blue and then i'm gonna spray it down here we're gonna do some more froth
i need something to spread where's that there where is it where's the uh where's the broom
the broom would be perfect right now where's the broom that little broom handled
no not the mop the broom where's the broom it's up here whatever where's the where's the broom
the broom where's the broom sorry under the elevator what is it where's the broom broom
where's the broom oh wait a minute what about this brush oh that might work hold on yes it will yes
it will yes it will this is the thing i should have used for the bob ross painting this can
spread around like crazy i need more blue here this is like the little bear cave like his little
domain right here this isn't the bear relax this is a fucking crag that he lives in dude this
motherfucker is gonna be lying on this rock just letting the water hit him in the face
as he's sitting under the waterfall look at that crag no no no no the waterfall is behind him
the what why am i talking like this the waterfall is behind him the waterfall is behind him he is
sitting in front of the waterfall they're saying shush oh there's still no bears because i'm almost
i'm done with the background now i'm gonna put a bear right here this is the hard part i need to
put some blue froth over here or something because this doesn't look right yeah we need some blue i
need some froth what color is this yeah i need i gotta fill this in holy shit that looks fucking good
good
holy shit looks fucking good look at that shading
now i have to put a bear in front of this what is it garbage in all capitals
do you don't see like the look the difference the shading and the in the in the all right all right
don't over froth it no what are you talking about froth andy coming in here i need a bear i i think
i need i sorry guys i gotta do hold on that's gonna be deeper up there that's gonna be a little
that's gonna be a little bit higher like this i trust the into i gotta trust it so glad i
trusted my intuition here get up there oops all froth
it needed some extra texture up here now i think it's perfect now it is nope now it is
instead of a bear in front of this i don't know how to draw a bear you know what just you know
before this whole thing is fucking ruined i don't know how to draw a bear okay we need brown first
of all let's clean this up a little like a should be brown like a grizzly bear don't do that not
brown i know it's not brown we're gonna make brown i wanted to this is we're gonna watch just wait
what's that i test it needs to be a little darker i need a reference google a bear first the only
thing to do it by from memory we want to google i know what a bear looks like darker even darker
than that that should be good there it is all right so we got our brown what does a bear look
like let's find okay let me get an image of a bear grizzly bear grizzly bear okay so this is what
we're looking for okay and the music back on so i just turned it off accidentally where did the
music go uh howling fjord let's stay on north wind why not bear what are we thinking looks like
a fucking gorilla should it be a gorilla instead a gorilla doing push-ups stay the course all right
no no it's all right i said it's not that bad you made a table make them chunky i know i know i'm
gonna i'm gonna fluff it up a little with some fluff i had to get the outline and then ears okay
ears hold on i gotta get the outline okay now i need another tool this motherfucker is 2d what
do you mean 2d i'm just trying to get the shape you made donkey kong i'm going in with the i'm
gonna go and do detail line work i need his shape first like his silhouette let me black black black
black black black black black black black black black black black it's an interesting technique
thanks dude bigger faster stronger what he's already bigger and he's already strong there
what that's definitely top five gamer moments 2021 absolutely top five do you see how fucking
well that was look at getting close getting close all right let's keep going it's all right we can
fix it we can fix it later i can fix that i can fix all this why is that different color why is
that different color oh because different brush no it's wet you fool what it doesn't look that
bad i'm gonna pat myself on the face here doesn't look that bad could be way worse than you all know
uh what the fuck was that i hit like i don't know what happened there
why did that even happen control z pretending i like i know but i know i wasn't but i know what
you mean this is stupid like why did that happen what the fuck are you kidding me come on man happy
little accidents you know i'm so chilled out right now this is i like this pretending just froth it
out i will sorry i'm not doing very much talking right now it's getting late this has been this
will be the last one it's very very late we're gonna do the detailed work on the bear and i'll
call it there and i'll see you guys tomorrow afternoon play hitman 3 tomorrow by the way
i'm gonna make sure i eat a full fucking dinner before that stream so my brain works it's gonna
be 15 minutes you need to smoke weed for that stream did somebody said add it take money off
the debt if i'm like zonked on the next hitman stream i ran out of brown just get absolutely
zonked i don't but how much are you gonna take off wait you took a billion one billion if i if
i play zonked off my ass tomorrow on hitman no are you are you serious i'm seeing a lot of deals
deals deals here deal deal deal are you are you you have to be mega zonked no i'm not gonna get
mega zonked i'll get i'll like do some by the way it's legal in las vegas by the way recreational
marijuana is legal so just want to make that very clear liar it's a felony in las no it is not
one billion for zonk there we go let's see oh my god watch me do so fucking much better tomorrow
this is what you guys want i'll just get regular i don't want to like promote like
fucking smoking and like doing that but i mean who doesn't like if you smoke weed you're gonna
like sit down and play hitman like that's what you do let's play fucking hitman dude's gonna be
crazy you were high on the simpsons hit and run stream no i was not it was literally just stone
cold sober that entire time all right let me i need black is it two or three i think it was three
what do we got so far you smoke it i do not smoke i have a little that i use i usually do between
like two and five milligrams of thc and cbd i don't smoke it's easier to control if i eat it
and i started really doing it for pain so i still kind of do weed injection is this the right color
i hope it is it it's not is it is this wet or is this wrong what or wrong looks kind of wrong
lighten it up wait yeah i need to light it up that looks wrong too just give me what's the stupid
thing this thing we got a deal what the fuck um i've read that much of you have voted yes for that
that's very surprising okay um like that's a billion that's one billion off the debt
we'll see we'll see i might just do it for fun and not like not have anything to do with that
but you know if a billion comes off ace cam has to be on that was not part of the deal
no you can't do that you can't add stuff like that you can add stuff like that that's not how
it works that's altering that's deal altering that's no that's illegal deal altering that's
in the fine print that wasn't it's deal altering deal is off what deal is off deal is off why would
the deal be off because i don't want to do face cam why is blue coming through this by the way
is that not dry i was a bear's face look like why does he look so weird 1.5 for with face cam on
two billion for face cam and he's got a pink mouth
i can fix it with some froth later don't worry what did you do um hold on i'm not done
i didn't lean back and go done no i'm busy i'm doing it does the nose need to be bigger
no it's it's that's a good size nostrils we need gray like circles okay let's the nostrils delete
the mouth no i have to i have to make the teeth he's got like a row of teeth here white or no no
not arctic white we need we don't need arctic white we need shaving cream on your face look
at how gray and yellow your teeth look by comparison white that seems to work gosh he's
kind of going like he's going i don't know how to draw eyes and shit i don't know how to do it
i don't know how to do this and then i had to fix this and i gotta give him fur this bear is
fucking zonked it kind of looks like he's like shit over here all right now he needs fur i'm not
doing anything how do we texture how do we do fur oh it's the same color shit you're right okay
it's fucking stupid it's like dentures hey it's and i think it looks okay now we gotta get some
froth going over his back because he's like way he's bathing froth him out of existence you know
what holy shit what a good idea holy shit that's perfect it's like he's he's he's there it worked
perfectly why is he like red what about the ears oh my god i forgot about the ears i'll get him
right now this is an aardvark the germadillo it's germadillo so can we see it can we see
it's germadillo from vttv holy shit that's uh that's not what that's supposed to be
that's supposed to be a grizzly bear i can't believe that's germadillo you gotta be shitting
me don't worry i got it i'm gonna do it there we go all right see it's there saved there's
no claws hey just you just can't see him through the froth sign it if i just roll like i see uh i
need to sign it come on what the fuck don't sign it why not i keep just forgetting where i put down
my stupid paint brushes here whatever doesn't matter sign sign sign sign look i whatever there
you go photo time no i want to i want a better picture than this this is like all dirty something
sure take this one here it goes it's not warm yeah it is it's a hot summer day and he is
frothing himself to cool down the hot day all right i'm gonna call it here it's getting way
too late let us vote uh that like kind of disconnected and fucked up like an hour or two ago
that was fun this is a great game this is really just fun to play uh again if you're curious this
was such art creative genius or something uh this game is free and i guess they're coming
out with an elaborate actual video game i have to say this wasn't a video game but they're coming
out with another real game i guess uh if you like what you saw and you like this game go get it
why wouldn't you it's free a lot of fun you know yeah when the full version comes out i'll play
it again it's got a lot of cool stuff in it but i'll uh i'll see you guys tomorrow tomorrow
we're gonna play hitman 3 gonna hang out and uh probably around 4 30 pst we'll start like
somewhere in the afternoon it's been a pleasure we're just about five hours look at that it's
been a pleasure let's run the credits before we go i'll see you guys tomorrow have a great rest of
your night take care of yourselves thanks for all the subs and everybody we had a shitload of them
thank you everybody seriously sorry to eu for uh i guess making the stream at like 4 a.m your time
but no thanks a lot appreciate nonetheless we'll see you tomorrow it's 3 a.m here now yeah on east
coast this is the late one late night streaming australia thanks you oh yeah that's right it is
it is what time is it in australia 14 it's what 14 15 hours ahead of west coast it's probably like
two o'clock in the afternoon seven o'clock at night holy shit it's seven o'clock on the 26th
25th what what day is it in australia right now 25th wow two days ahead one day ahead yeah
so we'll see you tomorrow get some sleep take care of yourselves hit man three tomorrow good night
everybody take care of yourselves i was a little premature on the goodbye didn't even get through
the t's yet i looked over i was like uh whoa wait a minute he's a little i was a tad premature on
that goodbye the t's he's losing viewers yeah i don't know damn it we raid wait we're gonna go
hopefully not seen in a while let's see who's live right who's live at like midnight yeah let's let's
go to lidwig we were we we uh we said hello to vinnie a few nights ago let's go say hi to lidwig
lidwig thanks for watching everybody see you soon goodbye see you tomorrow good night take
care of yourselves and get this raid off get this raid over like six or seven k make me fucking look
good i see you later