Hello everybody. Hello. Where is he? It's only been like one minute. Come on, I'm a little slow today.
The gas is empty. My car needs to be filled up. Oh, he's a little short today, a little. Yeah,
just a little bit. So, uh, last night I did mention that, you know, depending on how I
woke up, I had some things to do tomorrow, but if I got up and I was alright then we were
gonna go and so we're gonna go. We're good. Sunday stream, hope you're having a good afternoon.
Hope you got some sleep after last night. I did. A little bit of a hangover, but it's okay. We're
gonna play Sam and Max. We're gonna relax. We're gonna finish up season one. Only one episode
remains. We'll see how long this takes. You said it little buddy. And then depending on,
maybe season two, maybe start episode one or maybe wait, maybe play some more at how
this is gonna be one of those streams where we just chill and do whatever. After last night,
I need a, uh, I need a relaxing stream. Alright, so I got everything ready to go.
Oh shit, it is Cinco. Yeah, it's Cinco de Mayo. I drank on the wrong day.
Oops. Well, anyways, that's alright. No, I am not drinking again today. No.
I need a two to three week cool down period in between every time I drink. Hey, you've seen
that before. I have to get to do some audio stuff. May the fifth of vodka be with you.
No, don't give me this hair of the dog bullshit. No way. That's like, that's a crock of shit.
I'll tell you that much. Ready? Why on earth? What in any scenario would you drinking booze
make you feel better after drinking booze all day or all night? No, it just like,
it just fucks your brain up more and it just locks you down. It just puts you back into
being drunk again. No, it's water, potassium, you know, coconut water, pedialyte, just hydrate.
Don't like take a shot of whiskey when you get up in the morning. Don't do that.
Alright, so let's go. How loud is it? Not bad. Uh, I had to do some video game
tap. I remember that company, which is why every citizen will find a complimentary
government issued in the mailbox. Get to spray in America. Eat this mother up.
That building was really close. An announcement from the president of the United States.
I forgot he's president, right? You missed your cue. What? Oh, sorry, little buddy in
chief. I'm still thinking about our last case. Little buddy in chief said it was working for
somebody named Roy G. Ben. That's what you guys call me. But for who or who? We're detectives,
Sam, not mind readers. Hey, maybe we should ask you bliss mind readers. That's it.
No, that's not it. By the way, have you seen my copy of a medics,
the handbook for multicolored happiness by hue bliss colors? No, think Max. Think. Well,
I know I had it this morning. That's it morning in the ancient tongue of the mud
worshipping kapala who tech tribe of the Serengeti. Our word morning means he who
destroys the hypnotic rainbow man. That's the word he fears the most. So this Roy G.
Biv is the one person we've met who's never said the word morning. That means it's,
it's the commission. I never did trust him. No chowder head. It's hue bliss.
No commissioner. I didn't mean look, I need you to put out an APB on hue bliss.
Yeah, Max is still president as of now by the Greek goddess Selena and a chariot with dual
overhead cams and silver Fox mud flaps. We're on our way. Let's go. Max. The commissioner
said that hue bliss is currently staying at his exclusive prismatology retreat,
the blister of tranquility. Oh boy. I bet it's somewhere really cool and exotic,
like a remote island in the South Pacific or Des Moines. Even farther, pal.
The game is quiet. It shouldn't be. I'll turn it up. Oh, it's German moon. German moon.
Why is his face on the moon? How's the hangover? It's all right. It's not terrible.
I woke up looking down. It was like four to five on the 10 point hangover skill.
We've diminished down to about three. I'm good. Just a little slow. Bright side of the moon.
You woke up covered in cardboard and wine. Back on the moon, doesn't it? We made good time too.
We've still got plenty of generic brand powdered orange flavor drink mix left.
You always did know how not to infringe on a registered trademark, little buddy.
What are we doing first, Sam? Let's locate the blister of tranquility. Find out what hue bliss
is up to and arrest his unprincipled magical butt. Is that a visitor center?
Is there a center on the moon? Hey, don't scoff at that. Eventually you're gonna be able to go to
the moon for free. That's right. There's gonna be just a train you can take from here to the
moon. Not gonna cost any money. It's gonna be old news in like 100 years. All right,
Harry. Wait, wasn't this the- Well, well. Aren't you Teddy Bear? Once upon a time,
but no longer. Wasn't this person way bigger? This dude was like 10 feet tall.
How would a train work? Just lay train tracks down to the moon. It's gonna be like an Elon Musk
bullet train. They'll be floating moon beams or something. Doesn't matter. They're reusing assets.
Who are you now? I've gone back to being Harry Mole Man. Or should I say I've gone forward?
Prismatology has helped me find a new me where the old one used to be.
Prismatology. So this, that's the whole mind control thing. It's been hue bliss the whole
time. You see, yeah, there we go. You seem shorter than you used to. Tiny. I used to
use that exoskeleton, but Prismatology has taught me that size doesn't matter. Color does. Harry
Mole Man will never be sensitive about being diminutive again. Or about referring to himself
in the third person apparently. And also you explode in that whole factory. Prismatology helped
me put Harry Mole Man back together again. Looks like it may have left out a few pieces
by mistake. Oh, hold on. Streamlabs windows in the wrong spot. Are you still a criminal?
Are you still a notorious criminal? Or an obscure one like Kevin Mitnick? No. I don't know
who that is. I've postulated my lemma since Prismatology found me. It's the straight and
narrow for Harry Mole Man from here on out. All right. Well, I guess it's nice to see you again.
Actually, I'm still a little sore that he tried to get you to shoot me last time we
saw him. I'm channeling my saturation towards making amends for my past transgressions.
Prismatology has taught me. Yeah, yeah, we get it. So is Prismatology like a
take on Scientology? Is that kind of what the deal is here? All right. Where's Mr.
Hugh Bliss? Seen Hugh Bliss around here lately? To see the master I need only search my heart.
I meant see him in the traditional fashion. No. Windows. He's usually in the blister these days.
Okay, so where's the blister? Which way to the blister of tranquility? Enlightenment
is the only way to reach the blister of tranquility. How about we enlighten your
skull a little? Would that work? The blister is through that little box right over there.
Little box, all right. See you later. We've got important sightseeing to do.
Great! That's what we got, huh? Wait, wait. Okay, so this is the blister of tranquility.
Let's this guy back again. Wait, didn't we fire this guy? No, he went on vacation.
Hold on. What's a hypno beam display? Let's just look. What's supposed to go here?
These hypnotic goggles were an early prototype of the hypno beam technology currently being
used to further the worldwide goals of Prismatology. Wow! Invisible goggles!
The goggles were stolen a few months ago. Honestly, some people will take anything
that's not bolted to the floor. So, all right. What is this thing? Can I pick up a spoon? What's
this? Looks like a bent spoon with some peanut butter on it. The power to bend and rebend spoons
stored within this completely indestructible magical talisman was among the first mental
abilities to be developed and popularized by Hugh Bliss. Big deal! I can bend spoons with my
bare hands. One question, would it work on wrenches? Yeah, a wrench is close enough.
Interesting, interesting. Ah, you made me forget where I was. Let's see. Indestructible
magical talismans. Oh, yeah. The virtually indestructible display case is a triumph of
modern Prismatological science. So smash it, textbook. Virtually indestructible?
Extensive testing has been done on the case, showing it to be impervious to bullets, acid,
high falls, crushing force, sonic weaponry, diamond chip drills, hurricanes, poisons,
cynicism, and liquid nitrogen. Don't touch it, you might break it. Oops,
it's not held down very securely. No, let it break. Okay, so, yeah, how are they breathing?
There's no oxygen on the moon. What's with the chart? I bet it shows how Justin Timberlake
is descended from the moon people. This chart outlines Hugh Bliss's ingenious master
plan to hypnotize everyone on earth through connections with the U.S. government,
the internet, and the toy mafia. Well, that was close. That was a boomer joke.
You're right, I was. I wonder why I didn't know anything about this at the time.
Have you ever been to the moon? Have you ever been to the moon?
So you can't tell me what's there. You don't know what's there. You've just been
shown things on TV. You know what else is shown on TV? Dragons. And fire. Are dragons real?
All right, I'm doing like a moon isn't real thing and I don't really want to be the guy that
says that. The moon banger? What does this thing say?
While I was looking at your beautiful ceiling architecture.
What mafia? Don't try that again. I'll have to get ugly. I guess a lot of people have done it
already. Yes, but I always. Okay. All right, so we got to find a way to get by this.
So he's going to frisk to somehow get that out of here without him frisking us or without
him finding it somehow. Let me look around. There's the lunar lander. This is ours.
No, wait, what? It's a lunar lander. So is my aunt Tilly, but they can't prove anything.
It's a lunar lander. No, that wasn't an undertale reference, guys. Not everything is an
undertale reference. Lovely shirt. Can I get one Sam? Can I, can I, can I, can I?
You don't wear shirts, Max. I can still accumulate them, can't I? One moment,
please. What the hell? I didn't do anything. Okay, go ahead. So we have to get him to run
away somehow. He's going to be like, there's a slightly beat up robotic exoskeleton. I have
to go to the bathroom. They all have to go to the bathroom. We'll just get like the,
give him a soda. He'll just pee. All right. Well, what's going on with you? What's Superball?
Hey, small worlds. It's our favorite cabinet secretary and secret service man, agent Superball.
Favorite? That'd be like choosing a favorite child, Sam. I love them all.
It's Tuesday already?
I do like, I do like the tie.
What's a level red prismatologist? Level red is apex of prismatology, sir. You'd have to
undergo spectrum analysis to determine your current level. Spectrum analysis. Is that where
you lie perfectly still in a lead coffin while brightly colored cotton swabs are inserted
into various orifices? No, sir. We gave it up in 87. It's much simpler now. So let's
try it. What is it? Yep. We're level red. Let us in. I'm sure you're mistaken, but we'll
run the spectrum analysis anyway. Take this. A unicorn? What am I supposed to do with this?
Rub it, sir. Rub it, Sam. Harder. Hard. I'm sorry, sir. The unicorn says you're yellow.
No one calls us yeller. Draw, partner. Level yellow is frankly rather pathetic, sir.
Only level reds may enter the retreat. Regulations? Hmm. However, you bliss would
like to keep the unicorn as a token of his love. Rub it often to measure your progress
towards true bliss. I got paint. Do I still have to get paint? You do that. Okay. How does
the unicorn work? How does that unicorn work, anyway? By magic, sir. Right. Either that or it's
just a glorified mood ring that reacts to body heat. Or that. It's got a heated up ring.
You're not a believer, sir. I could never explain it to you. That works, too. Why are
you studying this prismatology, too? Not studying. I've mastered it. You mastered
prismatology by standing in front of a door? I am one with the door. We exist in the indigo
wavelength of reality. I thought this was a kid's game. The door is an illusion.
So long, Superball. Get out of here. Do I still have paint? So heat. I need to heat this up
so it gets red. We go back to the town, right? Yeah, so let's see if I can heat
this up. What, put it on a grill or something? Go to Bosco's? Earth. It looks cleaner from far away.
That it does. That it does. How does it do that when there's no wind on the moon?
All right, let's head back. I got my item that I need. Come on. Go, go, go.
Where are we headed now, Sam? We are going to the Earth. Terra firma. Does it actually show
you go there? Drive the car in space? No, I was going to say that would be really funny.
All right. Well, what is the final thing that they're doing? Let's check on Sybil.
See, the new is just called Queen. The Canada Leaf? What's with the Canada Leaf? Relax, A.
Okay. Hiya, Sybil. Hello, Sam. Hello, Max. But we prefer to be addressed by our official
title. Is Sybil hearing the voices again? The people, the people. You feeling all right,
Sybil? You bet we are. We just got the best job ever. We are the Queen of Canada. Queen of
Canada. I always thought Rush was the Queen of Canada. How does that work? Queen of Canada?
How'd you land that gig? Did you find half of an old locket dripping with syrup and
bacon grease hinting at a long forgotten lineage? Nothing that interesting, we're afraid.
We answered a classified ad. Yeah, the Canadians are practical that way.
They've been looking for a figurehead to give the country a little bit more class.
They said we were the perfect candidate. Can, L-U-L? That doesn't even work.
There's no like L or O or that's not, that doesn't even connect at all well, even remotely.
But you're not Canadian. How does this work? Heck no, but we took two quarters of French in
college and we spelled, hello, will you? If not knowing how to spell is enough to become royalty,
I could become President of the United States. You are President of the United States, Max.
By God, you're right, Sam. How come I'm not bombing anything right now?
Plus, we were the only candidate. What are your duties here? What kind of stuff does the
Queen of Canada do anyway? It's mostly promotional. We throw out the first puck in
hockey games, that kind of thing. This afternoon, we got to go pose for money. Sam, how come I
don't get to pose for it? We already talked about this, Max. Your gruesome head frightens
shopkeepers and plays havoc with ATMs. Our most important job is to look for ways to
spruce up the country. Well, do you need any help with your monarchy? We could be freelance
Thanks for the offer guys, but we've got things under control for now. You're helping a lot just
by not making any of the obvious Canada jokes. I got one. I got one. That's just not what we're
about. Maple syrup. Am I right? That's pretty good. How can you possibly spruce up Canada?
It's a paradise year round from the fresh air and great seafood of British Columbia
to the bustling metropolises in Ontario and Quebec. You still have that endorsement with
the tourism board? Every little bit helps make ends meet, Max, with the rate you go
through new shoots. How does he do it? I didn't complain when you were teething, Sam.
All right, so. See you later, Your Majesty. Queen of Canada. You may go.
Maple. Maple. Now that one makes sense. Nothing special. Nothing special.
Nothing special. These must be Canadian newspapers. I never realized how boring
newspapers would be without guns. I know this is not the exit. I'm not going to make that
mistake. Can I ever open that? Is it ever not locked? Mapleole. That's fantastic. All right,
let's go see Bosco. Mapleole story. All right, Bosco, what do you got? What hundred billion
dollar item are you going to? Hi, Jimmy. Up to no good as usual, I see. Back off, Buzz. Get
your own meat. I think we already did. The city made us pay for that one when we bent it.
What do you mean we? What do you mean we? What do you mean we? Check the tabloids.
President and assistant. Assistant? Needs Vaseline. Gave 10 community subs.
Thank you for the 10 subs. Needs Vaseline. A lot of subs. Big sub drop. Thank you.
Congratulations to those that got the subs. Okay, do you think I can do 10 claps without
counting them? Hey, Bosco. Oh, dear God. Did I tell you boys not to track mud in the store?
I just vacuumed. Hey, lady. We're looking for Bosco. You know him? Of course. He's my son.
You're your own mother? Is there no escaping these infernal time travel paradoxes?
Hey, guys, it's me, Bosco. We want to buy something. We want to buy something.
Did you finish all your chores? Yes. Why is he pretending to be your mother?
This is not a Russian or a French guy or why is it his mother? Do you have any completed
artificial personality disorder symptoms forms? You do? Wow, that really would have come in handy
earlier. Do you have any video of a chicken eating cow manure for laughs? These are all
things that we have. Do you have any global meatball sandwich positioning systems? These are
all things that exist. You gotta be kidding me. Do you have any three foot by two foot cue
cards that say don't vote for me? What? I can't believe this. Do you have any instant win cheat
codes for reality 2.0? Oh, why didn't we ask before? Do you have Hugh Bliss tied up back
there? Too bad. I was on a roll. Too bad. Well, what do you have? What do you got? Oh,
my little angel made the most precious device. It's called an earthquake maker and it's just what
you think. A diarrhea inducing cocktail? Max, why can't you be more like your brother?
He's not my brother. Sam, I don't want you hanging around with him. He's a bad influence.
That he is, Mama Bosco. That he is. All right, how much is it? Knowing you, Bosco,
I'm sure it's quite reasonable, but how much for this earthquake maker? A hundred trillion
dollars. A hundred trillion? You crazy fool. A hundred trillion. Look man, all I know is I
keep making up the most ridiculous price I can think of and you keep paying it. So I ask you,
who's the fool? Well, with a sales pitch like that, how can we not buy it? Remember,
no earthquake in the house. He's not wrong. A hundred trillion dollars.
Wait, what we can sell things to? You know, Bosco, we've collected some pretty valuable
merchandise on our travels. And we have the sneaking suspicion you've got a little extra
spending money. So how'd you like to buy something from us for a change? Okay,
do you have any copies of the uncensored 1982 Armada Santi lookalike contest on Betamax?
Nope. Oh well, that's the only thing I really need, honey.
Okay, well, what else? Mind telling us how you came to be a woman? Did you use lasers
or just do it the old fashioned way? Are you sassing me? Boy, I will whoop y'all behind so
hard you won't be able to see straight. But I don't see out of my behind. You will after
I get through with you. But why mom? But who in their right mind would dress up as their
own mother? No one. Good point. Look at me when I'm talking to you. Just for that,
I'm not going to tell you why I dressed up as her. Oh, come on, Bosco. We were only-
You just cost yourself dessert, mister. All right, well, see you later, Bosco.
See you later, Bosco's mom. Go clean your office. It's a pig style.
Mama Bosco. Buy the earthquake man. I am gonna and I need to make 100 trillion dollars.
Let me see here. Nacho machine. What can heat this up? Nope.
Cover it in ketchup. That seemed to work before. That's already packed with flavor.
Jerma, clean your office. Actually, it's real bad. Since last night, it's a fucking disaster in here.
It's I mean, there's just cardboard everywhere. Remember I told you I was gonna vacuum?
No, I didn't do it. Do a cleaning stream. I know one way to get-
Oh, here we go. Zap it. Red. Cleaning stream. Just vacuum the ground.
Little horns nice and red. Wow, I can't believe the microwave is a high-level prismatologist.
All right, so we need 100 trillion dollars for Mama Bosco. Anything else in here we can do?
We want to buy something. Give us one earthquake maker, barkeep. That'll be 100 trillion.
If you keep making that face, it's gonna stay that way. But my face is always like this.
See what I mean? Never mind. All right, so we can go in. We're not gonna do it yet. I'm gonna
check a couple places. The chat is overloading with mean power. Overloading. Wait, what's the
gumballs? Well, I'll be. The gumball machine actually contains gumballs. There's actual
gumballs in there. Wee! Oh, let me chew one. Let's go in the office. So we have dart board.
Sophisticated budget allocation system. Hey guys, I'm a memer. Hey guys, I'm a memer.
You forgot to add that part. Did you remember to feed Leonard today, Max? Sure. Let me rephrase that. What have you been
feeding him? You know, bits of string, leftover screws, random scraps of paper I find lying
around the office. This morning I fed him something that said, deed to the United
States of America. It looked tasty. Don't do that again. Why would I ever do that again?
There's no reason for me to do that again. Now all those poor bloggers have
to stand on street corners telling passing strangers what tv shows they like to watch.
Do it again. All right, well, if you're gonna ask me to do it again,
you're gonna pressure me into doing it. Maybe I guess I will. Well, what do you know?
The crucial piece of evidence in the Hudson River Merman Strangler case.
I'll have to remember to file that once we're done with this case.
Don't do it. All right, fine. I won't. If people don't want me to do it, then I just won't.
It's like if people ask me to do something, the viewers, you know,
you guys, I listen to your opinions, so I won't do it. Good for home.
Get rid of a dog and a bunny all quick and subtle like the message.
Okay. Hello, Mr. Pratt. This one's drawn. All right, well, is this gonna hurt me?
Hello. Sybil must have a cold or something.
No kidding. Did she say she thought she was a jar of spaghetti sauce?
This game really has kind of dialed it up a little here.
Rig the answering machine to shock them when they play the third message.
And didn't I just do that, though?
This is the third message.
That's the third message. Why didn't I get electrocuted?
Hello, Wanda. Sell. Sell. I didn't know you had a stockbroker.
That's the Sunflower Scout troop I'm sponsoring.
Oh, it was shopping. I get it.
Okay. I thought I was going to get electrocuted.
Anybody home?
All right. Well, let's just go back so we can get entrance to the Prisma Zone.
I didn't get it either. So, see? With a little sad face.
Where are we headed now, Sam?
Back to the moon.
To the moon, Alice.
Okay. So let's go bring the unicorn.
Footprint. What's that?
Somebody left a footprint here in the dust.
My foot's bigger.
No, it's not.
That looks like my feet with a shoe on.
All right. Let's get access here.
Hello, Superball.
Let us in.
Have you achieved level red yet?
Yes.
I'm utterly flabbergasted, sir.
I'd suspect a trick, but surely no level red Prismatologist would stoop so low.
We never stoop. We're posture freaks.
Enjoy the retreat, brothers.
All right. Up or down?
Who's going to go up or down?
Oh, we don't even get to see.
Sam! Sam! There he is! It's Hugh Bliss!
Hi. I'm Hugh Bliss.
Hi, Hugh Bliss.
Jesus.
I so hope you're enjoying my blister of tranquility.
You're all making such great progress unlocking the secrets of Prismatology,
and I couldn't be more delighted.
Neither could I.
Cool it, Max. You're scaring me more than usual.
I have splendid news.
My top-secret plan to hypnotize the entire world is nearly complete.
Soon, everyone on Earth will become one of us. None shall escape.
It'll be fabulous.
You're a good man.
Keep up the great work, everyone.
I'm Tickled Pink! Ha ha! An entire planet of Prismatologists!
It's like a dream!
It's a sour dream where you wake up screaming with a gun in your hand,
your pillow torn to shreds, and the upstairs neighbors calling 9-1-1.
That's right! The best kind!
P.S. Please don't come into my inner sanctum.
Thank you!
Well, here we go.
We have a very large area here.
Giant spork, statue, Lincoln, water cooler.
And this is our water cooler.
So this is where you've been.
We were worried sick.
Oh.
Couldn't you at least have left a note?
Sorry, Sam. He sent us an email.
I meant to tell you.
Tell a water cooler joke? I don't have any.
Look, Max. It's the giant stone head of your old opponent, Abraham Lincoln.
Welcome, brethren, to the blister of...
Oh, it's you two.
Not so tough without your fancy giant robot body, are you?
I can still bite off your fluffy little...
I mean...
Let me help you, brother, to overcome the orange of confrontation
and bathe in the yellow of peace and brotherhood.
Bathe in the yellow?
Just what kind of camp is this?
Okay, is prismatology helping you?
Is prismatology teaching you anything?
I'm working to master the miraculous power of gastrocinesis.
You can teleport human dictators?
No, he's talking about farting.
But now I'm working on gastrocinesis,
the ability to make anyone throw up with my mind.
Max and I are always looking for new ways to make people throw up.
Teach us.
As it is now, I can make people vomit with every part of my body except my mind.
Well, if you are a true prismatologist,
I suppose I'm obliged to help you.
But there's a problem.
I accidentally swallowed the gastrocinesis talisman.
Sam, is that ironic or sarcastic?
It's pretty damned inconvenient.
Throw up that talisman.
Can't you make yourself throw up the gastrocinesis talisman?
With gastrocinesis?
I haven't thrown up since 1863, right after I gave the Gettysburg address.
I was kind of nervous that day.
I didn't have anything prepared.
So long, Mr. Lincoln.
So we have to make Lincoln throw up.
And we do that not exactly sure how.
Is the rainbow supposed to be going in or coming out?
I think it depends on which way you're facing.
All right, spork, statue.
I never understand modern art.
I think that's the biggest, meanest-looking spork I ever saw outside of Chicago.
Okay.
This place is kind of freaking me out, though.
This is like the weirdest portion of the game.
You must be at least this tall to ride this ride.
Fascist oppressors.
All right.
It goes around through his mouth, right?
What does it end up?
All right, so Max, get in there.
Please keep your arms and legs in the ride at all times.
So here we go.
Did he take a photo of you?
That's a source engine door.
Yeah.
So we're gonna have to do something with that.
Whatever that is.
I'm not sure.
I've never seen ants meditating before.
I think this is a pool of artificially flavored fruit punch.
No cult should be without one.
All right, the chicken.
I'm beginning to think we already know everyone on the moon.
How are you, Mr. Featherly?
Oh, for heaven's sake.
My name is not Featherly.
It's Philo Pennyworth.
It's the guy that eats featherly.
It's the name of my former television character.
Have you no ability to distinguish between fantasy and reality?
Well, what's so important about that anyway?
Um, why Prismatology?
How did you happen to get into Prismatology?
You don't seem like the type.
It's an excellent networking opportunity for an actor.
Yes, this place appears to be littered with Hollywood luminaries.
Ordinarily, it is.
I believe there's a party at Kevin Bacon's home this evening.
So naturally, everyone is there.
Kevin Bacon's a Prismatologist?
Add it to the wiki.
How's the show doing?
How's Midtown Cowboys doing these days?
You mean you don't even know?
The show was canceled almost immediately after your first and only appearance.
All that flap over the tabloid photos of you two with that alien
brought the censors down on us.
That was no alien.
It was Hugh Bliss.
The show was ruined and my career along with it.
Okay, we've got a president right here.
President now.
I'm going to pretend I didn't hear that.
All right, what's with the hat?
What's with the hat?
I'm pursuing new opportunities in the entertainment field.
Can you make what are you pulling rabbits out of it?
Rats.
Or at least I'm trying to.
Rat.
What the hell was that?
I gather the rat out of the hat trick isn't going so well.
The principles involved are quite simple.
I could even teach them to adult like you.
Now hold on a minute.
But I'm having trouble getting the rat all the way out.
It appears to be stuck.
How long has the rat been stuck in the hat?
You misunderstand.
The rat is not actually in the hat.
It's stuck somewhere else.
The hat is acting as a dimensional portal to wherever the rat happens to be.
Wow.
Is it magic or science?
Oh wait, is there really any difference?
He's holding on to the...
Okay, so that...
I gotta get him off the meter.
Would you teach me how to pull a rat out of a hat?
Prismatology instructs us to shoot.
The rat on the meter.
But I've simply got to perform the trick successfully myself first.
I can't have you scooping me.
No, I guess not.
Okay.
Catch you later feather.
So what are we...
Pennyworth.
Things to do, right?
My name is Pennyworth.
Get a task list here.
Make President Lincoln throw up.
Get the rat off of the meter.
That's two tasks.
How to get rat off meter.
Well, here's Shark.
Here are the computers.
What are you doing here?
Hey, Max.
Is that our bug?
He's still got it.
Thank you.
You're a prismatologist too?
Yes, I am.
I'm so happy I could view rainbows.
Rainbows!
We'll just keep our distance then.
Are you actually going to puke?
Hi, what is this game?
This is Sam and Max.
They have sharks in the blister of train party.
Season one is the last episode.
All devoted practitioners are welcome.
Of season one.
There are two more seasons after this.
We're just cleaning up season one.
Look, Max.
It's our obsolete computer pals.
The cops.
They don't sound very happy.
It's so much louder than everybody else.
You destroyed reality 2.0.
Destroy!
Remember to adopt a more positive attitude now.
Are you going to do season two and season three?
Probably.
Okay, these games are really fun to just chill and hang out and play.
So they're very relaxing.
They're fun.
It's fun to hang out and just chill with chat and play a game.
And they do that very, very well.
Do the motivational song.
I do.
I really have to click this.
I guess I do.
Let's hear that motivational song.
Might as well listen to it.
Why, Sam?
Why?
I didn't tell you for how long.
And this has taught us we no longer need self-hyphen reinforcement.
We have look inside ourselves.
And we totally rock.
They don't need to do that anymore.
Sorry, guys.
I tried.
During what I saw in season one, episode five, six.
Is prismatology teaching you anything?
That one's my favorite.
It sounds like he's always cursing.
That is because he is.
We're learning the most powerful skill of them all to become the MP.
All right.
So what's their shtick?
What are your computers doing?
Puke, magic, and what?
Prismatology has restored our sense of purpose.
After you destroyed reality 2.0, we banded together to make a newer, even better game.
Coming soon.
And we'll rock your world.
You came to a private retreat on the moon to work on something as
insubstantial as a video game?
Not just any game.
We are creating the most advanced AI in history.
In a world where two forces battle for domination of a war-torn landscape,
only one will draw the line and reign supreme.
Do you get to shoot stuff?
It's not a good game until you get to shoot stuff.
Thank you for your feedback.
We will incorporate shooting into version 2.0.
Can we try it?
Okay, Max and I will try out this video game of yours.
Prepare to suffer extreme humiliation.
The year is 2048.
In a post-apocalyptic galaxy run by giant corporations,
you are a cybernetically-enhanced space marine with no memory of his past.
We actually have to play this?
Are you the chosen one, Fontole, by prophecy?
Do you have the strength to survive?
Tick-tack-toe!
Oh, no.
Shit.
I have to play Tick-Tack-toe?
I'm so bad at Tick-Tack-toe.
You've played against me before as a whole collective chat.
Fear me!
I'm not very good.
I am invincible!
I won.
You cannot defeat me!
Actually, I just kind of did.
Yeah, Roar.
Your calculations, your chances of winning were one in ten trillion.
The sun was in my eyes!
Thank you for playing Tick-Tack-Doom.
We'll continue to look within ourselves and improve our award-winning AI
to make it even more challenging.
It was too short and not hard enough.
I want my money back!
Please check again later.
What's the point of doing that, though?
Hmm.
There has to be a reason to do that.
All right.
Anyways, I've got anything else in here.
I've got to get the rat off the parking meter.
That's priority number one.
Shades of Albert Hoffman.
Is he the fat one?
I love that show!
Okay.
Let's go back down.
See if I can get the rat off.
What is this?
Oh, okay.
This is what's inside that door.
That's certainly an important looking door.
I wonder what's behind it.
Something really secret or something really ugly, I'm guessing.
Or a really ugly sanctum, right?
One can only hope.
Looks pretty intimidating.
True.
But only in an inanimate object kind of way.
So how do I...
I wonder how I get through that door eventually.
I probably have to pretend to be Hugh Bliss or something.
Menacing.
How long have I been live?
Why wasn't I warned?
I drunkenly said last night that I wasn't going to stream until Tuesday.
But I woke up and I was all right.
So I'm probably going to stream until Tuesday.
Where are we headed now, Sam?
Home.
But I got stuff to do tomorrow.
So that was why I said that if I woke up
all messed up and feel like shit this morning,
this afternoon, I probably wouldn't be able to.
But hey, we're here.
All right.
Let's get the rat off of the parking meter.
How do we do that?
Since Max and I never pay for parking anyway.
Those things just get in the way.
Just shoot it.
Can I just shoot him off?
Scare him?
Better not.
So what's his deal?
That meter's been out of order for years.
Just because it ain't white.
That don't mean people don't put money in it.
It's like an HMO.
Money.
So give it up, Jimmy.
Give it up, Jimmy.
Okay.
Money.
Hey, Jimmy.
Want to touch my unicorn?
No, just touch it.
What did I miss?
Anything in here?
I need money.
I need like coins or.
Hey, scratch and sniff lottery tickets.
Can I have one?
Chimps.
80% crushed.
How do I make him puke?
How do I make Lincoln puke?
A hundred trillion dollars.
Sybil?
Maybe Sybil has something to do.
Sybil just kind of said,
I'm the queen of Canada.
And that was it.
All right, Sybil.
Let's talk about this.
What do you think?
What do you think of this?
Hey, Sybil.
Want to rub my unicorn?
We have people who do that sort of thing for us now.
Hi, you, Sybil.
And L-U-O.
Okay.
If you're queen of Canada.
How come you're still down here in the States?
Are you kidding?
It's freezing up there.
We love our country,
but we've got to draw the line somewhere.
Okay.
Have you come up with any brilliant ideas
for improving Canada?
Nothing solid yet.
We've thought of a new slogan.
Canada.
It's surprisingly pleasant.
But we need something bigger.
Bigger.
Something to really put us on the map.
Something daring.
Brilliant ideas for improving Canada.
Nothing solid yet.
We've thought of a new slogan.
Canada.
We need a better Canadian slogan.
But we need something bigger.
Okay.
See you later.
Hmm.
A lot of open books that I can't close right now.
Show the unicorn?
I just, I tried to show the unicorn.
She just said no.
So we need a new Canadian slogan.
Abraham Lincoln Puke.
Rat off of a parking van.
Maybe like bring Abraham Lincoln like old nachos?
Wait, wait, wait.
What about in here?
This place should be open.
Is that a cat tray full of kitty litter?
Lefties is empty again.
No.
Except for the lingering stench, of course.
Let's go back to Bosco's.
Come on, Max.
Hurry up.
Yeah, that's what I was thinking.
Bring him like old gross nachos
or like a rotten hot dog.
I could use a hint.
Help me out with something.
Sure.
Um.
We can just get hints.
I won at Tic Tac Doom, but it didn't do any good.
Winning isn't everything, Sam.
Okay.
Never mind.
What about, what do you, you want to see this?
Hey Bosco, want to rub my unicorn?
I'm not that kind of woman.
Alright, so don't win in Tic Tac Toe.
Let's try it.
Let's try losing.
So my confidence is gone
because I thought I just beat the computer.
Turns out you're not supposed to beat the computer.
Where are we headed now, Sam?
Let's go lose.
To the moon, Alice.
Where's the lava?
Did it last night.
It's already done.
Should be an eight-hour vaude for you from last night.
Alright, let's go.
He ate it.
Eight hours for a four-hour total build.
That was actually a five-hour total build.
But drinking a bottle of wine
and talking about like VR and
if I sat there, it's quiet.
I could have probably done it in fucking three hours.
It's the experience.
Lava is my favorite game, okay?
Don't take that from me.
That don't, let me have that one.
That's my favorite thing.
Okay, let's lose Tic Tac Toe.
We'd like to try out that video game of yours again.
The box says one hour.
No, it does not.
It actually says 180 minutes.
The headset is 30 to 60 and the blaster is 180.
You do the math.
Alright, can you beat me?
He can't win.
No, I don't want to win.
I have to try to lose.
I lose, I lose.
That's it.
No, it doesn't matter.
I still lose.
Yeah, I lose.
Oh, darn.
You beat me fair and square.
Good game.
I totally beat you guys.
Our journey of personal awareness is now complete.
Now what?
We have mastered the most advanced artificial intelligence ever created.
You suck so bad, lol.
Let me try, Sam.
I know I can take him.
As super sophisticated AI entity.
Brother, speak so that the primitive machines may understand.
Of course.
During the Mordhau stream, I looked over and definitely saw that at least 10 times.
Hey, can we take this?
You've won free tickets to self-awareness.
You suck so bad.
The effects are limited to those of plumbiest composition.
It would have been better.
The amazing ability to see through lead may be inappropriate for some viewers.
It would have been better if the computer thing said,
how can you be this bad?
See, that went a lot too.
How is it possible to be this bad?
If you said that, it would have been great.
All right, so now I have the lead vision talisman.
A classic Twitch chat comment.
All right, let me see.
Hello, Mr. Rail-Splitter-Head.
So long, Mr. Link.
Nothing happened.
So I've got this eye.
Lead eye.
Is it like a scanner on a door or a scanner thing or something?
I have to hold the eye up?
What about the head?
No, that makes sense, wouldn't it?
You suck so bad.
Hmm, watch out.
It's going to scan the eye.
Neat.
Can we go in?
Hmm.
Wait, wait, wait, wait.
What the hell is that?
Neat.
Open.
There's a bowling ball.
Hey, I think that's my bowling ball.
That's my bowling ball.
So, what, do I have to drop the bowling ball?
Neat.
So, intimidating door.
Bowling ball.
Probably the earthquake.
Get the earthquake gun and have the earthquake go.
I need the earthquake gun.
What do I get?
A hundred trillion dollars.
Never mind.
I have to make him throw up that talisman.
No, I can't shoot it.
Can I?
I don't think I can shoot through the door.
Neat.
Yes, that's definitely Lou, all right.
That's definitely Lou.
Neat.
That's definitely Lou, all right.
Lou.
Did you do anything?
Hello, sir.
Don't bug me.
All right, what about the...
Okay, giant spork.
Can I grab this?
Can I take this?
Can I have this?
I think that's the biggest, meanest-looking spork I ever saw outside of Chicago.
All right, let's get back out here.
I need...
That was also the spoon that I just steal.
Harry, can I...
See you later.
Great!
I don't have anything to stop him.
Can I just...
Can I put lead in his face?
Nothing happened.
It really should work on securing this thing better.
One moment, please.
He keeps trying to walk out.
I have no idea how that keeps winding up in there.
Don't get cute.
I can't just walk out?
Too late.
What, you're telling me I just can't just slide like a DVD player into my pants and walk out?
Why not?
It really should work on securing this thing better.
Hilarious as it would be to mix up the displays.
Mix up the displays.
Like what?
Shut up, long head.
Can I like throw it?
What if I just turn and just fucking baseball through it into the space?
I'll need to get the case off at first.
Yeah, like throw it.
One moment, please.
I have no idea how that keeps winding up in there.
Don't get cute.
Too late.
Okay, what if I hand it back to him?
Someone tried to steal this.
It really should work on securing this thing better.
One moment, please.
I have no idea.
Too late.
Hold on, wait.
It really should work on securing this thing better.
Here, Max, hold this.
I meant in your hands.
Oh, he can eat it.
Whatever.
All right, we got it.
One moment, please.
Okay, go ahead.
All right, now spit it up.
Could I have that display case you ate?
Can you wait 12 to 72 hours?
72 hours?
That's some slow ass metabolism.
All right, yeah, now, now, hold on, hold on, hold on, hold on, hold on.
How fast do you digest metal?
Hello, Mr. Rail-Splitter-Head.
Can't you make yourself throw up the gastrocinesis talisman?
I haven't thrown up since 1863.
After I gave the Gettysburg Address.
I was kind of nervous that day.
I didn't have anything prepared.
What if I get the Gettysburg Address?
You're not still bitter about the election, are you?
Or your public humiliation?
Or the cruise missile that blew your body to tiny wig bits?
I can't, am I gonna hold it up in front of him?
No, being president is for chumps.
Only a grade A sociopathic masochist would want that thankless job.
Grade A?
I'm flattered.
Why the long marble face?
Because you two made me lose something more valuable than an election.
My one chance at true love.
This is all happening so fast.
I don't know what to say.
Not you, moron.
I'm talking about that radiant vision of beauty you had interrupt my family values speech.
You mean Sibyl?
Is that her name?
Sibyl.
It's like a chorus of angels.
I'm doing like a rap song.
Doing like a lot of raps out.
They just, somebody else will say the lines too.
For like one line in the beginning.
There'll be a verse and then somebody will just like say two lines with them and then
two lines at the end.
Or they'll do it again over the same track.
It's called accenting.
Yeah, that's what I'm just doing.
Aren't you married?
What about Mary, your mannish but devoted wife?
Why don't you find a nice giant statue of her?
Settle down and start cranking out little bouncing baby war memorials.
There are none left.
Lady Bird Johnson had all graven images of former first ladies destroyed during the great
enlightenment of 1963.
Okay.
We can give you Sibyl's phone number so you can set up a date.
I haven't dated in over 150 years.
I wouldn't know what to say.
Phone, Max.
Are we doing this right now?
If you'd like to make a love connection, press or say hell yeah now.
Just follow my lead, miss.
Can't answer that.
Hello?
Hi, it's Abraham Lincoln.
Wait, don't hang up.
I got needs, baby.
Lincoln and Sibyl ecstasy.
I'm issuing a romance.
But what?
Wait, Lincoln plus Sibyl equals ecstasy.
You know chemistry because I'm having an explosive reaction.
The formula, Lincoln plus Sibyl equals ecstasy.
Why are we doing this?
Okay, we'll do this again.
Let's try calling Sibyl again.
Hi, it's Abe again.
Uh, all right.
I guess, how about this one?
I am issuing you a Romancipation Proclamation.
Let's set aside our differences and commence on the reconstruction.
Fuck.
Canadian, right?
Let's try calling Sibyl again.
We have to do something Canada related.
It's Abe again.
Just relax, baby.
Think positive and Lincoln gonna make it all better.
Proper relaxation.
Girl, you got the curves like a racetrack.
Lady, you a stone cold fox.
You're almost as hot as your sister.
Honest, you're really hot.
I can't wait to go on double dates with you and your sister.
Why did he say it like that?
Hello, the rest of this conversation has been blocked by CC regulation.
Let's try calling Sibyl again.
Hi.
No, fuck, wrong one.
Recon.
Let's try calling Sibyl again.
Keep calling back over and over again.
Hi.
Relax.
Just relax.
Okay, you got curves like a racetrack.
You a stone cold fox.
None of these have anything to do with Canada.
Woman, you got a body that just won't quit.
That may have worked in the 18, but you know me.
Let's try calling Sibyl again.
Yeah, this is getting a little ridiculous.
Hi, it's Abe again.
Hi, it's me again.
I've called you nine times.
Just relax, baby.
Think positive.
Okay, you got curves like a racetrack.
Girl, you got tighter curves than a NASCAR track.
What?
Yeah, NASCAR is not Canadian.
Let's try calling Sibyl again.
Hello?
Hi.
Just.
Lady, you a stone cold fox.
It has to be this one.
All right.
Damn.
What do you want to do?
Start our own alien love triangle.
Tattoo my head all over your body.
Play some one-on-one love hockey.
There it is.
I figure we watch a hockey game.
Have a couple of beers.
Get some poutine.
You know, the usual.
Oh, Abe, I'm over the top.
What?
Did he actually say yes?
Hello, you just totally scored.
Congratulations, Mr. Lincoln.
Oh, my gosh.
What if she wants to get serious?
I can't do this.
I'm so nervous.
I've got butterflies.
I have to ask.
Where?
Stand back, Max.
Wherever they are, I have a feeling
they're coming back up.
He's going to puke.
Oh, I don't feel so good.
What if she and I can't hear you?
Oh, man.
And here I thought our trip to the moon
was going to be boring.
Max, be a sport and pick that up for me.
Not a chance.
He just puked up somebody puking.
Can I take this?
I'm not sure why you'd want to use
the power of prismatology to make people throw up.
But go ahead.
I've got more important things to worry about.
It's interesting.
Oh, we just had a guy throw up a talisman
of somebody throwing up so I can show it to Max
to make him throw up the spoon.
Interesting.
OK.
Hey, it's that display case.
Thanks, little pal.
Zoomed out for that.
I was saving that.
For what?
It's complicated.
But it has to do with my personal vendetta
against a certain major coffeehouse chain.
So can I make anyone,
can I make everybody throw up?
How do I, I need to break this.
Can I break it?
Throw it in here?
I'll need to get the case off at first.
All right.
Well, let's go make the chicken throw up.
Might as well make everybody puke.
We might get something.
I'm not particularly interested in seeing
the contents of his stomach.
Oh, that's too bad.
OK, so now I have the display case.
I need to get the case off.
I'll need to get the case off at first.
Can I just break it?
You've thrown up.
I think it only works on things with stomachs.
Wait, can I, can I make myself puke?
I can't shoot it.
Well, let's go see if we can make anybody else throw up.
Like you, for instance.
I'm not particularly interested
in seeing the contents of his stomach.
OK, what about you?
I'm not particularly.
I need to break this case open.
Can I stomp on it?
Crush it?
I'll need to get the case off at first.
It's pretty skinky.
I think I'll just leave it alone forever.
I need a battery.
Can I, wait, wait, wait, wait.
I can't break it on the spork,
but maybe can I break and I make it.
I'll need to get the case off at first.
Damn it.
Really?
I'll need to get the case.
I'll need to get the case off it.
And there's the bowling ball too.
Can I just have Abe crush it with his teeth?
I just need to drop it.
Drop it out the window?
Just drop it out the window over the office
and it'll just break?
Makes sense.
That's quite a rocket engine.
Can I turn this on?
Lunar lander.
Who is this?
Really?
That seems way too over the top to work.
Why would I just drop it?
It's a lunar lander.
It's a cartoon.
Yeah, I know, but I mean.
Wait, I can go up here.
Hey, the keys are locked inside.
So many of us are like that.
God damn it.
Really?
How do I get in there?
Hmm, nothing happened.
Come on, this ain't made out of lead?
The keys are locked inside.
Damn.
Okay, I have to get in there somehow.
I can't like bust out the window.
Shit.
Ah, I can't.
When I go up here, it goes up and the keys are locked inside.
I don't need like a coat hanger.
There's a coat hanger in the office always.
Where are we headed now, Sam?
I'm going to get a coat hanger.
Eris is one in the TV always.
Perfect co-op Jupiter.
There it is.
Sam, without that, we can't watch Colonel Mudshank's monkey party tonight.
They were going to vote somebody out of the monkey house.
It's for the good of the planet.
And besides, you had Colonel Mudshank's exile for treason, remember?
All right, let's get in there.
Open it up.
Keys.
You crack me up, little buddy.
Where are we headed now, Sam?
To the moon.
To the moon, Alice.
You crack me up, little buddy.
Okay.
Coat hanger.
Lander door.
Unlock.
Grab key.
Turn on.
Get spoon.
And then I have no idea what to do after that.
But we're going to do it really relaxed.
We're going to hang out and have fun.
Where do we go?
Are we going to a new place?
Oh, he's dead.
I think the controls don't work how they're supposed to.
Spoon.
All right, so now I've got the spoon.
For which...
What can I do?
Looks like that rocket melted the virtually indestructible case.
Bend the spoon and then...
Did the peanut butter on the spoon survive?
Sorry, little pal.
So use the spoon on the big spoon and bend it for some reason.
I mean, that's very clearly just a please come over here and use this item on me.
Giant spoon.
Here we go.
All right, now that's going to...
We're going to crash into when we're on the roller coaster.
So turn on the roller coaster and have the car crash.
Should we be in it?
Am I going to get a game over?
Should I save the game?
We're going to die.
Oh, what?
What?
What did that do?
What was the purpose of bending the spoon?
I think that's the biggest meanest...
Can I go the other way?
No.
I wonder if I can maybe turn the...
Maybe have it...
No.
It's going to keep it bent.
Okay.
So now I should be able to go up here.
Was there anything else that was bendable?
This is definitely bendable.
Neat.
Cool.
But I hope it didn't hurt the bowling ball.
There he is.
He is.
Jigs up, you bless.
We've come a long way for this, my friend.
So buckle up.
Because the freelance police are taking you downtown.
Hi, I'm Hugh Bliss.
He is.
You're just in time for the show.
Please, no flash photography.
Ahem.
People of Earth...
He's in the moon.
Hi, I'm Hugh Bliss.
And now, so are you.
Oh, shit.
You opened up the portal to Tristram.
You better go in there and save Deckard Cain while there's still time.
What have you done?
Oh, just enlisted a few billion followers.
Touch me and you'll have quite a happy, angry mob on your hands.
Not if we...
Reverse the effects of the Hypnobeam?
I don't think so.
For in all the universe there's only one force chaotic and destructive enough to stop me now.
But you wouldn't do that, would you, Max?
Who, me?
Well, I'm flattered, but...
No, you wouldn't.
Because I'm going to...
Drumroll, please.
Really?
What does that even mean?
It means I chop off every part of you I don't like.
It's like circumcision, but double the laps.
Hey!
Wait, what?
Here we go.
Goodbye, murderous hand.
Goodbye, gluttonous stomach.
Goodbye, slothful tail.
This is...
And with those naughty body parts, your vices are purged from your soul.
Bye-bye.
Jerkbag, I'm gonna use it to shoot you all!
Oh boy, a stomach!
Just what I always wanted.
Now come here and let me eat you.
Great, a tail.
I just want to lie in front of a TV until I die in a pool of my own slobber.
Is that a movie?
What's the movie?
Up? No.
What's it called?
The movie with the emotions?
Go away, rotten maxes.
I don't like you.
Inside out.
Now nothing can stop me.
I win!
Okay, bye now.
Yes, my children.
Let me soak in your happiness.
Oh, yes.
Mmm, more.
So good.
Oh, oh my.
So happy.
Max, are you okay?
Help me grab that ponytail freak show and reverse the effects of the beam.
But Sam, I love that ponytail freak show.
I want to have his love child.
No!
Bad end.
I swear to you, I'll get your vices back or kill us both trying.
I love you too.
Well, okay.
He still has fun doing that.
All right, we've got public address microphone.
The view screen.
I can see the retreat from here.
Apparently Mr. Mind reader has to keep tabs on his followers the old-fashioned way.
What?
Nothing.
Wait, what?
These crystals must operate something important.
No, I just think they look pretty.
A bit cliche if you ask me.
What?
Nothing.
People have earned working as hard as I can to break the spell and make you all miserable again.
Wait, where's my bug?
Can I get him to save anything?
Lunar lander key spoon.
Wait, it's worth a shot.
Can I turn these off?
Someone around here has got an incurable case of narcissism.
What?
Nothing.
Unfortunately, they appear to be quite indestructible.
Protected by magic.
All right, so it turns out I can't do anything about that.
I'm going to have to eventually come near and turn this off.
Anything else that I missed over here?
Statues, the view screen, I think that's it.
Let's just get out.
Fixed max.
Is everybody here all screwed up?
Get him in the...
Okay, get him inside the roller coaster car.
Come here.
Get in here.
Look at this now.
Violence is the bugaboo of a small imagination.
You'll have to pry this hand from my cold dead fingers!
Eat the fiery lead of my inalienable freedoms!
Not a very good shot.
All right, let's go.
We're going to go over...
Goodie! Moving target!
No, we can't get over there.
Wait, I can't like press the button?
Goodie! Move...
No.
So we have to make somebody run around.
Maybe I can tell Max to run around?
Dang it!
Darn!
He's bulletproof!
We both suck.
Hold on.
Can I do it from here?
Yes!
He's gonna get hit in the face by the spoon!
Wait, it's not bent!
What?
I bent it before!
Did you have fun?
I thought that...
I bet...
I didn't think I had to re-bend the spoon.
I bent it before I went up to talk to Hugh Bliss.
You suck so bad, Ella.
Dammit.
I can't see it from here.
And then you unbent it.
No, I bent it back though.
No, check the bot.
I bent it back.
I've got people that can vouch for that.
I did bend it back.
Check the bot.
I did.
I did bend it back.
Wait, where is he?
Why is he not in there?
Wait, I gotta wait for him to go...
Just go back in!
I gotta wait till he jumps in.
Do it now!
Come on, shoot it now!
Go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go!
Oh, we get to win.
Here we go.
Closed line incoming.
Three, two, one.
Oh, it's the hand.
That's what we needed.
Does he die?
Okay, so we've got...
Let's go out here.
See what's going on outside.
That's...
We have one of the three pieces we need of Max.
Before collapsing under the weight of his own laziness.
Anhui is one of the five fundamental forces.
He made it 20 feet.
No TV.
Why even go on?
You should all just lie on your faces and wait for death.
It's true.
I got nothing.
I'm a failure.
I thought people were supposed to be happy out here.
I don't want the verge of tears.
This guy's the death of the party.
What if it happened to people having a good time?
Hey, pseudo Max.
How's it going?
I need your tail for my little buddy here.
How about handing it over?
He's heavier than he looks.
Aren't we all?
Aren't we on the moon?
Wouldn't being on the moon make him lighter?
I'm not particularly interested in seeing the...
I don't think it works on people.
Except maybe if they're shaped like spoons.
Okay.
You have anything to say?
Howdy, Superball.
I can't talk now, sir.
The blue guy is really getting me down.
His supernatural lethargy is crushing my normally unbridled enthusiasm.
But Superball, you seem as chipper as ever.
Thank you, sir.
I work hard to put on a happy face, but I'm crying on the inside.
What about you?
Hi, Harry.
The blue rabbit's right.
I can't keep a job if my feet stink.
Why do I even go on?
Come now, Harry.
Give us a little smile.
Leave me alone.
I don't like this part turned it off.
Well, I can't turn it off.
All right.
Let's go.
Wait.
Can I put the bunny underneath here?
Can I slide him over here?
Eris.
No, no, no, no, no, no.
I'm just saying.
Like he's lying on the ground.
Maybe that'll make him get up.
I'll tell you what I mean.
Well, I'll show you something here.
We finally get to bend it.
Yes.
All right.
Now we can pull them out of the hat.
And I never pay for parking anyway.
That thing's been bent for a whole season.
I'm so glad to finally fix it.
Okay.
Holy heaping helpings of high fructose corn syrup.
He's eating everything inside.
Everything.
Bosco, do not freak out.
Attaboy.
Eat up so you'll grow big and strong.
What is the world coming to?
Bosco, pasta knobs.
I'll four.
Oh, my, that one does have an appetite.
At the rate he's going, his stomach won't even fit back inside you.
I've no need for my earthly stomach any longer, sir.
I'm on Pupus's handsomest of lemon, water, and sunshine.
As God is my witness, by the end of this day,
you will be eating cocoa nougat butterballs again.
Nougat really is so good.
It's so great.
All right.
So, uh, get him to...
We've got...
What does he say?
Excuse me, Mr. Vice Manifestation.
You look delicious.
Look, pal.
I need your stomach so I can put my buddy back together.
Hand it over and only one of us gets hurt.
I can't resist the rich, meaty taste of dog and rabbit.
Well, here we are in your stomach.
What?
What the hell did I just step in?
I'm enjoying the womb-like meditative quality of the pyloric sphincter.
Darn it.
Well, I've still got my magic, too, Hickey.
Something tells me I'm going to be smelling that for the rest of my life.
Well, that was, uh, disgusting.
We do it again.
It's beautiful.
Turn this off.
Um, okay.
So, hmm.
I wonder, can I do anything else?
Sludgey's.
This week's flavors?
Casper oil and Brussels sprouts.
Oh.
So we're...
Okay, we have to cover ourselves in something.
Has to be.
We have to cover ourselves in something he doesn't like.
Roast coffee?
I don't know what we're doing.
Somehow we have to make him eat us again, but this time with the coating he doesn't like.
I'm impressed by the gentle oscillation of the hot weenies.
Yep.
Still a garbage can.
I can't take the weenies.
Can I bend his stomach around?
No.
Well, I do...
I can go do the rabbit in the hat thing.
Because the rat is off.
I mean, the chicken...
The arc of the chicken can finally be concluded.
What about Sybil?
We're here.
Might as well just see.
Okay.
What's new?
Are you okay?
Hugh Bliss shot some kind of weird energy beam all over the planet.
Hi, I'm Hugh Bliss.
Oh, no.
And I'm perfectly happy, Sam.
Oh, and hello, brother Max.
Tangerine dreams and aqua wishes to you this day.
Why, thank you, Sybil.
You're looking especially lovely today.
This is horrific.
How will you improve Canada?
Let's really get to the hard-hitting issues here.
You've got to snap out of it.
Snap out of what, friend Sam?
For the first time in my life, I've got a perfect job,
a rock-solid relationship,
and an incomparable feeling of peace.
I've never been so content in all my life.
Don't worry, we'll fix that.
Prismatology is a sham.
This prismatology business is all a lie.
Is pure happiness a lie?
Is peace on Earth a hopeless dream?
Are unicorns imaginary?
Mostly, probably, and it depends on-
Whoa, what the fuck?
From a facility that processes nuclear waste.
All right, how's the date going with Lincoln?
How's things going with you and Mr. Lincoln?
Simply wonderful.
Isn't that right, Abraham?
Pretty lady.
He has such a way with words.
Why is he like this now?
Why is he doing this?
Why is he like this?
It sounds like Mr.
Look at me, I wrote the Gettysburg address.
Isn't as good with words as he led us to believe.
Oh, he'll be fine once he's managed to stop hyperventilating.
Are you two planning on having kids someday?
So long, Sybil.
What's up, A.L.?
How's the date going?
Oh, thank goodness you two have come.
Now we can talk.
Well, hello, Mr. Lincoln.
You're looking quite distinguished today.
What's wrong with him?
He hasn't been himself lately.
Whatever.
You've got to help me with this date.
The honeymoon's already over?
What's the problem?
She's really into me.
See there, Abraham?
That's the problem.
Oh, the Turk was a little bit of courage.
No, I mean really into me.
She's so nice.
It's giving me the creeps.
I thought you'd be used to blissed out people
after spending so much time at the moon retreat.
Sure, when you're around a bunch of other single guys,
that's one thing.
But this, what do I do if she wants to get intimate?
I'm not cut out for this.
There, there, Abraham.
That's just the yellow of your cowardice speaking.
Seriously, how long is he going to be like this?
I'm working on it.
How did you avoid getting hit by Hugh Bliss's
mind-altering happiness ray?
I miss the great blissification?
Dammit, I knew I shouldn't have stopped
by the gift shop on the way down here.
Anything else?
Do you know how to stop Hugh Bliss's
world domination scheme?
Why would I want to stop it?
Under Hugh Bliss, all men are created equal.
That's kind of my thing.
You and Sybil should think about starting a family.
This is all happening too fast.
It's been over a hundred years.
My stomach's doing backflips.
I don't know what women like.
Women like to be treated as equal partners
in love and trust, a foundation of honesty.
Seriously, make him stop talking.
I'm nauseated enough as it is.
Anything else?
You're ever the romantic, Mr. Lincoln.
Lucky at uniting a nation on the brink of war.
Unlucky in love.
You're ever the romantic.
Anything else from Sybil before I go do the hat?
Hi, I'm Hugh Bliss.
Have you had any new ideas for improving Canada?
With this new feeling of peace and tranquility,
I feel like my mind is alive with possibilities.
See, it wasn't, A, Lincoln wasn't married.
I only wish there was some way to extend this feeling
of goodwill and generosity to all countries of the world.
I always suspected that when the world turned nice and pleasant,
Canada would be the first to fall.
So long, Sybil.
Ah, Sam.
Hey.
All right, let's go to the bird.
Chicken with the hat.
To the moon, Alice.
Can now do the trick, which I don't know what that gets us to.
I'm at that point in my, was drinking coffee.
Or it's just the ice.
And the ice is slowly melted into that gross freezer taste.
You know what I'm saying?
When the ice cubes melt and it's only that gross freezer water.
I hate that.
I gotta go refill it.
Just don't drink iced coffee.
I can't help it.
I'm American.
I read this somewhere that it's only Americans put ice in everything.
Is that true?
Or did I get like Reddit lied to?
Okay, so now you should be able to do it.
How's it going?
Silence.
I believe I have finally mastered this pinnacle of
Hot coffee is better.
I bet you don't even use the metric system.
Rat from the hat.
I don't use the metric system and I drink hot coffee all the time.
I just like ice coffee.
I just remember I can't stand rats.
They're vile vermin.
Smile when you say that, Beaky.
Beaky?
Sheesh.
I hate this pulling out of the hat business.
Next time I'll find something better to hang it on.
What was the purpose of this?
Oh dear.
Did we get the hat?
There won't be a next time.
I shall never do this trick again.
Only Americans expect genuine info from Reddit.
If you would be so good to remove the hat from my presence.
Sure.
Okay, so now I have a hat.
So I have the magician's hat.
Hmm.
What am I pulling out of here?
Hey!
Okay, this is the...
I got the rat.
Now what if...
I can put him somewhere?
Yeah, I have a rat spawner.
Reddit, the front page of America.
Well, it was like an Ask Reddit thing.
It wasn't an article written by a scholar.
It was just, hey, Reddit, do you put ice in your...
Hey, Americans of Reddit, why do you put ice in everything?
And then it was people doing the long things.
Well, one time when I was in Germany,
I asked for ice and they looked at me strangely.
It was like a bunch of those.
That's...
I'm telling you, that's how it works.
All right, what do I...
Okay, what do I do with the hat?
Hmm.
I have the moon key thing.
Maybe...
Okay, I gotta pull a rat out.
Does anyone not like rats?
Can I make the rats like run somewhere?
I got a lot of items.
This makes people puke.
I have the key to the moon thing.
I can bend spoons with spoon-shaped devices.
And now I can pull rats out of hat.
Let me go back up in that room up here.
Well, okay, so I have these five statues.
Indestructible hues.
Uh-oh, chat's being weird again.
Prismatology is not the answer.
Unless, I suppose, the question is what's a really bad thing to...
Mrs. Betty Parkinson of 328 Cherry Lane,
ex-contestant, up to the moon.
Attention.
The owner of a celestial-class star cruiser license,
USS 1701C.
Please report to the front desk.
Your warp nacelles are on.
I want Sam to read me audiobooks.
And now, a medley of your lunar sent you la...
Oh, it's a callback.
Okay.
View screen.
I can see the whole thing from here.
I don't think I can do anything here.
Throw a rat at him?
No.
Maybe I can put a rat on the blue guy?
Have him eat the rat?
Just kill Hugh Bliss.
That's not how it works.
Okay.
Rat.
Will you move because of a rat?
Hey!
Nah.
Okay.
What about the unicorn?
I'm just gonna exhaust all options.
Do you like unicorns?
Not happening.
Do you like...
No, none of that stuff.
Well, we're gonna try to feed the rat to the green.
Hungry Max.
Urus.
Ah, the brute force strategy.
Brute force strategy is a lot of these point and click games sometimes.
And this isn't total brute force strategy.
I didn't do what I was doing up until this point.
This is nothing.
I remember the days of playing like original Monkey Island.
Or Toonstruck.
And those were so obscure.
Some of those things you had to combine like three items and shit.
Those games were ridiculous.
Okay.
Eat.
I kind of have to move out of the way.
Some of those games...
There's no way.
Maybe a guess if you could.
But that's kind of a game where you have to have a wiki.
Something smells good.
Hey, are you gonna eat that?
Well, I suppose I could share.
Toonstruck is like impossible without the wiki.
Now what?
Now make him throw up.
Did you get it?
Ah, done.
Next time I'm hanging on tight.
So hang on.
Do it again.
Hey!
Here, Max.
Come and get it.
So what happens if I...
Hold on.
Can I pull him out?
Is this gonna be Jerma Rumble live action?
Ladies and gentlemen, the great Saminian.
Hey, let go!
Is that my stomach?
Give me that hat.
Well.
Hey!
See you later.
I feel all warm inside.
Like my belly's a sort of cozy place where flavored popcorn and sugar drinks can meet and mingle.
That's my boy.
All right.
So we only have the blue Max left to take care of.
What would move that blue dude winning the lottery?
Scratch and sniff lottery tickets.
Hey, Bosco's mom.
What?
I thought you were Bosco's mom.
Oh, yes.
I'm Bosco's mom.
Hugh Bliss.
I need a bunch of money.
Identity really is a difficult concept.
How do you get money in this one?
We want to buy something.
Goodie.
Will you just give it to me?
One earthquake maker, barkeep.
A hundred trillion, please.
I don't have a hundred trillion dollars.
Aren't you feeling generous?
Yes.
But I need the money for my poor sick mother.
Hmm.
Uh.
One earthquake ma-
A hundred trillion-
What do you mean by a hundred trillion?
Do you mean you're being generous?
But I need the money for my poor sick mother.
Hmm.
Nevermind.
See you later.
Bye!
Hold on.
Do you have any parking meter that's fine?
Anything else?
I need the-
I think I need a Canada slogan.
Can I pick up the-
Can I call somebody?
I saw what you did.
Keep the payments coming and nobody has to find out.
Yeah, okay.
Love you too, mom.
Oh, mom!
No, that doesn't mean anything.
Never mind.
Roadkill calendar.
The endangered Point Arena Mountain Beaver.
Just yards away from a wildlife preserve.
Better luck next time, little guy.
Jesus.
All right.
What about the rat hole?
Anybody home?
Guess not.
Well, what would you know?
The crucial piece of evidence in the Hudson River Merman Strangler case.
I'll have to remember to file that once-
Is that what you say when you call home?
No.
I do not call my mother and say,
Mom, give me money.
No.
Wee!
President Moon.
Moon picture.
The moon was a lot nicer when it was still hard to get to.
Make somebody in the closet throw up.
Okay, this guy has tape on his mouth.
You want me to make the guy that puked that is tied up with a tape on his mouth?
Are you serious?
Hey, Leonard.
How's it going?
Oh, that was-
Hey, looks like your paperwork finally came through.
You guys cheated.
It's the deed to the United States and it's still moist.
Oh.
Okay.
Yeah, that was really messed up.
Use the deed.
What, use the deed?
Well, hold on.
Let me-
Every time I pop in a tape, it's a mess.
Eat the deed.
Stop reading chat.
Well, I-
Look, sometimes it's gonna fall through the cracks when I see that.
Okay, so.
I'm gonna show her the unicorn.
Eat the debris.
Steal the china.
Steal.
All right, let's go here.
Look.
No.
Max and I made civil throw up once before and that's something I never want to see again.
You look like you're in a shopping mood.
Might you be interested in, say, the United States?
What's the national debt?
How much is it?
Oh, lovely. We can call it Lower Saskatchewan.
What a perfectly delightful name.
Kid, for the tune of 100 trillion.
How much do you want to spend?
Oh, such a grand country deserves a grand price.
We simply refuse to buy it for less than 100 trillion dollars.
It's only fair.
We wouldn't hear of it.
That's far too much.
I'll handle this, Mr. President.
If you insist, Your Highness.
Is cash all right?
We've been dying to use the new Canadian trillion dollar notes.
Is that a picture of Celine Dion?
She's a national treasure.
Trillion dollar note.
Just did that in front of Abe Lincoln.
All right, let's go get it.
I got paid in Canadian.
Earthquake, then earthquake, and I'm good to go.
All right, let's have it.
We want to buy something.
We want to buy the Earthquake Maker.
Here you go, Bosco.
Thank you.
100 trillion in completely non-counterfeit bills.
Queen's...
Let me look at that.
Celine Dion.
OK, looks good to me.
Here's your Earthquake Maker.
A remote control?
Don't get me wrong.
I love TV as much as the next guy, but...
It controls my satellite defense system.
Only one button to work.
Satellite defense.
Just press it for an earthquake.
And this adheres, I hope, to all reasonable safety guidelines.
This is a real earthquake maker.
Who knows?
One more thing.
You have to be in range of the satellite for it to work.
All right.
Where'd you park it?
For some reason, I was suspicious of those blessed people on the moon.
It's on the moon.
So I left it up there.
How silly of me.
Got to use it on the moon.
Check.
Thank you, and goodbye, Brother Bosco.
All right.
This prismatology nonsense really gets my blood boiling.
That's from the heat generated by the limitless energy of your imagination.
What?
OK.
My limitless imagination is going to cause an aneurysm if you don't stop talking like that, Max.
What color of the rainbow would I be, would you say?
What do you guys think?
Never mind.
Like, by personality and everything about me.
What would it be?
Piss brown.
That's not a color of the rainbow.
Piss brown?
Oh my god.
I know what that looks like.
To the moon, Alice.
Do you ever have like a dark brown piss and you're just going,
holy shit, man, I got to drink some water?
It's happened like maybe twice in my whole life.
All right.
So we're going to earthquake him.
Earthquake maker remote.
Let's put the quake under here.
Let's see if I can get any reception for this thing here.
This isn't, I don't know.
I don't have brown pee, guys.
Don't worry.
Well, shame on you, Sam.
Cut the tail.
Cut tail.
I'll miss you, little pal.
Come on.
Is the streamer listening to me?
Cut tail.
Why is he not listening to me?
Cut the tail.
I'm going to be needing your tail.
He's not doing it.
My little buddy back together.
Whatever.
Sam, what are you doing?
You may not want to watch this.
Nice.
Kick cocky.
Cut tail.
Good job.
All of a sudden I feel like watching TV and eating orange marshmallow.
I was so invested and involved in an item that he's not going to use that no one uses.
Cut it.
Have I been away, Sam?
In a manner of speaking.
Hugh Bliss split you into pieces so you've kind of been all over the place.
Hugh Bliss.
I hate that guy now with his phony smile and his artificial happy happy.
What do you say we tar and feather that self-righteous jerk?
Good to have you back, little buddy.
Time to get ourselves some good old-fashioned payback.
And incidentally save the world in the process.
What are we waiting for?
He did end up using the melted ice cream axe for a large portion of the game.
Yeah, I know.
That's true.
But I did complain about it.
A lot.
I got really mad at it, remember?
All right.
So let's go back and talk to Mr. Bliss.
Worth this item.
What is this?
What's this straw pole here?
What color is Jeremy?
Green.
Yep.
All right, vote it.
Green, yellow, red, blue, indigo, violet, orange.
Green.
All right.
No, green is...
I'm all right with green.
I'm winning by a lot.
Yeah, no.
Brown's not on there.
I can see myself as a green.
Hold on.
Wait.
Color personality test.
Let's see if you guys are right.
Taking the color personality type test.
Personality color is equal to personality type.
Okay, hold on.
I'm going to take this on stream right now.
Damn, it's like 95 right now?
No, it's not.
Is it that hot in Vegas right now?
No.
What?
That was wrong.
Okay, let me open this up on stream.
And hold on.
Uh-uh-uh-uh-uh.
Color personality test.
Start the test.
Okay, let me just capture it.
I'll watch this be like...
There are a lot of questions on this test.
This is going to take like a fucking...
At least 20 minutes.
Why is everybody resident sleepering this?
You don't want to see this?
Nobody wants...
There's a lot of resident sleepers.
Okay.
Oh, shit.
My like window captures,
because I'm doing two window captures at the same time,
so it's fucked up.
Uh-oh.
Oh, let me try again.
Hold on, hold on, hold on, hold on, hold on, hold on.
Hold on, hold on, hold on.
This is the shit I get drunk to see.
Well, all right, see?
Then we're good.
We're cool.
All right, this will work.
One moment.
There it is.
You should see it.
All right, so here we go.
There are so many ads on this site.
It's kind of awful.
Okay, so this is the test of what color I am.
How do you think other people might describe you?
A good innovator,
a good creative worker,
a good leader,
a good honest hard worker.
So this is...
Okay, so a good creative worker,
a good leader,
let us vote.
No, this is what I think of myself.
You guys just told me what color you thought I was.
A good creative worker.
Okay, next question.
When you're given a briefing paper,
what do you do with it?
What do you mean a briefing paper?
Send it back.
I issue briefing papers.
I don't read them.
Skim it for the...
What?
Skim it and pretend I read it.
Read it carefully and act on it.
Rewrite it and send it back.
I would skim it and I would pretend I read it.
I'd be like,
yeah, yeah, yeah, I read the whole thing.
I would make sure I pulled out one or two sentences.
Okay, yeah, I would skim it.
Imagine you had to put some furniture together.
How would you go about it?
Grab all the pieces and figure it out without instructions.
Follow the instructions to the letter.
Get somebody else to do it
and supervise them.
I wouldn't.
I'd be building my own furniture.
No, I wouldn't do that.
I absolutely would not just do that.
Do I want to not have a chair done correctly?
You literally did this test yesterday?
That's weird.
Labo is...
Yeah, I would follow the instructions.
I would.
You're asked to provide an assessment of a colleague.
How would you approach it?
Discuss it with them
and tell them what you're doing,
what you're going to say.
Discuss it with them.
See what they want.
See what they want said about themselves.
Give it to them and ask them to fill it out honestly.
Just fill it out honestly.
I'm definitely not this one.
You're asked to provide it.
I would ask them to fill it out honestly.
Which of these things do you value the most in a relationship?
Respect, unpredictability, companionship, interest.
Companionship.
Well, okay.
There are way too many questions for this joke.
This is like an 18 second joke
and it's going to take like 25 minutes.
I'm going to go quick.
Here we go.
You're on the street and you see somebody in distress.
How are you going to help them?
Take charge of the whole situation.
Go and fetch them a cup of coffee.
Call for the appropriate emergency assistance.
I would call for the appropriate assistance.
If you can't find a solution to a problem,
would it most likely be because
somebody else must have let you down?
You haven't shown enough imagination.
You haven't worked on it long enough.
You haven't looked at it from enough angles.
Well, I look at it too much.
I look into that.
I look into stuff way too many times.
So that's definitely what it is.
I just hadn't looked at it yet
from like a million different angles.
Which of these things do you have
do you value most about employment?
Stimulation.
If you overheard a colleague talking about you,
which of these statements would upset you the most?
They are so conventional.
They are not fit to lead.
Their ideas aren't very creative.
They are not a team player.
If a colleague is...
Why is this all about colleagues and shit?
Isn't this supposed to be my personality,
not other people's personalities?
If a colleague is upset, how would you deal with it?
Tell them to pull themselves together.
Try to find a solution.
Think of something to take their mind off it.
Offer them a shoulder.
I would take something to take their mind off.
If you need ideas from your team for a new project,
how would you garner them?
Informal meal to brainstorm.
Circulate an email.
Put out your own suggestions and ask for comments.
Demanding a paper from each member.
That would be that one.
If a new system is implemented in your office,
which of these is most likely to be your reaction?
It's always the office too.
Resistance.
Adaptation.
I would adapt.
On a football team,
which of these positions would suit you best?
Quarterback.
Which of these activities might suit you best?
Freerunning.
Running alone.
Running a relay race.
Running with friends.
I don't like to run at all.
Whereas I don't run.
Whereas I watch people running from the stands.
Freerunning.
Because then I can stop whenever I want to.
If somebody at work has made you angry,
how do you react?
Try and analyze what has made you angry
and the reason why.
Have a reasonable discussion.
Attack them at every opportunity
or keep it to yourself and let off steam outside.
It is absolutely not free.
I would probably keep it to myself
and just I'd keep it to myself
and then like go outside
and like scream at the moon.
From what you know of these countries,
cultures, etc.
Where do you think you would fit in best?
Germany, France, China, Brazil.
I don't know.
I do see come to Brazil all the time.
I do.
I swear to God that's not a meme or a joke.
I see it all the time.
Which of these would you say is your greatest fault?
I miss details.
I'm too ready to take orders.
I can be too critical.
I'm inclined to daydream.
Definitely that one.
Which of these sorts of car would you most likely choose?
People carrier.
Single seater sports.
Would one seat...
Is it a go-kart?
Probably that one.
Which of these would you be most satisfied with
at the end of a project you were leading?
That it surpassed expectations.
I got the job done.
That everyone did as I said.
That it surpassed expectations.
On a plane, do you think you would be the best
as a co-pilot, navigator, flight engineer,
or chief pilot?
Too much.
Too much to do.
Probably co-pilot.
Because you just have just enough responsibility
but you're not like the...
You're...
I'd be the co-pilot.
There's an important deadline coming up
and it looks like your team might not make it.
What will you do?
Ask whether the deadline was never realistic
and if it should be altered.
Drive the team onwards to work harder and harder.
See if there were any corners which can be cut.
Just keep going.
You can only do your best.
Yep.
All right, I want like a reveal here.
Hold on.
If you were climbing up a mountain
and a member of your team couldn't go on,
what would you do?
Split the team up.
Some to go down, some to carry on.
Leave them with the team
and carry on on your own.
Turn the whole team around
but carry on with the rest
you'll get them on the way back.
I don't know if I would do that.
I would probably split up the team.
Some go, you know,
I kind of want to stay up
but I want to go up the mountain.
Yeah, I would split the team up.
He's going to be dead when you come back.
Yeah.
In a conversation, what are you aiming for?
A solution, inspiration,
a consensus, agreement, inspiration.
What is your attitude to workplace friendships?
They are a good thing if they happen.
They have no bearing on success or failure.
They should grow organically, right?
Yeah, yeah.
Last one.
Which of these things make you the happiest?
A life in which others look up to me.
A life in which I plowed my own furrow.
A quiet, contended life.
A happy, exciting life.
Are you ready?
Here you go.
Let's see.
Green.
No.
No, that's cool.
It's P. Brown.
It's not P. Brown, okay?
Creator, performer.
You like to constantly challenge where you...
Is that supposed to be me?
You aren't prepared to accept the status quo
without seeing as things can be done differently.
You think very deeply about issues
and you always like to bring a new way
of looking at things to the table.
You're very enthusiastic
and will be popular with colleagues.
You must make sure that you follow through
in your creativity with concrete results.
Nice.
Okay, there you go.
I did it.
How do I get the last 30 minutes
of the stream back, streamer?
They stream sniped me.
All right, we were going back up
with that earthquake weapon.
Could have done it at the end of the stream.
No, it was relevant right now.
Hey, little buddy, get him.
Hi, I'm Hugh Blake.
Stop saying that!
Huh?
What?
How did he get in there?
You little idiot.
You've ruined my hypno beam.
I should have killed you earlier,
but what can I say?
I'm too nice.
That said, die, buddy!
Wrong.
What the?
Where you at?
We are a space-faring colony
of sentient bacteria.
A sentence I really did not
expect to hear today.
We cannot be harmed by bullets.
We only need one thing, to feed.
You see, we feed on the endorphins
produced by humans experiencing true bliss.
So, you don't care if people
are happy at all.
You just want to eat till you drop.
Yes.
Hey, I hear that.
But you want us to starve.
And for that, you will die.
In the most fantastic display
of the universe!
Hey, gotta look good for the cameras.
What cameras?
Pack your bags, Sam,
because you just want an all-expense
day trip to your grave.
So who killed him?
And you get to watch him die.
Let the magic begin.
Ladies and gentlemen,
for my first trick, I give you
the Rainbow Wheel of Death!
Also known as Emetics, the ride.
Oh, I'm gonna throw up.
Add to Rainbow Wheel.
Not yet.
Exactly.
Throw some daggers.
No, hatchets!
Hey.
Sorry, I got excited.
I've got a better idea.
I'll just torture him mercilessly
until he begs me to shoot him
with his own gun.
Oh, well.
What's this?
What is that?
Wait, wait, wait, wait.
Spoon, Ben.
Spoon.
All right.
That Willy Mays never caught one
while spinning on a Wheel of Death.
Okay, and then we've got...
I have the Magician's Talisman Earthquake.
I don't think that's gonna...
No.
Put that back up here.
I think it only works on things
with stomachs.
Evil laugh.
And break magic rings.
Can't escape.
Magic junk.
I'm stuck.
I just bend them all?
Uh, what?
So that's how magicians switch places
with people.
By magic.
Oh, in retrospect?
So now he's stuck there.
I probably shouldn't have left
that lying around.
Way to go, Sam!
You did it!
Thanks, Willy.
It was that easy, apparently.
Frankly, I wish it had been
a little more challenging.
Kind of a letdown.
That's what I'm saying.
Excuse me?
I think you're forgetting something.
You forget something?
Me?
No.
I don't know.
Oh, yeah.
Oh.
My magic eight ball told me
to bring my antibacterial soap today.
Why didn't I listen?
Next up, the number one magic trick
at every priest modality party.
It's time to separate your bliss!
No, not that.
Don't worry.
This won't hurt a bit.
Until the saw hits you.
Then you'll die!
Cruesome!
I love it!
This guy's terrifying.
All right.
Well, I have like a second here.
Switch with him.
Swap all you want.
It drives the crowd wild.
Saw us, Sam!
We dare you.
Maybe I will.
All right.
Don't saw.
Don't do it.
You're supposed to saw me.
Cue bliss!
For my next trick, I present to you...
Saw his head.
I'm not gonna do that.
The lunar lander?
It's the ticket to oblivion.
Enjoy your stay in outer space.
Until you die!
I think I know what to do here.
Lock the door and then switch.
Or not.
Sam!
I'll give the guy one thing.
He does put on a good show.
Okay.
So we are now...
Lock the door.
I can't do that now.
What do you mean, you can't do that now?
I don't know.
That first step is a doozy.
I mean, I could switch with him.
But do I do something like just do...
Earthquake?
I don't think that's gonna work again.
Lock the door from the inside.
And then he won't be able to unlock it from the inside.
Right.
You know, that's a good point.
But I'm just trying to think a thing.
It's a cartoon.
It's like a rocket engine.
I don't know.
This is fun.
It's okay, everyone.
I'm all right.
I heard that.
Consider this.
A trap so deadly it would cause you to die.
That is deadly.
It's the cleansing path of annihilation.
Oh, could we skip this one?
I kind of have a thing about drowning.
Oh, let me think.
No!
Don't drown, Sam!
So do I just keep switching with him?
Switch, little buddy.
That's such a boring way to die.
Oh, shit.
It's a dunk tank.
Try to get cut in half instead.
Thanks, little buddy.
Well, water tank.
I can only hold my breath for nine minutes.
I don't think...
I think I just got...
Is it just as simple as one, two, three?
Wait!
Bacteria can't drown!
Woohoo!
So I just...
I'm gonna have to anti-bacteria something.
Shut up!
All right.
Wait, wait, wait, wait.
Wait, hold on.
I have a second here.
Bacteria.
The guy pissing the tank?
Oh, no.
We have to do this again.
Magic junk.
Magic salt box.
So it seems like...
He's gonna keep going around.
I can't go anywhere but here.
Maybe I can...
Hold on.
Attack the dog!
What if I switch back?
I can't do that now.
Oh, well, now I can actually...
Just let him do it.
Having my bliss separated is not what the brochures made it.
I need to like...
I don't get...
I have to go pick up stuff.
Can I make a puke?
I'm just gonna do it.
I definitely have to play anti-bacteria.
Okay.
Anti-bacteria.
Here it comes again.
What's that on the table?
All right, so hold on.
Magic junk.
Microphone.
Crystals.
How do I get over there?
Okay, now magic crystals.
No, I can't move.
I have to bend shit then.
I have to...
No.
Is there anything I can bend from here?
Like this magic junk there?
He's impervious to gastro-kinesis.
He can't...
I can't make him throw up.
I mean, I can bend these,
but it doesn't really do much for me.
He had another spoon.
Another spoon.
Spoon.
Shoot him.
I can't kill him.
Magic rings.
You can't kill bacteria.
That's true.
Bullets won't hurt bacteria.
They match the items with the spoons.
That's what I was thinking too.
Maybe just put them back up there,
but I can't...
I think it only works on things with stomachs.
I can't put them up there.
You have to shoot each individual bacteria.
Next up.
I'm trapped.
Anything else over here?
Annoying...
Not one of those 3D images.
If God had wanted pictures to be 3D,
he wouldn't have made them 2D.
Can I bend it?
Earthquake.
Evil Gumball!
No, nothing.
Saw us, Sam!
All right, I'm just gonna walk.
Next up.
Oblivion.
Saw the Lander.
He doesn't let me move.
Nope, not spoon-y enough.
I can't escape.
I don't know.
May I spoon on the saw?
Bring this down here.
All right, switch it again.
Now, hold on.
There's a lock.
There's the crystals.
There's the water tank.
What if I break the tank,
and I shoot the tank,
and I explode?
I don't think this is gonna work.
You have to dissolve them.
That's not gonna work.
All right.
Keep going.
Saw.
All right, switch.
Put Bleach in the tank.
I didn't think I could move.
Why is he letting me do this?
He freezes me every other time.
Wait, I still have to stop each one of these
from being able to do...
Okay, I get it.
So...
Blending bath of annihilation!
So what's the deal here, then?
Okay, um...
Key?
No, no, no.
I need to make it so this is not functional.
I can't do that in this predicament.
Why not?
I'm stuck.
No, I tried to shoot the lock,
but the lock didn't work.
I can't pull the gun out.
Wait.
No, like, can I do this?
The door's just open.
Oh, I'm boiling to the life!
That was it?
Just boil him?
That's the end?
Oh my god.
Is that season one complete?
I think that's it for season one.
Is there a secret at the end?
Hey, season one.
Is there a post-credit scene?
Why would you do that?
Bright side of the moon.
That was cool.
Oh, you're unhypnotizing everybody, I see.
That's fun.
It's fun just playing these games.
Just kind of...
I love the hangout.
Just chill.
Play Sam and Max.
I would do something like The Walking Dead,
but I already did them all.
If you play Puzzle Agent,
I have you're probably wondering,
well, if you like this,
why play all these other ones?
I've probably played them all.
Wolf Among Us, I've already done it.
What's going on on the screen?
And those experiences,
you kind of experience it
and then you don't again.
So if I want to play season one
or season two of The Walking Dead
or The Wolf Among Us,
I already know the story
and I know what happens.
I wouldn't really want to play them again on stream.
You played all the post-Walking Dead stuff?
Yes.
No, I did not do Minecraft story mode
and I don't...
I'm not going to do Minecraft story mode.
It's not going to happen.
No.
You signed yourself up now?
No, I did not.
I just told you no.
I played Grim Fandango.
Yes, I have.
Play season two, you mean right now?
We have a couple options.
I'm going to take a piss.
We'll come back and we'll assess our options.
There are a couple things to do.
But I do want to see this ending credit sequence
because it is very, very fun.
Play episode one of Minecraft story mode.
I'm not doing that.
I'm going to have to be an eight or a nine out of 10
shit-faced for you guys to convince me on that stream
to play Minecraft story mode episode one.
2007.
Wow.
It was a long time ago.
My website is down.
I would assume it is.
Well, there you go.
That's season one complete.
It was cool.
It was fun.
I'm going to go pee.
I'll be right back.
And we will figure out what are we going to do
for the remainder of the stream.
See you guys in like two minutes, three minutes,
something like that.
Be right back.