Let's go. Morning, Dread. Glad you could make it for reorientation.
I didn't expect that to work. This is your health meter showing how much health you have.
If it drops to zero, you will die. Oh, that's what a health meter is.
It will protect you from occasional hits, but it cannot stand. Watch it. Watch it.
Mission failed. They got fed up. They couldn't take it anymore.
They couldn't take my face punching anymore. And now the whole team is...
Dispense some justice.
Got a protest out here. Ladies and gentlemen, if you could please refrain from protesting this close to the city gates.
I'd appreciate it. You know what? Just, you're under arrest.
Put the signs down. Put the sign down. Everybody chill out. You're all under arrest.
Ten years for protesting? That sucks. Ten years for protesting.
Why is he going away for life? Why is he...
Dude, this guy's going away for life. He did the exact same crime as everybody else and he's going away for his life.
Holy shit.
Look at this lady. Oh my god.
She even has a thing on her back that says, oh yeah, oh yeah.
You see, I wasn't even going to make that joke. This game made that joke for me.
This is a female beer. It is. It even says it on her fucking shirt.
What am I arresting her for?
Three months for what?
Bank robbery. I'm on it. Bank robbery. Oh, bank robbery.
Toss another grenade. Got him. Get down.
Can't see anything right now.
This is worse than TF2. How long am I on fire for? That sucked.
Anybody else? I got one of you guys. I'm out of bullets.
I probably shouldn't be killing everybody right now, but you know what? They're shooting at us. They're shooting at officers.
What are we supposed to do? What happened to you? Is that a judge?
That is a judge. Don't spread it to me, dude.
Somebody help him. I feel like I need to help him.
Is there anything I can do to help you? I don't think so.
I'm pretty sure you're just on fire forever.
That's got to be a terrible, terrible way to go.
Move. You're going to have to move, dude. I can't arrest this guy if you're circling him.
Look what you did.
Dude, that had to be done. That had to be done, and you all know it.
Get out of my town.
Oh, does your buddy want to follow me around? Does your buddy want to follow me?
Is that what he wants to do? Not anymore.
Why are the people still out? The vampires are everywhere.
You think they'd be like an emergency bulletin. They're just running around killing everybody.
They're just running around killing every single citizen.
Okay. Okay.
You know, you could run. That's an option, you know.
Citizens of Judged Red City number five, you could run.
Break out. You can't handle that.
You guys could not handle that.
All you had to do was shoot. You guys went through the same training that I went through.
And you can't shoot a zombie at point blank range.
I can't even. I don't even want to look at you two.
You know we can.
Could use a little bit of help here.
Come on, people.
Again. Again.
Mr. Medical Man.
How is he the only one to get out of that?
This guy is the only person to get out.
And he literally has no weapons and he's been walking.
Oh my goodness.
I got too many bullets ricocheting.
What the fuck? That guy wasn't dead?
What? Oh, dude.
Dude, you know what just happened right there?
He just got a bullet ricocheted in his head.
That was awesome.
Wait, do I just have to survive during like a gang war?
Why are you shooting me?
You're supposed to be... There's a suspect in there.
What the... See what the fuck you did?
You turned and you shot me.
And it ended up getting you killed.
Like, what were you doing?
Holy shit, dude.
You need to get your glasses examined.
It's still blinking mission failed and I can still move around.
You get down.
Oh, it's another judge.
I went rogue.