Hello. Yeah, sorry. Sorry I'm late. I got carried away with something. I got a little carried away.
I don't know why my voice sounds like this. You know, it's weird. This is the first time I've
talked all day. I've not opened my mouth to speak a single word till right now. And it sounds like
morning voice. Yeah. Wait, is morning voice something that you have to kind of work out of?
If you wake up and you don't talk at all, you don't say a single word, will morning voice
continue to follow you until you open your mouth and speak? Really? I've never thought about it
that deeply. I have not said a single word. How come you're asking me that? I don't know. Maybe
some of you guys are doctors or scientists. I know a lot of you are. It's because you smoke.
That's why your voice is like that. I know I don't. Anyways, hi. Bro, your voice is so deep.
I don't know why it sounds like this today. I feel fine. It's not like, oh,
guys, my throat's bothering me. No, I feel completely fine. I just haven't spoken in
like 12 hours. Quick, do some impressions. Who could I do an impression of with a voice like this?
How about, I don't know. Who do you think? Who could I do? Patrick? Hey, SpongeBob. It's me,
Patrick. Oh, yeah, SpongeBob. Let's go have an adventure. Does that sound like him, kind of?
That wasn't even close. Oh, yes, it was. What are you talking about? SpongeBob, it's me, Patrick.
Bernie Sanders. Hold on a second. Hold on. Patrick. Patrick Starr. That sounds like Patrick.
Top LOL moments from Patrick Starr. Hold on. I need to hear. Hold on. Okay.
Hold on.
This ought to do the trick. That does the same sound. Hold on. What about this one?
I sense no danger here. How could it be dangerous?
Sometimes it's too easy. I'll just be honest. All right, let's go. Let me start the stream. Let me
say hello first. Did I even tweet? I didn't even tweet. Dude, you're starting 40 minutes late.
There's a reason why I'm late. Okay, do you understand? I've been sitting here.
So in pre-stream chat, we were just talking. Is that like 12, I don't know, 12, 15, 12 o'clock?
And I was doing something at the desk here, just typing away. And I got really, really
tired of typing away. And I got really carried away. And I looked over and it was, the only reason
why I noticed is because the chat got really fast. Because it was just over on my other monitor,
just kind of in the corner. And in my peripheral, I just see bing, bing, bing, bing, bing, bing,
bing, bing, bing, bing, bing, bing, bing, bing, bing, bing, bing, bing, bing. And I was like,
what's going on? Oh, that's right. That's right. I got to start. I got carried away doing something.
And yes, I will show you that thing potentially. And so if you're good. But today we're going to
play Sorcery. We're going to go back to it. I know a lot of people have been waiting for Sorcery.
I know a lot of you've been waiting to, let me turn the crickets off. There. I know it's been
kind of on the back burner for a few weeks, but it's back. We're going to chill. We'll play it
for a little while. I'm going to give a quick recap. We'll kind of just get our bearings and
see where we are in the game. How come you look like a cartoon? I don't, I don't know, dude,
because half the time you've ever seen me has been on a web. Okay. It's time for me to tell
you something. Your only barometer for the way that I look has been in professional studio lighting
and shitty webcam. I don't know what to tell you. It's a, there's a lot of, there's a large range
here. Barometer. What? How many pushups could you do live in a way? How many pushups could you do
in a life and death situation? Nowadays, probably not very many because of the chest pain that I
have. Probably not very many. I could probably realistically just go, I'd probably do at least
20. Five to 10 years ago, if you would ask that question, it would probably have been at least
60 to a hundred. At least. Barometer is air pressure, dude. What are you talking about?
You can say barometer to, barometer is a gauge, right? It's an instrument to gauge a certain
level of something. You can use that term to give, I don't know what you, it's, it's, what are you
talking about? It's a, it's an instrument, it's a measurement instrument. I could have said ruler.
It's a, whatever. All of a sudden all the science Andes are here. I told you everyone here is smart
and all of a sudden, no, you need to know what the, what that, it's just a meter, not a gauge.
It's literally for weather. I, I'm going to keep using it for what I use it for. I, oh, it's, you
know, it's the barometer for this. It's the barometer for that. It's an instrument of measurement
of some type of fluid that fills up with the air pressure. Okay. A moment is literally only 20
seconds. Change your pinned tweet. What is my pinned tweet? Hold on. Let me tweet. Hold on.
Speaking of Twitter. Let me actually make a tweet. What is my pinned tweet? It's not a sponsor thing,
is it? It links to teespring.com. I don't use social media. Whatever. I'll figure it out. All
right. I'll fix it later. It's from 2019. I don't use social media. I don't really care.
You're using social media right now. I don't. Okay. I don't use text based social media.
Does that make sense? This is visual and audio based social media. I don't really use the text
based social media. Anyways, do you really care that much? This is tech. I'm typing right now.
I am not typing. There happens to be a chat room and you happen to be in it. I'm happen to be
streaming. I am talking and using my audio and visual. This chat room is an accessory to
this channel, right? But I'm not in it. I'm not using it right now. What were you working on?
You'll see. It's very important. And all the 30 minute late LOL Andes, you're going to be very,
very happy when you see why I was 26 minutes late. But yes, we're going to play sorcery again.
Sorcery today. I will be on name your price tomorrow live in person on Austin shows channel.
That should be really fun. And then this weekend, we will figure out what to do this weekend.
I have a few ideas. Are you going to bring a booster seat? Yeah, probably. Probably because
I need it. Oh, flipped it on you a little bit there. How he flipped it. I flipped it on you.
Oh, oh, no. Oh, no. Mom thinks the joke is funny. Now I got to do something else.
Nope. It's still funny. Whatever. All right. So yeah, that's sorcery today. Name your price
tomorrow. I will host the channel. Obviously, it's Austin show. I have retweeted the announcement
tweet for it. So if you're looking for it, it's there. I will be hosting it here. And I will.
That's what I'm going to be doing tomorrow. The image they used for you. Yes, because this I don't
take pictures. I don't really. I don't have any photos like professional photos or anything.
The only photos that anybody can ever pull from. If I'm a guest on any show,
they just have to type in Jerma into the Google image search and find one. And there's like six.
They use that one because that is the latest like frontal face picture where I don't look like a
maniac. So whatever. I don't I can't I can't do I can't do it. I just can't do it. I can't take
professional photos. I can't do it. The whole time I would be sitting there. And I just can't I can't
look into that camera and give like a smile and like, Hey, yeah, what's up? Me Jerma. Yeah,
use this. I'm a professional. Hey, I'm a celebrity. Yeah, I'm an Eclan. Like I can't I
literally cannot do it. I just can't do it. It just I feel so weird doing it. Because I just imagine
one of these pictures of me like smiling in the camera professional headshot. I just and I just
say I I look at it and go ah, I can't self conscious. No, it's not about self conscious.
As I pose in the mirror naked all the time and I go holy shit. I go wow. Whoa. What are you kidding
me? That's what I do in the mirror. But I just like I don't know publicly taking a picture of
yourself. That's like a professional like hey, what's Hey, you know, hey, it's me, Jerma. You
know me. Yeah, that's right. I'm leaning on something. I've got my elbow up. My elbows
resting on a chair. That's me. Yeah. Hey, sponsor this channel. I just feel so it doesn't it doesn't
feel right to me. It just doesn't. I'd rather them use the subspace guy picture. Author section
picture Andy. Yes, that's a you got it. Exactly. That's exactly what I'm talking about. I just
can't do it. All right. So let's go over what's going on here. Because of all the people that
they have missed it. Hold on. Wait, wait a minute. Okay, we're good. So today,
we are in part three of sorcery. Let's take a look at the map. This is where we are in this section
here. For those of you that did, I'm just waiting for like a few minutes to be able to trickle in.
We are working with time control in this episode. Part three is about aiming these devices
at different places in the world. And when you aim it there, this section will be in the past.
So it's two full maps, one on top of the other, one in the present and one in the past. The last
thing we did is we remember that we did the weird ant colony. We got a few items. Let's actually take
a look at what we have for items. Just to refresh. We opened the door. We beat Kare. We opened the
door. We got all the spell lines. Yes, it was the earwig colony. That's right. We still have with
three giants teeth. Yeah, we did get you got Elden Ringed. That's what we have just to keep in mind.
Let's take a look at the spells too because it's been a while. We still have the ape,
which is kind of insane because I've never gone through part three full episodes of this game and
not had something else. Again, we got Zap as lightning bolt. Poff is protective force field.
Law is we can control non-intelligent creatures. That was a really good one, by the way. That was
probably the best intelligence I've probably ever said. The way that that flowed together.
That was actually unbelievable. Dumb makes creatures extremely clumsy. Hot is fireball,
obviously. Wall is invisible wall. Here's your whole book. We can cast spells. We can refresh
them if we need to. Ball Fondler, since being unbanned, has said a couple things. They've said,
when are you going to play Skyrim? Ball Fondler, you're on thin ice. We have a sword and a silver
chain. We can use this, I think, to kill ghosts or something. So let's see. What was the last
thing we did? Let's just take it slow here. Oh, wait a minute. What was the last thing I did here?
The bug clamors up the canyon's edge and drops you into the dirt, right? This is right after.
With a final nod, it turns its strides away. You call it a thank you to the bug, but it's already
gone. You look around once more. A few birds swoop and wheel in the crevice, turning circles
that are way below you. Okay, so then I did doze. I caused slowness. Let's just read what Ball Fondler
said. Let's see if it's worthy of a ban here. Ball Fondler, it's been a week and a half.
Play Skyrim. Ego Andy. Holy shit. Nice wiener, bro. He's fully naked, by the way. He's naked.
Camera or naked. Stand up. Skyrim. Play Skyrim. I will never back down. Well, I gotta tell you,
that last statement there, that shows perseverance. That shows that you can
take a life by the reins, you know what I mean? So you're okay for now. Okay, so yeah, we did slow
and we ended up slowly jumping across the gap and then falling down, right? So we're down in the chasm.
No, we made it across because we were in slow motion. All right, cool. Let's go.
Are we ready? We're ready. The world begins to slow down once more as you begin to speed up.
You feel somewhat light-headed, but otherwise well enough. The bleak plains stretch away once
more behind you. Wind whistles through the fissure. We can cast another spell. We made it across,
which the whole point was we were going to get across that chasm. Why would I? Oh, find safe
passage on the other side, okay. We could also, I think it's huff, create wind for no reason. Why?
Hey dude, I'm watching from Baodubok Ridge. This is a great stream. Hey, that's actually,
what time zone is that? You're like plus, what are you, like plus six, plus eight? That's crazy.
Do I just blow the horn? What's even ahead? There's nothing even here. Why would I just blow the
gale horn? What else can I do? I made it safely across. Why would I care? Float in the air? I
just, I made it across. Zip, cause teleportation. I think the game thinks I'm not across it yet.
No, we're just going to move on. You waste no time. You must move on. Why would I? To get,
oh, to get back across maybe. All right, we're going to follow the road. You continue across
the dusty plains. Darkness closes in. You need to rest, especially after walking all day without
eating. The road is barely visible through the dust. A few scattered bones lie in the path.
Look at the bones. You pick over a few of the bones, thin femurs, long arms, elven most likely,
but Black Elf, the wind has scoured them dry. You continue on your journey.
All right, it's time to decide where we're going to go. We need to pull. Are we going up? All right,
we're going to one, two, three. One is up north, which is heading this way. Seems pretty desolate
this way, but who knows? Might run into something over here. Two is back down to the fissure. Three
is going east this way. And four is, here's the secret fucking goddamn Elbertson family
egg salad recipe. I mulled it over. Figured, you know, this is a secret family recipe.
And I realized, what if I don't have any fucking grandkids? You all have to act as my grandchildren
because what if I don't? Well, I mean, I think I want, I think I want kids eventually, maybe.
I don't know, right? I'm thinking about it. What if I don't? You have to pass this legacy down.
Parasocial Andy. Yeah. All right. Hold on. Wait a minute. Let me fix this. Let me fix this.
I was saying that comically. You understand? I don't actually see you as my grandchildren,
right? That's fucking weird. That's strange and should not be taken seriously. Let me just be
very clear about that. But this is it. This is the real deal. Do you want me to go? Should I go over
it? I said, I thought a lot about this. I'm going, it's a secret recipe. You want me to go over it?
Okay. All right. Here we go. Secret family recipe time. I'm going to go over it very briefly. Well,
maybe not so briefly, but you know what I mean. All right. This makes enough for a few people
and it's a few, when you make it, you can put it into the fridge. It lasts for a few days.
Don't let this sit in the fridge for more than four days or so. That's kind of, you know,
I don't know. At that point, I'm not a food scientist. I'm not a food safety person.
I'm just saying it lasts for a few days. That's what it is. I don't know what happens after four,
which way, egg salad. Okay. So this is 12 eggs in a large saucepan. Make sure these are good eggs.
Make sure they're organic natural eggs. I don't know if it really matters or not, but that's what
I buy. You boil them. Get the pot boiled. Enough where you can fit this. 12 eggs. It's the whole
carton. Chicken eggs. No, not anything. What are the animal? No, chicken eggs. Who the fuck likes
egg salad? You will, if you make this recipe. Chicken eggs. Why so many? Because there's a
reason why it's so many. Here's why. If you, I just like making the whole thing because I know
I'll have enough for a few days. This is food prep. This is, you make the whole carton. Make sure
you have a big enough mixing bowl and everything, right? It's the whole carton because it's essentially
food prep. You're going to have a few days worth of this food. And by the way, you don't have to
just put this on a sandwich. It's not, oh yeah, I guess I'll put it on a sandwich. You could eat,
you could put this on other stuff. You can eat this in a, like a wrap, right? That's, I mean,
that's probably, that's kind of it. This is 30 days supply. 12 egg, what'd you say? 12 eggs in four
days is not good. Okay. Let's see your Uber Eats history. In four days, you don't eat all, is this
for like a few days and a few people? This is not a fried chicken sandwich. This is not a double
cheeseburger meal. This is an egg salad and it's healthy. It's good for you. It's got tons of
quality. I don't want to hear this bullshit about how eggs aren't good for you. That's bullshit from
the fucking seventies. I don't want to hear this nonsense that eggs, oh, you know, don't eat eggs.
I want an egg, only egg whites. Oh, egg white almond. No, I don't want to hear this. Mayo is
unhealthy. Mayo is oil. It's oil, whatever. You don't need to use the whole can. I'm not going to
hear this. I'm not going to listen to this bullshit. I'm not going to hear this. Egg salad with like a
piece of cheddar and maybe like a some, you know, on like a nice wheat roll or something or an onion
roll. That's better than a Burger King meal, okay? That's better than some of the big fatty cuts of
meat that sometimes we eat. This is not bad for you. I am, I'm going to, I'm going to continue with
my recipe. Egg salad tastes like shit. You haven't had mine. You haven't had my egg salad. I'm getting
very upset about this. What does Ball Fondler have to say about this? All right, fine. Let me get
through the recipe first and then we'll see what Ball Fondler has to say. Not yet. We'll get Ball
Fondler's opinion after and Ball Fondler, I don't want to hear it until after. I'm going to be clear.
Okay, so again, it's 12 eggs. I do that. Look, you can change this a little bit if you want to.
I do 12 eggs because I know I want to eat it for a few days. It's super easy. It's a sandwich.
You can put it anywhere. It's good. It's eggs. It's a little bit of mayo. It's a nice brown mustard.
Shut up. We're going to keep going. You peel the eggs. You put them in a large bowl and you start
to mash them, right? You can use the back end of a fork. You can use a mashed potato masher and you go
mush them up, right? But don't do it too much and don't do it too little. 12 eggs is literally a
week worth of salad. Well, that's a pissing ho- All right, forget about the quantity.
Forget about the quantity. Listen, you want me to share my secret family recipe with you or not?
Do you use your feet to mash these with? Stop. All right, listen to me. After you mash them up,
and not huge whole egg chunks, it needs to be enough where it's uniform. It's not a paste,
though. I don't want it not like sawdust. Chunky, but not too ridiculous. You want to be able to
scoop it up with a spoon. Okay, one tablespoon of mayonnaise goes into this. Don't use anything else.
You'll ruin it. If people use, what's the other stuff that's gross or like any other kind of
other mayo type stuff? Oh, I forget what it's called. Like, what's it called? I don't even-
Miracle Whip. Don't use Miracle Whip. It's not for my recipe. I'm sorry. That's not how it works.
There's other like mayo alternatives. No, it's a real mayo recipe. Real mayonnaise. Don't use
anything else. Your friends will think it's gross and then they'll make fun of me for having a bad
recipe. Fold in the mayo. You add one tablespoon periodically. Don't just squeeze in mayonnaise
and fucking ruin it. It's one to two tablespoons periodically as you're folding it in. It's going
to get to a consistency where all the eggs are coated. It's kind of melding together. It's folding
together. Make sure it's thick and chunky to pick up but not too, like not paste, right? Here it is.
Two tablespoons of Tabasco Original Hot Sauce. Fold that in. You can add a little bit more or a little
less depending on how you like it. There are some people that think hot sauce is awful and don't
want it at all. Then just don't use it. But this is my recipe. It's going to turn into this, I said
nuclear orange, right? But like, you know what I mean? It's going to turn into this orange.
This sounds foul. You haven't even tried it. When did you try this? So it's going to turn into this
like kind of orange egg salad. Don't use too much. Start small and taste it. You need to get your chef
here. You got to like mix it in and like, oh okay that's a little too much or that's too little.
Get it to where you like it. Then two tablespoons of ground brown mustard important. It's the one
with the seeds in it. Don't put the yellow mustard in here. You can do a little bit less if you want
but this is to add a little bit of sweetness and a little bit of spiciness to it. Not heat but you
know that like kind of nose tang that brown mustard has. After this, and remember you're
folding this in. Do a little bit. Don't do it all. It adds kick but not heat. Exactly. You get it.
Thank you. Kick but not heat. That's the point. That's the purpose. One teaspoon, don't read this
wrong. One teaspoon of onion powder. One teaspoon of salt. One teaspoon of pepper. Not more than that.
Actually probably less than that. I explain in the next paragraph. This is why it's so hard
to write this because some people think I don't want it to be salty. I want it to be more salty.
I wish it was more mustardy. By the way this is just for 12 eggs. Just salt. Just regular table salt.
Why did this take you 26 minutes to write? This took me 15 minutes to write and I was taking a
shit for fucking 20 minutes. Okay? There you go. You want the real story? Sometimes stuff is better
left unsaid. I'm sorry. Anyways, when I'm thinking about teaspoons and tablespoons,
I'm thinking you know when you get the pepper grinder and you go like
how much is that? Is that a teaspoon? It's however many
uh graz seven is. It's six or seven graz of pepper. That's probably a teaspoon. Is that less? Half
a teaspoon? If I would if I go like that would be about probably one teaspoon, right? Let me just,
I gotta... I gotta fix this. This is wrong. Don't take this recipe yet. It's not right. It's not
accurate yet. Hold on. That's that's more accurate. I- I'm just gonna be honest. Just to taste. Yeah,
Yeah, but, okay. Yeah, yeah, yeah, that's a good idea. That's true. That's true. True, true, true, true, true.
Add salt to taste. Add—but this—wait, this is way too much onion powder. Hold on. How much is this?
How much is a teaspoon of onion powder? Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait. Is that way too much?
I don't know measurements. A pinch? Add two—add three pinches of onion powder.
It's like you just add, like, a shake, shake, shake, shake, shake, and then mix it in. I don't know. I just do—
That's—chefs don't keep track. Baking is an art. It's not a science. Is that a correct thing to say?
Back in, like, the fucking 1200s, you know how many types of bread they figured out by just trying different things?
Half of the breads that you love to eat were done because somebody was like,
I don't fucking know. Let's try it like this. Who cares? Okay. So this is important.
This is all to taste. That's fine. Get a bulky roll. Preferably an onion roll. A bulky onion roll.
You know the ones. You've seen them. You want to spread that egg salad onto the bottom of the bun.
And then you're going to add one slice of cheddar cheese. I don't care what kind it is.
It could be sharp or even mild, depends on what you want. If you like sharp cheese, that's fine.
When this is done, you're going to take a bite and you're going to—taste it as you go.
I don't know what an onion roll is. Yes, you do. This sounds so damn good.
Yes, it does. It actually does. You are going to take a bite of this and go,
oh, okay, this is like kind of good. I have had egg salad before and I've made my own and I finally got it to where I like it.
What the hell is sharp cheese? Stop. Stop gaslighting me. Why did you leak this?
Because I don't know. I just was like, I want to get this down in case I get hit by a bus.
What if I—you know what I mean? What if I get hit by a bus? No one would ever know what this was.
Okay. So, you got it? You good? Okay.
What does Ball Fondler have to say about it? Curious.
Everyone wants Ball Fondler's take, so we're going to get it.
This isn't funny anymore, bro. Just play the game. And then they at me.
Egg salad Andy. 12 eggs. You really fell off since the last stream.
School homework Andy. He's cold.
You really fell off from two days ago?
You peaked at Pac-Man. All right, let's go.
This is a family recipe of a spinoff shitty sitcom. Where do you want to go?
You got the recipe. And by the way, all those anti-sorcery Andes that don't give it to them.
Don't let them have that recipe. That's for you. Only for like the 10k that are here right now.
That's for all the anti-sorcery Andes. That's not for them.
This is just eggs with mayo in it. Did you not read the part about the brown mustard did?
Did you not read the part about the Tabasco? Did you not read the part about how the consistency needs to be?
Do not read the part about the sharp cheddar cheese? Did you not read the part about how it needs to be folded?
And the ingredients going.
One at a time. Do not read the part about the dry ingredients go last.
Did you not read the part about it has to be not a paste? If it's runny, you got it wrong.
Did you not read the part about it has to be twelve eggs? Which part of the image you did not read.
All right. Looks like we're going to go east. 12312 three one.
One, two, three.
All right, we're going three.
Let's go.
We can't see your mouse?
Oh, well it was one, two, three.
Yeah, you could.
All right, the line of the road curves gently
as you follow it.
The moon moves slowly across the sky like a lidless eye.
The plains are wide and empty.
To the south, the fissure yawns.
Wide are here and furiously deep.
To the north, the land climbs a low rocky rise.
It's a streamer's choice.
We're gonna go up, off the road.
You leave the road and cut across the bone gray plain.
You're climbing up a low rocky rise,
not a natural outcrop as you first assumed,
but rather a pile of large carved blocks
over which the dust of many ages has blown.
Let's go.
You peer in between the largest stone blocks
and shift a few smaller ones out of the way.
You see nothing.
And then the glimpse of blue shines through.
Is it a gem?
A small lizard scurries out
from between two of the fallen blocks.
What can we do here?
Mud, great quicksand.
I could probably, yeah, I could do big and move the rocks.
I could do six, clone the caster.
So there's just six of us.
How, show how what it looks like so I get it right.
I don't have a picture of it.
Dopp is open locks and doors.
I probably, it was just, let's do, I'm thinking big.
Big or six, we'll do six, six is fun.
Yeah, we'll clone the caster, make it quicker.
Looking to the constellations overhead,
you craft a spell and five clones step out from behind you
forming a semi-circle.
Form a human pyramid, for fun?
All right, we're gonna form a human pyramid.
You organize a human pyramid
hoping to get a view across the land.
You place three clones abreast
then two more on top of them.
And finally you scrambled to the top yourself.
The view across the plane is incredible.
All right, let's look to the mountains.
You look over at the mountains,
but before you can make anything out, the spell fades.
Your clones vanish and you land
in a painful heap on the ground.
That's great.
I'm just gonna get huge.
Let's do big.
You turn the starlight into alignment around you
for a moment it seems nothing will happen
then suddenly you begin to grow
to three times your normal size.
Your clones grow at the same time.
Wait, I thought they were gone.
What is this?
I thought they vanished.
Should we make a pyramid as being huge?
All right, let's clear the rubble.
You and your five enormous,
wait, does it vanish as in they ran away?
Like they just let me fall?
You and your five enormous clones set out
about clearing the rubble.
Working in threes, you're able to shift the stones aside.
After a few minutes of work,
you've uncovered the blue crystal.
All right, take the blue crystal.
Gradually you shrink back down to your normal size.
One by one, your clones vanish.
You touch the blue crystal
and suddenly you feel yourself ascending.
Oh, you can teleport.
That's right.
It's fast travel on this.
Okay.
So, I mean, I think the idea is I teleport back here,
move this over here to the bridge when it's back normally
or this way, go back to the cave.
I could move this, go back to the cave.
Let's see, let me see.
Let me see, let's take a look.
Moment later, you're tumbling downwards from the sky,
the wind rushing past your face.
You are certain to shatter into a thousand pieces
and suddenly you're on the ground once more.
You're back on top of the stone tower
in the area near the southern cliffs.
The beacon is lit, it's polished crystal eye-blazing.
So, we could go like this.
We didn't do over here back in the past.
We could fix the bridge and kind of go across it
and see what happens or we could...
Ah, right.
Okay, so we could fix it and then have another one lit
and have it go somewhere else.
I think, okay, so if I go like this
and then I can go to this one and aim this one that way.
Let's do that.
Now we're in the past
and I'm gonna aim this back at the bridge.
Okay.
The fall from the sky is just as terrifying as before
but you land safely once again.
Takes a moment for you to regain your breath, incredible.
You're atop a stone tower which did not exist before
in the northern plains of Barubak.
Set into the floor here is a bearing track
on which a brass cylinder rests.
A blue crystal is set in.
You pat yourself down, check yourself over.
You're in one piece if a little breathless.
You waste no time in turning your attention
to the contraption on the rooftop.
The cylinder is similar to the one you saw earlier
although this one is slightly narrower
and about a cubit long.
On one of the side of the turret,
on one side of the turret floor is a trap door
which is closed.
So yeah, now we can go like this.
Okay.
I think I like this right now.
What do you think?
Should I go back to the bridge here?
Back in the past?
See what's here?
Or aim it this way or aim it this way.
Oh shit.
What do you think?
The one piece is real.
The one, what's the, what do you mean?
Go find the earwigs in the past.
I think I'm gonna do this
because then when I go across the bridge,
we can check out this area
and then in the present,
we can go check out the cave too
because I can get it aimed at the right angle.
Yeah, there we go.
All right.
That makes sense to me.
What about the trap door?
Can do big again.
Can do fog, summon darkness, force field.
Is there a sus?
There's no sus.
What about, I mean, I can probably just open it.
Don't give it up.
Give it up.
Turn your attention from the beam
to the trap door in the floor.
You need to get down from here somehow.
The trap door has an iron ring for a handle.
You give it a sharp tug, but it doesn't move an inch.
Where are we right now?
All right.
I'm thinking, correct me if I'm wrong here, audience.
We go up, explore all this in the,
we go up and explore all this in the past.
Wrap back down this way.
Check this out in the past.
End up at the cave in the present.
And then come back around this way
and potentially either go out here or come back up here.
That's not good?
Already did the cave.
We did, but remember in the past,
we went back and we talked to the sorcerer, sorceress lady.
I just made your egg salad and it tastes like gasoline.
It would have taken you longer to do that and know you're a liar.
All right, I like that idea.
Let's go check out this place up here.
You know how I know it's bullshit?
Because it takes at least 12 minutes to boil the eggs.
And then it takes like 15 to 30 plus minutes.
It's like a 20 minute ordeal to peel those eggs.
And then it takes another puppy five to 10 minutes
to fold in all the ingredients, you're a liar.
All right, should I twist it?
I'm gonna twist it.
You turn the iron ring, it doesn't shift.
Twist it again.
Undeterred, you twist the ring again,
but don't seem to get anywhere.
Twist it again.
You tug the ring, but you seem to be wasting your time.
Tug, twist it again.
Once again, you fiddle with the metal ring,
but however hard you wriggle and wrench at the trap door,
nothing is happening.
Give up, no, I wanna cast a spell.
No, no, no, no, no, no, go back.
I wanna, hold on, go back, go back.
This doesn't count as a rewind.
Okay, we're good.
There we go, all right, we're good.
All right, the trap door, open the trap door.
Wait, I thought, there is no cast a spell.
Oh, okay, I can do it here.
Let's do dop, it's easiest, right?
Dop is pretty much guaranteed.
Open locks and doors.
All right, you weave the spell and turn the spell's focus
into the trap door at your feet.
It shivers and rattles as though the wood was a beetle
trying to take flight.
But it seems unable to escape whatever is holding it shut.
The spell fades with the trap door still sealed.
What?
Did I just get huge and stomp through it?
All right, you bind the magic quickly,
swelling to the height of a tree.
I can't, what?
I can't like stomp through it?
You swing one massive leg over the side of the tower
and hop down to ground level.
Oh, okay, falling, what?
Oh, okay, so I just sprained my ankle.
You hit the ground with a heavy thump.
Gradually, you shrink back down to your normal size.
Looking back up, the tower seems terribly high.
Try the door.
You try the door, but it is locked.
Still, at least this tower has a door.
Oh my God.
It's too much, I only have three stamina.
I don't wanna blow the door off.
Let's stop the door.
Tumblers inside the tower door click.
Then a moment later, they roll over completely
and the door swings open.
The night air is cold.
The air is like ice.
So I spent all that time with the trap door.
Okay, we'll go inside.
You step through the tower door into the cool shade within.
Who knows how long it has been
since anyone last set foot inside, okay?
You stand in a wide, cool cavernous space.
The roof disappears off above you,
dimly echoing your footsteps.
The air is musty, perhaps undisturbed for centuries.
The room is filled with a thin, sickly smell.
You take a deep lungful of the stale air,
smelling something sweet and musty
that takes a moment to place.
It is the smell of tombs, graveyards, and crypts,
but not of decay.
Then you place it.
This is the Elbertson egg salad family recipe,
one of the most cherished secrets in all of Aniland.
This is the smell of dark vine,
a thick climbing plant that grows only in dark places.
Thankfully, it's not harmful
unless eaten in very large quantities.
Okay.
I'm casting a lot of spells.
Heal disease, I don't,
I mean, something's diseased in here, maybe.
Sun, ooh, create light.
I don't wanna do big in here.
I'll get crushed.
Darkness.
I think it's, yeah, let's do sun jewel.
You craft the enchantment and the sun jewel in your pack
begins to emit a brilliant, blinding light.
Warm light fills the chamber.
You look around the tower and the light from the jewel.
You make out strange, shadowy shapes
that climb the stonework.
The shapes seem to recede from the light.
They are dark vines, plants that grow only in unlit places.
They form a thick matting across the ceiling.
Let's cut them down.
You climb to the top of the stairs
and hack at the dark vines that grow across the ceilings.
They begin to drip a thick, oozing sap
onto the floor of the tower.
Try to just keep it up.
Search the room.
Yeah, this is probably like poisonous.
Instead of going through the hatch,
you use the light to poke around the corners of the room.
You find little of interest until you stumble over
what appears to be an old traveling pack.
Open it or kick it.
Let's kick it.
You give it an experimental kick.
It does not move, but only rattles a little.
There's gonna be a snake in here.
Is that rattle an adjective
or is that rattle an animal verb?
Do you know what I mean?
Like, what is that?
Is that adjective or verb?
It rattles a little.
Like, oh, my desk rattled.
Or is it like rattle, is it like an animal verb
or is this an adjective
for describing something moving around?
You open the pack and are surprised to find the brand
of the Aniland leatherers inside the top of the flap.
Digging inside, you find two stopped vials.
Examine the purple vial.
You lift the purple vial and shake it in the lift.
Liquid inside is thin, but shines slightly.
You recognize it, of course, blimberry.
You put it in your pack, an excellent find.
What about the brown one?
The brown vial contains a thick oil
that you do not recognize.
Drink it immediately.
Um, maybe I shouldn't take it.
Taste it.
Should I smell it first?
You unstopper the vial.
A heady, woody smell fills your nostrils.
This is an essence of bark,
much like the one you acquired in Carré.
A good thing you did not try to taste it.
You guys better just turn me into a tree or something.
All right, we're gonna keep it, okay?
I need, I'm gonna die.
All right, should I cut the vines or just rest?
This seems like a safe enough place.
This is a calm sheltered place to rest.
You should be protected from the elements
and from any creatures about at night.
You have eaten nothing today, but you have no,
you don't have any food.
And only a single vial of healing blimberry juice.
I kind of have to drink this.
You unstopper your vial of blimberry
and knock it quickly back.
You feel a little better,
and all traces of hunger are soon gone.
Then you stretch out and rest.
You seem guarded here, and you do not dream.
You reach the Northern Plains and met Elthera,
the mystic again.
That's who was in the cave, if you remember.
The sun may have risen outside,
but the only windows here are thin slots.
I almost coughed.
The inside of the tower is cavernous and empty,
but for a stone staircase that spirals around the walls.
Dark vines have grown up the inside of the tower
and form a thick matting across the ceiling.
Should I just keep cutting these?
I feel like that's a bad idea.
That's definitely a bad idea.
No, we don't do face cam for sorcery.
I need you to be immersed into the text in the story.
Not looking at like the boogers coming out of my nose.
No, we're gonna move on.
I think that's a bad idea.
You step out into the sunlight at the base of the tower.
You march onwards.
You have been wandering the backlands
for three days already.
You've not crossed the ridge,
but we did back in the present.
All right, so do you guys like that plan
of kind of go up this way and then down and then up here?
You guys like that plan?
We'll go up, circle back around, cross the bridge,
check out what this is and check out what this is.
That's a good idea.
Let's go for it.
All right, we don't need to pull.
Let's check out this.
You walk for half an hour across the grassland,
keeping your eyes and ears open.
The light from your sun jewel pulses twice and fades.
The air moves a little, still icy, but fresh.
In the middle of a tended field,
you come across a lone hut.
Peering through the grimy windows of the hut,
you see a stooped young boy sitting by a fire.
He's squatting on the ground, intent on something,
perhaps drawing symbols in the dust.
Hmm, we don't wanna get it.
Oh, and important, your egg salad may be gassy.
It smells bad.
That's eggs.
Eggs are a gassy food.
You don't blame me for that.
It's a gassy food.
You ate eggs, you ate eggs.
Eggs are gassy.
It's a gassy food.
Oh, by the way, I never said you have to make this recipe.
I just said if you're ever gonna make egg salad,
you could try it if you feel like it.
You don't have to.
It's delicious to me and my family, okay?
My family.
Okay, peering, yeah, yeah, yeah, let's go in the hut.
You push open the door.
The boy jumps to his feet, grabbing at a crooked stick.
Who are you?
The boy demands the stick in his hand is solid oak
and raised, ready to swing for your head.
What do you want with me?
Put that stick down before I beat you with it.
I mean you no harm.
Who are you?
Um, how about who are you?
Just a shepherd, he replies, stick wavering in his hand.
Who are you?
I am a traveler.
I am a great and powerful sorcerer.
I'm a friend.
I'm a, I don't wanna,
I don't tell anybody any of this stuff.
I'm a traveler.
These plains are wild and empty.
You must be tired.
Please, come and share the fireside.
It's all I have, but you're welcome to it.
He proposes stick by the hearth and gestures in welcome.
It is not much.
Thank you.
You live out here?
You nod to the boy and take a seat beside him.
The peaceful atmosphere and gentle warmth
is most restorative.
Where are you from?
Do you plate ice?
Have you heard of the seven serpents?
I'm on my way to Manpang.
Do you play dice?
You ask, reaching into your pack for your stones.
The boy shakes his head sharply.
My father plays dice with my mother
and it does nothing but make them argue.
I don't touch those things.
You put the dice away.
Ah, okay, whatever, kid, fine.
I was gonna put 20 gold on the table, but you know, whatever.
Where are you from?
Karima, in the foot of the mountains near the long bridge.
The boy lifts his crook once more,
but uses it only to poke at the fire.
Near the long bridge, okay.
Wait, what's it doing here?
What can you tell me about the towers?
The beacons?
They were built by sorcerers, of course.
I'm not sure what they're for,
but they're meant to keep us safe.
Safe from what?
I don't know.
My mother says rock falls, but I don't understand that.
Where would all the rocks fall from?
But the archmage can see the future,
so I'm sure what he did was for the best.
I can also see the future.
You tell the boy, you nod.
Would you like to see yours?
The boy nods nervously.
Wait, I don't have the thing.
I don't actually have the crystal, right?
What can I do?
Would you like to see your future?
Just cause slowness.
Open locks and doors?
Cause sleepiness?
Oh, I can read his mind.
Tell sap.
Oh, that's awful.
Cause depression?
That's so evil.
I could, but I can't.
Just freak him out.
Would you like to see your future?
And then touch the kid's hand,
and like, oh, I'm doing, oh, I'm floating.
What did you do?
Oh, you must be a sorcerer.
And the kid gets wicked excited,
and is like, yeah, I did that, yeah.
Oh my God, you're a sorcerer.
Oh, ah.
And you fall down.
Oh, you got me.
Like we're playing, yeah, that's perfect.
Don't ruin his life.
No, I'm gonna read his mind and then say what he says.
Okay, drawing the skull cap from your pack,
you cast the spell.
In his thoughts, you hear the prophecy
he is expecting to hear.
The same as that of Elthira,
of a desert wilderness and the death of all the land.
You take off the skull cap once more.
The boy watches you expectantly.
I see you as an old man with seven children.
I see you as a great warrior fighting the giants.
Or tell the truth.
I feel like this is game progress.
This is, laugh out loud, it ends here and I leave.
I see this land as a pale and empty desert.
You do not need to lie to know the future
of this place after all.
That's what Elthira saw as well.
The whole land and the marsh between the mountains,
a forest and the bridge to Iqlala destroyed.
Seems he does not feel like talking further,
but turns to stare away into the fire.
You bid him farewell and leave the hut.
You should have sapped him.
You still caused depression after all.
I didn't mean, whatever.
As the morning moves on, the wind begins to rise.
You walk through wide fields, thick with crops.
A few goats graze on low hillocks on the land,
watching you with beady eyes.
This place seems to be rich,
far richer than the villages west of Kare.
Seems impossible that it could ever become a place
as desolate as the backland.
Looking south, you see the tower.
Further on in that direction,
a river rushes through the plains.
You stride on through the long swishing grass.
Then from somewhere close at hand, you hear a voice.
Someone there, you got any water?
Have you?
Turns out, Yaz caused invisibility.
Is that all I could do?
Jig is available.
Hell is available too.
I could do sus.
Jig, Jig always works.
I tried to make your eggs and I got divorced.
I feel like there's a lot more going on
than simply you made egg salad.
I'm sorry, I don't have very much advice for you.
All right, let's do Jig.
Reaching up to the constellations above,
you create the spell.
Pulling out your bamboo flute and starting to play,
you soon begin to hear an exhausting popping sound
from somewhere in the grass.
Follow the sound.
The sound turns into a series of wet clicks,
which you follow until you all but stumble over a head
planted in the soil like a cabbage.
It is maniacally rolling from side to side
and flaring its nostrils as it tries to dance.
You keep playing until the spell finally fades.
The head in the ground is now quite exhausted
and looks almost ready to fall asleep.
Wake it up.
You squat down and greet the head, its eyes open wide.
Greetings, do you have any water?
I'm dying of thirst after all that dancing.
What are you?
What are you doing down there?
I'll get you some water.
You peer down at the head.
It is a man's, if an animate decapitated head
can have a gender.
He has shaggy hair, brown eyes and parched lips.
He's not shaved for some time.
No need to stare or stare all you like,
but give me some water.
What are you doing down there?
The head wiggles its eyebrows,
perhaps the equivalent of a shrug.
Still one too many goats.
Ishtar is a great place,
but they don't take well to goat stealing.
It gets their goat, as they say,
gets their back right up.
So you're a criminal.
You are surprised.
I was, but I'm reformed now.
Not that it does much good, of course.
It's too late for your soul.
Uh, reformed how?
You've been punished then.
Well, I didn't bury myself down here.
Did I?
Listen, give me any water or don't you?
Give him poison.
Give some poison.
I could have just put stuff,
a grenade in the hole with him and then pull it and run.
What the fuck?
I don't have a pebble.
Are you kidding me?
Cause quicksand?
What am I gonna like pour quicksand in his mouth
or something?
What the hell?
Should I read his mind?
I don't have the items for it.
I would have thrown a grenade at him.
I don't have the item.
Let's do the tried and true sus.
You spin the constellations into the shape around you
and a steady voice begins to speak to you.
It informs you that the head is of no danger
and can only be helped and be helpful.
Reassured you wait for the spell to fade once more.
Please, I'm really thirsty.
Why would I poison now?
Sus just told me that he's helpful.
I'll go get some water.
Do tell?
Well, sus can always be trusted.
No danger and can only be helped and be helpful.
So, sus usually doesn't lead us wrong.
I can get you some.
The head cracks like a tapped egg into a smile.
Bless you, stranger.
You've got a good soul.
Well, good souls.
What do I get in return?
The head wiggles its eyebrows.
All right, I'm not sure what I can do for you.
Have you heard of the seven serpents?
I want to lie and say yes, but I won't.
I've never heard of any serpents
and seven sounds like a lot.
What do you know about this place?
What, this place?
It's a punishment field.
I have no idea how many other unfortunates are here.
You can't even see them.
And they're quickly learned to be quiet.
Why are they quiet?
Sound attracts animals.
Lynch bugs, badu beetles, harpies.
Not like we can defend ourselves.
The head smiles thinly.
Look, I can't keep talking.
I'll die of thirst.
I don't know what you are.
I thought I told you I'm a thief, but they caught me.
The head's eye twitches as though itching.
Scratch the head's forehead.
You kneel down and scratch the head above its left eye.
It lets out a gasp of approval, murmuring.
You have no idea how that feels, stranger.
The head mumbles something, but keeps its lips closed.
It clearly isn't going to speak any further.
Just dig up the head?
All right, go get water or dig up the head.
Let's get a poll.
This is just one or two.
One, two, one, two.
Are we going to, I'll get you water
or are we gonna dig up the head?
Water, he's gonna die.
Wouldn't it be quicker if I dug up the head
and then he, well, maybe he can't really move.
Kick his head like a football, oh my God, dude.
All right, we're going one.
I'll get you that water.
Not like I'm going anywhere.
All right, so we gotta remember that this is where,
right here is where that head is.
So keep that in mind.
I won't remember, so you guys have to.
All right, let's head up here.
You make your slow way across the fertile prairie,
enjoying the soft chirping of the insects.
The sun continues to climb the steep sky.
Nearby, you hear the sound of hammers on stone.
You approach the sound to find a group of workmen
erecting a scaffold.
They ignore your approach.
As you approach the scaffold,
you are stopped by a large spin wearing a metal helmet.
Stay back, big rocks high up.
What are you building?
This seventh beacon.
This one prevent collapsing in the cloud mountains.
Also make weather nice.
He turns to glance over his shoulder
and shout incomprehensible insults
at a group of worker spins
who are clamoring about in the upper reaches of the frame.
Uh, I need to cross the mountains to the east.
You tell him.
He's the bridge we built for this.
The scaffold sits in a deep pit in the ground,
which is being used to hold foundations.
How does this beacon prevent avalanches?
Magic is magic.
We know this high, this wide, this strong,
strong enough to hold olephant.
The rest is them problem.
He jerks a thumb in a general eastward direction.
Who's problem?
He jerks his clawed thumb eastwards again,
but seems reluctant to say any more than that.
There's a crash from the site
and the spin turns around and roars
stomping back toward the construction.
Follow.
You follow him curiously
and see that one of the bamboo supports
has bent and buckled under the weight of two spins
who are now clinging on like spider monkeys
above the pit below.
The spin to whom you were talking to
is scratching his belly
and trying to work out what to do.
Wait and see what he does or help them.
I think he's just gonna let them die.
Help them.
You step forward intending to assist,
then realize you do not know what to do.
The two creatures are some height up
and swaying violently back and forth.
The leader is scratching his chin, clearly thinking hard.
You open your eyes to begin a spell,
but the spin knocks your hands down on reflex.
None that, we engineers.
Okay, with that, he goes over to the edge of the pit
and collects two unused bamboo rods
and lays them down across the pit.
He then gathers another two
and you quickly realize he's building a support framework
to allow the stranded spins to climb down.
You take advantage of this distraction
to walk around the site
and poke into the materials they have in their stores.
It's mostly as you might expect.
Bamboo, hardwood for cutting joists
and various hammers, chisels and lathes.
If there is to be stonework, that must be arriving later.
Behind everything is a small metal box
with a catch on the lid and a gourd of water.
Take the gourd.
You take the gourd and test the water inside.
It seems fresh enough.
It is presumably belonging to one of the workmen.
You put it in your pack,
remembering the parched head in the fields to the east.
You squat down and open the box
to reveal a small blue crystal that is currently dark,
but looks very similar to the ones
you have seen previously on the tower.
Hold on a second.
They're building another tower.
So in the present, this would be a tower.
Should I let them just continue to build it?
Or should I take it and then put the gem in later?
You see what I'm saying?
Because that's the blue crystal that activates the towers.
I think I'm just gonna leave it.
I hope this is correct.
I don't think they'll, they won't build it.
Yeah, I'm gonna leave it.
Yeah, why would they finish it without the gem?
Stop this tower from being built.
Fuck the timeline over.
I'm gonna leave it.
I feel like that's a bad idea.
You flip the box closed once more.
Whatever the jewel is,
it's presumably important to the builders.
The rest of the materials on the site are uninteresting,
except for a sharp, edged hewing ax.
Ooh, I'll take that.
You pick it up and quietly slip it into your pack.
It's time to go.
You move on, leaving the workers to their task.
All right, let's do this.
Let's give the water.
It is hot now.
You are starting to sweat under your cloak.
You walk back through the long, lush fields.
You look for the head.
Are you there?
Down here.
You find it in the grass.
Did you bring water?
Please say you did.
Give water to the head.
You open your pack and take out the water gourd.
The head follows your every movement
with insatiable curiosity.
Then it throws back its upper jaw in excitement.
You squat down and pour the water into its mouth.
It coughs and splutters, drinking to clear its mouth,
but not wanting to stop.
Wonderful.
You have no idea how wonderful.
That'll keep me going another day, at least.
Dig up the head.
I'll get you out of there, you declare.
That would be a great idea.
I'd be more grateful than you can imagine.
Grab him by the head and pull.
Just grab him by the skull and just lift.
What can I do here?
Oh no, that's a bad idea.
Protect from magic?
What if there's a, wait, hold on, wait, wait, wait, wait.
Is it possible that there's a spell here
where if he gets out,
it just is gonna explode or something?
Like a saw trap?
Maybe I should do magic defense.
We could do big, we could do six.
I don't, oh, I could teleport him out of the hole.
That's funny.
It's dirt, just dig.
We'll do six.
Six, oh look, if it explodes, it kills one of the clones.
Whatever, I don't care.
Five clones step out from behind you,
forming a semi-circle.
Dig up the head.
Working together, you dig the head out of the ground
in no time.
To find he is in fact a man
buried up to his neck in the ground.
Blessed throth, I can hardly believe it.
Turning to you, he lowers his eyes in solemn acknowledgement.
I am quite clear.
I owe you my life.
I will repay the debt any way that I can,
though I have little to offer.
One by one, your clones vanish.
He pats down his pockets.
I have nothing to offer you.
Search him.
Grabbing his arm, you quickly search him
to establish the truth.
Sure enough, in one pocket,
you uncover a fine pearl ring.
He shrugs, giving a half smile,
but lets you take it.
Your search is done, you step back.
He nods.
And so, we are quits.
Be well.
Then with a flamboyant wave,
he takes off across the field at a run.
After a few paces, he seems to trip on something,
but quickly gets up,
apologizes to something you cannot see,
and is gone into the mists of the backlands.
What a wacky dude.
There's another head.
Pearl ring, I think that actually is a big deal.
Hold on.
Something needs a pearl ring, doesn't it?
Yaz.
Oh, I can go invisible now.
It is Yaz.
Casting the spell while wearing a pearl ring
will render the caster invisible
to any reasonably intelligent creature.
Less intelligent creatures
will only be partially convinced,
and creatures with ears will still be able
to hear the caster when they move.
Okay, so it works less on low intelligence.
Yaz.
Slay.
Cool.
Okay.
So we know what's up this way.
I was gonna wrap around.
So we're gonna wrap around here.
I'm gonna go this way.
You carry on traveling across the lush grassland,
long grass brushing your boots.
Heat beats down from an empty sky.
A clatter of wheels makes you turn your head.
A cart is approaching,
driven by a broad figure in a long cloak.
Greet the figure, step aside, duck out of sight.
Should I just do the Red Dead Redemption 2 thing?
Hey, stranger.
Hey, hold on now.
Eh, fuck you.
You're a piece of shit.
You're an asshole.
What's wrong with you?
Don't want it.
I'm only kidding with you.
What's wrong with this guy?
Piece of work.
Moron.
Idiot.
Hey.
No, I'm kidding.
Let's greet.
You step into the cart's path and raise a hand.
The figure raises a fist in return.
Stranger, do you want blood?
Stay back.
What manner of creature are you?
What manner of blood?
What are the response?
You call.
The cart driver booms a cheerful laugh.
All kinds.
She throws her hood and waves towards the back of the cart.
I am the butcher of Badubak, stake of olephant,
blue hide of snatacat, ribs of goats.
Your stomach rumbles at the thought.
What do you fancy?
The driver gestures with a brandish cleaver
to the back of her cart,
from which a thin river of blood trickles.
Okay.
I think I can buy food.
What do you recommend?
She considers that for a moment.
The snatacat meat is the rarest, of course.
And if you've never tried invisible steak,
then you should, just for the experience.
It disappears from sight the more you eat it.
But bah, olephant tastes the best.
I have a lot of money.
Let's buy something.
I'll buy something from you.
She beams with pleasure.
What'll it be?
The olephant steak is seven pieces,
blue hide is 10.
The steaks are bloody and raw
and will be no good without cooking.
That's a lot.
That's like all my money.
That's too much.
The butcher nods sadly.
Then I wish you well, traveler,
but I am no charity.
Oh, wait, oh no.
Zap, the cart.
Wait, oh yeah, I'm just gonna go invisible.
She'll just drive by.
Yap, talk with animals.
Wait, there's something in the back?
Alive?
Is something in the back of this alive an animal alive?
Talk with animals?
Pulling up the green wig,
you put it on and cast the spell,
but the spell only works on animals.
So there's no effect other than the butcher
looking at you in surprise.
Is that supposed to distract me?
It won't work.
Oh shit, it's raw meat.
Oh no, wait, go back, go back, go back.
Rewind, I wanna rewind.
Trying to talk to raw meat.
I don't know if there was a, I don't know.
No, I'm going back.
Okay, cool, what do you recommend?
Yeah, that's too much.
Okay, what else can I do?
God, oh, I could pretend to be God.
Jig, I wonder how well Jig would work here.
Law, she's, okay, a non-intelligent creature.
That's not gonna work.
It's probably Jig.
That makes sense, right?
I can just have all the food.
What else is there?
What if I go invisible?
Can I just walk around and like take stuff?
I'm doing it.
Pulling the pipe from your pack,
you weave your enchantment.
The butcher's expression turns from surprise to horror
as she finds herself dancing involuntarily,
arms waving this way and that.
I'm a respectable butcher.
She croaks before whooping twice and spinning on the spot.
Stop this.
Okay, if I, before whooping like woohoo and spinning,
he's flossing.
I wonder, okay, stop.
All right, see, can I get some 50% off?
I feel like it's, okay, if I stop, she's gonna kill me.
If she dances more, then maybe I could get some food.
You keep dancing until she begins
to wobble at the knees and stumble.
She falls face down, but you keep her arms thrashing
and her feet pounding until she is fast asleep,
still slowly dancing in the grass.
Oh my God.
You lower the, wait, she hit her face on the ground?
You take three joints of raw meat
from the back of the cart.
It is all you can handle before your stomach begins to turn.
You need to cook raw meat.
All right, I'm gonna go this way and then down.
Oh, I think we passed through the spell.
You continue across the prairie.
Birds wheel overhead.
Slowly, the sun begins to make its way back down the sky.
The paths through the field runs north to south,
with another track leading away to the east.
Looking east, the path winds away towards tended fields,
and you can make out the small hut.
North, the mountains curve round,
creating a secluded corner.
You can just about make out the scaffolding
and the spin workman.
It is a pleasant enough place though,
which to stroll, you continue to walk.
All right, we're good, so I'm gonna just go back down.
Anytime you hear that sound,
that means we're changing times.
You walk on across the grassland
until you meet the edge of an old road.
The wind picks up as the evening draws on.
The route winds and wiggles as it follows the line
of the towering western cliffs.
You stride forward.
We'll go back to the bridge.
You step off the clear road
and walk across the now empty plain.
Clouds rumble as they roll across the dimming sky.
It'll be dark soon.
Back to the fissure.
The sun is now in the lowest quarter of the sky.
Soon it will be dark.
You follow the old road to the edge of the fissure.
The bleak plains stretch away once more.
Behind you, wind whistles through the fissure.
Keep going.
You waste no time.
Oh, is it in the wrong spot?
Shit, is it in the wrong spot?
Hold on.
I think maybe it has to be here.
I think so.
All right, you continue following the road.
As you walk, the paving improves.
It becomes smoother.
Another night begins.
You should try to find a place to sleep,
especially after so much walking on an empty stomach.
You stride across an open stretch of meadow,
the river to one side, babbling and chattering,
and the warm night covering the view in the other direction.
In the near distance floats the sounds of singing
and feasting.
It must be a village nearby.
Paul Fondler wants you to put Family Guy
in the top right of the screen.
No, I'm sorry, I can't do that.
That's literally illegal.
Put like an episode of Family Guy here.
I'm just gonna get claimed
and the stream's gonna get turned off.
It's on YouTube for free.
I think some of you guys don't understand
copyright rebroadcasting laws.
Just because it's on YouTube
doesn't mean I can stream it to Twitch.
I can't do that.
That's not how it works.
Oh, hey, it's on YouTube, so I'll just wait.
It's on YouTube, so let's just watch Family Guy.
I'm gonna get shut down in a second.
Paul Fondler is getting a little easy, Paul Fondler.
You have been unbanned, but keep in mind,
your power, you're waving some power around here.
You gotta be careful.
Put Family Guy in the corner.
You've got some power here,
and I'm just gonna tell you that, be careful here.
All right, let's listen.
You stop to listen to the carousing,
trying to place which direction it's coming from.
But with the winds tossing this way
and that through the grass, it's hard to place.
Night birds chatter through the sky.
All right, we need to rest.
Maybe I can cook the food.
No, I can't.
Laying your pack down on the flagstones,
you try to settle despite the cold.
You've not eaten today,
but there's nothing you can do to fill your belly.
You close your eyes and let your tiredness overtake you.
You dream you are a young boy once more,
lying on your back near the waterfalls of chawberry wood.
Gentle spray dusts your face.
You laugh and a droplet lands in your open mouth.
But when you wipe away your lips,
you find there is a slug there.
Spit it out.
You spit it out, but more and more slugs appear
until your mouth is thick with them and you are gagging.
There seems nothing you can do to clear your mouth.
Chew them up.
Reluctantly, you begin to chew the sweet, thick slugs
into a mass of flesh and slime.
More slugs pour over your face and eyes and you blink,
only to find a slavering bristlebeast standing over you.
Its spittle is drooling into your open mouth.
Rock turned to stone.
Talk with animals.
Pulling out the green wig, you put it on and cast the spell.
The bristlebeast's snapping jaws translate quickly
into a clear language.
Are you my mother?
Can you feed me as my mother would?
I am your mother.
I am your mother, you reply in a cooing noise,
clicking your tongue for emphasis.
Mother, you have become so very ugly.
Oh, you've grown so much.
You have grown.
Yes, I have.
The bristlebeast puffs up with pride.
Oh, I have some questions for you.
I must ask you some questions, my dear child.
The beast nods, but you can feel the spell starting to fade.
Where are the seven serpents?
How do I reach Mampang?
How do I defeat the serpents?
How about, how do I defeat the serpents?
Eat them, the bristlebeast replies.
The spell fades.
The creature begins to look around with confusion,
trying to locate its mother's voice.
In its search, it scurries away along the road.
You are safe and alone once more.
Oh, we can't have...
I wonder if the bristlebeast shows up later.
Eat them.
That's such a funny response.
By the way, why would I ask questions like that?
That's the exact response that we would have gotten.
Well, we don't have to fight anything.
We're safe.
All right, no new clues day four.
The sound of the river chatters around you.
You continue on your way.
I mean, we could go this way.
I gotta move these to different places.
Okay, let's go.
Can I not get in here?
Who the fuck is Ball Fondler?
Ball Fondler.
Some people are saying,
you're gonna get sniped again, Ball Fondler.
You're gonna get banned again.
What happened?
Stop snitching.
Leave him alone.
What?
20 of you have said that in the last two minutes.
He asked how many baseballs you can fit.
Bro, that stream was two weeks ago.
Ball Fondler, come on.
Come on, dude, that happened already.
Strike two.
They said, utter lies and pure deceit.
I can assure you, my friend.
Guys, I'm sorry.
Part of the deal with being unbanned was being unbanned.
That's it.
It wasn't you get unbanned,
and then I get to be a genie
that answers every question you ever have
for the rest of the time you're here.
Let's go in the tower.
The inside of the tower is cavernous and empty,
but for a stone staircase.
I gotta go up.
I'm gonna cut the vines.
You slash again at the vines across the roof,
uncovering the underside of the hatch
you saw earlier from above.
It is bolted shut.
The sap now covers your hands and arms.
It begins to cool and solidify.
This is a problem.
I need to do magic.
Uh-oh.
You open your arms wide to raise a spell,
but before you can craft your magic,
your arms set into position.
Your magic fizzles away around you,
and you are left like a statue,
both arms raised above your head.
You are now trapped stiff covered by a solid casing.
Tip myself over.
It is a drastic circumstance
which calls for drastic measures.
Throwing your weight to one side and then the other,
you begin to tip
and finally manage to overbalance toppling
off the staircase.
You tumble to the floor
and the amber casing around your body shatters.
You are free once more.
Oh, thank God.
That was the right move.
Enjoying your regained mobility,
you hurry back up the stairs once more
and pull the trapdoor bolt back.
The hatch to the roof falls open,
letting an array of sunshine.
Now it's time to move on.
You can go back out to the plane
or up to the top of the tower.
All right, cool.
So let's figure out what I wanna do here.
Adjust the beam.
So if I do this,
can I go back?
Or I wonder if I need to,
do I need to teleport to here
and then walk this way?
I feel like that's probably what I need to do.
Maybe you just can't activate it from this side.
If that's the case,
I'm gonna go teleport to this
and then move the thing.
That's probably accurate.
Yeah, that's definitely what I'm doing.
Yeah, that's fine.
All right, let me teleport over there.
And then, because this one has,
we've done all this,
I will move this one to somewhere else.
Over here maybe.
Okay, let's go.
Oh, actually, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
I wanna move this.
You're gonna play Breath of the Wild?
Yeah, eventually.
I don't know when, but eventually.
Oh, shit, what am I doing?
The teleport mechanic is sick.
It's really helpful.
All right, well, no, I can't.
I have to keep this aimed over here.
But I could do this
and then all this stuff over here
that I could go check this out.
So where was the,
this should be done now, right?
This should be done.
Should I go investigate it?
It got destroyed.
What the fuck?
Who destroyed it?
All right, well, whatever.
I'm gonna do this for now
because I wanna be able to go back, so that's good.
So the plan is let's check out this new stuff,
go down to the cave again,
and then up the plan.
That's what we're doing.
What the hell?
You join the road,
the moaning winds finger at your pack and sword.
From behind you, a voice says,
excuse me, turn around.
You whip around to find a small boy
holding a black face mask in his hand.
He pushes it towards you.
I already have one.
Wait, where'd you get that?
Where'd you get that?
You dropped it, the boy says.
Keep it, thank him.
You nod your head and thanks.
The boy smiles and puts the face mask into your hands.
Then he steps back and waits for something.
You squat down into your ankles
to be more at the boy's level.
He's clearly local
and is likely to know a lot about the area.
Where are you from?
You ask the boy.
Kare.
But I run errands all the way to Tin Pang,
sometimes enough talk.
You begin to chug the blimberry in your pack
as fast as you can, breaking every world record.
Where's Tin Pang?
Across the marsh, over the bridge, near the lake.
You can run there in about a day.
The idea that this boy can cross
the entire of the backlands is startling.
This is the most dangerous land you know.
The boy is starting to look twitchy.
Enough talk.
You lose interest in the boy
and stand back to your full height.
Old groans are so boring, the boy complains.
Without another word, you turn and move away.
Just being helpful, the boy shouts from behind you
before he disappears in the other direction along the road.
It's only later you realize he somehow
swiped the cloth skull cap from your pack.
That motherfucker.
I'm going back.
I'm just gonna punch you in the face.
Did I rewind?
Okay, here we go.
Excuse me.
What do I do?
You made the error before.
Why did you fall for it again?
It's been like five, six years.
Should I just attack?
Draw sword.
You draw your sword and the voice yelps.
I'm not attacking you.
I thought you might want this.
He's holding black face mask in his hand.
He pushed it towards you.
Thief.
Suddenly seeing that the top of your pack is open.
Not a thief, you dropped it.
The boy says looking warily, snatch it back.
You snatch back the face mask.
The boy lets you take it with a shrug.
Then he waits for something.
Move on.
No!
Do I have to lose an item here?
All right, what about, okay.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Where'd you get that?
You dropped it.
Okay, thank you.
Okay, offer him a reward.
You look in your pack.
Here, have three gold pieces.
You count out three gold pieces into his palm.
Wow, thank you.
By throth, I'm glad I followed you.
I mean that I was here.
You know what I mean?
Okay, fuck you.
Take my leave.
The final nod.
Do I have to lose this every time?
I'm not going this way.
I need, that cloth skull cap is so important.
Yep, no, fuck that.
I'm going down here and I don't, I don't, I can't.
No, I'm not doing that.
You walk across the prairie.
Rocky outcrops break the ground here and there.
It's a random event and you will always lose the item.
Shit, okay, well, not this time.
I know, I know, I'm playing wrong, I know.
Rocky outcrops break the ground here and there.
And as the trail rises, you are soon walking on bare stone.
As the sun climbs towards its zenith, the winds pick up.
The dusty plains have been transformed to fields.
Though the grass here is littered with rocks
that have tumbled down from the mountain range to the east.
From somewhere close at hand,
a strange whistling noise catches your attention.
The sound is coming from the other side of a large rock.
Seems steady enough.
The sound of a ever running wind.
Let's look around the rock.
You peer around the rock and a strange sight greets your eyes.
Whether a living creature
or a freak weather effect, you cannot tell.
But hovering a short way above the ground
is a swirling twist of air trapped in a cove formed by the rock.
All right, well, that's bad.
A small fly buzzes over the head of the whirlwind.
A moment later, it is sucked in and disappears from sight.
Try talking to the funnel.
Let's talk.
Greetings.
What manner of pestilence are you?
The whirlwind kicks a short distance up into the air
as if leaping, then settles back down again.
A reaction to your voice or merely a chance movement?
Okay, well, yeah.
You pull a goblin tooth from your pack and drop it on the ground,
casting your spell across it.
The tooth erupts into a column of smoke.
And a moment later, a goblin warrior is standing in front of you.
Order it into the whirlpool.
You order the monster to approach the whirlpool.
It strides forward.
Then something happens.
And a moment later, the creature has vanished completely.
The whirlpool itself seems unaffected.
Suddenly from somewhere above you, you hear a voice.
Hanalandr, I bring a message.
Look up.
You look up into your right, scouring the rock face
until you spy a small boy,
leaping from stone to stone like a goat.
I bring a message from Shadrach the hermit.
How can I trust you?
Trust me?
What are you talking about?
I've come from Shadrach.
He leaps closer.
It's about the fire serpent.
He's following you.
He's going to attack you while you sleep.
Shadrach foresaw it.
The boy has scaled halfway down the mountainside now
and is just above the whirlpool in the rocks.
He is about to jump.
Wait, wait, don't jump.
Don't go, don't do that.
Wait!
The boy hovers for a moment,
one foot on the ledge about to jump.
His eyes meet yours.
Then the rock his foot is on slips.
He begins to tumble downwards.
As he falls, you see him pulled through the air
towards the whirlpool.
Look out!
Magic protection?
Huff.
Create wind.
Wait, should I get big and grab him?
Call slowness?
Sense danger.
That would work.
I don't have a zip.
Maybe float?
A fix.
That would probably be the right one.
Protect from magic.
I'm going to do that one.
Let's protect from magic.
Because obviously the goblin didn't get killed.
The goblin disappeared.
There has to be some kind of magical spell here.
Or huff.
Wouldn't he just fall to the ground?
Oh, right.
Not protecting from physics.
Let's do huff.
Create wind.
Because I could just like...
All right, let's try it.
Looking to the stars, you craft the magic,
lifting the gale horn and blowing a loud note.
The wind blows the falling boy sharply backwards
away from the whirlpool.
He lands a little way down the path, momentarily stunned.
Then he's back on his feet and running towards you.
Thank you.
What is that thing?
I don't know, but it does not look safe.
The boy chuckles, clearly untroubled
by how close he came to being sucked into the hole.
Chadrack told me everything.
He says.
He checks things off on his fingers as he speaks.
The fire serpent doesn't like sand.
The water serpent doesn't like oil.
And the moon serpent...
Is scared of the dark.
Can only be killed once a month.
Can only be killed once a month?
Dislikes the light.
He's scared of fire.
The boy replies, remembering.
They are strange beasts, these serpents.
Anything else?
The boy shrugs.
Only good luck.
He says you will need it.
Because the archmage will want to kill you very fast
once you reach the walls of Mampang.
I don't think that was part of the message.
And with that, he is gone.
Running away out of sight and into the mists of the plane.
The funnel is still here.
Should have let him die.
I wouldn't have gotten those tips then.
What are you talking about?
Talk all languages.
Taking the wig from your pack,
you wear it and form your spell.
Then you attempt to talk to the Whirlpool,
but you get no response.
And the whistling sound from within it is unchanged.
You remove the wig once more, still puzzled.
As you consider the Whirlpool,
a creature in an all-covering hood,
lopes into view.
It is carrying something tightly in one hand,
but you cannot make out what.
Watch.
You watch as the creature comes closer,
passing with spitting distance of the Whirlpool.
Whatever they're holding,
it looks like little more than a rock.
What do I do?
Should I say hello?
Shout a warning?
You can see the stranger approaching the Whirlpool.
So quickly, you grab them by the arms
and haul them backwards.
In a surprise, they drop whatever they were holding
and the Whirlpool sucks it anyway.
It sucks it away.
Oh, God damn it.
The creature begins to shout in a language
you do not recognize.
Oh my God, hold on.
Just wait, I gotta put this wig on.
Wait a minute.
Wait, that's not an animal?
You put the wig on and go down on your hands and knees
and start barking at the creature.
Confused, he walks away.
Oh my God, all right, yap, right?
No, it's rap.
Talk all languages.
Removing the green wig,
you pull it onto your head and complete the spell,
but it seems to make no difference to the language
uttered by the creature.
What?
An animal?
Curious, unless this attempt at language
is in fact simply a series of strange noises.
Casting your spell has caused you to open your arms,
releasing the creature.
It dusts itself down.
Apologize?
You raise your hands in apology,
demonstrating that you mean it no harm.
Grumbling, the creature shambles away westwards,
knocking into you as it goes.
Follow the creature.
You follow the creature along the road,
but you have only gone a short way
when it seems to vanish from your sight into the mist.
You step back to the whirlpool, decide where to go next.
What?
Should I do yap?
Wait, should I go back?
Somebody made the egg salad, by the way,
and they said it was really good,
and they have a picture to prove it.
Hold on, can I share that on stream?
Could I share that, the person in the Discord,
can I share that on stream?
Do you mind if I share that?
Oh, they shared it in Discord already, okay.
All right, let me critique this.
Hold on, I'm gonna create,
let me make sure this is correct.
All right, hold on a second here.
All right, I'll tell you, that looks okay, that looks good.
Now you can make it whatever consistency you want, right?
This looks like baby shit.
It's egg salad, it's egg salad.
Stop, they said that this is delicious.
They said it's delicious, confirmed good.
Now let me tell you something.
This is a little wetter for me.
I would have liked it a little less mayo,
just a little, by like maybe 10%, 5%, maybe 10%.
I think you've got the right amount of consistency, though.
That's what I'm looking for.
It's chunks, kinda chunky, a little less mayo.
Confirmed good.
Yeah, don't zoom in, get it off the screen.
Was there any celery in it?
No, no celery.
All right, where are we?
That's what they do, this is what they feed pigs.
What do they feed pigs?
I actually have, okay, I know that pigs eat slop,
but what is it?
What do they feed pigs?
What is in that?
I don't even know what it is.
Everything, but what do you mean everything?
What is it?
It's vegetable slop, but you can't just say slop.
It's vegetable offcuts.
Whole grain oats and vegetable, why is it slop?
When I think of chopped up vegetables,
I don't think of like cement being poured, right?
Why is it like that?
It's whole grains and vegetables.
It's just compost.
It's expired vegetable, meat ophile, spoiled grains.
Okay, I have a follow up question.
Slop is made of 12 eggs, whatever.
You add water to make it edible.
Oats are dry as fuck otherwise.
Okay, so it's mainly oats, like oatmeal.
So it's oatmeal.
Okay, I get it, I get it.
So it's oatmeal with a bunch of other shit
like ground up into it.
All right, so is there a reason why?
How come you don't feed a pig, let's say,
oh yeah, you're on a diet of like fresh vegetables
or something, is there a reason?
How come it's slop?
Why do they eat slop?
It's a slurry of stuff left over that we don't wanna eat,
but it's cheap.
But would it be better if the pig ate better stuff, right?
Why have we pigeonholed pigs into just eating slop?
Does that make any sense?
What would they eat in the wild?
Well, yeah, but who cares?
They like it.
Dude, it's because we're fucked as a species.
There's enough, hold on, there's enough nutrients in there
and they don't care about taste, it's a win-win.
All right, I'm just curious.
I don't know if it's like,
oh, pigs like don't wanna eat slop in the wild
or they just eat slop and that's what they like.
They'll go and eat like mud and dirt
and like shit and stuff, they don't care, right?
Have you ever seen how massive regular pigs get?
Yeah, they get huge.
I actually learned about this in my American history class.
Pigs will literally eat anything.
Before modern waste management,
they were the garbage disposals in the US.
Oh my God.
All right, so the whirlpool is still here.
Pigs are eating Las Vegas casino leftovers
and it's saving the planet.
All right, so should I just walk into this?
Should I send another goblin in?
No, that would be a mistake.
I'm gonna do, hold on, there, this is it.
Safe passage.
Okay, the voice speaks into your thoughts.
It tells you that the whirlwind is a rare thing,
a place with only one direction.
It can be entered, but it cannot be exited
and is best avoided.
Interesting.
It's a rare thing.
I'm going in.
You creep slowly closer to the thing
until you are barely a sword's length away.
It remains in position, spinning rapidly.
From here, you can make out little more about it
except that deep inside something flashes.
Go in.
You reach out a hand above the top of the whirlwind.
The force that exerts downwards is quite strange.
Then suddenly without warning, it gets stronger.
The sound coming from the thing increases
in pitch dramatically.
Should I pray?
Let's pray to the ape.
You close your eyes and raise a prayer to the ape.
Has your request been heard?
You wait to see what will happen.
The force on your hand is getting significantly stronger.
I don't know.
You look to the heavens, hoping to find a spell,
but when you try to pull your hand back to begin casting,
you find you cannot move.
It is too strongly held in place above the whirlwind.
A moment later, the force has tugged your arm
down inside the whirlwind.
From there, you cannot save yourself.
You are trapped inside.
And whatever happens there is so quick
that you lose consciousness before you understand it.
The ape didn't even do anything.
All right, peer around the rock.
There's the whirlwind.
All right, this time we're gonna wait the creature, right?
Try talking to the funnel.
Okay, I bring him, oh shit, I went so far back.
All right, I bring a message.
How can I trust you?
Oh, wait, all right, oh yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
Okay, so what was it?
It was the wind.
These old adventure books are so bullshit.
Like you forgot to investigate a kitchen
and didn't pick up the garlic,
so you die to a vampire five hours later.
That's true, that's funny.
All right, it was Huff.
Okay, I don't know what that was.
It dislikes the light?
Scared of fire.
All right, you guys have to remember this.
Okay, I think we move on.
Unless I can get the item
from whatever that person was holding.
Oh, sure, I'm gonna leave.
I'm gonna die again.
Okay, here we go.
Here comes the creature.
Wave, I'm gonna wave a greeting, right?
Greetings, you declare.
The creature leaps in alarm, arms going wide,
and drops whatever it was holding.
A moment later, the whirlpool has sucked it away.
God damn it, no!
Whatever, follow the creature, he disappears.
Shit, oh, I fucked it up, I'm moving on.
All right, so I wanted to go this way.
Isn't he live here?
You make your way over the grass-covered rocks and boulders
following the trail where you can
and scrambling the rest of the way.
The sun has reached its highest point now.
Out of the shade, the air is baking hot.
Once again, you see the distinctive fishtail rock
sticking up from the earth.
There is no sign of Shadrach the hermit.
The fire outside the cave has burned down to black embers.
You try calling out for Shadrach once more,
but nothing more happens.
Wherever he is, whenever he is, it seems he has moved on.
You march on, feeling the day's first rumblings of hunger
in your stomach.
Checking through your pack, you suddenly stop short.
So, oh, come on, this stupid kid.
Oh, God damn it, I don't think I can do anything here.
If I look around, the little boy is gonna be here
and he's gonna take my cap.
He gets to you if you do the tornado encounter.
All right, well, I'm gonna look around.
You look around, but see nothing.
There is no hole in your pack,
but things do not simply disappear.
Think back.
You think back, racking your brain,
then you remember the creature by the whirlpool.
Oh, my God.
That's, no, it's too far, man.
It is, it's too far.
I fucked it up, it's way too far.
Revenge will be mine.
Lifting your voice to the ape, you vow revenge
should you ever encounter the hooded creature again.
But nothing changes as a result of your cursing.
You will have to find the creature
should you wish to recover the face mask.
God damn it, should I go back?
All right, what if I, I'm walking back here.
You are back at the pool of whirling air.
Shit, he's not here.
God damn it.
Okay, I wanted to go around here.
I wanted to go back here.
So you check the tree.
You wade once more through the long grass.
The woman with whom you spoke earlier has gone.
Let's go ahead and check this.
Have we gone back to the cave?
That's where we're heading now.
You walk on across the prairie until you join an old road.
The sun lowers towards the horizon.
Soon it will be dark.
The road is now well-paved
and bears the marks of many travelers
right down to steaming piles of cattle dung.
Someone seems to have dropped a package here.
Let's take a look.
You look down at the package.
It is a cloth-wrapped parcel
from which comes a strong smell of uncooked fish.
A cart rolls past without stopping.
I'm taking it.
You pick up the parcel,
the fish appear to be in good condition.
It must have fallen from a cart only a few hours before.
But where is there to find fresh fish out here?
I got a lot of raw food.
All right, I need to go this way.
The road curves gently as you follow it.
The sun has all but gone.
This road is a broad serviceable highway
designed for heavy wagons or marching armies.
On either side, grassy fields lead into the distance.
Oh, fuck off.
I don't have a face mask anymore.
From behind you, a voice says, excuse me.
I don't, what is he gonna have?
I don't have a face mask.
If I ignore it, does that matter?
Can I just leave?
I'm gonna ignore.
You ignore it.
Another mirage, like the one you heard before.
Excuse me, are you deaf?
Let it go.
You shake your head and leave the mirage behind,
grumbling to itself.
You continue on your journey.
Did I lose anything?
Where's my skull cap?
Fuck.
What the fuck?
I don't think I can stop this.
Draw my sword.
He's holding a cloth skull cap in his hand.
He pushes it towards you.
Okay, where did you get that?
You dropped it.
Okay, thank you.
He puts the skull cap into your hands.
Then he, okay, goodbye.
Thank you, I appreciate it, and he took the sun jewel.
Fuck this kid.
I'm running away, I'm going the other way.
You follow the road back to the edge of the cliff.
Clouds begin to tumble across the darkening sky.
The cliff face is covered in eyes and you freeze.
Then you realize that they are the eyes of stone icons,
carved from the rock face itself,
clustered as tightly as barnacles on a rock.
A few coins lie at the base of the cliff.
Look at the icons.
The icons are each about the size of a small dog
and are carved wherever they could be made to fit.
So I'm taking advantage of natural colors in the rocks,
buttresses and points.
Each is subtly different.
And though they are stylized,
they are clearly intended to be human.
You look at the scattered coins.
They're an eclectic mixture of metals and currencies.
Many are discolored from their time on the ground.
It is astonishing they have not been taken already.
You spy two or three gold pieces in among them.
A woman approaches across the grass from the road.
She looks familiar from somewhere, but you can't place it.
She nods to you and stops at the cliff face
to look at the icons.
Greetings.
You raise a hand in greeting.
The woman smiles a little shyly, but does not say anything.
She opens her bag and calm as anything takes out a hammer.
That's a threat.
Watch what she does.
You watch the woman.
She turns her attention to the cliff,
choosing a clear spot within reach.
She pulls out a chisel
and begins to splinter away at the rock.
See what she carves.
Slowly the carving takes shape.
Another icon with largest eyes and squat bent legs.
She performs the carving very quickly.
Perhaps she has carved several of these before.
Faster than you expected, she is finished.
The new icon sits in a cluster of other icons
and already looks as though it has always been there.
She steps back, putting the chisel away,
clearly pleased with her work.
What is this icon for?
You ask.
The woman smiles and you realize the brimming
with happiness that she is showing.
She raises her arms in cradling gestures and smiles.
Then she points at the icon.
Then with a hand raised,
she turns and hurries away across the grass.
You're alone once more facing the hundreds of curious icons
plus one in the ancient cliff face.
If I take the coins, I'm gonna anger the gods.
I'm gonna climb the cliff.
You try climbing the cliff face,
but despite the carved icons providing grips,
they have not been designed for the purpose
and they are spread too far apart
or clustered uselessly close together.
A monkey might be able to make the climb perhaps,
but a man with a sword could not.
You give up and drop back to the grass.
Just take the coins.
They're probably here for a reason.
They have to be here for a reason.
This is such bait.
This is RPG bait.
Sorry, we're not falling for RPG bait.
Can I avoid this kid now?
I'm going up to the tree and then over.
Yep, I'm gonna sleep here.
This kid will not be here in the morning.
You walk away from the cliff across the grassland.
Night falls.
You need to rest,
especially after traveling all day without food.
You set yourself down on the plane.
Sorry, there is no tree trunk to rest your back against.
You have eaten what?
You set yourself down on the plane.
Sorry, there's a tree trunk to rest your back against.
Why not?
You've eaten nothing but your pack is empty.
You lie back and try to forget your troubles.
Your dreams quickly become nightmares.
There's a rope around your neck growing tighter.
The King of Aniland stands before you,
cursing you for your failure.
You were sent for the crown,
but instead you wandered the wilderness like a fool.
Explain.
You open your mouth to explain, but you cannot speak.
You cannot even find words to breathe.
Claw at the rope.
You reach up to your throat to claw away the rope,
to find that it's swelled up to be as thick as your arm,
as those submerged underwater.
Then one end of the rope splits and bites at your hand.
There is no rope, but it's a snake.
Your eyes flick open and there's a spare snake
is wrapped around your throat,
breathing its miserable breath into your eyes.
Summon replica creature.
Oh, let me read your mind
while you fucking choke me to death.
A grenade that close?
What is D?
Oh, Doze, Slowness.
Hot would probably be bad.
I'm gonna say it's probably...
Oh, dude, Doze, Slowness.
You move the starlight into order around you,
and the moment the spell takes effect,
the serpent begins to slow down
to a fraction of its previous speed.
You draw your sword,
the snake leaps back from you, bearing its fangs.
All right, that was huge.
Let's go full blast.
5.5.
It's all right, I can do another full blast.
It's fine, I'll win.
Full blast again?
Yep.
That's damn it.
Oh, I almost killed it in one hit.
Again.
No, rewind.
I'm good.
Am I okay?
You attack sadly.
Oh, I'm depressed.
You feel somewhat saddened by the idea of conflict.
You swing out wildly,
not really expecting to chop the creature in two
as it tries to ease itself away.
You get a passing cut.
The despair snake is retreating, of course,
but you manage to more or less keep pace.
You swipe at the air with your sword,
for what good it will do.
Your blow hits home,
cutting into the soft flesh
of the useless snake's exposed neck.
The despair snake is moving more like a slug now.
You can't help feeling it seems quite pathetic.
Then the despair snake is oozing
across the rocks towards you with an unstoppable fixation.
You try a quick stab,
but the effort is wasted as it moves like water
and your blade seems to pass straight through it.
It knocks you backwards, your head spins.
You're just spinning
and the sweat is pouring down your face.
You must look awful.
Oh, it's pathetic really, but it's all you have.
All right, you feel much better.
That's funny.
You gasp with relief.
The cold night closes in over you and you try to sleep.
You found three new clues.
Okay, you cannot afford to stand around.
Do not stop me on the road.
You little shit.
Fuck off, rewind.
No, he's following me around.
He's following me around.
I have, whatever.
Would I rather have the skull cap for Tell
or would I rather have the Sun Jewel?
What's more useful?
The Sun Jewel is probably more useful.
I don't know.
The skull cap is reading minds.
Tell is so useful though,
but the Sun Jewel is so useful.
All the dark areas.
Thief, snatch it back.
Talk to him.
How do you know the seven serpents?
Sounds like one of Shadrach's stories.
So you know Shadrach?
Of course I do.
Everyone knows Shadrach.
He's a brute and beats children
if they make too much noise near his cave.
He seemed most ferocious.
He hates children.
He says they're all thieves and villains.
The boy's starting to look twitchy.
How do I cross Lake Iklala?
You can get a ride on a fishing boat
if you don't mind dawdling while they catch their fish.
The boy hops on one foot.
Where are you from?
Karay, okay.
I have to go now.
I really have to go.
Where?
Why?
I'm in a hurry, he answers.
Oh, God damn it.
Whatever.
I lost the Sun Jewel, but fuck it.
That's it.
It's gone.
Nothing I can do about it.
Whatever.
Okay.
What about this stuff?
Let me check this out.
You continue across the grassland,
falling into an easy stride.
The Sun continues to climb the steep sky.
The fields of grass are pleasant here.
In the cool shade of the cliff face,
you could pause and rest if you wanted to.
Okay.
You stretch out on the ground.
The very earth itself feels warm
and soothes your tired muscles.
The Sun is hot now.
Little bit longer.
You sit a while longer in the grass,
watching the clouds move overhead.
Then quite suddenly,
something hot erupts from beneath you
and scalds your back.
Oh, come on.
You've been lying across the blowhole of a steam vent.
Fuck.
Once again, you return to the foot of the cliffs.
The Sun is beginning to lower
and the air begins to cool.
Looking back up at the cliff,
it seems impossibly high.
It is as though the backlands
was formed from the boot print of a passing soldier.
Let's get up that cliff.
Looking up at the cliff,
you see a line of carved stone blocks,
which appear to be the remains
of an ancient staircase,
a way upwards.
But near the base,
the stones are worn and broken.
There's no way to reach them to climb back.
Probably float, right?
Or zen?
No.
I don't have zip.
How do I get up here?
Okay.
The voice suggests magic may be the only way
back up the cliff side.
Really?
I don't think I have anything.
Talk is disease.
How?
Zen or a zip,
which I don't have a zip.
I don't think I can get up there.
That's unfortunate.
I mean, I guess I can follow the...
No, shit.
The item stolen by the boy
can sometimes be found in the holes
full of steam from the game's first area.
Why, I was just there.
Use a rope?
What about here?
Can I do it?
Stop it.
Can I go from the cliff side?
You walk along the base of the cliff.
Darkness closes in.
You should find a suitable spot to sleep,
especially after so long walking with an empty belly.
Behind you, the rock rises almost sheer into the sky.
In the darkness,
you can make out little of the trail ahead.
Wandering away into the dark
would be a dangerous move.
Oh, it's in the other area, okay.
Check for visions.
You have no food in your pack
and the planes out here are desolate and largely unoccupied.
You will have to move as quickly as possible
if you were to avoid starvation.
Shit.
Shit, I can't get up there.
Fuck.
Are you having fun?
Yeah, this is one of my favorite games ever made.
Eat the fish?
I need to cook it.
Rewind Randy.
I'm gonna rest, I have to.
Without a...
Wait, there is no shelter at the foot of the cliff.
Well, there is less wind than at the top.
But without a bolt hole,
to nestle in you will be at the mercy
of any creatures that smell you out.
And there are not many hours of night left.
Rest here anyways, let's go.
Setting down your pack by the foot of the cliff,
you try to stretch out despite the wind.
The burns on your body make it hard to get truly comfortable.
You've tried to eat today.
You stretch out and rest.
What is left of the night is filled with visions.
You see yourself outside your body,
reaching forward to touch a blue crystal in a brass socket.
For a moment, a beam of light shines upon,
upward across the clouds, brilliant and alive.
Meanwhile, your body burns
and crumbles to dust where it stands.
A boy sits on a throne of skulls and swords,
wearing a crown carved from solid bone.
He seems not to notice you,
but plays with a carved model figurine of goblins,
trolls and demons, playing out a war.
Though he looks bored by it.
And even while you sleep,
you know the serpents are moving towards.
Mampang.
And every day you spend out here
is a day in which your journey might be discovered.
Morning comes, you rise,
brush the dust from your cloak and look about you.
The great cliff rises up into the sky,
unclimbable, looking ready to topple at any moment.
Okay.
All right.
So I can't get back up here.
So I did, I got to get back up here
and do this in the present.
Because we did pretty much all of this
in the past and present, besides over here,
which maybe we'll do that later.
Or maybe not.
And then all of this over here was done in the past.
So I want to go up here and do this in the present.
Let's get here.
Oh, I want to go up because I want to go to the bridge.
Rewind and erase the days of pointless wandering.
That would be cheating.
You follow the curve of the cliff's foot once more.
The sun is not crested yet.
The last peaks of the east.
The tower is visible some distance away.
A broken set of steps some distance above your head.
Oh, okay.
We're good.
You leave the shadow of the cliff once more.
The moaning winds finger at your pack.
Okay.
We're here.
We did this already.
So I'm going to go to the bridge now.
Oh, wait a minute.
This thing in the past.
I want to say this.
You walk on across the prairie
until you meet the edge of an old road.
It is very warm now.
You begin to sweat under your pack.
The road begins to trace the course of a nearby river
which leaps with fish and birds.
You pass a large stone totem.
Look at the totem.
The totem picks a short toothy creature with no hair
and with several ringed earrings in one lobe.
Not a god, but a god or a goddess.
Helper creature.
The type that steals through your window to murder you.
Should the powers above dictate it.
It leers at you with two wide eyes above pursed lips.
Touch the eyes or touch the lips?
Touch the eyes.
You brush your fingers over the eyes.
There is no click, no sting, no sense of energy.
Perhaps this totem truly is merely made of stone.
The totem's eyes seem to glint a little.
Touch the lips.
You pause remembering the ritual of corga
and the terrible price of incorrect worship.
What if this totem is a trap?
The mouth slightly open.
There is a darkness inside.
The lips feel slightly sticky to the touch.
Kiss the totem.
You lean down and kiss the totem on the lips.
There is a quiet click
and you feel a sting at the back of your throat.
You begin to hack and wheeze
hoping to get whatever has entered your mouth back out.
And after a few moments, a bee flies out.
Then a second bee flies out from the totem's mouth
followed by two or three more.
They disappear up into the air in a way towards the south
where you can see a field of flowers.
You gasp with relief.
The bee in your mouth did not even sting you.
Put the pipe in the totem's mouth?
What pipe?
You take the bamboo pipe from your pack
and slide it into the totem's mouth.
It is just narrow enough to fit.
You feel it stick into something.
Suck on the pipe.
Suck, suck on the pipe.
You place your lips to the pipe and suck.
A moment later, you're coughing again
and spitting out a bee.
Blow on the pipe.
You blow sharply down on it.
Suck on the pipe.
You suck the pipe.
It is hard work.
Then a sweet dollop of wax plops into your mouth.
You take it out.
It is not much, but enough to cast a spell with.
Blow on the pipe.
You blow down the pipe again
and faintly hear an angry buzzing
from inside the totem echoing down.
Suck the pipe.
You suck on the pipe once more.
The next bee you suck up manages to sting you in the cheek.
It is ferociously painful, if not a serious womb.
Blow on the pipe.
You blow on the pipe again.
You pull the pipe back from the hole.
The foreign is tipped with honey,
which you lick off before putting the pipe away.
A light meal, but still good.
But the now open hole has allowed the bees out
and they are quickly swarming from the totem.
What?
Finger.
Can I plug it?
All right, I'm gonna plug it.
You put your finger in the hole to block it
and are immediately stung twice.
Before you can be stung again, you take your finger out.
Put the pipe back in the hole.
You shove the pipe back in the hole,
but now you have no choice but to leave it there
or take it out and release the swarm again.
All right, take the pipe out.
You pull the pipe out of the totem's mouth.
The bees roar out an angry storm
and sting you two or three times before you can turn tail.
We're good.
Hey, I got a meal.
The road meets the riverbank.
The mid afternoon heat fills the landscape.
You're met by a cheering sight,
where once this spot held the ruined foot
of an ancient bridge.
Now a majestic stone arch rises high into the air
as it crosses the river.
A way across.
Let's get some water.
You lean out into the river and fill up the gourd.
The rushing water sprays on your boots.
Okay.
You gaze up at the impressive stone bridge.
Craftsmanship is incredible.
The whole thing seems to have been carved
from a single colossal block of stone,
perhaps from the cliff face behind itself,
and then lowered perfectly into place across the fissure.
What manner of creature would be capable of such a feat?
Climb up the bridge.
You haul your way up the first few steps of the bridge
until you're standing above the water.
The spray throws rainbows in the sunlight
across the endless grass plains on either side.
You can see for miles in either direction.
The tower to the east and the grassy plains ahead.
For the briefest moment,
the nose of a narwhal appears above the surface
of the river.
Then it is gone, dragged away by the current.
Looking north across the plains,
you see barren waste once more.
In the far distance,
a group of horses are steaming across the plain
at wild speed.
They're riders thrown from side to side.
Then in a cloud of dust, they are gone once more.
Is he enough?
Each step of the bridge would require effort
to climb otherwise the road leads away,
well-paved, to the east.
Okay, so let's cross the bridge.
The afternoon is drawing on.
You cross the bridge wary at each step
that the ancient stones will collapse underneath you.
But they hold firm.
All the way across and you reach the far side.
The grassy plains stretch away once more.
Behind you, the river roars and screams.
The mighty bridge leads back across the river from here.
You waste no time.
You must explore these fields further.
All right, we're going up here.
You walk for half an hour across the fertile grassland.
The sun begins to dip heading towards the horizon.
The road is solid flag-stoned track.
Not grand, but serviceable enough.
It is clearly frequently used by farmers,
wagons, and supply carts.
Oh, how any of those across the river is a mystery, okay?
The road curves eastwards towards the stone tower.
Smaller track winds north between clumps of trees.
That's the river, we already know what that is.
So we're going up here.
You leave the clear road and walk across
the now windswept plain the evening is drawing in.
You stride on.
All right, do I wanna go to where those fins
are working on the tower?
Or go to this kind of ruined town?
I think I can just sweep around here.
Sex, what are you guys saying, sex?
You walk on across the dusty plains
until you join an old road.
The sun is now in the lowest quarter of the sky.
It'll be night soon.
You stop suddenly as you notice a movement in the distance.
Three shapes are approaching rapidly across the plain,
throwing up a thick cloud of dust as they move.
As you watch, they turn and head towards you.
Hail them.
There is a hand to hail the approaching figures
to discover they are tall, thick set centaurs.
Hold there, stranger.
Calls their leader, pulling himself up to a halt.
We are backlands horsemen.
Greetings, you are centaurs, not men.
I request, what?
Greetings, the centaur unslings a bow
and fires an arrow into the dirt by your feet
as a warning to come no closer.
He notches a second arrow aiming somewhat higher this time.
Now tell me, what is your purpose here
in the living misery that is Badrubak?
I'm a traveler, I'm on a mission.
I'm on a mission.
A mission?
What mission could take you out here?
There is nothing here to find.
It's a secret, shh, don't tell anybody.
These planes seem busy enough.
Just as a rotting corpse is busy with maggots,
but you are no mere traveler.
You are a sorcerer.
I'd wager my brittle on it.
The others stamp their hooves in restless agreement.
The centaur at the back of the group and goes forward.
This must be him.
He mutters, not quite enough for you to not hear.
The one the serpent spoke of.
You've spoken to the serpents?
You're mistaken, you know the serpents?
If you try to stop me, I'll kill you.
You know of the seven serpents?
You demand quickly.
These lands are ours.
Nothing crosses without our knowledge.
Except for me.
You fucking idiots.
The centaur stirs restlessly on the dust.
We know of you now, Anelander.
Hiya!
All right, perhaps we can help each other.
You suggest carefully.
I may have something you want.
The centaur raises one thick, bushy eyebrow.
And what do you suggest?
You help me and you live.
I will cast a luck spell on you.
I can pay.
Do you play swindle stones?
This is just a, this is horseshit.
Should I lie to him?
Do you play swindle stones?
Oh no.
I know the people of Kaare are happy to lose their homes
to that game, but I will not.
I will cast a luck spell on you.
A luck spell?
You have clearly piqued his interest.
And what do you want from us in return?
Tell me of the serpents.
Happily.
We tell you everything.
Every man deserves to know how he will die.
Ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha.
That was all of them laughing in different tones.
Do you know the serpents weaknesses?
You mistake us.
We patrol these planes.
We're not wizards.
We do not know the ways of magic.
I mean, perhaps you've heard something.
Nothing.
You are on your own.
The fur of the centaur kicks the ground
and grumbles clearly unhappy that they are talking to you.
Where can I find them?
The serpents have scattered across the plane
and some are rushing to Mampang to deliver their message
while others lie in wait to hunt you down.
I need to find them all.
That might be yet possible.
The backlands are a strange place.
They shift, change.
The very earth itself is cursed.
Many who try to rush across find themselves
only turning in circles.
The serpents have crossed once before,
but they may be slow in returning.
They're looking restless.
Thank you.
You've been most helpful.
Now, the spell the centaur declares.
Yeah, I got your luck spell for you.
Create an illusion.
Gum.
Create glue.
God.
Oh, I could be like, yeah, here's your luck spell.
I am God.
Dim?
Cause stupidity.
Oh no.
Oh.
luck what this exists i don't know it though quicksand oh that's so evil i don't i don't
know it i don't i don't know it i don't actually know it i don't think i can cast it unless i
actually comprehend it right can i cast it i thought you had to comprehend it to cast it
try it consulting the constellations overhead you bind the spell and you feel a strange force
entering your bones as though you were growing stiff and you begin to shake quickly you direct
the spell's power to the centaur what a stroke of luck to have found a luck spell in this very spot
preening with satisfaction at his blessing the centaur kicks his hooves into the air
the creature smiles broadly now we are blessed you cannot hope to defeat us we will take from
you what we want the centaur wheels around to attack while the others hold back cheering and
waving their bows you have no choice but to fight what a dick all right we're going full blast big
damage big damage defend the centaur smiles with broken teeth you launch forwards hoping to take
the creature by surprise the centaur bellows and laughs turning about for a charge and you drop
into a crouch as the centaur stampede you roll to one side staggering backwards under the impact
he grumbles and stamps away he just did five i'm gonna go full blast you dummy you launch your
attack and your blade sings as it pair arts the air but the centaur is well out of reach so you
catch him with a passing blow he adjusts his harness all right you fall back the centaur paces
around you threatening but not connecting you coming in full blast full blast 6.0 no defend
shit an opening appears and you bring your blade in heavily but the centaur is racing back so you
do little more than scratch his side the centaur stamps his feet trying to shake himself into
action he wheels swiftly calling to his fellows defend you drop into a crouch as the centaur
charges at you furiously you duck his blade when it comes though it leaves you breathless for a
moment he rides some way back all right this is a defense so just do a tiny bit like 1.2 like 1.5
or something like 2.0 1.5 good all right once more you dive forwards you cut a sideways blow
but the centaur is well away from your blade careful now calls one of the others the centaur
growls at them uh this is going to be another low one right three or full blast dead you take
advantage of the centaur's aggravation to press forward and your sword moves like lightning the
centaur gives a great cry and falls to the ground a huge plume of dust oh man the second centaur
stampedes forward oh shit i gotta do this right stampedes forward i'm thinking full blast nine
nine oh i'm all right the creatures battering hooves are wearing you down
shit i have to go 4.5 all right good i caught it that was a good catch
okay he collapses backwards he races back defend he bellows with rage he's coming in hard i have
to defend i wouldn't be able to do it anyways all right you breathe a sigh of relief he draws his
bow so fast he all but fumbles an arrow all right i'm thinking like five got yep a chance opens up
swinging up from the low crouch you strike for the beast thick neck cutting into his flank you'll die
here i think he's coming full blast again full blast he has 10 stamina he just used three point
okay i'm doing it full blast he screamed you'll die here cantering away the centaur leaves a trail
of thick blood in his path he'll boil you for glue the last centaur goes his fellow god damn it i'm
gonna oh my god he's gonna charge in now i'm dead i'm dead well fuck whatever all right he came in
full blast with 10.0 i can't do anything about that i have to take this hit all right so now
you got nothing i can do like 1.2 what the fuck are you talking about what kill me kill me kill
me kill me just kill me just kill me kill me kill me kill me kill me already just kill me already
what the hell why am i winning wait hold on hold on stop stop stop i'm winning yes all right we're
good the last of the centaurs looks at you eyes filled with fear he circles around you trying to
stay clear of your sword spare him keep your life you declare the creature nods quickly and then
wheels around and races away the planes fall silent the two dead centaurs are bleeding quietly
into the sand the arrow fired by the centaur into the dirt is still here why spare because i was
gonna die and i was afraid to lose the next fight you tug the arrow from the dirt the shaft is as
thick as your finger the metal tip the size of a wet stone you slide it into your pack as a souvenir
there's no use letting their corpses go to waste the sands will cover them and their belongings all
too quickly rifling through their saddlebags you uncover four gold pieces a pouch of brown sand
and a sun jewel got the sun jewel back hell yeah thank god you take the jewel and slip it into your
pack then you leave the corpses for the dust and turn your back you continue on your way i'm kind
of i might just do this yeah pray for healing the ape doesn't really help that much it's good for
a heal though uh let's go up here to where the spins were working you step off the road and cut
across the desolate plain another night begins you need to rest in the dark you do not see the deep
pit in the ground until you stumble into it you land on something soft something moving from
nearby you hear a murmuring oh god you look up to the heavens but before you can find a spell
something wraps itself around your left arm a sorcerer murmurs a voice as your eyes adjust to
the dark you see you are not alone in the pit a man squats beside you with a pipe in his mouth
who are you you demand the man smiles and plays a few quick notes on his pipe suddenly the earth
below moves rearing up and you realize you have landed in a pit filled with snakes the man laughs
at your fear and soothes the beast once more with his music manata is me i'm good to travel earth
the snakes hiss and whine about their master but i am curious as to who you are you are a
traveler i'm too weak i'm too weak elegant i'm too weak elegant what are these snakes my pets
most beautiful creatures on this earth thing for them one of the vipers nips at your boot
please tell me of your travels i am weak i'm too weak i'm too weak i'm very weak i'm very weak
he nods then rest i will play for you and he begins to pipe a tune in your current state you
cannot resist it your eyes fall closed and you begin to sleep though as your eyes close you
realize your body is moving in time to the music winding and curving around the base of the pit
you dream you are sliding through long towers made of a green metal that parts as you move through
an ocean of blue shines overhead bright brittle a long tongue flickers from your mouth your body
feels infinitely long and your toes too far away to feel slowly you struggle awake you are curled
up around the snake charmer's feet amongst all his snakes but your belly feels full and you are
well rested my pretty feeling better now uh what did you do he chuckles and knocks his pipe against
his cheek um do you have any food i do not my snakes catch the food and we share the snake
charmer tips his head to one side and closes his eyes for a moment as though listening to something
i have said enough leave us kill the snake charmer ask another question do we ask a question
don't risk it just get out just i'm just gonna get out you clearly will get nothing out of the
snake charmer and scramble up out of the pit he begins to play once more as you walk away all
right he would yeah we would have got trapped i think again i mean i got food and rest whatever
okay uh all right hmm i do want to see what happened what's happening down here this is
now the dead of night the ground here is broken dry mud deep cracks and uneven surfaces make it
slow going to walk across let's look the deep fissures and layers of the mud catch your eye
it is as though the whole plane had been held high in the air and dropped it must have been
very fertile land once in a few cracks a thick clumps of grass still managed to grow you swing
your foot through one and it hits something quite solid kick harder you kick the obstacle whatever
it is and hear a definite oddly sickening crunch do i just stomp on something inside a particularly
thick clump of grass you spy something dry gray and round uh clear the grass you begin to part
the grass and reveal a familiar shape a human skull its upper jaw set into the soil it is almost
lost beneath the thick grass that grows from the top of the skull is this our friend i don't think
it's our friend because we we freed our friend let's look at it the skull appears intact no wounds
or injuries it is only lightly buried a little soil spills between the lower front teeth the eye
sockets steer through the thick green grass that cover the scalp all right let's pry the skull free
the skull is only lightly buried a good tug should pull it free you try but it does not come loose
lever the skull you draw your sword and slip it under the skull then lever hard the skull flips
up into the air with a snap and lands nearby a short bony stake is left in the ground interesting
resurrect the dead that would be cool oh well uh god illusion of worship something with a w
that i don't know why not uh the voice begins to speak to you the voice assures you there is no
danger here at all um i'm gonna keep the skull you put the skull into your pack in case it should
come in useful later though what for you cannot think okay it's not the most comfortable place
to rest especially with the body in the ground beside you but it will suffice thankfully you're
not hungry you close your eyes and let your tiredness overtake you a long night is kept
busy with vivid dreams a small rabbit hops up to your feet quite tame then raises its eyes
which burn bright and terrible red with all the force of a red eye of kare a huge bird with your
face swoops down from the sky long talons raking the dusty soil digging grave after grave and all
the while you hear a distant laughter from the east oh sick all right you march onwards there's
nothing here really uh let's go wrap around here and then we'll end up at this bridge you make your
slow way across the endless plane a few clouds boil in the sky scoured into the plane here are
deep curving ruts from a creature they're almost certainly the tracks of some creature that slid
across the ground switching from side to side most likely there are the tracks of a snake but
the size is hard to comprehend each groove in the land is large enough to stand in up to the
height of your hip it must be a serpent follow the tracks you follow the curving tracks backwards and
forwards across the plane they turn a little way southwards but continue on towards the mountains
does it still work does it still work how does it sound does it still work how does it does it
sound okay it does not work does this do anything i'm turning on the effects does this do anything
does this make a difference does it sound cool the tracks give out as the ground on a foot turns
from dust to broken rocks at the foot of the eastern ridge sitting in the low rocks and
humming to himself as a dwarf over his shoulder is a cloth string bag flick him over you regard
him with interest it is strange to see a creature out here alone on the plains the dwarf peers back
and what are you he demands are you here to rob me and what's all that fish smell oh that's a bad
scottish accent but you know what fuck it who cares i have some raw fish good for you i prefer
to cook mine but then i'm not a wild dog i'm sorry as he talks he slings his bag onto his lap and
opens it from inside he removes a chunk of heavy blackened bread you want some thank you you sit
down on a rock close you know we're going to do a different dwarf we're going to do a different
dwarf um we're going to do a different kind of is it going to be a different dwarf okay thank you
you sit down on a rock close by the dwarf and he hands you a chunk of bread it is stale and dry
but still provides some nourishment to starve off the worst of your hunger uh what's your name
mist stupid name for a dwarf dwarfs have names like gutter pace not names like mist but my
parents thought that they were something different didn't they you play swindle stones taking out the
dice i'll play you all right but i won't stake anything i've got nothing to lose that seems fair
let's just play let's go that doesn't that does not i gotta change it let me see oh good hand
good hand to start with mickey it's a good hand all right there i you know i've got two ones well
i'm no archaeologist can you tell him anything about the mountains two threes three threes what
makes you say that no one crosses the ridge no one has for hundreds of years okay so that
there's it absolutely has to be yeah i win oh even the kare then i knew i just came from kare two
twos three twos four twos um sorry man i win let me see all right uh how about one two no two
fours three twos that's impossible how did you leave kare the only way is the gate surely call
oh rt game crowd rt game crowd right what's going on thanks to the raid rt what's going on playing
sorcery was we're getting back into it we're on part three in the backlands thanks for the
raid welcome sorcery part three currently doing swindle stones with uh the this dwarf that i
found it's time for some magic that's right all right what does he say he beat pokemon black
version part one of the best mainline pokemon generations ever generation five though unfortunately
he lost is that game good i don't know i honestly i'll be honest i don't know what any of that means
every pokemon game is like kind of meshes together for me because i've never played one of them all
right you you literally won okay two here let me just ruin your day here here it is three twos
not possible i would like to get some extra information from you after beating you in
swindle stones you flick the dwarfs final die off the ground with a grin i win you tell him
the dwarf curses good thing we didn't stake would have made things even worse the dwarf gets to his
feet i'd better be moving on can't stay here forever i did that on purpose because everyone
what i wanted you to fucking cringe in your seat hey we could travel together he screws up his
nose at that my rations will last twice as long without your friend you can head out and starve
on your own well then i'm gonna take your bag i'm taking your bag the dwarf is all about walking
away but you do not let him go the idea of extra provisions is too tempting to ignore you reach up
firmly grasp the strap of his bag yeah what do you think you're doing give it to me i'm on a
mission to save the whole land give it to me before i make you give it to me stop that struts the
dwarf clearly now afraid stop it hex oh god what is that illusion of treasure but look at all this
treasure cause speed uh gack is fear i don't have the face mask leave him alone i don't want to hurt
well i just like snap my fingers and open a door i'm gonna cause slowness right all right illusion
of treasure you craft the spell and after a moment gold and jewels begin to spew forth from under
your sleeves i just have a bunch of like gold coins falling out of me who the fuck am i
what is this psycho this image makes me laugh i'm just imagining oh i'm gonna sit down and enjoy
some stale bread with you while gold goblets fall out of my sleeves who is this person what
a menace okay you after a moment gold and jewels begin to spew forth from under your sleeves and
from the neck of your boots rolling away across the ground the dwarf rolls his eyes don't you
think a dwarf can recognize false treasure when he sees it you must think i want to be dumb and
dead sorcerers you're all the same all right one or two let's have chat decide something let's get
a poll going one or two one is release and be fine all right two is fight gold coins why would
i need your bag stale rotten food in it if i have 500 million dollars worth of jewels on me and why
would i be carrying all this beat him with the hard bread yeah one or two one is released and
the other one is um fight i don't know i think he's a pretty pleasant guy yeah it's up to you
what a toddler too no give me the bag give me the bag i want it's mine no it's mine no give me it
treasure falling everywhere you need food i do have no food um this is too close to call too
close to call i'm gonna go pee and we'll see where it is too close to call i'll be right back okay
what's the uh it's a absolute 50 50 it's it's 750 votes and 750 votes um okay do it again okay i'm
gonna go let me go refill my drink do it again what the hell is going on here okay do it again
um that's impossible one is release the bag two is fight fight them and let me i'm gonna go i'll
be right back okay uh number one i'm releasing the bag it only won by like 15 votes 971 versus 958
god okay so release the bag you let the bag go and take a step back very well keep it the
dwarf stares at you for a moment and then dashes away across the rocks and out of sight calling
back only load a tick okay uh i got another poll for you up or down because uh i think there's a
couple things to do maybe here i don't know up or down one is up two is down you guys getting a lot
of choices right now isn't that cool one two i hate choices well then just put your arms back
behind your head and sit back in your chair for a minute looks like it's no well now you're doing
it on purpose even if you were trying to do it on purpose i don't even know how you did it that first
time okay okay come on one of them run away with it please yep well it's got about uh 10 seconds or
so to play out 750 to 754 757 767 762 and 70 you're never gonna get it right ever again it doesn't
matter how hard you try it's not gonna happen no it's too hard to do that again yeah all right
we're going down the rocks underfoot soon turn into a slope and then the slope gets steeper
until the going is hard and you are heavy breathing the sun is beginning to lower the air begins to
cool from the middle distance a curious sound reaches your ears let's listen you stop and listen
the sound is some kind of screech but quiet but close at hand but the mountainside is barren and
there's nothing that could be causing the sound let's do sus let's be safe oh my god okay reaching
up to the stars you create the magic and a steady voice enters your mind it tells you that there is
nothing to fear here but that close at hand in the mountains a serpent awaits this message
deliver this message delivered the voice fades you have barely finished the spell when something
happens a fearful shape begins to form a dark cowled creature with a skull-like head it seems
your spell somehow missed this how did you miss that it beckons with a single bony finger
run for cover in the rocks um what else can i do uh walk as a shield dim is caused stupidity
rock i don't have the stuff uh rap i could talk all languages okay the death wraith is still
groaning and laughing but somehow it seems unaffected by the spell though you strain your
ears you cannot make out any real words at all approach you approach cautiously the apparition
appears to be a death wraith like the one you fought in shinva's tomb in the kare's necropolis
as you step nearer it opens its arms wide to clasp you silver chain oh goodness okay you draw
the magic chain and wrap one end around your fist leaving the other free to whip and strike
that's a lot of stamina uh okay i'm glad i did that the death wraith drifts forward one hand
reaching for your neck the other holding a dagger aloft it howls with icy rage as it approaches
knife outstretched you gather your wits and drop into a defensive crouch you must turn you turn
the blow that you bend your back and it glances you shit come on i almost tripped over a stone
wow the death wraith drifts back across the plateau withdrawing but injured all right so
we're gonna defend okay the death wraith reaches out with its skeletal hand the wraith
cackles as you pant for breath uh i have to defend again yeah i would have gotten hit
you parry in a flash of sparks and metal all right now's my chance say like i have to do why
am i stamina so low got it oh it's because of the chain it's not the sword or the axe okay
you whip the chain and the death wraith's knife is easily turned the operation lifts a little into
the air this place will be your last yeah why is he talking now uh i gotta defend again yep okay
now i go full forward yep two more all right i'm gonna do this two more times i'm gonna go again
2.5 all right that's okay i still he still takes damage your bones will lie in my tomb i will eat
your skin oh come on it's gonna come in hard it curves its blade high into the air and grins its
death masquerade it's coming in hard yep all right i just gotta get a couple more hits in i'm gonna
say like three i gotta go i have to thank god i did that all right only one more one more i'm
just gonna fall blast right now got it death ray's dead you must not give in you slash the
death wraith with the chain with a final strike the creature wails and moans it begins to retreat
slowly painfully no longer floating the monster crawls a short distance away and the shimmering
haze once more returns engulfing the death wraith completely when it fades the apparition has
disappeared and in its place is a stout balding man who whimpers and nurses his wounds
let me be i mean you no harm what is the meaning of this the creature does not take his arms from
over his head leave wren friend alone he never does any harm just a little merriment that's all
behind you the apparition has vanished it was a mere illusion threaten you step closer and a
land sword poised tell me why i should spare your life answer me that of course of course
i should have known better when i saw you i knew i thought you're a warrior you're a wizard i could
tell i could tell and yet you tried to trick me from his pockets he produces a spiked metal disc
in a yellow vial of powder take them take them please what's in the vial you demand i don't know
what the powder is i just like the color what's the disc i should just take them both right yellow
powder oh the caster will then become exceedingly quick and may run speak think or fight at three
times normal speed however this spell requires the caster to sniff yellow powder before cats it is
it's cocaine all right i'm taking it you lift the vial of yellow powder to the light as you take it
there's a fine grainy powder the color of unchafed wheat or pus i'll take the disc too you take the
metal disc thank you thank you oh i'm so sorry how did you do tell me how you conjured the death
wraith unless you are very much mistaken this man is no sorcerer oh i it's just a thing i
learned to do it's all smoke and mirrors you know then show me your mirror of course of course
you step back a little oh i'll show you if you step back it's in the ground you see i'm no i
ain't not fucking going anywhere stay put you shake your head i've seen the illusion i want
to see how it works of course i can't do it though it's a natural phenomenon really it only
works here and only at certain times i'm sorry i'm sorry what do you know the serpents the seven
serpents the seven serpents oh oh yes yes of course i know the serpents i know all of them
all seven what can you tell me about them oh i'm you know they fly around don't they
so they have wings most of them do i four of them maybe five you're lying to me
the man flinches expecting to be hit all right yeah i don't know anything about any serpents
do you live here in the backlands looking around the wilderness they used to be a sailor my captain
was a brute we landed ashore and i ran off into the wasteland i've been wandering them ever since
this place is cursed do you know that you think you've reached the edge and then somehow you find
yourself back where you started it's like the ground itself was built in spirals yeah suddenly
the man's eyes turn upwards and his voice trails off into a low moan a moment later he has keeled
over something it seems has frightened him to death you whip around but catch sight only of
something moving up the slope of the mountain you continue up the winding path into the pass at the
top of the mountain the wind picks up as the evening draws on soon it will be dark suddenly
the sun is snuffed out like a candle a hissing sound begins to echo around the rocks and overhead
a larger moon than usual seems to rise from the horizon another trick you look up in surprise
the shape rises a little higher the strange almost translucent ball than the round shape uncoils
itself the shimmering body of the moon serpent is revealed hovering in the air above you its
wide fangs are open and it is coming for you drink it drink the snake bike snake bite antidote
light my tinderbox look at the serpent all right the moon serpent was what the moon serpent is
deathly afraid of fire okay so fire the tinderbox hot so wait am i about to just pick a lighter up
and flick it in front of them here it is i mean i just do i do i should i talk first what do you
think just go right for it i can always rewind but hold on the creature is enormous its wide
wings seem to stretch from horizon to horizon and its eyes are two yellow orbs its scales are
a mixture of circles crescents and flattened ovals and a very only slightly in shade from
flat gray to shimmering silver saliva is streaming down its teeth okay all right let's go let's do it
but i mean i could talk and well i mean is it an animal or do we just just rip the bandaid off
and throw the fireball at its face let's talk removing the green wig you pulled under your
head and complete the spell but the serpent only laughs at you stupid creature i speak your language
but why would i talk to you the creature is almost on you now all right it's time
fireball you wind the constellations into alignment around you winding a fireball in your
palm the serpent's eyes glitter in the light it does not seem scared throw it at the serpent
the flames of the burning fireball gutter as it flies through the air towards the serpent
but you score a direct hit and the fire quickly spreads across the creature's skin it seems fire
truly is the serpent's weakness one by one the scales pop from its hide peeling back and falling
like leaves to the rocks below the creature is screaming now in pain and terror what should i
kill it wait or just wait boy wait right the serpent has ceased its attack and is now lifting
into the air turning about making to run draw my sword and kill it you draw your sword ready to
finish the serpent off before it can escape the serpent darts low and you set yourself a battle
oh look at that stamina look at that stamina you're not gonna even have a chance what's that like six
oh that was close even though it is weakened you'll need your wits about you against this foe
you swing fast and high hoping to strike deep into the serpent's scaly hide the serpent stumbles
forward facing a painful arc towards you with crescent moon teeth bared silvery moons are
winking out across the creature's long back cold gathers around the edges of its mouth and this
we go full blast again and it's dead bingo done easy you press your advantage knowing only
too well this is a fight to the death you spin about blade fast and low the moon serpent's eyes
close to narrow crescents then fall dark its body seems to crumble before your eyes congratulations
you have defeated the first of the seven serpents of mampang the darkness in the sky disappears and
the sun returns as the serpent dies it seems to coil up shriveling away until all that remains
is a small crystal orb take the orb you lift the orb it is a precious artifact of great power
you put it carefully into your pack the bleak mountainside falls silent around you you feel a
new spring in your step one serpent has been defeated soon the rest will fall look around
you look around the clearing the marks of your battle with the moon serpent
are still visible in the dirt there's nothing else here except for a little stone work
by the eastern edge of the plateau the remains of a building perhaps or a ledge let's look you go
over to the ancient stone it sticks out from the rock a few fingers and breaks away only barely
distinguishable from the stone of the mountain another piece protrudes for a short distance away
whatever was here was large and beautifully wrought once but now is gone looking back west
across the plains you spy a dark smudge on the land a cloud of black dust rising from the wheels
of a great caravan of carts and horses crawling slug-like across the dust looking east you see
the plains continuing and then the edge of the forest of snatta dark and tangled somewhere
beyond is the distant glitter of lake iklala which you must somehow get across the edge of the
mountaintop ends abruptly there are a few carved stones and then a vertical drop you creep to the
edge of the plateau and peer down the drop is not vertical after all but skitters away down the
mountainside you might be able to skid down it but you couldn't walk and there would be a constant
danger of rolling time to head for lower ground one way or another we've been nothing but good
can we have a la la la la okay so that's the first serpent that is the moon serpent dead
we've almost fully explored these two areas do you guys all right let's do a poll do you
want to go down here to the new zone or would you like to wrap around and head up here and
explore a little bit up here because i don't think we saw the other stuff over this way
did we one is go back two is go down we could i mean you could go south too all right let's
just go for it let's go one two three one is back this way two is down to the new zone three is down
south here we go one two three also i would like to let you know that this is going to be one of
the final decisions of the afternoon i'm going to call it here uh at about four hours i need to
prepare uh to be on austin shows uh name your price tomorrow i will be on name your price
twitch.tv slash austin show i will be hosting it and i believe i believe i will also be on the
show after that you ever heard of hey donna i will be on that as well hey donna with will neff
and i think uh cutie cinderella should be a fun time they're trying to do a three-way tie
i didn't even look at it all right all right all right okay fine it's not gonna work but good
attempt it was a good try i have no clue what you're on about all right let me tomorrow i
will be on someone else's stream it's a game show and then leading into a comedy show that's where
i'm going to be tomorrow there you go all right one two three we're going to go down thank you for
uh voting the slope is windswept if you trudge onwards the sun is almost set and the sky has
turned a deep purple on and on you go pausing every now and again to scout out the land ahead
and suddenly you stop something is moving over the next rise approaching very fast wait and watch
you stop in the middle of the path and watch as the shape approaches it is a small two-legged
creature about half your size but it seems to be approaching at a remarkable rate
uh hail it raising a hand you hail the tiny creature as it gets close you see it as a small
gnome-like creature with dark skin and ugly features his little legs move at an incredible
rate and it helps itself along with a walking stick uh look at the stick you can't help but
notice the stick is carved into the shape of a serpent looking at the creature it's hard to
imagine anything could be so ugly its features are scrunched up as if drawn on paper that has
since been burned its hair is matted and filled with bones some used as ties and other the remains
from some creatures who have crawled in and died silently you wonder to yourself if the creature
is friend or foe have it whichever way you like it's a telepath indeed i am continues the creature
replying to a thought you did not even have time to formulate the gnome smiles do you think very
loud like shouting in a thunderstorm the remark does not make much sense i'll be your friend you
suggest very good now prove it it holds out a grubby hand expecting some kind of gift
uh you can have a coin you take out a gold piece and hand it to the creature who throws it
immediately to one side rubbishy metal if i want metal don't you think i can find my own um give
it an item you look in your pack for something you're willing to offer to the gnome i have a
shitload of these goblin tooth magic not you're not getting my chain you're not getting a giant's
tooth you're not getting the sun jewel you can have a goblin's tooth you hand over a goblin's
tooth the gnome shrugs accepting your gift thank you i suppose as the creature speaks its voice
begins to shift and change from the gruff croaking of the gnome to the softer tones of
a middle-aged woman i'll do you the favor of being honest about myself in return the creature says
and before your eyes the gnome transforms into a tall woman dressed in long purple robes who are
you i am din hold on i am dintenta wait i am dintentia dintentia of the steps others call me
the sham i was told to find you you exclaim remembering the riddle told to you by the
lord shinva in his second dying breath in the crypt of kare i was told you could help me
i am to ask you about the sleepless ram and we are well met who are you i'm a nobody
uh i am the sir i'm a sir should i be why would i say that hold on let me get this right okay no
i don't have any other really all right um i intend to i intend to kill the serpents i intend
to kill the seven serpents and she laughs many have had that intention very few know their
weaknesses but do you know them the serpents weaknesses are the most heavily guarded secrets
in the whole of man pang of course i know them or at least i know of two i would be grateful to
hear them i am certain you would know then that the air serpent has a weak body when in its
gaseous form secondly the serpent of earth must stay in touch with the ground what else do you
know i know your lack of gratitude is unbecoming and i should transform you into a toad tell me
of the sleepless ram the sleepless ram is in man pang fortress the guardian of the archmage
it is a statue of solid stone and your skill will be no match for its powers but it has a
simple weakness some kind of spell some kind of potion some kind of vulnerability a soft underbelly
perhaps or a single easily blinded eye the secret is much more simple so simple a child could use
it the sleepless ram can be sung to sleep where can i find the seven serpents one's off to hide
in the waters of lake eclala it means to pick you off as you cross but it will wait until you are
alone if you travel with the ferrymen you will most likely be safe if that's any help i don't
suppose it is what kind of sorceress are you a busy one why do you waste my time with stupid
questions she turns to leave begins to weave her spell around herself once more you wave her away
keen to continue your journey ventatia becomes an ugly creature once more and a moment later
has whisked herself away across the plains and is gone the climb is uneventful and the slopes are
silent is now marked on the map very helpful end of the stream voice yep end of the stream voice
you got it i will see you guys tomorrow not here but on austin show's channel and then uh i believe
i don't i don't know if hey donna is on austin's channel or if it's on g4 or will's channel i'm
not sure you will know wherever it is it'll be hosted so i will not be here with you in this
chat tomorrow but i will be streaming i will be live yeah i'll see you guys tomorrow take care
of yourselves thanks for watching after tomorrow i will be back this weekend so we will get something
rolling on either saturday or sunday keep an eye on the sus after tomorrow and i'll see you guys
this weekend and tomorrow if you want to watch that show take care everybody we've got a solid
i would say this one two three four five six zones each has two versions obviously right
we've gone through almost two of them seems to be about one stream per two zones so we'll be here
for at least another i want to say like two streams two and a half streams i don't know when we'll be
back for sorcery but we will it's fun just to do this everybody that enjoys watching this you're
here i think it's a good just kind of chill game to hang out and just mess around and
so i'm having a great time what time is the show tomorrow at 2 p.m pacific two o'clock tomorrow
pacific is when name your prices thank you guys and also thanks rt for the raid if you're still
here from rt's channel rt game crowd and i'll see you later take care of yourselves call your
mother goodbye good night see you soon