Alright, I'm gonna, I'm gonna play. Okay, I have to admit something to you. I played Vampire Survivors off stream. I know, I'm sorry.
Uh, we're gonna play a little bit though. I unlocked some stuff. I know, people are gonna be mad. Like, played without us. Played without us, yeah.
Alright, give me one second, I'm just gonna switch. That was creepy. That was creepy.
Maybe I'll do like one or two rounds, just to kind of, uh, pallet cleanse that weird experience, right?
Did you like it? I mean, you can't, how, how do you like that experience, right? It's kind of awful.
But it did, like, it did what it was trying to do, and like kind of freak you out and make you feel awful.
You know what I mean? It's like, ah dude, didn't you love that? No, like, I hated that. It sucked.
But that's like exactly what they were going for, right? So, I mean, yeah, it got, it did what it was doing, what it was trying to do. So yeah.
Alright, uh, Vampire Survivors coming up. Cool. Yeah, we need a little bit of a detox here, yeah.
Ooh, that's loud. What's the title right now? Haunted Coffee Shop. Winding down with some vampire survivors.
That's pretty accurate. So yeah, I unlocked a few more weapons. Uh, Holly and I were playing it.
Because I kind of couldn't get enough, so, you know. Your titles went from amazing to dog shit.
Yeah, but dog, I mean, I've, whatever. So, the last thing that I did, I can turn it up a little bit, that's too low.
Oh, I want to go over this too, because this is something that is very new.
So, I'm going to talk to Ludwig, but we might need to move a few things around.
Because we planned on Friday for being that kind of PvP night, but I think we need a little bit more time. We'll see.
Um, on Friday, I'm going to do something that I've never done before.
This is something that's brand new to the channel, and some of you in pre-stream already know what I'm talking about.
I'm doing my first ever sponsored game stream. That's for real, not a joke.
Uh, there's been, I remember a few months ago when I signed with Evolved, and they were going to start doing sponsorships.
And some of the bigger streams will have more sponsors, and I'll be able to try to make some extra money to be able to do some more of these things.
Uh, there's been quite a few things that I could have done already, and I said no, but I'm very selective.
Uh, the thing that's happening on Friday, the game looks fun. I actually went in and played the demo, and I was like, oh, this actually seems pretty cool.
The game is The Serpent Rogue. It actually looks really fun. Uh, it's something that looks pretty interesting.
It's all about the money, isn't it? I thought it was going to be a different game.
No, and, uh, okay, let me be really clear with this. Sponsors on this stream, I'm going to be pretty selective on, right?
If something looks like it's something I'd be interested in, something that I think would be cool, or that I think would be, oh, this looks like it might be fun to play,
then yeah. If there's an opportunity, then yeah. But I'm not just going to do something just because, just to do it. That's just not going to happen.
Um, so I would rather have those things happen naturally than just, oh yeah, sure, I'll do anything.
Um, so I can at least try to tell you that anything that's a sponsor on this stream is something that I have, like, used before,
something that I thought was interesting, or that I thought, like, actually that makes sense. I could kind of gel with the community, right?
So, I mean, every sponsor is going to be, yes, I'm sponsored to play it, yes, I'm sponsored to show it,
but I have the opportunity to be able to say yes or no, every time. Um, so, we should run ads as well.
Mmm, I, let's not, let's not talk, let's not get there yet. Let's not, uh, let's not get there yet.
I don't, I don't think so. I don't think that's going to have to happen, for any reason.
Yeah, The Serpent Row, it looks fun. It looks actually really cool. It's a game where it's like you, like an action adventure where you make potions and shit.
I actually looked, I was looking, you know, play the demo. Seems pretty good.
Yet, no. Can you monetize your breath yet?
Alright, I unlocked some people. I want to show you who they are because they're cool.
Uh, I unlocked this guy, Ramba. This, oh soul. This was pretty cool, this dog. I'm excited, you deserve the opportunities.
But I don't, I don't want to just do it just to do it, right? And, I mean, eventually, some of the idea behind some of this stuff is, okay, subs and bits don't, like, you guys don't, like, need to do that, right?
If I get to a point where I'm making more money through sponsorships, then subs, do you guys, I can, you can just fucking watch, you know what I mean?
Um, and you don't have to worry about that. And even now, even right now, you don't have to worry about that.
So, I'm trying to make a reasonable balance. And, obviously, obviously, I'm trying to make some money too.
Because, not just for the big shows, right? Because big shows really are expensive. And some of these shows are half, kind of, paid for, but not really.
And then, we have to figure out how to get the rest. Uh, but some of these opportunities, some of these projects, I mean, they're, they're potentially in the hundreds of thousands of dollars. Hundreds of thousands.
So, I want to make sure that I'm going to be able to pay for them and, like, not have to worry about it, right? So, that's the long and short of it.
I want to try to be transparent. This greedy motherfucker. Don't worry about it, bro. Yeah, I, but I've never done it before. Ever.
And it's something that I always said if I was going to ever do it, that I would want to make sure I was, kind of, on my own terms, right?
I unlock these too, yeah. All right, let's do XP. A lot of XP. Cool Down, Area, and Speed, and Magnet.
And, and don't, don't get me wrong, like I said, there, there's been at least a few opportunities that I've just been, like, uh, uh-uh. No, I don't think so.
Just straight up. And that's going to continue to happen, all right? I'm going to, that's going to keep happening.
Okay, so I need to survive on green acres. This is going to be hard. Random enemy waves from normal stages and enemy health plus 50%. This is going to be fucking hard.
All right, let's go for it. Enjoy your bitrate. So, uh, this dog spits out these flowers that shoot up behind you. They're pretty cool. This music is pretty good, too.
160p. That was a good title. What was wrong with that one? Oh, I unlocked this too. This is, uh, these are guns.
Fires quickly in four fixed directions. See if I can get both. Why are you fighting the Woj, Soy Wojak? This is 50% more health than random enemies. I haven't even tried this one.
Uh, I mean, I love lightning. Lightning Rod is like the best. But that's Friday, and Friday we were thinking of doing the Elden Ring PvP stuff, but I gotta, I gotta talk to Ludwig because we gotta figure out how that's going to play out.
I think we need a little bit more time. Oh God. Yeah, we'll chill for a little bit. I'll play around to see if I can beat the game at least once. They have way more health. This actually is kind of hard.
So the next stream will be on Friday. That's what I'm planning on. Okay. Damage? What do I have? I need the Duplicator Ring, the other gun. I need Tiramisu. I don't think the flower has an evolve. I think I'm just going to finish. Just damage.
Use the knife, oh God. But to cap the sponsor thing, there's like a few streams this year that I really want to do, and I need to be able to pay for them. Stuff that I've always wanted to do, stuff that I've like, that I really care about.
And I've said this to you guys before, and I have to reiterate it sometimes. The stuff that keeps me interested is what keeps me in this chair. And that stuff, doing those shows, doing the big stuff, is what is keeping me interested. That's what keeps me interested.
So, I want to try to do the things that I want to try to do. Turn up the game audio? Oh, I don't even know what I just bought. What was it? What happened? What did I just buy? I think it was another level of something? What was it? I'm crashing again. He's gone. Oh, actually gone.
Hello? Oh no, he left the chair. He took the money and ran. He left the chair. I really hope you guys understand that the last 10 to 15 seconds is probably the most important.
Thing I've ever said in my entire life on stream. Ever. I really just hope you guys understand. The last probably 15 seconds is the most important. Ever. Glad you got to hear it. Oh, I like the- Oh, these guys respawn. Oh my god, I'm gonna die. I need some help.
You know what I mean? That is so important to me. That is so important to me. That is like the most important thing. It's so important to me that you guys, that I can talk to you like this.
At the last minute, I've never said anything like that. Ever. To anybody, let alone people on a stream. I'm really glad that you got to hear it. The last 20 to 30 seconds again, I've never talked like that to anybody. I'm so glad that I could say it to you.
Oh, I'm so happy I could get it off my chest.
I think my internet's like fucked up right now. It's like 10 o'clock at night. What's happening here?
Ooh, I'll take the fire wand. Sorry, I'm kind of playing like shit. I'm just making sure my stream is still up.
Are we good? All right. I gotta pay attention because I have this fucking random shit.
You're stuck? Well, refresh. Yeah, refresh. We're good.
All right. There we go. Level two. Good chest. No.
Hey dude, erectile dysfunction is rare. You're not alone.
All right. Stop looking at your chat. Yeah, I know. I'm just like looking at the bitrate. I'm just concerned.
All right. There we go. All right. I can evolve this now.
The tiramisu is a revive, but it also evolves the gun.
Why is everybody omega lowing? Why is everybody omega lowing? Omega lowing?
Why is everybody omega lowing? Whatever. It's art.
I think if you have, if I get at least two more of these, I think I'll be fine.
I hope so. Yeah. I mean, why is there omega low?
Chest. Nice.
Ooh, actually, I got the upgrade. That's cool. That's pretty cool.
I might have to restart the run. This is not a great one.
I got hit. I don't know why. Why is my chat being weird?
Why can I not see the chat anymore? This is weird.
He's back. What? Oh, chat back up, please.
That was so emotional. Sorry, mods. I apologize.
I think I can salvage this, actually. Yeah, I'm dead.
Oh, I have a revive. That's right. Oops.
Sorry, I was too busy looking over. Is that a joke?
Um, I don't know what it looked like.
I'm trying to see what it looked like.
You suck at this. No, I'm just not paying that much attention.
Wait, did it, was I in the chair?
There was a point when I was not in the chair, right?
Have I been, wait, have I been in the chair the whole time?
Like, I have been sitting in this chair the whole time.
You were always in the chair. Really?
I, I killed the internet and like got out of frame and it came back.
And it was live for like 30 seconds.
And then I turned the internet, I could switch the internet again.
I turned it back on and I was sitting in the chair again.
But it didn't work.
I never left the chair.
How? That makes no sense.
Dude, I was live with the chair for at least a minute, at least.
Like, I was not in the chair.
And I crawled around the bottom.
I wonder if it's, if it's here, like on my OBS.
Because I will show you.
I will, oh, it got eaten by the buffer.
But no, if I did that once, the other like 15 times, it would not have killed me.
I did it one time because I was like, whatever, it's happening every fucking 30 seconds anyway.
All of them were legitimate.
Like, my internet just fucked up right now.
Except for the one that I tried to go away from the chair.
Yeah, these are real.
Let me try to salvage this one.
I can.
Let's get some health and I should be alright.
Nevada is a wasteland.
Okay.
I died on purpose because I want to do a real one.
Let's go.
New title?
We lost like 5k viewers from that.
Well, I mean, I get, I mean, it's like a 10 o'clock at night Pacific.
My internet's being a piece of shit.
Oh, I'm telling, I swear only one of those was a joke.
The other 15 were real.
So I figured it was like, alright, this is just happening anyways.
I just want to try to do something funny with it.
Alright, perfect.
Let's go.
This is the real one.
This is the one I'm going to win.
Alright, good, good, good, good, good.
Good, good, good.
I want the whip.
It feels like every time there's an Elden Ring stream there's bandwidth problems.
That is fucking weird.
Sorry, I'm just swearing.
That is very, that's odd.
Why is that?
Right?
That's very strange.
Okay, definitely want, I'll take the sand and water.
Give me these.
There we go.
Duplicator.
Hell yeah.
Evolve that into the super lightning and we'll be good to go.
Circular motions are really good with this because they spread around.
Just gives you like a little defense.
I think so.
Good.
Upgraded Santa Destroy into water, whatever.
More heroes.
Also, keep in mind I'm playing on the hard mode where the enemies have 50% more health.
I gotta try to survive 30 minutes.
I want that.
Alright.
Uhh, definitely that one.
Upgraded dusting.
Looks much better.
Uhh, more dusting.
This is not bad.
Ooh, nice.
Even more projectiles.
Very, oh, that's okay.
Okay, okay, that's okay.
Very good.
This is to do the song of mana, right?
Is this part simulator?
Uhh, no, this is better.
Bad, sorry.
Jerma does not read his chat.
Every time you see me go like this, I'm looking at chat.
Like here is like the top of the chat.
Here is the bottom of chat.
This is me looking at me.
What's going on, dude?
How you doing?
Doing pretty good.
Here I am.
More.
Pass through more enemies.
Alright, this is looking like it's gonna play out pretty well.
I'm happy with this.
More dusting.
Dusting kind of sucks early, but it's really great later.
I just did.
Ooh, alright, okay, okay, okay.
I want the other gun, because now I'm gonna shoot double.
And now I need the tiramisu and this thing can get upgraded again.
I can't put my finger, but Jerma looks weird tonight.
Looks like he's got facial reconstruction surgery.
What the fuck, man?
What the fuck?
What the hell?
Dude, what the fuck?
That's so fucking weird.
I see it.
It's the fucking hair.
I don't know what it is.
You guys are crazy.
My whip.
I didn't say it was bad.
Yeah, but that's kind of like implied that I got a bunch of surgery on my face.
You look like you're wearing somebody else's skin.
Look at the spam here.
This is awesome.
I need a couple evolutions now.
Otherwise, by 10 minutes, this is gonna be a disaster.
It's the...
Okay, you know what it is?
The fact that the light in the room is off.
The ring light is on.
And I haven't had a haircut.
I just thought about that guy that said,
Oh, hey, dude, what's the baseball stream?
I'm like a new viewer.
And then Ball Fondler replied and said,
Oh, dude, at least he's gonna shove an entire baseball up his ass.
And more than I was thinking about this,
and me and Holly were talking about this,
we're laughing our asses off about this because it's like,
Why would I need four or five months of planning to do that?
Like, oh, here it is, guys, the big baseball stream.
And I shove a baseball up my ass.
Oh, guys, get hyped.
The baseball stream is in four months.
Why would it...
Why would I need to do that?
Huh?
Oh, that's so fucking...
That's like so funny.
You have no idea.
And more than I think about that, it's just like,
Why?
Imagine me announcing that.
Guys, get hyped for the baseball stream.
Yo, baseball.
Yeah, what's gonna happen is I'm gonna be on camera
and I'm gonna shove a baseball up my ass.
Fog, you fog champ, let's go.
Uh, what?
I'm like hyping that up for months?
There's so many layers to why I think that that is really funny.
And I'm like hyping it up for months.
And then I just get permanently banned in 10 seconds.
Like, what did I...
What do you think is going to happen?
Why would that ever be something that you get hyped about?
Insane.
There's so many layers.
I just can't...
That's such an onion...
Oh, it's a joke.
All right, I want the whip, yo.
Look at how good the gun is.
It's insane.
It's so good.
Crazy stream this has been, huh?
This has been wild.
There's been a few wild ones over the last week or two here.
They're getting a little wild.
I want the chest in here because I want to know where it is.
When I get full levels, I want to be able to upgrade something.
Okay, here we go.
Yeah, don't die.
All right, I got to collect stuff for the weapon.
All right, I need four...
And I also think about this stuff, too.
The guy that wrote that.
Like, what are you up to right now?
Like, what do you...
Like, what does your day look like today?
Are you doing good?
Like, you're just hanging out?
Like, what is the Ball Fondler's, like, theme today?
You know what I mean?
I'm kind of curious.
Is this a cooldown game?
Yeah, it is.
All right, come on.
I hope the Ball Fondler's, like, doing good, you know?
Okay, hold on.
Please give it to me.
All right, level eight.
Dust is now a heal.
Very big deal.
Almost have this maximum.
All right, that's one max.
Do I have them both maxed out?
I need a little bit more.
Getting there.
The dust is now healing the shitload, so it's really, really good.
Jesus.
I need something to evolve right now.
We're very soon.
I'm going to get overwhelmed.
All right, here's another chest.
There's another chest.
No chest?
All right, go.
Collectathon.
Lightning.
More cooldown.
I want that.
I want Santa water.
Okay, getting there.
Seven.
Done.
I need one more and done.
And then this thing goes crazy.
Lightning Ring.
I have Duplicator.
Yeah, I do.
More cooldown.
More lightning.
Almost there.
Come on.
I'm almost halfway there.
Way too dank.
Actually, it is kind of loud.
Thanks for letting me know.
There's so many chests.
Just give me a max thing already.
Come on.
And then we can just coast.
I could open one of them, maybe.
That might be not a bad idea.
Oh, shit.
All right.
Oh, okay.
These bats are the worst.
I need chicken.
Okay, back this way.
More chicken.
Get it.
If I had a vacuum, this would be amazing.
Level eight.
There we go.
Perfect.
Hell yeah.
All right.
Now I need those chests.
And watch this.
Super gun.
The Fear Raggy.
Scales with revivals.
Watch this.
Yep.
Now I have another room for another weapon, too.
Lightning Rod.
Eight.
Hell yeah.
Go with whip.
Thunder.
Thunder Loop.
Evolve lightning.
Strikes twice.
Now I'm more confident that I'll be fine.
Area of attack?
I think I want that.
I need...
What do I need for this?
Yeah.
Actually, no.
Not yet.
I have to figure out what other weapon I want.
Whip again.
Ooh, yep.
I'll take it.
There's another one there, too.
I'm going to save that other one as well.
It's on.
Because of the cooldown, it's on permanently.
Kind of distracting.
Maybe I should just get area and forget about another upgrade.
Because area would be...
This would just keep spreading out.
Play Bloons?
I think I did it.
Didn't I do it before?
Do the whip.
Okay, so now I need to get Santa water up.
Bloons is fun.
I would play it.
I've got to think what else I want to do on Friday if we don't do the Elden Ring thing.
Because I'm doing the sponsor thing.
But I want to do something else, too.
I'll take a look.
New Bloons.
Or Inscription.
Play the new Bloons game, man.
Good luck.
Okay, I need...
Almost there.
Inscription.
Hey, B.
I feel like I have too much of a P-brain to do the later parts of Inscription.
I'm sure it's going to keep getting harder.
I'm just picking one of these up.
Paladins?
I'm going to wait and take that at the very end.
It's going to be insane.
I'm killing things so fast, all the coins are spreading out too much.
Ten more minutes and that's it.
I just take this.
Whatever.
Tiramisu plus two.
This thing scales with revival, so now I have two.
So much health on the ground.
Now let's get the chest for one of them.
So what do I want for another weapon?
What do I have as upgrades?
What does the book do?
The book Wand?
I know everybody hates Wand, right?
Everybody hates Wand.
I even embrace her.
Oh, I didn't want to pick that up.
Still alive after getting hit by this?
Axe?
Yeah, Axe is probably a good idea.
If I get the Axe, I'll do Axe and...
Ooh, but wait.
I kind of want this.
Now I need the curse item, which I have.
I'm probably going to be untouchable, by the way.
No one's going to be able to get over here.
Oh god, here we go.
Just don't move.
Play Five Nights at Freddy's 4.
You know, I watched a comprehensive lore video on Five Nights at Freddy's the other day.
I just did.
You know, the comfiest thing for me at this point is to just be in bed with my iPad and
watch just like 50 minute long comprehensive lore dissection videos on franchises that
I don't care about at all.
It's interesting to me.
I don't know why.
All right.
Give me the...
Okay.
Well, whatever.
I need the curse item.
It's not the curse item.
I could banish some.
I'm going to banish some stuff now because I don't want to see it.
You know what I think is probably interesting to me?
Because I know that there's a ton of people that are really, really interested in this.
And I almost get to sit there and be an observer saying, oh, I wonder what they're going to
think about that.
Will the community agree?
Please explain Five Nights at Freddy's.
Okay.
William Afton was co-owner of Freddy Fazbear Pizza or a different company or something.
And he ended...
Is this a spoiler?
I just want...
I need to prove that I've been watching.
William Afton had a son, Michael Afton, who went on to do something else or something.
It ended up being that William Afton was a pretty bad guy and ended up...
Essentially, he was a...
Well, it was a spoiler for Five Nights at Freddy's, by the way.
So he was a serial killer.
He killed people.
And he would...
He killed them at the Freddy Fazbear restaurant.
Eventually, people got sick and tired of it, of him killing people.
And somebody got figured it out and killed him.
And then they stuffed him into a rabbit suit.
And then he can't...
He keeps coming back.
And he got killed like five times now or something.
And then his daughter is the doll in the game that is called Sister Location.
You dreamed this.
I did not dream this.
This is for real.
This is what happened.
Look at all these chests.
And then Freddy Fazbear becomes Tony the Tiger in the new game.
And he's good and helps you.
He's like, oh, I'm going to help you.
And he talks about like nutritional food and stuff and wants you to be like healthy.
I need...
Where's the curse item?
But who is Freddy Fazbear?
Who is Freddy Fazbear?
That's what I want to know.
A...
I don't know.
Who is Freddy Fazbear?
Tomar Raid.
What's up, Tomar?
Thanks for the raid.
Welcome, Tomar.
Late night vampire survivors.
Thanks for the raid.
I looked at like...
I looked you directly in the eyes.
Hey, thanks for the raid.
Does that feel weird?
Like when I look directly into the camera and point and address you?
I need to banish something because this is not what I want.
I always figured that...
Okay, wait.
Pay attention.
This thing's going to kill me.
I always don't like looking directly in the camera because I feel like it freaks people
out.
I like looking just kind of barely off the camera.
Like...
Okay, wait.
Pay attention.
This thing's going to kill me.
I always don't like looking directly in the camera because I feel like it freaks people
out.
I like looking just kind of barely off the camera.
Like...
Looking this way.
What's happening?
Is that like...
Dunk, dunk, dunk, dunk.
That usually means something bad.
All right.
I got five minutes left and I win.
On the hard level.
Die!
Whoa!
That claw's huge.
Die!
I want to die!
Still haven't seen...
I got to start banishing other stuff.
Okay, this is where I'm going to see it.
Banish.
Well, I'm not going to get the upgrade, but I'll at least be able to get the...
There's luck, I guess.
Oh well.
I think this is a win, though.
It's going to be fine.
This thing has a lot of health.
There we go.
Finally.
Wait, what?
What does the title say?
Is it, I'm doing a speed run?
Money.
To all the fellow EU watchers, good morning.
Yeah, good morning.
The title's horrible.
What is the title?
I didn't do it.
What's the title?
Who fucking did this?
Why?
How long has it been like this for?
No hacks?
Who did this?
I'm deleting it.
Have the mods just been adding stuff to the title?
For like the last hour?
Bring that up.
No, that wasn't me.
I didn't do that.
That wasn't me.
You know, I'm so absent-minded.
The mods could probably just do that every stream, and I would not know if you didn't
tell me.
I gotta try to get to level like 100.
Level 99 with the dog.
I think I'm too far away, but I can try.
Gotta stand still.
Can I get to 99 in two, three minutes?
But it's just money.
Whatever.
That's cool though.
Money done.
Mods rioting.
Come on, I need to get to level 99.
I won't get there.
But at least I'll win.
I need to get to level 99.
I won't get there.
But at least I'll win.
Alright, this is where it's going to happen.
I sneak up here.
Okay, don't be stupid about it.
One minute. I got it. What do you unlock for doing this? Oh my god. This is gonna get actually kind of scary
I'm gonna keep moving. Don't let him collapse it 30 seconds. All right. I'm good. I got it. Five four three two one good
Yeah, cool. I'm what's going on here. Why is it so slow?
It spawns another one right if you every minute or something my faster
I don't have any movement speed or any slow down do I but I know of flowers doing that. Oh
Oh
All right. Yeah, you can't win anyways
Yeah, you can't win. Oh, I got skip another skip and that's it six point two million from the
quad guns
Very cool. All right. I'll see you guys later. I'll see you guys on Friday Friday. We'll do some fun stuff
There will be a sponsor segment on Friday. I gotta talk to Ludwig and see what the plan is
We might do it Friday. We might move it. I probably gonna say we need to have another few days
We'll do some fun stuff. We'll play much stuff Friday afternoon. I'll update you. What's the title say? No, let's title say
Let me see what the title is before I leave
One down mods writing gone among us higher pH value stream kill stream chaotic neutral vibes plus ratio
Do one of the mods get hacked? All right. I'll see you guys later. Thanks for watching
Thanks to the mods for helping do the Elden Ring stuff earlier
Thanks for you. Obviously for sticking around. Have a great night. That was fun
I've you know, I've really really like bounce around streams where it's like, alright, we got this
This is like a two-hour thing. This is like a couple hours. This is like two or three hours
I I like this a lot. I like kind of bouncing around they don't all have to be like this, but I like doing this
It's a lot of variety. I like it that scare that horror game was really really off-putting really terrifying. It was cool
Crazy experience. Give me some more of those kind of games. Give me some more of those kind of short horror experiences
I've missed a lot over the years. It's been a long time
There's a solid half dozen or at least dozen or so of those two ish hour three ish hour
Horror experiences that I'd like to play some more. They're interesting
I completely forgot about the barf drinker and juggles and all the other Elden Ring. That was so much fun
I'll see you guys on Friday
Keep an eye on the sus because I'll update what's gonna happen and keep an eye on the discord, too
I will converse with Ludwig. We'll see what's gonna happen. Your hair is fine, by the way
Don't let chat make you self-conscious. Oh, no, I'm fine. I'm fine. I know everyone's just walking around. I have to all right
I'm good. I wonder what was going on with the internet. It's weird
I'd say once every two or three weeks
There'll be one night where I just randomly every hour will just start dropping frames for like a minute or two straight
It's completely rock solid the rest of the time though
I would imagine it probably has to do with a VPN because I stream with a VPN a lot of times
They're gonna do some more recruiting for the Elden Ring stuff. I want to it's probably gonna happen offline
Just because of how difficult it was to kind of manage
The amount of people that we're trying to join so keep an eye on the discord. I'll keep you guys updated
Well, you know, I'll see you guys soon. Take care. See you Friday
Regardless of what we do. See you soon