Hi guys. Throw, throw, throw, get the rocks out of here. No rocks today. It's supposed to be a
chill out, hang out, the veg out stream. That means when you like eat a shitload of vegetables,
right? When you're a bodybuilder. You don't understand. The reason why it took me like
20 minutes or so, I got carrots, I've got tomatoes, I've got fresh, some fresh garden roots,
all sitting right here. And my coffee's still too hot to drink. I hate when that happens.
When am I going to do a cooking stream? That you'll maybe. But today we're going to do something
a little different today. Hang out and have a little fun. We're going to just play plain. Okay.
We're going to. Yeah, that's a nice scripted joke. Because I've been doing some more intense video
games for the last three or four screens besides Viscera, but that was intense too. Not today.
We're just going to sit here like this. I'm sorry. Like this. Hi. Welcome to an in real life stream
where I sit here and drink coffee and we talk about topics. You know what I mean? I'm not going to
shave. I'm not doing it. You know, what, what, what topic are we going to talk about today?
I think we're going to talk about what's the current state of magical wizard board. What's the
current state of that game? Does it even still fucking exist? I got this free mouse pad in 2012
and I've, I've never not used another mouse pad. I'm also a little tired today. Your audio sounds
bad. Wait, we've got some fun things to try today in our IRL stream. Now that I pulled that out,
I just fucked up my whole desk though. Kenshi won the poll. I'm probably going to play Kenshi.
We need to start. I need to just relax for a little bit. Okay. Just chill out. Why do I have
villain hair? Because I just do. I have to accept it at some point that I'm just, I'm a fucking bad
guy, right? You can't be a good guy with this kind of hair drinking out of this kind of cup.
Like this, this is a bad, this is a bad guy sitting here. Uh, anyways, uh, give me one second.
I wanted to try something today because I have this thing. I know the audio doesn't sound very
good, but that's for very specific reasons because the voice changer is currently as you can see,
turning the fuck off. No, uh, I have a bunch of different presets here that probably sound a little
fucking strange. I want to do this a bit. This is a bit coming up. Just if you're serious.
The thing is, I don't know what this sounds like. Oh, it sounds like this. That sounds fucking
horrible. Ow! What is this one? Hello? I don't know what this is supposed to be for. This is
called romantic Paris. I think this is just background noise. Yeah. I don't think that does
anything. Uh, but yeah, welcome. How many, how many, how many, do I have chat in the right place?
No, chat's in the wrong place today. I forgot. Dude, just do a date. Can I have two going at
once? No, we're not doing a fucking virtual date. I want to do a singing stream where I put, I was
going to get an elaborate costume. I didn't have any time though. And turn on this and sing and
like put like, like fuck up the video for a little bit and pretend like this is a real singing stream
and have people come in and yell at me that I have a like auto tune on. What is sword? Sword. I,
oh, it's because it's, it's because it's going like round round round. I get it. I get it.
The lightsaber sound. But is it really though? This is called zombie. Zombie. Same with this song.
This is not even the rap. You're layering. Let me tell you guys something. This is this kind of stream
where we talk about topics and I mean like Jesus. What's going on in the industry right now?
You've got blizzard is acting all crazy. What the heck is that? What the heck is going on here?
I literally can't understand a single thing you're saying. Should I speak, should I speak, uh,
uh, uh, it's gonna be possible. They're layered. I'm going to try to speak from the closet as the
monster in your closet. Like they're talking about politics. I want, I'm going to get in there and
be the monster in the closet and talk, like talking about politics. We're going to have scary music.
Hold on. Is there ambience with this one? Hold on. Let me see. What the fuck is going on? Can you
guys hear, can you hear me now? Does this sound normal? I, I, I, I should sound completely normal
now. I'm, I'm, I'm doubled. Wait. Oh, okay. Now I should sound normal. Do I sound? Here we go. Okay.
So if you didn't catch the thing I said, uh, uh, I want, I'm going to go in the closet there with
that voice on and just start talking about like fucking politics and be, and be like monster in
closet stream. Like sleep tight. Uh, sticks renegade just gave $50. Thank you so much sticks for the
50 bucks. And I just got to tell you, uh, thank you so much. Uh, you say, Hey German, remember that,
uh, no, I don't, I don't want that to be on. That's probably not something I should have on
it because this is a big fucking money donation. I don't want to like fucking mock it or anything.
You know what I mean? Uh, thank you for the $50 though, for real. Uh, Hey German, remember that
abscess surgery I had, uh, thanks to Crohn's disease. Well, I just found out the hospital
didn't destroy my wallet. Insurance saved me 98% of almost 10 grand. So since I'm not broke,
I'll give some of those savings to you for being the best content creator ever here in my heart.
Best content creator ever. I can't even thank you, man. Like that's, uh, I'm really,
really happy to hear that you didn't have to spend a shitload of money to fix something that
your body decided to do on its own. Thank you so much. Swift, Swift recovery. Thank you for the
$50 fucking dollars. The voice is crackling. It's probably because I have too much going on. Let me
test it out. Voice crackling, crackling, crackling. Is it? Probably have to mess with some settings,
but, uh, I was going to do IRL today. I'm not even paying attention to anything else that's
going on over here. Uh, cause I have, I forgot I did my title correct. I did, I did my hair like
so fast and I don't even, it doesn't even look that good and the lights are all wrong, but, um,
I wanted just to hang out today. Speaking of lights, I can brighten it up a little bit in here.
Uh, where's my mouse? Cause, I don't know, I like to do little IRL streams. Sometimes we just dick
around and do nothing. You know, it's fun. Sometimes you just want to do that and we'll
probably end up, cause I mean, I'm not going to sit here for six hours doing this. We'll probably
end up going to Kenshi or, uh, what's the other one? I have an uneven receding hairline. No,
it's, it's pretty even. It's just over here because my hair is pushed this way. So like see,
the other hair is like, my hair is like combed this way. So it's actually like here, but it's,
it just looks that way because it's combed it that way. Simpsons 100% run. Well, hold on. First
things first, I gotta get my goddamn, I gotta check my words with friends. Onomatopoeia,
that's a triple word score. Uh, I need to change the lights for one. Why do I give a shit if you
can see the screen or not? I don't understand. That's like not a big deal. I don't know. There's
nothing on here that's like that important. I'm like, wait a minute. Where is it? Try to change
this a little because this needs to be a little bit brighter. It's not bright enough for me.
I need more brightness. I don't know. I think, okay, I, I'm going to, I'll do this in chat
because I'm going to go in there and I'm going to hang out in there and be in chat and just
talk. And then I'm going to, I'm going to open the fucking door in like five minutes and there
are people that are just going to be, just pretend like I didn't start the stream yet.
Please fix the crackles. Does that fix it? Is that fixing crackles? Is it still crackling? Hey,
hey, hey, hey, yo, hey, hey, hey, hey, oh, oh, fixed. Okay. Good. So, uh, just give me a second.
Well, I'm going to, I'm going to go in the chat and just hang out for like five minutes.
So I'm just going to be in there. Let me just do like, yeah. All right. Just give me a second.
I have to go to my own stream. I forgot about that. I got like fucking weird pants on too, man.
All right. That's enough of that. I'm done with that. Uh, that was practice for later
because I'm going to draw, I'm going to make it red. Wow. That was really funny.
I thought in my head, it played out a little funnier. Scared of the dark. No, I was just in
there. I can't be scared of the dark. I'm just sitting in there. Uh, beer me, user name,
beer me a user name. Just gave five community subs. Thanks a lot beer.
He faced his fear. He can't stand chat that much. That's not true. That's completely untrue.
We're still crackling. What the fuck is happening? Hold on. I'm crackling. Why would it be
crackling? Cause I'm listening to it. Hold on. Is it crackling right now? What? Like when you hear
it through here, it's not right. So what the heck is going on here? It's just, it's well,
the voice changer is on right now. You know what I mean? It's on right now. He listened to one guy.
Oh, turn up the game. I unplugged something from my neck right now. I did not. I didn't know such
thing. Did the voice change that guy driving by? Oh shit. Still on the weird one. All right. So
here's what we're going to do. I want to try this. Set it up. Uh, go. I wonder how this is actually
going to sound. Now let's get the, uh, this might be very embarrassing. I got to make sure the voice
changer is on and working as fucking intended. No, don't worry. We're going to do demon in the
closet. We'll get, this is going to be a lot. I was just hanging out from it. It isn't already.
We can just reverse voice change it. No, you can't. Only like three people in here know how to do
that. Do you know how to do that? You know how to do that. There's people, people in here know how
to do that. I gotta be careful then. All right. So let's say I get, let's get it ambient in here.
Oh my God. It's still crackling. Here's what I'm going to do above that. Here's what's going to
happen. Ready? Turn off. Turn this off. That sounded any better? Is it still happening?
Tell me if it's still happening.
Cause that, that's the only other outliers to why that would be happening.
Cause that I had a compressor on, maybe the compressor was like, was fucking with it.
Let's, uh, still happening. Probably a loose mic now. It's nothing to do with the mic.
It's to do with the software pulling through. But I had this running during the Christmas
stream and it wasn't a problem. So I don't understand why the fuck did like 1500 people
just show up in a second. What happened? They were like 3500 people in it. It was like five,
5,000. Did I just get braided by Dr. Phil? Nice. Got braided. Well, welcome. Hey,
welcome to the setup of the joke that's not going to pay off. Rated by Robaz. Oh,
fuck. Yeah. What's up? It's like two raids in a row or two streams in a row.
It's like two or 3000 people. Damn. Well, thank you. Welcome guys. Uh, what's that?
Oh, it's an emo. I thought like, I thought something was wrong.
One mod spam. Turn up your mic. I'm so scared about the crackles. Okay, here we go.
I gotta, I gotta hear these first. Has it been like this the whole time? Why has it been on this?
That's not what I wanted. Oh my, this whole thing. Is it crackling now during this one,
this particular? Cause that would be a pain in the ass. Yes. Fuck. I don't get it.
Let me try something here real quick. Give me a second. I'm going to reboot this whole thing.
Not the screen like this program. I'm going to mute everything. So it should not be happening now.
Are we still, are we cracking? It shouldn't be at all. No, nothing, nothing, nothing.
Bang, bang, bang, bang, bang, bang, bang, bang, bang, bang, bang, bang, bang, bang, bang, bang,
right? It's because of God damn it. Okay. Hi guys. Welcome everyone to the
mic should work fucking properly because this is the mic that's actually plugged in over here.
First time singing on stream by the way. Now that that's settled, we're fine. There's no crackles.
A, B, C, D, E, F, G, H, H, K, L, M, N, P, Q, R, S, T, V, V, W, X, Y, and Z, right? We're fine.
Everything sounds good. Now. Hold on. Now. How do we sound now? I just rebooted it all.
I know it's a little quiet, but is it going cracking? That's the problem. No, no cracking,
no cracking, cracking, no cracking. I know there's a, yeah, the reverb is on because it's on this
church one. All right. I'm ready. You ready? You ready for this? I need to have like a karaoke
website. Let's go to, I need to make sure I know what this sounds like. A, hello? A, A, A,
A, A, A, A. This is that, that's doing it right? Sam's voice. Is it, it's no auto-tune? This should
be auto-tune on this. Is it not auto-tune? I think it should be. I was going to go with it.
So we got auto-tune, changing our voice to sound good, right? Okay, good. Now I need a karaoke,
free karaoke website. I turned off the auto-tune because it probably sounds stupid. Hey, what's up?
It's me. So now let's go to, well, what's a good free karaoke website? Turn off the dry signal,
leave it 100% wet. Okay. Red, uh, is this, is this a real website? What's a good karaoke website?
And don't you dare. Just YouTube it. Oh yeah. All right. Okay. How about tonight's gonna be a good
night karaoke? I think that sounds pretty good. I got my auto-tune on the tonight's gonna be a
good night karaoke. They always sound so shitty too. It's always like somebody did it on a Casio
keyboard. Okay. Here we go. I can see it. You ready? I'm going to see some, here we go.
I got a feeling that tonight's gonna be a good night, that tonight's gonna be a good night,
that tonight's gonna be a good, good night. Does that sound good? That tonight. Hello?
Come on. So this is not, uh, this is not an auto-tune. Right. That makes sense. Okay.
That's wrong. So, uh, all right. I can find the auto-tune. Hello. Hello. Hello. You can always
tell when it's an auto-tune because it sounds fine. Right. You got, I gotta go. I'm going to
rip through these octaves. Ready? This is auto-tune. It has to be. I'm ready. And in three, two, one,
let's bring it on.掌声 Come on, let's go. Clap it up. Clap it up.
Clap it up. Let's clap it up. I got a feeling that tonight's gonna be a good night, that
tonight's gonna be a good night, that tonight's gonna be a good, good night. I got a feeling
Tonight's gonna be a good night.
Tonight's gonna be a good good night.
I got feeling.
Woo-hoo!
It's gonna be a good night.
That tonight's gonna be a good night.
That tonight's gonna be a good...
Oh, doesn't the song have lyrics?
I've got that feeling!
Whoo-hoo-hoo-hoo, no, that's it. How long does this go on for? How long?
Yeah, good night, but tonight's gonna be a good day
Tonight's the night
Let's live it up
I've got my money
Let's spend it all
Go out and smash it like oh my god
Jump off that sofa
Let's get it off. I
Know that we'll have a ball if we get down and go out and just lose it all
Way
You fill up my cup
Shove it up
Ever but handsome. Let's spin it up. Let's paint that town. We'll shut it down
Let's burn the roof and then we'll do it again
Let's do it. Let's do it. Let's do it. Do it. Let's do it. Let's do it
Let's get fucking sued do it and do it do it do it do it do it do it
And do it let's get fucking sued
That's gonna be a good night that tonight's go. Look at this like fucking earn my cracking hair
I'm getting sued for this one
Let's leave it up, let's leave that sounds fucking awful. Let's live
This makes for the song is called I got a fucking
All right, let's what do you say?
Tonight, what do you say about that? What do you guys think about that? Huh? I got a feeling
That tonight's gonna be a good night that tonight's gonna be
Let me tell you about politics
Can I unmute that yeah, you can now do a different song
Why is this like a good this auto correcting for some strange reason? That's better. I mean that's scary music
Oh, god damn it the fucking voice changer. All right, so
You ready?
Turn the light on. I know I'll get like a scary light in the closet. Don't worry more red. Yeah, you're right
More red. I don't know how you're gonna be able to hear me from back there. Hey, remember those like
3,000 people that came in the raid. Oh
All right, why it's cuz the white balance is going automatically fuck off white balance. That's better. That's pretty red. Oh
What happened?
What happened
No, what?
Hello, what the fuck happened here? No, my god. I have to like read
I
Give me a break
It's the whole thing's crashed out. I guess this did this webcam just die. I think the webcam just died
This thing's brand new
Hold on. I gotta like read I could have you gotta be kidding me
What broke it because I changed the white balance. That's a lot of bullshit. Oh, yeah, I don't even know this thing's plugged in
I gotta like unplug it. I might this is gonna like crash the whole stream
This is not good
What the hell what I was just getting started with like the oh
This is not good. All right, I'm gonna try to rip it out because it's no. What are you doing?
Use the mic as a webcam. What does that even mean?
Use my microphone as a webcam
What I'm so confused
Hold on. All right. Everybody say it fucking Hail Mary because I'm ripping the cord out
Let's see if it happened. We good. Am I still live? I'm good, right? I think we're good
We're good. What happened to the camera?
Am I still alive and I mean that it work land physically. It looks like a thermal camera now
This thing's broken. All right, what the fuck are we doing? Oh, yeah, I was gonna get in that closet and say a bunch of bullshit
Yeah, hello. Yeah, good. No now something's really fucked up. All right, so I got yeah
I got three monitors one two three. All right, so let's do a straw poll because I want I'm curious at what you guys think
Here you go, please vote if you haven't if you have even if you have it has not been even one one
You understand just here you go
All right. So what do you guys want me to do? What are you looking for today? No, I
Was I wanted to see how badly this was gonna lose. What is monster discussion? Well, I don't I haven't figured that out yet
Can I vote for neither? Yeah
Just go like this
Oh already really I
Didn't do anything yet
Okay. So what do you what are we looking out here? That's a fantastic cup. It was a gift. It was a gift from my girlfriend
I don't know. I noticed you got it at some store. Probably get it on
Probably get on an Amazon if I were to guess maybe
Alright, so it looks like I wanted to see how badly karaoke was gonna get destroyed and didn't really get destroyed that badly
Which is kind of a shock
that clip that clip of me got will go around and it'll be like
What an embarrassment, but I know it will
And I'm gonna be lying there in bed just with my fucking iPad looking at clips of like good night
No, I'm gonna be like, oh fuck me. What have I done myself?
alright, so let's uh, let's go ahead and
Get some scary music. I'm gonna turn the light down. I don't know why I was going that high
Okay. So here we go. I got a loop this
This is
Why my computer is fucked up. Did I like sing so poorly and with a fucking voice changer on that it broke the computer
Let's see how this one sounds. That's pretty good
Now I'm gonna drop the light a lot and then I'm gonna have a light in the closet and I don't even know if you're gonna
Be able to hear me
The last time I fucked with the light on this thing. We had a huge problem
That's fine. A little more. That looks good. That looks good. That looks weird
Like my my lips never let my lips this big and red
Holy shit. This is not sweat on my shoulders. You can't do that one to me. Don't do me like this. That's not sweat
That's a light casting. I look like
No, it's my beard I
Look pretty fucking evil. All right, you ready?
This is gonna be awful this whole don't worry that let me let me like keep doing awful shit
So you forget how awful the karaoke portion of this stream was and that wasn't even karaoke it was just a joke
But forget it. Let's keep doing terrible shit. So like well look when there's like ten terrible bits in a row
What I what was the worst one? I don't remember what he what was the first one he did
Oh, he did like the carry. Well, that was other one
That one he like fucking went outside his window and screamed. I was fucking stupid too. All right, let's go
About the good climate
Monsters are real that's the tagline for this one
Oh
Was I incomprehensible we didn't hear anything no, just give me a clip
Show it to me I
Said some fucking good shit during that
Really? Oh god. Damn it. Oh, well, we got the gist of it. All right, can I turn off like the I'm gonna go back into here
All I heard is something about monsters being real. This is so fucked up. There we go. That looks that's better
Why does turning the brightness down fuck the whole thing up?
Something about the closet being too small. Yeah
That was part of it. I
Heard the word monsters ink. Yeah, I got my photos developing back there. That's what's over there. I
Heard don't call the police
anyways
So right now here's the funny story about that
Right there right there. I mean like I mean literally right there is
Probably where Kim's head is where she's lying down right now on the other side of that closet wall
so
She's probably just like
What the fuck is going on in that room? No, like she's on the other side of the she's on the other side of the wall
She's not in there. Look, you know what's in here
Oh
Eat your ass as a necklace. No, that's not what I said. All right, so
Have I been I've been sitting here for 51 minutes
It's been I felt like it's been like three
That doesn't even sound scary that sounds that sounds like shit
German shitting himself right now. No, I'm fine. All right, so we had our fun in IRL
You can see my face I
like my like human
Like boy face is just sitting right there. Like I said, we're gonna do I'm gonna change this from sitting around
Well knock not yet. Hold on. They cancel that not quite yet
All right. We're gonna do one more thing. What the hell is it?
There's also this one too
This just this just sounds like somebody punched me right here
Sounds like I'm something stuck in my throat. This is the chad voice
Yeah, I mean might as well just finish it up today
I'm just kidding. I'm kidding. I'm not gonna do it. Don't worry
Where's the root? Did it take me this long to find it? This is it?
This is it. I found it. This is like a hundred and fifty ones to click on here. What about this one?
Magic this is it. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Oh god. Damn it. This actually is the one. Okay, so I mean
What's the song with like that I want to sing before we move on the rats mixtape September. Yeah, it's a good one
How's the sun? It's pretty good
It's not fixing my teeth, it's not fixing it
But don't matter I can knock this out of the park. You can redo it. Do you remember?
The 21st night of September
Love was changing the minds of pretenders
Pretender and this
It fucked up it did it wasn't even on the screen
Our hearts were ringing in the key that our souls were singing
As we danced in the night. I remember
How the stars stole the night away
Yeah, but did ya say that you remember but did ya
Dancing in September. Ah, did ya?
Never was a cloudy day
Oh, no, never mind
It's not that part over again. Bah, do do bah, do do bah, do bah, do do bah, do do bah, do
Bah, do do but oh that's I fucking hate this. I almost just clicked stop streaming. I was like hovering over and almost just clicked it
All right, so we're gonna move on
Thanks for hanging out for the irl
Uh, I don't know what I did. It was more than one to do this for like an hour. It's what we're linking
It's not fixing my teeth it's not fixing it it probably sounds all right
But don't matter I can I can knock this out of the park. You can redo it. Do you remember?
The 21st night of September
Love was changing the minds of pretenders
and this
Why is it off? I was doing this perfect. Why is it off beat?
Oh shit
Okay, it's off beat because
This takes like about 150 milliseconds to change the voice
There's a delay
on the actual voice changer
I thought you just had no rhythm. No, that's not what it is
Don't point change. Yeah, I I actually can fix that in here, but
I didn't think about that
Too busy doing another dumb shit
Prove it with video evidence
I mean
Hold on is is this coming out? Correct?
Is that synced up because I have the it's it's turned off right now. It should be like ready
So but now that it's on
The length is the same. So
It's because it doesn't matter. Hold on a second. I got an idea
Make it go 150 milliseconds. No, I can do this ready. I'm just gonna delay
The yeah, they'll just do this. It should be better. No, so you tell me did I fix it?
Oh
Love was changing the minds of pretenders
No, what
It's worse now. How is it worse?
Maybe I have to do this
How many respects is it ready?
Yeah
Whatever sorry, was that too loud? I have a limiter on the limiter doesn't work. The limiter doesn't work
All right. Thanks for watching this stream. We're gonna play against you now. Okay. Hey guys
Welcome back
Uh, wait, I peeked
Why is it mike mike's not fucking whatever. I'm sorry
Uh, what do I need the stream?
Our plane just landed
Did you
Wait, did you shit in my it? I I just changed the microphone source
I'm really i'm really actually fucking sorry like doing that
fucked up like
Made a loud noise or something. Sorry
That's not my intention at all. I promise
Now it's delayed. Well, it's because I have to do this now
All right, let's play catchy
I forgive you this time
Thank you
It's not still delayed. I could see it in real time right here
Uh, what was it called the band of?
the band of mary, uh
frog frog crew
Play geoguessr. Wait, why am I getting a huge play geoguess geoguessr geoguessr?
You want more of this shit?
What is going on in this chat right now?
Oh my god
Yeah, I mean wait. All right. Hold on. I'm gonna play kenshi for a little while because
I I planned on it anyways
So then after after kenshi maybe a few three four hours of kenshi. I'll
Pull out and we'll play some
I don't why would I I don't want to I all right, we'll see
And i'm i'm getting booed
Now i'm getting booed
It's okay
We'll just keep the fucking camera on who cares
Well, this will be it. This will be the one webcam stream every three months that you get on this stream
That's fine
And then I need to move over here
Uh, this is the frog crew, right?
You actually want to know what kenshi is. It's a great simulation
Frog simulating kind of game where you you start as a frog
and you start as a tadpole and then from tadpole you go to
Um adolescent and then from adolescent you go to frog and then from frog you go to adult frog
And you eat fish and you um
Eat flies and stuff. It's really cool
You get a dog
Now this needs to move this way
And let's open it up
Kenshi back to kenshi
I'm probably gonna mute this for a second just because it's probably gonna be pretty loud
Let's go with that
You should see it right now