Oh, Dr. Pepper? No, here we go. All right. So while this while this cutscene plays out,
I'm going to sprint to go get a Dr. Pepper. Oh, I wait the cutscene. I have to hit like
X for the cutscene to like continue. All right, ready? 60 seconds. I have I have 60 seconds to
go get a Dr. Pepper. Here we go. Start counting the second I start sprinting. Okay, here we go.
Oh, what's the time? Did I make it? I think I did. Dr. Pepper. What was that like 31 seconds?
Something like that. Oh, no, why did my flash plug-in crash? Am I still streaming right now?
Hold on a second. That would have been bad. Okay, I'm still streaming. My like entire like
computer is almost crashed. Or did it? Oh, I think we're still here. Oh, we're here. Okay.
Everything just crashed. That was weird. Bottoms up boys and girls. If you're in the stream,
this is to you. Whoa. It always is good the first sip. Let's get going. Oh, chug it, chug it.
I can't chug it. I gotta savor this one. It's gonna last me a little while. Click here. Sound
come back on. All right. So what does this old dude want me to do? He wants to be a doctor or
something. Apparently he already is. Okay. Oh, the booster version 2.0. Please honor my final request.
What is he dying? Why is he dead? I'm looking at the chat right now and all I see is chug,
chug, chug. All right, fine. I will do it. I will do it. I wanted to like drink this.
I'm gonna puke on stream. Like you're gonna see me puke on stream. It's gonna happen.
I'm gonna savor it for like two minutes and then I'm not gonna tell you when I'm gonna do it.
So here's how it's gonna happen. I'm gonna just do it at a very random time. You're not gonna know
until it happens. So there you go. Oh, wow. That was great. I wasn't even reading that. Where do I
go? I have no idea. I didn't even read one word of that text. Can somebody tell me where I'm going?
Maybe I'll just talk to him again. Take suit and escape from this island, please. Okay. Well,
where the hell is she? I thought she like went to bed. So how do I equip it? Press the jump
button while airborne and boost in one of four directions. Yeah, I want to equip it. Are you
kidding me? Let's go. Oh, man. Look at that. Oh, this thing is, this thing is sick. All right.
Hold on. I gotta read the chat. Go to the grassland. All right. Well, let's go get her. Do I have to go
in the teleporter? I don't think so. So do I have to go to the egg corridor? I gotta go to the egg?
Right. All right. We're going to the, we're going to the egg corridor. You thought I was gonna chug
it, didn't you? No, you're never going to know when that happens. It's just going to happen.
Hey, dude. I don't know what's going on. Why are you asking me? You're supposed to,
you're the one that like lives here. Oh, that's delicious. Oh, look out, the frogs. Come on,
you frog freaks. Come here. Actually, I like this weapon. This weapon is fun to use. I should have
used it for a while now. Wow. Wow. That guy came out of nowhere. Look at that guy. Come here. Yeah,
flying gear team. Still level one. I gotta stop getting hit. That's my issue here. I can just
kill you. Open the treasure chest. Max missiles and max missiles increased by five. Sweet. Oh,
wow. I forget. Somebody just told me I could hover. I like completely forgot about that.
Whoa. Come here. Come here. Oh, that's so awesome. That lasts for a long time.
Uh, this game is free. Cave Story, the regular Cave Story, I believe is free. Is it? But Cave
Story Plus is not free. You can get it on Steam. I believe for $10. I could be wrong.
So should I, do I have to go in this door? Oh, that was such a bad idea.
Whose idea was that? Whose idea was that? Because we're no longer friends. It was my idea.
Jerma, you're not my friend anymore. Oh, do I have to have like a boss fight right now? I'm gonna
die. Why did I just kill that guy? It will harm your health.
I'll be fine. That's not the first time I've done that.