Hello everybody, or I'm dropping a lot of frames in the very beginning here.
Uh oh, this is a bad sign. Hopefully it situates itself
so we can stream a video game. Oof. Oof. Come on, pull it through here, man.
Pull it through. You can do it. Well, at least I hope so.
But, hello. If we're able to stream today, which we should be, hopefully.
Sam and Max, hope you're having a good day. And you all as well. I mean, not
just Sam and Max. I hope they have a great time on stream today.
Why are all the planets orbiting the moon? Uh,
because that's what it looks like through a telescope.
I don't, this, oh by the way, probably gonna get this remade as well.
Gonna add some planets, change it up a little bit.
You thought the title said what? Why? It's not moon.
That is the moon. But, uh, as of tomorrow,
I'll give you an internet update here. I've been told that
they're going to try to fix it tomorrow. Somewhere in the plant, who knows what
they're gonna do. But hopefully this is situated as of
tomorrow, or the next day. I'm gonna give them a couple days to
figure it out. But, yep, we're gonna do Sam and Max. We are at
the point in Sam and Max, episode three, season two.
Episode four, maybe. We'll do the two episodes, see where we're at.
Starting early because I have to go get Kim later.
So I want to be able to do that. Starting an hour or two early.
Give me one second, and we'll get started. All right,
let me move this out of the way. Man, I've dropped 20% of every frame
in five minutes. Fuck, that's not good.
That's actually a very, very bad sign to start the stream.
Not good. Not good at all. Give me, let's just hang out for a
minute. Because if this continues like this, I
might have to change my plan on the fly here. It wasn't this bad
yesterday, not even close. Well the day before that. But this
is like actually unbearable.
What mouse and keyboard do I use? I use an Amazon Basics keyboard.
And, that's true, I actually do. And a Razer Deathadder.
What a gamer. Yeah, Razer Deathadder and an Amazon Basics.
Well we're gonna, we're gonna try. Hopefully this
kind of gets over it in the next like 20 minutes or so.
If not then I have to change plans. We're gonna do something else because I
don't want to be dropping 20% of all my frames and try to
play something. But we'll, let's go. Let's give it a
try. Hopefully it fixes itself. Anyways, let's get over here.
Ay, ay, ay. Just calm down Jeremy. You just have to just relax.
Just relax. You don't have to, don't get angry. Don't start off in a bad
mood. Just relax. Breathe in, breathe out.
Let's breathe in. Let's do it together. And then breathe in.
I think collectively if we all do this at the same time, then it'll be
maybe I'll get even more calm down, you know.
If there's like 1200 people all doing this at the same time,
it's gonna affect me. I'm gonna get all of your energies
and I won't elevate, I'm not gonna elevate my voice today. We're gonna
stay silent like this. All right, let me
restart because with this game, as you know, it
kind of just jumps right into it. Again, this is season two, episode
three. And I would like to start a new game.
Keep doing what you're doing, everybody. Keep like breathing in and
breathing out slowly because it like fixed the internet.
It definitely didn't, but you know. Here we go.
You have interfered with my plans for the last time, Sam and Ma.
Taking your- I did already see this. You'll satisfy my dark masters once
and for all. And then I will use my army of the undead to take
over the world.
Damn you, Jürgen! I never thought he'd go for the cheesy evil laugh.
Insolent to the last. No matter. Oh, we shall see how you make me
some ice cracks after you are dead. Oh, looks like this is it, little buddy.
My whole life is flashing before my eyes. I wondered why I left my wallet.
I can't even remember how we got here. Come on, Max.
Remember, we were back in the office just back from Easter Island.
Wait, wait. Do the whole thing with the music and all that.
Oh, please shoot in the intro. Yeah, don't worry. I will. I'm gonna
get them all. Here we go. We can't- Dude, I need
to play some more of these types of games.
I gotta get some more, like, mouse shooters. I feel like I'm pretty good at
them. Doesn't being High Priest of Easter Island
and President violate the separation of church and state?
Blasphemy! Hitler is giving me a religious vision!
He's turning into Beavis. He's turning into, like, a corn holio.
Hey, not bad. Hello, Commissioner?
Wait, what? Not making so much noise? Speak up, Commissioner. I can't hear you.
We're having a zombie attack. What's that, Commissioner?
Zombie attacks? Jen running George A. Romero in a baby doll t-shirt outside
the food court with a $43 gift certificate.
We're on the case. The Commissioner says zombie attacks are popping up all
over the world. Is he washing his armpits? Boils on the decaying flesh of,
well, a zombie. Wait, who's attacking? They're coming from some place called
the Zombie Factory. Ha ha, zombies! Zombie attacks! You wander around aimlessly
and see what you can turn up. Meanwhile, I'll actually figure out
where they're coming from. One step ahead of you!
All right, so, Salmon Max. Let's increase the volume a little bit
to get that authentic Salmon Max experience.
Welcome, everybody. That was the opening cut scene. Zombie apocalypse.
Incoming. See, I think the internet has settled.
It's still kind of not good, but this guy's still in here.
He's been in here for like three weeks. Hey, Leonard.
Is there any lore? Do we feed this guy? Does he eat?
Or does Jimmy? I think I hear a tiny tumbleweed blowing by your side. No, no, he's still
alive. Yeah, but like, we have to feed him. We can't just like
let him die in there. All right. I just want to look around
the office a little bit. It's been a while. We got
Melee Earhart sure screamed bloody blue murder when we yanked her chair out
from under her. She's a baby. He uses photosynthesis.
Someone's setting up thousands of dominoes across the street.
Talk about way too much time on your hands. Says the guy
watching someone set up thousands of dominoes.
Should I do that? I'm doing that one day. All right, I'm doing that like
soon. I'm doing that as soon as fucking possible.
I'm gonna do a full domino setup when I'm gonna like
set a ball up and knock him down somewhere. Yeah.
Yeah, we are. I'm doing a full domino. Okay, they're actually, this is a zombie
puzzle. All right. Well, what do you, Jimmy,
what's going on here? What do you think?
The rats have set up their own little casino.
I want to show them a new sleeper hole I learned. The boss is busy.
He can't be too busy for us. We're the ones who gave him his big break.
Not to mention various smaller fractures and sprains. That's legitimately
the only thing worse than another nintendo labo stream.
Not if I, not if I hire like five people to help me do it, you know?
Not if I hired like five people and we make a huge one.
Clowns. Is there anything about the zombie factory?
Nope. We're screwed, Sam. That rat was our only lead.
Next labo stream confirmed. All right, can we talk to the zombies? Beat it,
deadbeat. Roll again.
All right, what about this giant stein? So the zombies drink beer. Flu, perhaps?
Let's press on. All right, so they drink, so they're not actually zombies.
They're just like drunk? The zombies beer stein.
Are they, are these just like really drunk people?
All right, what do I think down here? Let's start all the way. Zombies eat for free
here. Let's check this out. He was the
only woman I ever loved. Make a Rube Goldberg machine.
Yeah, maybe you should talk about this with your therapist.
She was my therapist. I need to hire like an
engineer to be able to do that. Lamont and Wallace, you're here.
Sam and Max, actually. Whatever, your friend here is driving me crazy.
Take him off my hands, would you? What's wrong with Lincoln?
Lincoln, what's, what's going on? What's going on? I'm shaking, Abraham.
She's gone. Left me. Uh, you're talking about Sybil's gone?
Sybil! Yeah, yeah. Of course she left you.
She dumped you like yesterday's breakfast when she caught you macking
on the moai heads. I was sure it was just one of her
moods. Uh, have you heard anything about a
zombie factory? Do you mean like a factory that comes to life after it's
been shut down, cranking out products in a hideous
parody of actual production, destroying other factories it comes into contact
with? No, that's not what we're looking for.
But I wish we were. Uh, do you know anything about zombies? What do you know
about zombies? Pests, uligans, they always gather
outside the memorial with their million zombie rallies and groanings.
Always playing that awful music they listen to.
All right, well how do you stop a zombie? How do you stop a zombie?
Beats me. Just between the three of us. I'm pretty hopeless at anything
except making speeches. Okay. What? That doesn't sound right.
Let's do all dialogue options. Take it like a man. Think of all the
advantages of being single. Like what? Cox Jupiter. Yeah, this is
really bad. I'm so desperately trying to swallow
my rage right now. You have no idea. If the webcam was on, I keep looking
over here and seeing it go down to like
zero and I like if their webcam was on you would see like
like this. Ready? This is what I'm doing. Ready? Look at this. Every like
like minute or two uh this is what you this is what I do. Like I'm looking
over here I'm like trying to pay attention and I look over and I go
it happens like every 30 seconds. I gotta fucking like just
chill. I'm so fucking like tortured right now. I am
being dying tortured. I look like Abraham Lincoln.
What?
That's fine. That's fine with me. Hey Kazzy, thanks for the five community subs.
He is a lot taller than I am but thank you Kazzy.
He's like seven feet tall. You can do what you want when you want.
You answer to nobody and nobody cares if you die.
Play the feeling. You can meet lots of new people and have a never-ending
string of shallow unfulfilling encounters. Grow a
Lincoln beard for next stream. I don't think I could do that.
I don't think this is helping. We seem to be working at cross purposes Max.
Maybe but this way I get to annoy two people at once.
Do it. I can't grow a beard. Don't you guys understand?
Keep a stiff hairless upper lip Abe. Soup store thanks to the five community
subs. Thank you soup store. Back to back five community sub drops
here. Thanks a lot guys. Any items in here? Dude you know what
actually might be causing this internet problem here? And that always
seems to correlate with it. Is when we get these crazy fucking
wins. That's definitely what it is. It's just
like doing damage to something and then they gotta fix it. There's like
crazy wins. You probably hear it. Yeah whatever. I'm not gonna let it
bother me. Let's just play. I turn on the webcam and I'm like
hanging onto a pole sideways. Help! Finally I have the wherewithal to
get that prepared. Hiya cops. Do you know?
Are you tired of paying a lot for your internet service?
What? Yeah actually I am. Well those days are over.
Welcome to a new type of internet access.
S.O.L. So simple even a zombie could use it.
Yeah it's pretty cool. Do you know anything about it?
Processing. We have gathered extensive marketing data on zombies.
Zombies need an easier less expensive way to access the internet.
That's why we developed Stuttgart online for the greatest concentration of
newly active zombies. Stuttgart Germany.
You've unlocked a new area. What'd he say that for?
We do not know. He has been like this ever since the accident.
Max when I'm done yammering remind me we gotta drive to Stuttgart.
Quick like a zombie. Drive to Stuttgart. Right forgot it already.
Okay so you're selling the internet to zombies.
Not just the internet but much much more.
From trivia to music, lifestyles to death styles,
and inventive new recipes for brains. Stuttgart online is the premier online.
Dude that's where the best internet is. What am I thinking? I gotta move to
Stuttgart. Everyone move to EU. Move to EU. I keep
hearing it. All right let's go. Stuttgart.
Didn't we destroy the internet? Luckily Elgor was able to recreate the
internet from his original plans. What's on the internet that would
interest a droning glassy eyed zombie anyway?
Elgor recreated the internet in his own image.
What is so great about Stuttgart online?
It's the fun easy to use online experience for
zombies and zombies at heart. Okay what about the car? We just want to
pimp our car. We no longer offer car upgrades.
Our income has been lower than previously forecast.
But this neighborhood has the highest accident rate in five states.
We have spent a lot of this year out of town Max.
So we've devoted our resources to developing the ultimate
online experience SOL. He finally wants to upgrade.
All right well what happened to the other thing? What happened to bluster
blaster? Where's bluster blaster? There was a
processing accident while developing our latest invention.
And finds him. Haddock is the best kind of fish. He's a different person.
And finds him. We regret any inconvenience this may have caused.
And finds him. Thanks for asking. And finds you.
And finds you. I like that one. That's a good one.
Can you guys fix it? Can you guys fix bluster blaster?
They had me fixed before they brought me home. He sounds like Homer.
It is Homer Simpson. After all this time
you're not offering any car upgrades? None at all.
We regret the invention. It is much too dangerous.
Intrigued? Go on. It's the super high-powered antenna for wireless
internet access while on the road. There are problems. Using it could
result in catastrophic electrical failure and spontaneous explosion of
your vehicle. Yeah it is. And what are the
problems? You're right. We want the antenna. Super high powered antenna.
We spent our entire savings on development.
We can only give it to you if you help us market SOL.
Take the provided CD launcher and use it to give
installation discs to zombies throughout the city.
We like marketing. And we love shooting things.
I like wearing short pants. Would you like to begin driving now?
Yes. Affirmative. Initiating augmented reality driving sequence.
Do the droopy boys. Wait wait wait. Is this pizza?
Not pizza. Pizza man? What's the newspaper one?
Newspaper throw? Paper boy. There it is.
I want to shoot things. Please deliver the magic of SOL
to the displayed number of zombies. 10 zombies.
We'll make that big. And you must do it in the allotted time.
Pizza man. Ready go. Do I have a cursor?
Um what's going on? Why is my cursor off the screen?
How do I? Okay it's right click. I'm sitting there driving into him.
This is newspaper man. Congratulations you won. He said that.
Well done. We've installed your new super high powered antenna.
We cannot be held liable for any injury or loss of life.
I'm liking the sound of this more and more.
Please demonstrate the operation of the antenna to our big winner.
Not too late. I don't want to see the bright light again.
Very well. Do the droopy boys. All right I will.
Oh boy. Oh no.
Got it. All right so we got the antenna. What does this do? So we can now
somebody say what the fuck is this? Wow. Salmon man. We installed something
well for once. I won't be able to just pull it off.
Okay so we got the antenna. Let's go. I didn't talk to Stinky.
I'll make sure I have a conversation with Stinky. Now do Garfield.
All right we want to. Ever heard of a zombie factory? You know anything about
a zombie factory? Oh sure. I was a foreman at a zombie
factory for a year while I was writing my opera.
They're good workers as long as you don't let them unionize.
No this isn't a factory that hires zombies. It's a factory that makes
zombies. Oh well then uh did you say zombies?
I thought you said elves. Elves? Zombies giving you much trouble Stinky?
If that is your real name. To the German boys. Oh no.
They're a nuisance but at least they eat quickly and leave.
Your friend Lincoln is the real horror.
Hey it's it's the voice that I do when I do somebody that's not me.
Literally almost 90 percent of people that I do a voice for it sounds
like this. Is that what you're looking for?
So have you heard from grandpa Stinky lately?
Like from beyond the grave? What are you talking about? Grandpa's still on his
Himalayan mountain climbing junket. I thought you said grandpa Stinky was
on an around the world cruise. Let's watch as the spider tries to
free herself from her own web of lies. Oh he sent me a
postcard. His cruise was hijacked by Sherpa
terrorists. They ended up making him their god and now they're following him
on a quest to scale the world's tallest peaks.
Well her story does seem to hold up. Do Kylo Ren?
Okay give Abe a break. Come on give Abe a break. He's on the rebound.
He keeps trying to pay me in confederate money. Who does that?
That doesn't even make sense. It was pretty nice of grandpa Stinky to
leave his entire restaurant empire to you.
Some empire? Zombies, deadbeat ex-presidents,
trivia cheaters. Makes me wonder if it was worth the effort.
If what was worth the effort? Oh nothing.
All right what's going on with the sun lamp? What's with a sun lamp woman
who will call Stinky for the sake of convenience?
So that's what that is. Oh I mean of course that's what that is.
Have to look my best you know. The magazine set such an unrealistic
standard of beauty for grandpa murderers.
Can we have the sun lamp? Can we have your sun lamp? What could you
possibly need it for? Does she just admit to killing her father? Max needs a UV bulb for his
teeth bleaching regimen. You think a smile this wife comes naturally?
Well go ahead. Teeth bleaching. I don't need I mean I'm done with it.
Why wait why do you she said some beauty doing in a restaurant?
Did you think the food wasn't hazardous enough without the threat of
melanoma? Oh that I was just going through some
of the old things Stinky grandpa had in storage.
I need a big box for packing things that need to be sent
away. Okay let's order some. We'd like to order something.
Supplies are low because of the zombie attacks so uh we're probably out.
You do realize that's not going to stop us right?
Go ahead. Do you have any enchiladas? Crab and salamander enchiladas in
green sauce. Sal I want new jobs in Greta
van Suster and doing double dutch on the back of a rogue elephant.
I'd like what's the special today? My special gooey molasses tar cake.
It's an ancient family recipe. Ancient? You've heard of the labrea
tar pits of course but have you ever tasted them?
So I'll take two slices. Sorry I used up the blowtorch on some
zombies who didn't tip. Are we ever going to meet the guy in the back?
You're welcome to look at it though just don't touch.
Okay so we can take the lamp. Let's just see what this is. Seared grouper in a
maple syrup reduction with bacon wrapped dates and toffee chips
served on a bed of Venezuelan newspaper clippings. Sal
number three. Chicken chow mein with chocolate covered raisins and a
caramel swirl. Sal give me a hyperactive spider
monkey and a powder blue cardigan and why don't we go ahead and wrestle
them to the ground and tickle them till they piece.
I have got to see what goes on in this kitchen.
Nothing for us thanks. Let's go get the sign.
Want to help me carry this thing around Max? I just want the bulb.
Get the bulb. Did you just get deja vu?
Just close your eyes and it'll pass. I'm looking over here with 12,000 drop
frames in 30 minutes. Usually I have like
ah that's so bad. 12,000 drop frames in 30 minutes is like
150,000 drop frames for the stream.
Fuck me. It's hard. I'm gonna just relax. No no no no no just
relax. It's gonna pass. It'll pass in like 30 20 minutes or
so. It's gonna pass and nothing will be fine.
Do you breathing? I'm trying to do my breathing. So we have a
light bulb. 2% calm.
Get lost. He's gonna start crying. It's just
very distracting.
Okay I'm fine. It's closed. Bosco went into hiding when we
convinced him T H E M were coming. Bosco's not
available anymore? Wait that's not true but I can't
talk to Bosco? It's closed.
It's getting worse. I need I need positive breathing.
Jerma call Jerma. He's crying. All right so what can I do with the bulb?
It's the UV bulb from stinky sun lamp. Can I
put that onto zombies? Six seconds in six seconds out six seconds in six
seconds out. I'm not sure quite where I'd stick it.
I thought like I thought starting early was supposed to
prevent the internet problems. It usually starts later. At least the last
like week it has. Okay let's go over to Sybil's.
Take a number and I'll be with you. Oh hey Sybil. Hi Sam and Max.
I'm uh out of applications right now so
uh let's just be friends. Sure. What happened to Abe?
I'm sure I don't know to whom you are referring.
So Mr. Mollman. Oh it's him. Sorry. He's back. Harry tell me more about
you. Well let me see interesting things about me.
You got nothing. That's it. He's got nothing.
Harry Mollman last time we saw you you were. Yeah yeah on the moon.
What's all this I keep hearing about zombie attacks?
They're everywhere. You boys have guns right? Are we just not getting through to
these people? Yeah we're really not that complicated
Harry. How's the suitor business? How are things
going with you and Sybil? Oh she's playing hard to get but
women have a hard time resisting my charms.
Oh she'll grope about me. High speed and have all the markets
started for me.
I'm sorry guys. There's nothing I can do.
Oh what do I do? What do I do about it? You know?
Oh it's all right. What do I do? Nice spam chat. Very cool. Coxy pasta.
I'm hoping that it just stops but right now it's
it's almost like I shouldn't play this until it does stop.
Like it's almost like I should just turn the webcam on and fucking smile at you
until like it's certain that I'm not gonna drop 20 fucking thousand frames.
We'll see if this goes on for like another 20 minutes or so I'm gonna
have to we'll have to do something else because it really is
this is getting to be just unbearable. I hate to break it to you Harry but
Sybil's not that into you. She's more into the whole hard rock scene.
Just wait till she gets a load of my oboe.
Was that clumsy innuendo or a pathetic attempt to sound cool?
Both. And you have no shot. You really think you have a chance with Sybil?
I'm in it to win it. All right do you know anything about the
zombie factory? Do you know anything about a zombie factory?
Zombies don't make things. They break them.
No it's a factory that makes zombies. Inconceivable.
That's like making hate and evil and awfulness.
So you're saying you don't like zombies?
Oh okay. What have you got against zombies?
Disgusting creatures. They're always breaking things.
Zombies are why we can't have nice things.
Zombies why zombies break things? Zombies is that they break things?
Yes stupid clumsy undead. And that bothers you more than the brain
eating? They're hell on knickknacks.
But oh he's still doing prismatology. Are you still into prismatology?
Oh no. Between the four of us I wasn't that into it in the first place.
You just relocated to the moon for it.
Well think how great docent looks on a resume.
You just relocated to the moon. What are you doing for work these days?
Well I'm hoping the stipend from this job holds me over.
Sybil's paying men to be her suitor? Of course not.
But they don't know that. That's Marge. See you later Harry. Zombie!
That was like a peaked Mike scream. All right anything in here besides talking
to Sybil. Let's see. Makes me feel like I'm in a deli. I am
not piece of meat. What gives Sybil? Did you start your
dating service again? Not quite. All my clients are applying
for dates with me. As kind of officers of the law we
have to point out that that's kind of illegal.
Does that mean we can shoot her to regain health points or something?
What? No. Get your heads out of the gutter. It's not like that.
I'm looking for my soul mate. How are you gonna do that? How are you
going to find your soul mate? Not by jumping in with the first
reanimated statue that comes along. That's for sure. I've got the
initial screening and then rigorous interviews and
finally the soul mater. I want it. The soul mater?
What does the soul mater do? Not sure. I want it in an online auction and the
instructions are all in Sanskrit. Something about ripping souls from
across the plains to reunite them with
corruptible mortal vessels. Doesn't that sound romantic? I could
just die. Sounds like a very real possibility.
What's going on with the picture? You can still clearly tell who that is.
All you did is you just you just gave like Abraham Lincoln
Batman eyes. You just made him Batman. All right do you know anything about
the zombies? Do you know anything about a place called the zombie factory?
Zombies? Where? Hmm. Irrational fear of zombies. I'll do a
Batman impression. Interesting. But yes I did get an email about
something like that from some friends in Europe
I'm sorry. That sucked. Sorry my mind is elsewhere right now.
That was pretty that was pretty that was pretty good Batman impression for
where my brain is at. Can we get the soul mater up with
that soul mater Sybil? If you're not married by now there's
not much time left. There's plenty of time. I still have a
lot of data to analyze while I figure out how the soul mater works.
Okay have you had a lot of applicants? A few. If you know anybody
anybody else of course send them my way. A lot of these guys have no chance
but I'm still interviewing them to be polite.
Speaking of which what kind of movies do you like Harry?
No I don't go to the movies that much because of my stigmatism.
Wait why couldn't you go to the movie?
Remember to lock up tonight so the zombies can't get in.
Get in? There are zombies right outside. I'm not going to lock my door.
This is a public place and they have the right to peacefully assemble
just like anyone else. It's nice knowing you chat. Wait what?
Oh man am I still live? That was a full-on zero.
Hello? I was at zero for like three straight seconds.
My blood is heating up. It's starting to get hot in here.
Six seconds in, six seconds out, six seconds in, six seconds out.
This is not like a walkie-talkie. It's like the fucking internet.
You know what I mean?
Sorry I didn't get that one. Over.
We have not much time.
Don't you want to give Abe another chance?
Abe who? You were telling me more about yourself Harry.
I was detailing my various prescriptions and inhalers if I remember correctly.
Yeah I'm just driving around through tunnels.
Streaming from my laptop. Just hold on guys.
Yeah I'm playing seven max.
I hired an uber driver to drive me through a tunnel back and forth.
We just went through one.
We just went through another tunnel. Hey we good?
How are you?
That seems like a waste of money.
Kind of like most North American internet.
LOL dude plus 40.
Good luck finding your soul mate.
This has nothing to do with blocks Sam.
I can't I can't guys I'm sorry.
We're gonna have to just hang out on camera.
This is 13 percent of the stream has been unwatchable.
It really is like every set it's just not I don't know I want to like enjoy it.
I don't want to have to keep because there's a lot of dialogue.
You know what I mean?
There's a shitload of dialogue that I don't want it to be like walkie talkie cutout drop down to zero.
So uh I'm sorry unfortunately that we have to change to do something else for a little while.
Uh this is this is the worst it's been since it started having problems again like last week.
So sorry everybody I really I really do apologize.
I'm not gonna let it get me annoyed or angry if for some reason we get green again in the next
20 minutes or so just hanging out.
Why is it always me and not other streamers?
What so many streamers deal with internet problems?
What do you mean I'm the only streamer you've ever seen with internet issues?
That's that's pretty rare.
All right let me just go like this.
You're the only streamer I've ever seen.
Nova's been fucked lately.
Yeah I've heard I heard about that too.
Call tech support on stream they don't do anything.
Me calling tech support on stream would be like funny for five seconds and then we would realize
oh they're just gonna tell me to turn my router off.
I'm just gonna ping your router and maybe that'll work.
It's gonna turn you off for a couple of minutes.
Well let's um well I don't know what am I gonna do now?
Let's go like this.
Hey!
That was gonna have a huge face cam right now.
Angry streamer?
No it's more defeated.
It's defeated streamer it's a little different.
He is ape Lincoln.
Let's talk about stream ideas.
Yeah I gotta change this.
If you if you're looking for Sam and Max and we'll do it again.
Maybe even later in like a little bit once we'll try to get this to go through here.
Let me just say what do I even title this stream right now?
Frames are depleting.
Transformer?
Maybe I don't know I'm I'm kind of a little pissy right now.
I don't know if I would be like I don't think I could do it.
I'm like a little pissy right now.
I don't know if I could get in there be like okay let's have fun.
I'm like I'm kind of pissy.