How you doing? How are you doing? How are you? Good to see you again. You know who I am. Welcome
back to the channel. My name is German on eight five and we've got quite a day for you today.
Tonight got a few things to talk about. We'll go over them one by one really quickly. Already
got a plus two, which means this is funny to somebody. What's up? So we had to change some
plans today because I originally was going to play GTA online, but I was told
into some research and I was shown a few things. That's just kind of impossible.
It's isn't it apparently one of the easiest things in the world to just like get into a
GTA online lobby and just like break it. So I don't think I'm gonna be able to do that.
Unless there's a different solution on maybe a private server or something. I don't know.
It's apparently very easy to get into games that people are in. There's a lot of like IP problems,
I think, and even just getting into the server itself. People can just kind of get in and
hack. I don't know. I don't know anything about it. It's just, it's apparently hard to do.
It's a scary hacker word. A hacker. I don't know. Oh, instead of that, you're a liar.
What? This is documented evidence. What are you talking about? I'm a liar. You're a liar.
If two cars crash into each other and you ask me, what happened? And I say, although that was a car
accident. Liar. What? It's two cars. That's just factual information sitting in front of you.
You're a liar. No, I'm just processing the information. Anyways, if I get another question
mark, I'm ending the stream. It's over if I get another question mark. Just in how it's looking
over there and seeing that, how upset that makes me. Question mark, question mark, question mark.
I know what I'm talking about. I'm an adult. I'm 36 years old. I know what I'm talking about.
I don't want to see that anymore. I don't like those question marks. Maybe be unhappy.
This sounds fake. It's all fake. Everything is fake here. Except for 5% of the time when it's not.
All right. No more stalling. Let's go. So instead of that, I'm not going to do GTA online. It's not
going to happen. I'll have to figure out something else to do with GTA if I ever do it. I've been
asked to do the last few months now, the last at least couple of months, a couple of Jerma
Universe fan games I've shown themselves on Steam. And apparently a couple of them are very much
elaborately well made. So I was like, why not? Why don't we check these out? So we're going to do the
fan games. And then we'll be back on Sunday as well. I'm going to stream Sunday. And let me tell
you, I've been doing some meetings and talking back and forth a few times with different people.
There is some exciting shit coming up in the next hopefully six months or so.
Some more exciting shit that is currently starting. We're having meetings. There's meetings.
You understand? I'm having meetings with people. Community Jake. I'm hopeful there's going to be
some really fun shit to do soon. Isn't it Sandy? Yeah. That's what I'm trying. Let's go.
I'm very excited today. You probably hear it in the sound of my voice. I am very excited.
The horizon is bright. It looks great. So let's just hang out for a little bit. I'll be back on
Sunday. Let's do this. This is Jerma's Big Adventure. The first one we're going to do.
This is it right here. I don't know if I need to play this with a controller, but I'm going to.
He isn't retiring. Not yet. No, not yet. That's still important work to do.
I'm the ghost that lives in everybody's house. There's still important work to do. I can't leave
yet. Not yet. Okay. This is a banger. No, don't call the Ghostbusters. I'm haunting your computer.
I'm not haunting you. All right. You guys ready? This is Jerma's Big Adventure.
Go ahead. Okay. Start. You ready? I'm ready. I'm excited. I think this is a side scroller.
I could be, I could be 10 feet tall. All right. Honey, hold E to tell a joke.
Okay. Good. Good. Good. Use A. Do I need to use A? Oh, wait. I could.
Oh my God. This is so stupid. Okay. What does it tell a joke? Is there a jump? Hold. Okay. To
tell a joke. Okay. Audience loved it. It's got controller support. That's how you know it's,
this is a real deal. Is there a jump? There is a jump. Tell another joke. This is so accurate.
Do not enter. Should I go in there? Look how sweaty I was. Hold. All right. Hold.
Coffee, Cheetos, chicken. He has three jokes. No, four. I walk funny. Is it like, is it like a
currency thing? Let me turn this up. Stop. Turn back. Uh oh. Dead end. Do not enter. Fall hazard.
Keep out. That's not that high, right? It's not about that high up. Jump in it? Fall joke. Hold
on. Wait, wait, wait. Jerma goes to undertale. Did you see my underwear? What is that?
What is that on my stomach? Okay. Apparently I was streaming outside.
I got an achievement. The achievement was actually called fall joke. Somebody liked it. Good. All
right. It's your thong. Joke charge meter. Charges with attacks. Tell a joke to heal.
The ooey gooey cheesy. Oh man. Okay. Do I have full health? I gotta go. I gotta go. I gotta get
out of here. I gotta get out of here, man. I gotta go. Is this what I'm like? Oh, this is a new
movement. This is actually hold to jump higher. Is this like a, is this like a Metroidvania?
Should I tell more jokes? Oh, I can't. I love how I'm doing the I'm falling thing every time I jump.
Oh, log. Oh, yeah. Loot get. Got it. Now I'm assuming this is my attack. How do I attack?
Right trigger to swing or right bumper. This is crazy. Hold to heal. Okay. So let's keep going.
Are there enemies in the game? Do I have to fight actual enemies? Why am I running like this? I'm
running like an absolute shithead. Ace wall while falling to grab edge. I promise I don't actually
run like this in real life. I can run actually pretty fast and well press it and hold jump to
boost jump off an edge. That's, that's copium. No, I'm serious. I don't run like this. I think
you've probably, you guys have seen me run. I don't run with like my neck out like that.
That was definitely for a joke. All right. Duck. All right. That's pretty cool. That's pretty cool.
Checkpoint reached. Are they bosses? Robot dinos danger. I have an ad for Fortnite on my screen
right now and I don't even have the raptor. Okay. They have lasers reflect projectile.
All right. That onion ring. I got an onion ring. What people already loves that one. What are you
talking about? That's like everybody's favorite. They can be bad jokes and I don't get healed.
Oh shit. Oh my God. This is actually a video game now. Oh, I can't. Oh, that's how many hits it
takes. There we go. All right. Good. You like that one. Marvelous. Ow. Okay. I got six squares.
This music too. Listen to this. Like you're already here watching. Why do I have to do that?
Why am I saying? I don't know why I do that. I am the annoying person. I'm sorry. Is it like,
is it like a currency thing? I'm the annoying guy at the movie or in the game that says,
Hey, look, you watch this part. I know I'm already doing it. Can you aim it? Can I aim it? Like
angle it? I can. All right. Use L and press. Okay. So I can aim the bat up or down. What?
This is genuinely a good game. I mean, it kind of is. How many remaining? Oh, I have to kill them
all. I see. Oh shit. I swing that way. I don't think I can swing to my left. Can I? I can't
swing left. This is the best game to screen because the game streams for me. I don't even
do anything. This is awesome. I barely even have to say anything. Why didn't I do this before?
All right. Here we go. This definitely bosses too. I can't wait. It's doing all the old hits.
All right. I got to watch out. So that's funny. That's funny. I like that one. That's not minus
two. That's a good one. Oh, I can't. It has to be charged up. I see. All right. All right.
I see. All right. I got to be careful. Pull them down here. There we go. Zonked. You need
more German juice for jokes. Oh, I see. I just get the hitting boxes and stuff. The giant enemy
spider. I love this. This is exactly what I'm looking for. Damn it. Head end down. Okay. Where?
Exit. Should I wait? Should I explore? Are there secrets? There's definitely secrets.
What am I kidding? Are there secrets? Yep. There it is. There's got to be Easter eggs.
I got to find all the Easter eggs. Did I miss a secret? Is it fall damage? No. It's not Easter.
Get at it. Can I go up there? There's a little divot right there. Can I go up here? Oh, I can go
up here. So what is this? Okay. This is all this caution symbols. What does that mean?
Exit. Exit. Exit. Exit. How do I get up there? How do I get up there? This is, I'm telling you,
this is a Metroidvania. I can't make it from here. Holy shit. Okay. That works. You go so much further
when you do a roll. Oh, fuck. Hold on. I'll get it. Is there a double jump? No, the roll jump works.
That's a Donkey Kong strat. Oh, come on. Do I have to get out of the roll to grab the edge?
Yeah. You have to get out of the roll to grab. All right. I got it. I got it. I got it. Wait,
wait, wait. There we go. You can't be rolling. All right. What do I get? Okay. All right. Somebody
liked that. Good. That was worth two funny points. Head to the exit. All right. Cool. Cool. Now what?
Robot dinos again. Oh, I have to activate all these with lasers. Oh shit. Okay. Can I flip it?
No. I hit that one. Thank you. Oh God. I did it. That's exactly what I had to do. Right here. Come
here. Up here. Keep going higher. Do to me up here. No, I'm not going to kill the raptors and
softlock myself. Fuck. I actually might've just ruined it. Oh, I got it. Oh, get out of here.
Shoot. Oh my God. He actually hit me. Any more there? Right here. There's only one more, right?
One, two, three, four, five, six, seven. You shoot up here. Wait, I can, I can deflect it. Does it
count? Oh, it does. Okay. I thought it turned to green. Do I need to kill them? I think I can
just leave. I don't want to miss the EXP. Secret. Is there one here? I, okay. That's not me saying
yeah, right? That's somebody else. I think I can get up there. No, no, I can't. It's not, that's not
me. Oh, there are warlocks now. And you know what? I guarantee I know what it is. I guarantee it's
going to be when I had the Harry Potter stuff on. It's definitely Harry Potter. Yep. It's going to
be the shock warlock. Is he stunned? How do I even react to this? This is so bizarre. It's,
it's so cool though. God, I would have loved to be like a warlock. You know what I mean?
I know he's high again. What do you mean? What? I don't know. If like magic was real, it'd be cool
to be like a warlock. I don't want to be the guy with the axe that runs up to people. Everyone's
like, oh man, I would be like a melee. No, no. What the hell is wrong with you? I mean, you can
have like, you can conjure demons and like stay at a distance and shoot shadow bolts at people.
Why the fuck would you ever want to have an axe in your hand? That's horrible.
Why can't you be both? You don't have skill points. Are you serious?
Hold on. I'm going to die. I'm going to die here. I'm going to die here. So what happens when you
die? What to menu? No restart from the checkpoint. Let's go. 5,000 hours in Isaac, by the way.
Yeah. Over the course of 10 years. Okay. During the smite scream, we already went over this.
You, if you are not actively playing a video game, you, it takes like weeks to get back into it and
get back to where you were. It's like, it's like the gym. You can't just stop going to the gym.
Yeah. I also used to be like 170 pounds of pure muscle, a stack of absolute shit and I was
unstoppable. I now like see my stomach when I take a piss now. That's just a fact. What? I,
just because I worked out before, I couldn't do it right now if I wanted to. I love these.
I love the warlock. All right. Let's heal. Welcome to episode one of Germacraft.
How did you speed that up? That didn't need to be sped up. No, don't.
Don't kill me. Come on. Don't kill me. Don't kill me. Me playing. You should give me extra lives.
Holy shit. I'm going to die. You want to get baked, Dave? Is that what you want?
All right. They're, they're all shooting at the same time. God damn it. All right. That's what
you got to do. Oh shit. Too many. Oh, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no. Don't shoot me. Oh,
fuck. All right. This is hard. This is hard. All right. This is a hard game. Let's go.
I'll get it this time. I promise you died to the warlocks omega low. No, this is not an easy game.
Here we are. Don't ever melee the warlocks. You attacked who? What? You attacked my friend who?
You attacked my friend. Oh, Malfoy. Okay. God damn it. That's not plus two. Everybody hates that.
Everybody hates that.
Damn it. See, look at everybody's free. Everyone's saying minus two. See, I told you.
Oh, I'm so bad. There it is. All right. This is where I was last time. I don't want to get
messed up again. Don't die here. This is probably going to get so hard. I'm already having trouble
in this room. Damn it. They said don't attack melee. I couldn't help it. I'm trying to aim
down. Come on. Who's left? This game is really well made. Yeah, it is. I took one look at this
on the screenshots and I was just... This is elaborate. This is very elaborate.
Fuck. Don't die to the warlock here. Don't be an idiot. There it is. All right. Let's go.
What's up here? Uh-oh. This looks dangerous. Damn it. Dude, that's not me laughing. There's
no way that's me. Anything else this way? No. It's supposed to be us. All right. All right.
These are the audience. All right. What's in the top? This is so high. This is expelliarmus for
every spell. Oh, shit. This is another way to go. What? I think it's random. Nice. I can't believe
it. I can't believe we just shot Otto. All right. So, we got Otto, Giant Rat. How dare they minus
two? I think it's random. I think randomly you get a bad one. Very quiet now. I think this is a
boss. Is there a checkpoint? Checkpoint? Is it like a currency thing? Casino? Well, I have to go in
here. I would not be mad if I didn't. What is this? Times 10? Times 2. 3x, 4x, 5x. All right.
But what am I betting? Inserted funnies. Oh, okay. Let's do 64 funnies. Let's go.
That's triple watermelons. That's triple watermelons. I just got what I was good.
Holy shit. It's 2x. All right. You can't. It has to be a max bet. Otherwise, I'm going to lose
everything. Seven. Give me another one. Nice. Oh, that's good. All right. Now I'm at 500.
I'm going to do a low bet because I feel like I'm going to run out.
Shit. Oh, that was a 3x. What the fuck? All right. I'm on a hot streak. Let's go. Oh, yeah.
Let's go. I don't think I can lose. I think it's rigged. This shit is rigged. I can't lose.
Bar? That's another bar. All right. I lost that one. That's a good. All right. Look, I made money.
It's a diamond. Three diamonds. Let's see it. Goodbye. I win. I'm done. That's 5x. All right.
One more. A thousand. Then we're done. That's it. I'm done after this. Give me the seven.
I'll take fruit. I'll take fruit. All right. I'm out of here. I'm out. I made over a thousand funnies.
I'm good. I'm done. Let's go. Yeah. I came in here with like 300. I'm leaving with 1500.
Oh, is that not a win? It doesn't matter what you went up. It doesn't matter if you don't go down.
Uh-oh. The giant enemy dinosaur.
What do I do? Select? Oh, shit. All right. Can I go down? It's not like Bowser, right?
Shields down. Wait, it's just. Oh, fuck. There's like multiple phases. Oh, man. This is not as
just self-expl... Oh, my God. All right. Hold on. I can stop talking.
Come on. All right. Out, out, out, out, out, out. The ads. Watch out. Does that hit them too? It does.
Okay. Good. Juggle. Just keep them juggled. Oh, this is bad. Okay. I got to hide.
Hold them one at a time. If I get hit like three or four times, I'm going to die.
Hmm. Shit. All right. We're fine. One more and we're good. That is it. Boss dead. Nice.
Does it explode? This is just what a regular stream is. I'm kind of realizing. Like it's press
X to fill dead air with various noises. I should have really said anything in like a few minutes.
It's just ways to keep you engaged. Wait, don't break them all. It's probably a secret somewhere,
right? Why would they put all these here? Yeah, I knew it. What's up here? I'm the rat. You need
to jingle the keys. We're children. That's fine. Reward. What's wrong with my guy? Truth. Truth.
What's the truth? You've done very well, young one. You've proven your strength to me. Perhaps
it's time to reveal my true identity.
Your grand. You're going down. Wait, wait, wait. Hey, hey, hey, hey. The secret is this.
I didn't press anything. Happy birthday. Oh, thanks. Secret about your father and
grandfather is that they are both here to celebrate along with the birthday of rats.
Let's go to the party. Jeremy. I'm so sweaty in that middle one. Nice. Very nice. No, it's not.
The stream is still live. It's not over. The stream is not over. 1586. Final time. 27 minutes.
Plus you played the slots. It's now that it's the best stream. All that gambling
paid off. There was a big adventure. A game by Warbler based on German985, the Spiegei.
Wait, truth ending two. Truth ending one. What does that mean? Complex. Very cool.
But with Unity, Adobe Photoshop, Premiere, and Audition. Oh, if I actually hit them,
you could kill them for the chips. All right. Can we see the other ending? I want to see the
other ending. That was so cool. Oh, look out for a wacky behind the scenes video. I wonder if that's
there. Thanks for playing. I want to see the other ending. Let's go. New game. Can I speed run it?
Wait, wait a minute. Oh, nice. Okay. I want to start from the post-boss region with no,
with zero points. What a psycho mode. All right. Well, I want to see the other ending first.
Okay. The other ending is to hit them and get the chips. Let's see what we get.
I can skip the cut scene. Okay. Oh shit. No, no, no, no, no, no, no. I don't want to see.
Wait, what? No damage. I didn't mean, I didn't need to. Okay. Hold on. This is very sad ending.
All right. Hold on. Let me do that again. That was the ending. Was that? No, it wasn't.
Let's go. Okay. New game. From that checkpoint. I'm going to hit them.
Start with, we'll start with $300. Okay. Go. There's more to it. I swear. Okay.
I was from the dev's mouth. Okay. I'm ready. We're going to kill the grandfather and go get chips.
You've done well. Okay. We can fill the dead air. You dog. I jingled the keys. Yes.
Let's kill him.
TV rovo.
You want to know about your father. I kind of want the chips.
Wait, this, this is a different outro. 300 funnies. Okay. Final time plus checks.
Average stream. That's fine. That's all right. That's fine. I don't have to be best dream.
Try psycho mode. Yeah. I'm definitely going to try psycho mode. All right. I'm going to do psycho
mode. Should I just start from the beginning? Let's go. New game. Okay. Psycho mode. New
conquest. So what's the difference? Welcome to episode one of German psycho adventure.
Screaming. I already have the bat. Okay. I've got a raid come in too from a J six.
Still was. Thanks a lot. Welcome everybody. I'll sing the rain. So the rate song. Sure.
Thanks for coming. Playing a couple of games that some of the community members have made.
And this is not, we're in psycho mode. I have glasses on. Is this a whole new game?
What's the difference? Oh shit. This is a different game. That other one was just
practice for this. Oh my God. Freddy dread is give 50 community subs. Freddy, what do you
have to write? Are you giving 50 subs? Wait, Freddy, give it all these subs.
Why he give it all these subs, right? That's a shit load. Welcome everybody.
What do you mean welcome? Like you've given a sub. You weren't here before.
I combined the raid and the sub. Well, some of you that just rated might not have,
maybe you have one. Maybe you got one of the drops. The giant enemy spy.
Thanks a lot. Freddy's here. That's a lot of money already. He's coming in hot.
Hope you're doing well, Fred. And I just called you Fred. Are we on those terms yet? And I call
you Fred. Loose. I just jumped in. You just made it awkward. No, I didn't. I've hung out with
Freddy Fred in real life. Okay. It's not awkward. We know each other. Oh my God. Now he's just
flexing. You don't know Freddy like I do. We're the rats. We're the rats. We pray at night.
We stalk at night. We're the rats. I'm the giant rat that makes all of the rules.
Let's see what kind of trouble we can get our Sims into.
So what do they do? Oh, I haven't spotted. Nice. I'm just like a psycho on the loose.
Now I'm really curious as to how this ends. We were on baby mode before.
Now we're in the real game. That was just a tutorial. Oh, this makes me want to install
Hollow Knight. Tell everybody I'm going to play it and then fucking play it for an hour
and then never play it again. I just want to play that now, but only for like an hour
and then never play it again. I think I got the hang of this. This actually looks fun. This is fun.
I wish he would do the doi doi doi again. All right. Just for you. I'll do it again.
I'm going to do a big one. Is he going to rival any of the doi doi dois I've ever done on this
channel? He's laughing at his own joke. I'm laughing at what the guy said on camera on
the screen. That was funny. It wasn't even me. That's a different, that's a character that I
played. It's not me. That was for that one person. Oh, fuck. Watch out. Coffee, Cheetos, chicken.
I do laugh at my own jokes. Yeah. I think, I think I'm the funniest damn person.
I actually kind of don't. I laugh at other people's interpretations of the things that I say.
That's what makes me laugh more than anything, I think. And people making stuff like this.
Holy shit. He's big. I can't wait till I, well, not to, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, not, I can't wait.
Let's rephrase that. I was going to say, I'm looking forward to eventually when I'm done
streaming. I'm not looking forward to that. Like, let's hold on. I got to, how do I phrase this?
When I eventually am not streaming anymore and I'm one of those people that does like a comedy
course at college, I can't wait to do a comedy course. Teach like once a week. Humor, humorist.
German985 teaches kids at the local, I don't know, like local state school. I'm definitely not good
enough for anything besides just like a, like a two year school. Nobody wants to bring me in
for like a, like a four year school. Nope, it won't happen. I'm not prestigious enough
for their, for their big, big, wonderful, like four or five year master's program.
Fuck you out of here. You don't need that. You come to my, you come to my class and you'll learn.
Comedy instructor. Yep. And the first day of class, I'm going to come in in a costume
and I'm not going to introduce myself. I'm going to make like noises and like get on the table
on top of the, like where the desk is and be like making elephant sounds and shit and like
lying on my back and like scratching my ears like a dog and stuff. And then I'm going to get up.
I'm going to take all the costumes off and I'm going to say, those of you that didn't take notes
on what just happened, get up and leave the class. Serious people only. We'll have you pick something
else. You're just getting fired. Like I wouldn't even show up to class half the time. I would just
forget. It's like 30 students just sitting there waiting in the like lecture hall. I'm just not
there. Can I say the same shit that I say to you guys? Oh yeah. I auto had to go out. So I'm not
streaming today. What? Yeah. I had to take my dog out. Sorry. It's been six hours. Um, okay.
So you've lied. No, I've never lied. Actually, I had a tweet lined up. Uh, it was, it's in my
drafts right now. Uh, let me read it to you. Let me read you precisely the tweet.
Tweet says, and I didn't send it cause I was like, no, I, I want to stream today
because I did, this did happen. So the tweet says this, I wrote this, um, last night.
Hey guys, no stream tomorrow. I hurt my balls yesterday. I accidentally smushed them.
I'll let you know when I'm coming back. I was just wasn't going to stream today,
but I did smush my balls though. That's not a lie, but I was like, no, I'll be okay. I can,
I can do it. But yeah, I was going to cancel the stream today because I smushed my balls
and I was like, is it worth it? Canceling the stream for people to see that. Maybe they'll be
worth it. Maybe you think it was funny. I don't know. I was like, no, I want to, I want to stream
even if it's for a little while. We didn't now, but I'm live right now. No stream tomorrow.
Oh, I got to pay attention. We didn't now. You plan on streaming tomorrow? No, but that was
because I was planning on not streaming today. But then I had this other epiphany in my brain
and look, listen to me. So those of you that have been following this channel for a long time,
been here for a while, years, a lot of you, which first of all, that's crazy. I'm like
surprised every day that people still watch this and still think that
stuff like that is still funny to you. But if you've been watching and noticing the sus
over the last three or four years, anytime I ever plan to do, oh, hey, I'll be, I'll be live like
Monday or Tuesday. Yeah, I'll be live on maybe like, I don't know, Saturday, Sunday. If there's
within three or four days of time ahead of that stream, it's guaranteed to be the next day.
If you see me right Monday or Tuesday, the stream is on Wednesday every time. So even though I
smushed my balls, I was like, no, I can't, no, I'm not going, I'm not delaying to Wednesday.
Nope. I don't care how smushed they are and make no mistake. They're painful. It's painful,
but I was not going to do that again. Oh, I don't know. Then it just had happened. Okay. I'm not
going to give you specifics of how it just did. Sometimes you sit down too fast or too weirdly.
Oh, you turn a weird way where you're sleeping or sometimes you, you fall.
I'm laughing at somebody said he paid somebody to do it. Sorry guys. I can't stream tomorrow.
I had somebody come over and smush my balls. That makes that tweet. No, no, no, no. Okay. All right.
We've got to move on from this, but just know, just know the stream was almost canceled today.
People are writing like, huh? Just relax. It's fine. Everything's going to be fine.
Was it left or right? It's both. How is not the question. The question is it did is the question
is, is right? No, no, no. It's not the, it's not the how it's the why it's not the why either. It's
the, it's the who, what, when it's the, when it was last night or tonight, whatever, whatever it
was. I don't remember. It's the, it happened. It's is it did. It's not, I'm not tiny. I'm compact.
The only information you have to have is there was a, I got smushed somehow and that's it.
You just dug yourself a grave. It did. You never cease to impress that.
I mean, how you, it's all fine. It's not, there's no who it's, it's not a who it's, it is. All right.
Get out of here. Man, everybody that says smush time out. Everybody that says the word smush.
And then that's it. Oh, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no. I don't want to kill them.
Oh, thank, thankfully they planned for that.
Hit it. This is the, this is the lesson here. This wait, this is no, no, no. This whole thing
did not turn into a routine where I'm still the professor at the college. This actually happened
somebody thinks that I'm talking about like being the professor still.
This is not like the lesson plan. I gotta hit it up. Damn it. There we go. How many more are there?
Episode. I was taking notes. Hold on. Hold on. Hold on. No, we're good. Shit. Is it one more?
All right. Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait. Shit. Oh my God.
He's aiming down. Oh my goodness. Okay. I gotta get up top first. Let's be on the test. There are
no tests in my classroom. Everybody has to do a performance. There are no tests. You have a five
minute piece or 10 minute piece you have to do at the end of the year. And then I am the sole judge
if it was funny enough for you to pass the class. Is it? Shit. You're a cool professor.
That's what I'm going for, man. I want like a cool, I want to have that cool professor vibe.
Shit. All right. I have to pay attention. I'm not paying attention. Okay. Now right here. Fuck. Oh
my God. All right. I don't get an A. My mom is going to send me to the glue factory.
I feel like we mean to go to work. What do you mean? You're going to go to the glue factory?
Oh, okay. Okay. We're going to, I'm going to go to the fact. Oh, okay.
Shit. I suck. I suck at this. I gotta move. Just move. Go, go, go, go, go, go, go.
No, you fuck. Holy shit. Okay. I need to, I got to heal. Holy God. Did I get it?
Is it one more? Shit. Come on. I need to heal. I think is it more? Oh my God. Jesus. Oh, I got it.
I got it. I got it. This is the weirdest class I've ever been to keep distance from warlocks.
I can kill them if I do one hit. Nice.
When's the parent teacher conference? You don't have those as a college professor.
I just show up and I do my lesson plan and then I just leave.
This is a full heel. Oh, I'm going to need it now. Oh my God. What are you a professor in comedy?
These teachers suck. He's playing video games, all class and you eat in class. Yes. As long
as it's not crunchy. You can eat whatever you want. As long as you're not going to make any
crunch mouth sounds. And if it's chewy, chew with your mouth closed. I don't want to hear the like,
the chewy shit. Crunchy is loud. Chewy can be loud if you open your mouth.
Slurping is fine. No, if you can eat quietly, you can have it. Nothing crunchy and no loud bags
either. I don't want to hear that. It'll distract me. No, don't bring like Lays potato chip bags
and you're going to crinkle up. No, don't do that. You're going to bring the smelliest food
imaginable. No, you can't have that either. It can't be crunchy. It can't be chewy. It can't smell
and it can't be hot because that's a hazard. You can't have like a bowl of spaghetti in the
room because what if you drop it on somebody? It burns them or something. That'll make a mess. Yeah,
no. Pop tarts. Pop tarts are absolutely perfect. Yogurt. That's really good. That'd be okay.
Pop tarts, crinkle. No, not if you're quiet. If you tear it right at the top and you make
it really silent, it doesn't make a loud noise. It's very light foil. There's three more of these
guys. Where are they? Coffee, Cheetos, chicken. What if it's for comedy? It better be really funny.
If you're doing a look at I have a loud potato chip bag routine, it better be really funny. I
fart in my chip bag. That might be funny. Where do you do this? Do you do it like you just come
up and say, excuse me, I need to interrupt the class and then fart into your bake lays?
Okay. Yeah, that's funny. See? I mean, I would tell you to sit down. I'd be like, all right,
now sit down. You little shit. Can you order a pizza to the class? No, unless it was, but here's
how you would do that. You would be absent. And so one of your peers that's also in the comedy
class would be like, I'm going to order a pizza. You would order the pizza. I would have marked you
absent. You would show up 20 minutes later in a pizza guy outfit, delivering the pizza to the
class. I would give you a, I would give you a stamp on that one. It has to be pepperoni with
cheese. Well, then you would know that's my favorite pizza. So you get, you know, points with the
teacher. And then if you got into the class and you had the bag of lays and right. And when you
got in, okay. So you, that the pizza delivery is called, you show up, you say, Oh, somebody
ordered pizza. And it's like, Oh, there he is. This is the absolute, this is the absent guy.
And you immediately grab a full bag of bake lays and you just fart directly into it.
I think that would probably give you an egg that combines both things you're talking about.
Now that person passed, they don't have to come to class anymore. That person doesn't need to
come to class. I'm just going to give you an egg. But if you come to class in a fursuit,
um, it's probably probably kind of hot in there. And as long as I could verify that it was you,
I don't know what your routine is. Okay. No, no. Okay. If you had an anthro con badge on
around your neck and it was you like, you came to the wrong place. If you're like, okay, that's
funny. You would pass and you could leave. Oh, fuck, watch out. Is it, is it like, is it like
a currency thing? I mean, he knows I just, cause I know it exists. I told you guys what I wanted
to do one day. I've never done it. I wanted to dress up in a full fursuit and just go and just
blend in and not have no one have ever know it was me. I would be in my hotel room is the only
time I would ever take off that costume. I would not talk. I would not tell anyone. No one would
ever know. I would just have to make sure that when I got in the hotel room, it was nobody else
with me. All the, everything's closed. All the blinds are closed. Everything is closed. Nobody
can, it is impossible. I would, I would leave my cell phone. I would leave my cell phone at home.
That couldn't get fucking tracked. Nothing. Nothing. Just go. It would be a big elaborate
costume. There's no way you could ever find out. You know, don't say swears. What would be the
point of it if nobody found out? You failed. Hand in your syllabus and hand in your fucking comedy
token. Sorry, you failed the class. Comedy tokens. One star on Rape My Professor.
No way. I would have five. I would be at least 4.5. You're telling you to, okay, hold on a minute.
You're saying that if you had a class that you just had to impress the professor for like a
minute and you got an A and you didn't have to go anymore and this guy lets you eat food in class
and all he cares about is you doing a little comedy routine and then he passes you.
You don't have to go anymore. Are you serious? I feel like that you would be full of five star
reviews. What an ego. How much is the class? Good question. How much would the class be?
I feel like it definitely wouldn't be free, but it wouldn't be expensive.
It would be like the cost of going to see Cirque du Soleil in the back row.
Maybe 40 bucks? 30 bucks? How much does Cirque du Soleil take you? Is it expensive? I thought
it was like 40 bucks to go see Cirque du Soleil. 32 bucks? Is it more than 100? Oh my god, I have
to heal. I just got headshot. Fuck. Okay, I wasn't paying attention. Fuck. All right, let me just
beat this first and we'll talk more about this stuff. You're worth Cirque du Soleil money? I mean
it's how much is it for like a class in college right now? It's just way too fucking expensive.
Depends. How much is a front row seat at Cirque du Soleil? I wonder. Maybe it's probably like
four or five hundred bucks for like a front row seat. 500? Fuck. All right, about 350.
Usually around 1 to 2k. Holy shit, really? Oh my god, I'm getting juggled. Stay back here and heal.
All right, let's go. The giant enemy spider.
Why would wearing a fur suit be hot? Do you think furries are hot? Are you a furry now? What is,
why is, what? Is it my turn? Like, I'm talking temperature wise. It'd probably be pretty
toasty in there. Oh, Darkest Dungeon 2 comes out, right? In like four or five days?
When does that come out? I want to play that. Changing the topic. Yes, it's a topic I care
very deeply about. This shit is bouncing. That's what's going on. Oh my god, Jeremy, come on.
All right. Well, it's not a change of subject. We were done with that other subject and I moved
on to a new one. I didn't change the subject. I went to another topic because we were done with
the first one. Oh my god, you got greedy. We were not done? What do you mean? You want to go back
and talk about my smushed balls? I don't. Shit. Oh my god. Watch out. That was actually kind of scary.
Oh god. Oh, get back up here. Way too many. Get rid of the big one. All right. Now I can go down.
Oh, shit. He got hit by that on the way back. I think that's it down here.
Is this game canon? It's in the German Extended Universe. Whoa.
All right. Only one more. One more magician. All right. That's it. Welcome to episode one of
Germacraft. Are there any non-canon streams? Oh, the smite ones. Is this a secret? Did I miss it?
No, we've already seen it. This is just Psycho mode. I already got to the top of this before,
right? Did I do it again? I mean, might as well. Did I miss something?
Chad, Germa isn't canon. Yeah, I mean, yeah, he is. I said smite. Well, smite streams are not canon.
I think a canon stream is the ones that, you know, the big projects probably. Those are all
canon. We got 20 community subs? Affmeric, thanks for the 20 community subs. Appreciate it. Thank
you. Thanks for 20 subs. Two zero. Are you going to put an edible in the Germa rumble? Oh no,
that's not what you said. I don't know why I read that like that. As a character?
Oh, damn it.
There we go. Is there anything up here? What about the JCU, the cinematic universe? Yeah,
sure. Hey, Neer, thanks for the eight. You know how we say it here. Say it with me.
Community subs. Everybody says it and we all like laugh. It's all thing we do.
I'll give immunity. It's Otto. I love Otto. All right, we're getting to the end of the
Psycho blog. I think I've done pretty well. All right. Watch it. What the fuck are you doing?
What is he doing? He killed Otto in Resident Evil 8. What are you talking about? Stop being greedy
and get him. You idiot. The guy in the big barn. There's a secret boss. Big barn. Oh, I have to go
back to the casino. Whoa. Oh my God. I'm not going to die in here. Am I? What the fuck? No,
I can't do this. Fuck, I didn't finish the joke and now I'm going to die.
Fuck. Oh my God. I can't. What the hell, man? I can't. No. How far back is the checkpoint?
Oh, thank God. No, wait, is this all the way back to the other room?
It's not. Thank goodness. All right. Well, I can't gamble. I'm not going to get killed.
Casino. All right. Fine. No, I can't. What is it? Lemon. Lemon. Lemon. Oh, fuck. Never mind.
We're going right by it. Okay. Get away from me. I don't know how the final boss changes.
No. All right. The giant dinosaur. Holy shit. This is going to be so hard. I'm going to stay
down here. Yeah. Fuck it. I'm staying here. I just cheese this encounter. What? Run, run,
run, run, run, run, run, run, run. I bring them over here. I get them over here. All right. One
more time. And then that's it. And then I get the true, true ending, but there'll probably be two
different endings, right? Oh, flying. What the fuck was that? Oh shit. Oh my God. Just hide down
here. Is it like, is it like a currency thing? I didn't get it. All right. I'll get it. Shit.
This is bad. This is really bad. This is really bad. Where are the dinosaurs gone? Where are they?
Did they fall down? All right. I win. This doesn't seem like I can't move. Can they shoot me? All
right. Oh, I just got feeding frenzy too, to run on my laptop. Holy shit. That's a celebration
moment. This is not smite. No, it's fine. It's fun. All right. I can still get the, uh, hold on,
break this, but don't kill everybody. They kill these people, but don't break the boxes.
Shit. Hold on. God damn it. Get out of the way. Is this the guy that beat Spampton,
Jevil, and Jerma Dinosaur first try? It is. I'm just going. All right. Here we go. I'm going to,
I'm not going to kill them. Let's see if we get the true ending and then we'll do the other ending
too. Just to make sure we cover all the bases. I didn't press anything.
After his brutal conquest, Jerma obtained the prize chips for real this time.
Oh, I get it. Okay. Seven 92. Very cool. I think that's it.
There's another one lined up here to play. That's right. Kevin McLeod
is the master of royalty-free music. Tried to get nine eight five for the secret ending.
That accurate? What happens to be getting nine eight five honeys? Can we confirm with the dev
that's real? Is it real? You can't cause they're in multiples of two. You can't get an odd number.
All right. Well, that was cool. That was from War, War Bill War Brill. Where are you? War Blur,
War Blur War Blur stats, brother lowest score. I score locked it fast. I unlocked all these.
Oh, I see. It's different modes. That was really cool. I'm going to play the next one.
Next one. I believe the one next one's a point and click adventure game.
Okay. Thank you. That was really, really awesome. I think it's called Otto's
great adventure or something. Let's do it. Uh, we're also, we'll take a break. I'll go BRB,
go pee, come back, play that one. I'll be right back. I forgot to say I was back. Sorry about
that. Derma and Otto, the curse of the late streamer. Music can stay here. Sound effects.
That sounds pretty good. Turn it up a little bit. All right. So this is apparently a point
and click adventure game. You do a new game. It's right somewhere in the Nevada desert
around 12 to 1 PM Pacific. You have an event. I'm going for the middle class.
That's how it feels. Sometimes. Yeah. This is actually how it is. I'm not even kidding.
I'm late for the stream. Chat's going to kill me. That's how it feels. If I know that it's
going to take me like 30 minutes to get ready and just like, fuck, they're just probably so
trying. They go as fast as I can. I better get over to my computer room as soon as possible.
Okay. So I have a toy. Look at rug. Okay. Use rug. Oh shit. There's a key under here. Give me
that key. I wonder what this opens. Looks kind of dorky. Looks kind of dorky. Get it? Oh shit.
I didn't until right now. Door key. Okay. Come on. Adventure games have to have bad puns.
Is it in my stomach? This is crazy. Okay. Bad. This is where the magic happens. I'm going to
give you a fully voice acted game by the way. You understand? Mirror. Whoa. Who's that handsome
hunk staring back at me? You can do this today. You're going to go out there and you're going to
show everyone what you're made of. You're going to show everybody what you're capable of. Not what
anyone else is what you are. You have what it takes. This is a map of the cartoon town I live in.
Toy blocks. Sorry. Sorry. Sorry. I'm sorry. What? Use toy blocks. I think they can stay where they
are. This is my prize possession. Made with real diamonds. Blue raspberry flavored. It's what?
Wait. Eleven? I don't know. I don't think changing the clock is going to make me any less late.
Anything else I can do in here? I got a key. I have a diamond pickaxe. Let's go. Headroom door.
Outside door. Can I look outside? Reddit room door. Okay. Well, who's on the air? Not me.
There's no time for distractions. I've got a stream to start. It's locked. I must have left
the key around here somewhere. This does not happen where I live. Because I would hide this
key and forget about it and forget it and have to put a shoulder into the door to get in here.
This is... I wouldn't do that. Okay. Here we go. Reddit shit. Holy shit. This is just... This is my
room. This is crazy. This is actually one to one accurate. What about the... Can I go in the closet?
Reddit shelf. My Reddit shelf is empty. I must have misplaced all my Funko Puffs.
I should keep an eye out for them. Sounds like some sort of side mission. That isn't important
to the main goal. I'm sure that'll be in the DLC. When does Lenarwall bacon? Epic.
Hahaha. Auto. Cool. Yep. This is also accurate. Dog bed? I wonder where Otto has wandered off to.
If I move his bed, where's Otto going to sleep? Rotto Beasts. Yep. You must complete all your
chores before streaming. I forgot to do my chores before stream. Looks like chat might have to wait
a minute. I'm sure they won't mind. This is... This is completely accurate. Yeah. Find something
to eat. Sandwich does sound good right about now. All I would need is bread, mayo, and steak yum
brand meat. That's right. Otto needs to go on a walk. I haven't seen him for a while. I wonder
where he went. Of course, I definitely can't stream without internet. Let's check the cable
box outside. See if anything's broken. Okay. So these are the tasks. All right. We're going to
take Otto for a walk and find something to eat. Cool. All right. Let's go. Wait. What's this?
Otto's note. Otto's note. One. Hey, everybody. It's me, Otto. I'm off on a big adventure right
now trying to find who stole the cookies. Are they outside? I should talk to the vroomer.
He's always outside driving his motorcycle up and down the street. Love, Otto. Who stole the
cookies? I'm going to find Otto. I've got to find whoever took all the cookies. I should talk to
the vroomer. Maybe he knows where Otto is. Okay. So I can go this way now. Use wall. I don't know
what good my hands would do against solid stone. Use wall. Oh God. Look at sign. It says
VOD watchers skip one hour. Weird. I wonder what that means. Go to door. Go to door on right.
Go to door up. There's only one choice. Go door down. Go door left. Go door left. Go door up. Go
door down. Go up. All right. There's a pattern here that I'm missing. Okay. There's two torches
on this one. Is that like yes and no? Like one torch is no. Two torches is yes or something.
What the fuck am I talking about? What are you talking about? There's more than one door in each
room. What? Oh, this room is no. Okay. What? I don't get it. I don't have any items. Okay. Maybe
if a door has two torches on it, it means it's the real one. With one torch, you just go left. Down
and left maybe. Torches don't mean anything. I found it. I must have gone the wrong way. I don't
think I'm supposed to be here. Secret button that kills you. Should I press it? That's a callback,
isn't it? What happened? I have a feeling that wasn't the right way. I should check the maze
again. What? Yep. Still a mailbox. Hmm. It's empty. I'll have to check back later. Do I get in the
road? Dean Dingus lost my vote after he strangled three people. If I put it away now, people will
call me a centrist Andy. Road. All right. Look at road. I've got to figure out a way to slow down
the rumor to talk to him. Will he just hit me? I'm just in the road. Well, that was a close one. I
should find a way of slowing him down. I'm not putting my hand on that. It's probably a thousand
degrees. Telephone pole? Telephone pole. Looks pretty tall. Can I die up here? What the hell?
Wow. I did not think it would be this high up. I hope there's no fall joke incoming. Of course
there is. Looks like another balloon from Boston is coming in. It's a cable box. Screwed shut. This
is probably where all the internet wires go. Listen, I don't really know how it works. Just
trust me. I can't open it. It's screwed shut. I've got to find some item that will let me
unscrew a screw. I need a screwdriver. I love the carnival in the distance.
I think I used it. I don't have it anymore. So I have to figure that maze out. Let's go back in
the house. I just want to slow down the rumor. What can I get? This is the Reddit room. What
about further down here? Okay. Hold on a minute. Let's see, man. Okay. Hallway. It's the clowns in
the house. Okay. Something about these two looks kind of funny. How do you keep getting into my
house? Select an action. All right. How about some bread? Ask for bread. Hey, can I have some bread?
I'll take that as a yes. Oh, nice. All right. Quest complete. Find something to eat, right?
I need more? How do you two keep getting into my house? All right. What about flirt?
You want to clown around for a bit? Uh, be rude. I hate your stupid clown guts. Oh, nothing. Can
I get more food? Flirt? You know what they say about guys with comically large shoes?
I don't think they like this. Sliding door? Let's go back. Oh, shit. Okay. Hold on. Garbage? Banana
peel? Banana was not very appealing. I know. I know. Sorry. Oh, sunflowers. Anything else in here?
What's in there? I've been doing some archaeology recently. Get it. Let's see. Geos. Grotto. Beast
cars. Buried treasure. Aha. What's this? Looks like some ancient Greek tablet. I wonder how
that got here. Okay. So this is a code. This is, I got to crack this code. Can I take it? A is A,
B is B, T is G, triangle is D, E is E, Z is Z, H is E, O is F, I is I, K is K, thick, M is M,
N is N, E is X, O is O, H is P, P is R, sideways, M is E. Okay. So it's just a, it's the Greek
alphabet. I feel like I'm going to need, I'm going to need to know. I'm going to need to,
I can't even say words. I'm trying to say it too fast. Slow down. I feel like I need to know
that later. Say that's better. What's that last symbol called? Infinity.
Okay. Use oven. Oh my God. It smells like death in there. What is in there? Is that a pot rose?
How long has it been in there? Oh, it's oven is ruined. Got to find time to clean it out later.
Sandwich toaster 9,000. Anything in the fridge? I must've locked it after too many
midnight snack runs. Putting a padlock on your fridge. Oh my trusty sandwich toaster 3,000.
It automates the process of assembling the perfect sandwich. All you need is bread, steak yum,
brand meat product, and tons of mayo. It seems like I'm missing some ingredients for the perfect
sandwich. Wait, what? I have to regurgitate this into the toaster? I don't think this works with
that. This is the bread. Still need to find the other ingredients. Okay. So we need steak yum.
Can I get that? Can't just reach in there? Oh, something bit me. Okay. Keep going. Use door.
Go to casino. Why is there a casino in my house? It actually did it.
It's the joke door.
All right. Let's go to the casino. Oh shit. Blackjack table. Mr. Green.
Okay. Mr. Green. He's mean. He's green. He runs a casino in my living room. That's about it.
Well, well, well, if it isn't little Jeremy Albertson. Act for more gambling. Yep. Time to
make that money. Actually, I'm just trying to get to the living room. I'm just trying to get to the
living room. Oh, Jeremy, it seems you've already forgotten about that little debt you owe me after
your last visit. What was it again? 5,000 bits. 5,000 bits? That's correct. You kept double or
nothing until I had to cut you off. That being said, sorry. In a show of good faith, I'll loan
you a thousand bits to get you off your feet. Thanks, I guess. Now run along and make me,
make yourself some money. You sure have a lot of money, Mr. Green. I do. It's all mine and you
can't have any of it. I have a question. How did you get all this money? How did you get all this
money? Gambling, of course, and from idiots. I mean, gamers like you, of course. I almost lost
it all investing in ball coin. Mr. Green, why are you green? Why are flamingos pink? Because they
eat shrimp. Oh, is that real? All right. So I have a thousand bits. Are you kidding me? Can I save
the game? All right. Save game. Auto save. All right. New save. Okay. So we have a thousand bits.
I need to get to 5,000 to pay off Mr. Green. No saves coming. What am I going to replay the whole
game again? We're going all in. All in. Let's go. 13 versus six. You stay on that. Don't move. He's
going to bust right here. See you later. That's very bad. I lost everything. Reset? Refund? Refund?
That's what... That's how you play that hand. Everyone's like, oh my God. Omega. No. If you
have anything over a 12 versus a deal of showing a six, you don't do anything. That's the highest
chance to win that hand. You don't do anything. You just don't know how to play blackjack.
What do you mean nobody stands on 13? You don't know how to play. This is basic blackjack strategy.
You don't hit on 13 versus six. Are you out of your mind? That's the bust hand. You don't hit on 13.
What are you talking about? You never win at blackjack. Blackjack's my game. That was a warmup
round. Mr. Green, have any money? I seem to be out of money. Wait, really? Already? I guess I'm not
entirely surprised, but all right. What's a thousand more bits to Mr. Green anyway? Try not to lose it
all again, Goku. Somebody said always hit below 15. That's not... Don't do that. Here we go. Always
hit below 21. All right. Double aces. I want to split these. I want to split these. I'll get a
21. All right. We're going to stay at 500. Eight versus... Come on. That sucks. This sucks. I have
to hit this. I had to. Yeah. 17 versus nine. I'm just going to lose. I always have to assume that
there's a face card underneath there. You have to assume that there's a face card underneath there.
Guys, I have way more experience than you do loading up the blackjack app on your phone for
15 minutes. You understand? That's not how you play blackjack. I'm screwed again. I have to hit
again. See? That's the way you do it because that's an 18. You see what happened? Do you understand
now? Anything over an eight, you have to hit if you don't have at least 18. You have to. Otherwise,
they flip over the 10, it's over. You lose. This is bad, but we're staying. You don't hit against
the 16 ever. You don't hit this. You just don't. That's why. See? Sit down. Sit down next to me.
Pull up a chair and learn something. This is bad. This is very bad. I have to hit. This is very bad.
I have to though. Thank you very much. I'll take notes. Take notes. I just won. See? That hand is
guaranteed to lose if you don't do what I just did. It's not lucky. It's statistics. Don't get a 10.
There you go. He's going to bust right there. Thank you. You can pay the debt back now. Yeah,
but I got $400 of fun money. Had to hit that. I'm going to get 10 right here. There it is.
Nothing. Nothing. 15. You're going to bust. Oh, yeah. Yeah. There it is. Yeah. I got $1,000 of fun
money. Let's go. 10. Let me give me an ace right now. Oh, you have money. Now I got $2,000 of fun
money. 14 versus an ace. Oh, it's over. All right. That's not bad. I win. Again. Let's go. All right.
Let's go. Come on. Last hand. Bingo. This is it. Give me 10. Oh, oh, you piece of shit.
Here's the money I owe you. Wonderful. Come back soon. Oh, he moves out of the way. Okay. I still
have money, right? 17 versus 2. Fuck. I'm staying. Lost. This is it. Last one. Blackjack. Oh, yes.
There it is. $20,000. Goodbye. I already paid it. Did I pay him twice? I didn't pay him twice,
right? I just paid him twice. What the hell? No. What? Fuck. Oh, it's all right. Whatever. I don't
care. I paid him. I paid him. I paid him twice. That was stupid. And I wanted to get that money
back. Use the telephone. Call Bear. What? What's your emergency? Send up something's wrong. I'm
sorry. There was an emergency. I'm playing an adventure game and I thought it'd be clever.
For sure. You're honest. They have a nice day. The door is locked. Use keypad. Wait, do I know
what this is? Okay. I don't know what the code is though. It's grandpa. What's on TV, grandpa?
TV's not on. There's nothing to look at. I just realized I don't even touch my nose when I say
that. Move out of the way, you little prick. You're blocking the TV. Grandpa, I thought you were dead.
I am dead. So what? You're acting like you've never seen a ghost before. Now move so I can
watch my soaps. What's the afterlife like? Yeah, it's not so bad. I had to crawl my way out of the
hell. But at least that was easier than working his damn remote. Oh, right. Uncle Ted sends his
love too. What am I? What the hell's going on on this TV? Oh, Steakums. How do I get those?
No, no, no, no, no, no, no. Oh, shit. Steak. Fuck. Whatever. I don't care.
555 yum. Oh shit. All right. 555 yum. What else is this like GTA? 555 yum. Hold on. Very bad, grandpa.
Hello, this is an automated message from Steak Yum LLC. Thank you for calling. If you'd like to
file a complaint, please hang up. If you'd like to hear about our promotional offer, please stay on
the line. Due to a recent recall and the resulting class action lawsuit, Steak Yum's LLC is legally
obligated to send you one package of Steak Yum brand meat product at no cost. Remember to check
your mailbox frequently to maintain optimal freshness of the product. Thank you and have
a nice day. Let's go. Right. You just said, wait, you're out of money again? You need more money?
Here's another thousand bits. Thank you. I'm gonna bust. Oh, okay. Let's see. Exactly. We're good.
Blackjack. 17 versus five. No, don't do anything ever. No, I hit the wrong button. I hit the wrong
button. I hit the wrong button. I actually hit the wrong button. I thought Stan was on the left.
Oh my God. What the? That was stupid. I thought that was Stan. Give me more money. This is ridiculous.
How many more times you're going to lose all your money? Well, I paid you twice. So technically,
this is my money. I gave you an extra $5,000. So you actually owe me 3000 more dollars. So that's
how this is going to work. 12 versus three. Shit. Oh my God. Give me the money you owe me. You owe
me 3000 more dollars. Give it to me. You must be the unluckiest man in Las Vegas. Take the money.
Lose it all. I don't care. This sucks. I hate this. Oh my God. Give me a fucking break.
He still owes me two grand. I'm gonna get it. I might not just not going all in. You're going
to run me out of business. You owe me another thousand dollars. There it is. All right. Nobody
move. Oh my fucking God. Okay. I blame this on the fact that I gave him five extra thousand more
dollars and I accidentally hit when I had a guaranteed win. I feel like I've already given
you more than 5000 bits of you owe me. Just take it. 19. There it is. Come on. Don't accidentally
do anything stupid. 18. Give me it. Good. Again. Again. There is the 20 versus the 19. Stay.
Whatever. Whatever. You keep getting aces. That's stupid. 20 again. Stay. Don't move. You're not
going to get any. You're not going to get shit. You're going to get 18 and that's the win. All
right. Here we go. Last one. All in 4000 hand. Let's go. Here's your 10. Here comes your 10.
Again. 18. I'll take it. Stay against two. Thank you so much. I'll take that money. I'll take it.
We're going to do one more. We're going to do one more at. We're going to do one more 4000.
Thank you very much. That's it. This could be a push because it's probably a 10 under there.
It's not. There's 12,000 dollars. Thank you so much. We're going to do one more at two,
which gets a 16 versus six. Don't do anything. Don't listen to people in the chat that say to
do something. Sir, I don't care if I lost. That's how you play that hand. That's how you play that
hand. Fuck it. No. Oh, I got to check my mailbox. No insurance. Don't ever do insurance. Don't do
insurance. Are we going to go outside? Mailbox. Wow. The package from steak from meat yums is
here already. That was speedy. Definitely been in there for too long. Okay. Now I just need. What
do I need? Mayo. Right. Okay. Get this in here. I got to do the maze. Let me get this in here first.
Was there something else I could do over here? I feel like there was. Okay. Is the phone. I need
the keypad to get in this door. Oh, grandpa. Right. Let me talk to grandpa. There's another
hallway. What else is down here? Framed picture. Jerma is a river in southeastern Serbia and western
Bulgaria. It is notable for passing the Serbian Bulgarian border twice. The Jerma originates in
the under and the undeveloped and sparsely populated area of Kragist in the southeastern
corner of Serbia. Starting from the area between the artificial lake Vlasina and the Bulgarian
border, it flows to the northwest on the eastern slopes of the Gramada mountain. Passing through
the village of Klesura, after which it enters an arid region stretching over the border into
Bulgaria. This is where the Jerma crosses the border for the first time and at the border crossing
of Strezimrivoci. Okay. Bathroom. Hair dryer. No, thanks. My hair is already dry.
Okay. Can I use the toilet? All right. Computer number two. This is my number two
I mean my second computer that I use for business reasons. Okay. Anything else I can do? Nothing on
the ground or anything? I feel like I'm going to need this. My hair is already dry. All right.
I'll probably have to come back here later. The mirror. There is. All right. That is funny. Okay.
Basement. This is kind of creepy. Oh, shit. Hold on. Hold on. Hold on a second. Hold on.
I gotta get this right. Give me one second. Give me just one quick second here. I'm going to make
it, you know, okay. Oh, yes. Okay. Oh, it's my good friend. He's a wonderful, wonderful man from what
I've seen. What are you doing down in my basement? What does it look like on your own business?
What are you doing down here? What do I do? Hot roast? I don't think this works with that.
So what? Banana peel? Okay. Wait, turn off the light. I gotta bring obviously have to bring
bugleberry something. Banana on the rumor? Yeah, I was thinking that too. Maybe grandpa has something.
Let's see. How did you die? What? You don't remember? I suppose I was a few years ago.
As I remember Demon Lord Zaraxas chokeslam me into hell, completely obliterating my spinal cord.
Can't live without a spinal cord, son. Nothing unnatural about that.
Yeah, I suppose you're right. What are you watching? There's nothing good on TV anymore,
except for that steak yum commercial. It's got a good jingle. What's the afterlife like?
It's not so bad. I already told you this. I told you already everything that you just wanted to know.
On a pot roast? I don't think that works. Put the hairdryer in the tub. What? Are you telling me to
kill bugleberry? What's wrong with you? Here's a tip I use all the time back in my chocolate
making days. If you ever make money, save. If you ever lose money, load an old save.
Infinite money glitch. Oh, this is, I hate when you need something like this versus three.
Because you can make so many things with a three, but I can't make very much anything with a 16.
I'm just gonna, I'm gonna stay. He's gonna bust right here. Yeah, that sucks. Like there's not
much I can do there. And if I had taken that card, it would have been 21, which that sucks.
One more time. Hit. 13 versus eight. That sucks. Hit again. 15 versus eight. That sucks. Even more.
Hit again. Okay. We're good. All right. All right. We're back. We're back. 12 versus 10. That sucks.
Come on. Give me something low. Okay. All right. We're good. We're back. We're back. All right. One
more of those. And then this is actually it. I'm done. This is the big one right here. 13 versus
seven. I have to hit that. It's going to be low. Thank you 21. Goodbye. Take it. Put it in the bank.
Put it in the bank. Here's that money I owe you. Wonderful. Come back. All right. Good. We're good.
Should have like four grand. Go outside. I gotta, I gotta figure this out.
Bob watchers skip one hour. All right. So what, what, how do we do this?
Go to the exit, the right. Okay. So I can go up or left. I'm going to go up and then left again,
then left again and left again, up or down. I'm going to say up, up again, right, down,
up or right. I think I'm going to bunker door. It looks like an old nuclear fallout bunker
generator. Lots of fumes coming out of this one. Wall dad looks like a construction worker. How
long has he been in my walls? Yeah. What was that? Jason, you've come back. Wait, you're not Jason.
My name is Jeremy. Who's Jason? What are you doing in my wall? My son, Jason, he was supposed to
bring me my pot roast for dinner ages ago. Well, I guess it's canceled because I can't get that
kind of food. So I'll have canned beans instead. Do you know how to turn the internet back on?
Well, sure I do. I did all the wiring around the house. I would help you, but I'm just so hungry
thinking about that pot roast. I simply could not lift a finger until I've eaten. It's not very
helpful. You know where Otto is? Otto, is that one of Jason's friends? I haven't seen him around.
No, nevermind. Okay. How long have you been in here for? It's hard to tell. Days turn into months
in here. Fumes from that generator sure don't help. Oh, well, it's a living. You make money
being in here? Not really. Just an expression. There you go. Well, pot roast, no way. Oh,
oh. Oh, I don't feel so good. I was going to help you with the internet, but here,
take the screwdriver. Just open the electrical box on the telephone pole outside. I'm going to
lay down for a while. Nice. Very nice. I'm going to get going. Pretty good setup you got down here.
Hey, don't touch that. Okay. Oh, I got to skip. Now, let's go to the internet.
It's the hearthstone noise. Touch that. And then we'll come down to the banana pill on the road.
Hey, Mike Toyota, thanks for the 20 community subs. Appreciate it. 20 subs. There's been like
three or four of those. Open sesame. Oh, God. Okay. What am I supposed to do? Oh, that was easy.
QTE of the day brought to you by. I mean, there's nothing to do with this.
This has nothing to do with this. Okay, so did I get the internet back on?
All right. Internet sorted. No problem. Very cool. All right, let's do this.
I think this works. I think I just killed somebody. An O from Otto. Note to self. Not a good lead.
Why would the rumor know anything anyways? He's never even seen the cookies. I should talk to
Jax. I saw him snooping around yesterday looking for a snack. The code to his room is
Omega LUL. Cookies. Okay, Omega LUL. Let's pretend like this didn't happen. All right.
Omega LUL. That's on this door down here. Wait, I can use the freezer. Frozen cheese.
Wait, I can get the key here. How is the rat going to smell the cheese if it's frozen?
I have to cook it. Cheese in the oven? There's no way I'm opening that again.
Cheese in the microwave? Oh, yep. Hair dryer. Okay, Omega LUL. What was it? It's LUL. What is L?
Which one of these is L? Omega? Which one's U? What's U? LUL. Got it. Okay. That's what the Omega
symbol is. Yeah, I know what it is. Oh, this is the old room. Cool. Okay. Hey, sorry for interrupting.
Have you seen Otto? A note of his said he was going to talk to you. Otto? Yeah. Oh, yeah. Right.
He was in here a little while ago asking me about cookies. He left this note here, but I'm way too
busy to reach into my pocket and fish it out. If I beat your high score, would you put down the
light gun for one second? You beating my high score? Didn't you die to pinwheel? You can try,
I guess. I also beat Dark Souls on stream, you know. You gonna let me play? Sure. Stop whining.
Mad Dog's Bottle Busters. Okay. I thought I just killed him. Where is it? Where is it? What's the
high score? I don't have ammo. It's probably a thousand points, right? 10,000 points? Damn it.
I got it. That's definitely a thousand. 1,200. Is that enough? You don't have to hit all of them.
But you actually did it? Beat my high score? That's right. The god gamer himself in the flesh. Now,
where's that note from Otto? Right. Sorry. I'm still in shock here. Here you go. Take it.
The cookie trail has gone cold. Jack doesn't know where the cookies are,
and I'm beginning to lose hope that I'll ever find the cookies. The only clue I have left
is the trail of water I found leading to the basement. Time to pay a visit to B.F. Bugleberry.
See what he can tell us. Oh, you can just play. Okay. Down to the basement. Maybe we'll have new
dialogue with Bugleberry. Wait. Let's do this. Very cool. Mm. Ooey gooey cheese. Let's do the
rat thing first because I feel like I'm going to need a key. Into the kitchen. Okay. Here's the
cheese. Thank you. I'm going to assume I can open this door now. It's the only lock in the whole
house. Huh? Oh, shit. I can make the sandwich. All right. Let's get the sandwich made. Perfect.
Now time to turn it on and get cooking. Make the perfect sandwich. Very good. Perfect. I was
starving. Feels like I haven't eaten anything all day. Well, you know what I mean. All right.
Now we have to go find Otto. Close the fridge? I just did. Go to the basement. Talk to Bugleberry.
Basement's all the way over here, right? Yeah. Oh, gamble? No. I don't need to.
Okay. God. Otto said you'd be down here. Do you know where the cookies went? Cookies? Ah, yes.
I've been using the cookies as ingredients in my cauldron. I have one left. What? I'm
guessing you need me to solve some convoluted puzzle for you. How did you know? I've been trying
to follow the recipe for the perfect German character, but the page in my book has been
ripped to pieces. If you can recreate the recipe for me, I'll give you the last cookie. I will.
Take a look at that recipe. Okay. In this order, these symbols in this order. Is this important
too? Is this the Greek alphabet? Hold on. What was it? No, no, no, no, no. Hold on.
I just want to see what happens. Jeremy Germstar. All right. That was an interesting one.
It's not the one we're looking for. I want to do that again. All right. We're going to do blue and
green. Blue, blue, green, green, and then red. Oh no, purple. And New Year's German. It's a
gotcha game. Well, that was an interesting one, but it's not the one we're looking for.
All right. What's the actual one? Let me see the recipe. Okay. Circle, square, triangle, star,
triangle in those colors ordered. Circle, square, triangle, star, triangle, red, green. I gotta
write this down. I haven't tweet this stream out. Don't write it down. How am I going to remember
this? Circle, square, triangle, star, triangle, red, green, purple, blue, yellow, red, green,
purple, red, green, purple, red, green, purple, circle, red, circle. There's no red circle.
There's no red circle. Where is it? Circle, square, triangle, star, triangle in this order.
Oh, it doesn't. Okay. So I just have to do circle. These are the symbols. So what's, what's not on
here? Circle, square, triangle, star, no hearts, no hearts at all. I get it. Okay. So we need to do
red, green, red, green, purple, blue, yellow, red, green, purple, blue, yellow, red, green.
I have to write it down. Purple, blue, yellow. I think I got it. I'm just going to write it down.
Why would I? You write shit down on these games. Just write it down. I'm writing it down. I'm
writing it down. I'm going to write it down. Okay. Why are there two triangles up there?
Oh, I have to use two triangles. I'm writing it down. Did I read this? I've read this, right? Met
a couple at a random restaurant who told me about a wrestler dying. I don't know them and don't know
the wrestler. I was in a city I do not know at all. I may have been visiting. I was invited to
his funeral and was trying to be polite and said yes. A couple then sent me a referral link to a
weird online system to accept the invite slash make payments. I ignored it and went back to my room.
I got ready to go, was in a full suit, and took a car a few miles away to the spot I met the couple.
I had the address written down for the funeral, but left it in my room. For some reason, I figured
it was right across the street from the restaurant we met. I couldn't find it. I looked everywhere.
After an hour or so, I went back to my room and said fuck it. After a while, I got a phone call
from the couple who asked if I was still going. The funeral was well underway and I didn't want
to just walk in at the end. They gave me the address and it was a 50 minute drive from my room.
They started having bad reception and told me to sign up for their referral link again before I
hung up. It was a dream I had. Did I tell you guys that one? Did I go over that one before?
No? I wrote it down. That's when I woke up. What was I doing? Oh right, I was writing this down.
Hold on, let me write this down. Why did he read it like he's never seen it? I mean I have seen
it before. It's been a while. That was December of 2020 is when I had that dream. Okay,
let's keep going. What was I writing this down? A note. New note. Okay, circle, square, triangle,
R, triangle. The order is red, green, purple, blue. All right, let's do it. Okay, so circle.
I need red. A red square. There's no red circle so we're gonna do red square. Green
square. No, green triangle. Thank you. And then we need to do purple. Purple
circle and then blue star. Yellow triangle. Oh fuck, what happened? Yellow circle?
It said there was two triangles. There's only one. It's orange. Isn't that orange?
Just use the triangle. Catboy! Is that the one? That's it. My finest creation yet.
Chad is going to love this. Just think of all the fan art. As promised, here is the last cookie.
No need to throw. I wouldn't if I were you.
I should take this back to Otto's bed. He can smell cookies from a mile away.
Off-brand bugleberry. That's, no, I, whatever. Let's go see if we can find him. Somebody said,
Jesus Christ. It's not real. It's not real money. It's not real as my bank account is not linked to
the game. Okay, here we go. Do we do it? Otto! It's Otto, the wonder dog. Ready for your walk?
That was a great walk. Hey, where'd Otto go? Where is he? Is there another note?
No. Backyard? Was it chocolate on that? What's the thing that, what is it?
It's something that is like chocolate but it's not chocolate. What's it called?
Carib. Yeah. Where's Otto? This had to have been finished very recently, right? Because this was
only like a month or two ago. This is a couple months ago. Be able to add all this? All the
dollhouse references? That had been pretty late in development. Where's Otto? Who's a good boy?
Otto. That's so cute. Is it time to stream? Let's see. I got an achievement that just said
minus two worst stream of the year. Blinking. I was just lost in my brain trying to find any
game. You can just see the cogs turning to like just say any video game. I have no idea. What was
the last thing I played? And that was really fun. Those two were really cool. Game by William
Enders aka 14 hour lunch break aka dev in chat art. Very good job. That was very cute. Additional
3D models. Look at that. Yeah, well done. That was really, that was really fun. Excellent, excellent
work. Both of the development teams that made these games. Jeff McCloud. Jeff McCloud is just,
he's the Picasso of royalty free music. Special thanks. German voice line emporium.
What? That exists? Very cool. Steam support team. I don't know. Was there an issue? I wonder.
Hey, thanks for making it. It's really fun. It doesn't know that there's a voice treasury
of everything he's ever said. Well, whatever. No, don't do this. We have to do this every...
Fine.
All right. We got, we got our expectations subverted three times there.
Very cool. Oh, I got an achievement plus two. If you're getting the German cough emporium,
the German sneeze emporium and the German yawn emporium. Why? Why do you want all that?
Why do you want a bunch of times that I've like coughed? That was really cool. I'm very happy
with that. That was a lot of fun. So now those are the two of the community games I wanted to play.
What am I? Don't what? End of the stream voice? Um, I actually probably maybe because
I want to get back to like Saturday, Sunday. So we're probably going to just go Saturday, Sunday
to kind of get back to normal here. Three hour Andy. I did say it was only going to be a three
hour stream on Twitter. Did I even tweet that? No, I didn't. What? Am I misremembering that?
I tweeted, right? What? What did I say on the tweet? Playing a couple of fan games,
hanging out for a few hours. All right. I said that. Yeah. Yeah. I want to do Saturday, Sunday.
I want to get back to that because like I said, I don't want to be once a week anymore. I want to
be like twice a week. So we'll, we can call it here. I'll be back on Saturday, Sunday for more
longer, substantial streams. Not just three hours. A few is eight hours. But I want to get in the
habit of even if I'm not going to be around for that long, I still want to pop in for a few hours,
like at least two times a week. I'm slowly trying to get back to not doing once a week anymore.
And we'll see going forward. I'm going to keep trying to add them as I can.
And I will see you guys on Saturday. We'll do Saturday, Sunday. I have plans. If you don't
know what the Halloween plan is, although that's next weekend, we're going to be watching a bunch
of public domain movies on Halloween like we did last time. That was one of the funnest streams ever.
Hopefully we have a good time again. We're going to watch at least three or four plus hours,
even more, maybe five plus hours of old shitty movies. See if we can find some. And by the way,
there's a possibility we might see the Ritz brothers return. I think they have another one
or two that we could watch. But to the people that made, and there's other community games too
that exist. I know during the community content nights, I know a couple of them came in. So this
is fun to do. I'd like to compile them every now and then. Really, really good job. This is really
fun. It's shocking to me that if somebody wants to put the amount of time that it takes to make
something like this just for fun and just to maybe have people play it and enjoy it and be connected
to this community and the stream and everything, it's mind blowing. So I hope it was fun to work
on. It was really fun to play. But that's going to be the end of the stream. I will see you guys
on Saturday, Sunday. We will get back to normal on the Saturday, Sunday, weekend, Andy schedule.
Let's do a raid. We raid, raid, raid Neanderthals? Yeah, sure. Yeah, let's go. I haven't raided
somebody in a while. What is Neanderthals playing? Minecraft? Time for a raid song? No, no more. Hey,
nobody wants to do the raid song. Nobody wants to do the raid song. The raid song was not,
I'm telling you right now, as comedy professor, your comedy professor, we talked about it like
two or three hours ago. That, that's not, yeah, that gets you removed from the class. By the way,
I want to make this clear too. If somebody farts into a baked Lays bag and you come in the next
day and fart into a baked Lays bag, I'm going to send you home, right? You can't, we can't have
like 30 people all fart into a baked Lays bag at the same time the next day, right? That person
got an A. You gotta do something else. And there's people that probably just came in like 20 minutes
ago that have no idea what we're talking about. It's fine. Go say hello to Neanderthals. I will
talk to you guys on Saturday. Have a great one. We will do some longer streams on Saturday,
Sunday. I have a lot of things I want to prepare. Thanks for watching. As always,
the community shit is awesome. I love to do it. I wish we could still do the community video stuff,
but I can't play eight minutes uninterrupted of Star Wars. That would get me removed,
I believe, from the platform. So we can't do that anymore. I'm surprised we got away with it as long
as we did, if I'm very honest with you. So, unfortunately, but if we can do stuff like this,
I'd love to do it. So have a great rest of your night. Thanks for hanging out for the few hours
that we were here. See you Saturday at 2pm Pacific. Good night. Goodbye. See you soon.
Oh my God. Wait, I didn't even do the outro. What the fuck? No, no, no, no, no, no, no,
it's too fast. Oh, I thought it was ending right now. Okay, I thought it was actually like you were
getting sent in now. I just fucking panicked. I wanted to do the subs too. I just was queuing
up the raid. That was actual panic. Oh my God. That scared the shit out of me for some reason.
I saw the bar on my screen was going in five seconds. I'm sorry. Oh shit, we're gonna- I'm
gonna have to cancel this. Can we get through the subs? I can't believe there's this many people
that still subbed to the channel. This is insane. We're not even gonna get through the Ds by the
time the raid happens. We're only in the Ds. We're in the Gs. I have to cancel the raid.
I have to cancel it. We'll do it again in a second. Just wait. Yeah, I'm canceling the raid. We have
to do it again in a second. I'm sorry. Wait, somebody just gave subs and it superseded my
ability to cancel the raid. I can't cancel the raid anymore. It's- 8-bit just gave 10 community
subs and I can't click any buttons now. It's taking over. You're just gonna go. I'm so sorry.
Oh my God, I can't stop it.