Stop punching me. Don't punch me. Don't punch me. Hello. Hello. How are you? Good to see you again. Get him.
I got a little froggy in my throat. Trying to get rid of him.
I can't. It's still there. Why? You're a noisy streamer. Hold on. This is why I've been sitting
here clearing my throat for like five- Okay, I'm back. That took long enough. Today, from the title
of the stream, you probably see we're gonna be playing Connect again. We're going back to it.
We're gonna start with one of the most popular fucking frog in my throat. We're gonna start
with one of the most popular frogs. The guy that goes, hello my baby, hello my darling, hello my
ragtime gal. I don't even know what his name is. He's probably the most popular frog, right?
Slippy Toad? Who's the most famous frog ever? Oh, Curret the Frog, right. Don't turn off by 360.
What are you talking about? If you're having trouble, don't turn off the 360. No, don't turn
off my 360. Okay, we're good. I thought my 360 just almost auto-powered down.
All right, hi. I'm just gonna- I don't- Here, look. I have to do this so I can get out of the
fucking way. We're starting. Hi. Oh, it's screaming at me. I got my wireless Bluetooth headphones.
Streamer alert? What's going on with the hair? And I don't- Okay.
I don't- My lighting in my room sucks. And this camera sucks. It's a horrible combo. I have one
recessed light right here that beams down an interrogation light. And then I have, like,
one of those Walmart Logitech webcams. All of them suck. Wait, hold on. Did you see my hands?
Even the expensive Logitech webcams, they're all- They're fucking terrible.
What ha- What the fuck? And they have, like, oh, the Logitech C29, the C40, the C920,
the C, the C- What are all these fucking webcams that all are terrible? Why do they all look like
this? Anyways. Anyways. All right, I'm still in a fucking really weird mood. It didn't leave
from yesterday. I don't know what the fuck is wrong with me. I think it's like the- the- the-
when the weather gets, like, a little better and nicer. Like, it's a reverse, like, full moon.
I- I like it more weird as the- as, like, the spring comes in. I'm like a fucking flower.
Anyways. We're gonna play Connectimals right now. We gotta test something first, though.
Where are you? There you are. You ready? I'm gonna put my finger up. Ready? One! One! One! That's not
right. It's a little delayed. I gotta go more delayed, right? Well, here's the problem. It's
delayed from me to the Connect. And then it's delayed from you to the stream. I see myself,
then it goes. See myself, then it goes. All right, I get it delayed a little more. Hold on.
It's a double delay, Andy. I know. Why's my room red? 750 delayed. Try that. Here we go, right? Pretty
good. One. Sweep. Sweep. Sweep. Sweep. Sweep. A little more. 800. I need a little more. More power.
800. Get it to 800 power. Try that. Sweep. Why do people cast like this, like, when they cast spells?
Just go like that. You ever think about that? In every, like, RPG and every fucking fantasy
thing, why do they have to do weird casts? Just fucking point and say fireball. Why is it like
fire? No, just go. That's so much easier. Fireball! Why go like this? That's fucking stupid.
What were we doing? All right. Sweep. Sweep. Go. Yes. I think we're good. You guys ready?
Because it's cool. Did you see my belly button just come up? All right. You ready? You ready?
Everybody? I'm just fucking connected up. This is Connectimals. This game's probably not good.
Here we go. I'm calibrated. Ah, welcome to the world of Connectimals. Did Peter Molyneux make
this game? Peter Molyneux made this game, right? Oh, no, he made another one with, like, a little
boy. What happened? What happened? This thing freaked out. What happened? What happened? What
just happened? What's going on? Wave to connect. Please face the sender. Sensor. I need a controller.
What the fuck are you doing? What? What did I press? Hold on. What did I press? Oh, it wants
sign in with your email. Fuck you. I don't even- I have no idea what that is. Holy shit, I have
absolutely no idea what this is. I have no idea what my password is. I'm just gonna be David
instead. Yeah, who cares? I have absolutely no idea. All right, David. We're gonna be logging
as David. He doesn't have Xbox live. It's like my little brother. Okay, let's go. We're David.
So this one's now with bears. Why does it have to be so far away? I'm just getting closer. I don't care.
Hello, and welcome to the island. To get started, put your arm out and hover over the start button.
That's Invader Zim. That's Invader Zim. Uh, what's his name? I know it. Richard. Richard what?
What's his name? Oh, I don't care about signing in. Fuck off. Richard Horvitz. There he is. Wait,
I'm not David though. Oh shit, I just stole David's identity. Guest. Select bear adventure. Um,
I think I don't want to do regular connectibles. To start, put out your hand and swipe it in front
of you like this. I like the way this camera is, by the way. It's a bad camera position. We need to
spring this. What the fuck did I just do? What did I do? Did I pick bear adventure?
Oh, there they are. Wolf den. I picked bear adventure. Should I do the first one first?
Why is my room red? You're a Satanist.
You're a curious looking pirate. Where's your house?
Whoa, 3D. Don't you our eyes be an explorer, yes? Well, you've certainly discovered something here.
Welcome to the island. Get out of here, you little fucking weirdo. But please come. Everybody will
want to meet you. We haven't seen anyone since the captains left on their expedition.
I didn't want to do this one. It's a sacred place. We call it the bonding circle.
It's where- I wanted to do the regular game. Where is everybody? Being shy.
No need to be shy, little one. Should I go back? Come on. It's where cubs start their
bond with their human companions. Okay. Should I do the bear adventure? Does it matter? Which
one's better? What? The bonding circle. What? We'll play the default game. All right. I'll
play this for five minutes and then I'm going back. Oh, this is back when like loading screens
were a majority of like the 12 hours of the game. It was like four hours.
Which one? Which should I pick? Whatever you're not sure what to do,
just follow me and do what I do. Okay. I could panda bear. Hold out your hand like this. I don't
hope. No, I don't want the panda bear though. Hold out your hand and swipe it in front of you.
That's it. Now, if you swipe with your left hand, you can look at the cubs to your left.
Go ahead. Left and right to me. Why can't I just turn my body? All right. So we got- that's-
we got brown bear, black bear. All right. Hold on. Grizzly bear. Grizzly bear is very cute.
Black bear. Black bear is like little dogs. All you have to do is put your hand out in front of
you. Don't worry. Oh, no panda or polar bear. Don't these- don't- aren't these mean-
Fucking connect is- is stupid. Go ahead. Reach out with both your hands and give it a good pet.
I guess we have a fucking polar bear. Oh, he's such a good boy. Left and right to move parts of
its body. He's so cute. Step left and right. I don't want a pet there. What the fuck? Oh,
polar bear. This cub is one of my favorites. No. Good. We can go somewhere else. What's this one?
Honey bear? A poo bear? A cinnamon bear? Hold on. I need to see the cinnamon bear. Oh, this is the
bear that's on all the cereal boxes. I like this one. How are you? Oh, he looks like a little fox.
I'm like down here. Down here. He just like shits in my hand. Oh, it's okay. It's all right.
Promise me you won't name it cinnamon. They really don't like that. Yes. That'd have been bear.
Karma, what the fuck? What? Oh, they just bit me. Oh, they are bears. Do you want to give your new
friend a name right now? Yes. Should we name him? I think it's time we gave your little one a name,
don't you? Say it out loud. Snuggles the first of his name. Snuggles the bear. Dryer sheet bear.
Dryer sheet. Do I have to press the button? Dryer sheet bear.
Dryer sheet bear. Dryer sheet bear. Oh, he loves it. I have to say that every time. He loves it.
Picture or something to identify this. Scan a picture. No. Like on my fucking printer. Looks
like you're ready to go see where you'll be staying while on the island. I have to go scan an image
and like upload it? Scan your face. Oh. Now that you have a bear companion to show you everything
on the island. What do you even do in this game? Or rather the home of Captain Lawrence Biddler.
Lawrence. What are these houses? You don't do anything. You don't do anything. You just walk
around. This is a baby game. Oh. This was like a huge seller. It's like the number one bestseller
in New York Times Connect list. My house? Oh, your house. Okay.
Where's my house? Oh, he already got in.
Those are the original like connectables?
I have to drink my coffee. You're ugly.
I were at each other's throats. You know, it really is impossible to be annoyed to death.
That's when Captain Blackwood decided it would be better for me to live with his best friend
Biddler. I think things worked out rather well actually. Oh. What's his name? Dryer? Sheet Bear?
What the heck are you doing over here? You goofball.
Journal. It explains what happened to the captains. Three weeks since we landed on
Mira. At first, I couldn't believe me eyes. Good pirate voice. But half a day's sail from the
moor. Let's see if I can match it. It's curious that we've never seen it before.
And probably it's not one-to-one so I don't sound like I'm lying.
And when we found me old friend Lawrence Biddler and little Lena here all alone.
Well, you can imagine my surprise. Lawrence told me about the gift that brought him here
and the story about the kingdom. I thought we days of treasure hunting were done after my
search for Felisaurum. But I have to admit, I can't resist the urge for more adventure.
I'm just, I'm antsy. I want to connect. I sent the crew away on the bonnie barnacle
and told the moor that Biddler and I were going to stay as long as the bears.
As on Lemuria, the bears are just cubs. Well, I have some theories about that. Up on the cliff
is an abandoned fort. 35 year old man playing video games.
It was built long ago by some band of forgotten pirates.
Don't tell anyone. Only to realize that their ship are scattered across the beaches.
Just suppose them. But what if they never left the island
and found the entrance to the hidden kingdom? How?
Tomorrow, all Biddler and I will travel. By the way, these jeans are way too small for
me now. I'm like a fat guy. I gained like 25. The ship passed on the island for months already
when captain Blackwood arrived. This bear can read?
The captain set out to explore the island. Captain Biddler asked me to look over the
house and the bears. I'm not sure what happened to them, but they never came back.
Where's my bear food? I want to like drop the bear food.
Over there is a map of the island. This is Fort Topaz. It's not far at all.
Let's go see if we can find out what happened with the captains.
I don't want to do that. I want to feed the bear.
It looks like your bear cub is ready to go. These cubs love to play at Fort Topaz.
Let's get- Okay, is it kind of weird? I feel like this is like,
bears are not like dogs. They're not like, oh, yip yip, come get me, my friend.
Like this is weird, right? Like why is the bear acting like it's a puppy that I just
bought from like, like a little small puppy. They'll kill you, right? Yeah.
Well, a baby won't.
I think your cub smells the fresh sea air.
This is a kid's game? I know. An adult playing a kid's game.
Look, they're so cute. He's acting like a puppy.
This is like a, this is like a dachshund puppy.
All right, let's play. How do, what do I do?
Friar Sheet Bear. Friar Sheet Bear. They've gone bipedal. This is where they
fucking- I just know I've saw this movie. They take over humanity.
Friar Sheet Bear. Hey, go. Oh, what'd you get?
Is it a whistle?
Yes.
It's as easy as that. Spin in place. Careful you don't get too dizzy.
Oh, it knows. To make a great team.
Okay, here's a fun one. The play dead trick.
All you have to do is lie flat on your back. Go ahead. Don't be shy.
Or you could just play dead.
Can I do like the Backstreet Boys thing? All right, fine. He's getting angry.
All right, I'll be dead. I'm dead. I'm dead.
I'm dead down here. I'm dead down here.
Okay, what about this?
Leave me and my friend alone. Give me a hug. What do I do?
I'm gonna do that. Teach him look at me.
Lie down. Look, lie down. Lie down. Down. Lie down. Lie down.
Good. Good. Friar Sheet Bear. Good. Friar Sheet Bear.
Up, up, up, up, up. I don't wanna do that again.
We get money? What trick? Star Jump.
All right, let's do this like a two-year-old.
Come here. Hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey.
Oh, a ball.
You're gonna learn from the master.
By the way, first one to fucking blink loses. How long can you go?
I feel like this is the kind of shit that was on Jimmy Fallon 10 years ago or something.
Oh, this guy plays juggle with his bear.
He's juggle with his bear.
Jimmy Fallon is not this good.
Yes.
Oh, I thought it was a key. Landmine.
What the fuck is wrong with you? What is wrong with you, dude?
It's a lot. I'm supposed to take a sip out of that.
Oh, juggle challenge.
Keep the ball in the air.
Okay. Pop as many bubbles as you can while juggling. I'm ready for this one.
Oh, you and me. Are these frogs? This is wicked fucked up.
I told you the bears were evil. Didn't even miss one.
Didn't even miss one frog. This is terrible. I think this is bad. This is not a bad game.
Did I pick the wrong... Did I pick the expansion? Did I play the regular game?
You do this in the regular game?
He hates this game. I mean, I don't... Don't worry. We're just getting started.
We're just getting warmed up with connectables. HD.
I got the Fable Connect game back here.
Able Connect. That one's supposed to have magical fucking spells.
This is just an excuse to get parents to get their kids to move their fucking arms around.
They think they're playing with the bear cub that they're just doing the exercising.
Wonderful. Congratulations. You've earned your first medal.
That's a gold medal. You'll get a shiny trophy too.
Do you want to try again? To the fort.
Careful on these steps. They can be slippery.
Speedrun. Isn't that just a window into...
Skip, skip, skip, skip. I had a chance.
I had one opportunity to get the hell out of here.
Oh, by the way, we also have more movies to make.
Thinking about that. All right. Let's play.
Anytime you want to play with one of your toys, open your toy box.
All you have to do is hold your arm out to the bottom.
Let's go. You can also just say, open toy box or open inventory.
Next game now. Hold on. It has been 30 minutes.
How have I been in for 30 minutes? Open toy box.
Toys are available. Hold your hand over a box to see what toys are inside.
Do you want to do it? Do you want to do it on camera
so you can tell that I'm not fucking faking it?
If you see a toy you like, hold your hand...
Toy boat, toy boat, toy boat, toy boat, toy boat, toy boat, toy boat, toy boat.
Fuck yeah. Go get it.
Who has the ball? I'm doing... No, I'm not doing juggle.
I'm not doing juggle. This game suck.
Should I move on? No, it does.
I thought this was like one of the New York Times Best Seller Connect game.
Did I mess it up? Don't leave.
Don't leave dryer sheet beer.
Is this a normie game?
Like eight-year-old normies?
What are you talking about? Wait, what?
Oh, yes. It's a normie game.
All those like seven-year-olds.
The seven-year-old normies.
Seven-year-old doesn't barely have to tie shoes.
What do you mean? Bro, juggle with them.
Fine. All right. I'm going to put in...
I'm going to put in the fable game.
This is actually a cereal box game for kids.
And let me do the rubber chicken.
Let me do the rubber chicken. Hold on.
Did he fucking record that?
I don't know he could do that.
Juggling.
Xbox record that.
That must have been really loud. I'm so sorry.
Holy shit. That was probably horrible.
Hold out your arm to the bottom right.
Not loud enough.
All right. Hold on. I see a sandwich right here.
There's like some sandwich.
Let's at least like do the thing.
Let me at least like give him a bath, right?
That's like fun. That'll be like fun.
Here we go. Let's give him a bath.
Cleaning is an important way of caring for your animal.
Able. Wait.
If your animal gets dirty,
just give it a good scrub with the cleaning brush.
Washing his eyes.
All over your cub's body.
Where's the water?
I think I'm about to be using any water.
Wouldn't that just be dry and like scratchy?
All right. Let me see what the other items are.
I'm not done yet.
Dryer sheet, bear.
Oh.
To change the direction of your throw.
To the face.
He's like bounced off his nose.
I'm trying to hit her.
That's bad too.
Longest throw.
Oh yeah. I'll show you a long throw.
Let's see that.
Good boy.
I'm going to the ocean.
Hey, hey. Look, look, look, look.
Look, look, look, look.
Look what I got.
Eat it.
Shit. This is so not synced up correctly.
I'm doing it and then it's happening.
Next game. Next.
Wait. One more item.
No dryer sheet, bear.
Okay.
Throw dryer.
Show dryer sheet.
What the what the fuck does he have on his head?
Sometimes your cub friend wants to play with.
Choose whether or not to.
By holding your arm out to the right for yes or to the left for no.
All right. I want to climb a tree first.
Look, I got a lot of cadet games to go through.
How do I do that?
If bears love anything, it's climbing.
Guys, no exception.
To get your bear to climb up the tree.
Move your hands above your head like this.
Step left and right to get a better view of your surroundings.
Wait. Am I on like a drone?
Your bear to climb back down the tree.
Just crouch down like this.
He's going to fall.
Your bear will slide down the trunk.
This is so stressful.
Slide down. Slide down.
If there are any little...
Come down from there.
Your bear is sure to gobble them up.
Oh, it's four bear.
It's bear.
Run to hold the part.
Oh my god.
Fucking fable.
Hold on.
Probably a lot.
Or a dryer sheet bear.
Fuck it, fable.
I thought this would make sure your room has enough space to play.
Don't look up.
An anvil going to drop on my head?
Webcam's too big.
Turn the lights off.
No, you won't be able to see me.
This is the Peter Molyneux one.
Wasn't there a Peter Molyneux game where he's like...
Take a seat, get comfortable, and get ready for your journey.
Try to sit upright and keep your legs uncrossed.
For best results, place your Kinect sensor in a central position, above or below your TV.
You may need to sit forward in your seat if it has
high arms, a low seat, or a soft back.
Make sure you have enough room to play.
Try not to sit too close to other people or objects.
You fired on me?
To access the Kinect guide while playing,
hold your left arm straight out to your side.
Try this now to begin your journey.
Left arm?
Where does it want me to go?
I just did that.
Oh!
Hold on a second.
Why is...
Resume and begin.
Resume, begin.
Why...
What do you mean resume?
What the fuck are you talking about?
Why is...
What do you have a resume and begin button?
This thing is bright green.
It says resume.
Oh my god!
Running Kinect ID.
Please space the sensor.
Oh, David.
You could literally like torture me and I wouldn't know the password.
Okay, start games.
Can you see me?
I'm in view.
I want to get this right though,
because this is an actual fucking video game.
I guess it's not that bad.
It's pretty close.
Face cam, face cam.
Hold on, let me write the face cam up.
It looks fucking dark as hell.
Don't touch anything.
I can't even...
I have like a fucking whole goddamn unit of like technical directors
to like play a console game on your PC.
You got to have like 10 monitors.
To stream a console game,
you need to have like fucking 40 monitors.
It's so dark.
It's not this dark in my room.
It actually is not this dark in the room.
You need backlights?
Move the lights.
I don't have...
What do you mean move the lights?
I have a recessed light in my sensor.
Turn on the sun.
This shit is so...
Why do all these like dinky little shit webcams
need like 5,000 megawatts of light
to like be shown up on screen?
You see me?
It's like we can literally send a fucking...
A rover to Mars.
But I have to put a 5 million megawatt lamp in my face
to show up on this without blowing,
blowing the fuck out the exposure.
Why?
No, it ain't the window.
I've had this problem for years.
It's your fat ass.
My ass is just like fucking huge,
like blocking out the sun.
Get a better camera.
No, they're all like this.
All webcams are like this.
That's why there's a whole company, guys,
that makes like streamer lights.
Because they know it's like a Band-Aid problem.
You know what I mean?
I ain't getting fucking streamer lights.
Uh, hold on.
That's red.
Red.
High balance is fucking horrible.
What the hell is going on here?
Let's go!
Where did you go?
Hold on.
All right, I gotta sit back down.
Perfect.
What's over there?
Oh, there's like a fucking toy over there.
All right, that should be good.
Where did you go?
The Kinect sensor having trouble.
Okay.
Whoa, look at me.
I'm like lit up over there.
Oh yeah, I remember this.
Shit, you can't do it.
All right, I'm ready.
All right, start game.
You guys ready for fable?
Your mic's in the middle.
I got you.
There you go.
Even the greatest of journeys must begin with a single step.
I completely forgot about old console games.
We're obsessed with having alone out bloom
on every single title that made the game run at 18 frames a second
to hide the fact that the game was ugly.
You guys remember that shit?
Wow, I'm so glad we're over that.
Come on, keep the pace up.
We've got a long way to go before we get home.
To me?
Good morning, Kaplan.
Thunder, with us holding up.
Should make good time today.
Daniel, I've seen Gabriel this morning.
Oh, not again.
Dammit, Gabriel.
Audio's desynced.
Where are you?
It is.
But I think that's the game.
I don't think that's anything to do with capturing.
I believe that's just the video game.
I can't wait to wash another animal with a brush.
Like in 60% of every Kinect game.
What do you think, Seren?
Come on.
DMT's kicking it.
I'm getting better.
I'm ready for whatever we run into.
Fucking ghosts.
Bumpy roads, bit of drizzle, stuff for legends.
Come on, girl.
Eat the horse.
Oh, come here.
The convoy will be moving on soon.
We better get you ready.
There's a fucking brushing game.
Good girl, Seren.
There's a good girl.
I got double brush.
We're gonna get this part of the skin raw.
There you are, Gabriel.
Kaplan, I thought you were getting the convoy ready.
Don't even move back.
Leave me alone.
You mean the triumph already left?
What were you doing?
I gotta move the mic over here.
Were you distracted by the butterflies?
Or were you just daydreaming about old fables?
No, I was just about to get Seren ready.
Look, I'm not letting you out my sight.
Does your horse need a brushing?
Don't show me that.
I don't want that to look weird.
Now get Seren harnessed up and let's get moving.
All right, I just need to get me-
Now, Gabriel.
Why even have that part?
You so badly wanted to have the horse brushing segment.
Come on, Gabriel.
We could have opened here.
The convoy will be miles away by now.
Why have the horse-
You needed the horse brushing segment.
We could have opened here.
Keep your moustache on.
Open right here.
I can't wait to have to hold the reins.
Come on.
Catching up to do.
The tribe will be well-
What do I do?
Track the reins once to make Seren trot.
Once trotting, you can accelerate to a gallop
by cracking the reins a second time.
Okay, I'm ready.
Continue.
Here we go.
What were you doing back there, anyway?
Nothing.
Yeah, and you'd have done that all day
if I hadn't come back.
Guys, I forgot to tell you.
I got the special connect seat.
It's connected through the USB-C
in the back of the Xbox.
To steer right,
pull the right rein towards your body
and push the left rein away.
To steer left,
pull the left rein towards your body
and push the right rein away.
While steering,
try to keep your hands low
and make large, clear movements.
All right, we're going off a fucking cliff, I think.
Hey, open your eyes.
Hey, it's called steering.
Try it.
Oh, what are we doing?
What are we up to?
What are we doing?
Uh, reconnect seat.
That's right, I forgot.
It has like a little launch pad.
You know what they used to fucking make?
Shit like that.
They wanted it to be like that.
When are you going to fix up
this whole cart, Gabriel?
Soon.
There was like a vest.
There was like a whole huge vest you could put on
that when you get like shot in a game,
it like vibrated your heart.
They so badly wanted you to get like
actually hurt and shit.
Hey, look at him.
I'm not doing that.
Let me guess.
You were up all night
reading those old books of yours again,
weren't you?
Well, not all night.
Into the wall, into the wall.
No, you only do the
drive into the wall joke twice
before it's too much.
All this dreaming about magic,
heroes, stories we read
when we were knee high to a hob.
It's got to stop.
We're not children anymore.
Do I get to pick like my class?
And start doing, Gabriel.
Old fairy tales didn't get me where I am today.
Head of the combo.
Do I have like powers?
Do I have a weapon?
I had to make sacrifices.
This is an insanely long
ride the horse opening segment.
We don't need this here.
You showed me how the ride on the reins, right?
Let's keep it slow through here.
Nice and easy.
This segment is far too long.
Gently pull the reins to your chest
to lower your speed.
Rough terrain will injure Saren
and less ridden over at a trot.
Oh, that's why I was getting all fucked up.
So make sure you take good care of her.
Easy now.
Slow it down, Gabriel.
There you go.
Why can't you drive like this all the time?
That's the way.
Sarah may be old,
but there's still a few miles left in the old girl.
All right, we're good.
Don't listen to him, girl.
He just wishes he had a horse like you.
Yeah, right.
That'll be it.
I think that was rough terrain,
but it doesn't matter.
I don't think this matters.
Except for the,
except for whoever's in the back.
Whoever's inside of the cart is like,
oh my fucking God,
I can't even drink my tea.
You and Saren are going for a swim.
Show me how fast you can stop this thing.
Just so I know,
I don't have to worry about you when we get there.
If you need to come to a full stop quickly,
pull the reins back high over your head.
Over your head?
Oh, all right.
I feel better now.
Now let's get moving.
Catch up to the comms.
I'm going to open up the back.
I'm going to go to the back of this thing and like,
open it up.
All the luggage is going to be everywhere.
It's going to be like an overturned table.
Okay, hold on.
Did we get over?
Where are we going?
What happened?
This segment is way too fucking long.
Oh, I have four health left.
Get me to the town.
As you travel, you'll come across
experienced orbs on the road.
Collecting these will allow you to purchase upgrades.
Green orbs can be collected at any speed,
but other colors require specific speeds.
You know when you put like a video file into like a final cut
or a premiere timeline and you right click it
and you just say like 50% playback speed?
I swear to God, I feel like that a lot of devs do like the,
put the game in and right click the fucking file
and do 50% fucking playback speed.
Just stretch the thing extra like another hour, two hours.
There's no reason.
Are people afraid that if they have like a four-hour experience,
not like a seven-hour experience,
that like it's going to be bad or something?
Like I'd rather have a three-hour experience
without me like fucking just stretched out timeline
and a seven-hour fucking filled with a bunch of junk.
Where did the time go?
Seems like only yesterday we were running through the fields
to play fighting sticks, not caring the world.
Hold on.
Sometimes I miss those days.
I swear to God, people, a lot of devs and maybe it's both.
Maybe it's like developers, reviewers, consumers, I don't know.
Like the prospect of having like a good five-hour game
versus like a bloated 12-hour game is I don't understand.
I'd rather have just to just cut all the bullshit out
and give me a fucking good game.
That's got to be, it's got to be eight to 12 hours.
Why?
Just make it good.
It's got to be 20.
I'm sorry.
It's got to be a 28.
It's going to be a 30-hour experience.
Just make it 15.
Doesn't matter.
Make it a good game.
Only 12.
There on the horizon, bower stone or bricks and smoke.
Why would anyone live in a place like that
when they could have the open road, eh?
Five hours with replayability.
There you go.
Okay, I don't want to do this segment anymore.
We've been riding on the horse for like how, honestly, how long?
How long have we done tutorial horse for?
It's been like 14 or 15 straight minutes.
I've just ride on the horse tutorial.
I read it nearly ended the world once.
Holy shit.
And just he's gonna take it from me anyways.
Wherever that storm's coming from, it's heading this way.
The whole game is a tutorial.
I need to ride ahead now.
We'll be at Reba's reach soon.
Have to make sure the tribes together when we cross.
Just make sure you keep up the pace.
All right.
Saren can go even faster.
While galloping, crack the reins once to make Saren sprint.
Each time you crack the reins to make Saren sprint,
you'll use up some of her stamina.
All right, let's go.
If the stamina bar in the bowden center empties,
continuing to crack the reins will injure Saren.
All right, watch the stamina bar.
The bar will recharge.
Horse riding sim.
This is not even a horse riding sim though.
This is watching a horse riding sim movie.
See how fast we can catch up with the trine.
You ready, girl?
All right, let's go.
Cross the bridge.
I can't wait to get to Shalefields.
Just think this time tomorrow we'll be across the river iron washing in the storm.
All right, how do I pull back?
Pull back the reins.
Looking up the clouds.
I care in the world.
Okay.
I was joking about my own saliva.
I can't go off the edge.
I tried.
Oh my god, a TV show.
All right, we got to see what this like Red Dead Redemption 2 stranger is.
Let's see.
What are we doing here?
Oh, I like choked on my spit and it like gave me a headache.
All right, stop.
Who are you?
I swear to god if he comes up with two brushes, I'm gonna be so pissed.
This is the whole game.
What you seek is for me to wallpaper your dining room a week next Thursday.
Uh, I don't think so.
Chicken chicer.
Oh, look, he's a little chicken chicer.
I don't have any silver.
No, no, stay, stay, stay, stay.
Oh, shit.
God fucking damn it.
I wanted to do that.
What if we didn't have the stretched out timeline?
Oh, and yes, that's me, the magician.
Excuse me.
I will be painting your walls and your ceilings if you want.
Just fucking tell me what do we want me to do.
I'm here.
We can be pretty fast when we have to be, eh, girl?
What's the world coming to?
Mad cuz bad.
So glad you could join us.
I'm needed at the front of the convoy.
Oh, thank god, thank god you could join us for the slow part of the tutorial.
Can I go with you?
Oh, you can't even speed up.
Stay here at the back, Injured.
What shall I do with the other eye?
Very funny.
Just do your job and keep up with the convoy.
I'm counting on you.
And make sure you don't fall asleep again, all right?
I'm not pulling you out of any more ditches.
Yeah.
Did you hear that, Seren?
Did you hear what he said to me?
Did you hear that?
After all the trouble I got into last time.
What even happened?
How long has it been?
He fucking fell asleep.
What?
He actually fell asleep.
Why did he fall asleep?
Red orbs.
Run, girl, run.
What are you doing?
Oh, catch up with everybody.
He fell asleep holding the brain.
Get to the convoy before it reaches the bridge.
Catlin might not realize we were gone.
I saw the death symbol and I was like,
I got to get some action in here.
Because I'm going to trust me again.
Damn it, Gabriel.
Where are you?
God damn it.
I'm trying to go off the edge.
I'm trying to get some fucking comedy on my screen.
All I had to do was stay awake.
Why didn't I stay awake?
Wait, I got to inject an absolute comedy home run right now.
Oh, malware bytes.
What are you talking about?
What?
Why is malware bytes popping up?
How long was he asleep?
This storm was miles away.
Oh, shit.
What happened down there?
I thought that was us for a second.
Just go flying.
What was that?
Why did he run out?
And what was that one's hand?
I can't hear you.
I didn't pick up the thing you said.
Sorry, but I'm going to assume you said to go to
Myanmar.
That's where I'm going.
Myanmar?
What did he say?
Myer Moore.
Like the Myer?
Manor Moore?
I hope he falls asleep again.
Oh, Microsoft Studios presents
a Lionhead Studios production.
What a seamless, seamless transition to the game.
Fable.
The Journey.
Starring you.
It's a fucking hog moment.
I'm ready.
Wake up asleep again, please.
And then maybe I have to go like this.
For an hour.
On that map.
Let's just try to get through Fairwood first.
Then we'll take it from there.
Oh, the GPS really took you a fucking shitty way.
Could have gone like straight.
There's like five roads that go that way.
Okay, here we go.
I can't believe that just happened.
I can't believe we're stuck out here alone.
Miles away from anywhere.
I just stayed awake.
We'd be across that bridge and on our way home by now.
Not stuck out here.
The map says there's a village up ahead.
There's a village.
Someone there will be able to help us.
Reach the village.
Triumph.
Go slower.
Give me those bits.
All right, we made it to Fairwood.
You have to be careful, Seren.
Need to be careful.
You've just earned your first upgrade token.
You can access your upgrades from the pause menu.
To pause the game now,
hold your left arm straight out to the side.
Are you fucking kidding me?
Upgrade me?
What the fuck?
Are you kidding me?
This is fucking awesome.
Calm down.
Whoa.
Upgrades.
Worst upgrade.
Redeem Fable Heroes Gold?
Oh yeah.
Didn't they do a thing where they made...
They did a thing.
They did do a thing, right?
Where there was this like slot machine game that they came up with?
Was it like a card game?
You made money and you could use it in Fable 2 or something?
I'm gonna hit that.
All right, pull it back.
When will we push the cart to one side?
God damn.
Like the Kinect is like the 3D glasses of the last generation.
It really was.
It was the stereographic 3D glasses of the last generation before this one.
I guess Shrub by fucking lightning?
Next game.
Not...
Hold on a second here.
Wait till I get a weapon.
Let me get a weapon first.
Sword.
Why does he not have a weapon?
Do we have choices to make like in Fable?
Like let the lady get eaten by the monster or like fix the ship?
Who's got...
Who?
Don't worry, I got this.
You new around here?
Yeah, me too.
I just rolled in.
You're not waving your arms enough.
More arm waving.
The only way we'll be able to escape.
He's shooting us.
Watch out, spikes.
This is a Disney ride.
Get away from this evil.
Do not let him touch the horse.
No, this is a Disney ride.
This is a Disney ride that you get off and you go.
That was not very good.
It's one of those boxes you go in
and you like go like this for like four straight minutes.
Oh, there he comes.
Look at those.
He's just screen.
And as you get off the ride and you kind of look around,
you're like, ah, that was like...
It took us like 40 minutes to get on that.
Can I just eat like the Mickey Mouse bar?
Okay, if like a YouTube video of the ride
is as good as the ride,
I don't know if it's worth waiting an hour for.
On rails.
This is not even on rails.
I'm not even really doing anything.
It is on, but like, completely on rails.
That's what on rails means.
Oh my god.
Whoa.
And right there you look over and your mom is like,
Keep going, girl.
You have to keep going.
It's like, oh, mom's having a good fucking time.
I'm having fun because mom's having fun.
Go look back, Seren.
Oh, flash.
Oh, they just took the picture.
And then every time I tell me if I'm crazy,
every single time I look at one of those photos of me,
tell me if you guys do this too.
I try so hard to not look weird.
I know exactly when the fucking flash is going to happen,
but I desperately don't want to look weird.
So I sit there and I'm like,
I'm like, don't want to look like I'm having too much fun
because it'd be like weird.
But every time I go in and look,
I always look like my face is made out of clay.
We have to find somewhere to stop.
Every time.
Just need to hold on a little bit longer, girl.
It doesn't matter if I'm like smiling
or if I'm like going like this or something.
My face always looks like this.
You have to hold on, girl.
I just look like shit every time.
I've tried to look good in those photos.
Like, I know it's coming there.
We're going over the bend.
I know this is where they take the flash.
I go like that.
I don't want to look weird, but it doesn't matter.
Even if I sit there and go like this,
I know the flash is coming.
Oh, let's go find it.
Okay, flash.
Let's go find it at the end.
Okay, where is it?
What the fuck, dude?
I tried to not look like a fucking weirdo.
Find a safe place to stop.
I'm giving this one some more time.
Whoa, girl.
I have to get those splinters out of you.
Oh, God.
Okay, here we go.
Whatever that was, it's gone now.
I know I'm scared.
The horse is now evil.
This is a loading screen to pull the arrow out.
Seren has been seriously injured.
Grab the splinter with your right hand
and slowly pull it out.
Be careful while pulling the splinter
or you may hurt Seren.
Then when you're done, grab the brush
and give her a nice scrub.
I'm sorry.
I got it.
Let me pet.
Let me, I'm too close, but so far away.
Let me pet the horse.
Oh, yes, that was a, let me, yes.
That was a loading screen to pull out a splinter
to go to a loading screen for a cutscene.
I'm just, I'm just like, I hate playing this game now.
I need to know what's in it.
I have to know.
Connect doesn't sound like such a good idea anymore, does it?
Poison from the devourer's attack is spreading quickly.
All right, after this stream is over,
I'm going to drop kick the connect
and see how far I can punt it on the football field.
I think I could get it, I think I could get it 30 yards.
I think I could, at least 20.
I need you to be strong now, girl.
We should leave now.
You have to hang on.
At least 15.
I think I could get it at least 10 to 15.
You give me a big enough shoe.
I think I could do it.
I'm having fun though.
We're almost there.
Follow this road.
Oh, no.
Then you must keep on moving.
The poison is spreading.
What happens if it finds us again?
The choice will have to be made.
What is on the back of this box?
To fight.
Fight? What chance would we have against that thing?
After what happened back there?
Beware the magic.
The fate of Albion is in your hands.
Your easygoing nomadic life is forever altered when you suddenly become successor to vast
and mysterious powers.
Set off to uncover the evil that threatens the land as you learn to control your growing magic
and bring to bear the power that will decide the future of Albion.
The power is in your hands.
Use your hands to quickly craft and wield magic in ways never dreamed possible.
Plunge into deep and immersive gameplay in your journey to save Albion.
Travel through the world of Albion in the best looking fable game of all time.
That's not real.
We've rid a horse for an hour.
We are still alive.
What it should read, what it should say is
use your magical hands to brush the horse back and forth four times.
Lean into the stunning beauty of removing a splinter.
I bet you we cast one spell in the next 45 minutes and I want to be certain of it.
Follow the stream, Gabriel.
He hates it.
Is she gonna make it?
You can see the future.
See is know everything, right?
See is know everything.
The injury that Devourer dealt me appears to have clouded my vision.
We have a chance.
That's such a funny, like, mysterious fantasy cop out.
Oh, I'm a seer.
Oh, yes.
If we don't get there in exactly 14 minutes, yes, the poison will get her.
Like, a seer can see.
Oh, yes, there's great evil coming in the next hour of gameplay.
Evil on the way.
I'm a seer.
I can see it.
I want to see her to be wrong.
I want to see her to be like, oh, the great and powerful evil is upon us.
It will be here in two days.
Oh, it's got big horns.
And it's like a squirrel.
And it's like, holy shit, that was a fucking squirrel.
You were completely wrong.
And then they disappeared.
They're gone the next day.
That character is gone because they know they fucked it all up and they left.
And you prepare, like, a week for this monster.
Namely guy did that.
I thought my fly was down.
Yeah, you ever see somebody seated getting up that fast and walking at you?
Oh, get out of there.
You got to get out of the fucking way.
You know what I mean?
Like, it's like, dog, I'm getting out of the way.
Get out of the way quick.
This guy got up really fast.
In the right hands can grant great power to heal or to destroy.
You hear that, Seren?
We'll have you better before you know it.
Karma, the fly was open.
I must warn you, Gabriel.
Power to save your horse will come at a price.
Then I'll pay it.
Anything to save Seren.
Very well.
This horse is dead.
Go, go, go, go, go, go.
The horse is going to die in 10 seconds.
He's dead.
Leave the animal here.
Don't be afraid.
No evil can approach the pool.
Uh, guy, my connect seat, it's not calibrated.
It doesn't think I'm sitting here.
I'm here.
I'm in the, I'm right here.
God damn it.
This thing, I have to recalibrate it.
I'm right here.
Oh my god damn it.
Here, here, here, here, here, here, here.
I shouldn't have done that.
I'm gonna puke.
That's too much spinning.
We heroes guard the pool and the artifact that lies beneath its surface.
Blaze, the hero of fire.
Stone, the hero of the fallen.
And soul, the hero of light.
Great champions who long ago...
What's her?
Approach the pool.
I thought that was me doing it.
No, that isn't me.
Gaze into the water.
Means to heal your horseless within the water.
I have to dunk my head.
Reach into the pool.
Oh my god.
It's so long since I've had water.
Understand.
What is this?
I don't carry much.
I like to play in water.
No, not my horse.
I like that horse.
No.
How do you sit like that?
Wait, what?
Where am I?
Where is this, what?
It wants you to sit like this?
This is place.
Welcome, Gabriel.
What are they talking about?
The pool has shown you a glimpse of the future.
But you have been brought here to learn a greater truth.
Your real trial is only just beginning.
Bolt is your primary damage spell.
To cast it, bring your right hand up to your shoulder,
then thrust it towards your target.
I look so like just lazy.
At least it's doing the thing I said.
Connection system must be calibrated to ensure accurate casting.
Cast a spell with a statue.
The entire new statue will appear.
Good shot.
Let me just fucking do the thing I want to do.
You know what's weird about this?
Casting.
You cast spells.
You can go like put your hand up and then go like this.
Don't you feel like you'd be giving somebody directions
at some point in the fucking game?
It's like, oh yeah, the grocery store.
You want to trot over down to Fairbottom.
And then just interrupted my fucking joke.
Whatever.
Okay, LOL, TLDR.
I killed a person that I was like over there
because I was giving directions and pointing around.
I'm clearly hitting this guy.
I just hit him.
Am I not hitting him?
No!
This hurts my fucking arm.
Wait, I can do two?
Next game, not hold on.
Don't tell me I'm doing it wrong.
I was doing it wrong.
Fuck, it's not even.
I can't hit that guy.
I can't hit him.
I'm too close.
I am not too close.
I must be dreaming.
Why was I too close?
No, I'm not.
I'm not too close.
Get me the fuck out of here.
Actually, what did you say?
Actually, right.
I can't take it anymore.
Connect Resident Sleeper.
The plot is so good.
The nominee for 2021 Meltdown?
No, no, no.
Push is your other main spell.
No, I'm good.
I'm good.
Bless.
Raise your left hand up to your shoulder, then thrust forward.
The spell will knock back your enemies, stunning them
so they cannot attack for a short while.
Stunning.
It can also be used to manipulate the environment.
Am I not getting a sword?
I don't know how many people on Christmas morning
sat here doing this.
They have a lot of brain power to do this.
I want to know the collective brain power
on Christmas morning, everybody doing this.
Dad, did you figure it out yet?
I can't say.
I'm trying to get the calibration to work, son.
This thing is wild.
It actually knows where my hand is.
Oh, I got it.
You want to try, son?
Am I really doing it?
No.
Are you sure?
I don't know what's happening.
No, not really.
Will, the power of magic.
It's a lot of fun.
Ran through the veins of the ancient hero.
Internal monologue going here.
This must be like a $200 fucking add-on.
You don't want to try it?
I'll be in my room playing my PlayStation.
Oh.
The push spell can be used to throw enemies and bits.
I'll call you in when I get it.
I think I get to a cool part.
You can hang out with me.
And once it is connected, sweep your hand
in the direction you want to throw.
Come on, man.
Come on.
I got to do this.
Me and my son are going to hang out together.
Got it.
I got it.
Wow.
Oh, I can move it around.
I can move this thing around if I move my arm around.
Oh, this sure is fun.
The push spell can be used to throw enemies
and bits of the environment through the air.
Cast push with your left hand normally.
And once it is connected, sweep your hand.
Oh, what's that?
What's that, honey?
We got Snickers ice cream bars too in the freezer?
Hey, Dad.
Oh, hey, son.
Come sit down.
Come sit right next to me.
Yeah, you see what I got here?
The push spell can be used to throw enemies
and bits of the environment through the air.
Cast push with your left hand normally.
Dad, get it.
I got it, son.
Ow.
Whoa, yeah, that was crazy what I just did.
I could make it fly with my hand.
You want to try?
No.
Can I have another Snickers ice cream bar?
Um, yes.
Yes, you can.
Really?
Honey, don't.
He's had three.
How many are in a box?
There are only four in a box.
It's bullshit.
All right, how about you can have one more, son.
Why don't you take a look at what your dear old dad can do here.
Okay, I think I'm done.
I'm done watching.
What?
No more ice cream to keep up here.
Connect.
Rack.
How do I get the fuck out of here?
Actually, I have a little sore.
I'll get it.
Don't worry, son.
Don't worry.
I'll get it.
Skeleton.
What's that?
Why is there a skeleton on the couch?
Honey?
How long has it been that I've been sitting here for?
How long has it been?
Is there a skeleton over there?
I'm done.
All right, wait.
Is it time to play Let's Cheer?
I'll be right back.
I'm gonna get some water.
That was absolutely fucking dreadful.
I'll be right back.
You know, I talked a lot of shit about, uh, about that game.
The more that I thought about it when I had a glass of water,
you know, the more that I think the Connect has a peripheral.
It's probably so limited that it'd be like trying to code Skyrim on an Atari.
You kind of just can't.
Like, what can we have people do?
Okay, they can wave their hands in the air,
and it can recognize their face,
and it has a microphone.
So if you make noises, it can tell.
Is there copyright music in this?
I feel like I'm gonna be in a lot of trouble.
We're about to find out.
I need to tune this.
Move this out of the way.
There's probably a shitload of copyrighted music in here.
Is this the correct gamer?
All right, here we go.
Okay, it's called Cheers.
The correct gamer?
It is.
It's called Let's Cheer.
Ready to save.
All right, this is going to be probably very embarrassing.
All right, so let's squad captain.
Here's where you pick your squad captain.
This is the person who stands up front,
and you'll need to watch and follow her exact moves when you're doing the routines.
Okay.
Once you choose your captain,
select the confirm button to pick your squad's color.
Megan, Brianna, or Hayley.
Okay.
I just broke the Kinect.
What did I say?
I've seen a lot of Megan.
All right, Megan's captain.
Confirm.
The other two are locked.
Squad colors.
Go ahead and pick any of the colors on the right.
Both your colors and squad captain can be changed at any time,
so feel free to mix it up later on.
Go.
Selecting Cheers will get us started.
Cheers?
Extras is where you can see all your current stats, awards,
and have some options to...
Okay.
Local, district, state, regionals, nationals.
There are five different levels of competition.
Local levels will have the easiest chance and dance routines,
where the national level will contain the hardest.
Right now, the national level of competition is closed to you,
but all of the levels are open.
You can pick any level you would like.
Okay.
Well, I'll go first.
There are several chants and two dance routines to pick from on your right.
Some items are locked and will be unlocked as you do well in the corresponding sections.
Shoot for two.
Celebration.
Now choose one that sounds good to you, and we can get started.
Okay.
Defense up.
Local football.
This is a great football chant to start with.
It has simple movements that should be easy for you to do.
Great.
Let's just find out how to do it first.
So loud.
Here comes DMCA.
Is it?
Are we going to get DMCA?
Six, seven, eight.
Defense.
Attack.
It's slow.
Push.
Defense.
Back.
Offense.
Defense.
Attack.
Do I have to sing it too?
Push.
This is so slow.
That offense back.
This needs to be faster.
It needs to be defense.
Attack.
Push that offense back.
Why is this so slow?
Back.
Let's crank up the speed a bit and turn on the score feedback.
Okay.
Six, seven, eight.
Defense.
Attack.
Push.
That offense back.
Defense.
Attack.
Push.
That offense back.
This is like, this dude is like daycare.
Defense.
Attack.
Push.
I have to sing it, right?
I can't do that shit.
I will try to get that.
I'm going to wreck my pants.
I'm going to do that and you're going to hear...
All right.
Let's get fired up.
I'm ready.
Let's go.
I'm just a fan in the audience doing their moves.
Why is he on a giant birthday cake?
Oh my God.
That hurt.
This game's...
They're not that long.
This is so short.
Okay.
How about celebration?
I guess I can have the month break.
Nah, I'll be fine.
Okay.
Um, let's train.
I'm going to train and I'm going to perform.
DMCA.
What?
Wait, is this a real song?
Why is everything moving?
Oh shit.
She's casting fireball.
This is embarrassing.
This is embarrassing to me.
Clock arms.
Check it.
Delete this stream.
Why don't you delete that comment?
I'm about to rip this one out too.
This keeps...
I'm going to go for a competition.
We're going right to regionals.
Okay.
Perform on card.
This is for regionals.
I can't do Mickey.
I'm going to get arrested.
If I do Mickey, I'm going to get arrested
because I got DMCA.
I'm just the guy in the front row on drugs.
The concert.
That's not that long.
It needs to be much longer than that.
It's like, oh, that guy is...
Oh, wait a minute.
I was trying to get...
I was trying to get in the...
Somebody like snatched me.
Somebody snatched me.
I was in the middle
and like before they took the photo,
somebody like fucking snatched me
and pulled me.
Look at that mouth.
I can't even look at it.
Yeah, keep that cover.
For sure.
Enough is enough.
What?
I'm going to get arrested.
How about be aggressive?
Oh.
That's like a disconnected job.
It's like a cryptid.
What the fuck is a cryptid?
All right.
I'm ready.
Be aggressive.
B-E-A-G-R-E-S-I-V-E.
Aggressive.
B-E-A-G-G-R-E-S-I-V-E.
I'm so...
I'm the fucking annoying person at the concert.
I can't get over it.
B-E-E-A-G-G-R-E-E-S-S-I-V-E.
Go get him.
Come on.
I'm ready.
There was no photo?
Oh, there was no photo.
Make the sus face.
No.
Do Mickey.
Oh my God.
I want to do this.
Disturbia is so bad.
Cheers here.
Start to separate the good groups from the bad ones.
I want to do Disturbia.
So fucking bad.
But I'm gonna get in trouble if I do.
Let's share and let's show them what we got.
It's a cover?
That don't matter.
You want the song?
Just sing over it.
Okay, fine.
Here we go.
Wait.
Hold on.
All right.
I'll do it.
Yeah, I'm ready.
Okay.
So it's like...
I got it.
This is the lyrics.
This is how they do it when they choreograph, by the way.
The person...
I don't even care.
I don't even give a shit.
I don't care.
You have to hear that.
When you...
When choreographers are doing a dance routine,
to the beat, they go like...
And that's when we get those two arms up
and you swing with the back shake.
Step, step.
I got a feeling.
What about district?
You're losing your mind?
District level cheers are a step above your local.
They contain slightly harder movements and routines.
I like to move it, move it.
I like to move it.
Do Mickey.
Why are we not allowed to have any fun anymore?
I would love to do I like to move it, move it.
But somewhere there's somebody with a giant fucking cigar
that they haven't asched yet.
And it's just like three quarters of ash.
And they're just like...
Then they take the cigars, then they...
They ash it into their own fucking mouth.
Why can't we have any fun?
This chat has a few harder moves in it,
but well worth the results it will bring you
when your fans are on their feet.
Like what?
Because you're going to hear,
I like to move it, move it on a live stream
in fucking Let's Cheer the video game.
No, no, no, no, no, they're not going to go out
and they're not going to buy that CD from fucking 2008.
Get out of here.
When was the last time any of you fucking guys bought a CD?
How many of you guys just use Spotify and like iTunes and shit?
Does it really matter if like I hear a song
from like 15, 20 years ago on a Brad, Brad broadcast?
Honestly, I wouldn't be surprised if somebody DMC'd this.
Like this is a song that, you know, this is on...
I have the cheer music rights.
Yeah, I did the Dribble Dribble Hoop Hoop song.
Sounds like a Wiggles song.
I want to get another picture.
I'm going back to Nationals.
We're doing one more.
One more and I'm going to move on.
Boo Star Andy.
Go to Regionals.
I want...
Okay, block out.
I'm going to try to get five stars
because I want to get a photo.
Want to chant to bring that basketball crowd into a frenzy?
Learn block out and watch them rock out.
We got four stars.
Why can't I get...
Why did I only get one photo?
Young and old alike will be dancing in the stands
as you perform this instant classic.
Hey, the words.
Okay, I'm ready.
Ready?
Okay, girls, are you ready?
Here we go.
It's time for us just to do Mickey at our competition.
No, no, no.
I'll just sing it, girls.
Don't worry.
Hey, without music, this looks fucking really weird.
I look like a fucking creep.
I can't do this.
Who can't fuck it?
I don't give a shit.
I do, I do, I really do.
I do, I do, I do, I do, I do, I do, I do, I do, I do, I do.
I do, oh, I do.
Too late.
Oh, no.
I'm sorry, I'll never do it again.
I didn't get one.
I'm done with the cheer game.
It wasn't very Mickey of you.
You're sweating.
Yeah, well, I'm getting up and moving.
What's next?
Hmm.
Oh, I know.
Take a shower?
Hold on, not yet.
Star Wars Connect?
I can't even play that one either.
Do an armpit check?
No, thank you.
This one is called UFC Trainer.
Oh, come on.
Update in progress.
I have a tantrum.
In the sea of comments, I saw somebody say, you're an adult.
A lot of text.
I can't be an adult and use the Kinect.
That's what they made this for.
This was made for six-year-olds and like 40-plus-year-olds.
I fit into the category of people that want to have this.
What are you talking about?
Everyone says, oh, grandma, grandma.
Kinect is the grandma accessory.
Don't I hit the threshold of being old enough to play this?
Yeah, oh, sad.
Good company.
They work.
40-year-old streamer?
Not yet.
I got some years in me here.
All right, UFC Trainer.
This is like a...
All right, this is like part of my body.
That's in a really weird spot, too.
I don't like where that is.
I don't like where this is.
Okay, whatever.
All right, punch to play.
It's going to mess stuff up.
That's kind of cool.
That was cool.
Why is my head so hot?
Why is it a thermal camera and I have like a hot brain?
Am I going to explode?
What was that?
I have like a really like a heat.
My head is so hot.
Oh, you know when you have to hold it for more than a few seconds.
That's...
Enter your age, height, and weight, please.
Come on, hurry up.
All right, that's...
Oh.
Would you like to use weights during your workout?
Should I lie and just say I'm doing it?
Oh.
The road to the octagon starts here.
I'm not doing any of these.
No, no, no, no, no, no.
What do you mean test?
Fitness test?
Take your pulse over 15 seconds.
What?
No one...
I'm doing this in jeans.
...in maintaining a UFC body would be easy.
It takes a lot of hard work.
It also takes...
A lot of hard work.
...preparing properly will not only result.
It'll reduce your chance of injury.
So what kind of preparation am I talking about?
What happened to my fucking fitness DVD?
I don't know.
What was it?
I need to know.
Oh, so this is what I'm talking about.
Oh, we're over here now.
Oh, you burnt the CD.
You burnt the CD.
You burnt the DVD, but you took it out before it was done burning.
So I only got the first like fucking 12 seconds.
...in front of the Kinect with your body facing sideways toward the sensor.
Make sure your body appears green within the octagon.
You just...
Oh, I have to lie.
You're not going to be able to even see me.
How do I do this?
I got to move the mic.
The mic's got to move.
Why am I so hot?
Oh my god.
What's going on?
Okay.
Now for the sit-up test.
Sit-up test.
What do I need to do?
...on your back, knees bent, and arms crossed in front of your chest.
Lift your upper body up so that your elbows almost touch your knees.
You'll have 60 seconds to see how many you can do.
Okay.
What's the world record?
Ready?
Go.
60 seconds.
Nice.
Yeah.
Stop if you're tired.
I'm getting thrown out of the gym.
30 seconds left.
Looking good.
Stop if you're tired.
I got it.
20 seconds left.
I got to get to 20.
Okay, stop.
Whoo.
Lower your body into a plank position with your head facing the connect sensor.
Make sure your body appears green within the octagon.
Okay.
Push-up test.
I'm going to try to get 100.
...with hands slightly wider than shoulder width apart.
I hope I can flat my weight.
...attractive.
Head looking down and slightly ahead of you.
Slowly lower your chest to the ground, keeping your body rigid.
Do you guys even see me?
...push back to plank.
You've got one minute to try to do as many as you can.
All right, you ready?
Ready?
Go.
60 seconds.
Bring it.
Stop if you're tired.
Keep it going.
I just want to...
Awesome.
30 seconds left.
I got to hit the spot where it thinks I'm moving up and down.
Again.
I can't do any more.
Okay.
22.
Stand in front of the Kinect with your body facing toward the sensor.
Make sure your body appears green within the octagon.
For these?
Okay, last test.
We need your active heart rate.
We're going to do some jumping jacks to get your heart rate up.
Let your arms hang at your side with your feet shoulder width apart.
Oh no, it's opposite.
Jump, bringing your arms up and spreading your legs.
We're going to do this for one minute to get your heart pumping.
Once we are done with the jumping jacks, I want you to check your pulse again.
I'll tell you when.
I don't know how to do that.
Ready?
Go.
60 seconds.
Good.
That's a four.
Stop if you're tired.
Then do it.
30 seconds left.
Hey.
Hey, can I...
Oh, okay.
All right, all right, all right.
If you're tired.
10 seconds left.
70.
Woo.
Now I'm going to count down from 15.
I want you to count how many times you feel a beat.
Okay, okay, okay, okay.
All right, I'm ready.
Three.
Two.
One.
Go.
One, two, three, four, five, six, seven, eight.
Well, 30, 40, 50, 60.
Ready to roll?
Three, four, five, six, seven, eight.
Nine, 15, one, two, three, four, five, six, seven, eight.
15.
Stop.
Please input the amount of beats you count.
Just like...
My heart would fucking fly away.
All right, what am I doing?
Five.
Hey, that didn't even win me.
Hey, bro, uh, go to the hospital.
That's... wait, that's only five?
Here's a summary of your personal information.
Whatever.
Not one of my personal information.
All right.
Activity.
No.
All right, hit the mitts.
I can't with your speed bag.
That's going to be so much fun.
Select a fighter.
Dan Hardy.
Select a routine.
Uh, we're going to go with...
I can do better than that.
Really?
All right, we're going to do easy routine five.
Oh, wait, wait, I got to do that too.
Stand in front of the Kinect with your body facing toward the sensor.
Make sure your body appears green within the octagon.
What's up?
I'm Dan Hardy.
Let's work focus bits.
All right, we're going to do some jabs and crosses.
Mixing it up with hooks.
All right.
A few kicks and some knees.
And some knees.
To keep you on your toes.
I'm going to give you something to dodge every now and then.
All right.
Are you ready to train like a champ?
Oh.
Jab.
Duck.
Take a bit more now.
No.
Keep moving.
Kick.
Jab.
You need to pick it up a bit.
Duck.
Kick.
Jab.
That's how we do it.
Cross.
Hook.
I got an idea.
Get it back and let's get to it.
We're going to mix it up now.
Jab.
Duck.
Good job.
Way to go.
Jab.
Duck.
Cross.
Hook.
Duck.
Yes.
That's how it's done.
Okay.
Let's move on.
Jab.
Duck.
I don't want to duck.
Dig deeper now.
Jab.
Hook.
Knee.
Jab.
Cross.
Kick.
You missed a few there.
Jab.
Hook.
All right.
I'm getting tired.
I'm tired.
Jab.
I need a break.
Cross.
Kick.
You're not listening.
Hook.
I need a fucking break, man.
Knee.
Connect.
I need a break.
You've got to keep moving.
Jab.
How am I going to take a break?
Duck.
Looking good.
Okay.
We're going to change it up.
Jab.
Duck.
I think you can do better.
Jab.
Let him hit me.
I get more rage.
Duck.
Knee.
You really got it.
All right.
I don't know what happened.
I guess I need to defragment my hard drive.
What?
I got an F.
I only burned six calories?
How is that even possible?
What?
I burned like a hundred.
You've got to be shitting me.
Free striking.
Let's go.
Heavy bag.
Tiger stripes.
Let's go.
Advanced.
I'm advanced.
If I punched somebody.
Oh boy.
Let's go.
Stand in front of the connect with your body facing toward the sensor.
Make sure your body appears green within the octagon.
I'm green.
Build power and endurance at your own pace and free striking mode.
Okay.
Work on your own combos and at your own pace.
The more strikes you get in the better.
Ready?
Go.
Quick.
Pulverize the target.
Rise the target.
Come on.
Keep that striking pace up.
Strike faster.
Don't let me down.
Keep attacking.
All right.
I'm done.
Keep that striking pace up.
Strike faster.
All right.
I think I killed them.
I think they're dead.
Don't let me keep attacking.
You picked five minutes.
Keep that striking pace up.
Strike faster.
It's like toilet paper roll.
He's got oh no he's got a fuel.
This thing's weight like a pound.
Don't let me down.
Keep attacking.
Keep that striking pace up.
Strike faster.
Don't let me down.
Keep attacking.
Keep that striking pace up.
Strike faster.
Don't let me down.
Die.
Your hits are nice and quick.
Pulverize the target.
Keep that striking pace up.
It's been how long I have to do this for?
Five full minutes?
I think I've been here for an hour.
I feel like I've been here for a full hour doing this.
I'm getting to 30,000.
Keep attacking.
Keep that striking pace up.
Strike faster.
Bring that target up.
Don't let me down.
Keep attacking.
Give it a kiss.
Keep that striking pace up.
It's like a ranged attack.
Like strike faster.
Ow.
It's a fucking waste of time.
All right.
How many calories did that burn?
What?
16 calories?
That was five minutes of just fucking spinning around like a psycho.
Five full minutes of just waving my arms around and jumping around at 16 calories?
What?
No way.
I feel like I burned more calories playing a horror game.
I swear to God.
I bet you I burned 40 calories an hour playing like Resident Evil.
All right.
I'm going to speed back.
I'm getting fucking tired.
I'm not doing that for five goddamn minutes.
20 beats per minute.
Lied about height.
Lied about beats per minute.
No wonder it's fucked up.
I didn't lie about height.
I'm going to be good at this.
Come on.
I want to go.
I want to do it with my feet, but like I can't put my feet on camera.
I want to do it.
I'm going to put my light up, my feet up and do it.
But I'll you want the fuck to clip that.
Five calories?
Late?
When?
All right.
I think it's time to move on.
Hold on.
I want to do tire flip.
Wait, there's more.
What else is in this?
Oh.
All right.
Tire flip.
Tire flip and then I'm moving on to...
Hole in the wall.
Oh, we're going to play hole in the wall after this one.
One minute.
Pog, pog, pog.
Is that all?
I'm seeing a lot of pogs.
Jerma's exhausted.
Yeah.
I probably shouldn't have picked the like fucking exercise game.
All the exercise games that are trying to make you like get tired.
I don't want to do this.
I don't understand this.
Dude, I'm just going to eat Cheerios and like reduce some calories and walk.
I'm not doing this.
Like just eat fucking like Honey Nut Cheerios or something and walk and jog sometimes.
I don't want to do this.
Hole in the wall time.
Two thousand and twelve Jerma long dead.
Two thousand and twelve Jerma didn't like flip monster truck tires.
Broken?
Whatever.
No, why?
I don't want to do that.
That's like Marvel character shit.
Like you want to be a Marvel character?
You can flip like monster truck tires.
You're a Marvel character.
You're like Captain America at that point.
I don't want to be Captain America.
I want to be guy on sidewalk walking by scene that like looks kind of good.
Two thousand and twelve Jerma would beat Captain America's ass.
No, two thousand and twelve Jerma would take the shield to the head and become decapitated
because I couldn't duck in time because I don't have superpowers.
I was just like a like a kind of stacked thick boy.
My head would come off.
I don't have powers.
All right, let's go.
Why does this font look so bad?
Connect tuner?
What's going on there?
Why is that in a weird font with a weird background?
All right, let's do it.
Hole in the wall.
I'm going to do the show.
It's a game show.
Let's go.
Unplayer.
Players who want to be in this team, please come over.
Everyone else, please move away.
What else?
Get away.
You step into the circle to join blue team.
All right, let's go.
Everyday life.
European workplaces.
Disco activities.
Art.
USA.
Oh, I can only do one.
All right, we're going to do everyday life.
Well, how does this game even work?
Why do you have to...
Welcome the blue team.
Oh, I have to get through the foam thing, the hole.
It's all simple.
Make the shape, fit the hole, and keep the pose to fill the gauge around the wall.
The faster you are, the bigger your score.
If you don't fill the gauge, you get a strike.
After three strikes, prepare to get wet.
Here we go.
Round one.
Where are we going?
Where we got?
I can make my fucking body any form.
Got it.
Come on, come on, come on, come on.
What is this guy doing?
Get, get, get, get, get.
All right, round one.
Round two?
Wait, there are pictures?
Oh, there's junk over here.
Look at all this trash.
That's supposed to be a dog bed.
There's a bunch of...
That's my VR headset.
And this thing's over here.
This is a spoiler.
A spoiler.
This fucking thing.
Come on.
How you doing, man?
How are things?
Well, you know, things are good.
Cool, cool, cool.
You've been sitting over on the dog bed?
Yeah.
Well, you know, the dog bed is comfy.
I thought that you'd be...
I was going to wait to put you on stream for a little while.
You were?
Yeah, I just figured it wasn't your time yet.
Why would you do that?
I'm ready to be on camera.
Okay.
What's your name, anyways?
Orange.
Oh, easy.
Really easy to remember and easy to come up with on the spot
without having any time.
Cool.
Hi, Orange.
So, would you like to go back into dog bed?
Of course I would.
It's very comfy.
Ow, ow.
I'll do a little bit of cleaning, okay?
Why am I using my mouse?
What else we got?
I'm here.
I think I'm here.
How do I get this off the screen?
What else we got?
This is so stupid.
Okay, you know what this looks like.
What's that...
What's that kid that dances?
The kid that goes like...
What is it?
He's like...
That's what the first thing I thought of.
Dwayne.
That's right, yep.
It's like...
That's the first thing I thought of.
It looks like somebody's like fucking threatening me to like...
Yeah, you're a dance.
Doesn't it look like somebody's gonna fucking kill me off camera?
Dwayne.
All right, let's go.
Let's do another one.
This is fun.
I like this one.
All right, how do we keep going?
No, that was close.
Oh, round two.
Round two.
Which one am I?
Shit, shit, shit.
Okay, got it.
Okay.
That was easy.
Jesus.
I got it.
Cleared it.
Photos time.
Dump truck.
Oh my god.
It looks like I'm wearing a rubber mask of somebody else's face.
That's a fucking rubber mask.
Okay, this is just like a shitty...
This is one of my model photos that I uploaded.
It's like Instagram to show you like how a bunch of a model I could be.
Underneath this is like there's two likes.
Yeah, it's my gallery, you know, my model gallery.
That one's not even that bad.
This one looks kind of bad.
I don't like that one.
It's scary.
It's a scary image.
Why does it always look like somebody took like ice cold hands and like put them on my back?
All right, let's go again.
Round five.
Round three.
Theresa May.
That's fucking perfect.
Oh my god.
I think I see when it takes the photo.
Did I get it?
Hey, I had to go all the way over to the dog bed.
Why was that so far away?
Very, very weird.
I look jacked.
I look huge in this picture.
What's going on with my face?
Just the reddit shelf, just right here.
It's the only thing in the entire fucking room.
It just looks so, it just looks so odd.
There's like shit all over the floor.
Somebody came in the room, like the T-Rex walked in.
It didn't matter what I was doing.
I had to be very still or I was dead.
Or you don't have a place to put your cardboard cutout of German 985.
I guess it's just gonna go over here and lean against the wall while I clean the fucking room.
Like this is, this is like you shoved the cardboard cutout of me and all your other junk
so you can vacuum over here.
How is it?
That was the last one.
Here comes the final.
See if I can get it.
The proudest possession.
New rule.
Which of the outline shapes are good and fit them to pass the walls as usual.
What are you talking about?
Don't get confused.
Hole, the holes aren't visible.
Oh Jesus.
Which one is it?
It's not this one.
I'm gonna fall over.
I can't, what?
Otto is gonna be in one of these pictures I think.
Otto came in.
Let's see if we can see Otto.
He like ran over here.
Oh my god.
Another cardboard cutout.
Just like a fucking like sprite in my hand in like the 7-Eleven.
I'm trying to find Otto.
Oh if you had friends over and these were saved and like this is dad just still playing
with the Kinect.
Oh that's where I didn't, I didn't know where it was.
I can get it.
I'll try it again.
Let's go.
I can do it.
Oh the show's over.
What?
Can I restart that one?
Oh god.
What the fuck?
Come on.
Next game.
Hold on.
Not yet.
I wanna pick another one.
I can't believe I failed it.
I'm gonna blow through this.
See if I can catch the camera.
When does it flash?
Did I get it?
He's a reason.
Brick stare.
I'm trying to see, I guess what I'm gonna do.
Ready?
No it's, when does it take the photo?
At some point.
I gotta, I gotta do a count.
Maybe three seconds after?
All right.
Go, go, go, go, go, go, go.
I want to unlock the next one.
I want to unlock the next challenge at least.
I'm gonna try as hard as I can.
Turns gray?
All right, it looks like right there, right?
I don't think that's correct though.
I think it is.
Oh!
Oh shit.
I'm not gonna get it.
Whatever.
I can look to see if we can get it.
Is it that flash?
I feel like, is it?
Let's find out.
Is my tongue sticking out?
No, it's not.
So it happens before the flash.
It happens at some point before the flash.
So here's what I'm gonna do.
Check this out.
See if I can get the photo
and then do the actual thing.
Here we go.
Ready?
Doesn't want me to do it.
See if I got it.
All right, it was, it's very easy.
Come on, dude, dude.
All right.
See if I got it.
This dude's a gamer.
Thank you.
Appreciate that.
Oh, it must start to take it
when the time, when the do, do, do, do, do, do
thing starts.
All right, this is it.
This is for everything.
Let's go.
And now comes the final round
of the everyday show.
We've added an additional rule
to make it harder.
Oh.
Have you ever felt lost in?
I'm on the shoes here.
It's time to face the final.
Well done.
He's strangled.
Congratulations.
Nice.
Ah.
Well done.
Try again.
You are still the winning team.
Gray?
What do you mean the gray?
The gray shadow.
I, I can't see that far away from here.
I want to, there's a 27 inch monitor
and I'm like 12 feet away.
It's the gray silhouette.
That's what it is the whole time.
Are you fucking kidding me?
I want to see this one.
I'm like, okay, diaper?
I'm, I'm like, well,
you're supposed to play this
in like a fucking, in the living room.
This is like a 26 inch monitor
and I'm like fucking 15 feet away.
Shit.
Come on.
We're survival.
At least one gamer is not signed in.
Don't care.
A little vibe check.
Let's see.
In quick survival mode,
there's an unlimited number of walls.
It's time to face the horde.
Unlimited number of walls?
Oh, I've seen this already.
Congratulations.
God damn it.
Oh, it's gone.
It's gone.
More?
Oh, I got it.
How many of these do in a row?
I've seen this already.
Congratulations.
How many times do I have to take a shower?
It was not even close.
It's lagging.
Did it get harder?
Am I stuck here forever
doing like the business man at the sidewalk?
How is he holding the briefcase?
All right.
Ten more of these
and if I don't see a new one, I'm stopping.
All right.
I'm done.
I think I only have unlocked one set.
I'm trapped here.
I'm done.
Get done.
Play until it crashes.
I lost.
I'm gonna wake up.
We got no pictures either.
All right.
Time to bring out.
Time to bring out the big guns.
Time to play You're in the Movies.
I'm gonna do like a few movies.
Where'd it go?
Time for You're in the Movies.
Actually, let me get some water.
We'll take one last break.
Oh, sorry.
I'm like bumping you.
I'm gonna be right back.
Get some water and we'll do You're in the Movies.
Ladies and gentlemen,
I might have to tell you a disappointment
Andy might be coming up here.
I'd have to postpone this.
You're in the Movies.
I completely forgot.
I had a green screen behind me last time.
Remember?
I'm not sure we're gonna get a good picture here.
I might need a green screen and some lights.
Yeah, that's...
That's...
We'll see.
We'll see if it looks all right.
Don't need that.
Oh, just...
We might.
I might not even show up.
So let's find out.
Normal people don't have green screens, though.
I mean, do...
I mean...
Do you want it to look good or do you want it to just exist?
You know what I'm saying?
It might...
It might be very bad.
We'll find out.
Normal people don't have Kinects either.
We just want it to exist.
All right.
Let's see what happens.
I don't know.
That sequel is never as good as the original.
I don't know if I like that.
I don't know if I want to do that.
How do I do this?
Hey.
No.
I fucking hate headphones so much.
When can I get the chip implanted in here so I can just go...
And there's audio.
I hate this shit.
I feel like I'm going on a goddamn scuba dive expedition when I put earphones in.
Like...
I fucking hate headphones so much.
It's not a Kinect game.
Come on.
Where is it?
Where's my Xbox vision camera?
Oh, no.
No!
Where's my Xbox vision camera?
I know myself so well.
Do you know how well I know myself?
Would you like to know how well I know myself?
Let me go ahead and show you.
Xbox live vision camera.
I streamed this like two fucking years ago.
Like a year and a half ago at least, right?
I had the Xbox live vision camera.
Now, you need that peripheral.
It's an old shit peripheral.
And I somehow, in my drunken ADHD, I was like, you know what I have to fucking do?
You know what I have to fucking do?
I have to make sure that I buy two of these because I'm going to lose one.
I've got a sealed-in-the-box Xbox live vision camera.
Because I was like, you know what?
Might as well just get two because I'm a fucking idiot.
Sell it?
What?
I've had this in a box in my closet for two years.
Can I even do this right now?
All right.
But should I try to find the first?
Wait, should I try to open this first or actually sell it?
Fuck.
It's an easy $12.
No, no, no.
This is not $12, dude.
Oh my god.
I just punched you.
I'm so sorry.
They're not expensive?
Yes, they are.
You know how much an Xbox live vision camera sealed is?
Xbox live vision camera.
This shit is expensive.
It is.
I think this stuff, I think this is like $150.
Dude, it's $50 and it's only, it's only $8.
It's in the, I'm going to get a pair of scissors.
I'm going to get hurt trying to open this.
It's the old clamshell, like, get stabbed packaging.
Ow.
Hold on.
Let me get a pair of, ow, ow, ouch, ow, ow.
Stop, what?
Ow.
Okay, let me show you this.
This is like fucking glass.
Like what, what were they thinking?
What were they actually thinking?
This is like, this is fucking glass.
Look at this, it's glass.
This is like, you're going to get like, I can't.
I thought this was a fucking Kinect game.
Give me a minute.
Dude, I'm telling you right now.
How did this last for this long?
You know what I mean?
How the fuck did this last this long for this shit to be like this?
Like, if I'm a congress member or something,
the first time I open a package like this,
the next day I'm being like, this shit's fucking illegal now.
This clamshell package, this is fucking insane.
Like, what the fuck were they thinking?
They're out of their minds.
And I've got tools here.
I've got like a fucking tool here.
I would have, I would have put a bill on the table.
That was, you put something in clamshell packaging.
The company has fined 500 fucking quadrillion dollars.
Ain't ever going to do it again.
Ah, that could have hurt me.
All right, I'm in.
Merry Christmas!
Why's there a headset?
Why's there a headset in here?
Put it on.
Let's start.
I have to plug in the camera for this.
Wait, oh no, this ain't going to fucking work.
Because I need to like, this, look at this little stand.
This ain't going to fit anywhere.
This is, this ain't going to happen.
I don't, I, wait, can I put, I think I can put it on top of the Kinect.
Let me see if I can get it on top of the Kinect.
It's the last time I actually taped it to the top of my monitor.
See if I can get it to stand on the Kinect.
We're good.
We're good, it's on.
Plug it in.
All right, hold on, the VRB.
It's peering on top of there.
Work!
Looks like it's on.
Holy shit, this looks horrible.
It's like, yeah, it's like 10p.
Wipe it off?
Is it dead pixels on this thing?
They're dead pixels.
All right, hold on.
Movie theater.
Make a movie.
Oh no!
Fuck, did the save?
No, no, no, no, no, wait, wait, wait.
I'm on David.
No, it's not in focus.
There's a dead pixel.
There's like five dead pixels.
Yes!
Need a green screen!
Are you sure you want it to exist?
You positive?
You can't even see me.
No, no, it's got to be better than that.
It's got to be better.
I'm candidate.
We're going to do this again another day.
Take your shirt off.
That actually probably would help.
What did?
Oh, what am I doing?
What the fuck am I doing?
Your audio?
It's like eating my whole face.
No, this ain't going to work.
It ain't going to work.
I'm going to set this up so we can do it for real.
It does work.
Holy shit, there's a line.
Put a blanket up.
I put a blanket up?
It's going to take like fucking 30 minutes
for me to get a blanket and put it up.
I don't have a blanket that can go up there.
Press RB.
I've been going to different color styles.
I'm going to call it here.
I want to get this ready.
That just made me depressed.
I'm looking.
I thought this was a Kinect game.
Well, wait.
Hold on.
Hold on a minute.
Oh, this one sucks.
You see yourself clearly in the background.
No.
Better shirt on?
Hold on.
Oh, son.
You forgot to turn your screen off.
You got to turn off this fucking Xbox again.
It's the shelf.
It's not going to be possible to have a screen.
All right.
Move the shelf.
Camera.
I got very much room.
Remove the shelf.
I can't just move a shelf.
There's a shitload of stuff on here.
I'll knock it over.
All right.
I'm going to res...
That's it.
I'll see you guys later.
We tried.
But very important.
God damn it.
It's close, but it's not going to work.
All right.
I'll see you guys later.
I'm done.
That was fun.
It's fun.
I fucking drained all my batteries doing the UFC fight thing.
I'll be live tomorrow.
We'll do it tomorrow.
Let me try to get it actually set up so we can do it tomorrow.
Family Guy music.
All right.
So I'm going to try to get this set up for tomorrow.
If I don't like the way it looks, just keep an eye on the sus.
Because if I can't get this the way that I want it,
then we'll do it again later with a proper screen.
If not, then I'll be back in a couple of days.
Okay.
I'm going to try.
Keep an eye on the sus.
It's to be determined.
I'm going to...
Tomorrow I'm going to get up early.
Maybe I can get this to work.
That was a lot of fun though.
It sucks.
What a fucking waste of...
What a waste of waxling.
No.
Should I be that harsh?
I don't know if I should be that harsh.
And I fucking sucked laughing my ass off.
Yeah.
All right.
If it's not this tomorrow, then I will see you on.
And I'll be very...
You'll just keep an eye on the sus.
If there's no stream tomorrow, then we will be live on the...
All right.
The sixth...
I got to plan this out here because it's...
The next stream is actually to be determined because the sixth is a big stream.
And I got to make sure that's ready to go.
So let's...
There'll be another stream in the next few days.
If you don't know, there's going to be a major stream on the sixth.
You'll see what it is.
Wonders of Archaeology.
I just need to figure out...
Because there's production shit that's going to be happening over the next four or five days.
And I kind of need to know exactly what's going on.
So you'll see that.
I will just keep an eye on the sus over the next day or two.
I don't really know exactly when the next stream will be,
but it will be within the next few days.
To be determined.
I will see you guys to be determined.
Have a great rest of your night.
I got to turn off this Family Guy music.
We'll see you guys within the next few days.
I'll see you soon.
I just want to make sure I get this right.
That same monkey eating the bananas.
Thanks, as always, for watching, everybody.
I'm going to go take a shower or a bath or either or.
And I think the Kinect is going to get punted as far as I can get it.
We're stream heart.
I don't believe that's accurate.
I don't think that's accurate.
I don't.
I had a lot of fun on this stream.
Usually I can tell.
And that guy.
No, you can't.
You're not going to get banned if having an opinion on whether a stream was good or not.
I mean, I'll call you a fucking dick.
You're not going to get banned.
All right.
Let us hold on a second here.
You're right.
Oh, yeah, yeah, yeah, yes, yes, yes.
Styr is RPing right now.
Oh, my God.
Are you serious?
All right.
I'm going to let's write Styr.
I'm very curious because I let's see how how GTA RP is.
All right.
Styr is RPing right now.
OK, so like he's not going to sing you a raid song.
He's like in the middle of RPing.
So let him RP if he's in the middle of like a routine or something.
I just it's all good.
You see, let's see how he does be nice.
I will see you guys in the next few days.
Take care of yourselves.
See you soon and good night.