Hey, what is going on, everybody? Jerma here with chapter 3 of Nightmare House 2.
Before we get started, crack open a fresh Dr. Pepper. Cherry Dr. Pepper. I actually haven't had this.
So let's see how good this is. Ah, smooth cherry Dr. Pepper. It's been too long, doctor.
Alright, so let's just go here. There's my bed. Pretty disheveled. Looks like a rotten corpse was lying on that.
Chair, get out of my face. Nothing in... No, let's just go. Time to go. Hello!
I remember that guy. I remember that guy from the end of the last chapter. God!
Don't want to have to deal with that guy.
Okay, so if I go into the maintenance room, I'm going to light on fire. Sweet!
Anything in here? Where's my flashlight? My flashlight wasn't even turned on.
Um, I don't think there's anything in here. I'm taking the gun out, though, because that thing...
Oh, I hate this chapter already, and I haven't even started playing.
Oh, can I open this door? No, but... Can I break this?
So what is this for? Well, how come I can... Oh, I can blow a hole in the wall, can't I?
Oh, what? No, I can't. Oh, yeah, I can. Cool.
So what the hell was in here? Oh, storage. Okay. I didn't mean to shoot the gun.
Ooh, a revolver. No, I didn't die. That's not that long.
Yeah, the little girl. She's a freak. Yeah, easier said than done.
By the way, where is this guy? How come he's not, like, chased by monsters?
Okay. Will do. So that guy's just not being attacked or anything. He's just kind of...
I thought the fire was a monster.
Ah! What the hell's going on? Oh, it was the fire again!
Man, I'm losing my mind here, guys.
Oh, that's nothing. Yeah. Nice, nice. Why? Why? Why? Why is it saying that?
Why does it keep saying that? Don't look behind you. Don't look behind you.
Dude, there's no vent here. Unless I can, like, blow this up.
Oh, okay, here it is. I would call this the first washing machine and not the third washing machine.
Another vent. Fantastic. Where's my gun? Ah! Is this thing you wear in a bikini?
Oh, no, that's just, like, charred flesh.
I'm just going to pre... Oh, I lost all my bullets in my revolver. Good job, Jerma.
That wasn't totally stupid. What? Hi. Oh, no! I hate these vents so much. Come on!
All right, home free. Home free. Ooh. Okay, we're good.
God, those things are so nerve-wracking. Charge the flashlight.
Can I go in? Okay. Somebody's in the bathroom. Nope.
Anything of interest in here? I don't think so. Nope. Let's go.
Flashlight. Thank you. This looks very bad. No bullets. Bullets. Bullets. Good.
What just laughed at me? That just sounded like somebody went...
Okay. What? Red. Everything's red. No flashlight works. No flashlight works.
Hey, lady. That's the lady. Come here. I want to question you.
I have some things to ask you, lady. Why are you such a creep?
I know that weird thing that was walking on four legs is going to appear and then puke on me.
I want this thing. This thing is dead. Flares? Turn that on. Does that do anything?
These look like flares. Okay, they are flares. What do I do with them? What do I do with the flares?
Oh. I need... I need four of these? Oh, it must be in here. Has to be. Yep, there it is.
Final power supply. Thank you very much. I'll turn the power back on in just one second, folks.
Pick it up! Pick it up, you bastard! Oh, my God. Get these stupid boxes out of my face.
Here we are. Just one moment, folks. Power be okay. There we are. Thank you. Turn it on.
And that is one big machine. Hey, there's the power. I'll take a sip of my Dr. Pepper now.
I'll take that as a reward. So now that that's turned on, can I just get out of the room now?
Yeah, yeah, I can. Fantastic. Cool. Here's the light for this room. Bullets, I'll take them.
And this... Hey, how are you? Eat lead. This guy's taking way too many hits. Come...
Get out of my face! Eat this! That's not working. Yeah, I'll take like 19 bullets in my face. That's fine.
That lady just appeared and I didn't like it. Come on. I'm going to turn around and these things are going to get up off the ground.
Guarantee it. Ready? One, two, three. No, not quite. I thought that was what was going to happen, but I was wrong.
What the hell? What the... Come on, man. This is ridiculous. You're going to get me like seasickness.
What the hell is that? What the hell is going on? Stop flickering. When you stop flickering, you're going to give me a migraine.
Get me out of here. Get me out of here. Climb the ladder. I don't even know where I am.
Somebody just said, Psst. Oh, I hate you. Can I drop down? Am I going to die if I drop down?
Yes. No, I'm not. Okay, cool. Okay, guys. Literally, I can't even see where I'm going. I'm just walking.
I'm just literally walking wherever I can go and falling in places. Up the pipe. We are now up out of the pipe.
Let's get out of here. Sweet. Sweet deal. And we have made it out of that. Hopefully we got out of that place with all the BS.
I seriously almost puked. Now where the hell am I? Can I go down here, it looks like?
All right. Thank God I'm out of that place. You're talking about just me throwing up.
What? Why are these things just coming out of nowhere? That thing just jumped at me and died.
What kind of a monster is that? I jump at you and die in midair. Get out of here. Recharge the batteries.
You're not dead. These things... Ready? Here we go. I knew it. Wrong one.
Let's go. Oh, now I'm talking about brightness. That was the brightest damn thing I've ever seen.
Can't do anything in here, it looks like. I can take my protein powder. Let's get out of here.
Check this door for any creeps. This thing just closed on its own, which means I bet you there's somebody in here having fun, hanging out.
Yep, this guy. How you doing, sir? Nothing. Which means... God! I got no light now.
How am I supposed to see where I'm going? How am I supposed to do this? Oh, there we go.
Everything's slow motion. Everything is slow mo. I don't like when things are slow mo. Get me out of here.
Get... God, that hurts every time. Get me out of here.
Alright, when she does that again, I'm not going to scream. Promise you. I'm just going to go like this.
Can't get in there. What the hell is going on? What is going on? Whoa.
Alright, listen. I don't like this. What is that? What the hell is going on? What the hell? Stop it.
Those are perfectly good beds. Can I at least take my protein powder? I gotta go in here, I think. Right? Yeah.
I can't even see where I'm going. I need this for the light.
There has been... I've jumped more times in this video than I think in all the Nightmare House videos combined.
And it's not even things that are scary. It's just like dumb things. Like falling off a ledge or being touched by fire.
Nothing like really that terrifying has happened. I'm just freaking out.
Um, okay. I'm missing something. What is it I'm missing? I'm not entirely sure. Man, this is so dark.
I need to like cheat and turn up the brightness. Wasn't that just a door here?
Okay, there was legitimately just a door, a thing right here. Where the hell did it go?
What? What's going on? What the hell is happening? What? What is going on here? Why am I like trapped in this room?
Um, are these walls getting smaller or something? Or am I just stupid and like not knowing how to go out of here?
Is there like a ladder? There has to be like a ladder. What is going on?
Dude, these walls are like closing in on me. I knew it. So what am I supposed to do? I'm gonna get crushed. I'm gonna get squished.
I'm gonna get squished. I'm gonna get squished. Where do I go? Oh my god. Oh my god. Oh my god.
Ah! What the hell? Dr. Peppa, let's drink it, baby. Oh my god. Okay. Is that the end of that chapter? It is.
It is. Goodness gracious. Well, thank you guys all so much for watching. I really do appreciate it.
And I'll catch you guys all soon. See you next week for Scare Saturdays. Woohoo!
I did not think that was gonna happen. I just thought there was gonna be computers.
Alright, guys. See you all soon. Oh, and I almost forgot. Take care, everybody.