Hello! Hi, ladies and gentlemen, welcome to the Germa 985 Holiday Christmas Special, and
the award show. I'm Germa, how are you? How's everybody doing? Oh, sorry, it's a little
chilly. Oh, it's snowing out there. I have a few things to talk about before we get started.
Thank you for joining me on this beautiful holiday afternoon. Over here is a schedule.
Everything you need to see today is right here. Awards are happening, by the way. Medius
categories ever. 27 categories this year. There's a lot. I hope you're ready. Oh, not
only that, we've got also the elf puzzle room. What is the elf puzzle room? Who knows? You'll
find out very soon. Do I see holiday cheer in the chat yet, please? There is a schedule.
Of course there is. Can I see some people Christmas, please? I need to see it. I'm not
going to go any further. Okay, so also, Bugleberry is in the building. Can we get some applause
for Bugleberry? Yes. Thank you. Thank you. Gonna be making a nice, delicious holiday
turkey from what I've been told. I don't know. We'll see what he comes up with. But also,
what's under the tree here? I'm going to be opening a lot of these presents. Remember
we did that a few years ago. They're under here now. It's going to be so nice. It's going
to be, I, wait, what's in this one? Hold on. I didn't peek. I promise. Oh, I think that
might be an Xbox. It could be an Xbox. I don't know. We'll see. We'll see. But anyways, before
we get started, how do you do a holiday show without, of course, an intro, without a musical
intro, perhaps? Ladies and gentlemen, please welcome, round of applause, Top Shelf Vocal.
Yeah, absolutely. Thank you so much for coming. Really appreciate everybody here. And from
hearing you practice earlier, sounds like you're going to do a little bit of jingle
bells from what I understand. Yes, sir. And I'll also be joining you as well as the choir
together. Are you guys ready? Okay. Is that okay? Of course it is. Hey, before we start,
Merry Christmas. Happy New Year. Let's get started. Dashing through the snow in a one-horse
open sleigh. All the wheels we go laughing all the way. Bells on bobtail. Yeah, we're
good. Okay. I think, I think we got our audio back. Yeah. Sorry about that. Sometimes when
you hack into a stream, your audio gets chopped off. We got it back. Welcome. I don't know
if you heard, but we're going to be filling this whole stream with modern warfare play
from the campaign. We're playing on just regular mode. Should be a lot of fun. So welcome. Just
waiting for the game to load up here. I think I'm out of snacks. Oh, here we go. Let's see.
Azra. Azra. Sounds exotic.
Ah, it's that guy with the mask. It's the meme. Okay. So far so good.
Hold RB. Ah. The Russians are working with Dairan? I'm looking. I'm looking. Let's see
here. Tank. Guy walking around. Guy walking around. Maybe he's by the helicopter. Oh. There
he is. He looks important. As you can see, this is a brand new weapons truck. It's got
all of the fixings, eight wheels, two peoples, and a gun. I'll take 10 of them. Yes. My Iranian
Russian soldiers. I'll take 10. They'll love these. Does this also double as a boat? Can
it float? Hmm. Alright. I gotta change target. Let's see. Protection detail. Am I, am I
to take them out? Is that what I'm supposed to do? No, right? That can't be right. Not
from this far. Oh, my target. Got it. Marked him. There's the buyer. He's the purchaser
of the brand new 10 vehicles. Go send it. Just send it. Okay. I get to steer it. Controllers.
It looks just like German's Christmas stream. Blown up. Gone. Perfect. And now the briefing
several months later. Mr. President. Come in. Leswell. General Shepard. General. I know
that look. What's that guy? You would be the first to know, sir. Damn right I would. Talk
to me. We have a hit on Gabrani's second in command. Hassan Zayani. Hassan Zayani. He's
taken up the mantle for Iran. Supplying terrorists. Money, weapons, intel. Well, he's ambitious.
He's dangerous, sir. He wants retaliation for the Gabrani strike. He's planning something.
Something big. We can't take him in Iran. He's not in Iran, sir. He's on the ground in
Al-Mazra. Al-Mazra. It's between Iran and Saudi Arabia. Well, let's get him. When? What
time is it now? Now? What better time than now? Send ghost. I have a skull face. Wheels
up in five. Marines are loading in now. You and the sergeant are leading the way on this.
Sergeant. It's open damage. Let's get ourselves away now, team. Save your seats, sir. Save
your seats, sir. Does this guy ever take off his mask? Negative, sir. Out here. Air strikes
are hitting enemy positions bordering Al-Mazra. Intel confirms a concentration of AQ fighters
converging in the valley. We believe they're protecting something. Surveillance indicates
soldiers guarding three structures. Major Hassan may be holed up inside. Ghost and Soap
will lead a marine special operations unit to kill or capture Hassan tonight. One Hilo
will insert two teams at separate offset points bordering the target area. Bravo team will
sweep in clear buildings one and two. Alpha team takes building three. All shooters have
got to execute authority, but we want Hassan alive for interrogation. Be advised, Major
Hassan is AQ's lifeline. If he is there, they will die for him. Good hunting. Sounds like
pretty good surround soldiers. Alpha team stays on board to land down range. Both teams
meet in the middle. Remember, we want Hassan alive, but this is capture or kill. Keep up,
sir. I like running, but walking. Doesn't look like I'm running, but I walk. Blackhawk
down. Blackhawk down. This is a real Michael Bay situation. Where are we going? What are
you saying? What's the deal? Alpha, we're moving to building one. Hold tight. Ghost,
we need to secure that crash site. No. First we clear first, son. That takes the heat off
Alpha. Then we secure the crash site. Roger that. Roger that. Let's move. I didn't hear
any of that. I'll just follow you guys. Force up to the house. Sweep through. Pow pow. Here
we go. First take clear. Negative on the son. See that. Second deck clear. Roger. Feets.
Okay. Three two. All stations, crash site is taking rocket fire from building two. Second
deck. Alpha, take in building two now. Hold fast. Seven one, form up. So we going in there
or what's the scoop? Sergeant, second structure now. Second structure. Okay. All right. Seven
one. Moving interior. Just stab that guy. Seven one moving to second deck. Sit down.
Enemy rocket stone. Solid copy. Good work. Oops. Ghost, we're secure. Negative on the
son. Roger. Kill the woman. That's in the rule of no women, no children. I just broke
it. It was an accident. I didn't mean to kill her. Casualty of war. You good, mate? I'm
good. Yeah, please stop it. I mean the PTSD I'll suffer for the next ten years killing
an innocent woman. That should be okay. Ghost, Soap. AQ's working with some good gear. Soap,
we're moving to the crash site to help the wounded. Rest of you, hold here and cover
us. Roger. Alpha zero two bravo zero seven building two secure. We're coming to you.
Alpha copy's off. Expect contact. AQ's waiting for us. Blue, blue. Damn good to see you guys.
You got five KIA, one wounded. It's just my gun. Five killed. Help me move him. And you
two are alive. Got it. I don't know. Get your gun on that tree line. Let's just leave him.
Private Burr? Sorry. Fire. I see him. I see him. Okay. All right. I don't like that.
What is this? It's so dark. Get your gun up. There we go. We're getting shot from over
there too. Be clear. For now, stay sharp on that tree line. They're still moving out
there. Seven six, call for fire. I want close air on that tree line. Raj, calling it in.
We're not done yet. Zero seven CAS is three minutes out. Roger that. Three minutes? Air
support's inbound. All visual. Incoming. Oh. Oh. Oh. Yay yay yay. I love those who can
smile in trouble. No visual. Back hug down. No visual. Incoming. Man down. Boy, I'm not
good at this campaign. Am I doing this right? Am I supposed to be on a gun or something
like that? Incoming. Yeah, it's heavy. Let's get him. Two three got hit. He's gone. Seven
two, I need you up here now. Raj, moving. Ghost, we should fall back to the host. Negative.
We hold or we push forward. The son's still out there. Seven six, patch us through to
the door. Raj, stand by. Seven actual kilo zero one. Fire is one mic out. Kilo zero
one, you're cleared hot on anything forward of our position. Danger close approved. Roger
that. People's incoming. Conserve your ammo. Let them get close. Here they come. Stand
by to engage. Get ready. It's on station. Kilo zero one, gun hit, gun hit. Are we clear?
All clear. All clear. No movement in the area. Roger that, seven six. Kilo zero one, holding
pattern. Seven six. None of you dead guys have ammo? Raj. Oh, there we go. The son is
still the target. Aye, let's go get this fucker. Alpha, you're with us. Roger that, lieutenant.
Let's move out. Stay near, sergeant. Those fuckers used us as bait, didn't they? They're
well supplied and fighting smart, thanks to her son. Aye, looks like you were right.
Your son's still here. Heli crash gave them an opening. Let's see if they took it. Running,
but walking. Look at this guy run. This is the worst runner in the history of the military.
Oh, yeah. Stay low until we're all clear. Sniper down. Who's hit? Seven four is down.
More snipers on the roof. Take them out. Are they seeing us? AQ's got night vision. We're
sitting ducks out here. Do you have a shot? Good shot. AQ's stuck out here. Whatever they're
defending is fucking big. Seven six, I want fire on that building now. Seven six, hit
that building. Don't level it. Kilo zero will be all for fire. Target is in the building
ahead of us. Do not level the building. Seven six, copy that. Making our way. Try three air
support. Yeah, on the side, please. All bravo, move up. I want this building locked down.
All the locks busted for sure on this. Seven one, moving interior. Let's see. That was the
worst suicide bomber I've ever seen. What was he trying to get done there? That was a bad
guy. You look like a good guy. You look like a good guy. All right, let's give this another
shot here. Suicide bomber, are you still there? Nope. Nope. Hey! What is up with these guys?
It's like they don't like me or something. Break. Okay, I can't hear it. I'm going to
take a break here. I think something's going. All right, let's try something here. Here
we go. Where's cat puke trying that brew? I mean, how do you guys feel about this right
here? This award? All right, I've seen enough. I think it's time to get back in here. So
namely elucidate. Here's the last time you'll ever hear that sound. It's very cold. This
is supposed to be hot cocoa with my hot cocoa poetry power. Okay, so the winner, who cares?
Does anybody give a shit about this? Who actually cares? Pre-recorded Andy, what do you say?
There are 27 categories. Ladies and gentlemen, your winner for worst cat puke is, what do
you think? Actual cat puke at 14.4%. You probably saw that one coming. Pitch black cat puke
at 14. It was very close. And then eating eggs with 9.8%. By the way, I think two or
three years running now, this is the most skipped category. Almost 20% of you that took
this poll just skipped it. What's going on? What's that? The hacker is ahead of you. I
don't understand what that means. What's going on back here? Why is that happening?
Can you put it back to the snow? I want people to think I'm in an actual place with snow.
We're in hell. Hold on. Hey, hey, hey, YouTube. What's going on with my backdrop? Your backdrop
is supposed to be snow and there's like meme shit on it. Are you going to try something?
Well, whatever it is, it didn't work. You know what? Why don't we mess with them back?
Why don't we send something that's really going to mess this stuff up? Hello. Stop talking.
Nobody talk. Who the fuck are you? Who am I? Who are you? What are you doing on my stream?
What do you mean your stream? What do you mean my stream? This is my Christmas special.
What are you doing here? Is this the guy? Is this the fucking guy right here? Hey, bro.
What's up? Hey, bro. What? So this did you just check it? Oh, yeah. He's a hacker. Wow.
He's so skilled. My name is the extinguisher. It's the extinguisher. Wait, what? You will
call me by my name. The extinguisher. Your name is the extinguisher. That's right. Did
you get that name like the fifth grade? That sounds like a terrible. It was sixth grade.
The extinguisher. OK, extinguisher. How are you? How are things? Why? What are you doing?
What? What? What? What is your goal here? Oh, my goal. My goal is to get you to apologize
for all the things you haven't accomplished. You've accomplished tons of stuff. We got
dollhouse. We got the what about the 100 gifted subs? 100 gifted subs. Yeah. What do you mean?
What happened about you not playing Yakuza? I thought you were going to play that one.
Yeah, I'm going to. I didn't play Yakuza. That's why you hacked the stream. And two billion
dollars of debt. What are you? The government? That's all right. Well, first of all, there's
a couple of things I will let me rebuttal. And after I rebuttal, maybe you'll give the
channel back. Well, maybe when you play Glover, Glover, I'll give the channel back. I played
Glover. That game sucked. When you play Glover, is that what you're really wrong about here?
And the chat loves it. All right. Well, I kind of don't give a shit about anything that
you're saying right now, because number one, I did try to give the community subs 100.
My credit card got declined like five times. I did try. My credit card got declined like
five times. That's literally what you sound like. Did you get his fucking area yet? You're
never going to find me, Jerma. So what the hell are you just coming to taunt us? Is that
what you're doing? Is that the fun you're going to have here? Yeah, that's why I'm here.
I'm here to taunt you. And I'm here to give the people what they want. Yeah. And what
is that again? You're just like hacking the channel. That's funny. That's funny. Everyone's
laughing about it. They love it. It's fun. Look at them. Look at them in the chat. Okay.
Well, thank you. I appreciate hearing from you. Now. Can you please leave me alone? I
should I have to do? Leave me the fuck alone. Wow. No. Yeah. Great respond. No. That's the
answer. Um, no. Okay. Well, you know what? What do you got? What do you got? Why don't
we? Why don't we send him something fucked up? How does that sound? You guys have
a connection? Do you have a connection? What if I do this? What do you mean? What do you
mean? What if I do this? Huh? Ah, that's not so fun. Is it? Yeah. Try that on for size.
Get that shit. Look at your face. It's so angry. You're such an asshole. Set. Can you
have a connection? Right? Send something back. Good. Send something. Send something back
right? Shit, you hacker. It's the extinguisher. You will learn my name by the end of this
stream. I'm not a gnome. I'm not a gnoblin. Did you do that? I'm a gnome. Can you be
a gnome? What? You're going to gnome the guy? That's so fucking stupid. Did you just gnome
on a live stream with over 20,000 people? That's so 2017. Why would you gnome somebody?
That's all you can do back? Get his location and send something else. Get us back access
for the love of God. You're never going to get it back. Give me a fucking break, dude.
Never going to get it. You send a gnome over there. You know how bad that makes me look?
Never going to get it. We got CatboyGerma. We got the Suski. He even turned off. I don't
know. We can't even turn this back to normal. What a disaster. Anyways, I may have made
a few of these. Look at him. He's struggling. You know, let's just get right into it. Everybody's
waiting for this category, and it's a good one. So let's take our time with it. Ladies
and gentlemen, here are the nominees for Worst Face of the Year. Dad, we really don't even
need to cut anything on this one. Just show his face and that should be good. Let's get
back to Call of Duty while he does that dumb thing. Alright, so let's see. Open this door.
I don't want to drop that gun. Let's see. Oh, somebody just threw a grenade in my right.
Wait, where am I?
Chat, man, the chat is going crazy. How do you feel about the extinguisher, chat? Are
you liking it? Ah, yes. It's so fat. How do you do that? How do you keep up with this?
Okay. We love the extinguisher. You see that? They love me. The extinguisher strikes. Yes.
Yes, the extinguisher. If you want to see more of me, this might be your only chance.
Love it. Alright. Well, I love you too. I love you too, chat. Follow me on all the socials
if you can find me. Not under the extinguisher, that's for sure. I would never use my hacker
name as my social media. Rule 101 for being a good hacker. Let's see. I'm going to clear
out this room. Yeah, you motherless bastard. Alright. In here. Let's just end your life
just in case. Hey, hey, hey. Did you guys not see me standing there? I tell you, they
really, the AI, they just sit there. Just wait for me to get killed. Oh.
There we go. One iced. Oh. Hello. Hello, you. I see you. That's it? Where is everyone?
Where's the guy? We're looking for Hassan. Hamad. Something with an H. Okay. Let's see.
What do we got here? Bills. Con Ed.
What do you think? On the way. We really need to shower. Reapply that makeup. It's creepy.
This isn't a factory of some kind, is it? Are they making widgets here? What do you
guys think of this run? Look at this run. Is this the slowest run in the history of
video game? What is that? What is that? Look at this run. Oh. Disable the night vision.
Oh, wow. Did I just, did that just bounce back and hit me? Hey, hey, hey. Follow me
for more cod tips. That's clear. You know what? Let's do the night vision off first.
So it doesn't bite. Yeah. Watch your ass there. That was a good one. Yes, I'm going
to slowly run up this. So it's Hassan now. Well, let's add it to Google Maps, shall
we? Here we go. Let's see. What the fuck is this? It's all in English.
You know what? The extinguisher's got to pee. All right. Sorry, that took me a little longer
than normal. My toilet's not working. I had to use my mother's bathroom upstairs. All
right. I hope you didn't miss me too much.
Uh-oh. Uh-oh. America sold weapons to a terrorist. They never do that. They never
do that. Clear the room. Let's go. Everybody out. Everyone except you, lady. She knows.
She knows this. Who sold the weapons to Hassan? Iran is in possession of American missiles.
American missiles in AQ's hands. Hassan has been passing out our ballistic missiles like
fucking Halloween. Oh, come on. You can't be surprised about this, General. Oh, deniability,
my ass. Iran's all over this. I want to know how many they have and where they intend to
use them. If Hassan is moving missiles, he has a smuggling partner. I would advise you
to find out who that is. Give my team two hours with those missiles, sir. I won't know
everybody who's ever breathed on them. Negative. I want them destroyed. General, there's valuable
intel there. This is an intelligence failure, Laswell. It's not going to be a tactical one.
There will be 500 enemy soldiers on that site by sunrise. We need a win fast. Bad move,
General. Gold Eagle actual to Ghost. Move your team and call for fire. I want those weapons
destroyed. What the hell's Amsterdam got to do with this? It's a smuggling hub. Amsterdam's
a smuggling hub? Since when? Who? The captain. I know there's a lot of bikes in Amsterdam,
but a smuggling hub? That's the first good news I've heard all day. I'll link up with
him and handle this myself, sir. Kate Laswell back in the field. I want this done right.
No mistakes. Is she going to paint her face and put a skull over her? Kate, I want Hassan
boxed up and gift wrapped. Until then, you keep this tight. The way they talk about human
life in this game is it's like a Christmas present. Amsterdam, smuggling hub. Let's go
to a cafe. Negative. Guys, you set? Good day, Cap. Yeah, I'm freezing. The water is freezing.
What just happened there? Pretty familiar with boating vessels. I'm not sure how or
what they hooked up onto there. Laswell, we're in position. Copy, John. What do you got?
AQ loading cargo into a barge. That's your target. Get aboard and find out who they're
working with. Sentries on the perimeter. AQ guard tool over the docks. You'll need to
take him out to get to the barge. Who dresses like that in Amsterdam? Who puts a bandana
over their mouth? I'll take the outside. You clean up the docks. Stay quiet. I'll make
you at a barge. Jack, on you, Cap. For a swim and a steel cold knife to your neck. Another
guy had to get up on here. I tell you, this would be a great spot to catch some bass.
Large mouth, small mouth, maybe some crappy. Great structure here for some big fish. I
like his sleeveless shirt here. Into the water with you. Knife to the neck. He sleeps with
the fishes. Ooh, yeah. That was pretty cool. Can I swim as fast as a boat? Apparently.
Why didn't he take him down? I was hitting the button. Unreal. All right, give it another
shot. Follow me for all your Call of Duty tips. The extinguisher. This time, catch you
by surprise, mister. I know all of you with your sleeveless puffy jackets. Seriously,
guys. So many. You guys all shop at the same place. Why doesn't he come? Really? Interesting.
These guys shop at TJ Maxx. Right in the gonads. Captain, I think so. Checkpoint reached for
the battle bus. Okay. Seriously, how do I drive this thing? Do I drive this thing?
You know what? Let's just go over here and listen to the barge. What? Yeah. Wait, what?
Now what? Oh, sleep. Go to sleep already. Oh, I killed you guys on that boat. Unreal. Unreal.
Did you guys see that? The extinguisher is getting extinguished here in my face. What's
a piece of the extinguisher? Why doesn't it stab him? Let's see. Interesting. Yes. All
right. So you know what? It's almost time. Chat, what do you think? Should I give this
stream back to Jerma? Should I give this stream back to Jerma? Should I challenge him? Should
I challenge him to a 1v1? What do you think? Extinguisher. All right. All right. You know
what, guys? I think that's what we're going to do. We're going to quit the campaign menu.
Hopefully, that saves there because I've got some stuff to do. Let's see here. An error
appeared. Don't say it ain't so. There we go. There we go. All right. The chat has spoken.
They want it. And they're going to get it. I wonder if Jerma will accept the challenge.
In for a world. In for a world of hurt. Get to a menu. It's not hacker. It's extinguisher.
Call me extinguisher, please. Still seeing a lot of hacker. Extinguisher, please. Call
me extinguisher. What is happening? Ah, there we go. There we go. Right. No, no. Ah, private
match. Let's see here. Let's create a private match. Free for all? That sounds fun. Let's
set up the parameter, shall we? No, no, no. I don't want to start the match yet. Let's
see here. Game rules. Let's go first to five points. We'll do a best of three. And the
map will be shipment because it's small. I don't want him to squirm and hide. Perfect.
What now needs to happen is the invite needs to be sent. Which I just sent. Extinguisher.
Yes, I love you, chat. I love you, chat. Thank you for respecting me, extinguisher. I appreciate
it. And you will be rewarded. Oh, yes. You will be rewarded. I promise you. I've got
a list of so many things that Jerma has not delivered on. We will be holding his feet
to the fire. Checking out some things. Let's see how long it takes him to accept this challenge.
Let's see here. What's going on in the chat? Kick his ass, extinguisher. I like it. Thank
you, I will. Oh my god, extinguisher. How this moves so fast. But I just want to say thank
you to all of you out there for your support. I really do appreciate it. No mercy for Jerma.
No mercy. I will show him none. Man of the chat. I love you, I love you. Extinguisher,
come back. I'm here. Extinguish him. You know what? I'm going to put all of these catch
phrases on a T-shirt. They're great. They're great. Let's see. Let's see what happens
here. If he's got the guts to accept. I mean, a man who dances like that doesn't have usually
guts to accept anything. Except his own mortality. It looks like the chat's on my side, which
I like to see. This is great. I suck? No sir, you suck. Hello? Hey man. Hey dude. Who's
this extinguisher guy? I don't know, he seems like a scum. Yeah, I don't like him. I don't
like him either. Who doesn't like the extinguisher? Nothing but love for the extinguisher. I'm
going to stretch out. Get ready. Get ready for this ass whipping that I will commence
here shortly if Jerma's got any moxie, any temerity, any guts. Hello from Ohio. Ohio?
Alright. Extinguish time. Yeah. He's so chunky. Hey Jerma. Hello Jerma. He's in the corner.
I mean, they all win. It's every single one wins. There's no winner for best auto moment.
It's just anytime he's on camera, it's fun. It's best. Do we need to even, do we declare
a winner? Send the message. They all win, I think. But wow, whoa, actually this is crazy.
Best auto moment of the year is. Hello auto. At 48% of the vote, sleepy auto in Jerma's
arms. And then at 19% snoring in the cheaper bed. And then 11% is auto is a little chunky.
It always gets chunky. What? Who is talking in my ear? Who's what? Hello Jerma. What's
up dude? I've got a proposal for you. I've already heard about it. People have been coming
over here. How's your stream going by the way? My stream? Yeah. How's your stream going?
It's going great. It's going great. How's the Call of Duty campaign? How's that going?
You get through the first part yet? People love it. I'm in the second level. I'm quite
good. People are asking for hot tips and I've been giving them out. Okay. So, and what
can I do for you? I've heard this. Oh, there's a 1v1 scenario. Yes, well, do you want your
stream back or not? I'm feeling Christmassy. Yep. I'm feeling, I'm feeling in the mood.
And you're feeling in the mood for what? Exactly. You want a 1v1 me and Call of Duty and I destroy
you and I get the channel back. That's right. Is that what it is? That's your proposal?
That's the proposal. Yes. So, let me just make sure I break this down completely. If
I beat you in a 1v1 in Call of Duty. That's right. You will give me the channel back.
That's right. No bullshit. I've set up the lobby and everything. First of five, best
of three. First of five, best of three. And you're not messing around or anything. This
is for real. Oh, no, no. I wouldn't lie to you, Jerma. Is he lying? I don't lie. You
lie. Do you have the information from him? They should have it. Do you have it? Yeah.
So, if I win, I get the channel back. If you win, you get the channel back. Let's fucking
go. Let's go then. Let's go. I need some support back here, please. What do you need? I need,
excuse me. I need a little bit of support here. I don't know anything about Call of Duty.
Time to focus up. Time to focus up. Look alive. Open your mouth. Open your mouth. What is
this, a team? What are we, boxing? You're supposed to do it very gently. We've done
Brover's Bro. We know you're not the best gamer. You got to focus. Stop, stop, stop.
We need this. Listen, listen to me. We need this. Quiet, quiet. Oh, wait a second. What's
the best loadout in Call of Duty Modern Warfare? Can you get him off the fucking screen before
I puke? What is that? Oh, thank you. I appreciate that. I think your play style is a run and
gun. Did you just put makeup on me? You're ready. What did you just do? War paint. Did
you just put war paint on? War paint. This is going to be off for the rest of the day
now. What the hell? You're ready. Just believe in yourself. What's worse, having paint on
your face for the rest of the day or having him on your channel for the rest of the day?
Think about that. Come on. Do or die. Hey, are you a fan of Ludwig? Variety streamer. Do
you know Ludwig at all? He does. Hello? Do you know Atriarch at all? Oh, you're talking
to me. I'm sorry, I'm setting up the game for you because you don't know how to play.
All right, all right, all right. It's time. Am I ready? 1 v 1. I get the channel back.
All right, so first to five. I'll put a 10 minute limit on it. Can I get everybody in
here, please? I need support. I need to be taught how to do this shit. I'm going to choose
the best match. Come on. Fuck yeah. Fuck yeah. What's your class? What's your class? I don't
know what class means, Ludwig. Submachine gun. Long light machine gun. Machine gun. I don't
know what any of this means. Am I in the lobby? Just focus. Don't worry about it yet. Why
am I going to buy stuff in the store? Don't worry about buying things. How do I get this
off? This is going to be on all day. Look, it comes off easy. It'll come off. It'll come
off. Did I get an invite? Why are you buying the skin? I was buying the bundle. Extinguisher.
Who the fuck are you? I'm the engineer. Oh, you were sitting here. Sorry. Extinguisher.
Come on, come on, come on. There you are. Can somebody get me a snack, please? Snacks,
snacks, snacks. Snacks, snacks, snacks. I don't want that. I don't want that either.
Do you want to chew it up? No. Do you need water? If you don't dump it on me. Okay, Jeremy,
you get yourself a little juice box. You get yourself some face paint. All right, go, go,
go. Everyone, I want to start a chant. Are you ready? Let's get this motherfucker. Let's
get this motherfucker. Let's get this motherfucker. Let's get this motherfucker. Start it. Start
it. Start it. Let's go. Are you sure you're ready, Jeremy? Go. Your whole existence is
on the line right now. This engineer was on Facebook for like the last probably hour.
Who have you been writing to on here? Still one of the most popular websites in Europe.
You ready? Let's go. Let's go. Extinguisher. You're the extinguisher? I'm the extinguisher.
What is this? Nutri-grain bar? What is this thing? Fuel. Where are you running to, my
friend? It's just waiting for host. Are you the host? Yes, I'm the host. You have to make
the call. Oh, I got to send you another invite because you don't know how to play. I'm in
the lobby right now, extinguisher. Okay. Were you booting me? You know what? You start the
back out of the lobby. Invite him. What the fuck? Invite him. Fight on your turf. Invite
on my turf? I'll play on your turf. It doesn't matter the turf. A lot of friends going on
here. Right there. Right there. That's him. That's him. Yeah, yeah. Where do I go from
here? Join game? Yeah, sure. Join his game. Fuck it. Hey, what do you think about that?
Are we ready? I just backed out of the game. I just backed out of the game. Who are these
people? Who are these people? Get out of that lobby. Who are these people? So many people
in this lobby. Invite him. Invite him. Invite him. I see him. I see him. Join in your
lobby. No, but I think he's in a lobby with a bunch of people. Let's go. Alright, alright,
alright. Come on, Jarvon. No, shit, there's people in here. There's people in here. Who
are these people? I think he's just in a regular lobby. He's in a free brawl. No, this is a
private lobby. He's in a free brawl. It's a private match. How are there random people?
How do these people get in the lobby? Who is Moise Bagel? His name is Moise Bagel. The
extinguisher doesn't even know how these people got in. A friend request? No, we're not doing
that. I need somebody from production to help me. Let's see. What happened? You gotta set
up a private party. Maybe customize. Invite him to your party. Create a private match.
It says you're in the main menu. You're supposed to be a hacker. And a free-for-all. He's good
at hacking, not Call of Duty. Invite him to the party here. Well, you leaked the stream
key. It was one of you two. I sent you in a DM. I don't know who leaked it. Well, you
are the one who was supposed to give it to production. Let me tell you right now, don't
have asked me for a stream key in a DM. That's actually stupid and I don't know why I
listen to you. Well, that's true. It goes two ways. No, we love it. We love you. Okay,
good news, he's in our lobby. Good news. Good news, everyone. I am still just thinking about
how much I want to strangle you. Right. Well, okay. Can the other people in the room hear
me? We're trying to get a private match. We can hear you. Can they answer this one question?
Classic. He wants to ask you guys a question. Is his face as red as his hair right now?
What's a good one? Do you want knockout? We want to go free-for-all. Free-for-all. Free-for-all.
All right. Five kills. Finally. I mean, the hacker, seriously, I thought you could set
this whole thing up. Locked. Good to go? You've got a whole team of people. Yeah. Where's
yours, by the way? We're all your team of friends. Yeah, right? Our friendship. Our
Christmas. Right here. Oh, we're going? Let's go. Okay. All right. Focus up. Focus up. Focus
up. Focus up. Focus up. Come on, baby. You keep spilling. Are you ready? You keep aiming
wrong. Is this a good loadout? No, no, no. Custom loadout, too. Try it on one. Yeah,
it's a machine gun. It's a running gun. Running gun. Keep moving. Okay. Keep on your toes.
So should I try to aim into the head or headshots or what? You're not wearing a headset? Headshots
or what? Headshots or what? Just hit him in the body. It doesn't matter. Just shoot him
in the butt. All right. Hey, yeah. Let's go, punk. All right. Okay. Come on, Jerma. Let's
go. You got it, Jerma. You got it, Jerma. You got it, Jerma. Let's go, Jerma. You're
crazy. We need the channel back. We need the channel back. Yes, we really need it. Tighten
up. Tighten up. 360. Don't stop, Jerma. Tighten up. We got Pepsi call on the phone. We got
everybody screaming at us. There we go. That's one, Jerma. Okay. Yeah, I can count. Aiming
a little low. Aiming a little low. Okay. Come now. Where are you? Keep the energy on him.
Come on. Are you camped? It's lame to camp. He can hear you. Why are you camping? Because
I need my fucking channel. Good camp, Jerma. It's just lame. It's just lame. Are you laying
down, Jerma? And now he can hear us and you fucked it up. I see you, Jerma. I see you.
I saw your cute little butt. Let's go. He's made things interesting. He's made things
interesting. Iron, but get steel, baby. Your butt was nice in those pants. Is this a bad
idea? Yeah, you're lying down in the middle of the square. There's a lot of openings.
Reduce the amount of entries he could see. This might fuck him up. Wow. Thank you so
much. Wow. Are you going to lay down the whole time? I'm not going to lay down the whole
time. I mean, let's go ahead and pound it right there. You're not going to lay down
the whole time? No, not anymore. Running gun. Head shot. Head shot. Right in the butt.
Walk around a corner. Should I go around a corner? Look at you. But I don't know what
the hell he is. How am I supposed to know that? So you have to go around a corner safely.
Ludwig, I don't think you understand that this guy's on my channel right now. What is that?
You don't understand if you fucking lose this game, you don't get your channel back. Yes,
the channel. I'm thinking of calling the channel The Extinguisher. Twitch is not going to
let you change my name to The Extinguisher. I'm going to change it to The Extinguisher
986. How many viewers does he have on that channel? 400 million. How many people are
actually on that channel? He's like a 30, 40K. He's big. Like I actually, I'm asking if
you want to do an upgrade. That's it. That's it. It's the first of five. The first of five.
You're hitting me a little hard. It is a flaw you have. It does it a lot. Wow. First of
five kills. It's first of five and we got two rounds, three rounds. All right, come on.
Tighten up. Two more kills. Two more. Two more kills. Maybe reload. Maybe reload. What?
Reload. Oh, I thought it automatically did that. You're still not reloading. What are you
talking about? I pressed R. That doesn't make any sense. You lung canceled it. That's all
good. You know what? You have your own style. What are you doing? You are shooting the bag
and you are, okay. Hey, hacker. Hey, Extinguisher. Yeah. Hey, are you playing with a
controller? He's playing with a controller. Let me just touch that. He's got a controller.
Yeah, not so funny now anymore, huh? And don't do this when you're talking to him. With your
controller. You've been talking about your hands on the mouse. Okay. It's first of five.
You don't lead there. Three to three. Oh, drop on him. Drop on him. Drop on him. This
thing sucks. One more. Were you dancing on top of that car? Tighten up. Tighten up. Slow
down. Slow down. Everybody quiet in the room. Shit. I don't want to press the button. Get
away from the bus, Jerma. What? Don't go near the bus? Stay away from the bus. Dude,
stop. I walked around the bus. Dude, the bus is, yeah, I should hide under the bus to be
able to find when he walks by, right? No, it's a bad idea. Oh, you're doing it, though.
You're doing it no matter what we say. It's all right, though. It doesn't matter. Man,
if he came from behind the bus right now. And aimed only at the bus. He would kill you.
The extinguisher is in. Yes. Bring it home. You're adorable. That went down my entire
body. I need one more kill and that's it. One more. One more for the channel. One more.
Come on, this is for the channel. Come on, baby. Are you nervous? Are you nervous? Tighten
up. Oh, and the extinguisher is coming for me. Is that what you're saying? The extinguisher
is coming for me. Oh, look at that. That's your channel. That's your channel. Best of
three is not over yet. Best of three. It's actually my channel now, isn't it? Oh, yeah,
best of three. Yeah, you want two more chances? No, this best of three. You said best of three.
I did say best of three. I'll give you best of three. You said best out of three. I did.
I did. Are you nervous? Look at your friends. Your friends are all hands on faces. They
don't look like the beach boys anymore. They look like the beach bums. Look at them. I
don't know what to do. Go, go, go. I'm not ready. I'm ready. I don't know what to do.
Go, go. Wait, wait, wait, wait. I cannot hear anything you guys are saying, by the way.
These are noise canceling headphones. Look at them praying behind you. They're worried.
They're worried. Is this a good loadout? Yeah. Good. Good. Good. You think it's good? Okay.
Keep it up. I'm walking this way. What I like about him is he seems like he'll stand by
what he promises. I think that's what a sponsor wants. You got it, baby. Keep it up, kid. You
got it. All right. What was that? I thought you gave it a finger. Hey, extinguisher, deal
with this one, bud. Well, I like that you're calling me extinguisher. Well, I don't know
your name. It's the only thing you said. You know my name. You drained my bank account,
too. Wait, what was that over there? Although I've heard you're two billion in debt. That's
fucking bullshit. Yeah. Yeah. By the way, I can hear every single thing you guys said.
Let's go, Jerma. Let's go, Big J. Jerma, Jerma, Jerma. That doesn't sound very confident.
That chant sounds a little weak. Jerma, Jerma, Jerma, Jerma. Doesn't hit as hard. That chant
sounds a little weak, Jerma. You fell down. I got to tell you, I love shooting you in
your cute little butt. First to five, you got it, baby. First to five. Yeah. Your cheeks
are... Yeah, you are a fucking cop. They're clapping. Press Q. Q? Cheeks be clapping.
What's that? What the hell is... What was that? Ludwig, what the hell was that? Try E. E?
Is this a grenade? I think so. Did he sit there? You think so? I don't know. It just was
on... I just saw the bottom right. He's holding a grenade. But the icon doesn't look like
a grenade. It could be like a Molotov. I hear him. Fuck it up. Come into the room in the
back, near the car. Hey, extinguisher, if you come into the room with the guy with the
gun at the camera... Oh, poor Jerma. I need to get one kill. Come on, come on, come on,
baby. Are your palms sweaty? No, they're actually very dry. Thanks for asking, though.
Your lips? I can help. Yeah, thank you. Is it because you smudged the war paint, do you
think? Could I... Jerma. Get this... Put it over there. Don't... Your butt's bloody. Come
on, come back, come back, come back, come back. Come back, she's in. Holiday spirit. That's
what we need right now. Holiday spirit. Stop touching me so I can focus. I have fun. I
have fun. This is so fun. Jerma. Oh, Jerma. Jerma. Jerma. Oh, oh, oh. Reasonable. I want
everybody else in the background. Out of the room. Welcome to my channel. The Extinguisher
986. Go to break. Just go to the elves. Go to the elves. Go to the elves. Go to the elves.
Extinguisher. Look at the chat. They're going crazy. Sweep. Extinguisher. Gotta love playing
PC players on a controller. And I won. You see? Not so bad after all. Gets a bad rap
to controller. Really. New era. So much easier. A lot less carpal tunnel. Can I get one more
of those? All right. Grab me one more of those. That feels good. I feel good. I feel real
good. Five and O. Look at the chat. Thank you so much. I was like. Yes. I'm good for
now. Yes. Extinguisher. I would love to see his face right now. Do they have enough keyboards
for him to break, I wonder? You don't have to have a mic or anything. Do they have enough
keyboards for him to break? What do you think, chat? Are there enough keyboards on the planet
for Jerma to break? Right now. There's no progress in this room. What is this? Do that
one. Do this one. There's nothing even here. God damn it. Hey! Look at this. Look at Jerma.
They're all drunk. They're all drunk. Shooting him in the face. Wow. Look at this feasting
One sippage. Christmas is over. A little thermite on your nuts. God bless America. Land that
I love. Let's see. What's this? Oh, more bullets. Great. They won't be able to recognize you.
We're going to have to put you in the tomb of the unknown soldier. That felt good. You
know what? Extinguisher is a little hungry after that victory. I'm going to go get a
snack. What are you going to do? Okay. All right. Don't do anything too weird though.
Oh my God. Don't do anything too weird. You all right? What the fuck are you doing? That's
connected to the toilet. That's not connected to anything. What? What? Okay. All right. I'll
hold on to something. I'm holding on. Whoa. What is that? What is going on? What the fuck?
Jesus. I'm nothing. I don't want to do anything. Bugleberry. You could do something else maybe.
Do something else. Something else. Do something else. I don't want to do that. Dude. No. No.
We'll sacrifice something else. Something else. Maybe. Does a crew member have something that
we can put in? Maybe like a. No. No. No. No. No. Don't let it. Don't touch those presents.
Don't touch those presents. Those are my presents. Do not touch them. No. Get out of here. No.
No. No. No. No. No. No. No. Please. Please. At least leave a couple. I'm taking this one.
This is my present. These are my presents. Bugleberry. Come on. There's got to be something
else you can do besides this. Don't listen. Don't listen to him. It's. Dude. Wait. Is he
still there? Bugleberry. Wait. Stop. Stop. Can you hear me? What the fuck? Dude. You can't
do. I need. Those are mine. I don't even know what's in those. Can it pump me into him? Is he
still there? Bugleberry. Can you hear me? Can I leave? Don't touch. Leave a couple please.
Oh my God. Chet's telling me to watch out. What's going on? I don't want to do this. I don't
want to do this. Bugleberry. I don't want to do this. Anything else please. Anything else.
Anything else. Is it an iPhone? Jesus. Xbox. The chat seems to be running me. That's my Xbox.
They're telling me to run. Bugleberry. Don't put that one in maybe. That's an Xbox. Where am I?
I can't run? Jesus. Where am I going to go? God. I'm a medium. I'm a medium. I'm going in.
I'm going in there. I'm going in. I'm going in. No. Let me in. Fucking come on. Get off of me.
My tongue's gotten dry. That game sucks. I don't care. Put that one in. Put that one in. I don't care.
That's probably the only one I don't care about. What is it? What's in it? Don't put it in.
Don't put that one in. Leave me one present Bugleberry. Please. One present. Thank you.
Thank God I only get one. Jesus. I have no idea. I just feel sick. I don't know. What should I be
feeling? What are you doing? Two points. Yeah. Bugleberry. I feel fucking sick. What was it?
Bugleberry. Something's wrong. How do you feel? What the fuck was that? Bugleberry. Stop. Stop. Stop it right.
Please stop. I don't even know what's happening. My chest hurts. My chest hurts. Is it even doing anything?
I don't think it's doing anything. I don't think it's working. I don't know. I don't think so. Maybe.
I don't. Nothing's happening. I don't think it's happening.
Get the channel back now, did I? No. You know what? Fuck. You are powerful. Magical listeners.
No. Stop.
Dude, easy on the language please. Bugleberry. Are you okay?
No. What the fuck just happened? What happened? What's going on? You piece of shit. It's you. It's you motherfucker.
I see you now. I see you. I can see you. What do I do about this? What do I do? What do I do? What do I do?
Oh, now you're scared. That's why I had a magician. I know a guy. You know hacking. I got dark magic motherfucker.
What did you do? What did you do? What is that? What is that?
I know we don't really know each other and this is really strange. It's really weird. Is your room cold right now?
It's very cold. My nips are. Yeah. Do you see what is under here? Yes. I have something down here. I don't know what this is. It's a swirling thing.
Do you have one of those in your room, dude? Yeah. Yes. Okay. I'll be honest. This is kind of freaking me out. I know Bugleberry. Hopefully Bugleberry is okay.
Do we call someone? I don't know, man. Hold on. Let me put my hand in here. Don't. Don't.
Can you see? What the fuck? Ow. Don't. Ow. Ow. Was that you? Was that you? Was that you? Was that you? I don't know.
Did it feel like someone slapped your hand? It felt like somebody touched my hand. Did you touch me? That was me.
Man, you motherfucker. How does that feel, huh? Does that feel weird? Does that feel weird? Does it? Stop. Stop. Stop. God damn it.
You don't choke me. All right, man. You want to fuck around? How does this? Does this sound? No. Don't. Don't. Don't you?
I'm going to kick you in the goddamn face. How does that sound? Don't you? Let go. Let go. Let go. Let go. Let go. Let go. Ow. Let go. Let go. Let go. Let go. Put it back.
What is wrong with you? Those were nice kids, by the way. Yeah, they are nice shoes. I'm glad you like them. You know what?
Look at you. My camera's all twisted. How do you feel about this, you piece of shit? It's a piece of wood. Yeah, it's a piece of wood.
It'll knock your fucking teeth out. What are you going to do with a piece of wood? I'm coming in there and I'm going to knock your head off.
Oh, hold it right there, boys. Santa. This has got to stop. This is not the Christmas spirit. What? Santa.
What is this? You've got to. You've got to. Young man, get over here. What do you mean? There's a Santa here? I mean, that's kind of funny.
There was nobody here before. Put that stick down. What? I remember the last time you used that stick. It's real. It's him. It's really him.
That's a real Santa. That's a real Santa. Dude, bro. This is the real Santa, I think. We cannot have any more of this. You are ruining Christmas with your dark magic and your foul mouth.
I don't know what to say, but I mean, the magic was not with me. I hired somebody to come and hang out. I don't know what to say.
Well, my magic-ometer sensed it all the way from the North Pole that something was not right in this place and I've come to set the Christmas spirit right again.
Okay. Okay. But that's going to require change on both of your parts. Okay. What do you mean? What do you want us to do?
I want you to reconcile as brothers. I want an apology from both of you. And we're going to start with Extinguisher. With me, Santa?
Yes. You get the chance to go first to be nice and to apologize to this little boy.
When you put it like that, I'm sorry, Jerma, for hacking your stream and playing the best game of Call of Duty that I've ever put on board.
Yeah. My bad.
Anything else?
You're not. I really do like your butt cheeks.
There's no place for that here, Extinguisher.
Thank you.
It was a compliment, Santa, but you're right.
Well, I mean, Santa, he hacked my-
Don't apologize.
He hacked my channel and he tried to-
Excuses.
He wiped out my bank account and he hacked the channel and I ruined my Christmas show and it was really kind of annoying.
Selfishness.
Doesn't sound like an apology.
No, it's not.
Extinguisher, I am sorry that I called you a dork.
I said that your hacking abilities weren't very good.
I mean, you seem like kind of a nice guy and then you seem like pretty cool.
So I'm sorry.
Really?
Yeah.
Is that sincere, young man?
Yeah. And that's- I also maybe want to say sorry to the crew.
I think I was a little mean earlier.
I've just been under a lot of stress.
Stress?
Stress.
And who else do you need to apologize to?
Maybe my mother because she thought I was going to be a doctor and I ended up being a clown on the internet.
But I mean, still doing pretty well.
And sorry, Mom.
I think that covers it.
Anyone else?
Dermot.
Oh, right.
The two by four.
I'm sorry, Santa, for- I didn't know.
How am I supposed to know when I-
Excuses.
But how am I supposed to know that it was you?
I didn't mean to get you with that.
I'm sorry.
Spit it out.
I'm very sorry to everybody.
Okay.
Well, that's what I like to hear.
And Santa likes when you make nice.
Thank you.
This is very big.
You're welcome.
I have a big candy cane.
And now, now that we have reconciliation here, I can finally grant you your Christmas wishes.
You've been so nice, extinguisher.
What would you like for Christmas?
Dude, you got a Christmas wish, dude.
What are you going to do?
Oh.
Um.
Oh, I got it.
Can you please, please make me silver in League of Legends?
It's about time you got out of bronze.
Yeah.
Wow.
Did you get it?
There you go.
I'm silver.
Whoa.
Thanks, Santa.
You're welcome, little boy.
It worked?
You're actually silver?
Yeah.
Dude, that's sick.
So sick.
Wow.
And now, for you, Turamo.
Money.
Oh, that's a good one.
Agreed.
10 million, at least.
Wow, damn money.
Okay.
Try again.
I asked for that.
I wish for the things to kind of go back to normal, the way they were before.
Before Extinguisher came on and hacked.
I'd like to do the rest of my awards and just chill and have a good time.
The way things should have been had you been nice.
That's true.
Ho, ho, ho.
You're right.
Santa can do that.
Whoa.
Did it work?
How do you feel?
I feel great.
Do you?
You're all jiggly inside.
Dude, hey.
How about this?
I'll take you to lunch.
What?
I've got at least 10 minutes on Friday.
I've got at least 10 minutes on Friday if you want to hang out.
I've got 15 minutes on Friday.
Yeah.
I've got an hour on Friday.
Minimum.
Oh, that calls for a real sit-down restaurant.
Do a group Tuesdays?
Yeah, let's do it.
All right.
Good for you.
You and me are going to go.
It's good to see you playing nice together again.
Thank you.
Bye-bye.
Santa, thank you so much.
Thank you so much.
That was unbelievable.
Bye, everyone.
The power of Christmas.
Yeah.
And the right magic.
Not that dark stuff.
You can never go back to that again.
Well, I think Beulah Berry might be dead.
Or he's gone.
I have no idea where he is, but we might not see him for a long time.
And remember, the mouth speaks out of that which fills the heart.
That's true.
So keep changing that.
And to all the community out there,
I want to remind you that this is the season for giving and forgiving.
And a Merry Christmas to all.
Thank you, Santa.
Seriously.
And Extinguisher, I'm serious.
We should go hang out.
I'm sorry.
It is the spirit for giving.
It is the spirit for reconciliation and hanging out and having a good time.
Holy fucking shit.
What a disaster.
What was that?
I meant to say Merry Christmas to all and to all have a very good evening
and to all good night and Merry Christmas to you.
And to all a good night.
Wow.
Are we on the channel?
Are we on my channel now?
Are we good?
All right.
So sorry, ladies and gentlemen, but sometimes it takes the spirit of Christmas.
Sometimes it takes Santa Claus to come out and right the wrongs.
Ladies and gentlemen, we are not done.
We are now on the channel.
We have control.
We're, in fact, just getting started.
So let's go into our next category.
This is category number 11, by the way.
There are a lot more to do.
So this is best rant.
And there's some spillage here.
And I'm going to need production to maybe help me eventually after this category.
Right.
I'm not going to say any bad words.
I'm not going to yell at anybody.
Production.
I spilled some cocoa earlier and I may need a little bit of help to clean it up.
How's that sound?
There we are.
All right, ladies and gentlemen, let's do this category.
This is best rant of the year.
Here are your nominees.
Thank you, Santa, for fixing everything.
I get exhausted.
My brain goes like, all right, man, that's enough.
No humans are supposed to be doing this.
You know what fucking humans are supposed to be doing?
Humans are supposed to be fucking picking up a wheelbarrow full of logs and just slowly walking with it and delivering those logs to the community.
And then those logs are used to build houses.
And then there's also a baker and a butcher.
No humans are supposed to be doing what we're doing right now.
Humans aren't supposed to be doing this.
Guys, when Ben Franklin was writing up the goddamn fucking Declaration of Independence, there was no guggity guggity in there.
There was.
Oh, yeah, we also need to make sure to leave some room for guggity, guggity, guggity, guggity, guggity.
There's no room for that, Ben.
Goat cheese is so gross.
Goat cheese is fucking vile.
I honest to God, I feel like everybody that eats people pretend to like goat cheese.
You pretend to like it.
I'm so serious.
I will die on this hill.
Goat cheese does not taste like dirt.
Goat cheese is this immediate, immediate, like flavor.
It's like right when it touches your lip.
It's just like, oh, what's on this?
Goat cheese.
It's immediately.
Oh, goat cheese, bro.
I love it.
Oh, dude, I would eat a ton of it on a cracker.
I love it on a cracker.
Of course I would.
Yeah, right.
What if aliens don't have anything?
Aliens could just be like, oh, wow, you have this thing over here that keeps your food from spoiling?
Oh, on our planet, fructose, we have, um, we got stuff.
What's that over there?
Wait.
Oh, it's a calendar.
What's that?
You keep track of days?
Who knows, guys?
The fact that you can have sounds come out of your mouth might be the most absurd thing that they've ever heard.
Hi, Mr. Alien.
How are you?
Their heads are going to explode.
Exactly what I told you was going to happen.
What?
What is this?
Why does this exist?
This is magic powers.
The game's fucking easy.
It's not even a hard game.
Instant kill moves are stupid.
Delete them.
Instant kill moves are fucking deleted from the game.
Instant kill moves, you should never have put those in the game.
They're fucking stupid.
Nobody likes them.
Not one person likes them.
The health is just too low.
He doesn't have any instant kill moves.
Okay.
If I chop you up in a meat grinder and the only thing that comes out and that's left of you is your eyeball, you're probably dead.
You're probably going to...
Not you.
I'm just saying, like, I'm not going to put you into a meat grinder.
I'm not going to put you into a meat grinder.
Okay.
We're going to take humans out of this.
If alien glob glob glob go one fucking shoots a disintegrating ray at alien glob glow two, if there's only fucking teeth left, it's fucking you're dead.
You're dead.
I run my dishwasher because otherwise it'll get gross.
I wash by hand.
I don't like that idea.
Oh, yeah.
It's like a bunch of fucking like salsa and like mess on my plate.
Just stick it in here and turn the water on.
No, I don't like the dishwasher.
I don't like it.
And you know, I also I don't like the dishwasher.
All the people question marking me right now.
So you enjoy putting like your dishes in this thing.
And then, like, for like at least one to two fucking hours, you hear it's fucking obnoxious.
It's obnoxious.
And it lasts for an hour, an hour, two fucking hours of this.
Twenty three.
There are more hungry animals back there, Freddy.
And that scary number.
I like that number.
Twenty three.
Hold on.
This scary thriller Jim Carrey movie.
The number twenty three is not based on any actual real like folklore.
I am not fucking around.
I'm telling you the absolute honest to God truth.
I've been afraid of that number since I've heard that movie.
I don't know how old was I when we come out like 20 fucking years ago.
How old was I?
And I was probably like, I don't know.
I don't know how old I was.
I probably was very influenced.
You were twenty three.
What?
Two divided by three is six, six, six.
That's what I'm saying, sir.
What do you mean question marks?
Yeah, it's actually biblically accurate, scary number.
I don't want the afterlife to be like this.
Every time people think of the afterlife.
Oh, heaven.
Oh, my God.
I'm moving on.
They're floating as a specter.
Oh, wow.
Look at it.
So Liz was missed everywhere.
Everything's misty.
And you're what?
No, I don't want to be like this.
I don't want to meet the caveman ancestor.
They're all going to be there.
I think we all think of like, oh, grandpa and grandpa and UGA and UGA is going to be there.
I don't want to go to hell either.
Because guess what?
You know, there's going to be somebody there that's going to be like, yeah, yeah, it's
fine.
Everything, man.
I'm glad to be down here.
It's like I don't want to be with the one like distant great, great, great uncle that
went to hell and hang out with him every day.
Oh, that's going to be fun.
Guys, why is there?
Why is there not an option?
Should I even do this?
I feel like everyone's waiting for me to do this.
OK, I'll do it in one sentence.
Instead of like 25 sentences.
So we're going to do that in one sentence instead of doing a 25 sentence explanation
of what I mean by this.
There is no add to cart option when you're trying to buy shit on Origin for the Sims.
There's like a hundred things to buy individually.
I got texted by my bank.
Hey, we've declined purchases.
There's like all these fraudulent purchases going through the EA store.
Like, no, that's me.
If that's me and it's dumb, you have to go through the checkout process on each individual
Oh, one sentence.
Shit.
I'm sorry.
I tend to go off the rails and that's not I don't know.
I just I get on a topic and I just don't stop and people clip it and then they send it away.
So, ladies and gentlemen, your winner for the best rant of 2022 is it wasn't even close
It wasn't even close at fifty four point seven percent.
Fifty five percent is the meat grinder, the meat grinder.
And then humans are not supposed to be doing this at seventeen point six.
Alien panic at nine point one.
It wasn't even close.
Look at the meat.
OK, let me let me defend myself.
The meat grinder category or the meat grinder rant was one person said something
and I was pretending like they were.
It's a made up person.
Right. This person doesn't exist.
When I say you, I'm talking about you in general, not you watching right now.
You in general, you in general.
It's not.
Oh, I'm going to put you in a meat now.
I'm not going to clip that, too.
So I'm going to stop talking.
When I say you, I mean just you in general, just you.
Oh, you know, if I put you into a meat grinder, I'm not saying you.
You get it. You understand.
Moving right along.
Now, here come the juicy ones.
These are the juicy ones.
There's so many categories left.
We just got started.
I tend to do impressions and some of them are very good.
Some of them are very bad.
I think some of my impressions are good.
Although people would tell me to do your impressions.
Your impressions are terrible.
So we'll start with the best.
We'll go to the worst after.
This is the best impressions.
I think I did a pretty good job this year.
I mean, people are doing that emote and I can see it.
They're like, blah, blah, blah, blah, blah.
My head's bobbing around.
Whatever.
You guys know what I mean when I say that shit though, right?
You have to.
I told Santa I wouldn't swear.
So I'm going to say, what the shoot.
So here are your nominees for best impression of the year.
These are the good ones.
At least I hope they are.
Now make haste to the tower and defeat the evil wizards.
Mermaid man.
Evil wizards.
Now we need to get into the boat and go get them, SpongeBob.
What are you doing, you old moron?
I am trying to do what it is a superhero must be doing.
Getting to the bank.
And who could forget Sir Gideon Ofnir?
The all-knowing.
There he is.
You drink?
Or I'm blue.
Chief of the Badlands.
The ever-knowing gold man.
The disgusting dung eater.
And of course, Sir Gideon Ofnir.
The all-knowing.
What's happening, my friend?
I would have voted for that one.
Meat.
Potatoes.
And lettuce and fucking gravy.
Spinach.
And radishes.
And I'm alive.
And I'm human.
I like to eat, too.
And I like to have children.
I'm here.
And I'm coming.
It's like, oh, Patty the Platypus.
I'm going to take over the entire world, Patty.
No, it's me, Doofus.
But that was actually really, really good.
And I would say that was probably the best one
you've heard anybody do.
Not showing anything under arrest.
I'm underwater.
Gentlemen, this is tobacco receive manifest.
Same voice.
Ever look at that headlock there, see?
That chap over there joined.
Or by pay us this.
Same voice.
Is the local got me on the penis before.
He has one voice.
Tom Scott, this water is electrified.
It will kill you if you stand within five feet of it.
Yahoo.
Whoa.
Oh, Bowser.
Ah, annoying.
Oh, boys and girls, it's a me, Mario.
Let me tell you something.
If somebody want to tell you to take drugs, always say no.
You say, Luigi, try to drink and do drugs one time.
And I said, no.
And he said, Mario.
So fucking god damn it.
And that's the bottom line, because Stone Cold said so.
Pretty good.
They're eating her.
And then they're going to eat me.
Oh my god.
Please can you do a quick Seinfeld routine about the word vast.
What even is vast?
What's that supposed to mean vast?
Just say big.
Just say large.
Say big.
Why do we need names for so why do we have so many names to describe what is effectively big?
I mean, if you want you want my vote, I'm voting for Alex Jones.
I don't think anybody does it.
Alex Jones, like, I can't.
I just I'm going to be really honest.
Find me somebody that can do that as good as I can.
People usually, you know, they go like this.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no.
Find me somebody that can do that better than me.
I don't think you can.
That's my vote.
That's what I voted for.
But your winner of the best impression of the year is, of course, it's Alpenny the Platypus.
Doofenshmirtz.
With 30 percent of the vote, that's a high one.
Then Alex Jones right behind it.
Sixteen point eight.
Not right behind it.
Pretty far.
Doofenshmirtz.
Alex Jones.
It's a hard word to say.
And then democracy manifests subtitles at 12.3 percent.
Doofenshmirtz takes it.
I think I can do a pretty good job.
And now, obviously, I do a lot of these every year.
And we're not just going to talk about the good ones.
We're going to talk about the bad ones.
This is the worst impression of the year.
I don't agree with some of these.
Let's be real.
Some of these are a little like, I don't like that character, so I'm just going to nominate it.
That's not how this works.
But just like the bad ones are also good ones, and what you just saw.
Here are your nominees for the worst impression of the entire year.
Did you do Jack Sparrow?
I'm done.
My career is over.
I'm ending my career.
It's over today.
OK, so I got a letter.
Jerry, when you read this letter, I will already be on the other side of the world.
I'm sorry about that.
I'm sorry that I'm not the father you wanted me to be.
The rest is up to you.
Do your best and live a wonderful life.
You always will.
That's the worst George I've ever heard.
It's really not. That's what I mean.
It's Gilbert Godfrey.
Hey, when I'm told, and I've been looking forward to this for quite a long time.
Health is more popular than ever in the Mushroom Kingdom.
Wasn't that tourney yesterday incredible?
But if we want to keep the sport interesting, we need some green players, you see.
And I just don't think folks can hit the green.
Whoa, wait.
That's not even that bad.
That's crazy.
That's all I had to do was just clear my throat.
We need some fresh faces on the leaderboard.
OK.
That was really bad.
I don't know if that's Toad or...
I don't know what game that was from, but it was a bad impression.
Ooh, Skywalker, I must say you are...
Is that bad?
It really was one word elongated.
You sound like the Swedish chef.
Do we have a Bobby Hill impression?
I'll try.
Yeah.
Hey, Dad, I'm sorry.
I can't.
But I tried.
What does Cookie Monster sound like?
It's like...
What does it sound like?
It's kind of like...
Cookies.
I love cookies, right?
Something like that?
Let me go all in with it and see what happens.
This cookie is delicious.
I love cookies.
It's heavy from TF2.
That's really not that good.
But, I mean, how do you even do it?
Let me try to do a dog.
Oh, Morty, we've got to be careful.
Put that back in there and we're going to go back in time to shave.
Actually, it is different.
Morty, Morty, we've got to be careful.
Guys, I've never seen all these movies.
I've never seen them.
I just know...
I know Christopher Lloyd.
Right?
His name's Morty, not Marty.
Morty, not Marty.
Marty, not...
I just dropped everything.
Do a Taz impression.
Not on a sponsor stream.
Whatever.
Why not?
I was just about...
Okay.
Taz Mania was just about to do that.
Somebody hitman style, put a fucking piano wire on his neck.
Patrick?
Hey, SpongeBob.
It's me, Patrick.
Oh, yeah.
SpongeBob, let's go have an adventure.
What was wrong with this one?
Does that sound like I'm kind of...
Yeah, it does.
Why was this on here?
Enjoy yourself.
Nope.
This is why it's a strange world.
This realm has a way of getting right into your heart.
And if that book becomes way more...
This one sucks.
I like it.
This is bad.
I will be expecting a very great thing from you.
It will get hotter in which you might not be able to imagine.
Geez, this one's the worst.
Does this win?
Voice is bad.
Shitty voice.
Worst voice.
Does that win?
You want my vote.
It's that one.
Look.
Okay.
You have to...
I am live.
I don't know how many hours a year.
But if I'm going to do an impression, sometimes you get shitty ones.
Sometimes you get duds.
I don't think the George was bad.
Why that George Costanza was so bad?
Jerry!
How?
Why would that be nominated that many times?
I think that one was fine.
Why was that so bad?
Question marks.
That sucked.
Was it that bad?
I don't think it was.
I think you're mistaken here.
They were all bad.
The frog one definitely won.
If it didn't, then there's something wrong with this community.
Ladies and gentlemen, your winner of worst impression of the entire year is...
What the fuck?
It's not even in the top three.
Toad was 23.2% of the vote.
And then Jack Sparrow at 18.9.
And then Patrick Starr at 10.9%.
One, two, and three.
What?
That frog was so bad.
Why is that not at like 80% of the vote?
All right.
Time for the meaty categories.
These are the ones that are full of flavor.
I'm going to take my time with these because this is my ego stroke here.
It's time for an ego stroke.
Until this one.
But, you know.
This next category is one that hits very deep to me and probably to those of you watching.
This is for the best joke taking more than five minutes to set up.
And what that means is that anything that took at least a few minutes to get rolling.
Okay?
At least a few minutes to get rolling.
So there were a lot of nominees, a lot of good ones, that I think.
And you're swearing.
Santa is already across the globe right now.
He's a very busy person.
So he's a very busy man.
Ladies and gentlemen, here are your nominees for the best joke of the year taking more than five minutes to set up.
Toad wasn't even bad. Stop.
Don't you think that would add some atmosphere?
If like after every major kind of area, every puzzle was like music played and you just heard.
Scorn.
That'd be kind of cool.
Jesus.
Oh, what the fuck?
Scorn.
Blood.
Lots of fucking blood.
Lots of blood.
That's a lot of blood.
Scorn.
I have to be better at fucking acting.
True.
Scorn.
I'm sorry.
I can't do it.
I don't know.
I look like a different person.
Leave it on.
So the twitch thumbnail gets it.
All right.
Fine.
Make this the thumbnail.
No, dude.
I.
This is fucking insane.
I think we're going a little too far.
I think we're going too far.
OK.
Are you ready for the culmination of what is the thumbnail right now?
Here you go.
Welcome to hell.
Now, listen, Buster.
Once we get down here, I'm going to make sure that we take care of this as soon as possible.
Now, I don't get that move at all.
That move is absolutely unbelievable.
It's one of those moves that you can't do anything about.
And I'm telling you, yeah, as ridiculous as that, get playing soon.
They're going to be like I can fly eventually, too.
How many fucking moves do you get before you?
I'm sorry about that, folks.
But I meant to say was how many moves do you get to do in a row before?
Gosh darn it.
You.
How many moves do you do?
Gosh darn it.
Or fucking wrong thing.
Wrong thing.
All right.
Here we go.
I made the medic.
I'm good to go.
I'm going to be killing these people.
I'm not eating bugs.
I wouldn't eat bugs if my if like my mother asked me to.
What about a doctor?
I don't know.
What does the doctor look like?
Is he like six feet tall?
Like 200?
Lean cut?
What does he look like?
And he is so fit.
He just got done cycling and he's got cycling shorts on and a lab coat.
Stop sharing your fantasy.
Just got just got done with a quick bike ride.
Kickstand comes in.
It's like sweat just glistening off his forehead.
So what brings you in today?
And I'm like, oh, wow, look at that.
That's why you got that.
What a head of hair.
Yeah.
I haven't had a headache, by the way, in a long time.
Different music.
You want to eat some bugs?
We're watching you in a bar, Jerma, do something wacky.
I like this one.
Hey, this one.
This one goes out to this one goes out to all y'all in the bar.
Hey, three, two, one.
Let's go.
Mmm.
Green tea.
They can't even hear me.
Should I try to communicate?
Hey.
You wait.
Look.
Hey, everybody.
Hey, I was on screen at a bar for those of you back there that don't know what's going
on.
Right.
I was typing and shit.
Yeah.
What about a Twitch moment badge for longest stream?
Wait, can I do that?
You were here for the longest stream I've ever done on this channel.
13 hours, 19 minutes and 41 seconds.
Ain't ever going to happen again.
Do I do another moment?
It's not ever.
Like the 200 people that just left.
You fucked up.
13 hours, 27 minutes and six seconds.
I think that deserves a quick bite of pizza.
Hey, man.
I can't believe you made it.
Was I on drugs?
Like what was I doing?
13 hours, 36 minutes and 52 seconds.
God, man.
I can't believe you were here.
Don't ever call the sus guy at 3am.
Hey, dude, can you speak up?
I'm in a construction site.
I would vote for this one.
I love this one.
Okay.
Why would you even go live?
Just wait till tomorrow.
Like who cares?
Fucking keep your stream off.
Okay.
What the fuck?
What am I supposed to do?
Guys, what does that mean?
Whoa.
A guy.
Hold on.
Watch out.
I got it.
Got to get this kill.
Oh, I died.
Shoot.
What if I just like pretended to fall asleep on stream?
All right.
I'm going to pretend to fall asleep on stream.
I think this is both categories.
Like, dude, wicked fucking tired.
I had a long day.
I hope it wins both.
And then you're woken up by the jump scare.
Fuck.
Yeah.
So speaking of which, I am a new man.
I'm here to do something that I said that I would never do.
And that's to play Destiny 2.
I love this part when he says the doctor.
I know.
I said I'd never do it.
But here we are.
Shpee.
That's the Shpee ship.
We're taking the Shpee ship to war.
You're fucked.
You took everything from me even though it's really not that bad.
And I'm going to punch you the first few times.
You better run.
And you better never look back.
Is this Scooby Doo, man?
Is this the mystery machine?
It's too dark.
Well, that was quite a year.
Those are your top jokes voted by you, nominated by you.
Let's find out.
Sorry, I just punched you.
Can I get some of this off my face, too?
This is going to be permanent.
I just did it again.
What the hell am I doing?
Ladies and gentlemen, the best joke of the year,
taking more than five minutes to set up is...
Oh, it's an upset.
It's an upset.
This is an upset.
With 25% of the vote, 25%, the ultimate thumbnail.
The huge thumbnail wins.
And then scorn, far away at 12.6% of the vote, far away.
And then sleeping to five nights at Freddy's with 10% of the vote.
That's kind of an upset.
I thought that scorn, all the scorners in the chat here
are probably going to be pretty upset about that.
Well, we did the good one.
So why don't we do the bad one?
If you think that I nail it every time, you're wrong.
I have a tendency to...
There's a couple of duds every year.
Eh, a couple of duds.
Not every joke is funny.
I don't expect them to be.
But how do you know if something's going to be funny if you don't do it?
Ladies and gentlemen, here are your nominees
for the worst joke of the year, taking five minutes to set up.
What if I just, like, pretended to fall asleep on stream?
That's right, there it is.
All right, I'm going to pretend to fall asleep on stream.
I'm going to put text on the bottom that says, like,
Dude, wicked fucking tired.
I had a long day.
And then you're woken up by the jump scare.
Fuck!
Yeah. Yeah.
I don't know how I got in this Discord call,
but I need somebody to help.
I got the wrong server ID, I think.
I don't know how I got in this Discord call,
but I need somebody to help.
I got the wrong server ID, I think.
Did you click spectate? It's on the bottom left.
No, I clicked a goddamn arrow.
Where is it?
I don't know how I got in this Discord call,
but I need somebody to help.
I got the wrong server ID, I think.
Who the fuck is that?
I'm going to have to go, I think, somewhere.
Guys, I think I got the wrong Discord call.
I don't know how I got in here.
I got the wrong server ID.
I don't know what's happening.
If somebody can troubleshoot with me.
I think I have to go up here.
Who is that guy?
What a weird guy.
This guy's weird.
He's a lunatic.
Was that somebody in the call?
What was that?
Oh shit, I didn't know it was still on.
It's been on for hours now.
I forgot your old voice.
Can we ban Iron Giant?
No.
All right.
All right, we just need to figure out a solution to our problem.
I don't fucking care if we lost.
I'm doing the joke.
Yeah.
What's up, Jack?
That was pretty good.
That was phenomenal, Jerma.
That was a pretty good one.
Oh, just one hit, one hit, one hit, one hit, one hit.
He's dead.
Okay, we're good, good, good, good, good.
Yes.
Yeah.
Hey, what up?
What's up, Jack?
I just bit my tongue in half.
We're in costume.
I'm Mercy from the Overwatch 2.
And who's that?
Hey, how are you?
It's me, Deadpool.
Nice to see everybody.
Oh, my God.
It's so good to have you here.
Yeah, special guest here.
So where do we start?
I don't know, man.
I just showed up.
I just got the call.
Yeah.
They were like, hey, man, do you want to be on Charlie Shaw?
And I'm like, I love that guy.
Of course I'm going to be on that show.
I knocked out that motherfucker in the parking lot, by the way.
He looked at me weird.
No, that sounds exactly what he deserved.
I'm going to hit that door.
Show him your high kick.
Yeah?
I went like this.
Hey, kids.
Soda.
This sucked so bad.
Nobody move.
It's starting to lag.
It's starting to lag out.
I'm starting to get sick, I think.
I'm going to get sick.
I'm at like 20 frames a second.
Oh, God.
It's getting sick.
Here we go.
Somebody said embarrassing.
Oh, shit.
This is bad.
Actually, be careful.
This might actually be flashing lights and stuff.
I'm not kidding.
These awards are embarrassing.
OK.
Here you go.
You ready?
This is the latest episode of Breaking Bad.
This is fucking stupid.
That was so bad.
This is fucking dumb, man.
This is dumb.
If Jerma reads this, he has to do a push-up on stream.
Oh, fuck.
I would have voted for Five Nights at Freddy's.
That's what I would have voted for.
But some of those I don't think deserve to be there.
I really don't.
Breaking Bad was just, I don't know.
I was just reaching at that point.
Because we were on the high of Scooby-Doo.
What's new, Scooby-Doo?
Coming after you.
Gonna find that.
And it's like, wow, this is so much fun.
I'm having so much fun.
Oh, what are the TV shows?
What are the television shows can we do, right?
I was reaching on the high.
Ladies and gentlemen, your winner for worst joke of the entire year.
The worst joke of the year is, with 32% of the vote,
someone got in the Discord.
Someone got in the Discord, and it wasn't me.
Oh, someone's in the Discord.
Sleeping to Five Nights at Freddy's was 22%, but hold on a minute.
So number two is Sleeping to Five Nights at Freddy's.
Number three on best of the year was Sleeping to Five Nights at Freddy's.
So it was top three on here and top three on here.
You guys need to make up your mind.
And then doing push-ups was 16.8%.
I would have voted for that one, probably.
The Breaking Bad one was pretty awful, but, you know,
I'm not looking forward to these next couple categories.
These videos are probably 10 minutes long.
Something about the worst and best noise categories this year,
I mean, the mods went through it.
Me and Holly went through it.
We had to narrow this down.
Best and worst noise of the year,
there were 60 nominees until we really had to get rid of some.
I think we brought it down to like 25 in each category.
So strap in, turn your volume down,
because here are your nominees for best noise of the year.
Or turn your volume up, if that's what you care about.
Jesus. Oh, what the fuck?
No!
How long are they going to hold? I can hold a Wilma for.
Wilma! Fucking long, dude.
Oh, I got a drink too.
That's pretty sus!
There was a cricket outside last night.
I swear to God, I always wanted to record it,
like just get audio recorded,
because this thing was so loud and it was going super speed.
It wasn't...
This guy was looking for somebody.
It was like...
It was like static. I couldn't stand it.
You know what sound that makes too.
It's like...
You just like that because it sounds like the teacher noise.
Way!
I can put it over my head.
I'm moving an amount of water from one room to another.
I can go like this.
Should I do this?
Okay, I'll do it.
No, I just heard that in my head.
It hurt.
I heard somebody laugh off camera.
This is the Tasmanian devil in the electric chair.
Okay, this doesn't sound right at all.
And let's do a scream test.
Woo!
Fixed it.
How do I look plastic today?
I mean, I don't feel plastic.
Dude, too loud, too one up.
Fuck!
Oh no, it's one of those...
Are you wearing red because you're the imposter?
Yes.
When I'm lying in my deathbed and I'm connected to like...
You know what? I'm like 90 or something.
I got 100.
And everyone's like gathered around the bed and everyone's like...
Oh, let's just say goodbye to grandpa, right?
You bet your ass that I'm going to be like...
You bet your fucking ass that's the last thing I'm leaving you with.
Fuck!
Give it, give it, give it, give it, give it, give it...
How many people are here right now on the channel?
Do I have a number?
65.
There's 65,000 people here.
And you just got subjected to that.
So, should I apologize?
Or should we wait?
Should we wait for this one?
I'm gonna hold my apologies till this one.
Ladies and gentlemen, the, oh, I may have ripped it.
The winner for best noise of the entire year.
Was it ever gonna be close?
Let's spam it in the chat.
You know what it is.
Spam it.
I'll do it if you spam it.
Scored.
With 39% of the vote, scorn absolutely killed it.
Gimme, gimme, gimme was only 15.
Scorn absolutely dominated this category.
And then are you the imposter was three.
So scorn, a scorn sweep right there.
40% of the vote almost.
39.7% actually.
Which is, that's a lot.
So to the almost 60, 70,000 people that are here right now,
I apologize for this next category.
I apologize in advance.
I said a lot of sorry's already,
but it's time for another one.
I'm sorry about this category.
Most nominees, I think total,
that had to get dwindled down,
but we have a best noise, we have a worst noise.
They could just be the same category.
I should just do a thing where it's just noise of the year
because why even have two categories?
Here are your nominees for worst noise of the year.
It's just, you know what I mean?
It's just the, it doesn't even lather up either.
I'm so, that was bad.
You've seen me do it like a hundred times.
It, you can't dodge them all.
He's like, he's turning.
Oh shit, he's turning.
He just growled at us.
Wrong game, wrong game from software.
Wrong game.
Like some people eat a lobster.
Like it's literally the last thing they're ever going to eat
in their entire life.
And they like, what's in here?
Oh, and it's just like, God damn it.
What are you doing?
Oh, there's some still in there.
And I just, I just, I don't like it.
I don't like it.
I don't like it at all.
It's revolting.
It's absolutely fucking revolting.
How about you fucking relax?
Young Madduck, apprentice to Hunwit, the dream chanter,
removes his instrument from its case.
Its features, compose, take on a startling dignity.
Let's hear it.
This is on here twice?
How many times was this nominated?
Can I just say this is the worst moment of the whole year?
I can say that, right?
It's my channel.
Wait, so when it goes, does it?
It goes like, I just threw one of those nerf,
you know those nerfs, whistlers?
The thing that like Brett Favre
was in the commercial and he threw it like,
ah, look there, I can throw this a hundred yards.
And it goes, I just threw one of those.
Now I know what this is for.
We're all the way over here.
So.
What's wrong with you?
What's your limit?
Hold on.
No.
Oh, I'm sorry, everybody in production
probably fucking just cringed.
Did you guys hear that?
What the fuck was that?
There is recency bias, I think, on this one.
We have some recency bias, I think.
I don't think, I can literally see it through the paper,
by the way.
I peeked.
Ladies and gentlemen, the worst noise of the entire year,
recency bias, come on.
The multiverse is squeal at 20% of the vote.
Not that bad.
Growls at chat with 18.8.
And then I don't even, I don't know what this one is.
Suck, snort, wheeze, cackle.
Do we even know, what is that one?
I was trying to watch, but I couldn't even,
I don't know what that one is.
Very good to know.
A third most skipped category.
13% of you that took the test did not take this one.
You're like, fuck it, I don't wanna hear that.
I don't care.
Which makes sense considering there's so many categories.
And okay, but multiverse is squeal.
Hey, multiverse is a great game.
You should try it.
You know what?
Can we check in with the puzzle room?
Let's take a look at the puzzle room.
How's the puzzle, the puzzler's doing?
Damn it.
No one's doing anything.
Have they not done any of the puzzle?
Zero, hold on.
There's only one person doing it.
I'm going in there.
There's only one, they're all just like eating sandwiches.
I need to see the progress.
Oh my God.
I'm not gonna be angry.
Hi everybody.
It seems as if there is,
it looks like you've blocked out some areas.
Can you get this?
Where's the camera?
Can you see this over here?
They have one edge of one of the corners.
What have you been doing in here?
What's going on?
What are you doing here?
What is this?
You're playing cards?
Yeah.
Excuse me.
What?
Santa said to be nicer.
So if you could please finish one section.
This was a lot of money.
This cost a lot of money.
You heard Ludwig and you heard H. Racker.
By the way, where the fuck are they?
Sorry if I swear.
You know what?
They're drinking.
And they're drinking too.
You know what?
Deal me.
You wanna go?
Blackjack, you and me.
Who wants to go?
You and me?
Blackjack, I'll be the dealer.
Where are the cards?
Let's go Blackjack.
What are these comically huge cards?
Hey, by the way, is this the Ace of Clubs?
Nope, that would have been fucking insane if it was.
You wanna go Blackjack?
Ready?
You're not gonna play Blackjack?
I got this.
Why did you write this?
We wanted to see that movie.
You wanted to see that movie?
We wanted to see it.
In here.
We were hoping.
You just wanted to see Avatar 2, The Way of Water.
We don't pay us enough to go watch it ourselves.
What does this one say?
Send hot cups of, that's a funny joke.
My name is Danny Elfman, please hurry.
Are you kidding?
I actually don't get it.
Do it for Puzzle Girl.
Who's Puzzle Girl?
You.
What are we doing exactly?
Do it.
Okay.
You ready?
Everybody here is being, by the way,
everybody here is being paid.
Just wanna make sure everyone understands that.
How much you bet?
Hey, don't worry, the bank will take care of you.
Here's like 600 bucks.
Right there is eight, nine, 10, 11, 12, 13.
That's 14.
What are you gonna do?
Versus a, by the way, can you see this?
I got a 10 showing here.
What are you gonna do?
You're gonna hit.
That is eight, five, 10.
That's 18.
You're gonna stay?
Staying, okay.
Don't look.
17.
Stop!
Give me that.
Give me that toy.
Don't give it to him.
Santa, if you're watching, I'm just being funny.
Give me that toy.
I made sure to not, five, 10, 15, 20, 25, 30, 35, 40,
45, 50, 55, 60.
You just made $60.
Gonna do another category.
Excuse me.
Merry Christmas!
What do you mean you can't do, wait, wait, wait, wait.
Can't do math?
What happened?
I can't do math.
Wait.
Count those cards.
Hold on a second.
This is 17.
That's 10.
18.
What are you talking about?
She won.
We can't count.
That's literally 18 versus seven.
What are you talking about?
I'm a man of my word.
So guess what?
All the elves in this area, you're going to split $60.
Woo!
Elves, elves, elves, elves, elves, elves, elves, elves,
elves, elves, elves, elves, elves, elves, elves, elves,
13 elves.
Ladies and gentlemen, 13 elves divided,
60 divided by 13 is?
$100.
Yeah!
Each.
It's like two bucks each.
Hey, how about this?
We'll double your pay.
Woo!
How much they were getting paid in the newspaper.
Whatever.
I mean, they were paid to do a puzzle
and they didn't do it.
Let me make sure, let me be very clear.
They were paid, they were all those people
who were paid to be here.
They were all paid to be here to do a puzzle.
What if we talk about how much income is that worth?
I'll double their pay.
Fine.
Yeah.
How about this?
Hey elves, can you hear me?
Elves, you can hear me, right?
How about this?
You get one section done.
And I mean even a border.
And I'll quadruple your pay.
I wonder if they'll do it.
I will five times your pay.
Get a border done.
A hundred each?
Look, now they're all standing.
Now they're all ready to go.
They're like, holy shit, let's go.
They were all sitting before.
Now, hey, can we give it up for the elves?
In the chat, give it up for the elves.
You know, hey, hey, hey, hey, you know what?
Hey.
Let's five times their pay for fucking no reason.
How does that sound?
I'll do it.
Easy.
Do the puzzle.
That's what you're here for.
And I may have almost hit somebody in the face
with that turkey that I threw.
All right.
We're at the next category.
This is best one guy moment.
One guy, there's a lot of people here.
I imagine some of you don't know what the hell this means.
A one guy is when somebody kind of derails the stream.
I will see it.
I will comment on it.
And it changes the outcome of the rest of the day.
It's not just, oh, yeah, yeah, I read a comment.
No, no, no, no.
A one guy moment is you've changed
the course of history completely.
Here are your nominees.
The best one guy moment of the year.
I don't, I'm not gonna encourage this behavior,
but I'm gonna tell you something right now.
Don't fucking, this is not to be encouraged,
but it was just like, what the fuck, man?
Somebody asked what the baseball stream is.
And I said, whatever.
And then like, it's been like five minutes.
It's been like at least five minutes.
Somebody like added that person, I think,
and said he's gonna shove an entire baseball up his ass
on stream.
This person's name too.
Yeah, what the fuck?
Their name was Ball Fondler.
Okay?
Remember, you're on the website.
What?
You're on the QR code?
It's taking this friend of thumbnails.
Is it there?
All right.
What?
All right, now put the tarantula in my mouth.
Put the tarantula in my mouth.
I'm gonna be like shocked that it's in there.
You know what I mean?
Like.
I can't even believe it.
He's, the dev, the dev is even sick of this joke.
The dev is like, all right, this is kind of funny,
but like fucking hurry up.
I mean, we have to summon the person
that's called barf drinker.
Okay?
And then that's it.
Oh my God, I'm gonna get BM'd, aren't I?
I'm so stupid.
He's throwing rocks at me.
All right.
No, no, no, no, no, no.
No, no, no.
I'm not gonna let this happen.
Oh my God, I'm dead.
All right, I can't believe it.
We're watching you in a bar, Jerma.
Do something wacky.
Hey.
Hey, this one, this one goes out to,
this one goes out to all y'all in the bar.
Hey.
Three, two, one, let's go.
Mm, green tea.
They can't even hear me.
Should I try to communicate?
Hey, you, wait, look.
Hey, everybody, hey.
One, two, three.
Yeah.
Oh, I wanna show this too.
Hold on.
Somebody, somebody actually made this.
These are really romantic candles.
Oh, it probably stinks up here.
Boss, I filled the room with red candles like you wanted.
Jerry, you fucking idiot.
Boss, you have to get the red cinnamon apple candle
from Yankee Candle and put it in every room.
Somebody said just eat a handful.
That'd be so fucked up.
You'd probably have like,
you'd probably have like a fucking like mental breakdown.
It's not designed for that.
Eat a handful.
That'd be fucking disgusting.
I'm kind of curious.
I'm curious, let's go.
It tastes like hamburger meat.
Do you want Mario drug PSA?
Be-ah-hoo, be-ah-hoo, be-ah-hoo, whoa.
Hi, ladies and gentlemen.
I'm Super Mario.
We've made a lot of jokes here today.
We've had a lot of fun.
And I'm an actor.
But let me just be the first to tell you that,
you know, it's not fun.
What is not totally be-ah-hoo, drugs and alcohol.
This is by somebody in the community.
Are they comfortable with you sharing their name?
I don't wanna share their name if they're not comfortable.
But anyways, they discovered a new way
of isolating viruses that kill
antibiotic resistant bacteria.
Somebody in this community.
And the first one I discovered using this method,
I named after Germa.
This is apparently fucking working.
Against bacteria, antibiotic bacteria resistant shit.
That's me in there.
That's me taking care of that.
I'm in there and I'm getting all of those fucking molecules
and I'm destroying them.
Make a sandwich with wood.
Make a wood sandwich.
I can't, I can't.
Submit this.
Play for now.
Okay.
Fucking quit the goddamn game.
I exited the fucking game.
What the fuck is happening?
If Germa reads this, he has to do a pushup on stream.
I want to be so.
Ah!
Oh fuck, oh fuck.
If I put the ring light around your neck.
If I put the ring light around my neck,
I could actually fit.
That would be fucking stupid.
Wait a minute.
Nice swag, thanks.
I was told that if I spin a hundred times at $10,
starting with $1,000 on this slot machine,
that I will be able to get to $10,000 plus dollars.
There's a person in chat here who is putting
their stream chat life here.
They're going to be banned from the channel
if it doesn't work, or they're gonna get VIPed if it does.
Three, four, five.
Oh my God.
I'm so sorry.
Hello.
Yeah, and guess what?
You can hear me, huh?
You can hear me pretty well.
Not like it was before.
What the fuck, dude?
I'm not gonna drink a, hold on.
All right, hold on.
Let's tweet that.
How long is this fucking?
Yeah, so hopefully it sounds all right.
These things are pretty cool.
These things, let me try a scream test.
Can I try it?
Hold on.
Can I scream?
Can I scream in your ears?
I'm gonna scream in your ears.
They should fucking remove geometry from school.
Teach people how to do their taxes.
I got some soft locked?
How?
No, I'm not.
Someone tell Jerma I can tell them how to fix their save.
How do I do it?
That's so funny.
How do I fix my save?
Let's try X560Y330.
New tweet.
No, wait.
Z330.
Oh, Dev, looks like you're having a little bit of trouble
with geometry, aren't you?
Looks like the Dev is having a little bit of trouble
with geometry.
Just like, Dev, when was the last time
you were in fucking high school?
When was I?
I am gonna get so validated right now.
I suck at math.
I am in my 30s.
I haven't had to do this for years.
Go look at the tweet right now.
I'm gonna fucking, I'm framing this.
I'm literally going to frame that tweet from Dusk Dev.
No!
I don't want, all right.
Can I just delete all the weapons
besides the shotgun and the,
I don't wanna like, oh, eh, eh, eh, eh.
Yes.
Oh, sorry, that was loud.
Unequip all of your weapons.
That is definitely the way.
Yes, unequip all of your weapons.
As the voice actor for this fight making fun of me.
Ah!
Bro, that looked like Battle Chess.
You can turn me back on.
Battle Chess.
Oh, that's, oh my God.
You just ruined Dark Souls 2 for me forever.
You just ruined Dark, I can't even play this again.
Andy Funny Voices.
You said that wrong.
No, no, no, no, no.
Excuse me, I gotta correct you.
That's Funny Voice Andy.
Andy Funny Voices.
I love that.
That's my favorite comment of the week.
That's so, I love that wording.
Time that person up for five seconds.
If you lose, you have to get one of the gyros from Arby's.
I love this, this was so fun.
This was so fun.
Grossest fast food item.
You know what's crazy?
I don't want to eat fucking Arby's.
I don't want that at all.
I'm gonna try as hard as I can.
I'm gonna be silent now.
Oh shit.
Oh no, I wanna get Arby's.
I did it.
Sorry, Arby's fans.
Not tonight.
Causing havoc on the highway.
We're on break core for this.
Restart, restart the mission.
Restart the mission.
This is fucking with my head.
Imagine if the police were listening to this.
It's too fucked up.
So there are a lot of funny people in this community.
I've known this for a long time.
This is not a secret.
The stuff that some of you guys come up with is insane.
I'm just sitting here watching and laughing along with you.
I couldn't ask for a more fun community.
Seriously, I love it.
Your winner of best one guy.
Remember one guy, you know who that is?
We all know, come on.
Your winner with 48.8, 49% of the vote.
It's Ball Fondler.
Of course it is.
Ball Fondler, congratulations,
you won best one guy moment of the year.
And then after that, 10%,
day one Elden Ring played at the bar.
And then 9%,
Stanley Parable Dev adds a spider into your mouth.
Barf Drinker, you would have had my vote, Barf Drinker.
You were 1.7% behind that in fourth place.
This was one of the most least skipped categories.
Congratulations Ball Fondler
for making an unbelievable moment of the stream.
Ball Fondler has been banned like three times.
Ball Fondler's comments since then,
do you know what they are?
Play Skyrim.
Okay, dude, are you gonna play Skyrim?
Hey, play World of Warcraft Dragon Flight.
Okay, I'm not gonna do probably Skyrim maybe.
All right, moving right along.
We are getting into the top seven or eight categories
and they're getting juicy.
This next one, this one's got a lot of nominees.
What is it?
Yeah, congrats Ball Fondler, you made a fun moment.
Best scare moment of the year.
Horror games, jump scares, scariness.
Anything that's freaked me out could be nominated.
Here are your nominees for best scare of the year.
I know, I just was doing that to freak out, you know,
like, you know, pity, you know what I mean?
Ah!
Hi, I'm just playing.
I was doing my task.
Ah!
Like, I started to like look this way
and this eye, this eye, I went like, I went reverse cross.
I went frog eye for a second.
Did he leave the room?
Holy God, this guy sucks.
Ah!
Back, but this, ah!
God, I'm so sorry.
Holy shit, that was, that was like the worst thing
that has ever happened to me.
What the flying fuck are you doing, lady?
I'm just going up the stairs.
I don't give a shit if he hears me.
I thought he was downstairs.
Oh my God, that was the worst thing ever.
That was probably the worst thing ever.
In a circle.
That was the chicken.
That was a fucking rooster.
That was a rooster.
That was actually a rooster.
I don't know what that means, but whatever.
Jesus Christ, dude.
Where is he?
Whoa!
Oh, the fucking thing, the drape.
I thought like a tentacle came down and grabbed me.
Fuck, dude, why?
I'm all cracked out now.
Holy shit.
What the fuck?
Ah!
It's like a monster.
It's just sound effects.
There's not even, nothing here.
There's nothing here.
Oh my God, it's a bat.
Hey!
Okay, I got a frying pan.
Oh shit.
I have what's it called, flash.
I could throw it at everyone.
I've got six minis.
Oh!
Run!
I'm sorry, I don't know how to skip this.
Oh, I went in the dumpster.
It's okay.
I thought you were getting killed.
No, I thought I was dead, dude.
I was like, what the fuck?
Somebody like sniped me.
It was terrifying.
That would be a fucked up start.
To Mickey Mouse's clubhouse.
Where do I go from here?
Okay.
Turn it off.
Turn that off.
Close it up.
What?
I'm wearing the same sweater too.
Where are the other cookies?
I have the same clothes on.
Relax.
Holy shit, dude.
Are you kidding me?
This is not even scary.
Did I just fake that?
No, I really didn't.
I swear to God, but like that was way over.
I've never played a scary game in a long time.
Oh my God, how am I alive?
I am absolutely, I was like, what are you pointing at?
Oh, it's a cliff.
Jesus.
I just shot down my computer.
I think I shot my computer.
I think I shot my computer down.
Wow.
A lot of scares this year.
A lot of scares.
I want to know what you guys picked.
No fanfare.
Let's go.
Yeah.
It technically happened last year.
Wearing the same clothes.
The volume warning puppet combo scare
with 20% of the vote.
It's the one where it looked like I saw a mouse
go through the bottom of the screen there.
Yeah, it looks like, yeah.
I mean, come on.
Charborg corner jump scare with Among Us
is at 13.7, number two, 13.7.
And then Iron Lung at 7.3%, number three.
I mean, the cutoff of the awards
was right at that puppet combo stream last year.
So, honestly, I think a couple of years
came off my life after that.
I felt awful after that stream.
I think I remember talking about it later,
being like, I feel bad, I feel awful.
I have a headache, my chest hurts.
It actually felt terrible after that.
Anyways, we are getting to the final seven awards.
This is getting juicy.
I've said that four or five times, but it is.
Time to get to the big ones.
Now, every year, I like to sing some songs.
I sing, I get involved, I enunciate,
and we are going to show you now
some of those nominees for what that means when it's good.
Not bad when it's good.
Here are your nominees for the best singing of the year.
Hopefully it's good, because I haven't seen this.
Boop beep, boop beep, boop beep, boop.
Boop beep, boop beep, boop, boop beep, boop.
You got a friend in me.
This is on the other one, too.
This is on the worst singing back.
You got a friend in me.
When the road looks rubberhead,
and you're miles and miles from your nice, warm bed,
you just remember what your old pal said.
Boy, you got a friend in me.
Boop, boop, boop, boop, boop, boop, boop, boop, boop.
Boop, boop, boop, boop, boop, boop, boop, boop, boop, boop.
Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh.
Oh, you're playing Dark Souls?
Hey, son, what a game you're playing.
Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh.
Oh, I wonder.
The only thing I remember from Arcane was...
Oh, the misery.
Every single person is my enemy.
That's the only thing I know.
I don't know anything else.
You gotta find that mystery.
This is Scooby-Doo, coming after you.
Look, it's Scooby-Doo.
This is the fucking new Zoomer shit.
This is not what I wanted.
To the streets.
Got me up the cigarette,
cause that step shoe's on my feet.
Need to find a reason,
reason things went wrong.
Got to find a reason why my money's all gone.
Oh!
I could still get high,
and I can play the guitar
like a motherfucking riot.
Not this one, I hope not.
Scared?
That's what you want.
I'm gonna march out here and just start singing
fucking John Jingleheimer Schmidt.
What are you doing now?
You're supposed to be scared.
John Jacob Jingleheimer Schmidt.
His name is my name too.
That's bad.
Whenever we go out,
we always shout,
here comes John Jacob Jingleheimer Schmidt.
Why is this, is this in the other one too?
I'm gonna go to the bathroom quick.
This is terrible.
Sing, chat, a la la la.
Little baby don't say a word,
I'm gonna buy you a mockingbird.
If that mockingbird don't sing,
I'm gonna buy you an ironing.
If that diamond ring don't shine,
I'm gonna buy you a glass of wine.
When you get old enough, over 21.
We get an apples and bananas remix?
Are you talking about like the,
I want to eat, eat, eat,
apples and bananas.
That's what you mean?
I'd like to eat, eat, eat,
apples and bananas.
And feel like I belong.
All right, give up.
This one's good.
Way, I can go the distance.
I'll be there someday.
If I can be strong,
I know every mile
will be worth my while.
I would go most anywhere
to feel like I belong.
Well, I liked that last one.
That was pretty good.
Brother, we'll see what you think.
Ladies and gentlemen,
the winner of best singing of the year is,
I don't know if production has it ready,
but I'll just wait till you do.
Can we just play?
Can we just play it?
Do you know what won?
DMCA, no, the channel will get shut down,
but who gives a shit?
They don't have it.
Okay, it's with 31.1%, 31% of the vote is,
oh, the misery.
Okay.
At number two with 25%,
all the Hatsune Miku fans, po-pi-po.
And then Hercules, go the distance,
which was actually the good one.
That was the good one.
At 9.85%, good job, by the way.
Good job.
There you go.
But now, I do want to do something very special.
We saw them earlier.
Didn't really get a chance to show off
what they could actually do.
Feel like it's a good place to do it, though.
Ladies and gentlemen, please welcome back into the studio,
Top Shelt Vocal,
full of actual good songs here.
And I'm gonna get out of here
because I shouldn't be here.
Santa did tell me to be better.
Top Shelt Vocal, ladies and gentlemen,
with a couple of songs.
Joy to the world, the Lord is come.
Let earth receive her King.
Let every heart prepare him room.
And heaven and nature sing.
Joy to the earth, the Savior reigns.
Let men their songs employ.
Rock fields and floods, rocks, hills and plains.
Repeat the sounding joy.
He rules the world with truth and grace.
and makes the nations prove
the glories of His righteousness
and wonders of His love
and wonders, wonders of His love.
Thank you. Thank you so much for bringing us back.
For bringing some joy to the world.
We're gonna slow it down just a little bit
because tonight, we want to bring in a holy night.
O holy night, the stars are brightly shining
It is the night of our dear Savior's birth
Long lay the world in sin and error pining
Till He appeared and the soul felt its worth
A thrill of hope, the weary world rejoices
For yonder breaks a new and glorious morn
Fall on your knees
O hear the angel voices
O night divine
O night when Christ was born
O night, O holy night
O night divine
Thank you all so much.
Thank you. Yeah.
Happy holidays to all.
Thank you. Yeah, thank you for having us.
Thank you for having us.
Appreciate it.
That was absolutely unbelievable.
Thank you. Thank you.
You all out here to actually do a song.
So with that, now don't listen.
I don't want you guys to don't listen to this.
We're going to go to the next category,
which is maybe the worst singing of the year.
Maybe.
I sing, you've heard me, I've sung before a few times.
A couple times, yeah.
Here are your nominees for the worst singing of the year.
Right after that great performance.
You guys killed it.
That was fucking amazing.
Somebody said Bjrk?
What do you mean Bjrk?
I don't sound like Bjrk.
What do you mean?
All I think is like...
And then somebody says Bjrk and I'm like fuck.
That's how you can punch to the face.
All good friends and we all get together sometimes
When you're feeling down and you're feeling out of luck
And out of change
We will work together and we will have...
I'm sorry.
That's what I expected.
I expected that.
She's such a misfit
Always ready to fight
She's got a super beam
And she's raising high
If you believe you're strong
So you know the whole song?
I don't know.
I heard like a minute of it.
I think a good night song for Boba.
Boba, the kitty
Have a good rest
See you in the morning
Boba, such a good kitty
Good morning, good morning
Good morning to you all
I'm gonna take a fall
It's such a wonderful world we live in, in this nice street.
We're almost there. Here we are.
Oh, the misery
Every, every, my, every single person is my enemy.
Here it goes, here it goes.
We go from Nashville to Norway
To Zimbabwe, to Chicago, to Czechoslovakia
And back
But she'll
Fucking god damn it
The weather outside is bright
What's wrong with this?
I got fire and solar light
Since we, since we no place
Hold on
Since we no place
I'll get it. Shut up.
Since we no place to go
Let it snow, let it snow, let it snow
Use that part.
What's wrong with that? That was fine.
You've got a friend in me
Got a friend in me
Two people
Having more of a laugh than I have
That's it, right?
Alright, I'm gonna count you guys in, okay?
3, 2, 1, go
She sang over the hills
It instantly voice jammered me
Take your headphones out
Wait, wait, wait, sorry, sorry, sorry
Take out your headphones
Okay
Ready?
3, 2, 1
She sang over the hills
Peaks a shy but sure dawn
And sure as the sun rise
I'll someday be gone
But recall me my love
And our joy may live on
And you do, and you do, and you do
That's a howl at the end, that has to be a howl at the end
Some of those weren't that bad
I mean, cringe, is it like a most cringe category?
Maybe, no
I have to top shell vocal, I don't
These were close
It was pretty much every single nominee
15.5, 14.4, 13.9, 13, 12
It's all of them, you couldn't choose
But if you had to, with 15.5% of the vote, it's Bjork
Bjork wins
And then right underneath that 14.4%
Was Beatbox Oh the Misery
And then 13.9% was the Splatoon 3 Laughing Song
I mean, the Bjork
That stream I would have nominated for worst stream of the year
Is it in there?
It might be
Alright, let's count the categories
Count the categories, we've got one, two, three, four, five
We've got, what, five or six categories remaining?
These are the huge ones
These are the major, massive categories
Are you ready?
How you guys feel?
You guys in the Christmas spirit?
Holiday spirit?
Yeah?
Can you please do a Bjork?
Yeah
Pretty good
I tried
Bjork is a very talented singer, by the way
More talented than I will ever be
Times 100
Just make that clear
I have nothing on Bjork
Zero
What's that say?
That is best gamer moment of the year
Did I do good in a game?
Did I play Call of Duty versus a hacker?
Who may have been cheating, we don't know
See him for lunch or dinner on Friday
Extinguisher, if you still hear me
I like extra lettuce on my hamburgers
I like crunch
Best gamer moment of the year incoming
These are the moments that I actually did very well
Not this one
Don't look at that one yet
It's not time for that one
We're going to put that down
And we're going to show you the nominees
For best gaming moment of the year
This is when I did well
Here are your nominees
Somebody's probably actually insane
Ban that person for an hour
And then you bet a little bit there
And then maybe I'd be like
What's 50 more?
You know what I mean?
It's a nominal amount
Somebody said Elmo
What does that mean?
Jerma, you absolute idiot
Am I stupid?
Because I just won the game
That's a three of a kind
You just got shot
Were you here?
Were you in the room?
Were you in the fucking room?
I got a bet for you
And I complete my own mini golf course
In less than 20 strokes
Six
And seven
Here comes seven
Motherfuckers, you didn't think
I was going to skip the whole goddamn course?
Yes!
You all lose
Never bet against me again
What's happening?
Am I winning?
Am I beating them?
I don't know
Did I win?
Why won't he fight me?
Hurry up, run
God damn it
I knew it was a problem
I have to be off to this guy
Before he rings the alarm
Fuck, come on
Why is he so much faster than me?
I got him
I beat him
These are pretty good moments
That game is so hard
They made it too hard
Ultra kill devs if you're watching
Your game is too hard
The hardest game at Walmart
It's not even at Walmart
No, that's an old callback
The game is hard
Just to let you know
Anyways, ladies and gentlemen
The winner of best gamer moment of the year is
This was huge
44.6%
Almost 45% of the vote
The ultimate poker bluff versus Ludwig
Wins
Come on
He took all his money
He's here somewhere
He's back there somewhere
Sorry Ludwig
Beachy and poker
It's my game
And then after the first try
Cuphead DLC boss at what?
14.8%
That's not even close
And then beating
Ulcerated tree spirit early
That was so impressive
You beat the tree spirit
Who cares?
That was like 30 levels too early
I accidentally walked into that boss
So that's pretty impressive
I think
So there you go
Weirdly enough
The mini golf course
Was fourth or fifth place
People thought the Ludwig bluff was way better
And just like the good
There's also the bad
I don't remember these nominees
But they were way more than best
I think they were
We had to narrow it down
Because I think they were like
Oh wow
We had like seven nominees
For best gamer moment
And 70 for worst gamer moment
So we really had to narrow this down
Honestly
I don't even know what's on this list
I haven't seen it
I just knew we did a few passes on it
Because we had to
So here are your nominees
For just like best gamer moment
Here is the worst gamer moment
Of the entire year
Worst gamer moment
This is a nine minute category by the way
So strap in
And fire
Jesus
Give fire to the tornado
Bro there ain't no tornado on the screen
Hand the fire to the tornado
But do it quietly
Orc Minecraft fire
Me
Me build dirt house
And burn it
Is
You ten
If
None of these work
Eftensib
Ecten
Eltens
Elt
Elten
What is this word man?
What is this word?
Contestant number two
Extensible
Extensive background
Shit there's a flag right there
What is it?
Oh my god
It's Switzerland
What?
Excuse me?
Why is this thing coming alive?
Stone talus
I'm fucking dead
It's gonna do a lot of damage
Yeah it's gonna do a lot
We can try
Might as well right?
Yeah you can back out whenever it's looking rough
We get fire
Oh fuck
Ow
I'm coming I'm coming
Don't let it reset
Oh shit it killed me
No
It killed me too
What the fuck
What the hell
What the fuck are you talking about?
Is that not supposed to do that?
On my screen you're holding onto nothing
You're just floating
How long am I supposed to hold this for?
A while
Um
Um I'm gonna run out of
I'm gonna run out of grip
Hold on hold on
What?
Shit
Alright
Seven minutes including chest
I'm gonna put my headphones in and just shut the fuck up and do it as best as I can
Thirty seconds
I just ran back to the entrance
Time
Oh that's what ruined everything
Six fifty six
Nineteen
That would have been it
Oh no
Time
That was it
Yeah nine seconds alright
Yeah
Go look in here there's a fucking clock in here
Oh my god
You can lower the...
I'm getting Luigi alright
I'm getting Luigi
I'm gonna need these later
I'm taking them with me
I'm taking all these with me
Don't
What the fuck
Can I have one?
Can I please have one?
Why did it let go?
Nice
There's one other at least one other player for sure
Guys
How do I land?
How do I what?
Dude you kicking butt right now dude
Nice
I can't even
This game is fucking easy
Shit
Do not flip the car
Under any circumstance
Don't do it
It's not funny
It's not a joke
It would be annoying
Because you just wasted like thirty five straight minutes cutting wood
Jeremy
I know you think you're quite the comedian
But this is not the time to do that
Let's go
And a lot of people are gonna think that that was on purpose
But it was not
Like a utility
We're good we're good we're good
We're good we're good
Big points on the board right now
Big points
We have a replay
Review
Oh fuck I got beam I got beam
I need red I need red
Oh guys we need to get to the fucking
We need to get in the car and get the fuck out
I need res I need res
I don't laugh
Double res double res
Shit
He's not a gamer
Double res double res
Smith don't
I'm coming around
Don't shut it
Do you have a way to get out of here?
I guess you just run
Behind you
Flashbang going out
God damn it
What the fuck
Back back back back
Oh no
I don't know where the person is
Wow
Jesus
Whoa
Really?
Whoa dude
That was bad
I have to leave now
That was awful
I can't
I uh
I didn't get anything
We're in trouble
How do we
How do I solve
Half of these are from
Is there anything I can eat
That takes me to the last bonfire
How do I fix this
Into the forest
I'm so sorry
Shit
This is bad
Um
I think we're in trouble
We're in trouble
See here
Keep your eyes on the lady
Where is she gonna go
I got it
That was easy
Oh Bodo don't be feeling too bad
Ain't nobody can
What?
Wait what happened
Was I not even looking
Hey let's do the rest of this
With my fucking eyes closed
Stop making jokes
Stop
Oh my god
What am I doing
Why did I do that
I was gonna make like a joke
Where I was gonna close my eyes
And cast a spell
This hurt so bad
What the fuck are you doing
What am I doing
Why would I do that
Internally
I was so internally mad at myself
I swear to god
Kill him kill him
I can't do it
I don't know how to do it
Kill him
What
What are you doing
A lot of good ones
But there can only be one winner
I'm trying to peek
Let's see
I can't see through the envelope
Your winner
For worst gamer moment of the whole year
Actually surprising
24.4% of the vote
Kill him
I don't know how to do it
From Among Us
VR
And then at 11%
We're going way down
11.7%
Margaret is one hit away
Let's do the rest of this with my eyes closed
And then trying to land in Fortnite at 9%
Apparently that first one was so bad
I don't play Among Us
I don't play it
How was I supposed to know that
Is that
That's not
That's not a worst gamer moment
That is a
I didn't do the tutorial moment
Because I wanted to get in and hang out with my friends
And play video games
What
Is that a fucking crime
Oh boy
This is a big one
Coming up next
This is number 24 on the night
This is the worst overall stream of the whole year
Or worst stream segment
What do you think the worst stream this year was
I have few guesses
I don't know
Let me
Before you show the nominees
Oh
It's toasty
Every stream I try to have it be fun
I try to have a good time
An idea that maybe
Oh this is a new idea
Maybe this is an old idea
Every stream I want to be fun
Right
That's the whole goal
As a streamer
You want the streams to be good
Sometimes you miss the mark
And we're about to find out
How badly that mark was missed
Ladies and gentlemen
For 2022
Here are your nominees
For worst stream or stream segment of the entire year
There's one other
At least one other player for sure
This is pretty bad
Alright whatever
I don't play Fortnite
I don't play this game
I just want to hang out with some cool friends
Streamer friends
Right like what the fuck
Is that so bad
Guys
How do I land
I have what's it called
Splash
I could throw it at everyone
I've got six minis
Big pot
I don't know
I went in the dumpster
Okay for all of you
Worst stream ever Andes
Alright
I'm not going to redress it anymore
I'm just telling you
You need to respect me for a minute
This sucks
That's how you know
Excuse me
What do you mean
This was picked in pre-stream chat
This was a prank
No this is not a prank
I like people
In the pre-stream people were like
Yo dude Glover Pog
How much I'm looking at chat
The hacker wanted me to play this by the way
Which I don't know about that
This is
This is kind of
This is a PogChamp game
Dude you fell off
You can't fall off in 20 minutes
Okay
You can't fall off
I didn't fall off
It's been 15 minutes
You don't fall off in 15 minutes
Okay 20%
90%
Is Buster already made
What am I doing wrong
It's 20% and 80%
Or 10% and 90% right
Settle down it's fine
Dude this is genuinely worse than the clock
What
How is this worse than the clock
I'm doing what it says
Is what I'm supposed to be doing
If you can get it to work
It's definitely a lot better
The person was standing still
And I couldn't even kill him
I'm so bad at this game
Next point up
Let's go
That's me
That's you
Oh I thought that was a bad guy
We're good
Bye bye
See you guys later
Be blessed
Shoot
I was bought a fragger
Tell him you're the sus guy
This one was so mad
This is streamers choice
This wins
I'm about to veto this
All gone
I think I have to veto this whole thing
In the meantime
If there's any more You Laugh You Lose compilations
I'd love to watch them
Maybe just
We can get them vetted quickly or something
But I ain't watching
I'm done after this
This is a fucking bullshit idea
This is one of the worst ideas I've ever had
Figure out the Disney lyrics
Up on that beach
Up on that shore
Up on that many people galore
Makes you kind of think
I can go the distance
This was good
I'll be there someday
If I can be strong
I know every mile
Will be worth my while
I figured it out
Any of the bosses that have like the
Ludwig has it
Godric has it
Ibritas has it
They all have it
Bro that looked like battle chess
The string was so bad
Somebody just said
It was
It was fucking terrible
Oh my god
He just ruined Dark Souls 2 for me forever
No
Yes
Funny story about the Dark Souls From Software tier list
And I'm going to be honest
I got halfway through that list and internally
Wanted to stop
But you can't
It was like another three hours
It was like a four and a half hour stream
I remember getting halfway through
Scrolling down and just going
There's like a hundred bosses
I still haven't rated yet
Internally I wanted to turn the stream off
But I didn't
I powered through
And it was a mistake
Could have just played
Could have just played like Picross
And people would have been happy
Ladies and gentlemen
The winner of the worst stream of the whole year
It was close
With 27.6% of the vote
Number one
And then 26.2
All these votes count by the way
Oh I'm not going to vote
Because I don't think it counts
27.6 in one
26.2 in two
Number one
The Fortnite tournament
I think I was alive for four minutes
And the stream was like three hours long
And then baby sensory videos
Baby sensory videos right behind the 26.2
That was a bad
I thought that was so funny
When we first talked about it
Oh dude what a fun idea
I'll do baby sensory videos
I don't know
They're scary
If you've seen one
They're terrifying
It wasn't even funny
It was just
It was odd
It's just odd
You know
Okay those of you streamers out there
If you're watching
You know when you get that moment
When you're doing something
And you just go
Fuck this is bad
And I don't know what to do
I don't know how to get out of this
How do I get out of this
There has to be a way I can get out of this
And there isn't
And you have to sleep in the bed that you made
That was the baby sensory
Because I hyped that up for a week or two
Oh we're going to do baby sensory videos
It's going to be crazy
Wow we're going to talk about them
And after one or two
I wanted to turn the stream off so bad
And I was like I just want to go
I want to take a bath
I just want to get out of here
But you can't
Number three by the way was at 15%
Mythbusters the game
Yeah it wasn't very good
These are your worst streams of the year
I don't play
I don't play video games
I'm not a video gamer
I am though because Elden Ring
I beat Elden Ring
I beat Dark Souls 3
I beat Dark Souls Remastered
How can you not say that
I just
I don't play certain types of games
I don't play Fortnite
I don't play Call of Duty
Who cares?
Right?
Whatever
You know what?
Let's go check in with the elves
Follow me
Elves I'm coming to say hello
There's a noise in here
Hello
What are you doing?
Investing
We're investing the money
brainstorming
That you promised us
What do you got here?
How do you feel about investing in NLTs?
NLTs they're going to take off
NLTs
Not what you're thinking
But they're actually LTs
Yeah
That's cool we have other ideas
Gingerbread
Robots to build puzzles
Yes
You need that considering you haven't done a god damn thing
But wait a minute
I feel a little disrespectful
Clearly there's some stuff happening
You've done a border of one of them
Oh she has
Puzzle girl
You ought to just stop
I was doing it still
You wanted to give me your phone
That's good
Oops
I got a better idea
How about this?
Why do I hear Smash Brothers?
Activities
We were also playing games
You're playing games?
Alright
I tried to hide it
You play games?
You're playing games?
Alright
I tried to hide it
You play games
I'll give that a sick
Oh nice
Hey these are a thousand dollar chips
These are a thousand bucks
Not if nobody's getting these
Hey elves
Yeah
Do you think it should be snowing in here?
We're doing puzzles
Hey chat
Should we start snowing in here yet do you think?
I don't know
You're not stealing it here yet, do you think?
I don't know.
I wanna make sure I see it first.
Should it start snowing for real this time?
Snow.
Do it for puzzle girl.
Snow, snow, snow, snow, snow, snow, snow, snow, snow, snow!
Snow, snow, snow, snow, snow, snow, snow, snow, snow
snow, snow, snow, snow, snow snow, snow
lets go!
Get you!
They were bored.
You know, all my presents got deleted, you know that, right?
It's gonna be okay, it's gonna be okay.
It's gonna be okay.
Who is this from?
From all of us.
From all the elves?
The elves.
Buck doing the puzzle, by the way,
because it's literally impossible.
Okay, from the elves.
What is it?
Maybe it's...
Could it be an Xbox?
What is this?
That's the baby with the puzzle.
Hey, give it up for the elves, can we please?
Give it up for them.
Why did I do that?
It's like being at the lunch table.
We're at the lunch table.
Meatball covered in gravy and all the fucked up...
I did that stuff when I was younger.
Give it up for the elves.
They did apps to fucking lootly nothing the whole day.
That's good.
Actually, that was an experiment to see if they could actually do anything.
It was like, oh, let's get 15 elves to be in a room
and do something and make a puzzle.
They didn't even come close.
They were just drinking the whole night.
But that's fine.
That's fine.
But I mean, the snow was fine.
They were fine.
They were a good group.
Now they got to clean all that up.
I can't believe I put that in my mouth.
More puzzle, pog, pog, more puzzle.
The mic is fucked up.
Did I fuck the mic up?
Did I ruin the mic?
Mic, oh, no.
All right, we are down to the last three categories of the night.
It's been a wild night.
Maybe you've had a few alcoholic beverages.
Maybe you haven't.
Maybe you've had some tea.
But we're getting down to the last three.
And these are special.
This next one is favorite collab appearance.
I did a lot of other streams this year,
going onto other people's channels and traveling.
And there was a lot of shows that I was on that were not mine.
So this was fun.
It was actually really cool to go hang out with other streamers.
This is your favorite collab of the year,
whatever that one happened to be.
So here you go.
Here are your nominees.
We only got three more.
Favorite collab appearance outside of the channel that of you.
I can't even talk.
Of the year.
The favorite of the, of you, of the, of the.
Next contestant is definitely not photoshopped
and is very caked up.
Ladies and gentlemen, let's hear it for Jeremy.
Actually, I wasn't going to bring this up.
His podium is bigger than mine.
I want to replace Mike.
It's at least a quarter of an inch higher than mine.
He's got podium envy.
Did you not read my writer?
Let me tell you something.
You bastard.
My podium might be one or two inches bigger than yours,
but that doesn't matter.
You need to relax and go back to what you were doing.
Yeah, get back to what you're wrecked, please.
Have a seat in that, Jeremy.
Have a seat in that.
Bring that down for him, Will.
Oh!
Wow.
Yeah, the criticism.
Oh, look at that.
Okay.
37 this year.
Oh.
We are not insured for this.
The winner of Name Your Price
between Jerma and Mia
is Jerma!
Congratulations!
This is where it gets very heated
because I know you have a two right here somewhere.
And ladies and gentlemen, we did it.
There's no fucking way.
And then, like, you bet like a little bit there,
and then maybe I'd be like, you know,
what's 50 more?
You know what I mean?
It's a nominal amount.
What does that mean?
Oh, Jerma, you absolute idiot.
Am I stupid?
Because I just won the game.
That's a three of a kind.
You just got shocked!
My music's been buffering all day,
so I was going to count until it buffered,
but then the music didn't buffer this time,
so I've just been counting.
Rock.
Yeah!
You just got to get the right leverage.
Oh, my Lord.
Hercules.
We're in costume.
I'm Mercy from the Overwatch 2.
And who's that?
Hey, how are you?
It's me, Deadpool.
Nice to see everybody.
Oh, my God.
It's so good to have you here.
Yeah, special guest here.
You just missed Jerma.
Did I?
Yeah, he was a great guy.
Oh, he's a fun dude.
He's kind of a weird guy.
Kind of a weird guy.
But I just missed him.
You just missed him.
Wow.
So, hey, me and the Merc with the Mouth,
let me tell you what I'm going to do today.
I'm going to take...
We're going to make pumpkin pie.
I'll tell you what's going to happen here.
I've been waiting all week to do this one.
All right, get in there.
I don't think I made it.
I'm assuming it missed.
I can't tell.
Ooh, you know what?
My lips are dry right now.
Oh, are they?
What?
What the fuck is...
Did they get...
I just cut to Jerma doing exercise.
Wait.
Wait, what?
Did they miss that?
Yeah, it was just Jerma doing this.
Did they miss that shot?
I was preparing.
I was stretching.
Yeah, and how about you tell us
what you have in your pocket earlier?
Yeah, he's got lip balm on a Q-tip.
You're actually calling me out for this?
Yeah, pull it out, man.
I mean, it's not...
Pull it out.
So, it's...
This looks fucking weird.
I saw him using that.
That is a dab that you smoke weed out of.
No, this is not drugs.
It's in a drug baggie, but it doesn't mean it's drugs.
Jerma?
We won.
You lose, that's it.
No, you lose.
Sorry, sorry.
Hey, congratulations, guys.
Yes, thank you.
Congratulations, guys.
Thank you.
Congratulations, you guys.
I just won.
That's it.
Got it under control, though.
I'm going to land this.
It's going to be an S-tier pilot, by the way.
I want you all to do your reviews.
I want you to say thanks for the S-tier landing.
And have a great rest of your evening.
Landing show.
Okay.
Oh, my God.
Don't worry.
Jerma?
Yeah?
If we don't make it out of this one?
Yep.
I just want to let you know, you're a great pilot, okay?
Thank you so much.
This may require both of us.
All right?
By the way, I've got a bag under my back that has 50 grand in it.
What?
I'm just making sure somebody knows.
40.
Push back.
Oh, boy.
Okay, push back.
Okay.
Hold on.
To the side.
There you go.
30.
Oh, my God.
Oh, Jesus Christ.
All right.
We're okay.
We're all right.
Oh, my God.
We're good.
Oh, God.
We're on the ground.
Oh, we made it.
We made it.
Oh, my God.
I may have switched my balls.
Okay.
Hey, wait a minute.
We got a guest here.
We got the amazing Jerma.
Everybody clap.
Oh, my God.
I expect a wonderful time to see you.
Yes.
Sit here?
Yeah, you may sit there.
Okay.
Sit here.
Now, I hear you put on the biggest production of Guys and Dolls Twitch has ever seen.
Well, you know, they're close.
Who's this tweet about?
All right.
Is it a reply to Jerma985?
Or is it a reply to Super Galactic porn star Mia Malkova?
That fat, juicy ass.
Fat spelled with a P-H.
P-H.
Which is the good.
Yeah.
I'm going to say 2020.
I'm going to say this is about me.
Wow.
All right.
What do you think, Donna?
Am I missing something?
I'm going to say Mia Malkova.
I would like to say Jerma is a little full of himself.
It is Mia Malkova.
Yeah.
But I mean, that's all I have to be.
I wondered by one of that tweet of me showing my ass in the mirror.
What?
Anyway, let's take a look at some of our competitors.
Jerma, what question did you ask me earlier?
I asked you what the accelerate button was.
Who's your teammate?
You.
OK.
Let's go see how other people are doing.
Are you sipping it right now?
No.
I just opened it.
It's harder to chug a cold beer.
You know that.
But it tastes better.
You don't chug for taste.
Everything is taste.
Everything.
You can't just chug.
What do you mean, taste?
This is a typical Golden Knights fan.
They almost won the goddamn Stanley Cup the first year, by the way.
They did.
Almost.
How long ago was that?
That's not great.
You don't love that for them.
I used to do that when it turned out.
By the way, I don't really like Mario Kart.
Let me be very honest.
What?
Why did you accept doing this?
Because I think you're cool.
Really?
Yeah.
Oh, thank you.
Statistically, those ones do, actually.
No, exactly.
I'm thinking about fucking Toad in this next last round.
You want to fuck Toad?
Is that what he does?
I will say something before I open this, that thanks to all the other streamers that let
me kind of participate in their shows, because it's fun.
And I hope that you liked it.
I hope you thought it was fun, maybe me participating in everything.
I did a lot of stuff this year.
So there's a lot of people doing really, really cool shit on these platforms.
So it's an honor to be able to participate and have fun.
So thank you.
Thank you to all these nominees, everybody that's in here.
It's been a lot of fun.
It has.
Thank you.
I actually do mean that.
Thank you so much for letting me be part of your cool shit.
But what was everybody's favorite?
They're all good.
What do we got here?
Who was the favorite collab of the year?
Ladies and gentlemen, it is...
Ooh, close.
28% of the vote.
And then two was 25.6.
Number one was Tommy Time with Critical, which was so much fun.
That whole group is so awesome.
That was an unbelievable experience.
Name your price with Austin Show at number two.
And then Bro versus Bro, Bro versus Bro, with Ludwig, Bro versus Bro.
Ludwig is here.
So Ludwig, you came in third place on Best Collab Stream.
I don't know if he's even here anymore.
But yeah, that means a lot.
It means a lot to be able to be a part of other people's shows.
I hope I made them more fun.
And if I didn't, then maybe I won't get a callback.
All right.
Don't get sentimental.
Don't start crying.
There's a lot of people watching you.
You've probably heard that weird burp.
We're getting to the last two categories.
There's only two left.
There's Best Overall Stream or Series and Best Overall Event.
We can start with this one here.
It's been kind of a wild year and there's a lot to go over.
So I guess I don't need to introduce this too much.
This is the nominees for the Best Stream or Stream Series of the year.
And here they are.
You guys are losing your fucking minds.
It's not a log splitter.
What the...
What is happening in this chat room?
Look up a Google image of a log splitter.
I'm fucking freaking out right now.
Log splitter.
He's a based socialist.
Ow.
Job!
What?
What the fuck?
What am I supposed to do?
Guys, blue flash means an attack is unpairable.
Guys, when Ben Franklin was writing up the fucking Declaration of Independence,
there was no Guggerda Guggerda in there.
Oh yeah, we also need to make sure to leave some room for Guggerda Guggerda Guggerda Guggerda Guggerda Guggerda.
There's no room for that, Ben.
Where are the jokes?
They bemoaned, they screamed, they gnashed their teeth and said, entertain us.
Right?
Is it there?
Alright.
What?
The dev.
The dev is even sick of this joke.
The dev is like, alright, it's kind of funny, but like, fucking hurry up.
Whoa, watch out!
My thumb!
Hold on.
Ow!
Hold on, I can't see.
The camera got messed up.
Steve, go on the road.
You're driving on the wrong side of the road, Steve.
Steve, you need to be on the right side of the road.
Otherwise, my fucked up plan is you're stuck in the middle.
Steve, you're stuck in the middle of the road, Steve.
It's too dark!
I need a handful.
Disgusting.
I'm kind of curious.
I'm curious.
Let's go.
It tastes like hamburger meat.
I can't even eat it now.
Oh, why'd you do that?
This was S.
I was going to put it in S.
And now I'm like, there's a pregnancy test in my mouth.
What the fuck?
I don't know why I just felt like I was being held hostage.
This is fucking weird.
I would...
This is weirdly...
Oh no, I don't have to do anything because I have magic.
All the people that aren't magic need to do all the work.
This game's for fucking kids.
I don't give a fuck.
I'm playing a fucking kids game and you guys are fucking shit in the fucking chat.
Yeah.
Okay.
Pickle nose.
Did you fucking say that?
Oh shit.
Oh, this is bad.
This is bad.
Um, I think we're in trouble.
I think we're in trouble.
Whoa!
Oh shit, it's gonna break.
Stop doing the Mario.
I'm sorry.
I'm sorry, everybody.
I'm so sorry.
Just doing the Mario thing.
That person's trashed.
I didn't call it a cookie.
In a few minutes, we'll tell you about a $40 million giveaway promotion.
You can get a fabulous rocket ship for a friend and settle during the next few minutes.
No way.
No.
But try to flip and food flops.
Try to grip and food drops.
Shit face.
I'm telling you, shit face.
You need to flip or turn.
Are you about to win?
Oh, it's Seattle.
God damn it.
What?
Houston.
The space needle was just on there.
What is it?
There's a flag right there.
Oh my God.
It's Switzerland.
How many times do you have to do this routine?
The troll too yell.
What?
Whoa!
I think I saw somebody's dick.
What was that?
That was weird.
What's going on?
Oh, fuck.
I'm flying far and quick.
Wait, did I save it?
Dude, yeah.
That fucking face squat.
God damn it.
Excuse me?
Whoa!
What's happening?
Somebody's stabbing me.
What?
What happened?
Dude, this is illegal.
That's illegal.
Oh my God.
Hurry up.
Hurry, hurry.
I just shit my pants.
What?
My popularity is dwindling.
How am I supposed to do anything when everybody just attacks me?
What the fuck do you want me to do?
Where'd he go?
I missed.
This was so fun.
Just a psycho.
I'm sorry.
No, I don't mean it.
I don't.
All right.
You can arrest me.
I don't know.
This is weird.
Everybody looking at me.
Don't look at me.
What the fuck?
That's like a monster.
I was trying to snap his neck.
I was trying to strangle him.
I'm trying to strangle him.
Hey, give me that gun, motherfucker.
Back.
God, I'm so sorry.
Holy shit.
That was like the worst thing that's ever happened to me.
He just stole Austin Powers' mojo.
Jesus.
Give me a fucking brick.
That was fucked up.
That was actually pretty fucked up.
Score.
I'm sorry.
I can't do it.
What is powering?
We have one minute and 15 seconds to go this way.
So we're going to go up.
Where did you go?
We're going up.
What the hell?
Oh, coffee.
Oh, Cheeto.
Roadie bitch.
Get off the fucking barrel.
Get off the barrel.
That was awful.
I don't like this.
I hate this.
Oh, holy shit.
People are so ugly with light, aren't they?
Holy shit.
People are so ugly.
Look at it.
All right.
Oh, Jeremy, you look real handsome today.
You sure about that?
Oh, no.
He killed that guy.
What?
Oh, my God.
I am so confused right now.
There you go.
I told you it was real.
Hey, let's do the rest of this with my fucking eyes closed.
Don't make a joke.
Stop.
Oh, my God.
What am I doing?
I put you up in a meat grinder.
And the only thing that comes out that's left of you is your eyeball.
You're probably dead.
Now, I don't get that move at all.
That move is absolutely unbelievable.
It's one of those moves that you can't do anything about.
And I'm telling you, yeah.
But you know what else is as ridiculous as that?
Yeah, like we're going to get planes soon.
They're going to be like I could fly eventually, too.
So those are your nominees for best stream or stream series of the year.
I feel like there are a lot of good ones.
I feel like there was a lot of fun this year.
I say that every year, but I do mean it.
And let's see.
I'm going to start crying on camera.
Right?
I'm going to start crying.
I'm going to cry.
It's going to happen.
Just wait.
All right.
Ladies and gentlemen, the what you have decided was the best stream or stream series of the year.
Oh, the misery.
No.
Elden Ring at 27.2 percent.
And let me tell you, it makes sense considering I streamed that game for almost two straight months.
There was a high chance it was going to be Elden Ring because it was a third of every stream I did this year.
And also a game of the year, by the way.
Elden Ring at 27.2.
Underneath that is infomercial React Andy.
I'm going to have to do more of those React Andy streams because OK.
And then I didn't even beat Breath of the Wild yet, but Breath of the Wild number three.
By the way, this is second most least skipped category.
So people wanted to vote for this.
But Elden Ring, obviously Elden Ring swept everything, swept the game awards, swept my awards.
Right.
So obviously it's going to win.
And it was so fun.
Those are some of the honestly those are some of the funnest streams I had.
I think ever on the channel.
That game just had so many fun moments.
Once in a generation, you get it.
All right.
Ladies and gentlemen, it is time.
We are approaching the final category, which it's a small category, but it's fun to do.
The last category of the evening is best overall stream event.
There was only about four or five this year.
I love doing events.
I think they're fun.
Get people together.
Have a good time.
This is an event.
Can't vote for this, though.
But hey, maybe you can next year.
Hey, maybe jot it down for, you know, best event of the year.
The German 95 holiday Christmas stream.
But yeah, this is going to be it.
This is the last category of the evening is what you thought the best stream of the year was.
That was an event stream.
We did non-event.
Here is event.
Here are your nominees.
Most least.
So what I've decided to do is over the last few months, we've scoured the country.
Trying to find who I think could potentially be able to replace me.
And a little bit of Ashby.
All right.
Great.
And another one here.
Ashby.
All right.
Then we got a little.
Might be a little too much.
A little bit too much Ashby.
I would pull back on Ashby.
Pull back on Ashby.
All right.
You got it.
Everybody had three jokes.
The rats.
We're the rats.
We pray.
At night, we stalk.
At night, we're the rats.
You think you can beat me?
I know I can beat you.
I don't know what I'm going to beat you at.
Oh, you know you can beat me.
I will.
Go ahead and cue the music.
Good luck.
Weird monopoly man.
Swedish monopoly man.
What is planned?
You guys synchronized this?
10 years.
We've had TF2.
Look at me.
That's me.
I just want you to know.
You can Google all that.
He knows nothing.
I could tell who it was the whole time.
What?
Oh.
You shot.
Good job.
You shot him.
You're not.
You just got it.
Hey everybody.
What's going on?
It's me, the sus guy.
I've been muted this whole time.
It feels weird.
Emergency meeting.
We can watch the door.
We'll watch the door.
You take care of your task.
No one's coming through this.
You're safe.
It's these two.
It's definitely these two.
No.
It's these two.
Help.
Okay.
So press the, what do you have?
An index?
A button?
Kill him.
I can't do it.
I don't know how to do it.
Kill him.
I can't do it.
I don't know how to do it.
Kill him.
How do you do it?
Do it.
Kill him.
I don't know how to do it.
30 seconds before you can kill.
What?
What are you doing?
I agree.
Get this guy out of here.
How do we get, how do we get, how do we get this guy out of here?
I turned around.
Criken jump scared me.
No one's listening.
I'm listening.
Okay.
I should probably be on this camera.
No.
He, he.
I should look directly at you.
Okay.
All right.
It's my birthday.
Everyone quiet.
Sir.
Happy birthday.
So.
By the way, can I just say.
I should be on the live camera for this one.
No.
This is.
We have 47 seconds.
There's only 40 seconds.
Welcome to Car Shield Field where we have Germa Baseball Association action for you
tonight.
A big time matchup between the California Circus and the Maryland Magicians.
Do you like that, that call from Elbertson behind home plate?
Sometimes you're not sure where the pitch missed, Elbertson always lets you know.
Big magic slowly.
Oh.
What a play.
Oh, we got a first pie in the face.
Oh.
Elbertson.
Pie in the face.
The circus.
What did that play call dad because.
Oh, and he is tossed.
Is this.
Oh.
We, we've got a streaker.
We've got a streaker ladies and gentlemen.
Before the JVA, the math may be a little bit off.
Look at this.
He's pulled it down the line.
It's fair.
Elbertson speeding past first.
He's thinking two.
Throw comes in the second.
Oh, he takes a quick turnaround and a good decision by crew chief Elbertson.
He rules himself safe at first.
And that one's in for the call strike.
Oh, two.
And oh my goodness.
Everyone clearing the.
Clearing the bench.
For the Magicians.
Oh my goodness.
This is bad.
Feed him to the lions.
Yeah.
Feed him.
Feed him to the lions.
Don't you think?
But you know, it's not Yahoo.
And what's not cool.
Drugs and alcohol.
For the organ, Steve.
Let's go.
You can see my dick.
If you want to see it.
Freeze it.
Yahoo.
I can't.
Oh, man.
You guys are unbelievably funny.
All right.
Let's get it.
The winner of best event of the year.
It's only about four or five of them.
So let's see.
It's going to be close.
It's not close.
It's not close at all.
Forty two point seven percent of the vote is the German Baseball Association.
And then the suss guy finally plays among us above who will replace me, which the suss
guy was twenty four point five percent and who will replace me at nineteen point four.
This was also the least skipped category of the year.
People wanted to vote for this.
And that's it.
So I am going to say good night.
Thanks, everybody, for watching.
It's been an unbelievable experience.
Before we go, before we go, I got to thank a lot of people.
But let's go ahead.
You know, we got them here and they're incredibly talented.
Let's bring out Top Shelf Vocal again.
You guys are so good.
We're not going to just not do this.
A lot of time and a lot of work and a lot of energy went into this.
I know people didn't expect.
Oh, well, you didn't do your award show.
Whatever.
OK, cool.
Like you do every year.
A lot of people were involved.
And I do want to say thank you to a very specific few people.
Let's bring off brand out Ludwig, Atrioc, Nick Stans.
Stans is not here right now because obviously, you know, his shoulder got a little screwed
up.
But seriously, guys, it was a fucking blast.
Always a pleasure to work with you guys.
You guys are amazing.
Let's bring off brand, everybody.
There they are.
You know who all these people are.
And then BTS, Beyond the Summit.
Working back and forth with Beyond the Summit was you guys have been some of the easiest
production company to work with ever.
Tons of I know I'm a fucking weirdo and I know that we had a lot of phone calls about
what the hell was going to happen here.
So I huge appreciate it.
You guys are amazing.
Come on out.
If we get some of you guys to come out.
Dakota, especially.
I want Dakota.
I want the elves out here, too.
Elves.
You probably can't see them anymore.
But top shelf vocal is good.
Yeah.
Come on to the front.
What an incredible 2022.
Oh, Bugleberry.
Bugleberry, you're OK.
Are you serious?
Did you make it out of the portal?
You made it out of the portal.
Bugleberry made us cookies.
Bugleberry.
Bugleberry, please give me a hug.
I'm so glad you made it out safely.
Thank you everybody for watching.
This was a wild day.
Huge thanks.
All I can say is let's move forward to 2023.
Yeah.
Merry Christmas.
Happy New Year.
If we don't see you next week, we'll see you very soon.
Anybody want a cookie?
One, two, three, one.
We love you.
I can't hear Ludwig.
Glad tidings we bring to you and your kin.
Glad tidings for Christmas and a happy new year.
We won't go until we get some.
So give me it right now.
Glad tidings we bring to you and your kin.
Glad tidings for Christmas and a happy new year.
I can't hear Ludwig.
Glad tidings we bring to you and your kin.
Glad tidings for Christmas and a happy new year.
We won't go until we get some.
So give me it right now.
Glad tidings we bring to you and your kin.
Glad tidings for Christmas and a happy new year.
We won't go until we get some.
So give me it right now.
Glad tidings we bring to you and your kin.
Glad tidings for Christmas and a happy new year.