How you doing? Good afternoon. I hope you're having a good day today. I hope you had a good last four or five days.
I've been pretty good. It's been kind of a wild couple of weeks, wouldn't you say? This is a normal streamer voice.
Geode Andy, that's me. Geode Andy.
500,000 follower Andy, what'd I do? What did that happen? Where do you see that? That's not- no, no, it's not. No, it's not.
I'm at 499.
097.
499,000.
That's not 500. You just made me celebrate for something that's not even real. Is that a lot?
That's a lot, right?
That's a lot.
500,000 followers? How many subs did I have on YouTube? On the main channel?
700,000? Well, that's a lot. Yeah, that is a lot. Not even seven figures laughing my ass off.
Hey, we're halfway to seven figures. That's what you meant to say.
Hey, hey, the glass is half full. Glass is not half. Empty glass is half full.
Now give me some more orange juice or I'm gonna complain to the fucking manager.
So we just gave 10 subs. Hey, Tangie. Hey, Tang Dynasties. Thanks for the 10 subs.
So, um, we have- there's a lot of shit we have to talk about. A lot of things to discuss.
I feel like this is like a company update stream. This is like a business update company
newsletter stream. That's what this is gonna be.
First of all,
thank you for the insane support on the last stream. That's a number- we broke over 50,000 concurrent viewers.
Which that's fucking insane. That's- I can't even- that's a-
That's like double what the highest view count I've ever had was. It's remarkable. I can't even- I can't even believe it.
And yes, I had- I know we- we were not prepared for the, uh, the enthusiasm, I guess,
for the Grotto Beast stuff.
But I know everybody has a ton of questions about Grotto Beast. Like, from every angle, it's like,
Hey, hey, tell us more about Grotto Beast. Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait. Hit the brakes for a second.
There-
Just hit the brakes. I know everyone's really excited about it. I can't- we- just give me a few weeks.
Please. I- trust me when I say I want to be screaming about the stuff.
But I- we can't- we have to just wait a few weeks. Give me a few weeks. We're still-
I need like a company policy fucking generic PR statement. Where do I get it from?
I need a- I need a generic company PR statement. Let me Google one.
Generic PR statement.
Okay, let's see. Generic PR statement. We've got to get a good one here, because just- I can't- how do I word this?
What you- when you- how to make a statement to the media?
Free press release template. This one says talk is cheap.
Anyways.
Just- just hold off for a little bit. There's tons of projects in the works. There's tons of announcements that I have. Lots of them.
There are probably five projects that are in the works, and these are not things you're gonna see a year from now.
This stuff is hitting the ground running, and there's gonna be major, major shit to talk about over the next three weeks.
Which leads me to the next thing we're about to talk about.
So because of the amount of projects that are being worked on, and the amount of stuff that's happening- remember, 2020 got all fucked up here.
A ton of projects got moved to 2021. I have to get this medical stuff under control. I have to.
It's getting to a point now where there's so many interesting things that are gonna be happening over the next six months.
I have to get a procedure done. I have to do it.
So,
I hate- I hate- I hate- I don't want to say it, but I have to. I have to go on another break.
Because I'm gonna be doing a bunch of doctors appointments, and I'm actually gonna try as hard as I can to get a procedure done.
I'm probably gonna get injections, whether that's intercostal injections or trigger point injections into my back area, into my chest area.
We have to try a real treatment plan here.
Because there's too many things going on this year that I have to not be like,
Ah! Ah! Ah, hold on. Yeah, give me a minute. Ah!
I can't- yeah, I gotta sit down for like an hour.
There's too much shit going on. I have to take care of this.
So, this is- I'm not gonna go on break for as long as I did last time. Last time was to make sure I didn't have anything
really major or horrible
going on. I spent like two or three months
somewhere in the middle of 2020.
That was to rule out everything that could have been really bad, and we did.
So, I came back. I changed my kind of streaming policy. It helped a lot.
That like four to six hours instead of like seven to eight hours, it really was helpful.
But now it's time to actually get a- I need- I need to get something done. I have to get a procedure done.
So, the next- I would assume probably three weeks, and this is not- this is not three weeks into two months, I promise.
I'm going to go get something done, and I will be back. And I'll be back on-
This is not intentional, but you know, I'm- I'm- please, trust me what I say. Me coming back on April 1st is
not like a joke stream. I'm coming back on April 1st.
So,
maybe- maybe I will do something. I don't know. Just keep an eye out.
But this whole break is not to have something weird happen on the 1st. Something weird probably just will happen on the 1st.
So, I want to make sure that's out there.
I have a lot of personal stuff. I have a lot of family stuff, and medical stuff.
That- I need- I gotta close the book on this shit. That's TLDR.
Now, what this means for you is,
when I come back,
we're- I probably shouldn't do this on the 1st. I'm gonna have like four announcements.
Like major announcements. I don't- I shouldn't do- should I do that on the 1st of April?
I feel like people think that was a joke.
Maybe I'll do it on the 2nd of April.
Okay, so April 2nd, you can expect a bunch of major announcements.
So, I'm not gonna do this on the 1st. Save the announcements for after. Do it on the 1st. That'll be funny.
It's gonna be wicked funny, but I- let me just- I have to be very clear. I'm
overwhelmed by this shit that you guys have been saying. It's- everyone's been so
supportive. I've seen so much, like- I think at one point,
this stream was trending on Twitter, like number two in the United States.
When I was told that, I was like, you're a liar. That didn't happen. It was a joke. You made that up.
It's like, no. I was getting like sent screenshots and shit. It's like, what the fuck is going on?
And I'm really, really also happy to see that-
that Nevada Science Center. A lot of you guys are supporting
those guys, and they were so, so nice to do that. They put up with a lot of my bullshit.
So, I'm really happy to see you guys are actually supporting them. So, it's really good to see.
So,
TLDR,
tons of major shit that you're gonna hear about on April 2nd. I'll be back on April 1st.
I'll see you later. Alright, goodbye. No, I'm just kidding. We're not gonna stop there. We're gonna chill today.
I'm gonna play Picross, and I'm gonna not answer any questions at all about anything,
because I can't. So, let's just hang out for a while. Just leave already.
Just leave.
No, I can't leave right now. I'm here. I'm right here.
Somebody said that- did somebody say that was a really shitty direct? Can you imagine if that was a direct? Is this-
like, Doug Bowser comes on the screen. He's like, alright, so, I mean, I can't really talk about any of this stuff,
but like, I mean, like, Mario's cool.
We got this Mario guy, and like, I mean, you might see him. Maybe. I don't know. I don't have any fucking idea.
Thanks for all the support, guys, on like, Mario 2.
It's like a 10-minute thing of him just bumbling around, just not answering questions.
He's actually- he's like, somebody Google me a generic PR statement in front of, like, a
gray-white background where he's just sitting there, like, green-screened in. You're so handsome. I'm not even on screen.
Do you think your surgeon will recognize you as the Among Us guy? I hope so.
Although, maybe not. I kind of hope not. Don't you feel like he would, like, deliberately kill me?
Oh, you're the Among Us guy. Yeah, that's me. Oh, wow.
He's like the, like, the gas and like the, like, the anesthesia's going in. I fucking hate that meme.
You're never gonna wake up again. I'm just like,
right before- I gotta get my, I gotta get my last thing out right before I die.
I'm just right before I go out. I'm like,
that was pretty sus.
We get a face cam? No. Why did you moan?
No, that was like, I'm going under from the anesthesia.
Like, nobody- you don't know what sound you make when you're under anesthesia, when you go, like, have surgery.
They make you count back for some ten, and then you just wake up in a bed.
You don't- who knows what you could be- sound you can make, and it's like,
ugh, or, ooh, or, ugh.
Those of you that have had anesthesia before, you just, like, you're sitting there.
Okay, I'm lying here. I'm ready. I guess I- I guess- I'm- I woke up in a bed. Oh.
What happened? Oh, it's done. Oh.
All right, weird.
Who knows what sound you make? I mean, stop, stop. What? Like, in a hospital.
Don't get too excited that I'm not playing Heroes of Might and Magic 3.
I'm just playing the soundtrack for you.
A lot of people really just got really excited because that's the intro to Heroes of Might and Magic.
It's like, no, we're playing Picross. That's one of the nice OST.
Oh my god, he's gonna minimize and he's gonna be in the next campaign!
So we're gonna play Picross and just chill. I can't wait to talk about some of these things.
Play- play Heroes. No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no. We'll do that when I- I don't know. I don't know.
We'll do it when I come back.
Yeah, what's that now? Let me just get back to- let me- let me figure out how to play this game again.
I think it's a cloud save file.
Let's do this one. Open this one. Can I open this? There we go.
So if you don't know how to play Picross, let me show you how it's done. I actually don't- I forget everything.
It's gonna- we're gonna take some learning here. It's been years since the last Picross stream.
Um, it's been, I don't know, like maybe like six, eight months? He's doing a tuber voice again.
What are you talking about? What do you mean? I'm not doing a tuber voice right now.
Stop getting in my head. So if you don't know how to play Picross, we'll do a quick TLDR first of all.
So these are squares that need to be filled in. So there needs to be 13 squares filled in on this
column, right? A row is this way. I don't know where they are. I just know there's 13 of them,
but I can deduce with logic, reasoning, and skill that I know where these could be, and it makes a picture.
Eventually, it makes a picture. Thanks for the tutorial. Everyone knows how to play Picross.
Oh really? Because when I played it a year ago, everyone was like, what is this garbage? Get it off the screen.
And then half of you got addicted to it the next day. So let me deduce here. So if this- how many- what is it? 15 by 15?
So that means that there has to be- this has to be correct. 1, 2, 3, 4, 5, 6, 7, 8, 9, 10, 11, 12, 13, 14, 15.
Therefore, these middle ones have to be here. So now we have- we can- we can do some deduction.
Or can we? I'm not sure. So only four in this row. Can I do anything- and by the way,
but for those of you that have never played this before, if there is a space between numbers,
it means there has to be at least one space in between. Has to be. So for instance, if one was
right here, there would have to be a space for the next one. Have to be. That was incorrect.
Deduction Andy. Is your mother approved of this game? My mother plays this game, so I'm sure she does.
What about color? Color doesn't matter. Is it custom map? Oh yeah, oh yeah. Well, I'm just
gonna get back into the swinging things. We'll play the custom ones. We'll go in the workshop.
So it's 15. So 8, 9, 10, 11. So that means- hold on, let me see. I always hate when I don't get a
bunch of free ones down here. I need the bingo free space down here. 4, 1, 3, 3, 1.
This could be the 1. Single 8 means one square in the middle. Yeah, right. 1, 2, 3, 4, 5, 6, 7, 8.
1, 2, 3, 4, 5, 6, 7, 8. 1, 2, 3, 4, 5, 6, 7, 8. Right, okay. So that has to be where-
one of them has to be here. Has to be. Your mom plays this? This is Jeremy's mom playing.
It's pre-recorded. Is this too hard? It's not too hard. Trust me when I say it isn't.
Oh, what have I got? 10 here. 11. 5 and- hmm. The second 8. Oh, where is it? Where is it? Okay, here we go.
Yeah, because that's 8. Has to be 1 here. Then we got these two. This is part of the 5.
Has to be right. So 1, 2, 3, 4, 5. Or 1, 2, 3, 4, 5. I wonder. 3 and the 8. Oh, here we go. Yep.
Right, right, right. This is the 2. Alright, bingo. So check this out. See what we have just deduced?
Do you see what we just deduced? This has to be that 2. Block it off. There's your 2.
Now, 1 is somewhere over here. Are you guys excited about this yet?
Then that means 1, 2, 3, 4, 5. 1, 2, 3, 4, 5. This has to be right here. So this is part of the 1.
Check that out. This is one of the 1s. Because it can't be 1 here. So 1, 2, 3, 4, 5. Or 1, 2, 3, 4, 5.
You got it. You're understanding it. I'm gonna drop a deuce. He-he-he-he-he. Alright, that's funny.
That's wicked funny. Did you catch the game last night? Did you have any hot fudge sundaes?
What grade are you in school? The brain hurts. Flap, flap. Let's go, let's go. This is a boomer game.
Yeah, well, I just told you I wanted to relax today. I wanted to tell you about some of the important
projects going on and the fact that I'm literally taking a 3-week break. Alright, what do I do?
Okay, I know I gotta tell them I'm like, I'm like taking like medical leave again. Oh, what?
Should I, should I play Picross for like a few hours and like tell them I'm leaving? Oh shit,
hold on. Wait a minute. This is important. 1, 2, 3, 4, 5. 1, 2, 3, 4, 5. Bingo. Check this out.
1, 2, 3, 4, 5. 1, 2, 3, 4, 5. It's got to be like here. It has to be here. This is part of the
four. It has to be somewhere in here, the five. Bingo. Tell mom to stream in your absence.
I would, my mother would take one second on the stream and look over and be like,
son, why do you do this? Why? Did you see what they were saying? And I'd be like, ma, ma, ma,
money. It's not, what do you mean money? I didn't raise you like that to care about money.
Be like, ma, ma, just, just relax. I'm making money. No, no, you're supposed to do it because
you love it and you love doing it. No, no, no. Oh, remember when you first made your first
YouTube video, how much you thought that was fun and how you were just doing it for fun.
Yeah, time to change, ma. No, not the son that I made. Ma, ma, get out of here, ma. You don't get
it. No, my son. And then I have a really deep realization like in like 45 minutes later in the
movie and I like understand now and I go back to like, like how I began and I like do it because
I love it. That's after I throw her in the volcano. By the way, just want to make sure you guys
understand where we are in the movie. Spoilers. All right, let's keep going. Let's get, we got to,
we got to deduce this. So this is part of the four. So if, okay, hold on. So this is the part
of the four. That means it has to be two ones after this. That means it would have to be,
it'd have to be this, right? This has to be where it is because there's no way this,
the four will fit. So this has to be the four. There you go. These are done. Pretty cool. Now
here we go. Perfect deduction. Ladies and gentlemen, ladies and gentlemen. Oh my God,
I'm sorry. I don't know what the fuck's wrong with me. It's supposed to be a winding down
hangout stream where I tell you them. All right. So one, two, three, four. It cannot possibly be
higher than that. And it also cannot possibly be lower than this. Two, three, four. So here you go.
Ain't nothing over here, but it could be up here. This is also has to be part of the four. Therefore
one, two, three, four, nothing. It can't be over here. One, two, three, four. It could be
there, right? Technically. This is where it gets interesting. So this is part of the three,
the one, two, three, or one, two, three. This has to be the second three because one, two, three,
even if it was this way. Oh no. No, no, no, no, no. It could be that. I don't know that
for certain. I can't be certain of that. I'm too dumb to understand this. Do the eight column.
Oh, right. We've got some more info here and here. So this has to be part of the eight.
I guess it doesn't have, what does it? One, two, three, four, five, six, seven, eight. It does.
Okay. Does that give us any more info here? This is either two or the three.
This is the two. I feel like I'm in a zoom meeting, zoom class.
You know what? That is the worst insult ever. That's such an insult. Like it just is.
That's a perfect insult. You didn't say this stream sucks. You didn't say like, oh wow,
this is kind of boring. You said this is like a zoom meeting, dude. And it's like, that's
the worst thing where you could have described this at all as the teacher. All right. So let's
see. One, two, three, four, five, one, two, three, four, five could also go down here.
Yeah. We can do this one down here as well. One, two, three, four, five, six, seven. Therefore.
So these are good. One, two, three. Okay. So this is part of the two, which means this is
probably done. Yeah. That's definitely the two, which therefore this is gone. This has to be the
two, right? There's no way this is the three. This has to be the two. Look at how much we're
learning here. No, no, wrong, wrong, wrong. No, no, no. What do you mean? What, what, what?
Wait, wait, wait. What are you talking about? What's wrong? One, two, three, four, five.
One, two, three, four, five. Yeah. It could be, it has to be these three. I had it right.
This could be the five. Oh, wait. You're right. Because this could be like that. I see what you
mean. Okay. Yeah. Actually, I don't know that info. You're right. This is, this is not, this is the
three. Because there's no way this is the five. This is definitely part of the three.
So if it was one, two, three, there you go. Bingo. Okay. I don't know that for certain yet.
This teacher sucks. There are 12,000 people here. Yeah, I know. I'm, I'm, we're doing a,
but yeah, welcome everybody. All right. Where else can I go here? Can't do anything in here.
Or can I? Make a sentry noise so they don't leave. Well, if they're going to leave,
they're going to leave. I can't, I can't tell them, but they have to stay here.
You better not leave. Just make that really clear. Better not. What do you mean? Well, what if I
leave? Well, then you're going to miss something huge in the next 10 minutes. I'm going to play my
own Picross game so I don't get the urge to yell at you. Yeah. Pull it up, man. Let's go. All right.
Let's go down over here. So this is part of the five. There's a one over here somewhere.
Or one, one, two, three, four, one, two, three, four,
two. It could be either this way or this way. And it could be these two as well.
This is one of the threes. It could be either side because this is part of the three or the four.
Damn it. What about this eight? One. Oh yeah. Yep. Yep. Yep. Wait, wait, wait, wait.
Cause we, we made some more room here. So one, two, three, four, five, six, seven, eight.
One, two, three, four, five, six, seven, eight. Oh shit. All right. Look at that.
We shaved off some space here. This is the five and the other eight as well. Can I do that though?
One, two, three, four, five, six, seven, eight. One, two, three, four, five, six,
seven. I don't have enough info for that. I don't think you dismiss us already. No, you're stuck here.
Well, I can do this though. So this is the three, which means one, two, three has to be here.
That's one, two, three, one, one, two, three, or one, two, three. Therefore this has to be one,
two, three, one, two. I don't know the info on that yet. Nevermind. I don't have the info.
The bell rang. Stay in your seats. Stay in your seats. All of you have detention now.
Every single person in the room in the class has detention. All of you. None of you are going
anywhere. You all have detention. Teacher, I'm hungry. No snacks allowed in my classroom either.
Bell doesn't dismiss us. Jerma does. I need to go to the bathroom. Well, sorry. The weird key
attached to the giant wooden plank that has the bathroom key on it is out right now. You're gonna
have to wait till Jerry comes back. All right. Let me focus. This is part of the five. I need
the top one here. I'm going to beat Jerry up. Well, now you're suspended. Not only do you have
detention, now I'm suspending you. Five. All right. Fuck. Pay attention. It's been a while
since I played Picross. I gotta get this right. Three, two, three, five. I feel like I can do
something here. One, two, three. Okay. I can do that. Oh, wait. Hold on. Yep. We can do this too.
Yep. All right. So here we go. Look at that. There's no way it could be eight here.
There's no way it could be. Yeah. Okay. So let's let's go over here. So we have one, two, three,
four. One, two, three, four. Fuck. One, two, three, four, five, six. One, two, three, four,
five, six. There it is. Six. There it is. Oh, there it is. Genius. The picture sucks. Well,
you don't even know what it is yet. You can't know that yet. What does that do here? This has to be
the three. So it needs to be one, two, three, or one, two, three. Well, that's the only thing
I can deduce from there. Now this is part of the four. So one, two, three, four. Sorry. It ain't
there. One, two, three, four. One, two, three, four. Okay. Teacher, I have to go. I have to go
to the bathroom. Look. Do you all have to go to the bathroom? Everybody has to go to the bathroom?
Well, I don't know how. There's how many stalls and how many urinals are in the bathroom? I don't
know. Jerry's vaping. I can see. Oh, Jerry's vaping. I can see him out the window. He's out
there like behind one of the trees outside the school vaping. Oh, no. What's he doing? What's
he doing? Oh, no. He's spinning around. He's spinning around. He's got the wooden key to the
bathroom. Oh, he just threw it up on the roof. You little shit. He's running. He's gone. He's
taken. Someone's going to call his mom. Okay. Um, well, let me, let me come over here and call the
janitor. Pick up the phone. Pick up the office phone. Yeah. We're going to need the janitor to
come down here. We need another key to the bathroom. Jerry, you always, you always just making
trouble. Okay. So where are we? Eight. I do any more here? I think, yeah, I can. The same exact
thing. Ooh, I did it. That's a three. Four is part of the five. Wiggly. Oh my God. I'm not even
paying attention. I'm getting so many subs. What the? Don't swear. Stop swearing. Oh my God.
Imagine, look, people stream themselves doing all kinds of wild shit. Imagine a teacher streaming
and like thanking subs in the middle of the class. Hey, nuclear waffle. Thanks for the 25 community
subs. It cutesy. Thanks for the 10 community subs. Lone K five community subs. Tank top typhoon,
five community subs. AWP five community subs. 25 community subs from Wiggly Joe. 25. Thank you.
Anyways, Genghis Khan, when he claimed, when he took over China, he was,
all right, guys, I got some subs. So give me a minute. You would never learn anything in that
classroom. Nothing. It would just be the teacher shouting out subs. That was a recycled doctor
joke. There's a bunch of new people here. I can recycle old material like a doctor doing surgery.
Okay. So the sick, the row of six, take a look at this. This is really interesting. Those of you
that don't know how to play this game. So I have blocked off places where there's no way it could
be six. There's not enough space for it. So it has to be down here. Therefore one, two, three, four,
five, six. You love when that happens, don't you? Don't you just love when that happens?
The row is done here and now we have more info. So if you understand this, now this has to be
one of the fours. Take a look at that. Absolutely clean. This is the three over here. So this has
to be part of the five. Really cool. Really, really cool that we're able to deduce that,
deduce that. This is part of the four. Therefore one, two, three, four, can't be over here. One,
two, three, four, can't be over here. What does that do for us here, folks? What does that do for
us here, class? What are you doing? How long does this bit last? This is not, there's no bit. I'm
playing pick-ross. You hate Tetris, but love this. Yes, because I have more than three seconds to
make a decision. I can turn away from the computer screen and talk over here about a
12-year-old shot putting a bathroom key under the roof and I didn't lose the game.
What are you talking about? All right, so that's done. No new info here. It probably is. No,
it's not. Oh, it can't be here. Look at this. Nice. Okay, cool. Cool. All right, now we've got more
info. One, two, three, four, five, six. One, two, three, four, five, six. Take a look at that.
You've got your two. Now you've got your two and this is done because this has to be here.
That's not done. It doesn't know how to pause Tetris. You can pause Tetris. One, two, three,
four. One, two, three, four. Okay, can't do anything else here. One, two, three, four. One,
two, three, four. That's the five, right? There it is. All right, so now one, two, three, four, five.
One, two, three, four, five. Has to be here or here. Did that give us anything? There's the three
right there. Bingo. Got it. This is also part of the three. Can't be here. There's your three.
Done. Got it. Oh, speeding up. He's speeding up. He's getting on the freeway. Four. One, two, three,
four. Here we go. Take a look at that. I'm on a roll. X more things out. Oh, let me see. What
can I X out? Can't do this. Three, two, one. This has to be the two, right? Right? Yeah,
has to be. Get rid of that. Five and two. This could be one, two, three, four, five. Space one,
two. Can't decide that one yet. 13, five, six, seven, eight, nine, ten, eleven, twelve.
13, 13. Okay. What the fuck is this? Isn't it not a stream game title? Why have you asked that?
Can't you? It's a stream title. It says it's wind down Andy and then it says playing
PictoPix. He's very sassy today. No, I'm faux sassy. No, it doesn't mean anything. One, two, three,
four. One, two, three, four. Oh, there's your one. I love when that happens. Joe Biden raid.
What the heck? Oh my God. Why do you X? I couldn't even read it. I don't even know what he said.
That's like funny about doing the big stream from like four days ago. Is there people that probably
that's the first time they'd watch the stream and they're like, whoa, what the heck? That was really,
that was really cool. I wonder what the next stream is probably going to be something.
It's pick cross. I'm just sitting here pick cross like yelling at my students in my fake classroom
and then I leave for three weeks. I got the most follows I think in one day, four days ago,
and I'll get the most unfollows a week from now when I haven't streamed. But whatever, you know,
like if you try the lasagna, it's my favorite. Here it is. Thirteen is done. That means I can't
do that one. Oh, one, two, three, four. One, two. Walk it off. Walk it off. Walk it off.
Four. One. That's done. Here's your four right here. One, two, three, four. Can't be here. Yeah,
like ice cream sundaes. One, two, three. Can I do this one? There's three. There's three.
Okay, let's do some cleanup here. I love this game. It's the most relaxing and fun thing ever.
Take out these whole rows. I'm going to assume it's probably here.
All right, that would be clean. We don't know that yet. What even is this picture?
It's like a swan or something. Don't guess. Four, four. Oh, here's the four.
What even is this thing? Three, six. Okay, we have our info here. One, two, three, four, five, six.
One, two, three, four, five, six. Cool. All right, does that do any worse? That's three and one.
We're looking for a two and a one over here. What about this five? One, two, three, four, five.
Got that one. This is part of the two. One, two. It has to be one, two here. It can't be up here.
Does that help us do anything else? Maybe a little. Here's three. Could be here. Could be here.
Don't guess. Do something funny, sus streamer. There's another one done. Suss. All right,
what else we got? That's two. Oh, here we go. Lock that off because the two is already done.
There's your six. There's your one. Done. There's your four. Done. There's your six.
Okay, there's your three. One, two, three, four, five. One, two, three, four, five. It can't be
these two. It's that one. There's your one. Now we need a two. It's got to be one there.
Please pee your pants and piss yourself when you beat the level. Oh, that was weird. Okay,
we're almost done. I have no idea what this image is, but we're almost done with it.
One, two, three. One, two, three, eight. All right, this row is done. I didn't even mean to
do that, but we did it. One, two, three, four, five. One. Nice. Okay, that clears out this row.
There's four here. It's four down here. Eight. There's one somewhere here. One there.
Hold on. One, two, three, four, five. What did that do? It gave me something else. It's eight.
Eight, two. Bingo. There's a two. And there's your eight. I keep saying in there's your.
Oh, and there's your two. There's your eight. There it is. We got that. There's that one.
There's your two. There's your six. There's your five. I need something more interesting to say.
All right. Oh, we're done. Done. This is done. Is that? What picture is this? What is it?
It's a squirrel. It's a squirrel. It's a squirrel with a big tail. Oh, wow. I thought it was a swan.
That was cool. You know, I did see people say squirrel. Blue star. Better than one.
There's your two. There's your three. There's your four. There's your two.
All right. What about this one? Oh, all right. Well, this one. Oh, that's interesting.
This one's got some. This is 15. Maybe we can go in here. One, two, three, four, five, six, seven,
eight, nine, ten, eleven, six, seven, eight, nine, ten, eleven. Cool. So the nine then
is like in here, right? That's accurate. Seven is right in the middle. Or maybe not. I don't
know. I don't have that info. Nightgerma, enjoy the break. Thank you. I'm going to try to do as
much as I can. A lot of stuff going on. And I want to make sure I make this clear again,
because a lot of new people trickled in from the beginning of the stream about 40 minutes ago.
Um, let's make this as short as we can. Tons of stuff in the works, stuff I can't talk about.
I have a lot of major announcements when I come back. Leaving to take care of some personal
family and medical things once and for all, trying to close the book on that medical shit.
Going to try to get a procedure as fast as I can in this month. Reason for that is because
there's so much stuff going on in the next six months that I have to get it under control. So,
and if I don't, then it's going to be a real pain in the ass for me.
Well, I'll be back on April 1st. And no, that's not a joke. I will be streaming on April 1st and
April 2nd. I will give the announcements on April 2nd because I can't do it on the 1st,
because then people are going to think it was made up and it was a joke. I'll be back on April 1st.
And hopefully by then I would have had a procedure to deal with this costochondritis
disc spinal problem. We have no idea. We're still trying to figure out exactly what that is,
but at least I can get some injections to stop it from happening. Stop the
pain from showing itself all the time. That's the idea. Early April fool's pick raw stream.
Oh, I hope so. Okay. Here we go. This is part of the four. This is part of the two.
This is part of the four. This is part of the 11. This is part of the nine. This is part of the
part of the, ah, okay. This is part of the, let's do it one at a time. One, two, three, four.
This is part of the four. Sorry. Seven. One, two, three, four, five. Okay. One,
two, three, four, five, six, seven. That's some new deduction. Does that give us anything here?
We've got the one. Um, I don't, this might not be part. I don't know if that's part of the one.
This could be part of the three. That could be part of the three. The one column. I mean,
no, the one middle column one. Oh, right. I see what you mean. I'm sorry. I'm so sorry.
You're going to do a health updates on Twitter. I will. If there is a procedure I'm going to do,
I will tell you exactly what it is and exactly what that recovery time will be on it. But
make no mistake about it. I'm ready to close the book on this. It's been like three years.
And although I was fine after the geode archaeology stream for like three days plus
after that, it was tight. It was sore. And I'm just like, I have like, I have to get more.
We got to do something about this. Like now he has big balls. Um, why? Just, just, just,
just deny that. Just say, stop. No, why? I'm not talking about this. What the fuck am I doing?
Listen, who doesn't, what the fuck's happening? Just say that was weird. Don't say that there.
There you go. That was weird. Don't say that done. I'm done. I don't know. Why do I have to like
reply to that? Like just, that was weird. Don't say that done. Where are we going? Here we go.
This is the, what I was trying to do before. I love this. This, this sounds like really scary.
It could be that way or one, two, three, four, five. Hmm. Okay. You guys taking guesses of what
this is? I'm going to say it's a boat. I think this is a boat with the eight. Yep. Hold on.
One, two, three, four, five. One, two, three, four, five, six, seven, eight. Hold on a minute. One,
two, three, four, five, six, seven, eight. One, two, three, four, five, six, seven, eight. Damn. Okay.
What do we got here? It's a toy boat. It could be, yeah, it is a toy boat, toy boat, toy boat,
toy boat, toy boat, toy boat, toy boat, toy boat, toy boat, toy boat, toy boat, toy boat, toy boat,
toy boat, toy boat. I, the music playing in my ear distracted me. It's a crab. I don't think it's a
crab. I think it's a boat. Hmm. Three or the eight. Probably the eight because then this would make
sense, right? This would be the four. Well, this is a guess. I know you're not supposed to do that
here, but I'm using enough reasoning to do this. I know you're not supposed to do that. I did it
anyways. Song is pretty scary. Mad. It's wrong. Okay. All right. All right. We're fine. Um, so
this is still eight. Any more? This is part of the three, three, five, one, two, three, four, five,
one, two, three, four, five. I can't do anything else here. Three, four, five, three, three, four,
five. Can't do anything with these ones either. Um, what about this row? I've been listening to
the Heroes of Might and Magic three soundtrack because it's one of the best. Oh my God. What
was it? Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa. Oh shit. This was done. Oh man. Nice. Okay. Maybe it's not a
boat. Um, it's got really nice soundtrack and it's one of my favorite old PC games. So that's why
it's out here, man. Working with uncertain information. Yeah. I know. What does that do?
Oh, that helps a lot actually. Cause now that brings this in. I can add to this, can't I?
Okay. Added this, which is part of the five. Very nice.
With all this, cause there's no five there. Three can't fit in there. The seven can't fit in there,
but a seven can go up this way for sure. And that one is now done. That takes care of the seven.
It sounds like mouth sounds. We need mouth sounds. Two can't go here. Oh, hold on. One, two, three,
four. All right. What do we got here? This is, these could be the, I think these are the two ones,
or this could be the two, could it? Two, one, one, three. This is, this, this is possible to be the
two. I don't know that yet. Three, four, five, two, three, four, one, two, three, four. Nice. Okay.
This is one, two, three, four. Everything else is done. Whoa. Whoa. Whoa. Wait a minute. One, two,
three. Whoa. Oh, this is wrong. What happened? Oh shit. What happened? This is wrong. This is wrong.
Oh, this is all fucked up. Is it because I guessed? No, is it? Wait, hold on. I need to
backtrack a little bit. What happened here? Seven, four, eight. Let me get this one. Let me,
let me get this one. So this means, this row is the problem somehow, or this one.
This is why you don't guess. I can salvage it though. Hold on. I think this is still correct
though. It kind of has to be. One, two, three, one, two, three, four, five, six, seven, eight.
Start over. No, what do you mean start over? One, two, one, two, hold on. Relax. One, two, three,
four, five. One, two, three, four, five. One, two, three, four, five. One, two, three, four, five.
All right. Five, one, three. Eleven, two, one, one, three. Two, one, one, three.
It's been 10 minutes. You should be done by now. You're, you're, whatever. You're in detention
or something. I don't know. That's guessing. No, no, no, no, no, no. What did I just do? One,
two. Where was it? Over here. One, two, three, four, five. One, two, three, four, five. This is
right, right? Five, one, three. That was a guess. Column three and four. You can eliminate a lot
on the second row. Yeah, I can. That's eight. One, seven, eight. One, two, three, four, five,
six, seven, eight. It has to be there, right? And then this is one, two, three, one, two, three,
four. Let's make, is this, do we got this right? Hey, do, do we got this? There's nine. Hey, do we
got this? Guys, I think we got this. None of you are clicking on the screen at all. It's me doing
this. Oh, we're so close. It's just me doing this. I think I fixed it. Okay. I, these, this is very
right to be wrong. I'll be honest with you. Fuck. Shit. One, two, three, four, five. Oh no, it's all
wrong. It's a bunny rabbit though. It's not a bunny. Where did this go so wrong? I did, it's this,
this junk here in the middle is what's good. Everything's good. This is correct over here,
I think. Shit. Five, one, three, something right here. Ah, no. It's cause I guessed on the one
educated guess and it fucked up the whole thing. I think it's, it's like one column is wrong.
I can salvage it. I know I can. Everything needs to be shifted like one square to the right.
I think this one's wrong. That'd be one. There's one. Okay. One, four, four. Hold on. Hold on. Four,
five. Oh, I have to fucking restart the whole thing. I have to restart. I've messed, I just
fucked something up. And when you mess one thing up, the whole project is over. Shit.
I hate it. I hate it. All right. All right. I still want to, I want to do another one. I just
fucked the whole thing up. I fucked everything up. Is that nine? One, two, three, four, five,
six, seven, eight, nine. All right. See if I was lying in my bed doing this shit, I would just like,
I would just go, oops. And restart it like five times. Four, eight, eight, three, four, five,
six, seven, eight. Okay. Relax. Two, three, four, five. Two, three, four, five. That looks good.
You only, you don't, you cheated the, can you explain this more? Sure. I actually will. Because
then a lot of people were not here the last time I played this. So the whole goal here is to make
a picture. I'm giving some information. By the way, this game is way cooler than Sudoku.
So if I'm sorry, but Sudoku is shit in comparison to this. But if you've played Sudoku,
it's about numbers on the edges that you have to fill squares in. This one, you have to make a
picture. Each one of these rows and columns has this many squares filled in on this space here.
So in this row, there is five in a row, one, and three in a row. In between these three numbers,
there has to be one full unoccupied space. Has to be. And the idea is you have to logically deduce
where those squares are filled in based on the knowledge they give you. At least one. Yes,
yes, at least one. It could be one, it could be five spaces. Has to be at least one space.
Sudoku is sick as fuck. Oh, we have some Sudoku people in here that think that Sudoku is better
than Picross. Yeah, hey, hey, hey, back to the Sunday newspaper, right, Grandpa?
Hey, how's that Lady Superstar on a Foxtrot, Grandpa and the Funnies?
One, two, three, four, five, six, seven. I can't deduce that. It was a really weird laugh too.
I'm sorry about that. Okay, so no more guessing. Get this right. Don't be an idiot.
You're a boomer for even knowing what Foxtrot is. Why? Six column, the six column,
six column, the six column. I thought this was, okay, hold on. Three, four, five, six.
One, two, three, four, five, six. Very cool. All right, so this is where I got screwed up last time.
This has to be part of the five. One, two, three, four, five. Let's just say it's right here. One,
two, three, four, five, space one, space one, two, three. This is not part of the three. It's
part of the five. Tell me I'm wrong here. One, two, three, four, five. This has to be the five.
That's good to know. That's not a guess. That's not a guess. Okay, let's keep going. Doing that
allows me to go like this. One, two, three, four, five. That's a correct move. Yeah. You're at 500,000?
I'm not at 500,000. It might happen this stream, and if it does, then oh my God,
you're going to hit me celebrate. You're not doing this fast enough to satisfy my satisfaction.
Wait, did I read that right? Okay. Stop. Stop. One, two, three, four, five, six, seven,
five, six, seven. Thank you. Correct. Correct. All right, I'm slowly deducing.
Hmm. Five, six, seven. One, two, three, four, five, six, seven. All right. Okay. This is where it got
messed up last time. I'm not at 500,000 yet. I have a monitor right here that shows it.
We're at 499,576. I have the live real-time data. You're not. No, I'm not. Refresh the page.
I don't have 500,000 followers. I have 499,576. Debated. That's actually really cool.
Weren't we just talking about how I passed 200,000 like six months ago or something?
What's happening? All right. This is where I got messed up last time. I just made it an assumption.
Three, four, five, space one. It's probably right here, right? I mean, come on. Come on, right? It
has to be. That's a guess, but that is a really good guess. That's assuming. It has to be there.
It can't be anything else. That's not an assumption. That is a deduction from logical reasoning.
No, it has to be there. There's nowhere else it can be. No, I can see a real-time clicker,
a ticker of what I have for subs right now. No, I mean, for 500,000 subs. Oh, my God.
It rounds up. No, I'm at 499,600. That would be a billionaire.
Okay, so that was solved. I got that fixed from last time. One, two, three. One, two, three. There
you go. Therefore, one, two, three, four, five. One, two, three, four, five. I got that done.
Is it crack time yet? I think it's been crack time since the stream started like an hour ago.
I blew this one too. I blew it. Now we go for it. That was the problem. I knew it was something
right here in the middle that you have to start over so you can see what the hell is going on.
Very cool. Now I got this. Okay, now I did this. It can't be there. These are ones that can't be
played. They can't be done. I just lost 100 followers. I think something you guys don't know.
I'll tell you right now. There's so many people are coming and going on this stream. It's really
weird to look at. Would you guys like to know how many people unfollowed the stream?
Three days ago. Where can I see that info? I know I can see it. Can I?
It was unfollowed. I know I can see it. I'm unfollowing right now. The music is fitting.
I don't have the data right in front of me. Just to let you know, hundreds of people potentially
unfollow a day. I don't even know who they are. I don't know where they came from. I have no idea.
Well, I don't know. Hundreds of people follow and hundreds of people unfollow every day.
It's something like that. What's the noise? I don't know. My window's open. There's crickets
and shit out there. There's also a full band out there too. Pretty nice though. I'm going to keep
the window open. All right, let's keep going. This is much better. Okay. Now, no guessing.
It's definitely not there. Three. It can't be there. It could be here and it could be here.
Four. One, two, three, four. Yeah. Is it there already? Okay. One, two, three, four. Can't be
there. Three, four. Okay. One, two, three, four. Can't be here. One, two, three, four. Can't be
there either. Interesting. One, two, three, four. One, two, three, four. Which gave us this. Which
gave us the seven which means we can do one two three four five six seven one two three four five
six seven okay no guessing it's the audio this is outside why are you playing a math game
we can't hear you all right it's time to ost change it up sure how about um how about super
mario world foe ost this is what was i just doing i was right here this is okay three has to be one
here that's that there can't be any more we just got this nice good deduction jeremy you did a
fucking fantastic job people should be so proud of you but this is part of the six one two three
four five six done now wait slow down i get dmc8 from super mario music i don't think that's gonna
happen isn't like video game music in a weird area where it's like you're safe from dmca because
it's video game music as long as it's not like a licensed record label song right what if i was
playing super mario yeah this is fine look if i get in trouble for playing super mario music on
a twitch.tv video game website stream what the hell am i doing what the fuck are we doing here
like what what was the point of live streaming like what was the point of streaming video games
if we what are we i'm gonna have to have a stenographer come in and just like give you a
live i'll just like tell you what i'm doing like i said i'll just be like on a webcam and i gotta
tell the stenographer what the fuck i'm doing if i get dmca for nintendo music on stream
and the roller coaster is going down that's all i gotta say okay that's wait hold on one two three
five one two three four five good all right i think i can i can do this one now one two three four five
six seven eight shit what happened what happened what happened what happened something happened
here what happened one oh fuck something happened one two three four five six seven eight no it's
okay i'm so good i did not guess that's not happened we're good i don't know if this is a
one or a two this is the three one two three shit okay hold on let me do something here
here. I'm so nervous now. I don't know why. Why would I be nervous? Okay. Well, that's
done. This is it. Okay. Cool. What did that do for me? Two? Maybe the one? What did that
do here? Seven. Where is it? Oh, right. You're right. Thank you. Nice. Nine. Oh, now I, okay.
Hold on. I can do this now. Two, three, four, five, six, seven. Can't be there. Five, six,
seven, eight, nine. Five, six, seven. It's a guess. Can't do that. Eleven. Eleven. Good.
I can't. I can't do that yet. I can't do it. I'm too nervous to do that. Too scared. This is
five. One, two, three, four, five. Can't be here. One, two, three, four, five. Right? No,
that's not accurate. One, two, three. It has to be one here though. Right? Three, four, five. Not
accurate. As I know it is. It's accurate. It's a crab. I don't think it's a crab. And you know
what? It's probably a fire. Maybe a flame. Three and the eight. Three and the eight. Right. Okay.
So then this is, I got, I messed this up last time. One, two. This has got to be the eight.
This has to be like this. Three, four, five. Is it a bird? I think it might be a plane. No,
of course not. It's Superman. Give me the fucking minus twos. Give them to me. Give me. Give me
them. I want to see them. I want only the chat to be fucking minus twos. It's all I want to see.
I better see it. Make me feel fucking horrible. Make me. I deserve it. Okay. This is done. There's
one. Is it the second one or the first one? Because if this is the second one, then this
is the three. Okay. I can't, don't guess. I got to put my like singer spin on it. Is that row done?
Is that row done? Have we talked about this? But like anytime somebody does a song that's very,
the Mario theme song is very, there's no, it's just dun dun dun dun dun dun dun dun dun dun dun.
It's like the national anthem. Like dun dun dun dun dun dun. But when you get like then the
singer syndrome, you have to make it your own. You have to make it different. It can't just be like,
oh, say, can you see? No, it's going to be like, oh, say, can you see? Like they have, you have to
do your own like, wow, it's going to be, I got to make it different. Nobody just like sings a song
that's a very old like song that everybody knows. You have to give it your spin. True. Yeah. That's
always annoying. Well, I mean, I'm just telling you how it is. You did the same joke from the
Fear 2 stream. All right. Well, let's, hey, how many words have I spoken in the English? Okay.
Do this for me. I want one of you to do this because we'll see if that's the case. I don't
know how many words I've spoken on stream. I've said every word in the dictionary,
like a hundred times each. I've said every fucking possible sentence. Like I've talked
50 million words. I'm going to backtrack onto one of some of those words sometimes.
I've said 500 million words on this stream. You said that same joke in the Fear 2 stream
back in like 2017. You're a liar. All right. Well, this is done.
I'm so sorry. Hey, remember that? Like how many unfollows am I going to get in a day?
Oh, we're almost done. Oh, what is it? What's it going to be? It's a bat. It's a bat. Yeah,
this is a bat for sure. It's a bat. It's a bat. You're embarrassing me. You're getting
secondhand embarrassment because I'm annoying. Oh, very cool. Wait, wait, wait. Yeah. I haven't
done this one yet. I remember this one. I love that one. I mean, listen to quake two. Um,
this one's going to be hard. 15 by 15, seven, eight, nine, 10, 11, 12. So there'll be two spaces.
Um, two, three, four, five, six, seven. I just thought my connect. I just like my connect.
I thought it was falling down on me. I just freaked out. This one is hard. Yeah, it is six.
It's 1112. Yeah. What we could do is so let's say it was so two, let's just do this. Like
let's just say it was this way space this way, right? That's like, that's not accurate,
but that's like, will give us some space here to work with. So technically this can be blocked
off like that temporarily. That's guessing. Yes, I know. If I do one, two, three, four, five, six,
seven, and then one space two, we have this whole quadrant is, oh, that's guessing. I know,
but technically speaking, I should have this much like room at least deduce that. Yeah, that's
accurate. Let me do what I'm doing. One, two space one space. So like I have this much room to work
with for the seven. I was right. Thank you. One, two, three, four, five, six, seven. One, two, three,
four, five, six, seven. The seven that has to be like that. It's impossible for it not to be.
I can hurry up. Timer's going up. Okay. Same deal with the other ones. So there's another group
that's like that, right? Six and the five. Let's just say it was one, two, three, four, five space
one, two, three, four, five, six. That means that I have to, I'm getting intense. I think from here
I can do, I was going to do it. And now ladies and gentlemen here to do for the, before the baseball
game, the sped up time of hurry up. You've got to get to the end of the Mario level. We've got
Jeremy Albertson. Hey everybody.
Yeah.
Four, five, six, seven, eight, nine, 10. I don't know what to do on core. Turn on shuffle. Why?
All right. I need to deduce. Stop distracting me. I think that's my best bet. I really do one, two,
three, four, one, two, three, four, five space one, two, three, four, five, six. The six has
got to have one, two, three, four, five, six. Right. It has to be here somewhere. There has to
be three in a row here. I don't, I, I don't, it's, it's, that's tricky to, that's a, that's a guess,
but it allows me to do this. Are there 12 K people watching this? Because you, you, you got here too
late. I just, I just like, you should, you should have been here five minutes ago and my views have
been going crazy. If you could see what I did right before you got here, I did a handstand.
Oh, I'm so fucking exhausted. I did a handstand for an hour and we had a timer that was a one
hour handstand. Like, and you fucking missed it. I'm like exhausted and I had to sing the national
anthem upside down and drink like milk upside down and shit. It was a big like follower thing
that we did. I had 500,000 followers today. It's not normally this many, but there's usually like,
maybe like a thousand people here. I don't know. This is crazy. It's a huge increase. I had to drink
milk upside down. It was like, and it went on my nose and stuff and everybody's laughing and like,
the views just kept going. I mean, I, and I was like, I got to relax. That was ridiculous.
I rode like a horse in here. Like, you don't have, you don't idea what's going to happen the next in
the 500,000 follower stream. And like, I rode a horse around. Yeah. I'm tired. I just want to
play fucking Picross. I don't, I didn't just think there's many people going to be here.
Where should I go now? Rated like 20 times. Yeah. I remember, I remember favorite streamer X said,
holy shit, this guy's riding around on a horse. He just did a handstand and like drank a glass of
milk upside down. What's going there? All right, guys, we're going there. They all did it. It was
weird. It's crazy. Cross out the three row. Yep. That helps a lot. Even if this is a guess,
but it's, I think it's accurate. It gives us some more stuff to work with here. Okay.
Anything more than three in a row. Damn it. Oh, that sucks. Called networking. Milk keg stand
sounds awful. Yeah, it does. What kind of, what, what, why would we be doing milk out of a keg?
It seems really weird. That's like a prank. Oh man, we got ears. We got, we got bush light in here.
Let's get them up there. Yeah. Oh yeah. You want to do it? Yeah, I'll do a keg stand. Let's go.
All right. Take it off. Go ahead. Come on in. Put it in your mouth. All right. Let's jump upside
down. So tell them. This tastes something about this. Oh, it's milk.
Freshman drank milk. I do one. First character song. And this song is playing. Oh, fuck it.
Fuck this place. Drinking milk out of a keg. You lost viewers. All right. What do you want
me to say? I do. What do you want me to do? Like, whatever. If people are going to leave,
they're going to leave. All right. You losing viewers. Oh, well, whatever. Who cares?
There's 12, 15 million people live right now. If you don't want to listen to the Mario fast
song while I talk about chugging milk out of a keg while I sit here and just don't play the game,
then you're gone. There's somebody way more interesting you'll find. Is that accurate though?
Boom. All right. I'm done. Let me skip ahead. I don't want to hear this fucking shit anymore.
There we go. That's better. So let's just say that's that. Ego. I don't have an ego.
Say that anymore. Love. Whatever. Why are they all so fast? Go. Okay. There we go. Scary music.
Can I do this up here though? One, two, three. I can't do it up here.
Where am I going to find the place to start from? It's not here. I don't know if this is the two or
the three. I don't know what this could be. I don't know what this is either. You just did 10
minutes? What? This isn't PictoPix music. This is disarming a bomb music. Five, six column.
I can't do this though. One, two, three, four, five. I don't have enough. This is just guessing.
This is a straight up guess. Okay. Yeah. I didn't die. Nope. 499, 789. I think I think I'd rage
put this one. I don't like this one. Five, six. I can't do the five, six. How could be down? I
maybe I could just maybe these two in here. Like it would have to be like one of these two, right?
It has to be that though. It has to be. But that doesn't help me at all. The blue wire. I'm going
so slow. Yeah, this is a guess, but that doesn't even give me that much info. I mean, technically
speaking, I could guess and this could be like six could be down here, right? Could be that. And
then this could be part of the four, one, two, three, four. Then this is done. Do not guess.
Don't guess. Look behind you. I'm fine. Seven. I can't do anything with the sevens. There's
nothing more than a four, five, six, seven, eight, nine, 10. Remember you suck at this.
Okay, we're done with Mario. I'm done with this hurry the fuck up music.
And now, ladies and gentlemen, to sing the Mario Galaxy opening theme song for the entrance of our
baseball game. German 985. He seems to be frozen. He's clenching the mic very, very tightly in both
of his hands with his eyes wide open. He's supposed to have been singing by now. Somebody get down
there. Get down there. He's frozen. He's done. He's clenched completely. Now he can't do it.
Thank you, ladies and gentlemen. German 985. Catch him on Twitch. Somebody get him the fuck
out of here. Get him. Go get him. Just can the music. Go to the interlude shit. Interlude,
interlude. Thank you. Go get him. Wait, I might be naked in this image. It's like three guys just
with one arm on my back just like moving me and I'm just slowly walking just clenching the fucking
microphone. And then it all what an embarrassing fucking last ditch effort. I start to sing.
Oh, everyone's clapping. He's almost off. He's almost off the field. Get him off. Okay.
And they cut the mic. They like pull the cord. I'm rage quitting this one. I can't do it.
For me to do these, I need like the one guaranteed space that I know I can do. And
there's none of them here. Fuck. Just guess. Try the five by five one. I have to guess.
I have to guess. I'm guessing. Whatever. Therefore, this is two two. They're all such
little numbers. Like, what the fuck? This one sucks. That didn't even help me.
Five, six, seven. I just have to take a wild guess. Whatever. So this is four, maybe the two, three,
vertical four, two, two. You sing the decay rap. I think I've done that before.
Too many low numbers. I don't like, I hate that. I like having the little, little numbers.
Four, two, two. I don't know if that's accurate up here. Three, three, one, two, three, or one, two,
three. That's all I can do from that. Three row, three, three row, three column. What are you saying?
You can do the horizontal two, four, two. Okay. Let's just say this is the last two,
which I might not even be. It could be that. I don't have it. I can't do it. I don't have
enough info. Where is the fucking info? There's no info for this. I'm guessing. I'm trying not
to guess. Where's the sure thing? Where is the sure thing on this list? I don't see it.
Four, two, two. Vertical is a sure thing. One, two, three, four, one, two, space one, two.
Vertical four, two, two is a sure thing. Where? How? The two, two's could be anywhere. They could be
here. They could be here, here. It could be two, space two. It could be two, space two. They could
be anywhere. Fourth row down on that row. One, two, three, four. Make progress. You can do it.
I believe in you. This is a guess though. I think this one just sucks. Look at all these dumb one,
two, one, one, two, one, one, two, two, two. It's like, no, get out of here. This one's stupid.
Four, okay. One, two, three, four, one, two, three, four. Now does it go this way or this way? The two.
No idea. Vertical seven. One, two, three, four, five, six, seven. One, two, three, four, five, six, seven.
Okay. This is two, four, two. This, there's the one, one. Is that, but that, if I guessed,
I took a guess. I have no idea if that's accurate or not. I've done, how am I supposed to know that?
It's not a guess. It is a guess though. I had to deduce that and I had to make an educated guess
to get this even in the first place. Okay. Hold on. How are we doing? Now this is two, four.
There's your two. There's your four. Who knows where the hell the other two could be?
There's your three. That's done. All right. These are guesses. I don't know. I have no,
I don't know how to play the game. Two, two. Okay. One, two, three, four, five, six, seven.
One, two, three, four, five, six, seven. Should we be dancing? Getting there. All right. I need a,
uh, okay. Hold on. That's going to help a lot. Three, three, one. This is probably the three right
here. Right? Cause then it'd be two this way. Right? Yes. I think that's correct. No. What?
So this could be the one. I don't know. All right. Hold on. I feel, I really feel like it's like right
here. Three, four, five, six, seven. One, two, three, four, five, six, seven. This is one. This
is probably the one. Yeah. It has to be. Three. This is a three here. One, two, three. Not there.
One, two, three. Can't be there. Okay. I wrote the soundtrack. What? What? Dude, did you seriously?
Are you serious? Oh my God. Welcome. Welcome. We need to welcome that person. Oh my God.
Hey, there's another one. Okay. That does do. I feel like this is nothing. They have to be over
here. Otherwise, what the hell is this connected to? Or right here, I'm assuming. You know where
to put the one. Do I? Yes, I do. Don't I? Right? Like that, that's pretty, that's pretty, that's
pretty close. Okay. Could be one too. No evidence. The music is making this worse.
Like I'll, I keep just seeing Mario running. Okay. So this is the ADHD is just fucking striking.
It's ugly head here. Like I'm playing this game in front of my screen, but I am seeing in my head
Mario running around on planets. Like I'm playing two games at the same time. I'm just in that game
in my head just playing it. And while I'm just here now, like I just collected a coin. I just got
like two coins. Oh yeah. Oh, I did the thing where you do, you spin around accidentally.
Cause the wee boat like crossed the plane. You didn't even mean to do it, but you get,
whoa, whoa. You get really annoyed by it for a second. Cause you're like, oh, I didn't fucking
want to do that. All right. Where are we here? This is two, four, seven, one. Where's that one?
Or, oh, okay. Hold on. Good. That's one of the twos. This has to be the four. Okay. So therefore
one, two, three, four, one, two, three, four. That's a risky move right there. Cause this
has to be the only, that's the only one I could put there. Right? Wait one, two shit. It could be
here. Yes. I know. Yeah. I know. Stop playing Mario galaxy. I've stopped playing Mario galaxy.
I'm playing Mario galaxy in my head. Shit. I just did like a super jump from one gravitational
planet to the other gravitational planet. It was just like pulled me in and I went all the
way around the planet and went up and then landed. Okay. Hold on. Let me focus. This is,
if this is the other three right here, I know that's a guess, but one, two, three,
that means there's the other two. And then I have the four over here. I'm just going to,
I'm going for it. That's a guess, but I'm going for it. I think that's correct. Isn't this a
space for one down here somewhere that lets me continue. So therefore one, two, three, get rid
of that. One, two, three. That gives me the second two. One, two, three, four. One, two, three, four.
One, two, three, four. One, two, three, four. Now what? Oh shit. One, two, three, four, five, six.
There it is. I knew these are going to be closed off. One, two, three. One, two, three. One, two,
three. One, two. It is one, two, three, four. Okay. It could be either one of those. Relax.
Who's this guy talking? Oh, it's, of course it's a Drupal985. Three. This has to be the three.
Therefore that's the three. This is the three. One, two, three. Okay. Seven goes down all the way,
right? Cause that would be four to two. Wait, hold on. Is this the guy that found an ancient
treasure on stream? I did. This is part of the three. One, two, three. I can, I know I can deduce
this right now, but my brain just can't do it. One, two, three, four, five. One, two, three, four,
five. My brain is so small. No, I have a huge brain. It's just, I don't know. I feel like I've
like sucked like an intelligence vacuum in the back of my head over the last like 10 years.
Three, four, five, six, seven. Where could this actually be though? I know I can do this. Let me,
all right. Quiet. Quiet, everybody. Quiet. If I do this one here, what would be,
this is the second two and that would be the three going this way. I think that's correct.
And then now I've got three. Seven is now five, six, seven. Five, six, seven. What's this? That's a one,
two, three, two, space, two, three. Okay. Hold on. Three there. Three, five, seven. One, two, three,
four, five, six, seven. One, no. I hope this is correct. Now could this be this way? I think
that's done. Right? Oh, I'm just going. I'm just going. I hope this is correct. Three, two, two,
one, four. I need four here. One, two, three, four. You guys think it's a gun? Okay. Hold on.
Second row. Three, two, five. Okay. Good. There's the three. Yes. It only took me
30 minutes to get here. Now this is one, three, one, two, three. Okay. Now I've got a mess over
here to deal with. Is it a shark? Yeah, this is a dolphin. It's some type of amphibious fish or
something. One, two, three, four, one, two. I think you Pat stares at for the raid. Pat stares at.
Welcome, everybody. We had a good stream, Pat. I'm Jerma. Currently doing. What are we doing? We're
doing Hick Ross with intense music behind it. Because that's what we do here. Super epic,
intense streams. X, X, X, X, X. Go with the fucking X, X, X, X, X, X, X, X, X, X. All done. All
of them gone. All right. What are we doing? Done. This one's done. Two, three. Oh, it's almost done.
Our dolphin is almost done. Our dolphin. Oh, oh, that was wrong. What went wrong? What went
wrong? What did I do wrong? I was like, no, I wasn't paying attention. Two, one, two, two.
Oh, this is a no, no, no, no, no, no, no. Wait, wait, wait. Stop. One space, one space. Why is
this three? What happened here? How did I, what did I do? What happened here? One, one, did I do
wrong here? You're almost there. I got, yeah. I almost, I just got to fix this somehow. Move
four. This looks out of place. Start over again. Oh my God. Get out of here. Two, one, three. This is
two, one, one, one, two. Oh, goodness. This is so almost done. Where is this? Move one from one, one,
two, one, three. It's like done. It's the eye. Yeah, that's the eye right there. But what is this
thing? That shouldn't be there. All right. Turn off the fucking, like, we're about to like fly into
outer space music. I need to concentrate. All I could see was be strapped to an astronaut chair.
Just like going up into the moon and stuff. Like get that off. I need to pay attention.
I think it's down here. Um, where's the mistake? Where I, where's the fucking mistake? What is it?
What is this stupid ass mistake? One, three. This is, this is all fucked up. Move vertical one,
three, down by one. Move vertical one, three, down by one. Wait, what? Vertical one, three.
What happened? Fill in the four. This is wrong. Oh my God. What is the fucking wrong here? What
is the problem? What did I do? Seven, one needs to be over one. Like over here. Oh no. No. Okay.
Hold on. One, go back more? No, I don't think so. Two, one, two is bad. Two, one, two, bad. Two,
one, two, bad. Who is back here? Here? Three, four, done, done. Seven, two, two, three.
One, two oatmeal. I don't know what that means. One, one, two. One, one, two. One, one, two.
But where is the mistake? Oh God damn it. One, does this need to be moved over? There's so many
X's and shit on the screen. I have no idea what's going on. The bottom of one, one, two is the
mistake. You have one, two, one, one, one, like here. And then, so where the hell does this two go?
One, one, two. And then one. Oh my God. I'm like literally like seeing colors right now. It's like
everything's just mixing together. Three is two. One, one, two is throwing. Help me. Just help me,
please. One, three down one block. Then where's the one go? This two is done. Two, one, two,
two, one, two, two, one. Oh my God. Somebody help me, please. Oh.
Oh, there's one. Fucking finally. Oh, get out of here. Come on. Okay. Whatever you say, win.
This is 15. So three, four, five, six, seven, eight, nine, 10, 11, 12, 13. This is interesting.
Three, two, two, three, four, eight, nine, 10, 11, 12, 13, eight. I can do this one. Let's just say,
for instance, this is occupied. It looks like one, one. So let's, I guess what I got to work
with. So we got one, two, three, four, five, six, seven, eight. One, two, three, four, five, six,
seven, eight. Cool. So what does that do for us here? What does that do? I'm so, what the hell
was I doing? I don't know. I thought that was going to be funny or something. I don't know
what that was. I thought that was going to be funny. I was like, oh, I'll make like a noise.
That wasn't even, why would I do that? There's no reason to even do that. Oh, this is the song,
is the song. Oh, let me make like a loud slurp, snort thing. I don't know. That was not even funny
at all. Okay. One, five, six, seven, eight, nine spaces. I think I can do this one here.
Five and five. I don't know if this is the one or the two.
That did not help me at all. One, two horizontal can make a lot of X on the right.
Well, here's the problem though. I don't know if this is the one or the two,
because if this is the one, the two could be anywhere over here. I feel like I can
get this one somehow. Let's see. One, two, three, one, two, two, three. I mean, it's got a
Five lets you place one on each side, doesn't it? It's very loud. Let me turn that down a little.
The fives can do one on each side. I guess this could be one here and then one here.
Is that possible? One here and one here, right? I think that makes sense. Oh, shit. Nice. Okay.
Hold on. One, two, one, two. Take a look at this. If that's accurate, which it should be.
Now this helps here. Not really, but kind of. This doesn't even help at all, actually.
I don't know if this is the three or the one. It's probably the one.
Louder? All right. It's a little louder. Relax. Three, two, two is easier now.
It is. You're right. One, two, three, space, one, two, space, one, two, three. Oh, it doesn't.
That means it would be, hold on. Oh, this is blocked off.
We'll do like this then. One, two, three, space, one, two, two, one, two, three. Shit.
It's not, I can't do it yet though. It could be, this whole thing could be moved over one spot.
You can play some. I guess I could. Which ones are guaranteed? I would probably say that this
one's guaranteed. That's the only one that I think is guaranteed, right? I got 500k? Did I?
Four, nine, nine, 98. No, we're not there. Four. Oh, no, we did. That's 500,000. Holy shit. Cool.
500,000 followers on Twitch. Wow. Thanks, guys. It's been a lot of fun. Cool. 500k.
Speech. Rub-a-dub-dub. Thanks for the grub. Part. Why, you little. So this one is accurate, right?
Because if it's one, two, three, one, two, three, these two can be placed. These, I don't,
I can't do these ones though. Fuck, I'm unfollowing. What are you talking about?
So that helps. That helps a lot. Well, that helps a lot. All right. So this changes everything here
because I might be able to actually do this now. One, two, three, four, five,
space, one, two, three, four, five. Most of these can be filled in. At least a lot of them can.
Which then one, two, three, by this whole row. Wait. Wait, what happened? Hold on. Why did I
just do that? One, two, one, two, three. Okay. Oh, wait. I'm freaking out. 500k song? Omega Low
under 500k. Well, it's not these ones. Not these ones. Is that incorrect? Wrong. Wrong. This is
wrong, right? This is one, two, three. I can block that off. This is probably the three.
That's probably the three. One, two, block this off. All right. Five, five is wrong. One, two,
one, two, three, four, five. One, two, three, four, five. One, two, three, four, five.
It was right. No, I think one, two, one, two. No, that's right. Oh my God. This is a Nancy
Drew game. Yup. That's not right. Are you sure? I think that's correct. Because then that gets
rid of that. That is right. Yeah, that's correct. So then it's not, I have to just worry about the
eight here. Three. Can't be that way. So one, two, three. It's close. I can't do it yet, though.
Oh, fuck. What do I do? Three, three. No two here yet. Four, four, three. You filthy animal. Oh my
God. It could be one, two, three, four. One, two, three, four. One, two, three.
I can't do it. Three, two, row. I can have stuff blocked.
You messing with me? Are you messing with me? All right. So this would be the three. One, two, three.
Three. Can't beat any of these. It has to be here. You messing with me? That's done. What about here
now? So this is definitely the two and the two somehow. Oh, fuck. This is wrong. So it was wrong.
The five was right. Three, two is the bad one. This one here. Three, two wrong, not five. Oh,
this one's wrong. What else does this logically go? The X's you put on three, two are wrong.
This was, if this is two, then this can't exist here. Remove the two. Shit. So if this is, this
nothing over here can be used. This is correct, right? If this is correct, then I can't do
anything up there. And with this one. And this one. And this one. Okay. So how, what the hell?
It has to be, is this the two then? This must be the two. Maybe not. It could be one, two, three.
This could be three, two. Hold on. Okay. Hold on. What does that do for me over here? It's mate. Four,
four, three. I can't do the four, four, three yet. Let's see. One, one, two, three, four. One,
two, three. Let's see what it looks like. Can't do that yet. Oh my God. Relax. Bird row from the
bottom. Fifth from the left. I can't, I like, you just gave me directions. Wait, wait, wait,
wait, wait, wait, wait. This is three, five. I mean this one, two, three space. All right.
The three has to be here. There's your two. There's that. There's three. Cap that. There's the one.
One, two, three, four. One, two, three, four. There's three. Close that off. That's the one.
This is the two. So one, two, nothing over here. One, two could be over that way. There's the two.
The first one, of course, there's the four. This row's done. This gives you the three,
which completes the two. Complete that three. What do we have here? That's the one. What about
here? One, five. There's a two over here. Which has to be one of these. That's your three. Lock
that off. Okay. This has to be four. That's done. There's two. Two, two, three. Ooh, this is getting
exciting. Three. Lock it off. It killed this whole thing. Four, four, three. Oh, that was so
satisfying. I love that. Three. We need two and then two somewhere over here. Here's the real
question though. This can't be three. This has to be the three. One, two, three. Oh, I don't know
that yet. Hold on. Okay. Good. Can any of these be brought from the bottom? This is the one.
Yep, it is. Also a one. Here's the eight. Cool. Can't be a two here.
I'm not doing that. People are gonna actually like think that's fucking annoying. Like, I would.
If it were me in the chat room right now, I would be like, that's annoying. And like,
just stop doing it. It's not funny. That would like annoy me. That would be actually annoying.
There's one. There's also a one. All right, now it's all coming together. Can't be here. One, two,
three, four, five. There's the three. When it all starts coming together, I love it. It looks so
wonderful. There's your two. Wait. Don't get too crazy about this. That's one, one, two. This is
the last two. What even is this thing? I have no idea what this is. What is this? What is it?
Flame? Oh, it's a campfire. Nice. It's peanut butter jelly time. That actually did kind of look
like that. Nice. Okay, is there any more that I didn't do back here? I did them all back here,
right? Nice. Look at how many I did. Well, here we go. There's still more to do. I kind of want to
do a huge one. Where's the first 20? Okay, this is 20 by 20. This is gonna be a mess, by the way.
Good luck. This actually is good. It's 16. One, two, three, four. Technically, one, two, three,
four, right? Does it need to have four on either side? All right. Oh, it happened. It actually
happened. This is the equivalent of getting in breakout the ball stuck on top in the first or
second shot of the game. You'll see what I mean in a second. Nice. Okay. Oh, 15, 16, 17. Oh, wow.
Okay. So, this is connected here because it's one by 15. That's one, two, three, four, five, six,
seven, eight, nine, ten, eleven, twelve, thirteen, fourteen, fifteen. Space one. Well, could this be
the one? And we go wham. One, two, three, four, five, six, eight, nine, ten, eleven, twelve, thirteen.
Nope. Has to be connected. This is done already. Holy shit. Cool. Anything else already done? This
is done. This looks like some kind of, is it like a box? Four. Can't be in the middle there.
It's a snail. Yeah, it's probably going to be a snail. Okay. Seven. I think it's in the middle.
Is it? One, two, three, four, five, six, seven. Okay. Two or two. Don't know yet. It is a snail.
Yeah. Is it going to be a snail? One, two, two, one. All right. A cat? Will it be like a cathead?
No, it's not a cat. Four, two. Don't have the info for that. Two could be in there. One, fifteen.
A lot of shit over here. Let's see. One of these is four. One of these is two. That's the first two.
Or the second two. That could be the second two. Nope. One, four. One, two, one, two, three, four.
One, two, three, four. One, two. Wait, I don't have that info, do I? Yeah, I do. One, two, three, four.
Nine, one. Oh, shit. Cool. All right. And it's four. Nice. Yeah, it's definitely a snail.
All right. So that means two, one, one. Close that off. There's your two. There's your one.
The whole thing is gone. Maybe it's a dog. Four. Anything else? One, two, two, two, two, two, two,
one. What about this one? One, two, two, one, two. Dinosaur? I think you guys got it right. I think
it is a snail. Four, three, four. One, two, three, four. Okay, so that's two. Block that off. That's
one. Block it off. Block it off. And fifteen. Take a look at that. Done. Nice. Four. Got it. Two. Close
it. Two. Close it. Sixteen can, I think, be completed here. Almost. One, two, one. It's a one-up.
It is a one-up. Oh, shit. Okay. Yeah. Is this like Mario? Wait, this is wrong. One, one, two, three,
four, five. One, two. How's that wrong? It's a number DMCA. How did I get DMCA'd over this?
That's right, right? No, no. Stop, stop, stop, stop. Don't be an idiot.
It's done. Two, two, two. One, one. Done. One, two. Shit. One, two, one. Oh, there it is. Nice.
One-up. Extra life. It really did look like a snail, though. This one is very weird. Okay.
Uh, I guess let's just start putting it out. One, two, three, four, five, six, seven.
Seven. One, one, four. One, one, one, one, one. Okay. Ten, seventeen, eighteen. But hold on.
Let me just do this first. One step at a time. Seven. Okay. All right. Four. There's another
four in here. Number nineteen is the whole way down. Oh, shit. Okay. Yeah, you're right. It is.
The bottom is blocked off. You're right. Okay. Oh, my God. I have to do the top now. All right.
I'm getting overwhelmed if I don't stop. What else do I have that's guaranteed? Somewhere in here.
One, two, three. These are all ones, so just block it off. Bottom one. Ten, seven. Yep. One,
two, three, four, five, six, seven. One, two, three, four, five, six, seven. Now we do the
bottom. All right. This is done. All the way up. This one is done there. One, one, one, one.
No, that's four. Four. All row. Nice. Oh, God. This is the most boring game to watch,
Jerma, please. Go watch one of the other 700 million streams. Just change the look.
An infomercial is on right now on this channel. Just like, you can flip around. Is this a QR code?
I don't know. Yo, it's a QR code. No, this is fun. I'm having fun. Can I go this way?
Picross is like one of my favorite video games ever made. It's right next to Diablo II.
If this shit was on that 100 best games of all time list, it would have been numbered three.
One, one, maybe 10. All right. Wait, wait, wait. One, two, three, four, five, six, seven,
eight, nine, 10. One, two, three, four, five. It's all in here. He loves Picross,
but he hates Tetris. Yeah, because Tetris is stupid. Fuck you.
I don't like Tetris. Is that illegal to say? I don't like Tetris. I don't like Tetris.
It's gonna be the four. Nope. Yeah, it could be. That is illegal. All right. Hold on. Almost done.
Three, four. So it can't be this one. All right. There's so many ones and fours. I'm gonna lose
track here. One, one. Next thing is two fours in a row. Is this a maze? I don't know. Well,
there's another one here, another one here, and then a seven. One, two, three, four, five, six, seven.
One, two, three, four, five, six, seven. Right? The seven has to be in the middle here. Good. I do
not like Tetris. Tetris is fun to watch somebody that knows what they're doing, but not for me to
play it. He said he loved Tetris in an Overwatch stream like four years ago. I'm making it up. I
don't know. Show me the clip. You show me the clip of me talking about how much I love Tetris.
You tell me. I want to see it. One, four, one. There's another one here. Find it. Find it.
I need the fours here. This is one, four, four, one, seven, one, four. Let's just say it's here.
That means it would be one, two, three, four. I can deduce that. Do I read chat? I've been reading.
How would I come up with all the things you guys are saying? How would I come up with all the things
you guys are saying? Okay. That hit a seven writer. Nope. That's a one, seven, one. Shit.
False comments. I Tetris. No, I get too frustrated when I play Tetris. I can't do it.
I get omega frustrated. Okay. One, seven. It's going to get harder. I guess I'll get harder.
Then two, three, four, five, six, seven, eight, nine, ten. There's another one here. So let's
just say it's here. That means let's just say one, two, three, four, five, six, seven, eight,
nine, ten. Does that do anything for me? It does. That actually does a lot. I hope it's right. Okay.
One, two, three, four, five, six, seven, eight, nine, ten. How are you guys doing? I didn't ask
that. Did I? Did I ask that? Did I ask how you guys are doing today? I should have. How are you?
Hard things. You got a test tomorrow? Shit. It's all right. You have to do fine. Remember, don't
worry. But if you get, as long as you get like a C plus to a B minus is fine. Don't let anybody
tell you differently. I've got seven here. There's one here. Get this one. I'm going to have to start
here. So let's see. Two, three, four, five, six. Now it's still the same. Okay. Xbox. Turn off.
Going kind of sad because I don't like school. Neither did I. Neither did I. I actually really
didn't like school. I thought it was like boring and annoying and it pissed me off. But I did it.
I got through it. I was doing enough. I think we put too much pressure on like kids to do really
well in school. We teach them stuff they have to memorize and then we base how smart they are based
on how much they remembered. Which I think that's not the correct way to do things. But you know,
I'm looking for the one that's over here. This is almost done. Here we go. One, one, four. This is
the four. One, two, three, four. One, two, three, four. I think that's correct. This has to be the
seven. Oh God. This is a guess, but it's I'm taking an educated guess here. This is a guess,
but whatever. Guessing Gary. I think that's right. But people learn so differently. I honestly,
I think our entire education system has been still doing the same things that they did back
in like the forties. Like there's so much shit that we need to know that we need to learn that
are important. Like why are we still treating school like it's a 19, like fucking 20? I don't
understand. I don't know why. We literally have cars that are going to fucking start driving on
their own. We're still using the same like educational system from like the fucking thirties.
Why? I don't know. Oh, I was, I thought you guys, okay. I thought you guys were saying 7-Eleven.
Like 7-Eleven, like go to 7-Eleven. I thought it was like a weird stream joke thing you guys
are doing. Seven, seven. Okay. Hold on. Oh, right here. Like go to 7-Eleven, 7-Eleven,
get like a Slurpee. I don't know. I thought you guys are making a weird joke. Oh wow. That
changed everything. Oh shit. Okay. This one was done. Hungry, hungry hippos. Actually not a bad
idea. One, one. It's done. What the hell are we looking at here? You know what I mean? Like,
what is this? Four? Four? Some kind of maze? Hold on. Go back. I think, I think I just didn't
want to do that. Hold on. Four. What is this? Labyrinth. That's kind of dull. Labyrinth.
Oh, this one looks cool. This is 20 by 20. Oh no. It's an FTK maze. This is the whole thing.
Any of the big ones? Seven would be one, two, three, four, five, six, seven. Two, three, four,
five, six, seven. I mean, I know I can't deduce that, but I don't care. I'm keeping it there.
N-eleven, 12, 13, 14. Uh, new ISD. But, um, Hearthstone. No, no, no. Hearthstone. Fine. How
about The Sims 1? I think that's pretty good. I'll be playing this when I get back. I'm gonna do a
Sims 1 stream. Multiple streams probably. Okay. Well, very obviously this is connected together.
There's no way it's not. Eight, nine, ten, eleven. That would be, let's just say one, two, three,
four, five, six, seven, eight. Space one, two. Or we could do one, two, space. So that would be
right there. One, two, three, four, five, six, seven, eight. One, two, three, four, five, six,
seven, eight. Three, four, five, six, seven, eight. All right. That looks pretty good to me.
Fourteen would be how much on each side? It'd be like this, right? Six, one, two, three, four, five,
six. Yay. Yay. Gabby J. Yay. Yay. I have, I have an actual curiosity for you guys.
How many times over the last five years on Twitch have I done the super punch out Gabby J. guy?
It's probably like five to ten times. I've done it a lot. It's been at least three to five times.
At least probably ten. I don't know why it just pops in and just does it. Okay. Seven. There it is.
I didn't do it yesterday. I wasn't streaming yesterday. What are you talking about?
He did it yesterday. Three, four, five, six. Two, three, four. He did it yesterday. Six, seven.
All right. Getting there. Revoice Andy. Ow. How did you just hurt me? Well, this is interesting.
Is this the two or the seven? Probably the two. Wait. One, two, three, four, five, six, seven.
Can't be down here. That's the seven. But then none of these can be correct. Cool. That shaves that
down. One, two, three, four, five, six, seven, space, one, two. All right. So let's just say
there's one, two. I'm just saying. That doesn't mean it's, I just scratched your, I scratched you
in the eye. Could it be there? Interesting. Interesting. One, two, three. This whole row
is done for this one. It's probably the two in here. One, two, three. Oh, this is wrong.
This is ugly. What happened here? I think it has solved this, which means this is three and this
is three. One, two, three. Killed out. One, two, three. Killed out. I'd like to solve six, six.
Okay. One, two, three, four, five, six. Get out of here. Get out of here. I like this one. It's
cool. I like this one. This one's nice. I'd like to spin, please. Oh, right. That's from the
Little Fortune game. Is it a goose? I don't know. Well, one is this again. This is completely toast
down here. Nice. Very nice. Very nice. Wait, don't assume. And one, this all goes away. One, two,
three, four. Block those. Can't be there. Can't be there. How does he read messages the moment
they come out? The Five Nights at Freddy's guy. I don't know if this is the four or the three.
It's probably the, it's the four. Okay. So that means this whole thing is done, which means this
is done too. And so is this. Is it a flamingo? It's probably a flamingo. I think it's a flamingo.
Three. Okay. Right there. And this is a three. One, two, three, eight. Two and eight. One, two,
three, four, five, six, seven, eight. This is going to be one. Hello, everyone. How's the stream been?
It's been really comfy and just cozy and hanging out. By the way, reiteration, Andy, because I don't
know how many people have come and gone. We'll just give the quick TLDR again. TLDR. I just
pressed F4. Hopefully it didn't do anything weird. Okay. So I am not going to be streaming
for three weeks. I'll be back on April 1st. There's a ton of projects, huge announcements to make,
some very exciting stuff. A lot of you guys probably going to really, really be into.
So keep on the lookout there. TLDR. I need to get my medical shit solved and treated. I need to get
a treatment and a procedure for it because it's like six huge fucking projects that if I don't
get it solved, then it's going to be horrible to deal with. So I have to get on top of this
before we do any of these major, major projects among some other personal things. So there you
are. Got to get on top of this because I can't let it just sit around. I can't keep just like,
well, I don't, I did all this stuff six, seven months ago, eight, like a year ago. And I,
there's nothing really, there's nothing really horribly wrong with me, but there's something
wrong with me that needs to be treated. Oh, there you go. I have to get on it because it's starting
to cause problems again. There we go. That's the one, daisy three, one, two, three. All right.
That's done. What about here? One, two, one, two, three, four, five, six, seven. I can't do it yet.
I remember this song. This is the four. I don't know. All right. Hold on. Close my one eye.
Oh, what the hell am I doing? Yeah. All this is nothing. All this is nothing too.
Okay. Does that help me or three? Okay. Well that's done. Uh, one, two, three, somewhere over there.
12, one, two oatmeal. I think that's right. One, three, four. It's gotta be a three in here.
Wait this way. Two, one, two. Oh shit. That's it. That's two, one, two, one. And now that therefore
this has to be connected here to, it's a flamingo. One, three, four. There's nothing here.
One, three. Definitely not here. Okay. One, two, three, one, two, three. Third row here. Okay. Good.
And then here's number four, two, two, two. Why does it have a weird like
puzzler? What's it called? Four, three, four. Is that the three or the four? I don't know.
Five, three, five, three. Here. Is it a swan or a stand? It could be like a staff. I don't know.
Could be something weird. One, three, four. Crane. Yeah. Two, two, 14 going down. Oh shit. Hold on.
One, two. Well, 13, 14. I think I can deduce that. Yeah, that can be deduced. Four, three, four.
The leg's kind of bent. Did I do it right? I think that's good. That looks a little weird.
I think that's correct. Done. Done. Three. This is toast. This is toast. Toast. Two. Three. Three.
What are we missing here? All right. What is it? A turkey? That's an ostrich. Very cool. All right.
I'm going to do something else real quick. I want to go to the workshop. I'm very curious about
something. See, this is what I did. So these are all from the workshop and they're hidden.
What are these? Because they're hidden. I'm kind of afraid. So this is 78. This is 30 by 30.
I'm going to play it, I guess. Oh my God. This is so much. 30 by 30. So if it's 20, it means
it kept one, two, three, four, five, six, seven, eight, nine, 10. Two, three, four, five, six,
seven, eight, nine, 10. These are guaranteed. 23, 24. Oh, hold on. One, two, three, four, five,
six, one, two, three, four, five, six, one, two, three, four, five, six, one, two, three,
okay. 26, 27. Don't torture yourself with this. But what does this have to do with
Jerma? This is the final boss. 22, 23, 24, 25, 26, 27, 28. I can get a lot of these right here.
22. Hold on. Let's see. One, two, space. One, two, space. 22 now. One, two, three, four, five,
six, seven, eight, two. Okay. So we go like this. It has to be there. Somewhere in there.
Now check this out. We get a lot of info here. Oh, come on. Give me more data. Give me some more
data. 20. Is that 20? I don't know. One, two, five, six, seven, eight, nine, 10, 15, 16, 17,
18, 19, 20. Cool. 15 now. So down to here. 15, 14, 13, 11. Okay. And that's all the data that
I have right now. It's going to be the J. We'll find out. All right. 22 now. So we can go,
let's count. So 22 minus eight on either side. One, two, three, four, five, six, seven, eight.
One, two, three, four, five, six, seven, eight. There we go. I'm very curious of what this actually
is. 21. Holy shit. What are the arrows on the top left for? I think to zoom in. 21. Okay. This is
all the way across. 21 though. Is that, let's see, five, 10, 15, one, five, 10, 15, 20, 21,
two, three, four, five, six, seven. I mean, that's, I can do that. Six, five, again, five again,
four. Cool. Seven, seven, eight. What the hell is it? What is this? Is it just nothing? No,
it has to be something. It's not just nothing. Well, here's the five and then this is the six
on two, three, four, five, six, nine. All right. What else can I do up top? Let's add these together.
Six, seven, eight, nine, 10, 11, 12, 13. That would be 21 across. It's 16. So let's go like this.
Two space. Now we, so now that's 27. So if it's, wait, yeah, 27. We need 16. So 27
was, what am I doing? Right. Six, seven, eight, 14, 15, 16. So how many, it's 10,
11 spaces on either side. Six, seven, eight, nine, 10, 11, 17. It's one, two, three, four, five, six,
seven, eight, nine, 10, 11, 12, 13, 14, 15, 16, 17. One, two, three, four, five, six.
This is a pain in the ass. Five, 10, 15, 16, 10, nine, five, six, seven, eight, nine. Okay.
One that's 22, right? 22. That'd be 20. So one space would be 28. So we need to count,
um, we need to count 28 minus, we need to count six spaces on each side. One, two, three, four,
five, six. One, two, three, four, five, six. Okay. That do anything for me? Well, this is
definitely part of his 13. One, two, three, that'd be four. That's, I have six, 13 here. Is that 13
the whole way across? Okay. 21, seven. I can't do that here. Uh, this one could be done. That's,
that's 21, 22, 23. Not yet. Three, 21, 22. Yeah, we can connect this, which would be one. That's
five. God damn it. Little green lines. I'm 21, 22. Jesus. I'm almost done with that. Okay.
It's a terraria screenshot. I don't know what it is. 22 across. Why are these here? Why are these
here? Why do they put these here? These, these don't belong here, right? No, they don't.
Across to your past self. Well, 19. Let's connect 18. Maybe not. Um, this is eight.
Now it's actually just eight across, which makes this six. It's going to be among us. I don't have
any, I don't think that's what this is. Any of the huge numbers I didn't do yet? 23.
These sell candles that smell like you. Oh my God. You psycho. Four, five, six. One, two, three,
four, five, six. Oh, 21. What was it? 21, three, 21, one, three. Where's that at? 21, one, three.
What side is it on? Oh, 21, three. Okay. Oh, nice. We got even more data. Oh, I love when we unlock
data. Good. This is three, 15. That's done. And that's done. The whole thing's done. Okay. Cool.
What is the, okay, come on. 26. I feel like I can do this one. 26, one. That's 26, 27, and 28.
Let's go down here with space. So that would be, I need to count backwards if we're at 28.
So two, so one, two, and then the rest of these can be filled in. One, two, fill in the rest. Okay.
Get rid of these. I invested my life savings in bald coin currently filing for bankruptcy.
Seven, and then this is nine, nine. Is this nine right here? One, two, three, four, five, six, seven,
eight, nine. Perfect. One, two, three, four, five, six, seven, eight, nine. How many are here? 10, 11,
12. Some three on both sides. One, two, three. Fill those in. Cool. It's going to be 100% your
dumpy. Well, so this is six and 12. One, two, three, four, five, six. One, two, three, four,
five, six. It's definitely this one at least. 100%. Remember, it's just going to get high
and drink Heal for three weeks. Medical leaf my ass. Well, this is connected. Is there anything
I can do up here? All right. 20 and three. That's definitely connected. Six, eight, two.
I can't believe you just read anything someone says. Why not? It's not like that big of a deal.
It's, they're just, all right. This, what about this 16? Let's get this one. There you go. There's
your one. So if it's 16, there's 30 spaces. That means 30, 29, 28, 27. So count 11 spaces. One,
two, three, four, five, six, seven, eight, nine, 10, 11. These can be filled in. Mario. Watch it
just be a Mario like shitting thing. Like the ASCII art. Is he getting paid to play this?
Yes. Yes, I am. Yes, I am. I am getting paid on this stream.
Not by the company that made this, but by some of you. Some of you have paid me today. Saved.
287. That'd be eight, seven. This is how many? What is here? 15. Wait, wait, wait. This is probably
15. Closed up. That's part of the 15. This is definitely part of the 14. Wait, it might not be.
I don't know that yet. That's a guess. All right. One, two, space. Is this all I could do here?
Yeah, I already did that. That would be one, two, three, four, five, six. What about these rows here?
This is nine. Nine, nine, four, five, 11, five, two, three, four, five.
I connected there. What the hell even is this? Six, 14. I feel like I'm missing a bunch down here.
18. Let's do this one. 18 and one. Let's see. One, two, three, four, five, six, seven, eight,
nine, 10, 11, 12, 13, 14, 15, 16. It has to be there. One, two, three, four, five, six,
seven. That has to be blocked. Also seven. That's already blocked. Also six. One, two, three,
four, five, six. Okay, that's fine. This is also six. One, two, three, four, five, six. One, two,
three, four, five, six, five, five, nine, ten. Pot of coffee? Okay, hold on. This one here seems
like it could be done. 12, seven in a row. Eight, nine, 10, 11, 12, three, seven. Damn it.
You need to start pretending. I don't think so. I'm overwhelming myself. This 17 right here.
Look at 17. One, two, three, four, five, six, seven, eight, 13, 14, 15, 16, 17.
Shit. One, two, four, six, seven, eight, 13, 14, 15, 16, 17. I think that's it. I think so.
Then it's like two. Yeah, that's right. Eight, four, five, six, seven, eight, one, two, three.
Okay. All right, getting there. You can't assume the bottom two. I can assume. Yes, I can. Six,
12. This is broken up here. Let's just assume that this is one, two, three, four, five, six,
right? Right? Let's assume that. Three, four, five, six, seven, eight, nine, 10, 11, 12.
No, don't assume that. Let's just, we have to assume it. Forum two is in here. Wait a minute.
One, two, three, four, space two. I think this is going to be one, two, three, four, or one, two,
three, four, space two. This is so much better than bi-mode one. This is a great song.
Did we do this? Is this done? One, let's see. Five, 10, 15, 20, 22. No, it's 21. It can either
go up or down. I don't know why this is freaking me out so much. I think this is connected.
Okay, this has to be connected. This is part of the 14. 12, 6. This is part of the 12. All right,
what about up top here? 12, 10, 2. Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa. Here we go. Is this 12 right here?
Four, five, six, seven, eight, nine, 10, 11, 12. Nice. This is part of the 10. Three, four, five,
six, seven, eight, nine, 10. All right, I can't deduce that yet. Is this your face? It could be.
I don't know. Is it the chin? Is it the thing face? It could be either one of those.
All right, I got, what about this one? 13, 4, 2. 13, 4. Uh-oh. No, wait, that's one. Okay.
This could be the two or the four. It's probably the four. One, two, three, five, 10, 12, 13.
Well, let's deduce it. 10, 11, 12, 13. One, two, three, four, five, six, seven, eight, 13.
I'm going to assume this is the four. I don't think that's the two.
All we have left is fours and threes, so this has to be connected. This could be this way first,
so this is good. It's not singles. It has to be connected. Not singles. Wait, hold on. Wait,
I don't know that. That's not for sure. 2, 13. It can't be any of these. Oh, shit. There we go.
13. Oh, there's your three. Okay. One, two, three, four, five, six. Definitely not that way.
We got 16, two. There's, I got one here. Four. One, two, three, four. This has to be one of
these two, right? Is it the goblin face? It could be anything. It's part of the three. 19, 22, 26.
I love this song. This is awesome. Piss? Yeah, that's a good idea. I'm going to go piss.
Be right back. Go pee. See you in a minute. I swear to God. I swear to God. That was an animation.
That's cool. There's no escape from you guys. That was terrifying. Very, very cool. Let's
head back to it. That's so cute. What I was going to say is I swear to God, when I drink water,
you know, when you fill up like a Brita filter and it takes maybe five to 10 minutes, maybe 15
minutes. But when you pour it at the top, it filters the water down at the bottom. I swear
to God, that's what my body does. I drink a water and my inner Brita filter just does it. Just takes
all the impurities and I piss it out within 10 minutes. Why do I pee? I have to pee so much.
Why do I pee all the time? Why am I constantly peeing? I think I process urine faster than a
Brita filter does. Anyways, you need to replace your filters. It's your kidneys. I've had my
kidneys checked. I've had my kidneys ultrasound. I've had blood work from my kidneys. There's
nothing wrong with them. They're like perfect. But how? They're not. They need to be more efficient.
Are they too efficient? All right. Anyways, where are we? Your kidneys are fucking jacked.
All right. Here's the three. Close that up. Over efficient kidneys. We have some info here.
Three, nine, one, two, three, four, six, seven, eight, nine. You can't do it. You're pregnant.
Oh, shit. Hold on. So this is the eight or the seven? This is probably the seven.
Seven, none. Then we have eight. One, two, three, four, five, six, seven, eight.
We got how many spaces do we have? Five, 10, 11, nine, eight. That. Perfect. So that's one. We got
a one and a three, one and a two, one and a two, one and a two, one and a two.
This is the six. Oh, two and a two, one, two. Oh, yeah. It's definitely the thing,
face. It for sure is. All right. So what about this? This is seven and the two is
somewhere over here. Is 12 fit here now? You cannot deduce it. We have to go like this.
Three. All right. And then six, which is done already. What's left up here? Just a couple of
ones. Yeah, this is custom made. This is on the workshop. One, two. This is part of the two.
Therefore, this is part of the 10. That's 12. Yeah. OK. Three, four, five, six, seven, eight, nine,
10. Hey, wait, I can't be there and can't be there either. Wrong. No, it's not. It's the dump truck.
No, it's only the thing face. It's a baby elephant sitting on his hind legs. That's an amazing
imagination you have. OK, cool. This is like looking at a cloud. Everybody sees something
different. Nineteen. Well, it's obviously not down there. It's a baby dragon. Oh, I could probably
see that. Wow. Well, this has to be the six because there's no way it has to be filled in.
What is this one? Wait, one. What did I do? One, two, six, two, six. Wait, where am I?
One, two, six, two, 11. One, two, three, four, five, six, seven, eight. Oh, God, this is wrong.
What happened? This is so many numbers. Wait, wait, wait, wait. No, back up, back up, back up.
What did I take away? God, I need to like zoom in. Jesus, this is painful. Two, six,
two. No, that's correct. What? Two right here and then 11, four, five, six, seven, eight, nine, ten,
eleven, ten, four, two. Okay, is there four in here? Anything else I can do in here in the meantime?
Three, nine. Okay, that's done. This is 14, three and a bunch of other stuff. This is 15, four,
a bunch of other stuff. 23, one, one, 17, two, one, 16, one. Oh, yeah, let's just together. Hold on.
One, two, three, four, five, six, 13, 14, 15. Let's see, so it can't be down here, right?
15, 16, so it can't be either one of these. That would be 14 this way. Is that correct?
11, 12, 13, 14. Hell yeah. I was done. One, two. This is nine. Five, six, seven, eight, nine.
And this one is, hold on, slow down. Eight, one, two, six, seven, eight, three, two, three, three.
All right. 12, two. We're getting there. Almost did his that face. This is two. It'll be that way
and then it would be one, two, three, four. Jeremy, can you help me with my homework? Yes,
a multiple choice. Question one through 10. A, C, B, A, C, A, A, A, B, D, A, D, B, A, B, D, C,
A, C, D, B. Done. A, C, D, C. That was more than 10. Oops, that was like 12, whatever. Who has
multiple choice for homework? That would be so awesome. Oh my God, that would be incredible,
wouldn't it? You don't have to get it right. You just have to hand it in. You imagine being in
homeroom and just writing like B, A, B, B, B, D, C, A, B, B, D, B, B. Done. Hand it in.
Does everybody have their homework? Yeah, I do. Here it is. Oh, okay. Thank you. Check for the day
of bringing your homework in. Do the bottom row? No, I can't do the bottom row. Why did you lie to
me? Bottom left. Five, 10, 15, 20, 21, 22. All right. Give it your best. Mine was better. All
right. 15, 5, 10, 15, 9, 3, 1, 11, 2. Now it's done. 16 this way. 2, that's done. Okay. Nice.
Oh shit. What happened here? What happened down here? 22, 16, 2 is busted. Is it?
Bottom right should not have Xs. Is this 22 though? 1, 2, 3, 4, 5, 6, 7, 8, 9, 10,
19, 20. No, that was wrong too because it could know it was right. Then there's a 2 in here.
Um, there's nothing here. Or here. It can't be. 16 to the right one? 16 to the right one.
When are you gonna play The Sims 1? Um, when I get back. That's what the first thing will do.
I'm really looking forward to playing it. This is a pretty lackluster 500k stream. I didn't even
know I was at 500,000 followers. You told me that an hour ago. I didn't have time,
didn't really have time to prepare a 500,000 follower stream. Look, the archaeology stream
was for 500,000 followers. There you go. You're actually at 500. This is wrong somehow down here
and I don't know what the problem is. 19, can't be any of these. That's 3. Where are these last two?
The 1, 16 row, please. 1, 16 row. Here. What's wrong with it? 1, 2, 3, 4, 5, 6, 7, 8, 11, 12, 13,
14, 15, 16. What's wrong with it? What's the matter with it? Attach it to the wall.
You mean like this? Then, oh man, it's starting to get painful to look at. So many numbers.
Um, so then this would have to go away because that's your two, but then there's not 14 here
anymore. 11, 12, 13, 14, which 13, 1, 2, 3, 4, 5, 6, 14, 15, 16. Shit! On the right is not the two.
Look, there's like a hundred numbers on the screen. Bottom right two. This is, this is
fucked up though. 23 isn't right. God damn it, man. That connects to make 16. This does? Wait.
This is 16, 1, 2, 3, 4, 5, 6, 7, 8, 9, 10, 11, 12, 13, 14, 15, 16.
Two. That's over. There's still shit that's wrong. 18. These are connected. 1, 1, 2, 3, 4, 5, 6.
1, 2, 3, 4, 5, 6. 1, 2, 3, 4, 5. Uh oh. 9. This is 2, 4, 15. 1, 2, 3, 15, 4.
And 4, 4, 2. There's a 1 in there. Move 16 on the right down 1.
Like that. Like that. Do we got it? I don't know. Okay, so now that's 18.
Two in here somewhere. 5, 10, 6, 12, 8, 6, 1. That's blocked. But this is wrong. Oh wait,
change that. That's 5 now. This is 9. We believe in you. 2, 2, 2, 2 at 2, 2, 1, and 26, 1. What?
Somebody just said true? 26, 1, the 1 goes to the very bottom. 26, 1. 1 to the 1 to the 2.
1, 1 to the 2 to the 1. 2 to the 1 to the 1 to the 2 to the 6. Get out of here.
All right, so this is 16, 2. That's done. What about this one? This is 1, 2. This is the 3.
This is the 12. 4, 5, 6, 7, 8, 9, 10, 11, 12. This is the 3. 1, 2, 3. Can't be here.
1, 2, 3. Can't be here. 5, 12. That one's done. This whole row is done. 4, 12, 1. Can't be any of
these. This one now is 1, 3, 5, 6. Is he streaming from his bathroom? Streaming from his bathroom.
I mean, I guess I'll give you a courtesy flush. Okay, where were we? Is this 12 in here? No,
I can't. This is 1, 1, 1, 2, 3, 12. Can't do that. This row's done. Do I have everything
blocked off that needs to be blocked off? 22, 1. This is it right here, right? Where else would
that 1 go? Here's the 2. It's with the 3 and then 20. That's done. Nice. Why highlight your message
when the word toilet will catch his eye? That's a really good point. 18. None of these make any sense.
I really love Germestreams. Toilet. What community Jake on? I want to talk to him. Well, that's too
bad. What do you want to talk to him about? Huh? What do you want to talk to him about?
Toilet. Toilet. Toilet. Toilet. Toilet. Toilet. Toilet. Toilet. Toilet. Toilet. Toilet. Toilet. Toilet.
Toilet. Let me just finish this and stop distracting me. 5, 10, 2. This is 11, 11, 5. All right.
six twelve
Okay, well, how many one two?
Wait nice three. Ah ha
aha
Require you you require my assistance. Ah ha ha ha ha ha
Ha that's not Trump. Why is that Trump?
Aha, you require my how is that Trump? What are you talking about?
eight six one two
three four five six one two
nine seven that's a four
this is a
two
two six three six
Show us the real Trump voice. Okay
Okay, I'm doing anything you want to do
Yeah, I don't have any other questions, please
two three four five six nine nine
eight nine
four
politics
That's my favorite cupcake flavor toilet
It's probably I'm less of a cupcake guy and more of a muffin guy
I think muffins are better cupcakes, especially when they're really dense. I like a nice dense blueberry muffin
That is what I want more wet less dry. I don't like a dry cake like cupcake. It's gonna be moist
So this is how I give you the my determination for what that would mean by this
If you take a muffin and you squish a piece of it between your fingers
If it sticks together and acts like a snowball like it squishes together and is wet. It's slightly damp
That's how you know, you've got a great muffin like slightly moist
blueberry moist dense muffin or chocolate chip or coffee cake a coffee cake muffin
Cupcakes are I think that junk I do because all you do is you just bite the top off and just
Put the right you don't even eat the rest of it
The actual cake part of a cupcake is a good part that I don't like to eat
So why just might as well just take a spoonful of frosting out of the container. That's what I want
All right, let's connect this. This is five here one, two, three, four five finish that one yet
I don't know where these go. All right. There's my funny four here one, two, three four one, two, three four
one of these one three two four one three two four one
Be six. Oh shit. I can't be anywhere in here. Wait, hold on another two in here. That's actually pretty great
Yeah, it is. I sure he's passing really good
It's almost done over to this other side here. Anything be completed here five five eleven five
Well, this is this the best song in the whole album I love this one it's fantastic or I need to pick a place and just stay
These are all done. This is done. This is done. This whole everything over here is done. I need to look be looking this way
13 here we go. All right, one two, four 13
There we go to wait a minute. This is wrong
nine
What happened 13 is too long
Move 13 up one six one
two
I subverted and this would be one three two one three two two
takes care of that
nine seven two three
three six or
one
One one here in here
Someone made this. Yeah, they did. Does it kill him when the clock reaches an hour? I've never seen the song movie before. Oh
Six one six eight
It's a three in here too. One two three
Shit, I don't know. Mmm, the one goes over here. I have no idea. All right, so I'm gonna concentrate
I'm not I'm just not I'm gonna stop talking
So I'm just gonna concentrate and stop speaking, but it's okay. You'll still hear things
Not like any of this commentary has changed at all
Shit, I don't know
Mmm, shit. I don't know if the one goes over here
The one goes over here. I have no idea
Mmm, the one goes over here. I have no idea shit. I don't know. I have no idea shit. I don't know. Mmm
The one goes over here. The one goes over here. Mmm. The one goes over here shit. I don't know. I'm done. That's annoying
do six
Just solve it. What are you? What do you think? I'm doing it six one two, three, four, five six
six
Is it two in here? There's another six in here. Mmm
Mmm
Mmm, I think the one goes over here. I think the one goes over here
Shit, I have no idea. I have no idea. I think the one goes over here. I have no idea. Mmm
I think the one goes over here. I think the one goes over here. I have no idea shit. I don't know
eight six one two three four five six
One wait, did that do something for me? Sixteen one
Dude, there's a two in here
There's another four
There's a three and a three and a four
Okay, wait, nice. Okay, that one's done. Finally
Where's the 18?
Three four seven seven six four four three
Nice. All right, we're almost done
Very very close one two
three four five six seven eight nine
One two, three, four five six seven eight nine. Oh boy
Three it's nice jazz. What? Yeah, what? Oh, this is Sims, right? I thought this was Mario Galaxy again
I feel this is not I don't think I can do the nine yet
Two three so it has to be here one two three
one two three
That would be part of the two. I'm assuming. Let's see. This is
roses
one
one two one
two
One there it is. Okay, brings us to the end here
This is what's wrong with that? What's wrong with the eye?
or
I've one two three four five one two three four five one two three four five
one three
one two
This is done
One what's going what's wrong with his eye?
17 2 1 1
3 that doesn't look right. Is this not done correctly 1 4
4. Oh, wait a minute. This is wrong 3 and then there's a 4 in here dear. Wait, this isn't the wrong place
One four five. Oh my god. This is so fucking messed up
This is five and this is four wait wait no no four five
four
one four five four one what four five
four one
What's going on here?
Or or
Jesus
Just X amount. I can't like I have to like hold my eyes closed for a second
What am I looking at turns fucking music off? I feel like I'm just stuck in a fucking elevator
Alright, what are we doing? Get me a Kimmy out of the goddamn elevator
one two one
four
five four
That's right
One four. Oh, man. I'm like just exhausted looking at this. Just tell me the answers
I'm exhausted like I feel like it has did a hundred people's homework
Wouldn't remove all of the left eye. Well, you mean my left or his left. I mean his left. Where's the other two?
X's don't belong on one four four three
Okay. Um
This is a really bad stream. Hope you have a great three weeks Jeremy. Good night
No, you could have just said the second part
You could have just said the second part. Fuck your eyeball out. Alright skip to get other music. Give me out of the elevator
I guess this is where it's name
Sims 1
Where I
Can't even look I don't know. I'm lost completely. I'm like I'm my brains over
My brains fried is done. I'm so close. But like I can't finish it
This is like when you study right before the exam and you get to the point
We're at like the flashcard number 20 like 30 50 500 and you're like, I can't look at this anymore
If I like went to sleep and woke up and came back, I probably would beat this
one
The fact that I have to look all the way down the screen. Okay, two three six four one
There's two ones in here somewhere
There's like two in the wrong spot and I'll just never figure it out top of the right eye should be filled in
Yeah, like in here, but it's like everything's moved around
Go back to the way it was before hold on like back here before I freaked out
One four five four row delete the left eye one four five four row
happened here
Your other left. Well, yeah, I thought you guys are on my left
So wait, so there's nothing he there's nothing here
How could there be nothing there?
What's wrong with this? I?
Okay, so there's a one here. I need four
or three
one two
That right, I think
Exactly, that's correct. There's another one
Okay, there's this two one four four three has an incorrect X one four four three
One four five four still wrong. It's so close. I just had it's it's just pissing me off
Get rid of the X's in your left. Eye. They're wrong. So race the entire eye
Six it's just so much fucking info three six six. This is done. Like this is correct
That's it. There's no more you can't put the sixes anywhere else. This is done, too. It has to be right
I can't put this over here. The mouth is wrong. What the top row is wrong
I'm not gonna reset
I just I'm at that point where there's like five things wrong and really specific place and it requires me moving the whole fucking
Picture like five pixels to the left fuck Hearthstone get off. All right, I'm gonna start the bottom eight six
one six three six three five
two two
six six three
Reads a four is this the other four?
Was it in here?
That kind of has to be in here
Get rid of all the X's in one four four three all of them
Shift the nine on the top row one space to the right
Okay, now what?
now
the left has the left two has to
re
These are done. These are done. What was this?
Okay. All right. All right. All right. All right. Let me do I need to go like they inject protein like into my neck
I I'm my brain can't do it anymore. That's the one that's scary
Look at the two look at the grip. All right, but they're out like they're like 15 twos here. You're so close
I know but like it's like one of those things like fucking where's Waldo if you can see Waldo
I know but I can't see Waldo. I have no idea where Waldo is
He could be like with a chef's hat on right here flipping pancakes. I can't see him. He's right there
Sucks when you get this far like you I can't piece it together. I'm turning off chat. I'm minimizing the window
I have to just fucking sit here and stare at it
Hi, four four five four one
Four one two three
six four
One one one one one one. There's two ones here somewhere. No, don't do that. Oh no
I'm lost like completely. It's I like the image is done in my brain
I mean like the image is completed so I can't fix it. I can't fit the image is done in my head
It's like oh, there it is. There's this face. I can't like I can't fix it
It's like five blocks
What is this toilet two two six six three should be two filled in after the second X. Hold on
I'm gonna I have to sit here and stare at this comment two two six three two two six six three
Should be two filled in after the second X. Thank God that guy has a toilet in his room
Two two six six three two two six six three. All right, that one's done. Give me another one. All right
I want this row now move two three four four over by left one
I need some toilet people. I need some people that have toilets in their rooms. I can help me
It's like yeah, I've ever just done in my brain. I'm fucking just twisted right now toilet German
I love no. No, I need one. Wait. Wait. Thank you move three and two three four four row one left toilet
Okay, good. Thank you. Move three in two three four four two three four four one left
Yo, I need more toilets for you sound like a dad
toilet take toilet take a look at the one two one four two three one column one
Just made that up. You made that column up one two one
You're fucked. Take a look at this column. You're fucked one
one three
four
one
Two one there has to be a two in here. Where's the two go here? Where's the two go here then the two two?
Five take the five six one column and move it three left
Why can't I finish this? There's no five six one column
Where's the five six one?
Two two six six three is wrong toilet two two six six three move the second to right one
That's what you just told me to do the opposite
Two two six six three. What was it move the second to right one two two six six three
Overwrite twice toilet like that two to the one to the one to the three toilet
Get rid of the five in the right eye two to the put that one back
No, I need toilets that I only listen to toilets one four four three
One four four three put other four in left eye like over here
Put the five back you hooligan toilet put the five back toilet happened nice
What about this one? Why wait a minute? What's today?
What is today? This is today. Wait, this is not even today. This is tomorrow. How did you do this? This is tomorrow
Okay, 15. All right, let's get this one done. All right that thank you. That was a lot
I really appreciate the help because I was stuck and I was locked
Well 13 so we can do if we deduce that this could happen to 1 2 3 4 5 6 7 8 9 10 11 12
It's the whole damn thing. It's been deduced 10 11 12 13 14
We can deduce that
Yeah, one is that okay. You're the one in yesterday. I mean, I'm on Pacific time. So all right, what else we got?
Seven eight you're 15 downs. Therefore. That's fine. Five ten eleven twelve thirteen
single four
nine
So we got one two, three, four, five six, seven eight nine ten eleven twelve thirteen twelve eleven ten nine one two
Three four filament one two, three four filament secret boop 15 down
Is there a 15 down? Where do you see 15 down? 10 11 12. So just go like this and we got 10
1 2 3 4 5 6 7 8 9 10 11 12 2 on each side
Left 2 are done. Oh shit. I think we can finish this one 5 10
11 12 13 we can so that's 5
1 5
Cool
This is probably this looks like fireman bridge the 8 up
1 2 3 4 5 6 7
Wait, no, hold on. Hold on. This is for one of the fours
That's probably the first four. Yes, of course it is
7 1 4 1 2 3 4 5 6 7 there we go
to the top row
Okay, this is the 5
1 2 3 4 5 can't be these ones. Oh
We need music. Yeah
7 1 4 is a free toilet. Okay, 7 1 4 is a free toilet 7 1 7
1 space or I believe this one is 2 4 5 6 7 8 9 10 11 12
No, not quite
Or 1 4 is a free toilet or
Correct. Okay, so we got 1 2 3 4 1 2 3 1 2 3 4
Okay
1 2 3
I keep watching that video. Um
This kind of has to be it or 1 1 4. Yeah, this is fireman. I already know what it is. Okay, um
Um 8 1 2 3 4 5 6 7 8 1 2 3 4 5 6 7 8
This is done. We did
2 2 1 2 1 2
interesting
Definitely fireman without a doubt
Okay, 5 3 1 good 9 9
Which one else is done? This is 3
Or this is a 4 5 3
8 very cool. Let's go to the Mario fires
And
1 9
1 2 1
It's just 1 1 2 3 4 5 6 7 8 9 10
Okay, this is almost done
Pretty much am done. This is you. It was an auto. Let me see you. Let me see if autos right here
He wanted a snack. It was just like open that door and give me a treat
Ran and gave him show Otto. No, boy. They give Otto snack. You fell for it. Okay, let's finish this up 1 2
That's done
That's done. That's done. That rose done 1 2 3 4 5 6 7 8 9 1 2 3 4 5 6 7 8 9
Yeah
Done
This one you didn't do anything
Who knows what we adventures we can uncover? So, oh wait, this is my chance
This is my chance to do this and have it make sense and have nobody leave. This is the League of Explorers
Who's ready for some adventure? It's me. Sir. Friendly Margleton
Now you can't leave because it made sense as to why I did that. It's the worst character ever. I think why is it?
Come on play. All right. Let me get this done
I mean I can just fill it in
Let's do it. Hurry up. Let's do it. Hurry do it
Let's guess
started guessing
Big head
All right, where was I before? Okay. Okay. How am I supposed to pull this out of here? That's okay. That was correct
What are you hurry 1 2 3 4 5 6 7 8?
All the X's in
What do you mean 9 please 9, please
Or let's call them 9 add 2 on top
How do you know that though? How do you know that?
7 3rd from what he's toilet 7 a toilet that guy's wrong. You have to go on the bottom
Yeah, how would you know that you that there's no way to know that?
Almost done undone done. I need one. This is 1 2 3 4 5 6 7. Okay, it's not right
I don't know. I don't care
5 plus 2 is 7 on I toilet 7 plus 2 on the other side. I
Yeah, there is fireman. I told you 9 vertical you did you just did that today?
Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait. No, no, no. No, we just did this one another one here. Okay
Well, what about a little small one? This one's fit. This one's huge, but maybe it'll be easy
Although no, no, I want to start the other ones. This one's 30 30
Let's see this by Devin. I wonder if they're in the chat right now. It's possible. Was this 30 by 30?
It's not even 30 by 30 and 20
24 what about Jesus?
Scared the hell out of me. I look at this one yet. It looks very complicated
Although wait a minute. No, it's not you just gave me the whole thing for free. Oh my god. I was gonna be fun. All right eight
seven eight
five four
three
two two two one
I love when I give you all this free info. It's awesome six and they're all filled in
Get that all done
four
Is this fireman again invite me? I think this is fireman again different version. Okay, what we got?
nine
Seven here one, two, three, four, five six seven eight nine ten eleven and
Nine eight seven. So one two, three four fill them in with the four spaces on the other sides
That will be three two three
Okay, what is this is this a toilet wait, did we already do this one I think I did this one already
Did I yeah and like in the slots?
No, well, that wasn't this one. That was the one
nine
six seven eight nine ten eleven twelve thirteen
twelve eleven ten nine
That was a different one. All right. Wait, wait, wait, so we get five down here work from the bottom. So you get extra space
Lock it lock it
six
decide
Okay, what about down the sides next at some of those columns? Thanks for the toilet. Appreciate it. I appreciate the
Toilet advice I do and nine is in the middle here. We got one two five six seven eight nine. There is
this side five
one
three
either one of these
Here that's one one three
Two three four five, which is a two
Stamp that that's six here
three
means this makes this a
two eight two toilet
Thank you
Eight nine ten eleven twelve thirteen fourteen thirteen twelve eleven ten nine eight
There's your three three four one two two column is free three four one three four one two two
This one free to four three one. I think this is free as well or three
one three
Not free, but I know most of it one two nine one
Two three four five six seven eight nine
Okay, this is dick. I'm not doing like a dick or something, right? What is this? Okay. Um,
three four five six
Do this yet? All right, two eight two
Eight we're in there pick Ross bong
Four six two, where's that?
one four six two one
two, let's see one two
two three four five six
Two one five two one and even though the two
Five
No, I don't know that info yet
One four four two column free one four four two two one
It's free
one four four two
But you don't know that
Yeah, I don't think you know that do you you can't know that
Second two nine three row has more info
easy focusing
Nothing is free. I don't think I can do that. No, I can't do that. I can do that
One one four five one is free now
It is for you. Look at these two is one two
two two
No, I can't do that. No, I three. Hey
One three four one is also free. Is it one three four one? I
Don't know where the fuck that row is one three four one. It's two among us characters
Hi instead of looking over there in this having people say one four three two one one four is free
I'm just gonna just play or three one three one. I don't know the info
Liars, they said I wasn't gonna look over at that
One five one two five three two row free now toilet. Oh, I'm not looking I'm playing. Excuse me or three
One okay, that's I can't complete this but one of these is the eight. Let's go one
five six seven eight
It'd be any of these can't be any of these that can't be any of these that also can't be in here
And this could be a thing that could be a thing that could be a thing
877 cash now a little bit over here seven
Or six two or six in here one two three four fives
Five six
Would be that
Can't do the two
That's a two on there's another two here. There's your eight done
There's your three done
That do anything else for me down here?
Who is the chin? I don't know what it is
three four one
one four
Okay, that's all I can do there one three four. So this is one three four
This one's done
Three in here somewhere
That one's done. So yeah, it's definitely it's the snort. Yeah, it's the snort
Two there's your nine connection here
Six seven eight nine
and four five
Done getting closer
one two
Little one six seven can't do that one. Wait, two two that was done
Three four five six seven
Five six seven
four three
one four three
Two and we've got a one three
Three is three the bottom is your three
for the one up here and then
Three one it's got it's coming together
four
three two
Very nice
three
one, uh-oh
What happened? What happened? Where am I?
one four four
Okay, we're good one four
Only couple more to fill in we're done
three seven
three
Aha, there it is
It's so fixable
It's the original blue one too, I'm actually here. Oh, hold on. I'm curious if I get rid of that most popular
Suspended how about top rated?
size size will do
Let's do like ten and by like ten
What's the top rated ten by ten one on the store?
This is the top rated one of the on the store and then on the workshop
In nine, all right two zero two two
nine
seven
It's a T. It's T
Okay, what is it? Hi. Oh, there's the part this pie. Cool. All right. What about this one?
That was it. That's 600 votes over this one. It's not a level in the game
Could be what that off this off all blocked off. All right, so six I can just do that whole row
four five six seven eight
We have six seven eight
So let's do just do this one two, three, four five six
Seven therefore one on each side
All right, that's two
Hmm, two three. Oh that toilet. How far P can you go? I don't know
another six
Five six seven, it's gonna be one on each side
nice
That's one also a one also a one
one
Also a one. This is Marvel music. No, this is Arthas Menethil this theme song from Hearthstone. I guess
This is four two
One two, three, four five six seven eight one on each side. Thank you very much
This is the this is generic shit
What you don't think that?
That's come on that they could be anybody's song
Mickey Mouse could walk out to this music and it probably makes sense one one one two. There's the two
How's that how do I have nothing up there
done it and
It has to be down here no else place it could be
No, wait, one, two, three, four five. Oh shit. There we go. That's better
That's better. What is this? It's like a guy with a sword
What is that? It's Arthas Menethil
King George
All right, we'll do one more. I'm gonna do one more and then I'm gonna get gone
We will reiterate one more time. What's gonna happen over the next few weeks. I know you guys have a lot of questions. I
Know you guys have a lot of things that you are want to ask and I cannot answer them right now
I will answer them very soon
Who's free?
Six one two, three four five six
You're getting what is a dog. I think it's like a dog face
This looks like a dog. I won one one one. That was so quick. That was that was speed run
graph giraffe with breakfast
No more hard stone. We'll go back to heroes of mind magic
the end
Last one. I love it. It feels so good to do that. Okay
Nine
Okay, we can get these
Sixes, let's see one two, three, four, five six
Seven just one on each side cool
Be there this is the blood elf theme and heroes of my magic. I have three click with your middle mouse button toilet. Oh
Oh
Whoops, sorry
Would have been nice if I was using that the whole time
That was that's too bad. But whatever
One there's three
Do the middle finger
three
No
All right. Good morning. Good morning to you, too. All right, what is it? Oh, it's a magic bunny
Yeah, I all right
Let's make sure we reiterate this one more time. You know, I'm like, I'm repeat myself Andy tonight, but I kind of have to
Only I want to make sure everyone knows what's going on
If you missed the first part of the stream you missed the middle part of the stream
Get the credits rolling too. By the way, there was a lot of community subs. Thank you everybody. Let's go over this very quickly
Let's go. No, why don't I just go I got to talk about this one more time
So I'm gonna be taking some absence here
I'm going to finalize and get to the absolute treatment plan of
This chest and back problem that I've had what's likely to happen is over the next few weeks
I'm going to try to get either intercostal
Injections to shut it up
Probably do it a few places somewhere along the spine
Trigger points and an intercostal potential intercostal nerve injection. I'm gonna try it. I want to try it
I want to do it
Because there's a lot of stuff going on in 2021
The I'm essentially we're we're hitting the ground running on a lot of projects
So there are at least four or five more streams
Like the archaeology stream that you will see within the next six months
This is not like oh, yeah, there's worse. You know, I get like a year when we do something like that again
Because of the nature of doing as many of these as we kind of can in 2021. I have to get this under control
I also have some family stuff and some personal stuff to take care of too. So this is likely to be the final break
before I
Hopefully get over this bullshit with my back and chest and everything and if it's not then i'll keep doing it
But this i'm at least gonna go get the injections. I'm gonna i'm gonna just I talked to my doctor about it
We're setting up a plan. I'm just gonna be like
Just stick me just stick them in me
Because I want to get I need to get a treatment plan. I have to it's been too long with this shit
It's been three years now, obviously I ruled out all the bad stuff and that's what I was doing the two or three months
I was gone ruling out everything that could be terrible
But it's time to take care of it
So I will see you on april 1st and on april 2nd
I will have a shitload of announcements some stuff you're probably really going to look forward to
I know you have a lot of questions about the streams that you may have seen about roto beasts
Just hold off. I will give you way more details. There'll be a lot of announcements in a few weeks
We'll see what I come back with on the 1st of april. Okay
So again, if people don't know what's going on just you tld arm
I really hate to take all this time off because i'm sure you guys all know we just you know
We passed 500 000 followers. The channel is as big as it's ever been and that's kind of like the I guess
I'll be real with you. That's kind of the sad part about this for me is
The channel is like at peak popularity right now like the last like eight to ten months
And i'm just like fucking off every three months or so, you know what I mean?
So that's like kind of sad but at the end of the day
I never cared about that shit. Anyways, you know this channel could have 5 000 viewers
2 000 viewers or 20 000 viewers
I'm still gonna just keep doing the things that I do and if you think it's fun if you're here then
Well, I hope you enjoy it. I hope you like this stuff that we're doing here. Um 20k or 2k
It doesn't matter but not less than 2k. Absolutely not less than 2k. Uh, and I again before I go
There was just so much
It was like an overwhelming amount of things that we were seeing for the stream for the archaeology thing and i'm just so happy that
um a lot of people involved in that project got like the
Attention and the recognition that they deserved and i'm really really happy about the nevada science center stuff, too
So I will be back on april 1st. I'll see you soon. Thanks for watching everybody
This should be the final time that I disappear for more than a couple weeks at a time
And when I get back, maybe i'll maybe i'll fucking run a lap around my room and tell you that I got the
Intercostal injections take care of yourselves. I'll be back on april 1st. Good luck to you all as well. Have fun
Don't miss me too much. I'm not gonna i'm not going for like three months. We're only going for like three weeks
That's it. And then i'm back and i'm gonna be at least 80 to 90 percent time to go get the injections
I'll see you soon. Take care of yourselves
Good night. Goodbye. See you april 1st 80 to 90 percent andy. That's me rerun the simpson stream
My god, that's so funny
I just do that again
I just
Run the simpson stream
I actually might do that because it's so stupid
That sounds really dumb
rerun the rerun
Oh my god
Uh, is that my that might be funny?
All right, maybe i'll do that
All right. Good night everybody. I'll see you on april 1st. Take care of yourselves. Have a great few weeks
Sorry, I have to do this again, but I really hope this is the last time I have to do this
Good night. Bye
See you very soon. There's a lot of fucking shit planned a lot of stuff gonna happen in the next few months
I hope you like it
Bye