Hey, what is going on, everybody? Jerma here with kind of a different video today.
Oh, not really different, but a little bit different than what you've been used to the last few months of the content of my
Channel. What is going on with this? What is going on with this guy?
And what I mean by that, sorry, I was interrupted there, is this is gonna be just a laid-back live commentary.
I haven't done one of these in a long time, and I feel like it's kind of overdue.
A lot of the stuff on my channel lately has been, hold on, see if I can get this off, I'll pull this off.
Dammit, almost, that was close, oh well.
But a lot of the content on my channel lately has been like wacky and crazy, and that's like, that's who I am.
But I also want to do more stuff like this, where I just kind of hang out, talk to you guys about anything really, and
play some video games. And today we're playing TF2, playing as the cow mangler, as you can see.
And I'm going to get that sentry gun. I'm gonna get it.
I'm gonna use the strategy where you shoot it, you right-click it, and then you kill it with a shotgun.
Or this guy will just uber it, we'll see.
There's a-
Ooh, ooh.
Gotta kill the engineer.
There we go. Okay, good, good, good. So, what?
What? Looks like there could be one or two. Let's shoot that over there, get rid of this.
Bang. Yep. All right, we're gonna try the shotgun strategy.
I'm gonna try the shotgun strategy again, the cow mangler, and then shotgun. Sentry's right around this corner.
Let's see if I can do this. Where is it? I need to know where it is. There it is. Okay, here we go.
Ready? Shotgun strat. Three, four. There it is.
Oh, at least I got the sentry gun. So it works. It does work.
It's fun to do as well. Sometimes if you're running straight at a sentry like that,
and you charge up the cow mangler and you sprint at it, it's pretty intense, especially if there's an engineer nearby.
It's really fun. What? That didn't even hit him with anything.
Knew he was low on health because he wouldn't have ran away. Hi. Oh, he got me.
Which one am I gonna use? Should I use knife? Should I use gun? Should I use knife? Should I use gun? Knife? Gun? Knife?
Gun? Knife? I don't know. Gun? Knife?
Oh boy. This is what I'm talking about here. This is what I'm talking about. That's what I want. Come on, spy.
Do you do your work? Oh, yeah, that's what we call teamwork. That was teamwork for sure.
I wouldn't have gotten there in time, and that spy did a hell of a lot of good things, and this spy
is being a real son of a bitch. Be careful. Get full health. Let me get full health and full mana.
You know, a lot of people forget this is a window. I always forget that.
I always think it's like, oh, they can only that I can only see them in one place.
That means they're gonna come from one place.
It's a window right there that you can shoot through. People are like hiding. Damn.
Oh boy. There they go. Keep it rolling, boys. Keep it rolling. That's what I like to see. We're gonna win.
I think we're actually gonna do it. I missed it. It's okay.
Distracted. Distraction. Nice job. Need some help here.
There's a sniper up there. I know he's there. What? What?
What? What just happened?
He was like on an invisible platform.
You guys saw that? That was that just like ultra lag for that guy? And what is this guy doing?
There's a spy. I need to see that spy. Hold on. I don't even care if I'm burning. That's spy. Where'd he go?
He's over here somewhere. No, no, don't kill him.
Dude, that was... somebody play the Benny Hill theme song.
That was amazing. I loved every single second of that. There's another sniper on this team. That's really good.
I'm trying to find him because I know he's gonna kill me over and over again.
Get... please.
Thank you. Is that him? That's him. He's good. This guy's good. This guy knows what he's doing.
Ooh.
Refill. Get a little bit of a refill. That guy was standing in the same spot again. And his buddy. Got you both.
Be careful next time. Watch yourself. Missed that headshot. Don't know how. That guy burned.
I could probably take out this sentry gun. I don't know what the hell I'm doing.
Ah, shit!
We have one, two, three, four, five, six, seven. We have seven snipers.
That's a little ridiculous. That is just a little bit ridiculous.
You know, I always thought that when a Spie became an adult spy, they, uh...
they kind of grew up a little bit and stopped acting kind of like crazy.
I don't think that's true anymore. I was like disguising as an engineer. Not entirely sure why. Oh, that's uh...
Another one? What the hell is going on? What does he do? What is this guy doing?
He was just like crouching in the middle.
This guy is great.
That was a good like strat. Just like crouch in the middle. Oh dear. Oh, it's your toast. I'm gonna get you now.
Oh, I'm not. That just scared the hell out of me. That whole group of people,
I got like stage fright. Get on the cart. Get on the cart. Get on the cart.
We need to get on the cart. So badly. They have so many defenses, like we have to get on here.
There's like a thousand different defenses. And he's dead. Nice job. All right. Well, that's probably gonna wrap it up here guys.
Um, but this is the last life. This'll be the last life. Shit. I didn't time that right. Wee!
Oh, get me away from you guys. Nudist guys. All right. Well, sorry.
I was like just like talking and I lost my train of thought because like that nonsense.
But I'll see you guys all next time. Thank you so much for watching. Take care everybody, of course. And I'll see you all
next time.
I don't know like when to go for the stab. How did I get that? That was a chaos stab if I've ever seen one.