How's it going? What is happening? How are you? What kind of tea do I got?
Uh, black tea today, actually. I said I don't drink black tea, but I really want the caffeine today.
And it's black tea with nothing in it, which is the worst kind of black tea.
Black tea with nothing in it just kind of tastes like water with.
Okay. Do you know, you don't like it like a seltzer water.
Seltzer water just has that it's water with a little bit of flavor, just a little bit.
It's a black tea is just kind of dry water with a hint of something kind of bitter.
I normally would put honey or sugar in it, but not today. I don't really have any.
All right. Let me, let me tweet and we'll go. Give me one second.
All right. Let me get comfortable this out of the way today. We're going to play a world box.
This was in the recommended channel. Looks pretty fun.
It's a game where you just kind of control everything.
I guess you watch civilizations kind of come and go.
The God game seems kind of fun. I've heard it's very, very interesting.
They just had an update, I think. Uh, it looks like a day or two ago today.
Maybe I don't even know. God complex Andy.
Hey, are you drinking hot Dr. Pepper?
I feel like that would not be as bad as I think it is. It's bad.
If you okay, if you took 70% of the sugar. Oh, fuck. Hold on. I got to restart the game.
Hold on a second. I've been idling here for like 20 minutes. Hold on. I gotta restart.
If you took like 70% of the sugar out of Dr. Pepper,
I feel like it would not even be bad hot.
Although I have no idea. It could be awful. Let me reopen it.
All right. Is this a randomly generated? I think it is.
There we go. Okay. Move back over here and come on.
Hey, there it is. Turn the volume on. There's no sound or anything yet.
All right. So this is, this is it. This is world box. I'm very ready.
Tutorial bear. Let me just take a nice sip of my tea.
Hi there. I'm tutorial bear. Take a moment and hear me out.
Super world box is a game about creation and destruction.
Control is simple. W A S D arrow mouse. There's a lot of info. Hold on.
W A S D arrow keys to move the camera. Right. Q and E to control zoom.
One, two, three, four, five to select powers and then escape quits the game.
I'm going to accidentally press that. It's literally only four. Yeah.
But it was just like, all right. So it's Q E W A S D. I got it.
All your powers are the bottom panel. Here are some important buttons.
The save button. Use it to save and load your worlds.
Custom worlds. Create worlds with bigger size.
World laws. Customize rules for your world.
Drawing. Tools to create your world so you can make your own world.
Oh, this is like a dragon or something. Change brush size for some powers.
This button will be on the left. Civilizations. Use it to create villages
and mess with kingdoms. Creatures and monsters.
Looking for dragons. That's the place. All right.
Nature and disasters. There's also some tools to help your civilization.
Destruction. Here you can find bombs and nukes.
Okay. And other various powers and menus.
There's so much stuff in there. Try them out and experiment.
Enjoy the game. Oh, shit. Okay. What do I do?
I just wiped out the only fire. Oops. Can I restart?
Don't give me this power in the first five seconds of the game.
All right. Create your world. All right. I'm making my own world.
I'm deleting all this. Oh, my goodness. You didn't save it.
It doesn't matter. All right. How do I make a new world?
Create new world. Here it is. All right. Choose the size and select a template.
Continent. Oh, shit. Okay. Hold on. So these are the resources.
So I think, do people just live? Animals start to spawn? What is this?
A bee. It shows how many kills it has. What the fuck?
All right. Hold on. This is the Fortnite map. Wait. Let me look at it again.
Continent. One big landmass. Box world. Islands. Boring planes.
Donut. Toast. Pancake. I think we'll start with this.
We'll just start with... I gotta figure out how to play.
Cool. So let's see. All right. How do I get people?
Civilizations, kingdoms, and villages. Okay. Kings and leaders.
See the location. Oh, we got trees. Oh, humans. Basic human with basic needs.
Where should I put them? Will they just start a civilization?
All right. So what do they do? All right. Good luck.
All right. We're going to spawn an alligator. Oh, wait. They're starting.
Wait. They're going to kill it? Now he's like a... What is this structure?
The only two humans on earth. I guess the one... Uh-oh. They're retreating.
Oh, no. Oh. Fucking assholes. Nuke them.
Okay. Humans? Elves? All right. Let's do like...
How many humans should we do? All right. All right. All right. All right.
Let's do... I got like... What? Okay. Should I put elves somewhere?
What about orcs? All right. Dwarves. Will they be friends?
Didn't I play this already? I did not. All right. So they made a fire.
They're making like a house or something. There's a mine here.
All right. Let's put the dwarves over here. All right. So there's 10 dwarves.
New kingdom. Wait. They made a new kingdom.
Okay. Let's put animals here too. Hold on. I'm just... I gotta populate the world.
Turtles and shit. Okay. Cool. Make a frog kingdom.
Uh... All right. We'll put the frogs down here.
I'm not fucking up the whole ecosystem, right?
Piranha? Rhinos? What is this? Oh, this is the king.
This is the king of the dwarves. So I think they just... Do they have children?
View kingdom. There's 10 people in Gursul. They have one village.
They're researching. Okay. This is just gonna end up... Did they fight?
Will they become friends? All right. Hold on. What about the sponge? Vortex?
Shovel? Wait. I can make mountains.
Shallow water. All right. I'm gonna make a mountain range over by the dwarves.
Oh, they already have mountains. Oops. Oopsie.
What do you mean you've ruined it? No. They live in the mountains.
Oh, wait. I think they are having children. All right. 10 versus...
No. I have to make it even. I'm gonna make it even.
Three more, right? I'm gonna put rhinos up here too.
Oh, we'll put rhino island. Nature? Temperature? Oh, I'm making it hot.
No, no, no. I don't want to do that. Make rat island?
Okay. Can they build structures? That would be actually pretty funny if they could.
The humans are developing a lot faster than the dwarves are.
What's going on here? Their favorite food is sushi.
The dwarves' favorite food is sushi. What? What are the humans' favorite food?
What is this? Cider. Okay. What traits?
Peaceful. Never attacks first. They have individual names. Okay.
Oh, yes. The dwarves love sushi. The dwarves are probably eating raw meat.
What are you doing? Oh, I guess they have different preferences. Never mind.
Stop poking me. Okay. All right. Let's make some more kings and leaders.
Yeah. Who? They show up on the map. Show... Wait. Armies? Enemies? Boats?
What? 12. Wait. Okay. So the humans are developing faster than the dwarves
with the, you know, civilization. But the dwarves are...
They're having more children faster. Okay. Let's add some more.
Uh-oh. Oh, should I leave it? Should I just see what happens?
The dwarves are having way more sex than the humans. Coffee?
Bless creatures to make them stronger. Madness?
Divine light. Oh, my God. Oh, wait, wait, hold on. The humans are catching up.
The dwarves have... They're currently mastering the navy.
Wait a minute. Where are they going? What is this thing?
There's nobody even on this boat. Why were they... They couldn't just... They
couldn't walk this way? It's a fishing boat. Okay. They're
keeping up. Should we add another kingdom? Yes. Okay.
Um, what should we do? Orcs? Or elves? All right. Orcs.
Where's it gonna be the orc? Okay, the orcs are gonna be up here. Yeah, like here.
Okay, they're already attacked. How many do I need? Ten?
All right. That's good. Okay, there are 13. The orcs are OP.
Save this. Statistics. 15 years. It's taken 15 years and it's only... You only
could... Okay. Infected? Natural death?
Death from hunger? Creatures eaten? New village has been founded.
New kingdom has been founded. Okay, the orcs are progressing rapidly.
All right, they're doing well. All right, we got to put the elves down here too
then. All right, should the elves be on like a little
island or something? No, they'll be down here. Far away. Far
away. And the elves have been around for centuries, so there's gonna be like 20
of them already. Oh wait, this is the frog kingdom!
Oh shit. I may have just caused a problem. That's okay, right?
What the hell is this? I didn't make this a giggly?
Okay, well, they'll be all right. So we have the... Wait, what's this?
Is this a different... Who is this? Is this an orc?
So wait, this one guy made his own kingdom.
This guy's fucked. Okay, well, good luck. Wait a minute. No, it's got two now. All
right, let's just see what happens. This is interesting to me. All right,
they're doing a little... They're expanding. Uh-oh. Okay, we already got this. Now I
need to... All right, let's let's add some stuff.
Let's bless the elves. No, they have plenty of frogs.
I'm gonna... Okay, I'm gonna bless this kingdom with chickens.
I don't know if that does anything. I don't know if that matters, but whatever. I
think there's gonna be conflict here. Bless them with rain. Rain. All right,
who's... Who do we bless with rain? These are the
underdogs. Here, I grant you rain. There you go. And candy.
Click show kingdom zones in the civilization menu.
Interesting. This is like a game of risk. Funny, okay.
So how do they own this much land? Click on the boats.
Um, I don't know what these boats are doing. Uh, humans,
should I bless... All right, we'll bless them again with
uh, enchanted seeds. No, that's cheating. How about let's bless them with an
earthquake. Acid. You're progressing too quickly.
It's time for you to have to deal with some acid. Plain soil.
It's... They've slowed down. Favorite food. Burgers.
Children zero. Children four, okay. Likes bread. Children eight. Holy shit.
You are responsible for a major percentage of everybody here.
What about you? Zero. Ten. There's two people here that are
responsible for half of the village. All of these...
They're currently in there now. Okay. Where are you going?
They're expanding. What's this? What's going on? What's this? What are they doing?
What is this? What's this banner? Wait, they have shields.
Uh-oh. They're getting ready for war already?
With who? War has already been declared. Should I slow them down?
I'm gonna slow them down. What the fuck was that?
I didn't do that. What's happening? Where is that happening?
I'm not doing that. Wait, are they fighting? Oh shit!
No, it's... Oh, let me bless them. That's unfair.
That's not fair. They just got... They get lightning striked?
You good? Everything's good to go? Random lightning strikes?
Give them money. Yeah, their kingdom kind of sucks.
Sponges. Copies pixels under it to others around it.
Pickaxe. Removes grass. Shows where... Oh, shows where armies are going.
Shows where armies are going to attack when...
Some other god hates these elves. Okay, so it's showing where they're gonna
attack. I think, wait, people are dying in the
in the elf camp. I definitely want to see where they're
going. What happened here? This kingdom is
disintegrating. The one guy kingdom. 24 versus 13.
Wait, they're all defecting over here. Why are they all defecting?
Is it because this area is just fucked up? Because it's lava. I can change that.
There. And make some cool water. Nice ice cold water. Oh, another human
kingdom over here. It's because you gave them a chicken.
What, it created a whole civilization? What about... Wait, where are those
frogs? Did they eat all the frogs or something?
Wait, how can I see where all the animals are?
Statistics about your world. A hundred deaths?
What? No, I'm sorry. I'm sorry. This is not... I'm not gonna let this...
I'm not gonna let this slide. I'm sorry.
Get out of here. That's too much expansion. No, I'm sorry. That's not... I'm sorry.
You don't... That's too much expansion. Candy? Create the candy biome.
Should I just make candy island over here? Okay, I'm gonna make candy island over here.
Oh, wait, should I just put a bunch of candy... Wait, okay. So this
candy over here. Corrupted seeds. Mushroom seeds. Grass seeds.
Let's make them fight for this island. I mean, it already was grass, but let's make
it really, really just like nice and lush.
They're persevering.
Is the orc actually gonna be able to kill the bear? No.
Oh, wait a minute. This is probably a bad idea. Oh,
all right. Get rid of this. This is enough of this. I just want to make it a
little harder for them. Cad Till has become the biggest kingdom
and the one guy kingdom. Wait, where's the actual one guy? How many kids do you
have? 39? Holy shit, dude. Every...
Wait, that's kind of fucked up. Doesn't that imply
that... Wait, how is it possible that you've had 38
children and there's 38 people here? I don't know. I think I have to get a
tornado. From the other kingdom? Uh-oh, we're gonna
fight here. Are they gonna go for it? Are they going for it? The orcs
over here are scattered. They're not preparing.
No, they back down. Wait, where they... Where they going?
Uh-oh, they're getting an army ready over here too.
Dude, what's with all the lightning? They're kind of just hanging out.
Oh, all right. Check this out. Let's make this whole thing fucking awful.
Fruit bushes right in the middle. Good luck. Fight over the bushes.
Amuse me. Fight over these fruit bushes. Amuse me.
Come on, you're just gonna... Uh-oh, a deco... Wait, what is this person doing?
They... Oh, now that they're part of this place.
38 children. Is that even... Like, I feel like at some point it's just 236%
full hunger that's gonna get ugly over here. Who's got the biggest kingdom?
77. They've been very busy. Villages? Cultures? Force kingdom to start a war.
When used on a village, that's not a capital. It becomes its own kingdom.
All right, I'm curious about this. Let's take a look. 11 houses, 16 people in the
army. 27... How did... Who died? Okay, so this is the leader of this village.
They have no children. They get in boats. Oh, he got killed by a bear. That's right.
No battles. Okay. Still no fight yet. What about a dog? You guys... Who should get the
dogs? You can all have... Okay, you can all have three dogs. Weird building pattern.
They kind of came back strong though. You guys... Let's put a few... A couple of cows.
Um... Wait, I can make enemies? All right, who should deal with the first... Who should deal
with the first group of, uh, like, attacking bandits? Oh my god, there's so much more that
I didn't see. A dragon? UFO? Beehive? Make Monster Island. All right, hold on. First,
I'm gonna make... We need to make somebody... A village has to get attacked by bandits.
Make Dragon Island. This thing is scary. All right, who is the most progressed?
It's either... You... You... You Boredran? E.S. or Ostod? Who needs a challenge here? E.S.?
I can check. Yeah, let's... Let's see who could use a challenge. Statistics. What about your world?
Oh, no. World laws? Kingdoms can declare wars and treaties. Yeah. Cities can rebel when
have low loyalty. So that's what we've seen. Kingdoms will send settlers to establish new
villages. They have armies. Allows the stealing of borders. Babies will be born. Everyone needs
food to live and creatures can die of old age. Baby animals can be born. Animals can randomly spawn.
Okay. So... World history. Demons from another realm have invaded this world. What? Since when?
Uh-oh. I didn't have to do anything. This thing has almost six... It's six hundred health? All
right, let's see. Here you go. You guys can have, like, a bunch of chickens and, like, two cows.
And let's, like, bless them with water. Here. Have some, like, grass seeds. This... They're looking
at each other from over... Okay. So now they can start their entire kingdom over here. They're
already doing machinery. Ah! What's going on here? Nobody in it. Is this a... Is this a diplomatic
ambassador of the Demon Kingdom? I don't know. Stone? Uh, let's put some... Actually, you know what?
Let's put some stone up here. I feel like they need it. They definitely need it. I just killed,
like, three people. Oops. Fill the hole up here. Now mine this for resources. Plants? All right.
Let's do some plants over here. Lemon seeds on the top of the mountain. Getting close to each other.
Hourglass? Change the flow of... Ah! What happened? Baby tornado? What's going on? Why are we all
celebrating? What happened? What are we celebrating? The King Oz of Zagad is dead. Oh, I crushed him
with a rock. Zoom out? Oh. Why is there a tornado kingdom? And why would the whole world celebrate
a tornado? Oh, right. Uh-oh. Okay. Favorite units? Oh, I should have favorited the guy that had like
40 kids. Can you handle that? I think they have the biggest army.
I'm picking favorites here, but it's all right. I'm gonna give it to everybody. Don't worry.
What are you doing? Favorite food? Cider. Mood normal. Children 16. Is this like, um,
can you put more plants? I mean, more plants, you think? Should we make it? Let's, let's,
let's heat something up. When do they start killing each other? I don't know. I would imagine
probably soon. There's not much, there's no more, there's nowhere else to go. Okay. Let's put some,
uh, oh, a hot spring. Volcano. Snow! Okay. Let's, let's, let's make some snow. This would be nice.
Give him like a winter wonderland. I hear hitting. What's being hit? Oh, they're killing a sheep.
All right. Should I drop a, uh, I don't want to drop on it. A heat ray. Robot Santa? Oh,
what about fireworks? Okay. Let's do, let's celebrate the fact that we just had another
30 kids. Am I going to light them? What happened? The size is too big. That's all right. I can fix
it. All right. That's, that's my apology. I gave you like six chickens. There's some cooled water.
It's time for war. This gag pond has 40. Oh, they're all here. All right. It looks,
I can influence this. Here it comes. I'm thinking about throwing a fireball at some point. Lava.
No. Um, they're getting very close. There's a lot of play out. Poison the water. Uh, they're just
matching each other's speed. Nobody wants to make the first move. They're all peaceful with each
other. 45 deaths from hunger. Other deaths. Are they still over there? It's like two. I picked them
up. Burning feet, fire, blood, fireproof. Cool. Um, all right. I think this is as big as the world
is going to be able to get. Cause I mean, we have so many kingdoms here. It's time to start a little
bit of conflict. What do you think? Like I'm just, okay. I'm just going to put a grenade over here
and it's going to be like, what the hell was that? Right? It's like, what was that? Oh,
they're just sitting at the border. Okay. We could make it be, we could speed the time up a
little bit here and see what happens in like a hundred years. Increased. What was it? Times one.
Okay. I could do times two maybe, right? Oh man. All right. What do you, what should I do? Times
five. What does the world look like? Uh, yeah, this is happening now. This is definitely happening.
No, fuck you. No, fuck you. No, fuck you. Well, how big is their army?
Attack speed. I don't know who's going to, who's going to hit first. You just drank coffee.
Here we go. Here we go. They're getting too close. There it goes. Oh no. They're fighting over,
they're attacking their huts. Just freak them out a little. I am angry. Stop fighting. Holy shit.
They wiped them out. They wiped them out completely. Nobody even died here. The one guy kingdom
is now very strong. Absolutely wiped them out. That's bad for you. Let us bet next time. Well,
how about this? Why don't you bet on who reigns completely supreme here? You got, um,
I think the dwarves have been wiped out. No, they're not. The dwarves are here. You've got,
I don't know. Should we go by kingdom or just humans, dwarves, orcs, or I don't know. But I'm
going to be influenced. This is killing a lot of people. All right. Don't vote for these people
because the tornado just went through the whole village and I think took out a lot of people.
Oh man. Are they all right? All right. I'm glad I tested that over there because eventually,
oh, God's just testing. Um, like this is still going. Just, I want them to make sure they know
what they're dealing with. This little tornado is causing so many problems. All right. It's,
we're at, we're at halftime. Everybody gets a dozen chickens. Why is nobody going to Candy
Island? It looks like, okay, we can speed up time a little bit now. Relations. These diplomatic
relations with other kingdoms. Death is health. They're militarist. Damn. Okay. War is peace.
Okay. They're at peace with pretty much everybody besides, I'm not worried with anybody. They
already destroyed everybody. Where are you guys? They're currently at peace over here too. Culture
level. How many villages this has? Peaceful militarist. Click the light bulb. Research.
Common knowledge is windmill population. Okay. Move over here. All right. Nobody else is at war.
We can change that really quickly though. I thought they weren't at war. They're gonna. All
right. I, we got to slow them down. I'm actually going to slow them down a little and then great
heat. What are they doing? Did you guys already, uh, do a poll? I don't remember. What are they
doing over here? What's going on here? Why are they all hanging around the windmill? All right.
Let's speed it up. Times five. Nobody decided to go over to the islands. What was going on over here?
Gold mine. Change the laws of the world now. Okay. Okay. Here we go. Natural disasters,
other disasters. Minerals. We need to start some fights. Look at the grayed out options.
Creep tiles like tumor pumpkin biomass would stay even after base structure is gone. Eternal lava.
Okay. Make a volcano. Look at the grayed out options. Hold on. Let me see. Peaceful monsters.
A hundred. Limit maximum population of a hundred. Villagers will also participate in insane. Really?
Okay. That's fine. Go up. Hold on a sec. This is as high as, as high as I can go. Kingdom tab. Let's see.
Okay. Is it still snowing over here? Mods are watching Sopranos. Oh, that's all right. So,
let's do, what is this? Under development. Okay. Force a kingdom to war. I think this is probably
going to be very hard to beat. Everyone's kind of just chilling. This is fine. I want to speed it
up one more time. Another times five and see what happens. Put on earthbound OST. No, that's all
good. I need to concentrate. Maybe in a minute. All right. It's time. Here we go. Here's my plan.
I want to see. Crabzilla. I feel like Crabzilla is going to end the whole thing. If I, if I click
Crabzilla, this is going to be a disaster. This was not my plan to play this all night, by the way.
I just wanted to check it out. I really liked this so far though. It's fun. Just like kind of
people watching. Save it. Oh my God. Thank you. Uh, where's the, no, do not quit. There it is.
Actually, I want to, I want to see the difference. What's the difference? 14 years versus 85,
four kingdoms, three, two cultures, five, three villages, seven, and then 359 population. Okay.
Uh, I'm just, I'm curious. I'm, I'm curious to see what happens here. Let's, let's do something weird.
Um, okay. Lava cloud. Robot Santa. Where should robot Santa spawn? How about over here in candy
world? Okay. So what, what are these two Santas? He's not doing anything. Oh, it's for everything.
Right. Okay. Okay. Well, I'm really glad I spawned that over here. Wait, this, look at this. Hold on
a second. I have an idea. What am I doing? Just staying over here? Oh, it's cause I can only go
here. Okay. It's forest soil and I put grass. I'll connect it. I'm going to put grass. I'm,
I'm very curious to see what happens here. You can make the world way bigger. That's pretty cool,
but let's see what happens when I do this. Uh, let's make some more elves over here.
Give them a chance. Let's give them a shitload of resources too. Why not? A bunch of water,
bunch of seeds, bunch of mushrooms, a bunch of enchanted seeds, a ton of lemon seeds,
tons of fertilizer. Oops. Bunch of fruit bushes. All right. This is the place to be.
Lemon Island. Animals. I put some already. They're fighting. Okay. Let's see what happens.
There was no pole, right? So I can just kind of mess around. Now that we have the world is here.
Ooh, they split off. Take a look. How are the demons? The demons have the same three. I'm
connecting. Why? They haven't developed any technology. They've just been walking around.
Give the orcs a boss to fight. That's a good idea. All right. The orcs are going to fight
five skeletons. Let's see if they can handle it. They look at how huge they are. Here we go. Ready?
They destroyed it. Oh my God. That wasn't even a... All right. What about a dragon? All right. It's
time for a dragon. We're putting a dragon into the orc kingdom and we're going to put it up in the
corner. Here we go. What is going on? Are these monkeys? Wait, there's monkeys that have made...
It wants nothing to do with the monkeys over there. Why are there so many? I didn't put these here.
Oh my goodness. Okay. Get him. Get the dragon. Fight it. What are they even throwing? I actually
don't want the kingdom over here to die, so I'm going to help. All right. Now blow it up.
Fuck. What happened? Shit. Oh no. Sorry. They can rebuild. They can rebuild. They can rebuild.
I got to bless them. I got to help them. No, everyone's fine. They're doing just fine over
here. You better stay the fuck away from Monkey Island. In fact, I don't trust that you won't.
Change the size of the rain. How do I make it bigger? Oh, right. Like this. Ooh. All right.
Let's bless everyone with the cooling, clean, crisp mist. Here we go. Civilization simulator.
All right. How about... People are drowning? Who? What are you talking about? You're stuck in the
wood. You're stuck in the wood age? This is going well over here. They need minerals. Okay. Like
ore. All right. Give the monkeys gold. Yeah. It's a good idea. They deserve it. You know what? Let's
put some gold over here too. Let's just give it to everybody. We need to make this a little
more enticing over here. Some mithril. So are they going to start making more advanced things?
Silver. The monkeys don't even care about this. Oh god damn it. Oh, I think I just killed a few
people. Stone. You got to get through the demons. All right. Let's pass some time. Let's see what
happens to our civilizations. Curious. Okay. Oh, wait a minute. Something happening over here.
This group in the middle here has gotten really, really a lot of people and they're starting to...
Yeah, this is a problem right here. The elves have... The elves are probably going to take it.
We need more metal. Do we need more metal? More ore too. Should I just make ore island? Okay. I'm
going to just make a... I'm going to pick an ore island. Just one piece. No, this is just
developer island. Okay. Stone. I think it's a little smaller. They're already coming over here.
Oh, wait. The demons. The demons can actually make it over here now. Oh, big mistake. They one shot
everybody. That's not good. I think that was just the king. Well, stop coming over here. What are
you doing? Stop. Why? You know what? Just let them fight. They're slowly just trickling over
here and dying. I don't know why they're just running over here. They're slowly... All right.
Why are you still alive? Dude, get out of here. Thank God. I may have just made a big mistake.
Well, that's their army, right? One demon is going through this whole thing. Okay. They got it. A
lot of people died though. Oh, they've made another kingdom. Okay. Let's keep going. All right. This
silver. Let's do ore and then I'm going to speed it up times five and see what happens. No, no,
no. You don't own this. This is, this is developer island. You don't own this.
Nobody owns this. Nobody owns this. Stop making a, you're not making a town here.
You're really going to... All right. Who are these people? You're really going to come over
here and claim developer island. Now you've angered me. Holy shit. That's not what I thought that was
going to do, but it worked. Oh, I thought it bounced down. It's okay. It's all good.
Stop, stop. You know what? Whatever. Go ahead and claim it. How's monkey island doing?
They're thriving up here. Look at it. Everything's peaceful. Everyone's friends.
It's rhinoceroses and chickens and frogs. They defended it from a dragon. They have growing trees.
They're being sustainable up here. Look at this. I want a little bit more ore. Let's do gold too.
And then adamantite. Okay. We have our ore island and let's do some bushes too. Berries.
Oh, I can't put it there. Why not? Sure. We're like a geyser again. I mean, this is,
wouldn't you want to claim this whole area? If you've got like 10 different civilizations on
earth and all the resources are running out and all of a sudden half a mile off the coast,
the water level drops and there's an island with every valuable resource ever invented,
you're going to cause a lot of problems. Okay. Let's speed it up and then we can do some wacky
stuff. They've already, yeah, they already claimed it. The humans. Wait, is it the humans or the
dwarves? I don't know, but this is going to be a fight here. They've already claimed it.
Kingdom lair. Looks like these two are, this one's doing the best. This one's stayed out of most of
the conflict. This one stayed pretty much not any fights or anything. These people have been in a
fight. These people obviously have been in a fight. The elves have not really done very much.
Monkey islands doing fine. Wait, monkey islands getting attacked by lightning. Oh no, it's not.
Okay, cool. That's not good. It's happening over here. Which island is mine? I don't know.
They're on the border over here. The other thing that I was going to do today, I wanted to play
pizza tower. I was going to load that up after this. Everybody hates the candy kingdom. Yeah,
I'm surprised. Nobody's, yeah, I think nobody likes it. Let's get some stats here.
520. Infected. Infected. I don't know what that means. Yeah, they claimed it. All right,
let's see what happens. I'm going to do this. Let's see if there is anything. Let me save it
first. I like looking at the progress. It's cool. Let's see. Ready? Yeah. Look at the left and then
all the way to the right. 14, 85, 129. Population slowly increasing. Okay. Uh, try summon the giant
crab. Gray goo? Do crabzilla. Okay. Where should crabzilla spawn? All right. Good luck, everybody.
Wait, I control it? Well, okay. Well, they're all gone. Are you serious? I'm unstoppable.
Nobody is going to stop me. I'm sorry. That's how would they ever deal with this?
Can I be killed? Okay. All right. Oh, I didn't, I didn't think that was going to happen. Sorry.
Uh, a-otade. Sorry. Almost all of the earth. They already took almost all the resources.
What about here? Lava cloud. I'm curious. One person. One person. It's just like,
holy shit. I don't even know what just happened, but I will rebuild. Good luck.
That's determination right there. All right. What else can I do here? How about, um, earthquake?
Where should I do it? Oh my goodness. Damn. Okay. Hey, make a hot climate up here. Infinity coin.
Meteor eat ray. Really guys? Really? Now, now you decide to go in after all that.
Was this seen as an opportunity of weakness where a bunch of this got wiped out? So they're like,
all right, well, let's go in. That's kind of messed up. They have flaming swords. They're
running now. Like, get out, get out, get out, get out, get out. Wait. No, no, no, no, no, no.
Now it's actual constant total conflict. Everybody. Okay. The everybody's just fight.
Everybody's just attacking each other. I don't even know who is it. Wait, I need to see the map.
That the kingdom map thing. Ooh, it's pretty splintered. They're trying to take this. They're
not going to get it. Especially when a cloud of acid rains. Now they didn't get it. That's a very,
oh my goodness. That's loud. Why is this as a typewriter?
Everything is wow. This person is very big. All right. Stop, stop typewriter ring. They don't
even care. I got it saved. So don't worry. We're good. What about this? What's gray goo?
I didn't want to do. Okay. Oh my God. It's eating the whole place. What are they going to do?
Why are this person so big? Oh Jesus. Oh my goodness. How do I stop it? How do you stop it?
How do I stop it? I didn't want to. Okay. That's not what I wanted to do. That's, I wanted to,
you said, I didn't know it was going to be that big. I didn't know it was going to be that big.
Water? Dude, water is not going to stop this. How do I stop it? You can't stop the gray goo event.
No, no, not monkey Island. Anything but monkey Island. Wait, wait, wait. Stop, stop, stop. Pause.
Oh my goodness. Escape route. No, no, stop. Stop. I'm trying to save. I'm trying to save somebody.
Is there anybody left? No, you don't understand. Go over this way. You don't get it. There's one
other rhino that you guys need to make friends right now. Well, wait. Okay. At least we have.
All right. Well, that was kind of fun. That was world, um, world box. That was my favorite
character. How dare you? All right. That was world box. That seemed kind of crazy. Let's,
let's move on to pizza pizza tower. I did not know that that was going to do what that did.
I thought it was just going to make some goo on the ground. That's fun. Tired of it. No, not really.
I just, you know, I feel like if you wanted to really, really make a ton of kingdoms and stuff
kind of, my brain is a little too small for that, but definitely fun to play. All right. Pizza tower
time. How about sorcery? Uh, no plan for that right now. I got to plug this in. Uh, yeah. Let
me disclose this. Give me one sec. BRB for two minutes or three minutes. Give me a sec.