Somebody get in that nice car.
You killed me! The cops.
Wait what the hell is going on?
That car he like floored it when I shot him in the head.
Oh my god! This guy's out of his mind!
Wait why did he fall out of the car?
I dunno. I- bro let me in.
Where is he by the way?
Did he fall into a wormhole?
How are you guys doing? Can you guys come over here?
I'm a dying need of help.
part of me is kind of glad I had the shitty bike so I couldn't get over there
in time no I died okay boo what are you doing what are these three cops look at
these guys they're just stuffing into each other
over that German a cop just got out of the car died he was driving and just
opened the door and went ah welcome to the bus okay I'll get in welcome yeah
this is the bus stop hey guys how's it going welcome to my bus hello bus driver
how are you doing oh hey oh hey where we are we gonna go to the
market where we going off we go hey doors all right okay
oh look at how much fun we're having on the school bus what a bunch of like a
bunch of weirdos man we're just criminals just all in a bus just like
can I can we like change seats can I like move over like walk out of the car
oh let's get up any brother you just get up oh my gosh look what's what is the
explosion what's going on down there what the hell was that I don't like other
people in this server they're trying to like time bomb us and blow up the bridge
they did a little too like soon oh there's a helicopter oh oh goodness
gracious we're under fire we're going so fast look at the cop car hey hey the
funniest part about this driver's if we light on fire we're never gonna get out
in time we're gonna like nonchalantly walk out the door
imagine if you were on a bus and it was on fire and everyone just like one
of the times just get something dude I would be pushing people out of the
goddamn way I would be like punching people to get out of there let's make
our getaway oh I was trying to run you over get up get up you I want this give
oh I see explosions oh okay here we go before I'm coming for you guys the same
like Fast and Furious car right now oh are you really okay I'll wow what do you
you just like it's teleported up my screen oh boy oh my god that looks
ridiculous awesome we landed rolling fat I tried to like bowling ball it into
you guys oh bye boo oh hey get in somebody's car oh that guy just he's
not dead it's a miracle this keep this guy alive man this it's a miracle this
guy's still alive I shot that I shot this guy in the head and he front flipped
into his face and now he's standing back up with what the sir you are some type
of angel or something because you I don't know how you survived that oh no
what's going on the police officer he's still alive he's still alive he's still
getting riddled with bullets he's still alive dude this guy is a champion I feel
like he's gonna fall over dead dude I wonder how many times this guy's gonna
get hit oh my goodness is he still alive he's getting back up wow man oh oh help
look at all these police officers hold on I want to see if this guy is truly
invincible dude this guy all right is he gonna get up do I hear a helicopter I
think I think this guy's finally seen his end of days oh man no no I will get
it back no you deserve I'm alive we're gonna go off of the last jump you know
what I'm saying like just the last one shit and I get his car I'm gonna get
his wheels hey there's another one there's another cop right here there's
another one coming there's another one this guy's a little bit more aggressive
wow wow yeah slow down a little bit slow down a little bit everyone stop line up
and they're gonna go off at the same time it's gonna be epic okay go oh wow
hit the job all right here we go are they gonna believe they're gonna block
the way I'll shoot his tire so he's not oh this is so many I just the cop is so
many I think I like dude did my car just hit somebody no oh my god I can just see
him coming straight any cruises coming off too oh no it's so funny that it's
all started to fly off now now begin survival mode all right survive how I'm
not doing survival mode there's so many cops playing man versus machine right
now it's like versus machine what upgrades you guys gonna get all I've got
is the pistol I got a pump action shotgun do take cover I'm taking over
this rock I'm sorry I have to do this but uh oh what do you why'd you do that
they made me oh you turn you turn cloak