All right, fun. That was Disney Infinity 3.0. I couldn't, I couldn't even get it to fucking turn on.
Um, okay, great. So now, uh, should I try Ultra Kill? I know they had the new update, right?
Does Steam Cloud work for this game? Because I'm gonna be in trouble if it doesn't.
Because I had to uninstall a bunch of stuff and I uninstalled Ultra Kill.
So hopefully it worked. I'm gonna be sad if I have to start over.
Dude, what is going on right now? Disney Infinity 3.0 broke my computer.
These are all set the right way, right? I think so. I think we're good.
I gotta remember how to play though. There we go. All right, so we are, which one was I on?
5.1? Harmless lenient standard. I swear to God, Disney Infinity broke the computer.
Standard, right? So Act 2? I did this. Layer 5. Wrath. Let's go.
Okay, so I gotta, how do you play? I gotta remember how to play the game. This is important.
All right, let's go. Act 2. How do you play? This is my favorite game. This game is sick.
I just gotta remember how to do everything. What are the buttons?
Yeah, yeah, yeah. Jump, dash, left shift, slide, left control, weapons. Okay.
Don't weapons have like powers too? Yep, you can dash in the air.
How am I going? Blue hook points act as slingshots. How do I grab that? R? Oh, okay, yep. Cool.
It's an underwater level. I already don't like it. Checkpoint.
Does not build up hard damage while underwater. Go nuts. Have fun.
Oh yeah, I have the machine gun. You can get rid of all the bullets, right?
Underwater sounds make me want to puke. Okay, we good? Yeah, it's a new update.
This is all new. Whatever it is. So I can choose a few. Oh, thank God.
Shit. All right. Oh my God. You're, you're alive. Oh my goodness. I feel like I'm on drugs. What?
Stop. How do I sink? Okay. No. Oh, I need sound. Dude, this is just proving to me just how much
audio is important for me when I play a game. I can't play. It's like, I can't see. You know
what I mean? I can't see. I actually can't see. By the way, this is, this is, I don't want it there.
Okay. Way better. I can actually use this now. I'm playing with no sound.
That's the only way I can do it. What is doing that? Why am I taking so much damage?
How do you heal? What's the, there's a heal? What's the heal? I haven't played so long.
How do you heal? Blood? You forgot everything. I've played like 150 games since I played this.
It's mouse four. Hold on. Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait. Change arm. Oh shit. Hold on. Weapons have
two modes. Oh, I have to think about this. Fuel is blood. You're all you have. Right, right, right.
Okay. Okay. Okay. What is change arm? Right. Okay. I have a punch. I want whiplash on mouse four.
Very right. Okay. You can switch these. I don't need to read what these do again
because this has a different mode too, right? Yeah. What mode did I like? I think I like the
shotgun. What's punch? House five. I'm going to make it like V or something, right? Maybe middle
mouse. Okay. Let's try this. You play Madagascar too? Um, no. Shit. Oh, no. I fucking fell. Where
am I? Oh, this is brutal. Floating around in the water is like, I can't think of a thing that I
would rather not do than this. I'm in trouble. Where is it? Where am I? I feel like I'm cooking
with like eight pans on a burner and they're all almost done. And I'm like, oh shit. Wait,
hold on. Grab that switch and flip that. I got up with the patties done and everything's about to
burn. Give me the health. I don't want to fucking float around. What are you doing? Um, die? I did
it. Did I do it? Thank God. Oh, how long am I in the water level for? Please say five minutes.
I hated the shit in Mario too. Every time it was a water level. I just, okay. Can one of my friends
play for like an hour? God, I need the skull. All right. I guess I'm going to go this way. Wait,
there's a skull in there. Can I go back in here? Was there a skull in here? There was. Okay. How
do I pick it up? You look like a carrot. Thanks. Is that a thank you? All right, let's go. Oh,
I can breathe. Get out of here. What did I just do to myself? What happened? Oh, that's the special
move for that. That thing explodes in your hand. I forgot how it works. Hold on. How's it work?
Okay. So if you do it more than once, one, two. Okay. One, two. Okay. I get it. What was this?
What was that? Secret? Ooh. What'd I get for that? Get me out of the fucking water. I hate water so
much. Dude, if I could drain every lake in every video game I've ever played, I would. I want water
to be scenery, not a gameplay mechanic. I don't even know what is fucking happening right now.
You literally just played a fish game. Yeah, but I would have drained that lake. Shit. I got no
health. Dude, am I crazy or is this like a hundred times harder than what I did last? Am I on the
wrong difficulty? I feel like this is unbelievably harder than it used to be. Am I playing on the
wrong difficulty? Skill issue. Dude, I don't know. Holy shit. All right. Come on. Let me get
fucking, let me sit up a little. Bro. Oh, I need that fucking health. This guy's got to die
immediately. I didn't mean to do that. Jesus Christ. What is happening? Who's shooting me with
this stuff? Even throwing a coin? Dude. Oh yeah. Don't hit me. What the fuck is happening? No
fucking way. Did that go through your legs? Oh, where'd he go? Holy shit. That was hard.
I didn't even know what was going on. I didn't know where I was. Holy shit. That was like omega
hard. Okay. So what? One more through here. Stop saying omega because it's omega weekend. Dude,
that was omega hard, right? Where are you? There you are. Why am I here? Okay. Thank goodness.
No checkpoint. Fucking water. Don't kill me. That was way, that was like nothing in comparison.
Okay. There's that checkpoint. I didn't get the points to the health of that.
Why? There's a parry too. I forgot. What's the parry?
Interrupting sentries. Red arm. Oh, okay. That's right. Punch. Don't kick me. Oh,
that was pretty sick. Hey, for anarchy. Anarchy. What the heck? I need that blood so bad.
Whoa. Yikes. Oh, I did it. That was insane. That was actually insane.
Genuinely. That was ridiculous. That was, that was hard. Don't touch any water. How would you do
that? Don't touch water in the water level. Hold on. I need to read this. Okay. Coin to deflect.
One of them is a charge. Let me see. Let me play with it. Right. Okay. Yep. Okay. This next one,
the shotgun has a couple things. Overheat and launch the shotgun's core. Yep. Pump the shotgun.
Too many pumps will make it blow up. Okay. Nail gun. Let me see what these were.
Shoots the magnet. Okay. I know that. What does this one do?
Alt-fire while shooting to overheat. So it goes. Yep. Okay. Rail cannon. This is new.
Because this one is just boom. A piercing instant piercing shot.
Pierces through all enemies. Pay attention to your piercing position to maximize destruction
of piercing. Don't use it in water. Oh, okay. Why is the game so hard? Am I crazy or is this
game way harder now? I was doing like 50% of my health every time I did that in the water.
Drill. Okay. All right. What is malicious? All right. Cool. Yeah. This game is sick. Let's go.
Hold. Punch. Yep. Yes. So this is a, you go whack. I not do it now. How would this be?
What do they make melee? Didn't I? Oh, I can't do it. All right. Let's do it. Five two. Okay.
I looked at chat. My fault. That does not hurt. Oh, the game's crashed. Oh, no. It's asking me
if I want to do sticky keys. Why does sticky keys exist? You know, in 2022, I really could not
answer that. I have no idea. I don't know if it has to have some use. Don't fall. Shit. Sponge him.
I need to kill this thing very quickly. Where are you? Oh, my goodness. Oh,
it's gone already. Oh, okay. If you kill me from all the way back there, I'll be very upset.
What the heck is wrong with you? How do I kill this? I have to run. I think idols can only be.
Oh, now what? Oh, I can't open those. How do I break it? Oh, yikes. Oh, my. Oh, my God. These
guys are protected by the idols. How do I break? Oh, I guess throwing baseballs at me. I gotta get
up there. Oh, it's so hard. Please die. No, turn into a fucking lawnmower. How do I? Oh, die.
Die. Die. Sponsored stream. You lost your mind. I didn't make it. Sorry. I'll get it right now.
It was red. Boy, I need red. Yo, yo, yo, yo. Oh, no, no. I want this thing.
Dude, there's no, there's no way. There's no way. You know what I mean? There's no way.
I already put that there. OK, so that's horse shit. So I have to just get ready.
Here we go. Ready? OK, go up here. Don't even think about it. Give me that. You piece of shit.
Oh, no. Oh, no. Oh, no. Oh, no. Slow down. Oh, yes. Thank God. All right. We're good.
I had it. Harry, Harry. There's a different mode. Paris, Paris, Paris, Paris, all Paris, all Paris
and real gun. Hey, hey. Oh, what the fuck is going on here? How do I do this? What happened?
What happened? I just want to hear the rain. Can you not parry the blue? How do you? How do
you? I want to pair the blue. How do you parry blue? Use coins, use coins, use coins. Is it
coins good against them? Pretty good. Come on. Get on the barrel. Get on the barrel. Get on the
barrel. It shouldn't have been that tricky. Yeah. Why were you squished into the ground? How did I
not hit you? Oh, I missed. See ya. Now what? You play IRL like my grandpa. Sorry. That guy was
crazy. Turn the music back on. Don't fight the ferryman. I just walk by. How do you not fight
the ferryman? You could have paid him. Okay. How much is this? I'm almost at it. Should I buy it?
That wasn't even the boss boss. That was just the mini boss. I'm actually on the ship. You know,
I am so glad it was not just underwater. Thank God. This is like, I hate underwater levels. I
just do. I'm so happy that it's not that. Everybody left. Okay. I'm going to get lost here. I guarantee
it. Jerry. Jerry. What is? Where did you? I don't even know that guy spawned. You reflect triple
combo. Ready? Hyper combo. Ready? No, no, no. Get out of my face. These things suck. Just give me the
land cannon. I thought it was dead. Stop attacking. I hate these things so much. Oh my
God. Because they just so you can't, I can't like jump up, jump, jump. Nothing to grab onto.
Bounced off his skull. It bounced off of his skull. Explain that to me. I need an explanation.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no. I got juggled. Oh my God. I wish there was a double jump.
Please. I'll pay $50 for it. Make it $50 DLC. I'll buy it. Make it $50 DLC. I'll buy it tonight.
Use the hook. You can hook onto enemies. Why didn't anybody tell me that?
What? No. Where am I? Where am I? All right. Come here, you piece of shit. Die. Shut up. Do not.
Right? Yes. Being blocked. I think I'm winning. I think. This game is insane, dude. Seriously.
What do you got? Oh, you line up. Shut up. Shut up. Shut up. Huh? Where am I?
What am I shooting at? Where is it? Oh, Jesus, dude. Where? Oh, what the fuck? You're alive?
No. Hey, extra crispy on the menu tonight. I'm sorry. We're good. Where do I go from here?
Because I need a checkpoint. Where's the checkpoint? What is this? I need a checkpoint.
Rocket launch. Direct hits cause explosions. Indirect hits will launch enemies. Does it have
another mode or no? Okay. I can hurt myself with this. Air shots. That hurts. I get up there.
Can I jump up there? I don't think so. I got it. Use the clock and then shoot it.
It's probably slow motion. I would imagine. That's cool. Ooh. You know what game was so fun?
Tribes. Tribes Ascend was so much fun. I wish I could play it. I guess I could play it, right?
What is going on? Wait, what's it doing? Bro, it's Omega gaming weekend. Just play it already.
Maybe. Maybe I'll do it. That's fun. Really cool addition. I like it a lot.
Not going to do that shit. I'm sorry. Sorry. I'm not going to fall for that. Not right now.
This way? I forgot. All right. Let's go. I made it. All right. Nice. I can't believe Disney
Infinity 3.0 didn't work. I'm very upset by that. Dude, I got a pretty good idea for what's coming
up next. We'll have to see. Am I doing this right? Make it? Do I get a checkpoint? I can't buy it.
Oh, I can. That's a lot of money. What does it do? Mires an instant beam that causes a large
explosion on impact similar to a certain familiar face. Holy shit. Okay. I can't. Oh,
what's grabbed? I can't grab. Where's my grappling hook? Why can I not grab? R? No. Mouse 4. I didn't
unequip it or something, did I? Whiplash. Mouse 4. Oh, that's weird. Wow. I didn't want to do that.
Okay. What's the strategy here? I think I'm doing only cannon. I didn't hit one single fucking.
Wow. Why am I jumping into it? I thought it's a jump rope. Where did I just go?
No blood. Excuse me. What are you talking about? All right. First of all,
unequip all this stupid shit that I have on. Unequip this. Unequip this. Unequip this. Actually,
keep that. No. No. Get rid of that. Yeah. Nail gun. Keep that equipped. Just this one. Actually,
no, that's fine. All the rail cannons and the rocket launcher. Okay. I don't want all this crap.
I feel like I'm like cycling through weapons like an idiot. We're good. We're good. Good.
Everybody settle down. It's doing it again. I can parry that. Why? I thought that was the shotgun.
I need to heal. I'm in like lunge at me. What? What happened? It explodes. I tried to parry.
I didn't do it. You can only parry with the blue arm. What was wrong with that? Blue flash
means you can't parry. Oh, so why am I trying to parry? Who told me to do that? No. No blood.
No blood. None of that blood got on me. That's pretty damn good against the loliathan.
What am I doing? I'm going to stick in them. God damn it, man. Come on.
I can parry the bullets, but that doesn't really help though. Huh? Where's the tail? Where's the
tail? Is it dead? Oh, that was crazy. Damn. Damn. That was crazy. Crazy. Damn. That was crazy.
That's it, buddy. You're going in the drink. Voice actor? What do you mean I'm going in the
drink? What does that mean? I don't want to go in the drink. How do I get out of here?
I need more than that. Under 10 seconds. I'm at 6-1. Should I be concerned? You know what I'm saying?
Cry for the weeper. Oh my God. I'm about to... I'm going to put the game on easy. Holy smokes.
I got one. What the fuck? Oh. Holy shit. Got someone. This song goes hard. Is there even a
song playing? Oh, do I have to write these? Okay, so now where do I go? This area is terrifying.
Yikes. What? Just die. Kill me. Just kill me. What happened? Did I die? I don't understand.
I don't know what happened. I guess I did it. Where's the place to put this? Stop it. Wait,
why am I locked out? Turn on the music? Music on. How come I can't get in here? I'm missing
something here. Can I put it down? What did I do? This is the beginning of the game. You
accidentally do a speedrun strategy and you softlock the game. Wait, that sucks. If I re...
Oh, shit. It's not that far. There it is. Oh, come on. Carry the shotgun bullets. That's right. I
forgot. All right. The weapon combination that I have is really stupid, so I can't do it.
I physically can't press the buttons because that's left click and middle mouse at the same time.
So this is going to be hard to do. All right. Let's try this again, please.
I guess I can do it. It's hard to do because I accidentally scroll the wheel. It still says
Disney Infinity 3.0. Does it really? Are you serious? No, it doesn't. Come on. Don't do that
to me right now. Where are you? It's doable. All right. Now what games we've played so far.
We played Disney Infinity 3.0. That's it. Ow. Okay. Let's try this again and not screw it up.
Okay. Here we go. So now I put this on the thing, right? What do I do? What do I take this?
When you say go right, you have to understand that when I read go right, I don't know if I'm
in the orientation. Downstairs. Music up. Okay. I'll do music up. What's this? Okay. What's that?
Okay. Start it. Start the encounter. How do I start the encounter? How do I start the encounter?
How do I start the... Just die. Just die. Just die. Just die. It's a waste.
Geez. I didn't have enough things. You piece of shit. Just die. Oh my goodness. It's so many
things on the screen. Delete that weapon. Come on. Respawn the things. All right. Don't give me this
shit. Oh, where? Oh my God. I didn't... I don't want this weapon.
Oh, what's that? Let me do it.
This is like the moment of impact of a car accident. You know what I mean? This is like
the moment of impact on a car accident. Just times a thousand. You know what I mean?
Just like... Ready? Go. Give me the doubles. Give me the doubles. Come on. This is it.
What's up? What happened? Don't you dare step back up. Hey. A checkpoint. I got to get a
checkpoint. Is there a checkpoint in here? Where's there a checkpoint? I need a checkpoint right now.
Is there a checkpoint anywhere? How are you still firing at me? Dude, you shouldn't be able to do
that. Thank God. I need a checkpoint. Come on, dude. What is going on here?
I'm doing a lot of screaming. I'm sorry. People are probably like annoyed by this by now.
Come to me. Okay. What? Get a jump? Oh, shit. What the fuck? Dude, I don't know where to go.
I'm tethered to that person. I don't... Why is it blocking that shit? Oh, no way. Dude. I'm going to
watch the YouTube videos. I'm going to be eating this. Stop that. It's fucking cheating. Oh my
fucking God. Oh, no. Please don't do it. Why does it explode so much in my face?
Please.
Is anybody alive? Who's alive? Who is alive? There's nobody left alive. Shoot a coin. That
guy's dead. Oh my... Oh, my heart hurts. I thought I died. I thought... Did I die? Oh my God. I thought
I went in the fucking lava and died. I was supposed to say no way. No fucking way. Oh my God. Wow.
Wow. Wow. Wow. I thought it was instant kill. Oh my God. Get me out of here. Oh my God, guys.
No fucking way. And this is 6-2 now. That's not even the end. I got to fight the boss.
I'll turn it up for the final encounter.
You've taken everything from the machine and now all the means is perfect hatred.
Anakin, don't. Keep running for yourself. Is this where the Gugget is coming?
Is this where the Gugget is coming? Yeah? All right, let's go. I'm not giving you a second.
Break you apart. Splay the gore of your protein form across the stars. I will grind you down until
the very spot you fly for mercy. My hands shall relish, ending you here and now.
My God. I can't block. Oh. Jesus. No way. You can't be serious. This is so hard. This is so
goddamn hard. What the fuck? Oh my goodness. Oh my God. Why am I getting that close?
Shit. OK. You piece of shit. Oh my God. Damn it.
No. What is going on? I panicked. This is so fucking ridiculous. Hey, it's this
Omega gaming weekend, man. I got to play some more stuff. This is a fucking sick game and yeah.
It's way too hard. It's just way too hard. It's way too hard. It's just too hard. It's just too
hard. It's not going to happen. It's impossible. It's just it's like an unbeatable encounter where
it's like you can't fucking do it or whatever. Get this stupid fucking thing off. This thing
just hurts you. It's awful. Is this? Show me what you were made for.
Just kill me. It's over. It's over. Just kill me. Kill me. He killed me in one hit.
Oh, god damn it. He moves so fast. It's just like I parried it. Shoot him. When he teleports behind
you, it's not even fair. That should remake the game. They should redo the whole game. Make the
whole thing from scratch. The whole thing from scratch again. Is there a reason why it's OK?
This is a problem. Changing my weapons as mouse scroll is fucking ruining everything
because melee is mouse scroll click. So I'm like, I'm this boss is just OK. You want to play this
game? All I feel like I'm doing is just putting my head just underwater and just screaming
underwater and then lifting my head up. I feel like I'm just yelling underwater. I'm just going like
That's all. This is it. That's the whole thing I'm doing. What do I want to change it to?
You want to give it a try? If you think it's so funny, then come try it.
Dave. We're sitting in the back. All of you. You too. Greg. Fuck you, Greg.
I do a live show. I do a live video game show and only five people show up.
I don't know what fucking time zone I'm in. When does he do the ding? When the fuck is the goddamn
thing? When's the ding? He wins the ding. He's not going to do a ding now. All of a sudden,
I don't feel like doing a ding anymore. Is that what I'm understanding? Where'd he go?
Um, usually I want the devs to look at this. Usually he comes down and there's like a few
seconds. I want the devs to take a look at that. I want the devs to take a look at that one.
Something might have been wrong with that. I parried it. I'm not playing this game anymore.
I'm done. Dude, I can't even tell. Get the shotgun. I don't want to. Wrong arm. Well,
why is it doing that? I don't understand. You. Okay. That's my time. That's my time.
That's my time. That's my time. I need to do it.
I'm the taste of victory. Yeah. This tastes. Is this my blood?
I've never known such a relief. I need some time to think. We will meet again, machine.
55 restarts holy shit into the ceiling how does that work is it gonna be is
there enough more to act to later or is there more to act to there's a lot you
missed so is the game feature complete at this point I guess I could just read
the ending cutscene is that okay I beat the thing and I'm asking you it's
answering the question right now it's like guys so can you guys anybody tell
me if there's something that's on the screen as can you tell me what happens
at the end okay let me read this pieces never fit because your light is sword
and fire wait what this is me I'm reading I'm not pretending how to read
I know how to just I'm just taking it in it's funny when I try to look up where
you are is right there next to the camera so just hurts so Gabriel comes
and kills the council and they're like don't why are you doing this and he's
fighting for hurts am crazy I genuinely did not I just wanted to get to that
next forever okay now it's time for the part of the stream where I go full cam
and pretend like I'm doing a movie watch along like Amazon Prime or something you
know if you find it funny if I just set that full screen and pretend like I'm
reacting to a movie that's not here well actually you know what let's save this
let's save this let's I want to start with this tomorrow I'm not the stream
still going but I want to like get popcorn and shit and snacks and pretend
like full cam I'm watching a movie and it's like oh yeah you can for legal
reasons I can't put it on the stream but it's like you can queue it up with me
and I'm gonna I'll do it I'll do it for like fucking 30 straight minutes what
movie should it be and I'm just pretending to react to stuff that
happens in it that's gonna be so hard jaws to the Incredibles I actually have
no I've never seen the incredible start to finish I have no idea what happens
and then if you actually took that and like cute it up with the movie that I
said it was it might be actually kind of a funny watch along I've never seen the
incredible start to finish all right that was cool that was a very hard that
was awful in a good way I don't mean the game awful I mean it was just very hard
and very terrifying and very scary now we're gonna we're gonna wind down a
little we're gonna pull it down just a little bit because we're gonna play
hamster playground now I think very cool