Hey, what is going on everybody? Jerma here with Facecam Fortress 2, Mondays edition.
Playing as the Demoman. Hold on. Needed to kill somebody.
Playing as the Demoman on King of the Hill Badlands. This place is bad. Bad, bad, bad.
Whoa, whoa, whoa, okay, okay. Don't freak out here. It's just a sentry.
And it's gone. Oh, oh, oh my god. Thank you, my goodness. That was... What the hell is going on?
Oh my god. I'm speechless right now. There was just three big sentries, I think. One up there, one down, and one to the right.
Holy crap. That jar lag. Wow. Oh my god. Okay, good to know. Good to know. We're getting beat. Help me.
Oh man, I'm gonna die. I'm just gonna burn out. This is gonna be a sad death. Where's the health?
I'll thank every single god that exists for this medic. Get that guy. Where is this sentry now?
Is it still over here? It's right there. That thing's going away right now. See you later, sentry.
Another one. You guys are relentless with the sentry guns. At least I got the point.
Oh, by the way, everyone was telling me in the last couple videos, they said,
Jerma, your room is an absolute mess. So I do agree with you, so I'm gonna clean it for you right now.
Just a pair of scissors. We don't need those. Let's see. Some kind of disc. This is an expensive camera.
Oh! You see, I just made somebody gasp. Somebody just went, Jerma! Okay, we just lost.
You know what happens when you lose? You do it again, and you win this time.
Should I stay, Demoman? That's the real question. Hmm. How many Demo- What do we have? I'm staying. We only have one. It's me.
Hiya, where ya doin'? Oh, I'm gonna take that sentry out!
Alright, let's actually win this time. Gotta get a victory under our belts. Come on, dudes.
How did I miss you? You slippery bastard! Oh my- Get the hell over here!
Somebody, you know what? Someone's getting crushed with this. I'm going to crush someone.
I'm mad right now. I'm mad. Bro.
Wow, this is- I can't believe I'm actually still standing here.
Not this time! Alright, at least I got the point. At least we got the point.
Oh, this engineer. No, let me kill him! I need to get the kill! No!
God, okay. Oh, and welcome to FaceCamp Fortress 2, where Jerma runs around in circles with the-
Okay, there we go. Good, good, good. Good. Get that kill.
That engineer's not gonna build anything in that room. Not while I'm on my watch.
I try to say, not on my watch, and I say, not while I'm on my watch.
Not exactly sure what those words would mean together. That was actually like a literal phrase.
Not while I'm on my watch. Oh, you bastard.
Finally. I landed a shot on somebody.
Ugh! Alrighty. Get outta here.
Let's get a long range shot right there. That would've been sick. Too bad I didn't get it.
Oh! Baby!
Come on, somebody stumble outta there. Somebody stumble on outta there.
Oh, that's how you smash!
That guy turned the corner and just got absolutely decimated.
Oh, that's one way to lose.
Anything up here? No. Spy, though.
Perfect opportunity right here for one of these.
Oh, never mind!
Everything in that room is going down right now.
I'm just going to lob stickies into that window and just absolutely kill everything.
You ready? Are you ready for this? I hope you're ready for this.
Oh, that medic is a brave soul. What a brave bastard.
Swinging away with his bone saw. In a room full of people and a sentry.
I commend you, good sir. But you, on the other hand, whatever.
You know what? He can keep his pride. It's time to destroy everything in that room.
Oh, I got one guy. Oh, come on. Get in that room. Get in that room.
Oh, there it is. Sentry down.
And big heavy up. Big heavy dead.
Anything else in this room that I should be aware of? Yes, there is.
Anything else I should be aware of here? Look at all this carnage.
I wonder what happened in there.
Keep him closed off. Keep him closed off.
Yeah! That's going to be it.
Cool. Top rack.
13 points as a demo, man. Blink.
I promise I'm not going to kill you. I promise.
Oh, you walked away from one taunt kill into another one.
But I didn't get it.
Alright, we'll do one more life and then I'm going to close it up.
One more life as a spy.
And what we're going to do here is actually very, very important.
Alright? I'm going to try to not kill anybody.
I just want to blend in.
I just want to be on blue team. That's all I want.
But first I want to kill this medic.
Okay, now I want to just blend in.
Alright, here we go. Ready?
Not going to try not to kill anybody.
Just want to pretend that I'm on blue team.
Alright, guys. We got to get on that point.
Alright, yeah. We got it. Sweet deal. Awesome, dudes.
Alright, we got to cap this. Come on, guys.
Cap it.
Alright, nice job, you guys. We did a good job here.
I commend both of you guys.
Got to get that sentry up, man.
I don't want to get backstabbed by any spies because I'm a sniper, you know.
Aw, I got to snipe.
Get that stuff up.
Come on, let me zoom in here.
Got to be careful.
All kinds of things can happen right now.
You know, this guy...
If I...
You know what?
I'll see you guys all next time.
Of course.
And...
Oh, well.
I was going to end it by...
That was funny.
But you know what? I guess I'll end it from right this.
From right this, yeah.
One.
And...
Two.
Three.
Come on. Who wants to kill me?
Somebody kill me.
Somebody please kill me.
Oh my god.
You got me.
Alright, guys.
That's going to be it.
I will see you guys all next time.
And of course, take care, everybody.
Time to clean my room.
Let's go.