I know, I know. I'm late, yeah. Is it literally late anymore? Should we really call it late anymore?
Should we just call it normal? It's just normal. He's tired? No. He's tired. He sounds sick.
Yeah, because I kind of am still. I got COVID the first week of November and it's like,
some days I just feel fine and then some days I'm just like, oh, my like, my throat hurts again.
I'm negative for COVID though. I think my body's just still kind of getting over it.
This is not abnormal for me. Whenever I get sick, whether it's cold, flu, any illness that's going
to cause me to cough, sneeze, or have a sore throat, this shit always takes a long time for me to get
over it. It always kind of lingers for at least a few weeks. But yeah, still kind of getting over it.
Milk and cheese voice. I haven't had any today. Oatmeal voice. I haven't heard that one.
But there's a lot to talk about. There's an unbelievable amount of things we have to go over.
So in my smooth radio voice, I think I'll tell you. Hold on. Hold on. Okay, so I'm going to
just wait a second. I'm going to wait to be able to trickle in like we usually do. Just chill for a
minute. Are you dreaming right now? I don't think so. Because that would mean I'm dreaming
right now. So if you're dreaming and you're typing here, that means I have to be dreaming
because I would see you write that. I would have to be asleep. There's no way we're both dreaming.
You're an astral projection. Weird. That's not how that works. Well, okay, but I saw it in my chat.
So if you're dreaming typing that, that means that I have to be asleep too. And it's my dream,
not yours, because I would be seeing that over here. That's my dream, not yours. Let's stop
talking about your dream. You know, when I hear my dream, I'm way too dank. Just me talking. Am I
loud? I'm a loud person, I think. That's why I try to like shut up sometimes. If I ever get like
really excited, I'll be like, oh, I can't wait. I'm very conscious about how loud I can get.
Who do you think is going to win the World Cup? Um, I don't, I don't, I don't know. That's, um,
football, right? Soccer. I'm just going to pick. I'm going to say, uh, what teams even playing
is like, it's every team like in the world, right? I don't know who's got the good team this year.
I guess I'm just gonna jump on that van wagon. Hey, who has the good team? This is somebody said
TSM. Can you imagine? Oh, dude, I think like, I think cloud nine Brazil is going to get it.
Yeah. All right. Who's the team that's like, everyone thinks is cool. Everyone's like
waiting for them to play. Cause I, let's go. It's definitely Scotland. No, Argentina. Mexico.
Does Mexico have a team? Does Mexico have a team this year? I mean, what do you mean this year?
It's why am I saying that Mexico in it? All right, let's go. I'm Mexico all the way. They're going
to go all the way at least top five. I don't know how it works, but they're going to be at least top
five. Where's your Mexico shirt? I don't know. I it's gone forever. I don't know where it is.
I loved that shirt. It fit me so well. I thought the, I that was like my, one of my favorite shirts
and it's gone. I don't know what happened to it. No sponsor. There is a sponsor today, but not till
later. So today we have breath of the wild. We're going to be jumping into as well as after two or
three hours, we're going to hop over to multiverses. Season two is out for multiverses
and Warner Brothers has sponsored the stream. So I'm like, yeah, let's go.
Warner Brothers has been very good to this channel. So, and I do, and I think multiverses is fun. So
we're going to try it. There's some new characters that I haven't played. What platforms is multiverses
on? Well, we'll get to that. We'll get to that. Cause I, I'm not so sure either. I have to figure
that out. Are you a happy boy? Yeah, I've been okay. I'm very busy, but all right. So you guys
ready? It's been a few minutes. Let's talk. Number one, the end of the year awards are upon us.
This weekend, we're going to open up nominations for the end of the year awards. You will be able
to nominate for two weeks. After two weeks, we're going to collect all the information. We're going
to collect all the data. It will be a voting period for about two weeks. And if all goes
according to plan, the show will not be on new year's Eve this year. It will be part of
a Christmas extravaganza. So there's going to be a big holiday stream this year,
hoping planning, trying to get there. And it, it will be part of that stream. So that's the plan.
I, but don't want to talk too much about it because it's not, we're not quite guaranteed.
We're pretty much guaranteed, but I don't want to announce it too hard yet. But the plan is,
but regardless, there's going to be an end of the year awards like there is every year
in the discord. A channel will open with just like we've done in previous years.
Will Battleaxe be before this? That is a great question. There is, there is a chance that the
Battleaxe stream might happen like maybe even in the same week as the holiday stream. There's a
lot going on. If not, then the Battleaxe stream will be like in the first or second week of January.
Still trying to figure it out, but they will happen. These two streams are going to happen
within 30 days of each other. But all right. Are you guys ready? Let's, we're going to do some
Breath of the Wild, chill out for a little bit. And then from there, we're going to go into
multiverses, which should be fun. Why do you hate being an old man? What? I hate being an old man.
Samus Forrest is going to come back next week. So here's the, here's the plan. Oh, okay. No,
I'm going to wait to talk about this until like, maybe a little bit like an after an hour. We'll
talk about it. So this weekend, be on the lookout for the nominations channel and I will talk about
it again when I, when we stream again. Um, you know, I want to just say more than one, a few
times GrottoBeasts.net. If you haven't already, and you want to be able to be notified and be
ready when that goes on sale, I would go to GrottoBeasts.net right now and sign up. We're
trying to gauge again, how many units we should really be prepared for. That's important because
that's close. That's very close. I think the excitement levels are starting to rise on that
a little bit because it's, it's, it's very, very close to being starting. Is it an NFT?
No, it's not. It's physical cards. You already knew that though. That's, and you know what,
I'm, I'm upset with you. You already knew that. What is this? Pinned chat. We can pin chat now.
Oh shit. Look at that. What? It happened. It works every time. Yeah, it does. All right,
you guys ready? We're going to play Breath of the Wild and then we're going to move to Multi Versus
and then I'll give you the schedule for this coming next couple of days. I want to get the
end of the year award stuff situated this weekend. We'll be back on Monday with probably some more
Sims 4. We have to keep continuing that McNulty arc and then maybe like Tuesday or Wednesday of
that week, depending on how far we get in the McNulty arc, we'll see how that goes.
All right, here we go. Let's play Breath of the Wild. This is going to be a chill session.
You know what I mean? We're just chilling today. I feel like the streams have been a little
unhinged to the last of the last few days. So we're just going to, we're going to do some,
just we're going to relax and just go shrine hunting. You know what I mean? It's been a little
wild. Oh, I think we need it. We need a breather here. It's always unhinged. Somebody just said,
do you want us to be serious? Cause I, oh shit, I took too long. My switch turned off.
But yeah, lots of fun things happening. Battleaxe stream is being worked on. Christmas stream is
being worked on. Grotto beast is coming. End of the year awards are happening. There's a lot going
on. What happened to my screen? Oh, it's not plugged in. Oh shit. Hold on. Wait one sec. Not
plugged in. I was wondering. Back here. Yeah. Reach back here. Did I get it? Okay. Get on.
We're going to talk about this. I'm going to talk. I've forgotten to talk about this like a dozen
times. I got, I got to, we have to, we got to talk about this. It's so important actually.
Okay. So do you guys also, does it also make you a little angry? I gotta make sure my notifications
are up. So every monitor always has all the inputs underneath tucked in and then in a weird spot.
Does that annoy anybody else that like you have to like lean down and stick your head up and like
pull your arms around? I just wish they were somewhere simple, like on the side or something.
You know what I mean? I know, I know people are going to go, dude, your cable management
will be stupid. You wouldn't be able to have monitors next. But I mean, I feel like some of
these are just so tucked in and so hard to reach. I feel like this has to be a better solution than
like tucked into a cave behind your monitor. You're right. Okay. I thought people were going to
think I was crazy for this. All right. And let me just go here. No, I don't want to put parental
controls on. Okay. There we go. What have I turned for? Can you turn parental controls on
for yourself accidentally? No, you can't, right? You can? Okay. That's weird. All right. Let's go.
You guys should be able to see it now. Back into a breath of the wild. Ready to play. You're going to
McDonald's? Oh, sick. All right. The last thing that I did. Kind of loud, isn't it? Maybe not.
It's a little loud for me. I just beat the second guardian. So now what the heck do I do? I was going
to say the F word, but I didn't want to say. Okay. Let's see. Where are we going? So I just
did all this. I did a Goron city. I did the beast. It was sick. What did, why do I have all this
marked? All right. Look at this entire area over here that I have not even looked at.
Where should I go now? Go south, go south, go west, west of the volcano. I mean like,
like this way, like over here, go south, go south, go. You know, I've seen a lot of south Andes and
I think I'm going to listen. So you mean like down here, down here, down here, west, south,
like southwest, like right here. This sounds like a pretty good place to go. All right.
All right, let's go. Let me get on a tower. Let's make it happen. Move your cam. Oh, that's right.
I'm blocking some stuff. Aren't I? What are your thoughts of the, of the death of Twitter?
You know, I was thinking about, um, I was thinking about just releasing every one of my drafts.
Just like, I like guys, I'm releasing the drafts and just take like a bunch of screenshots of like
one, like 30 tweets and just putting them as images next to each other. Do it. Release the
drafts. Yeah. I'm going to unclassify the tweets. Why is it camera in a weird spot? Hold on. Yeah.
I'm a little too far forward. Okay. There we go. All right. So you're saying, so for here,
let's do, uh, I'm gonna go this way. Let me take a look and see if there's any shrines because
that's the title. Got that one. Got that one. All right. Looks like over there. Wait, no,
that's not Southwest though. Everyone's going to be screaming at me. It's this way. What's this
cathedral? Have I been in there? No, that's where I found the, the guy, right? All right. I'm going
this way and I'm going to get that tower. That's the plan. And I'm going to teleport there. You're
the guy. I don't know what I'm, I'm the guy of, but I don't know. You may have found me. I might be
the guy. How the heck is everybody doing today? Already cold. What are those? Oh shit. All right.
Hold on. So I don't want to go that way. I want to turn around and I want to, where's the tower
over there? I don't have any cold gear. It's all right. I'll be out of the cold area in a second.
Oh my God. And hopefully I just didn't die. This is definitely not cold over here, right?
Is it cold up here? Trine? No, let me get the tower first. That's, that's priority number one.
That's absolute priority number one. That hurt. Oh, I fell from actually kind of far. Yeah. It's
not cold over here. This is the Elden Ring area. Don't say what, hey. All right. Hey, do you guys
think that Elden Ring's DLC is going to get announced in the next like month? When do you
think it's going to happen? I'm so ready. I hope, I hope it's, but I hope it's ready and I hope it's
good. Don't bat-chest Elden Ring. It's like one of the best games ever made. Don't, please.
I was actually thinking about game of the year, right? Cause like, oh, the game of the year,
right? When it's coming, it's coming up. And I'm just trying to make my top five or top three.
And I can definitely say Elden Ring is number one, but also, are we bat-chesting Elden Ring?
Have we got, we have not gotten there, right? We've gotten to the point where you bat-cha,
it's like become Marvel. Like if I say Spider-Man, for instance, everyone's going to go Spider-Man,
bat-chest, that wasn't like that like five years ago, 10 years ago. Have we gotten to the point
where From Software now gets the bat-chest treatment? It can't be, right? No, I, I don't,
I don't, I don't agree with that one. No, I don't agree with that one. I think you guys are wrong.
What's this? Pump it up, brother. This is our ancestral training ground.
Us three Goron blood brothers are in the midst of a contest of endurance.
Feel the burn, brother. We're trying to become strong and powerful Gorons. Right now we're
competing to beat the heat. So sweaty. We're Gorons, but the heat is too much for us these days.
Remember, what are you talking about? It's too hot to handle in Goron City,
so we came here to train ourselves. I have an idea. Come join us. Yeah, come try the
Contest of Endurance. Okay. A guy like you has a burning passion in his belly. It's inspiring.
All right. When you already step up onto the platform, then the Contest of Endurance will
have to like take the heat or something like burn. I have to like get burnt or something.
Everybody bat-chesting Elden Ring. I can't believe it. Why? Did somebody make a post on like the
Elden Ring Reddit or something that's like, oh man, you have to have a really high IQ to understand
the story of Elden Ring. You know, like America and all this shit. It's like, did that happen?
Did that happen? And now everybody is giving it like Rick and Morty treatment. I, I don't believe
it. You guys are full of shit. I know it. Okay. If you leave the ring or pass out, it's over.
Prepare yourself for the Contest of Endurance. The air has become very hot. Okay. So what? Am I
allowed to heal or do I just have to, do I have to do fighting? All right. Condense the body.
Condense it. Make it center your body together. Breathe deeply, but not fast. Deeply, but not
heavily. Slow breaths. Condense your body. It was fucking easy. You're amazing. Is it because of
the clothes I had? Okay. I'm granting you the highest honor, the chance to participate in the
Contest of Ultimate. Oh, that was just a joke. Okay. Toughest test known to Goron kind. You see
the ring behind me, the one surrounded in fire. Do you feel it in your gut? What a bad idea it is
to go there. Your gut is dead on. That special training area is even harder than the last one.
This contest won't just challenge you with heat, but also with fire. If you lose your focus,
your body will catch fire. Make sure you're prepared for this. It said that passing this
test will reveal a shrine. Fuck, I hate being on camera. Is that heat resistant gear you have
there, brother? A real Goron man shouldn't have to rely on wussy stuff like that. Goron up and take
the challenge with, uh oh. Okay. So I can't wear heat resistant gear. So, all right. Let me get,
let me figure this out. So can I drink a heat resistant potion or something? Or is that,
is that illegal too? So I don't have heat resistant stuff. If I drink this, will it,
will I get, will it be mad? This is technically, it's technically, it's cheating. Okay. You're
going to dope, doping the fire contest. Try it. I don't want to try it because this is,
this is good stuff. Let me see if I can handle it without that. So let me heal. Um,
I need to make some new food. I got to go on like a food run because I want to have full,
at least full hearts for this. Uh oh. I'm probably in trouble here. I'm just going to go,
can I just find something to eat on the ground? Like, can I just pick up rocks and like eat like
the dirt on the ground and shit? Like, can I just eat the dirt? There's got to be just random shit
I can find on the ground, right? I'll be right back. I got to mark this because I'll lose where
this is. I can bring it to Congress. I swear to God. Bring it. A is B, B is A. Bring it. I swear
to God. No, it's right here. Okay. I need to find just something to eat. Is this a track? Oh,
I thought this was like, um, a thunder mountain from Disney. I was about to get really excited.
Do you have food? I know, but it has benefits and I don't want to eat it. Oh, whatever. I'll just
eat something. Who cares? Equip an ice weapon. Will that help? Okay. Why would I walk into that?
No, I'm taking this off because I don't, I don't trust anybody here. I'll just wear. Oh,
you have the torch. All right. So I'm going to just eat whatever. It doesn't matter.
I can get it back. Yeah. What is this? Whatever. Just drink it. All right. I'm ready. Let's see if
I can wait. I got to take all the, I got to take these clothes off. Does it matter what I put on?
Just put on the regular. All right. Here we go. Ready? Same. Leave the ring of faint and it's over.
I'm for the world famous contest of ultimate endurance. Go. Um, what else is, what is burning?
Wait, I can block. What do I do?
Oh my God. I just cheated.
Does that count?
I, that counts, right? I win, right?
I win. So epic. What a powerful display. What fire. That was something else. Nice.
Did I get a chest or something? Oh no, it's a shrine. I unlocked a shrine. Oh, that's so cool.
Well, that's a shrine or some such really appeared just like that. Am I still burning?
The legend is true. You won the contest of ultimate endurance, little man. You're amazing.
It's still burning though. All right. Well, all right, cool. So this is the shrine. Of course,
the title says it's shrine. I do need to heal though. I should probably put the fire gear back
on, right? Yeah. All right. I need to eat something because this is bad. I was going to eat the
movement speed shit. I have to go on a cooking thing, right? Movement speed. I just, I need to
I'm eating the food. I'm not going to do resident evil rocket launcher with this shit. I know I will
just eat it. Just eat it. Eat it. It doesn't matter. Well, I'm not going to make this ever
again. Just eat the food. Eat this. Do it. Why can't I press the button? I like don't want to
press the button. I can't do it. I can't do it. Okay. Don't waste ingredients. I can go on an
ingredient hunt. I just ate a legendary fish. Derma, please. The shrine will heal you. I don't
know what this shrine is. This might be a combat shrine. Reload. I thought they could be combat
shrines. This is not, was it not a combat shrine? You know that I don't. I told you I wasn't going
to get upset today and I'm already getting there. How am I supposed to know there's not going to be
like a combat shrine? Okay. No, no betting because I don't want people to lose money.
All right. So what is this? Move. Oh, wait. Oh, it's a gyro. I thought I was going to fail
that one somehow. I stopped playing chess and started just playing checkers. Everyone gives
me shit when I play this game about that. I'm just playing checkers. That's it. Don't play chess.
Fucking do it. Fucking grab it. Who's that button? Hit the button underneath it. Thank you.
I got it. I got it. It's right there. It's literally right there. I just have to be,
I have way more time than I think I do. Why did it stop? That's not fair. You can't give me the
Zelda you did it music and then turn, take it away from me. So what, how do I keep this up then?
What if I do this? That just turns it off. It doesn't do anything for me. What did you think
was going to happen, Jeremy? Well, somebody asked, what was that? Oh, somebody asked this like an
hour ago. They said, what are you drinking? It's a green tea energy formula and it's really good.
Okay. Do I, did I have it right? Is there a second one of these that I just didn't see that's
behind me or something? I have to freeze that in midair. Stop. Whoa. Nevermind. All right.
So what's going on here? You have to keep it up and I think it has to be quick. No, there's no way.
How do you do this? I just let go stand on it. Oh my God. That was so easy.
Oopsie. Rook, Bishop to E2. Queen to B11. King, F6. I'm on the wrong board. What am I doing?
That was, I just had to stand or whatever. All right. Let's take a look at this one.
So imagining you have to put out the fires. No, you have to, all right. Oh shit. Okay. So I have
to make, I have to light them on fire with that torch, which where even is it?
Why is it not lighting? Oh man. This is going to be awful. Okay. So I have to turn the water off
on each side while I, no, I'm sorry. I'm just going to fucking
light the torch on fire and shoot arrows at it. Oh boy. Oh man. Okay. What does this do? Oh,
all right. So, oh God, there's gotta be, maybe I can put one of those things on it. Can I light
my shit on fire? I don't think I can light it on fire with anything. Can I? Let me see.
This is not even fire. This is fake restaurant fire. These are fake restaurant candles. This is
not real fire. Okay. So now that I can't do that, wait, is there a torch? I can't even leave.
I'm glad nobody could bet that I was going to do this in seven minutes.
All right. Let's just do it the way that I was going to do it. And I'm going to just,
okay, we need to turn this off for a second. Oh shit. I'm close. I only need to look. Okay.
Hold on a minute. I just have to get two. Well, there's one on the left, one on the right.
And I think I know what to do here. I need to lower the one down here,
freeze it. And, oh man, I think, I don't know. I think I, okay, let me try this.
Stupid. All right. Why would you crouch? Oh fuck. There's only one more. No, I don't get it. I don't
understand. Wait a minute. I can't reach that. I can't reach it. No, it's definitely that you have
to click on this and then freeze this and go up there and then freeze that one and then turn it
and use the magnetic thing. And it's a bunch of bullshit. It's just a bunch of horse shit. It
really is. Okay. So I need to freeze this and then magnetize. I don't know. Can I magnetize? Can I
spin this without? No, I can't. Okay. Please tell me. Is this bait? Is this right here? Is this bait
or do I need to use this? Is this bait? No. Christmas tree. Give me some help. Christmas
tree. Christmas tree. Christmas tree. Football. Present football goal. I have no idea. Okay.
Football. Well, I can spin it like this and get all the ones here. Okay. So I just don't worry
about the ones on the left and right. And if I put the one, if I freeze this one and I try to light
the one on the left, the one on the right is going to put out the thing that's on the right.
So I have to freeze the one on the right and turn and then, I don't know. Here we go.
I wish I could hand this controller to one of you right now. I wish I could just hand it to you.
Like I would hand it to you and I would just sit back and just bite my fingernails while you did it.
Song Santa mallet. Okay. That hurt. Song. Sing a song with Santa mallet.
Some people keep saying magnet, magnet, magnet, but I don't know what I would magnetize because
the, what is that? What do I magnetize here? That's, this is the only thing I can magnetize.
Like pull this down or something. Oh shit. Oh, I can put that on. All right. I figured it out. I
got it. What does it have to do with Santa? Ooh, inventory is full. What do I have? Bullshit. I
can just get rid of the torch. All right. I got it now. Cool. Okay. I don't, now, now it's easy.
Now I just freeze that. Okay. I was going to say, this is so confusing. There it is.
And there it is. There it is. There it is. God damn it. There it is. Light this. What is it?
Light it. I was going to say, give me a break. Wait, what about that chest? Where was that chest?
Oh, I don't get it anymore. You got the chest. No, there was this chest. Wasn't there?
And there's just one sitting back here. You can freeze things. Omega stupid.
I have not heard omega stupid before. Omega stupid. Hey, you can freeze things. Omega stupid.
All right. So how many do I have? I will tell you because you can't. Okay. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah.
I just wanted one. Omega stupid. That meant freeze. I don't know, man. People were doing
presents. Santa mallet. That to me, that does not mean freeze. That means when Santa
comes to deliver the presents, hit him over the head like Tom and Jerry. That's what does that
mean? Oh, the treasure chest. Okay. I'm thinking like Santa comes to get the presents. What's the
mallet then? The mallet. No fucking clue what the mallet was. Yeah. I don't know what the mallet is.
The mallets would freak me out. If you didn't have the mallet there, maybe I would have understood
that. But to me, it's like, hey, get ready, hit Santa with this mallet. All right. Cool. That was
fun. Okay. So now, oh, right. The tower. D-Gen stream. What the hell? How is this a D-Gen stream?
Open this box. What's that? I thought I just kicked it off the cliff. Oh, wild berry. All right. I
gotta take a picture of that. Got it. Okay. Because now I can search for these if I want to. Climb,
please. Jesus. I swear I was trying my hardest to get that. I was, I was really trying. Okay.
Almost there. Any more shrines up here? It's actually not even hot. I can take off the hot
gear. Oh, wait. Hold on. We gotta, I gotta be ready for this. Yeah. I'm gonna take the hot
gear off. I don't need it. I want more defense. You know what I mean? God damn it. It's all right. I
can still do it. Wait, wait, wait. Why are these not exploding? Sorry. I just like screamed. What's
that? Ooh, it's a boomerang. I can't carry anymore. I'm out of breath by the time I got here.
That's going to be the most menacing thing I've ever seen. If you imagine you have to shoot somebody
with a bow and arrow and they have a big weapon in their hand and they are sprinting side to side
and you and they're getting closer and closer, that would be so horrible because like your aim
has to be true or that's it. All right. What that, um, this boomerang over here. Okay. There it is.
Cool. This thing does a lot of damage. Do you have any shitty weapons to get rid of this? 36 damage.
That's pretty good. I get everything I got. It's good. Anything terrible that I can just use right
now? All these. Okay. The boomerang looks cool. Yeah, it does. Your stomach's killing me. Just
take it easy. You know what helps me? Ginger tea. I'm telling you, inventory is full. I didn't want
to do that, but it's all right. All right. So I need to see what, what, how I've held onto this
Renek bow forever and people just keep telling me what, should I even have this? You should just get
rid of this. Throw it away. Get rid of it. No bat chest. Keep it. What's so special about this?
I don't know. I don't, I want the higher damage. It has higher zoom. If I don't need the zoom,
my aim is pretty good. His aim is good. Okay. Where's the, there's a longer shot. I don't want
to fight you. The thing dogs can't climb. This is high up the ladder. This fucking ladder kid.
You have to shoot explosives with fire arrows. I guess that makes sense, but I'm still upset
about it. All right. So what's over here? I have really itchy eyebrow. Oh, that means there's a
ghost in the room. Is your face really itchy today? Oh, that means a ghost is talking about you.
Right. What's this for? No, dude. It's just dandruff. Like scratching my head and dandruff's
just falling on my shoulders. I'm like dandruff, clearly dandruff. Oh man, a ghost. Your itchy
head means like somebody's talking about you. Like, dude, no. No, it's sneezing. Somebody help
me here. It's like, oh, if you sneeze, it means somebody's talking about you. It's something
stupid. What is it? Somebody please help me. Something with the ears. Your ear's itching or
something, right? Your ears are warm. What? It's itchy nose. I had, no, I was close. Yeah. I had
it correct. Itchy nose. Your ears are itchy. That kind of shit. Yeah, I had it right. I mean,
maybe a little bit, but whatever. It is sneezing. There's a bunch of, there's a lot of things.
What is this? I'm going to have to take a picture of that. It's having hiccups. Did we just kind of
try to find ways to make it so people are talking about us? That's why everyone seems to be saying
something completely different. Like, oh, all these people are talking about me. Oh, itchy nose.
There's a ghost in the room. Like, no, your face just hurts or itches today. What? Oh dude,
you ate that Big Mac a little too fast. Yeah. We're talking about it right now. You ate it way
too quickly and it was fucking weird. Oh, it was perfect actually. Was it? I don't know.
Why is he electrocuted? Flurry rush. This is a weird camera angle. Am I controlling the guy
and fighting Link right now? This is very strange. Okay. Which way? Left is right.
Get out of the way. Change the camera. Boomerang. Is it gone? Where'd it go? What? What are you doing?
I was trying to get it to fly back at me. What? There's a night shield, broadsword,
a lot of items here. A lot of goodies. Ow. This thing's about to break, so I'll just keep using
it. All right. This is the silly electricity monsters. Somebody's talking. You prefer the cold
or the heat? Um, I, I don't, it's, it's interesting because I kind of go, I flip flop on it. Uh,
so I live in Las Vegas and you get extremes, kind of both. Uh, sometime Vegas is like 115
degrees Fahrenheit. What did I just get during the summer? And then it gets to be like 30 to 40
during December, January, February. There's a topaz. Oh, cool. I, I bounced back and forth
though, because I love the heat. I love just a burning hot day where you just like the haze in
the air and just like so hot out. Cause as you guys know, this is important. If you don't understand
the context behind this, I am, I, I, I clothes. I like light fitting, comfortable clothes, tank top,
pair of shorts, t-shirt, pair of shorts. And I can just be the tank top shorts guy
seven months out of the year. It's a big, big reason you are that guy. All I'm saying. Okay.
You can look, it's not like 80. You can call me that guy. It's not like 85. It's 120 degrees outside.
You understand it's not like, Oh, it's like 90. No, it's a hundred and 18 degrees Fahrenheit.
You're a pool boy outfit. Oh shit. Can I sneak up? Nevermind. I don't care anymore. It's actually
very nice in Vegas now. Sort of this, uh, like September, October, November, the fall. It's a
really, really nice kind of crisp pool, 60 to 80, 60 to 70. It's nice and crisp outside. It's got
that frisbee ball scent. You can die in this. Okay. You know, that frisbee fall sent nice and
kind of cool, like 65, breezy. I'm not, I don't know. Why would I fight them? I have to just jump
to this. Wait, what is all this shit? All right. Wait, wait, wait. I just fight, just kill. Why
are there so much shit everywhere? Moblin arm. Why is it coming back without a head? I thought
you just get rid of the head. Why is this keep coming back? I got the head. I already killed
the head. Where's he going? He's just going to, he just went into the water and died. All right.
That was weird. He was telling the other guy that I was here. Ooh. All right. I gotta take a picture
of this. Your album is full. What do you mean my album is full? Let's look at them for a minute.
That's pretty good. Why did I take these? I did not, I didn't take these. Did I take these? When
did I take these pictures? I didn't take these. I did. I guess I, I remember. Okay. I remember
taking. Okay. I, these are definitely where my pictures start. Yeah. I took this one. I definitely
didn't take this one. Oh, right. I was trying to get a picture of this big dragon. Nice vacation
photos. This really does remind me of vacation photos. Have you ever tried to take a picture
or something like, Oh, look, this, this like a parade went by or there's a thing on like a
cool thing on a ride to take a picture of if you're allowed to take pictures and this is what you
end up with. And it's just like, I don't even know what this was. I guess it was something far away
that I, it's kind of cool. I guess it's a very bad photo. Your camera's delayed. Yeah, it should be.
The mic is delayed too. Cam desync. What? Like right now? Why are you guys just noticing this now?
It just got very desynced all of a sudden. What? One, two, one, two, three, four, five,
six. What? It's actually fucked. What happened? I didn't, I mean, I've been sitting here just
sitting here. Is this, this is a new thing from like the last five seconds. I don't know what
happened. It just did it out of nowhere. The mic is faster. What? That should not be happening.
I have it set. Hold on. All right. So right now it should be really out of sync. Like right now.
It should be like, holy shit, this is unbearable. Right now. It should be matching now. This should
be fine now. That's so weird. That doesn't make any sense. No. Are we good now? Is it fixed? Stop
gaslighting him. I'm so confused. Why would this happen? It's better now? That's right. One, two,
three, four, five. I, I don't know what happened. I didn't touch any buttons you saw. I've been
playing. All right. So I have to delete some shit. Okay. Delete. I just select. Okay. No, I want to
keep some of these. These are like sentimental. Definitely not these. Definitely that one. I
remember this one's actually really sentimental because you could actually, this is when I was
freaking out. It's still delayed. I don't fucking understand what's going on. Um, this is pointing
in the direction I need to go. And, uh, I was having a fucking meltdown about this. And this
is like proving that what you guys are saying is fun. Refresh that worked. Yeah. Maybe refresh
the stream. Cause I, this should be no reason why that's happening. Why can't I take a picture of
this? I guess I can't. Maybe I already did. All right. Let's do this. So it's good. All right.
I get it. I get it. What do you, what does your room look like? You're going to Lowe's?
Like the hardware store. It's just a gray background. Doesn't make any sense.
Thank God. Oh, but I've made it. You rendered on a different layer than the background. I'm fine.
Why can't I jump on this? I'm going the other way. I'm just going the other way. I'm just
turning. I'm going to go the other way. I'm going, I'm going to look, look what's over here. Look
at all these. Why am I digging through the mud to get them all here? Just put them all in here.
Just put them all in here. Why am I doing that? Just dump them all in here.
It's giving me a fresh supply, but why is, I thought, um, okay. What's the, why would they
put all these here? Tell me why these, what are these doing here? What are these doing here?
Why are these everywhere? If we were not supposed to use them, it's just a giant red herring.
Why? Why would you put them here? No, there was, that was a fruit I could have eaten.
Stop yelling. I, yeah, I did say I was going to chill today. You're right. You're right.
All right. So now I just have to grab this. Okay. There we go. Good. Now I can just jump to this.
There we go. All right. Everything's fine. Everything's fine. Now I have to be careful
that I'm not going to screw this part up. I don't know what happened. All right. We're good.
God watch your skip three hours. Don't. Why do you always like lean out of the frame to
take your sip? That's weird. That's fucking strange behavior. I do what I'm going to do.
You do what you're going to do. It's all there is to it. What is this? What is this emote?
Omega stupid. Did somebody just add that? I thought it was, I thought it was a gnome.
What happened in my head? Oh, oh, mega stupid. All right. I got it. Yeah. Finally,
we have the DLC. I think I have everything. I bought the game like four years after it came out.
So I'm imagining I have pretty much everything. What is it? All right. This is like a sorcery map.
There's one mansion over here. What is this? I mean, this is where we're going.
This is where we're going. There's only one road. That's, that's where we're going to go.
There are no towns on the way or anything. We'll find out. I'm stamping it. Okay. Well,
what about shrines though? Let's take a look. I see a shrine. That wasn't a shrine,
but there's one right next to it. I feel like you would puke from doing that.
Your stomach would go up into your brain. Who's talk? Oh, they, I don't know. I don't like the
talking thing that keeps freaking me out. This you guys think is going to find Ganon's house.
Like, it's like a historical landmark or something. Oh, this is where Ganon lived.
This is his house before he became an evil mastermind with a small quaint house in this
little village. Now it's literally where he lives. I, did you just spoil the whole game for me? If
you did, then you're going to get a permanent and say ban thinking about it. Thinking of
pulling it over my head permanently ban for spoiling that shit for me.
You'd bite your tongue. That would be like a
Is it true that you hate Elden Ring? Those who that are saying that
be yelled at by me right now. No, that's game of the year. Oh, wait, I forgot. I didn't even
talk about it. Let's keep, we've got to talk about the rest of the game of the year stuff.
Elden Ring. Um, guess what else is on that list? Huh? Guess what else is on that list? What's
number two? Tell me. No, it's not God of War. I haven't played it. I'll tell you what it is.
Go on. No, it's not scorn. No, people are missing out on this here. People. I think people are
forgetting what came out this year. That is like really cool. Really unique. Oh, they can't talk
because it's emote only mode. Oh, oops. We'll go back over this in a minute when you can speak.
Okay. So this is, uh, what do we do here? Easy. I thought everyone was just Omega lulling me and
like bat-chesting me. I was like, why can't people talk about our games of the year?
So this, I needed one of those balls, which I'm just going to take one of these. Never mind.
No, we're not going to, don't add Omega mind. That's just, it's, it's pretty funny, but I don't
know. It's stupid. Not even one hit. It's going to be Indiana Jones or something. We're going to
pull this off and then we're going to get like attacked. Don't tell me I didn't know what I was
doing. Omega mind. Have you guys even seen that movie? I want, okay, put a poll up. Have you seen
Omega mind? Have you seen that movie? I feel like most people here have not seen it and they just
pretending that they've seen it. The key. Yeah. Do a poll. Have you seen Omega mind?
I doubt it's more than 50%. No, it's not. And there's no way it's no, there's no way that it's
that there's no way it's 80 plus percent of you. Stop shooting me. Okay. I've had enough.
Okay. Mega mind 3d, 80. Okay. So 81% of you I've seen mega mind bullshit. You've seen two clips
from it. You've seen two clips from it because you typed into YouTube, penis music origins.
Don't act like you watched the whole movie cams. De-synced again, dude. What is wrong with this
fucking camera? Yeah. All right. So that's electrifying the water. Oh wait, I need,
I want to electrify the water. So what's, what's going on with this? What's the problem here?
It's electrifying the water. Look, what was that whole thing with if there was batteries in the
ocean or what was it? You can let them out because now they can't backseat. What, what was that whole
thing where if you put like, okay, like how far away would you need to be if somebody put like
a battery in like, or like a car battery in the ocean or something? What was it? It was during
hitman. We talked about it. 80% of you have not seen mega mind. I don't believe it. It's one of
the worst popular kids movies. I basically, it's a kid, it's a kid's movie. I thought it was just
like a general audience movie. I don't think it was like a movie for kids. That's what a kid's movie
is, but not really general audience equals kids. That's yeah. I guess that's true. I guess that's
true. All right. Somebody get on the road. It's for everyone. E for everyone. Oh my God. I thought
that was a huge monster. I thought this was actually like a big thing that I could go. Holy
shit. What's down here? This is the roof of this place. Game of the year. Okay. So let's talk about
game of the year. I think that vampire survivors belongs there. Vampire survivors up there for game
of the year. That, yeah, that came out. Gunny rush rooms. See, I'm tired. Tired of going normal
speed. I tried rush rooms when I was five years old. Can't think of it. I ate them every day
without fail. Back in the day, I'd win every race I ran thanks to those things. But to 55 years later,
now I can barely drag these bones off the ground without those rush rooms. But no matter how many
I eat, I just keep thinking to Scooby Doo. I just won't leave. I'm just too old to pick up those
rush rooms when they grow up. Scooby Doo is such a funny character. I thought Scooby Doo was like
dumb when I was younger, but like a little bit later going back and watching, it's just like,
what a funny character. Raggy. It's such a strange character. I know like funny voice equals funny.
Oh yeah. He's got like a goofy voice, but I don't know something about it. It's just funny.
The cam is de-steeped. I wish I know what the fuck is going on here. Let me try this. I'm gonna
have to like reset this every so often. Right now it should be, I'm gonna try something here
bear with me. I have no fucking idea why this is happening. I need one sec. Yeah, Game of the Year.
Vampire Survivors. Definitely Elden Ring. Right? Definitely Elden Ring. I'm just grasping for words
right now. You know, Elden Ring. Definitely, um, yeah, definitely Elden Ring. What? But what is
this camera is so bad. I actually am going to hook up a DSLR by the way. This is the worst camera
I've ever used. It really is. I don't even know what to do with this fucking thing.
This thing sucks so bad. It's like not even funny. Why is the exposure going crazy? It's like trying
to go light, dark. The exposure is moving in and out. It's raising and lowering. See? I have auto
exposure turned off at the hardware level. This is the worst piece of equipment I've ever purchased.
This is the, this is probably the worst streamer piece of equipment I've ever bought.
Okay. Um, let me try this. Okay. Hi. Is that better? How about now? I don't
believe it's still desynced. Jesus. Are we desynced? It's better. I think I just keep refreshing
this auto exposure. This thing sucks. I'm hooking up a DSLR and I'm, everyone's going to give me
shit for it because I'm going to look weird for the first like three or four days. I look like
I'm on like fucking 16 millimeter film right now. All right. Is that better? Am I desynced? It's
better. It's a piece of shit. I, I, I'm going to fucking break this thing in half when I get this
DSLR set up. Okay. Uh, let's keep going. DSLR. Yeah. I'm going to set it up. It's going to look
so much better. You know, I'm going to turn it on. People are going to say uncanny Valley Andy.
You look like a rare steak. Quiet. Okay. So what was that mission? Something. All right. Rushroom
Rush. He's offered to trade a diamond for 55 rushrooms. I'm not going to do that. What are
you using? I'm using a logitech Brio. And in my opinion, this thing stinks. I'm just telling you
my actual product opinion. I think this thing stinks. This thing stinks. That's it. That's
my problem. That's my opinion of this product. I'm just giving them my opinion of a product.
This thing stinks. Okay. I need to make some food. Nice Amazon review. You have one star
and then an all lowercase with no punctuation. This thing stinks. And it's just a wicked shitty
like iPhone picture of the, of some guy holding it with like old man hands and the boxes kind
of toward the cardboard of the boxes torn up a little and he's holding it and he's holding the
whole thing in his hand zoomed in really close. It's always like a carpet. It's always like a
brown carpet underneath this. Always. Okay. You didn't think the monsters could have,
but they're fine. They'll be back any second now. You haven't run into any of my friends in the
room. Please let them know that sesame is waiting for them here. Okay. Bring this up. Look into this
one. Dell ultra sharp webcam. Is it good? Is it good? Or does that thing stink? What was that?
That the critic, John Lovitz, that old animation or his thing was it stinks. That was, that was a
show. No, I'm saving my rupees. Ah, that talks too much. I know. I know I really do.
Do we hear a song? It really is. People wonder why it takes me so long to get through anything
because it's like 75% me just talking and not moving and like 30% playing the game.
Oh yeah. His, his Elden Ring playthrough. What would that take him like 50 or 60 hours?
Oh, 275. No, I got, I guess what stinks is you're not grinding modern warfare to war zone.
Did you watch when I played Call of Duty a few months ago? I don't, you don't want me to do that.
Okay. So cool. So now let's get on the road. Can I get the horse?
This is not a horse outpost, is it? It is. All right. Get, I can get pranked too. This guy stinks.
I'm weird with games though. I really am. Same thing with TV shows. I like what I'm streaming
would just sit in here playing and I'm just screaming, whatever. But it takes me forever
to do anything even in my own time. So I will, Oh, I'm going to watch a TV show. That sounds good.
Episode one of Game of Thrones or whatever. It doesn't matter. And I'll be like, okay,
let's go queue it up. There it is. It's time to watch the episode, but wait,
I need to go to the bathroom. I'm going to go to the bathroom first. Okay. So I go to the bathroom,
I go pee. Okay. That was cool. That was fun. But I want to like something to eat first too,
because I have to be in like the perfect mood to sit here and watch this or do this.
And then I'll make a snack. I'll get some food. I'll eat it. And then I'll be like, wait,
there's no blanket here. I need a blanket on my legs while I'm sitting. Okay. Well,
I have to go get the blanket. Is it, is it, was one clean? I'll get a, maybe I'll freshen
up in the dryer or something like that. Right. It's like, it's like an hour before I sit down
and then I sit down and it's time. Why won't I fucking leave? I sit down. The show is about
to start. Wait a minute. Wait a minute. I'm not quite ready. Let me take a shower first.
Let's take a shower. And then I'm like clean. I'm fed. I have no, there's no bladder, right?
Walk down the stairs. Horses aren't, what do you mean horses aren't allowed? There's a stable
right here. There's a stable here. It's right. It's literally the entrance to the stable is
in this area. I can't, you need to get your shield up. How do I do that again?
How do I do the shield thing again? It's like jump and then like left Z and A.
It's hot. What were we just talking about? In the desert. All right.
You're searching for Kalisa, legendary treasure hunter. Then your search is over. You're looking
at her. I've been in the game for over 20 years. When I set my sights on a treasure, you can be
sure that I'll claim it. Okay. For a second, I thought it's cold, not hot. I thought I was
really nervous. I thought I was like, holy shit. I thought I was like starstruck or something.
It's cold. I don't have any cold armor. I have swim speed shit. I have cold drinks though, right?
Okay. Mid-level cold resistance. This one's for 11 minutes. Let's go. What's over there?
Oh, it's the third guardian, the octopus, the camel. We were not under water.
That was kind of a long cut scene. Oh, fuck. Why? I think I got the point.
Like after the first two shots, nothing unusual here.
This is Karakara Bazaar.
Why is that?
A law-forbidding bow mails from entering the city. You don't know about the divine beast
Va Naboris? Supposedly it's the guardian deity for Gerudo people, but it suddenly started
acting up a while back. There's nothing we can do to stop it either. It's protected by a fierce
sandstorm and intense lighting. Though it hasn't yet, it could easily head towards Gerudo town
with this oasis. I do my best to keep an eye out from here. I don't need any thanks. This is my
job after all. The lighting, the lightning, whatever. The desert's hot. Wait, say that again.
It is hot during the day. Oh, it's like Las Vegas. All right, so let's go. Something here though.
Is it cold to go in here? Why would I wake somebody that's sleeping like that?
What am I going to do? Good evening, though. I guess it's Savsaba in Gerudo, isn't it?
But before I say any more, if we met before, I came from Rito village. Have I been to Rito village?
Far to the north of here, it's a modest village on the Kabantha frontier.
I had a great plan, you know. I left Rito village, tried to earn some money out in the world.
It's so incredibly hot here during the day. It's been tough to work up the will to go any further.
I'd like to see what Gerudo town looks like, even if I can't go inside. It's just so hot.
I heard there's an elixir that can help beat the heat. It's made from insects with cooling
effects and monster parts. They don't seem to be selling the elixir anywhere. I've heard insects
with these cooling effects live in the cold parts of the Gerudo highlands. But well, the monsters,
they're rough, to say the least. So I'm not having a lot of success getting myself motivated.
How do I pronounce it? Am I pronouncing it wrong? What do you got? What do you got? Definitely. Ooh,
summer wing butterfly. Its wings absorb the warmth of the sun. Cook it with monster parts
to create an elixir that makes you feel warm. Ooh, I'll take all of them. And I'll take 10 arrows.
I'll take all of these, too. I guess I spent my money on something.
Scam likely. Whoa, it's just lying on the ground. Oh, this is cool. I like this weapon. All right,
so I got to just get my way into, is it Gerudo? Gerudo? How am I saying it? Can you spell it out
phonetically? Oops. Everyone's saying it at the same time. Gerudo. Gerudo. Gerudo. What was I
saying? Gerudo? All right, Gerudo. I got it. Gerudo. Thank you. I need to do that. Gerudo.
Oh, sorry. I want to buy? I only saw arrows there on the counter. Oh, wait,
bow aren't allowed in Gerudo town. What do you got? Oh, all right. What do I need here? Probably
fire and ice arrows. I have 27 ice arrows, but probably fire arrows, right? Buy everything.
There's 20 rupees for one. 20 rupees for one. 50 rupees for one. What? The guy outside sells
these for like fucking five bucks. Whatever. What's up here? Climbing to the roof. That's
what I'm doing. Why did I do this? There's nothing. Wait, what am I looking for? Stop backseating.
You just pissed somebody off. You just pissed somebody off. Somebody in the chat just was
getting annoyed. Well, I'm just going to go. What are people trying to spoil? Hey, yeah,
just get on the roof and wait there. Oh, tower. Yep. I'm getting this. Here's about the main
mission right now. And there's a shrine. Sick. Where is it? The arm. I don't want to pick this
stuff. It's not worth keeping. I don't need any of this shit. I don't need any of this crap.
What? Oh, you electrocuted me. I get it. Oh, my God. Stop. Don't touch. Die. What the hell?
That sucked. This will add to the resistance, right? No, it just resets it. Sorry. Whatever.
Please don't say hell. My dad will ground me. I don't want to fight. Leave me alone. Oh, I thought
that was a rock. All right. Seriously, you just did so much damage. OK, I got to get to the shrine
right now. Get away from me. I got to make some more food, too, eventually here. Come on. Where's
the dunk dunk? Dunk dunk? Dunk dunk? Dunk dunk? All right. Oh, good. Nice fucking amber there.
So there's going to be a new category this year, like there usually is in the end of the year
awards. And I don't know if it's even worth putting on, but, like, Polly and I were talking
about it. And it's worst fake overdoing Boston accent routine. And I'm like, I said, are people
even going to be able to find that? And I don't even know if anyone would even be able to find
anything like that. And that's as bad as that. I'll be honest, that might be my favorite category
ever of the last five straight years we've been doing it. That's like my favorite category.
That's like one of my that's my favorite thing. I love that so much. It would stay if I did it
enough. I don't think I did. I think I did it once this whole year. Or did I? I don't know.
I don't even know it can be a cat. Can it even be a category? You've done it like 12 times. I have
not. No, I haven't. We got over it. We got over it. I know we did. Oh, fucking starlight kid. Oh,
my God. I have done that more than a few times, haven't I? I forgot about that. Have I done that
a lot? Maybe I've done that a lot. Maybe as we sure that's not the only time I really kind of
leaned into that. Well, if it's on there, good luck finding it. Okay, so this is what is going
on here? Monster EDF. Monsters. Oh, my God, there's a giant monster. These monsters look
just like us. Insects. Where's the new EDF? Isn't that coming up? Is it already out?
It's already out in Japan, right? I feel like I can do something with that.
We're batchesting EDF. What do you guys even like? What do you guys like? You guys like anything?
You guys, what do you guys even like? Okay, so this is where this was. This is a restaurant candle.
It's not real. All right, so what does it want me to do? Just pick it up and bring it this way.
You're too far away. Oh, that's convenient. Wait, what else is here? Okay, so now we'll let,
can I turn this on? That's down there. I got it. I figured it out. Moonlight. Yeah, this thing is
worse. Moonlight. 25, that's good. Ooh, mentor. Like, guiding moonlight.
You are at my side all along. Monsters! Okay, so I can move these around.
All right, get that out of the way. There's a lot of shit going on in this shrine. Okay, what's this
for? Okay, does that stay on forever? There's a, there's a treasure chest over here. Definitely
gonna open that. Ancient core. So what's the point of being able to do this? Can I move one of these
places? Yeah, so vampire survivors, Elden Ring, and what's number three? What's number three?
You can't talk, never mind. See, the problem with every time I try to come up with a game of the year
list, I run into this issue every time. I am such an erratic weirdo when it comes to playing games
and when games come out and when games have released. For instance, I'm playing Breath of
the Wild right now. This game came out almost, what, five years ago. I have no sense of time when
anything has ever released because I'll play a game from like 2006 and then a game from like 2018
and then a game from like 2020 and then like 2022 and then like 2019 again. So I just don't even
know when anything's ever released. So I need to be reminded of like what I played this year
that actually released this year. And you guys can help me with that when you're allowed to speak
again. Might be a while. So I gotta bring a ball up here. Ball. Where's the ball? I hope nobody
heard that. Ball. Oh, you cheated. Thank you. I don't have any lightning arrows. Where's the ball?
Where's the ball? Where's the ball? Gift sub, please. Did I fuck the whole thing up? Did I
mess up everything? Because I don't think I can, I don't have the electricity ball or whatever cube.
Oh, there it is. I should take this with me. I'll take you down with me. What's that from?
That exact way that I said that. What's that from? From something. You fall down.
Oh, Resident Sleeper. It's a puzzle game. Hey, take that somewhere else. Take that somewhere else.
There we go. I got it. Oh, there it is. I thought it was a game crash. I'm gonna bring it with me.
I think that's the plan. It's definitely gonna be something weird where I have to take it with me.
There's gonna be some chest that I can get, right? There's nothing. I feel like this would be a
thing to do. I can't do this with them. There's a chest in here. Stay right there. Right? Yes,
there's a chest in here. Okay, so I gotta move. Hold on. Just walk off. All right,
let's just get over here. Far enough away where I can move this. So I didn't even need to, whatever.
Ooh. Get ready to nominate that one. Am I in trouble? I can make a comeback.
No, I don't want to. I want to go.
Shit. Where is it? Oh, no. It's just out of range. No. I freaked out because the big cube was behind
me and it was pushing me off the platform. I freaked out. Where am I? Where am I? What is
this place? What's going on? Where the hell am I? Okay, now this... How do I get back over there?
There it is. Hey, if you do not like this in the chat, you're dumb. That's what it means today.
If you do not like this today on Twitch, it means that you're dumb. Let's do this the correct way.
Yeah, it's opposite day, so if you do ResidentSleeper, it also means that you're
having a ton of fun and shit. All right. Do I have four? I think I might have three or four.
That was kind of a cool one. That was a fun one. That is number three. Okay, so I need one more.
Levels of Copium never seen before. What did you say? Not only did you make me lose a possible PB
and Minesweeper, but I trusted you. PB and Minesweeper? Like a speedrun? All right. This is
going to sound really weird, but I just realized that I was sitting kind of like on my left ball
for the last two hours and it hurts. It hurts a lot. I've been just sitting on it.
Had that ever happened to anybody? It's like my body hurts. I just realized it right now.
No, I don't want to do the hero thing. Okay, so I got to go. Where's the tower? I want to get it.
It's like over here somewhere. Oh, look at that. I don't care. There's a tower right here. I lost
all my points, dude. You suck. Well, you're gambling. What do you mean? I didn't tell you
to do that. Yeah, sorry. I don't know that people do like side bets on this stream of if I'm going
to like shit my pants or not. I don't know what you're doing over here. That's interesting.
That's very interesting. I know how to get that too. I got to jump from the top.
Where's the tower? Wasn't the tower right over here somewhere? I did see. Did I see it? Where?
Not that one. There's another one over here. Oh, there it is. I don't think I can do this though.
Hold on. I got to go around. I got to go this way.
He's freezing. I'm going to be fine. So I'm not going to be fine. I'm going to take a speed
potion right now. High level movement speed boost. We'll do mid level. Hurry up. Equip a fire weapon.
That works. Oh my goodness. It works. That's cool. That's really cool. I didn't even know that.
Okay. So that chest is I got to go up a little higher and float to it right here.
Something to get up there. What's in there? Okay. It's like, are there five arrows in this chest?
Is it worth me getting this? I don't think I can use the magnet on it. Can I? No, I can't.
Made it a wood or something. Get the tower first. That's the smart play and I'm going to
listen to that person because that's the actual smart thing to do. We're close enough to that.
Let's just get it. Mark it. I know where it is. It's right there. Like this thing here.
Go. Can you please do a link impression? I could. Yeah, sure. You have to go all in and I'm not.
I'm not sure. I'm not sure I'm ready to go all in right now. Does that make sense? Like it's like
Tasmanian Devil. You have to go all in to do it. I definitely can't climb that. So we have to go
all the way up. No, I would have swung, but anything to not use the weapon. I don't want
to use the weapon. It's nice. I would rather die than have my collectible fire sword get damaged.
Fuck. Okay. Look out below. Stop yelling things like that. It's like, no, it's like, no, it's
lame. Like don't do that. It's like an ironic joke. Like, oh, look out below you monster. Like,
I stopped doing it. I don't even think it's funny either.
That's an awful way to go. Suspicious. I forgot that emote was still here. What was the point of
that? Wait, they're not attacking. I thought they were going to, they were circling me. I thought
they were going to attack me. Shit. Do it. Oh, that's so annoying. By the way, I get figured out.
Hold on. Oh, I hate that. It's the worst. I'm trying to look at the light to sneeze. I had
to sneeze and I was trying to look right in the light and then usually it works. But the
light's not bright enough. Thank you for the Wikipedia article. Uh, and the reason why it
didn't work. This light's not on. That one is, it would have worked. I'm sitting in a,
that's why the camera looks so stupid today. I just like changed the tone of the room.
Nice gamer neck. Show us your pants. No, you don't, why would you need to see those? There's
no reason to see them. All that matters is streamer. This is, I'm streamer from here. That's it.
No. I think I saved it. I have to get high enough where I can glide back over there.
Where am I? Oh my God. I'm just, I'm going to, I'm going to be fine, right? I'm just going to
teleport to like the, yeah. Okay. Thank God. I'm sorry. What the hell? Why did he do that?
He just got sucked in there. I was trying to say Monka W, but my voice cracked while I said W.
So it sounds really, really bad. It was like Monka W. Oh, we're going to run off the edge.
Get down. Did he just run into the wall? This is weirdly placed.
Thank God. I got something for you. Where is it?
Where did the explosive go? Somebody tell me. Don't throw that. What is happening right now?
I'm so confused. Where are my weapons? You. Hi, Sarah. Not even a hard game.
I need some more shitty weapons. Roasted wild berry. Okay. I don't know what the
fuck was that? I did. I don't know. All right. So now I have to get all the way up here.
It's just tricky. The sword. Wait, where is it? You're being extra goofy today. I don't know.
Sometimes I just get in a mood. It just kind of happens. How'd you only get one? See ya.
Oh, I could have just done that. No, stop asking for sounds that are out of meme
circulation. They have been for a year and I get from here. No, it's that's that from that
that launch pad up there. Did you play Hades? I did. I liked it. I thought it was great.
I streamed it a few times. I imagine this is being weighed down to a bowling stream.
I actually don't hate that idea, but we have to go through all the sports. All right.
Oh, not all of them. Roasted hydra melon. Oh, that's 50. 20. Easy. Crickets. I'm not sure
what that's for, but whatever. I bet you can't toy boat. I did an unbelievable toy boat. This was
yesterday. Oh yeah, this was the day before yesterday. It was an unbelievable one. It was
probably the best one I've ever done. I genuinely believe that. That was the best toy boat that I've
ever done on this channel. There's no way it wasn't. Well, I need to bring that.
How many was it actually in a row? Because once you get to about six, seven, eight, nine,
10 in a row, it becomes actually like, whoa, you did it for real. Stop. You're 37. Relax.
Top 10 gamer rage moments. Jerma985 had a little bit of trouble with the magnetic box puzzle
next to Gerudo Village. I have to go all the way down here. Number 15. Yeah.
Top 15. Yeah. Moments. I was wanting to make a parody of those and have it just be something
so dumb and specific that nobody has done. We're going to go over the top 15. Let's go is on Twitch.
Like why? Who cares? We're going to go over the top five. Let's freaking go.
I want to do it so bad and have me be number one. Yeah. Oh, top 10. Ooh. Oh,
ooh. And there's 10 different streamers doing this. You know, get like a bunch of top streamers
just to like do it for a joke. Like, oh my God, I can't believe it happened. It's like a thing
people do. And of course I would still be number one. I would be the top three spots. Like I got
this meme locked down. This thing's kind of dumb. Why do I have a smoky eye today? The lighting is
wrong. You know, just make something up that no one has said. Make a new phrase that people
do in times of exclamation. Somebody said I had white walker makeup on. Here we go. It's time to
jump. I got to land this. I've got to get it. Even if people are going to scream, no, this is wrong.
I'm doing it. I've already done it. Very good. Let's freaking go. Let's go and make this fake
exclamation higher and rent out a whole huge place and have a fake land and have people playing
street fighter and have like a hundred people in the audience and somebody wins the tournament
or whatever it is. And they, they say the thing. And that's like number two. This is not real.
Yeah. Where's this accordion coming from? What does this open? Everybody in the audience,
it's just like on the count of three, like here we go. He's going to say it. Everybody
fucking scream. I have two commentators just talking. There's a person here,
really intense commentary and they all kind of say it too afterwards. It's like a big thing.
People do, you know, like sometimes I just really wish I had just like unlimited money.
I would just do this stuff like once a week. So what's going on up here? What did you get from
McDonald's earlier? Didn't go to McDonald's earlier. Now somebody else was saying they're
going to McDonald's. I hope to play the song for the hero someday. Wait a minute. Hey,
I think we're going to hear it about me. Let's hear it. Oh, here it goes. Prize. I wasn't looking
at all. I just haven't read the last word. Let's do it again. Cause I wasn't listening. I was
looking over at the chat. What was it? It said something about a prize. Oh, that's all right.
I got it right here. As light shines from the Northwest skies from the towers, shadow and
arrow flies. Here's heaven's light to reveal the prize. Solve the riddle of the ancient song.
Okay. A light shines from the Northwest skies. Where is North? Light shines from the Northwest
skies. That's the sun from the tower shadow and arrow flies. There's the shadow. Okay. From the
shadows ta whereas what is it? Here's heaven's light to reveal the prize from the shadows tower.
There emits a prize through the light of the beam. You'll get adjust your eyes. I don't get it.
As the sun shines from Northwest, the tower shadow and shoot an arrow at the shadow. Here's
heaven's light. Shoot an arrow. I'm just gonna do it. Whatever. Or is that fire? Is this like
you have to shoot the top and blight at the top of fire shadow of the tower when the sun is North.
I think I missed my opportunity. Yeah. I missed my opportunity. But do I have to wait? How do I do
this? How does it work? Is it that thing? I think it might be that thing. Come on. It's not. Oh,
oh, the shadow is gone. Can I sleep till morning? How do you pass time? How do I pass time? I'm
just said this part and Oliver sounds like the arcade game sound effects. What? Okay. So it's
I just fire, but fire. Well, where do I have to put the fire? What time is it? It's 10 PM.
It's got to be with the sun shining. I'm not stupid. I know one day I want to just hire
CG artists to put like an overlay over like an app, like a food blog. Just be like,
and have like a freak out. Why is it taking 10 minutes to travel? Not like this, not like this,
not like this. This guy sucks. Not like this. This guy sucks. I have to burn this. I have to
blight this on fire. I have to burn that. No, what's this tent you guys are talking about?
There's no tent. The shrine right there. Wait, what? Tent? You mean like hit like this, burn
that that tent hit instead of that. You want me to burn this? What do you want me to burn this?
I'm going to burn that. No, burn the tent, burn the tent, fire, tent, fire, tent.
What? Oh, that looks like a tent. No, what do you want me to burn? Bomb, tent, fire,
resident sleeper, tent, fire, resident sleeper, fire, sleep, sleep, fire, go to sleep and then
do a fire. How do you sleep? Sleep, Doritos, sleep at the fire, sleep at the fire. There's a fire
somewhere. I don't, there's no fire though. Where are you? Should I jump down from here?
Should I jump down right there? Should I jump down right here? Jump down here. That's a lot of nos.
Okay. Um, what's that? Is that it? Ow. Okay, fire. Did I miss my opportunity or something?
Tent, fire. What's the, where's there a tent? I missed my opportunity. So I have to sit. All
right. How do I, is there like a drink I can drink that speeds time up? Tent. What is a tent? I don't
have any tents. Okay. This would, Oh, I didn't know you could do that. Now I shoot this one.
I'm going to, I gotta be ready now. This is going to start glowing and then I shoot it with a fire
arrow. No. Huh? What do you mean? No. Just do I just stand in this? I don't understand what you mean.
Just stand in it. Okay. I, I, I 6,000 viewers left, almost 7,000. Okay. Here we go. Okay.
What's going on? Where is it? Here it comes. This is it. I am playing with fire right now for no
reason. Here it comes. Fire, sun, sun, sun, shoot the sun. Shoot the sun with a fire arrow or just
shoot the sun. Oh, it's not time yet. You guys didn't have anything to do today. Let's go up.
Is it a shrine? Oh, it's a shrine. My favorite thing. Cool. I wonder what's in here. This is
a secret. I like these little secrets. It was supposed to be a campfire. I thought you were
trying to tell me to shoot the tents, like the camps, like you need to burn that tent over there.
I don't know. So this is a test of a modest test of strength. All right. Well,
let's go ahead and get this ready. Damage food. Maybe. Yeah. Why not?
I got my really good guardian weapon that I've been saving for this exact moment
and I'm ready. I hate you already.
Oh, take him out. Take him out before he does anything. Take him out.
A lot of stuff there. That wasn't that bad. Guardian sword plus. It's a 60 damage.
Oh yeah. I get rid of this. Guardian spear. All this stuff. Nice. Okay. So this would give me
four and I can upgrade. What should I upgrade? Health or I'm going to do stamina, I think.
What do you guys think? Frost blade. Oh, that's really cool. That's so cool. And I don't know
sword. Oh, this spear is really not that great. Actually, what is the spear better than the sword?
Yeah, probably not. Health for the master sword. That's really cool looking. All right. Cool. So
I'll do health. Find a shrine. Does the master sword break? That's yeah. Does the master sword
break? That would be okay. It doesn't. Pepe laughed. All right. Well, I don't know. Kind
of not really, but yes. All right. Well, that helps. Don't worry. I'm just not going to use
it once and just throw it again at the end of the game. People think that's a joke, but I'm
actually going to do that and see if I can beat it. Collect all the legendary weapons and just
throw them all again. Okay. It is time for us. It's been about three hours. It's time to move
here to sponsored part of the stream. We're going to play multiverses for a couple hours or so.
I do want to get to, I do want to do that. Yeah. Let me just make sure I'm where I want to be
the next time. Yeah. Season two of multiverses is I think started today. Just a couple of new
characters that I haven't played with. I think they just announced, um, what did they just
announce? Hold on. When is frog detective going to happen? Frog detective is going to happen when
my, when I can do voices, one of three voices. So I'm going to take a quick BRB. We'll move to
multiverses. It's going to be sponsored by Warner Brothers. They've been really good to the channel.
I have not played multiverses in a little while. This ranked now. So I'll be trying that out.
Probably going to rage quit it in five minutes. They announced Marvin, right? Marvin Martian.
That's funny. Where's Daffy Duck? I want Daffy Duck. All right. I'll be right back. Uh,
going to get everything set up. Should be like maybe a few minutes. And thanks for watching
the, uh, this portion of the stream, breath of the wild. I'm still enjoying it. We'll see it again
soon. I'll be right back. I'm for multiverses. I am going to do a couple of things first before
I go there. Like for instance, this doesn't need to be on anymore and neither does this. That looks
good. Okay. I will be right back. See you guys in two, three minutes, maybe a little bit more.