I am back. Who's ready for Gotham Knights?
Did I scare you? I didn't mean to. Yeah, so I went to the bathroom, filled up my drink.
Very cool. Get the audio going. Make sure you can hear this.
All right, it's time to begin. This is a sponsored segment of today's stream.
Like yesterday. Fix the BRB music. Yeah, I know.
Okay, let me make sure you can see it. There we go.
All right, let's get this over here. Where am I? Where did I go?
There I am. Facing the wrong direction. Let's flip that.
Bang. And now you will be able to see the game. There.
All right. We played yesterday. We were playing as Nightwing.
We're going to play as a different character today.
Thank you to Warner Brothers for sponsoring this part of the stream.
The game is out right now. It's out now.
Gotham Knights is on PlayStation 5, Xbox Series S, Series X, and PC.
What was the last thing we did? All right, what character should I play as?
I want to play as a different character.
And I guess the question is, how do you change a character?
Play Red Hood? How do you change character?
Red Hood? All right, we'll do Red Hood today.
You have to ask.
There's definitely a way to do it, right? Did I not unlock that part yet?
Is it on the workbench? Do a poll?
Actually, you know what? All right. Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Let's do a poll. I want to play as a different character.
So do you want Robin, Red Hood, or Batgirl? Let's get a poll.
All right, let's open the Batcomputer.
So all right, yeah, this is the last thing we just did.
Harley Quinn called from Blackgate Penitentiary.
Oh, you have to go to the suits. All right, well, let's go take a look.
I'll give you a nice look at it so you can see what you're getting into here.
Suits are... Where are they? Here they are.
Okay, here you go.
We've been playing as Nightwing. We're going to play somebody else.
Robin. Robin has the big bow staff, and it's Robin.
Batgirl has... I think she throws stuff to get like...
Red Hood has guns, I think. What character are we doing?
Dude, Red Hood has guns. Yeah, whatever.
It's neck and neck. Batgirl and Red Hood. Robin is in last.
A lot of people are really kind of sleeping on Robin here.
I think Robin's probably going to be really good.
All right. Is it really that close? I can't see.
It's too close. Well, we're not doing it again.
Who's winning? 47%. That was close.
That was very close. Let me just tweet.
All right, we're doing Red Hood.
I threw? How?
Oh, all right. I probably should have done this.
Brute Strength Powerhouse Brawler Master Marksman 27 Power.
I should have done this.
Expert Hacker Tough as Nails Single Target Bruiser.
Well, we're doing it. Let's do Red Hood.
Oh, my. He's huge. He's massive.
All right. Let's start the patrol.
Oh, so yeah, I have a panel.
If you're interested, click the panel. Click the panel image.
You can buy it. Pre-order it.
Although the pre-order is over. I mean, it's out now.
It's literally out right now.
All right. I'm ready to begin.
Again, thank you Warner Brothers, sponsored.
Let's go. Time to protect Gotham City.
In case you want to use that anywhere.
Like you're absolutely more than welcome to.
You can if you want to use that clip.
Me, you know, get ready.
All right. I'm excited.
Actually, right when I started having fun
at Internet Problems last night, and that's not here right now.
So let's go. What is Red Hood's moves?
Wait, I should look at. Hold on.
I want to see the. What's he got?
Abilities. All right. Hold on.
I have two points to put in because from my understanding,
when you level up any character,
you level all of them up essentially at the same time.
I guess that's to prevent you playing through the whole game
and being like, you know what?
I want to play as Batgirl, but I'm literally at zero
and I can't do anything.
So we have marksman, brawler and vengeance.
We have two points.
Red Hood performs a perfectly timed evade
that generates momentum.
We have that also critical damage by 20 percent.
Red Hood can aim longer at a target to deal four times damage.
I think that's what I want.
Should we do guns?
Definitely. I mean, perfect evade.
You need it and then guns.
If you the longer you aim, you do more damage.
Done. What are the other ones?
When Red Hood throws an enemy,
he attaches a concussion mine to them that explodes.
That's pretty good.
That's three points.
Okay. I feel like I'm going to like this character.
Let's see. Is there like a little crime I can do just to learn his moveset?
There's got to be like a crime going on.
Yeah, over here.
Oh, shit. What happened?
No, get off the bike. What are you doing?
What happened? What happened here?
Do you need help? How do I help?
Was I too late?
How was I too late?
Did the criminals already get away?
I'm such a shitty superhero.
Get back on the bike.
All right. Here we are.
Quiet. All right.
I'm going to dismount. Let's go.
I'm getting like texts.
My phone is just blowing up right now.
Red Hood, where are you, man?
Red Hood, your location says that you're over by like the...
Where are you? You're going the wrong way, dude.
Why does it say you're inside of the museum?
Just make a bunch of shit up.
I actually don't know where the fuck I'm going.
There we go.
Okay, let's go.
What? Why am I shooting behind me?
How do I shoot?
All right, that's pretty cool.
Okay, this is awesome.
Man, is somebody just shooting at you?
What is this move?
Put this camera away.
I didn't even need to fucking look.
They're not even paying attention.
Yeah, I got a gun too.
Huh?
All right, I think I got the move set down.
I got points for that, right?
Paul Nightwing, he's crying.
No, we're Red Hood friends.
No.
All right, I get it.
I get the move set.
I want to level those guns up.
By the way, there's gear in the game too.
So he doesn't have any gear.
Right.
Okay.
Well, I guess I do have better stuff.
So these are better pistols.
We're going with the Beyond Suit.
I probably should have put the gear on before attacking anybody.
And what else?
Melee.
Cool.
All right, that's better.
All right, Harley Quinn.
I love how everybody can do a wheelie.
I thought I could grab something.
I bet Robin can't do a wheelie.
Oh, please.
We'll find out.
Is Harley Quinn just sitting?
No, isn't Harley Quinn in the...
All right, let's do it.
This is probably a boss of some kind, I imagine.
That's this suit does look awesome.
And you see somebody walking down the fucking street like this?
Do an E3 walk.
What?
Wait, I'm not supposed to...
Oh, I'm not supposed to be here?
I'm not supposed to be here.
I'm just a guy in a huge superhero costume.
Just walking in the front door.
Ah, yeah.
Yeah, we got a guy in a fucking superhero outfit.
Walking into the front door.
Looks like he's armed.
How do we proceed?
What would you even say?
All right, let's do it.
Cassane, find a way into the prison.
I guess I have to get in here.
Belfry, I got in.
Next stop, Harley Cell.
The X on her map corresponds to Cell Block 3 past Nexus processing.
The guards have withdrawn their patrols from that block.
All right, let's...
So there's no telling how bad things have gotten in there.
Are there guards in here?
Sure, he did.
I missed.
I'm getting another...
Red Hood, man!
What are you doing in there?
Wait, I shouldn't be...
We can't let Red Hood...
Am I gonna open this door with my bare hands?
Oh.
Wait, interrogate.
Interrogate, interrogate.
Did I?
I can't interrogate.
You've interrogated.
I love when he does the lip thing.
What do I do?
Yeah, Mike, I don't know why.
Whenever I play Gotham Knights...
I wonder why my webcam does this.
Well, this webcam stinks.
I don't think I want to do this.
Avoid taking damage.
Defeat all the invades and don't take any damage.
That's gonna be kind of hard.
All right, let me see if I can take some out before we get noticed.
And then let me play the stealth aspects of this game the way I'm supposed to.
Well, don't slam him on the ground.
Oh, shit.
Is there somebody just puke?
I think somebody just threw up.
Oh, no!
Whatever.
Did I shoot him in the face when I did that?
Holy shit.
Get out of here!
Fucking scoop slam.
You were trying to...
Pursue him into the fire.
I was trying to go for an environmental...
Wait, is this it?
What do you know?
I feel like I would do something like that.
Looks like you've been eaten well.
Still as big as an ox and twice as mean.
Been a while, you good?
So it is different.
Was it too much to ask you to visit earlier?
So each character has different dialogue with every encounter.
That's kind of cool.
What was it?
Hayden.
Are you real?
He asked me to profile some criminals.
On account of my being a brilliant psychiatrist.
Guess of all the criminals he knew...
You'd be the one to ask.
Hey!
I am not a criminal!
I'm misunderstood.
She's got a board up there too.
Look.
You know what I'm here for.
Hand it over.
He just grabbed the bars and he just rips the bars off the fucking wall
and he's got the whole thing in his hands and just throws it behind him.
But I'm missing my piece de resistance.
I need you to follow up on this here card.
It's hard to catch paper.
Holy shit.
That's the most impressive thing that we've seen a superhero do for the last two days.
You're not making this easy for me.
It should be done in records.
Bye.
Okay.
Exit cell.
Block three.
So we're gonna go get whatever this is?
They're the inmates from the corridor.
All right.
We got it.
That guy's gonna accidentally hit me in the head.
Can he hit me in the head accidentally?
He's gonna like he's gonna hit me with his backswing.
Oh god damn it.
I'm glitching out.
I'm phasing out of reality.
Okay.
Just get across.
All right.
I'm good.
The camera's fucked up.
There's an elevator in the nexus.
Maybe that goes down the basement.
What the heck's wrong with my camera?
Let's keep doing that.
Dude, you need more RAM.
Your VTuber model is...
Holy shit.
Okay.
Oh my god.
Momentum ability.
Enemy armored attacks can only be interrupted with piercing abilities such as barrage.
Gain momentum.
And then I got...
Okay.
I have a new move.
Holy shit, dude.
I shot you like 50 times.
Shoot behind you.
Why am I not...
I'm so stupid.
I'm trying to aim.
Geez.
All right.
Go.
I'm gonna get hit once.
Mm-hmm.
Oh.
Another one.
Oh my god.
You're gonna get me in two hits.
Don't kill me.
Oh my god.
Rocks.
Why would I have to defeat the guards?
Really?
No.
Why...
Defeat the guards?
I...
All right.
Fine.
Okay.
I'll defeat...
You actually got a hit on me.
Okay.
The guards don't even have weapons.
I know.
This is so unfair.
Come here.
Had a choke slam.
That was fucking sick.
Yeah, like those guys have bare fists.
I don't want anything to do with this.
I have no more healing, by the way.
This is bad.
Why would I even fight them?
I'm all right.
How do you get more heals?
Are they just consumables?
Ooh.
Chest.
Can you stealth take down the big enemies?
He fell down.
Turn around.
Unload.
I'm trying to get the perfect strikes.
It's hard to do with Red Hood.
Don't let him put the shield up.
Oh.
Low with the difficulty.
No.
It's got to stay at hard.
All right.
Records room.
Shoot them when they have the red flashing.
Too smart to just send me on an errand after an old file.
What do you want me to find out?
You're a hard gamer.
Yeah.
I play games on hard.
No, actually, I kind of don't.
There's something more in this catalog.
Oh.
Chest over there.
They're bullet spongy on hard.
It's got to get better weapons.
Find and examine marked items.
Okay.
Prisoner profile.
Cyrus Gold.
Convict, they say.
Crook, they say.
Murderer, they say.
But soon peace will be mine.
Died on Saturday.
Buried on Sunday.
Born on Monday.
They have no idea.
Oh, I thought that was like a poem.
Is it?
Harley, how did you get access to the PA system?
She's just on the PA?
Okay.
There we go.
Scan the card catalog.
Index locations of all documents stored in the records room.
Okay.
Look at the...
Up here.
Over there.
Can I open that?
Analyze.
Bingo.
Here's what Harley was looking for.
Here's your documents, Harley.
I think I found out all I can about this case.
I wonder what Harley will have to say about it.
I'm going to open the door.
Potentially this is tied to what Batman was after.
This is a boss.
This has to be a boss fight, right?
I'm going to be fighting Harley Quinn.
How does Harley want from this file?
Mine is a maze, but it's still amazing.
She must have a good reason.
She's going to open the door.
She's going to take it from me.
And she's going to go like...
I can't do a Harley Quinn impression,
but it's going to be something like...
Oh!
I can't do a Harley Quinn impression.
Good job, everyone.
You made things even worse.
It doesn't belong to you, dicks!
What are they even fighting?
All right.
Is this getting his head bashed in with a bat?
Look at how many times...
This is awful!
Oh my God!
Oh, shit!
That person's a psycho.
I'm coming.
Relax.
Where else do you need to be?
Do something?
What do you mean, do something?
I'm not supposed to protect every single citizen
as the title of the stream.
Never mind.
Why are they all fighting each other?
All right.
This guy is throwing lit toilet paper out the fucking window.
You guys are going to be real pissed off
once somebody in this prison has to take a shit.
Larry, did you have to throw 200 rolls of toilet paper?
You can just throw in one or two.
They're all doing it.
Please talk more.
I do these movements.
I do this like in the kitchen.
Is the pizza here?
What?
Go, go, go!
Chase the balloon, quick!
Where did it go?
Where's the balloon?
That guy has two shattered ankles.
Oh, shit!
It's mayhem!
Where's the music coming from?
What am I doing?
To beat the riot?
To shoot the balloon down?
I don't even know who I'm attacking.
I'm just fighting random people.
What the fuck was that?
Hey!
All right, I have to do that, though.
I have to do that.
I actually have to fight them.
I'm just going to stay back.
Who's throwing the lit toilet paper?
Because you're dead first.
It's you.
Get...
Okay.
Just kill this guy.
Hit him.
Somebody hit this guy.
This guy right here.
Stop.
Get him.
Grab him!
All right.
Let's just be...
Hey, buddy, buddy, buddy.
Listen to me.
You and I are going to pretend to be fighting
so people don't come and fucking fight us.
But we're going to get out of this alive together.
Just...
Oh, fuck!
Dude, I got somebody.
Just pretend to be fighting.
No one's going to fight both of us.
Watch out.
Watch out!
Oh, you piece of shit.
Over here.
Go over that way.
That way.
Over there.
Oh, shit.
I'm sorry.
What is the song?
No!
You killed...
I didn't even see...
All right.
I'm going in hard now.
I'm going in hard.
I'm killing everybody in here.
No more messing around.
I got hit directly.
All right.
I'm going for it this time.
It's Livin' Lovita Loca.
All right.
Take...
Ow!
All right.
Goodbye.
Oh, shit.
This is fucking crazy.
That guy's just taunting me.
Now, fuck you, man.
Get out of the server.
Let somebody else play.
There's three people trying to queue up to this place.
And you're...
Come on.
You thought you were going to hit me, didn't you?
I guess this guy's on fire.
I completely missed you.
Dude, are you seriously sitting there calling me a vigilante right now?
Don't...
I'm going to have to fight two huge people.
Nice teamwork.
You and me.
Uh-oh.
There's only two left.
Don't kill me, please.
Shit.
Oh, god damn it.
Oh, my god.
I got fucking whirlwinded.
Shit.
Oh, I'm actually fucking pissed.
I'm going to turn it down to medium.
I'm turning it down to medium.
I'm sorry.
I'm turning it to medium.
It's way too hard for me.
Just for this part.
My...
I don't have...
I didn't have any...
I didn't find any good...
I have to craft gear.
I was playing with Nightwing the whole game.
I don't have any...
I don't have any items for fucking Red Hood.
Unload.
Oh, hell yeah.
That was perfect.
Perfect.
All right.
We're fighting two different fights.
Just crossing into each other.
Why did that guy fall?
Don't you dare kill me on medium.
No!
You are so much more powerful than me.
It's not fair.
You...
Okay.
Well, per the rules of the superhero agreements,
you are now part of the Gotham Knights.
Congratulations.
Oh, my fucking God.
That was so fucking funny.
Dude, you suck.
I'm...
I'm doing fine.
I'm doing just fine.
All right.
Get...
Look at...
She's destroying people.
I'm just staying back.
You fucking idiot.
Why would you...
Get him.
Kill him, not me.
Why would you do that?
I'll be back later.
I'll be back...
Don't!
Dude, I feel like I'm...
I feel like this opening was like a Royal Rumble.
No, not on the rematch.
No!
Please die!
Thank God.
All right.
We go.
Ow.
All right.
Let's go.
Swing.
Swing at me.
Dumbass.
What's going on?
I had to reload.
I mean, don't have fun without me.
Watch out.
Big...
Big guy coming in.
Die!
Okay.
I did it.
Wait.
The room is...
The camera is glitching and showing like other parts of my room.
That's fucking hilarious.
What the fuck is going on with my camera?
It's like putting my chin down here like this.
Dude, we can see your...
No, you can't.
Okay.
We're good.
What is it?
Oh, it's...
Okay.
I see what it's doing.
That's fucking funny.
All right.
Let me go pee.
Let me pee first.
I'll be right back.
I haven't peed.
Okay.
That was fucking funny.
That was fun.
I'd be lying to you if I didn't think that was an incredibly enjoyable experience.
All right.
So what is going on with my webcam?
Like, honest to God.
Why is it freaking out?
It doesn't make any sense.
Help us.
Yeah, it seems to only happen with...
I don't know what...
It's something to do with how it's pulling in through OBS.
I don't know.
Should I plug it back in?
Was this happening yesterday?
I don't remember this happening yesterday.
I remember it was glitching yesterday, but it was like teleporting around the room.
I bet you can't even remember what you were eating yesterday.
I do.
I remember.
What the hell am I supposed to do with this, Harley?
Crime weapon.
The camera's having an out-of-body experience.
Well, I'm sorry that's happening.
It really shouldn't be.
But I'm going to turn it back on.
We still freaking out?
All right.
That was fun.
Let's keep moving.
Fix your hair.
I just did.
All right.
So I get my...
I get my shit back.
Change it back to hard?
No.
All right.
I'm just going to teleport back.
That was a wild mission.
I'm going to...
Yeah, I'll keep it on medium.
This is the AI reconstruction of your room.
Why is there like another person?
There's another person here.
Hold on.
I want to see what this looks like.
Let's see.
So this is an AI of the room?
AI recreated the room.
Why is it...
What's the opacity for?
Oh, right.
This looks like you took this picture in a submarine.
Like this is my submarine streamer room.
Yeah, why is there another person over here?
What is that?
I don't know.
All right.
Well, interesting.
I think maybe it thinks that's a mirror.
I imagine that's probably what it thinks.
It's evil.
I don't know.
I have no idea, man.
I think my OBS is crashing.
What happened to my thing?
Oh, there it is.
I mean, I could just like unplug the webcam
and go without cam for a little while.
If it's that annoying.
Whatever.
One crime stopped today.
Not zero.
At least one.
We updated the board.
All right.
Talk to Alfred.
Thinking about what happened at Blackgate, Master Jason?
I can't believe Harley got away.
She played us.
And I'm sure she's got more shit planned.
She hasn't left any other messages or maps.
Do you have any leads on where she might have gone?
Not really.
But the freaks are usually your partners in crime.
A good place to stop, then.
OK, unloading clues.
Open the book and examine the evidence.
Is it up here?
There it is.
Let's take a look.
Harley's profiled some seriously anti-social prisoners here.
Look, something's going on at Blackgate.
We lean on that warden.
We're set.
These records go back centuries, man.
The warden's new.
I doubt she's involved.
How did I miss this?
All right.
Harley's stupid system makes no sense.
Hey, Babs, what did you figure out?
They all got out on appeal.
That's what Harley was tracking.
In every case, key witnesses were murdered.
Look, they were all pinned up with knives, just like Langstrom.
Bruce is onto something.
Oh?
I think I've got something.
Oswald Coppelpot, the Penguin.
He's like everyone else in here.
Except he served his sentence every single time he was arrested.
Someone must have hung him out to dry.
Might be he's willing to talk.
He runs the Iceberg Lounge now.
Claims he went legit.
He definitely runs more than liquor through that bar.
I wouldn't know.
That man would never take me.
If you wanted a fake ID, Tim, all you had to do was ask.
Oswald's dangerous.
And we can't forget, Harley's still out there.
Careful.
Relax, dick.
We got this.
So we're going after the Penguin?
All right.
Reach the Iceberg Lounge.
We got it.
Let me see what we got.
Should I do some more of just like crime fighting?
I feel like I should.
Secret identity compromised.
Protecting Batman's secret identity is vital to protecting Bruce Wayne's legacy.
Reach a specified location and plant fake information, giving Bruce Wayne an alibi.
If you're caught, you won't be able to plant the fake info again.
Until the next night.
Really?
Okay.
I'm getting overexposed here too.
Go like this.
I need to at least do like one or two.
I have to do at least a couple.
Like crime stopping things.
Drop the gamma on this.
It's a little too overexposed.
That's better.
Okay, reach Iceberg Lounge.
What else is there?
Only one of Gotham's rich and powerful has served actual prison time.
Oswald Cobblepot, aka the Penguin.
Aim of visit.
I think I have a point to put in.
I do.
Crit damage 20%.
What's the second thing on the third tier here?
Every round Red Hood shoots has a small chance to deal five times the damage.
Only applies to ranged attacks and precision aim.
Okay.
I need...
I'm not gonna do anything.
I need two points.
Again, this is a sponsored segment of the stream.
This is sponsored by Wanda Brothers.
Gotham Knights is currently available right now on Xbox Series S,
Xbox Series X, PlayStation 5, and PC, which I'm playing on right now with a 3090.
It's an open world game.
You can play as four different characters in the Batman universe.
Currently playing as Red Hood.
There is full co-op.
Pretty cool.
Make the webcam bigger.
I don't know.
It's too small.
Better take a different way in like Batman would.
Go up in the roof.
Let me take a look.
Hold on.
Let me see what it looks like.
Okay, cool.
Let's go beat up the penguin.
Let's punch him in the face a million times.
Wait, co-op is actually kind of nice.
There's like three co-op games.
Yeah, that'd be the whole...
I think the whole purpose of the game is to do...
To have just to jump in with a friend and just run around and solve crimes and stuff.
Yeah, it's all co-op.
All right.
Talk to the penguin.
The tax manual.
Yeah.
Like this guy pays taxes.
The coin with his name on it.
This guy is something else.
Is he just in here?
Is this like the penguin's club?
Something's definitely shut up.
What?
Was that quiet?
All right.
That was silent apparently.
You were at where club...
All right.
I just got one more guard.
Go down.
Whoops!
I pressed the wrong button.
No, no, no, no, no.
Don't follow me.
You psycho!
All right.
Just get...
I can do that too, you know.
I need to do a silent takedown.
I got to drop aggro.
I want to get the bonus.
No, who cares?
I'm going to just get you.
How did you do that?
Ooh.
That's a broken face.
All right.
Where's the penguin's office?
Can I grapple anything?
Yeah.
It's locked.
Really?
That door's sandalwood.
Custom job.
Fixing it's going to be a pain in the ass.
Yeah.
Just answer my questions and I won't break anything else.
Smile.
Viral video of you assaulting Reformed Citizen is the last thing you need right now.
Reformed?
Guess all that time in Blackgate did the trick.
Funny how you weren't able to weasel out of it like so many of your pals.
That is actually cool that everybody has their own dialogue
because they have to record four different sessions.
Someone's done their homework.
That's cool.
I want to know who's handing out get out of jail cards.
If you really want to go down this rabbit hole,
you need to know there's no coming back from it.
Never stop me before.
Penguin, which Gotham bad guy do you think you are?
I'm going to spell this out for you.
Well, I think I'm the Joker.
With the bad guy.
Say it.
You're not worth it.
Get lost.
Because I'm the Riddler.
That's who I think I am.
Well, I can't just like grab him and like smash, smash, smash his head against the desk.
Oh, chess.
Oh, wait, maybe he does think he's the Riddler.
Guns.
Wait, what is this painting?
Okay.
Well, that's cool that we get to actually meet Penguin there.
I don't get to punch him in the face.
Is Penguin that old?
I mean, I think Bruce Wayne looked a little older in this.
He looked like he was like older.
So I think this is takes place kind of maybe a little bit later.
He uh, well, all right, turn to the bell.
Belfry.
Penguin was a dead end.
Whatever he knows, he's not telling.
I had to come back to the Belfry and we'll regroup.
Sounds good.
Thanks.
No, no, I'm not doing that.
I'm going to stop some crimes.
I'm not going to be zero crime prevented Andy.
We're stopping some crimes.
Otherwise, am I even a superhero at this point?
Like I need to protect the like the community and stuff.
So I'm going to let's go.
This one's right here.
There's some people stealing shit over here.
Okay, let's do it.
What's up?
Look at this.
What's this huge guy?
He's got like a jet pack on.
What the fuck?
Holy okay.
Electricity guy.
No, I didn't get it off.
Shit.
Ow.
All right.
Crime stopped.
I did it.
I prevented the crime.
Let me do one more.
There is a big one going on over there.
I need one behind me.
There's a chest over there.
I need to do at least two.
Should I get the chest?
I want that chest.
I'm getting it.
Check your gear upgrades.
Holy shit.
44 defense.
This thing's pretty sick.
I wonder how many outfits there are for each character.
So that's this is I'm just gonna run up by a car.
You don't know if they don't recognize me
because I'm in a different costume.
It's me the red hood.
I'm trying a different look.
I'm trying a new outfit
and I think it looks pretty good.
It's equally scary but equally I've got authority
and I have you know you don't want to take a picture
for your Instagram or anything.
You would have taken a picture with the fucking Batman.
Wouldn't you?
All right, here we go straight ahead.
Crime in progress.
I'm on it.
Stop.
Look what we have.
It's me.
I've reloaded and shot him.
I actually like this outfit.
All right.
Crime.
Crime stopped.
That counts, right?
Oh, there's another one right here.
Right down the street.
How did I just get in here?
Where am I?
I'm like in the sewers.
How did I get in here?
There's a loot box down here.
Yeah, there is.
I'll get it.
Is this a loot box?
What is this?
That was not a loot box.
Criminal activity.
I didn't do anything.
I didn't prevent any crimes.
I think they have to be the big ones.
All right, let's keep, we'll keep, we'll keep it rolling.
Let's keep it rolling.
All the AI images.
Yeah, they're looking fucking weird.
You didn't prevent anything.
You were just killing people.
All right, what do you got, Al?
Penguin kept his mouth shut.
Batman made this stuff look easy.
You may be surprised to learn Batman struggled with similar challenges early in his career.
So for a time, he focused his energies elsewhere in the city.
When word of his work got out, people were more inclined.
To cooperate.
The city.
We've been so wrapped up in Batman's last case, we ignored the rest of Gotham.
Gotham may not know Batman is gone.
I always feel like Red Hood is about to punch whoever he's talking to.
There has been a marked increase in gang-related crime.
Plus whatever shit Penguin's up to these days, maybe if we mess with him.
And if we look at crooks, they'll feel like talking.
You've also received messages from Lucius Fox and Detective Montoya.
They may be able to help.
Thanks, Alfred.
Guess it's time to take a page out of Batman's book.
I promise it's an excellent read.
Okay.
New email.
Oh my god, I'm not...
I mean, I haven't read any of these.
Batman sent me a fucking email?
What?
I got an email from Batman.
If you received this message, then people have started linking the words Bruce,
Wayne, and Batman online.
Which means my idea...
You think he knows that people are searching?
As you might understand, the Google Trends search is looking like Bruce,
Wayne, and Batman together.
I'm seeing a lot more of those in October of 2022.
Okay, so sorry I missed the email, Batman.
Our PR problem?
We have a reputation problem.
What with citizens of Gotham running at the very side of us and the GCPD hating our guts?
Mr. Dorius, my history teacher, used to say,
people fear what they don't understand.
I think I've come up with the perfect solution to our PR problem.
We start a podcast.
No.
Now, now, let's not be so quick to judge.
What exactly are you proposing, Tim?
I haven't gotten quite that far yet.
Maybe it's the four of us debunking myths about what we do
or debriefing our latest case.
We could answer listener questions.
We call it Podcast Nights or Bat Chat.
We can workshop the name, but I think it's a good idea.
We even already have fun interpersonal dynamics and banter,
which is the perfect for audio.
No.
See, we're already doing it.
Whenever you're being a party pooper, I'll just be like classic Red Hood.
If people will love it, we could do t-shirts.
I'm playing as Robin.
I'm going to play as Robin.
Realize I forgot to send flowers.
We're in the neighborhood.
Let's meet in my building.
I'd like to give you them impression.
Lucius Fox wants to give us flowers.
Does he know couriers exist?
Knowing Lucius, I suspect he has something far more useful for us.
Okay.
Head straight to the roof.
Check the evidence board.
Nightwing is fun.
Red Hood is fun, too.
Watch.
I'm going to play as Robin.
It's going to be my favorite character.
Okay.
I got some new stuff here.
Penguin's criminal deal.
Penguin's organ trafficking.
Lucius Fox.
Detective Montoya.
Okay.
There's a lot of stuff to do.
Harley returns.
Freaks have been teaming up with some unexpected allies.
Investigate their crimes to find out what's going on.
We got to do some interrogations.
Okay.
Time to patrol Gotham City.
I want...
What do I want to track?
What do you want?
What do I want to do?
Let's do...
What do you want to do?
Who should I go for?
Harley Quinn or...
Penguin.
Because there's...
Harley?
Penguin?
I'm seeing a lot of people say...
Let me just see who has a cooler potential plan here.
Yeah.
So let me see.
Stop a criminal deal to interfere with the Penguin's activities in Gotham City.
So that's like...
That's a Penguin marker.
Tracking an activity.
Stop an organ trafficking operation to interfere with the Penguin's activities.
All right.
Let's go do this.
Let's go stop some organ trafficking.
What's this?
I'm eating like a can of soup out of the can?
What?
I was just thinking of that time we all made dinner together,
and Tim got tomato sauce all over a bruised bass.
I don't remember that.
What?
You just eat it.
No, you have to.
It was the same year...
You know what?
Never mind.
Dumb story anyway.
Well, I could tell you a story.
It's about being dead,
then brought back to life by a pit of mind-altering goo.
Hey, I didn't mean...
I don't know what's worse.
Having a chunk of my life taken away from me
or coming back to everyone thinking I'm gonna snap.
I'm sorry, Jason.
We shouldn't have.
I shouldn't have treated you like an outsider.
My god, you're such a boy scout.
No wonder you were the first.
Dude, you gotta clean and peel that thing.
You gotta clean and peel that carrot.
Let's go.
Didn't peel the carrot.
All right, it's time...
Stop some crime.
What do I want to do?
This, right?
Okay.
Stop Penguin's criminal deal and to get his attention.
I'm doing this.
Let's get the Peng...
Let's mess with the Penguin.
Robin?
I'll switch to Robin in like 10 minutes.
That's me.
I don't even want to go this way.
Do I want to go this way?
Oh, because I have to go across the bridge.
Right, right, right, right.
Hey!
Oh, okay.
Got him.
Crime prevented.
You're welcome.
Stop murdering people.
What am I supposed to do?
Just run?
Yeah, that's what I'm saying.
There we go.
One more.
All right, defeat all enemies,
retrieve the mod chips,
and do grab strikes.
10 enemies.
Wait, there's stuff over here.
Nice.
That's my favorite move.
What's up?
All right, I gotta interrogate somebody.
Nice try.
Don't kill the level five.
Oh my god, Jeremy.
Shit.
I think there's still a high level over here too.
Or...
I wanted to grab him.
Who's left?
Oh, you're here.
What do you know about the penguin?
Whatever.
All right, there's another one.
Penguin's organ trafficking.
All right, we're gonna do this one now.
It's pretty close.
Have a nice night.
I spawned right in front of that guy.
One guy.
God damn it.
All right.
Make sure I interrogate somebody.
It's really important.
They put that wall there just so you would run into it.
Should I just go...
What if I went the speed limit?
Let's go.
All right.
I have to interrogate someone.
Level five, right here.
Here it comes.
No interrogate?
What do you know?
Where's the container?
Oh, that's a plaque.
I have one minute?
Get away from me.
Get out of the way.
Where's the...
Where are the organs?
Where are they?
What?
Drop site, drop site, drop site.
Where is it?
I gotta go right now.
I got him.
I've got organs.
Do I give it to you?
All right, we're good.
Thanks for the delivery.
I've got a medical team lined up who can use it.
Glad I got here in time, man.
Nice.
All right.
So I'm messing with penguins still.
And is he pissed now?
Wait.
Why do they have a pig mask?
True.
Interrogate.
Nope.
They have spray paint?
All right.
I'm just gonna throw you all in the ocean.
Come here.
Yep.
Just go into the water already.
It hurt.
There's not water.
Oh.
I'm kind of afraid to jump in there.
All right.
So now we've got citizen chaos.
There's also...
Oh, Lucius box.
Fast travel, I think.
That's a fast travel unlock.
See what Detective Montoya wants.
Robbery in progress.
Probably this, right?
Oh, yeah.
I'll switch to Robin.
Yeah, let's do that.
Let's check out...
I want to be able to play all the characters.
I want to do all the characters.
So you can vote.
See, two crimes stopped.
I'm good.
18 enemies defeated.
Two silent taketowns.
Yeah.
All right.
Get a poll in here.
Batgirl or Robin for the last portion of the sponsor segment.
Which, by the way, WB, thanks again for the sponsorship.
Game's available right now.
I got a link in the panel below.
Who do you want to save for the next 30 minutes or so?
I have to pee again.
I keep needing to pee.
Well, I'm drinking a lot of water.
All right.
I'll be back when the poll's done.
One more pee.
All right.
How are we doing?
Batgirl.
All right.
I'll play Robin tomorrow.
I'll play a combination of them both.
That's fair.
All right.
Let's do Batgirl.
There are four characters.
Robin's the only one we are not going to see tonight,
but you'll see Batgirl and Robin tomorrow.
You promised us Robin.
WB, you got to save the best for last.
You saved the best for last.
Play as Alfred.
I don't think you can play as Alfred.
All right.
Batgirl.
Expert hacker.
Let's do it.
Oh, I was like, wait, where's my costume?
OK.
So anything update so far?
Look at the board.
OK.
So let's go talk to...
All right.
So we did those two.
We got to talk to Lucius Fox and Detective Montoya.
So let's go talk to them both.
I do want to see what Batgirl's moves are.
I know.
I think my teeth are falling out.
Oh, Jesus.
All right.
Batgirl.
What do you got for moves?
Whoa.
What is that?
She's got like a baton nunchuck?
That's her ranged.
Yeah, she throws.
She throws shit.
She has the batarang, right?
Cool.
What about gear?
Different suits.
Cool.
I like this one.
OK.
Cool.
Well, it's definitely going to be this one.
Tonfa.
Cool.
All right.
So let's do the...
Let's go this way.
Gotham Knights.
Available right now on PC.
PlayStation 5.
Xbox Series X, Series S.
It's there.
It came out today.
Why are you so narrow?
I'll fix my webcam when we play the scary game, OK?
Open world.
Here's the whole map.
Co-op.
The whole game.
I'm closest to...
I'm close to...
Detective Montoya will mark that.
Let's check out...
Oh, I need to do points.
Justice, grit, or oracle.
Using AR mode, Batgirl can disable certain devices like cameras,
turrets, and mines.
That's pretty amazing.
Increases Batgirl's base house by 40%.
That seems amazing.
Or Perfect Evade.
I feel like I want that.
I always start with Perfect Evade.
Critical damage.
Defense.
What is down this tree?
Overcharge an enemy's gun or device instantly applying a bioelectric...
A bioelectric elemental effect.
Most enemy attacks can't interrupt Batgirl's heavy melee attack.
That's pretty good.
Batgirl can revive herself once after her health is depleted.
OK, we're doing this tree.
No interruptions or...
This one's like defense, right?
Batgirl receives a 75% defense bonus when hit by an enemy counterattack.
We'll go with this one.
I can get them both.
Yeah.
Self-revive will be good.
OK.
All right.
Let's go.
I like the cape.
Cape.
C-A-P-E.
The cape.
It's scary every time.
All right.
Here we are.
Hi.
What do you got?
Some kind of mission?
Don't you sneak up on me like that.
I actually kind of did.
Not the bat I was expecting to see, but if he trusts you, so will I.
Likewise.
I assume you've got something in mind.
Fill me in.
Well, since we lost Gordon, some cops are back to playing dirty again.
Kane doesn't like it, but she's not doing much to stop it either.
So I've heard.
She's not half the commissioner he was.
I know Batman was helping Gordon clean up the force,
but now any cops who used to be on Gordon's team are getting their asses handed to them.
The gangs are ambushing them because they won't take bribes,
and dispatchers are giving them the worst assignments because they make trouble for everyone else.
Hoping the gangs will do their dirty work for them.
That's horrible.
Well, look, I hate to ask, but can you keep an eye on cops when they're facing off against the gangs?
I know a lot of my fellow officers have issues with vigilantes, but they need the help.
Watch out.
Helping is what I do.
And those who actually care about Gotham will hopefully see that we're on the same side.
Thanks.
I'll try to get you some resources to help you protect everyone in Gotham.
Not just us.
Sounds good to me.
Let's go.
Okay.
Side activity complete.
Contacts offer tasks to help clean up and protect Gotham City.
Help various contacts during patrols to earn distinct rewards.
Okay.
Hey, you saved someone's life out there.
So now we gotta go talk to the box.
Oh, is that a bat memory or something?
Oh, I gotta, my webcam's gotta go off for this.
These are cutscenes.
The game's multiplayer?
It is multiplayer.
The whole thing.
The whole thing's co-op.
What's a gal like you doing in a place like this?
Same as you.
Wait, did we?
You're visiting an old friend.
We do?
I keep waiting for him to step down and, I don't know, give some inspiring speech.
Tell us to get back to work.
Maybe he didn't think I was sticking around.
You would have hated this.
They put you on an actual damn pedestal.
Maybe he'd understand.
He always said people needed symbols.
Something to believe in.
Yeah, but we both know he met you bats.
Not him, except with the squared up jawline and better glasses.
They changed his face?
Yeah, it's hard to tell from here, but it looks nothing like him.
Wish we had him back.
Yeah, me too.
See you later, Jim, bat girl.
He looks just like I remember.
So that, yeah, so that's a, there are the, yeah, there's like little things around the
city you can think, activate cutscenes and stuff.
Let me link this.
There we go.
Okay, so I need to go to Lucius, who is down here.
He's pretty far away, isn't he?
Kind of.
Am I lazy and teleport back here and then go or, no, we got a crime right here.
I'm gonna do this one.
I also want to learn some moveset stuff with bat girl.
Yeah, we'll open up tomorrow with bat girl.
Well, the game, I mean.
We'll stream something else for the first couple of hours.
What is, what is happening here?
Investigate the crime scene.
Oh, wait, this person is dead on ground.
What happened?
Okay, let's investigate.
Oh my goodness.
Find five clues to learn what happened.
Got shot in the chest.
Okay, holding a ring.
Power worker's union ring must belong to the victim.
The motive of this crime was likely not monetary.
Notebook says data and notes on power boxes.
Ammo type is too common to trace.
Positive ID on the victim of Gotham.
City worker reported missing in recent weeks.
The regulators likely tried to glean information from him about the city power grid.
Which clue points to the current location of the suspects?
Wait, what?
It's, we're gonna go to the power grid, right?
Discover what happened and where the suspects are hiding.
Which clue points to the current location?
Oh, okay, okay.
I get it.
I have to select the clue.
So it's the power box shit.
And that's it, right?
Solve it.
Wait, it's not?
Gunpowder residue.
Wouldn't this say is where the location, where they are?
The ring?
Oh, right.
No, not correct.
Gunpowder?
Oh, all right.
Crime resolved.
Oh, I was gonna say that we didn't find them.
Okay, so now where are you?
Over here.
Is that illegal hacking?
Criminal in hiding.
All right, we'll do this and then we'll go wrap around to Lucius.
Is the camera still fucking up?
Is my camera still freaking out all the time or is it not bad right now?
Not really.
Yeah, I can see your bald spot.
Oh, that's all right.
I'm gonna try to see why that's happening.
I'll do some troubleshooting tonight.
So tomorrow it doesn't happen.
All right, let's go track this person down.
I don't have a bald spot.
Look, I'll go like this, look.
All right, so who's the killer?
Okay, reach the hideout.
Oh my God, there you are.
All right, you're on.
No, oh.
Beat two enemies at the same time.
Defeat with momentum abilities.
What's with their voices?
Oh, holy shit.
All right, that girl's pretty cool.
Nice.
They're not getting up anytime soon.
I did it.
All right, now Lucius.
There you are.
Made some pretty good progress, I think.
Where's my car?
I like you can just summon the car.
It just appears.
It's just ready.
How many beers do you drink in an hour?
I don't know.
We have one, who cares?
All right, cut scene.
No place like it, is there, Mr. Fox?
You're trying to give me another heart attack?
Batman taught you everything, huh?
Just the important things.
Sneaking up on your allies, for one.
But not how he managed to be in five places at once.
I feel like if I look away, everything turns to chaos.
You got a computer up here?
Bad doesn't fall far from the belt from what I've seen.
Um, thank you.
Don't thank me yet.
This is not a secure place to be doing work up here.
Like, this is kind of secret work.
Your mentor and I always knew that something like this could happen.
When I left Wayne Tech, we kept some research going.
There are a lot of eyes on you now.
No one's looking at Fox Tech.
Brain's gonna ruin that computer.
As long as I got a break between the guilds,
you'll still have everything you need to carry on Batman's legacy.
Speaking of which.
Whoa.
These flowers are gorgeous.
It's Luke's design.
A custom bird to help you get around a little quicker.
Hefty enough to support exactly one hero.
With this, the sky really is the limit.
Now you can thank me.
Thank you so much, Mr. Fox.
Do I actually get to fly this?
Belfry, if this isn't enough to convince Penguin, nothing left.
Be careful.
Penguin's going to have an angle here.
Okay.
Reach...
All right, we're going back to the launch.
I'm dying to try this baby out.
How do I start?
You're getting ahead of yourself.
Before you can use the bird, you'll have to clear a path for it.
Clear a path?
Whatever I need to do.
Lately, the GCPD is not content to have jackboots on the ground.
Somebody's shooting a machine gun.
They launched a network of surveillance drones to patrol the skies.
If they're looking for you when you try to get airborne.
They won't hesitate to take me down.
What do you recommend?
A creative programmer could convince those drones to overlook certain targets.
But for that to work, close-up scans would be required.
For once, I'm not the one who has to handle the programming.
I'll get you those scans, Mr. Fox.
Get to solve crimes?
The cops have the city divided into sectors.
The set of drones watching over each one.
Until you scan all the drones in a sector, consider it a no-fly zone.
No flying until the surveillance drones are taken care of?
No problem.
I'll send you the location of the first one so you can get to work.
Okay, so we could also...
Let's do the...
I'll do that later.
Let's go do this.
Yeah, let's go take on Penguin.
I'm ready.
Only two crimes?
Well, I'm...
You'd better not be hurt this time.
I'm working on it.
Are you going to do a face reveal?
It's very, very soon.
Very soon.
In like five minutes.
Face reveal in five minutes.
Wait, what?
Uh, I've got to stop Penguin.
Dude, I'll be here.
Yep.
For the first time ever, you're going to see my face.
All right.
I wonder if you actually fight the Penguin.
I'm so curious about this.
Talk to the Penguin.
I'm here.
Defeat the Penguin's guards.
Avoid taking damage.
All right, well, I couldn't say anything about stealth.
This game really makes you feel like Batgirl.
Don't think so.
Shit, I got hurt.
Okay, nice.
She's kicking the shit out of us.
Oh my...
You can't fit in here.
All right, that was pretty cool.
All right, Batgirl is part of the...
Batgirl is the coolest character in the game.
No, please.
Cool, cool, cool.
Nice.
Penguin!
Nowhere to go anywhere.
Nowhere to hide, Penguin.
Open up.
I'm going to have a rocket launcher pointing at what they're doing.
So you can use the door after...
So where were we?
Listening.
You may have questions, but I can think of a few reasons not to answer them.
They could have probably just heard that with music.
Am I supposed to be acting?
Oh, okay.
There's one in the chess set.
Well, I'm an expert hacker, so I got this.
Where are the bugs?
All right, so I'm going to pick up one of these bugs.
Things that's bugged.
I'm going to turn it.
I'm going to aim my mouth right where the bug is as close as I can.
And I'm going to go...
Where are they?
Where are the bugs?
I need to just smash them.
Under the desk or something?
Okay.
How do I...
Can I punch?
The face reveal?
Dude, don't rush it.
Oh, okay.
How do I destroy them then?
Plant.
Yeah, she's an expert hacker.
Two and one more.
I feel like I could probably do this.
The singing.
It's...
I'm kind of afraid that it will be...
It's either going to be, wow, holy shit, I can't believe you can actually do that.
Or that was like the cringiest thing I've ever heard in my entire life.
And I'm not sure which one.
I'm kind of afraid to do it.
Bring over that bottle of whiskey.
You want to try?
This is like really fucking dumb.
I'll try after.
Here's what I don't get.
How come you had to serve your sentence while the rest of your rich friends got a free pass?
They were favored.
I wasn't.
Who'd you piss off?
No one talks about them.
A lot of whiskey.
Not a whispered word is said.
The court of owls isn't real.
This is how you get off your chair.
Yes, it is.
The powers club.
Yup.
Where the super rich go for shits and giggles.
Might be worth a peek.
Personally, I stay far away from that raptor's nest.
But it's fine if I head in there.
I lost years of my life to Blackgate.
You go do what you do best.
Just don't tell them I sent you.
Is he a good guy?
Is he a bad guy?
All right, I'll try.
A little practice.
I probably hurt somebody.
I'm sorry.
Do you think he's up to something?
I wouldn't be surprised.
But he seems pretty convinced that the court of owls exists.
Okay, I'll do a deep dive on the court while you're out.
Sounds good.
Awful.
Very cool.
All right, let's put some points in.
Let's go back to the bat cave, whatever it is.
I'll do my face reveal.
And then we're going to move on to another game.
We're going to play Deadly Night.
Okay.
Check on Alfred.
What's that sound?
Probably a mother hen?
What the hell?
All right.
That is going to be it for today for this game.
We're going to move on to Deadly Night.
That was Gotham Knights again.
The game is out now.
It is available.
You can get it right now on PS5, Xbox Series X, Series S, PC.
There's a link in the panel image.
And also we'll be playing it tomorrow.
Thank you, Warner Brothers again for the sponsor.
I know this has been like an Omega sponsor.
But WB has been really awesome to work with.
And it's been a great supporter of the channel.
So I'm having fun with it.
Like I said yesterday, I would be lying to you if I told you that
I was not enjoying my experience.
Open world games are just kind of fun to mess around in.
And here comes the face reveal.
Okay, here we go.
Was it all right?
All right, give me two minutes.
I'll be right back.
We're going to switch to Deadly Night.
It's a scary game.
It's late at night now.
It's going to be terrifying.
And I'm going to play it.
It is not a controller game.
So give me like two, three minutes to get this ready.
I'll be right back.
And again, there'll be more Gotham Knights tomorrow.
See you soon.
See you in two minutes.