Okay, um, so I gotta tell you, I'll be back in five more minutes.
There is delicious food, and I need to eat it. I'll be right back.
I'm just gonna go eat something. I'll be back. Just give me like five minutes. Not even.
I'll be back in exactly four... eight... four... I'll be back at 420! Yeah! Perfect.
All right, be right back. I'll be back. Oh man, that was good.
Oh, so good. Late. Yeah. When you get into that mode where you're just eating... I was looking
at the clock. It's like, it's been four hours and 20 minutes on the stream, but this next bite of
delicious fried rice is... that's all I'm thinking of right now. All right, settled down. All right,
let's do Isaac. I'm just gonna play one game of Isaac. We'll see. Oh, I need... I need my controller.
Oh, it's on the... hold on. It's in the other room. One more BRB. I promise I'm not gonna eat food.
I do... I do like the, he hates streaming comments. All right, I got my tea refilled
because it's true. It's not true. Dear, slander me like that. Look, Isaac. I kind of... I want to
play greed mode. What is... What is this? Easter eggs. Look at how good I am at this game, by the
way. I just love playing as Samson in greed mode. It's just... that just is the way it's gonna work
here. All right, it's been a little while. I have the mod still, right? Yep. One bone heart. Should
I pick that up? Wait, what is this? Oh, he cheated. I forgot. It's a bad item. Well, I want to take
hits with Samson, so... By the way, I'm gonna have wicked bad food voice. One of the reasons I don't
like to eat before streaming. I know it's probably other streamers that have this mentality as well,
but when you eat and then it's time to talk for four or five straight hours...
No, that's one of the reasons why I don't really eat a lot before streaming. Yeah, you get that
really bad milk voice. All right, just give me... Yeah, hit me. I need to do more damage than this.
Bullshit. Dude, I got S++ today. I'm very proud of myself. Can I just tell you?
I killed 150 enemies in a row. Like, I got an A for the first time on my report card. I am sprinting
home to show mom. All right, that's all the hits I want to take. It's almost like a look, look, see,
see, see, ma, look. I forgot this is greedier. It's harder. I thought I died. It's a heal.
Hmm. Play Tainted Samson instead. I like the regular Samson based.
Mimics Isaac's movement on a 0.66 delay. Deals 30 con... Ah, this thing...
This thing kind of stinks, doesn't it? Just restart. I don't think you need to do that.
It's fine. It's probably actually not bad here in greed mode. Hey, what does this guy look like?
Um, and um, Tingle. Yeah, you know that guy Tingle from Zelda? Spitting image. He's definitely
naked. Uh, that would be kind of weird to eat. Oh, hold on a minute. I got a food voice.
I don't know if I'd want to eat food naked. That would kind of be annoying. I don't... I would not
like that. That would suck. Uh, I don't have enough hearts to get this. You've never done it.
I don't think so. Should I get the key? Sharp key. Because if you think about it,
that's a deal. That's five, 10, 15, 20, 25. That's 25 cents worth of keys.
But now I don't have to worry about keys anymore. Just don't throw them. No bombs either. What the
hell is that? Modeling clay? Ooh, I like that. There's a 50% chance to grant the effect of a
random passive item each room. That's kind of good. I'll try it. I guess I'm going to do more clay
stuff. I told you guys that I started doing it, right? It's not something that I don't plan on
doing it on. Oh my God. More keys. I don't plan on doing it on stream or anything. It's like a
little hobby. This is not bad here. Hmm. There's a key. This is a really bad idea. I don't think I'm
going to do it. King baby. I set a PhD. All right, let's get hurt. Come on. Keep hitting. Hit me
again. One more time. Not from a champion. From a regular enemy, please. Back off. I didn't even do
it right. What? Hit me. What? What was that? That run sucked. That build was awful. Yeah. What does
a s'more do? It's over. You failed. Finally. Finally. Let me do it. God damn it. I'm so fucking mad
right now. I kept talking over it. I was talking over it. I was like, finally I get to do the pitch
down echo reverb sneeze joke that I've been waiting like a month to do. And I talked over it
while it came up. That's so irritating to me. That's so, I'm actually mad about that. Somebody
just wrote bless you with a bunch of question marks. I'm going to die again. Hold on. I don't
even know why I care about it too. I'm just like, yo, next time I sneeze, maybe I'll just turn on my
filters. It'd be super funny. I bet you so many people are going to go. All right. This is the one.
We're going to, I'll get a bunch of dog shit items. There we go. Run is officially on. I hope you're
ready. I just need a shit load of tears up and we're good. Strength, arrow cod. Nice. Brain worm.
Just don't screw this up. I need tears up so bad. This is low. All right. We're good. This could be
a destructive run as long as I don't totally blow it. Then I'll be fine. Get tears up on a damage
brain worm increased tier size. It's available. I didn't even see this guy. All right. This is range
brain worm for sure. I'm personally begging you to buy brain worm. Oh yeah. I wasn't going to miss
that guys. How personally invested are you in this run? Keep it going. This could be the one. I don't
know how you're going to bet on it, but oh, by the way, I'm thinking of a crazy idea for channel
points. I just have to make sure I can do it. So all you channel point Andes that have been asking
about it for a long time now, I might have something cooking here and it's pretty sick.
I'm just telling you, I got to, I might have a really disappointing news when I tell you like,
oh, nevermind. I can't do it. What's this? Wait, what? Ma of the void. Will this replace my big
charge tears? Take it. I only have one heart. Use the card then buy it. Use the card for a free heart.
Don't take it. I think this one, I'd rather have this one. I made my decision to damage up, right?
Did it even do two damage up? Now take it. Card. What? The card. Wait, what? Everyone's yelling at
me. You're a dumb ass. What? I didn't, what did I do wrong? I didn't want this thing. I didn't want
it. It's an active item. I didn't want that thing. At least I get my 3d glasses. I want a bomb. I
don't care. I'm doing it. Nice. Let's get out of here. How come I, why did I vote? Yes. You're
going to be fine. All right. So I want to, I want to run over this shit. Nice. Nice. Take that up
here. Nice. Uh, my brain worm has to go away though. That's worth it. All right. And now I
want to blow this up. I think I'm going to keep the brain worm. Tinted? What do you mean? Where,
where, where? Sick. Penny is a free win. Yeah. Let's go for it. I want money. It's all about
the money for me right now. I'm taking it. Yeah. This is great mode. Aim up, aim up. Whatever that
is. Double tapping a fire button makes Isaac sneeze blood. Sneeze deals 150% damage. Really?
That's not going to mess with my thing. Is it? Cool. It doesn't. So I can be like, boom.
Here's up. Yes. The play is to go. Let go pop. Let go pop. Randomly grants the effect of none
of this matters. Right? What does this question mark for? Why is there a question mark up there?
In the top left is a red question mark that appears. Why? All right. Let's start it.
The pill is behind the spikes. It's an unknown pill. Right? All right. Let's go. I like the sound
it makes. Does this count as a brimstone or no? Just a charge move. I gotta take some hits.
The money to damage. Ow. Oh, nice. I'm okay. Taking the hits. This stinks. What? My character?
What do you think? I just, I just killed them all. Oh, it's only two tiers from monstros lungs.
Many tears. Oh, what was that by the car battery? Yeah. What the hell? What about the devil room?
I didn't want it. Okay. Let's get out of here. We're doing good. You had enough health. I'm,
I don't want to throw any more hearts away. Huge. Although do I want the damage?
That's a lot of damage to lose. Is it worth it? I guess it's DPS for versus straight up damage.
Right? It's probably better. He's better be good. Fuck you. Monstros lung is all about high damage.
You just fucked up. What do you know? Probably a lot. Actually not even the worst thing that
could have happened. Come on. Give me something. Yes. Empty heart grants a heart container when it
went at one red heart or less at the start of a new floor. Why can I pick this up? I have to
bomb it. Oh, I've never seen that before. I just ran over that like an idiot. Range D eight
multiplies Isaac's damage tiers, range and speed. He's faking it. No, I was reading chat.
I'm going to blow through this whole level. Just watch. Oh my God. Disgusting. No one even
touched me. I did that on purpose. I felt bad. What even? I honestly don't even know what keeps
hitting me. I don't even want any of this stuff. Too much to give up. Seven seals. I don't know.
I only have four hearts. It's not worth it. Look at the money I have. All right. I'm thinking about
a reroll. Oh, I definitely want this. Maybe the I want the range. This thing is not going far at
all. I like being able to just throw it like across the room like this. Oh, hell nah. He went for
range. What? What we have? Oh, I like range. I like being able to hit things from far away.
Take some damage for a free heart container. I'll do that on the next. Look at all these doubters.
Everybody was just saying, why did you do that? Why did you activate the nail in here? I don't
know. Maybe because I could get fucking double this doubled. Yeah. Right now everyone's on the
phone trying to figure out how to refund a betting channel points because they just saw what I just
got. And that's tech point five. Occasionally fire lasers in addition to Isaac's tears. Okay.
Sounds great. Let's replace this. I can't lose now. Not possible. All right. I'll do it again.
Manny pack. Yep. Oh, only applies to the right eye, but these are coming out of my mouth.
Cause I didn't do anything. Yeah. I need to save money. That's true. We're going to get to 49 or
50 coins. All right. I need, I need to get hurt. Why are you, what do you mean? Why are you collecting
the coins? The two of diamonds is just doubles your coins. I don't think they have to be in the
ground. What about the sneeze? The sneeze doesn't really do anything. Why are you reading chat?
Because I'm a live streamer. Mom walked in. Yeah. Fuck you. Yeah. Mom. I'm just showing,
just hanging out with friends. Yeah. I'm okay. Yeah. I'm going to get it done. Five more minutes.
Yeah. Okay. So I, I'm just going to use it now. Stop leaving the room. You just unsubscribed.
Um, let's take the diamonds now and whatever. I'm going to shopping spree buddy in a box. Nice.
Nice. Cano. I didn't see what it did. What it does for Kano old tab to see what it does.
Drop it. It's the right trigger to drop everything. Right. Okay. So I was three blue spiders and three
blue flies. Oh, okay. That's cool. Godlike run. That technology thing is awesome. Save money,
save money, save money. Oh no, it's crumples. I think I'd rather have the two damage and that's
it. The nail is just two free damage. Almost there. Yes. What the fuck isn't chocolate milk?
Won't that override? No, I don't want that. That's going to override everything. This definitely
doesn't stack. Oh, I see. A lot of you guys are going to lose a lot of channel points if I
don't take that. I see. That's why a lot of you're saying it. We literally believe there's no way
this guy's serious. Wait, is that for real? You'll never know if it's stacks or not. If you don't
take it. What? Uh, please take it. I beg of you. Does anybody actually know if it stacks?
I'm terrified to actually touch this. Ask chat GPT. Hey chat GPT does, um, chocolate milk
and monstros tooth. I'm not picking it up. I don't want to touch it. I'll look it up. Does
monstros tooth and chocolate milk stack? Yeah. Monstros lung. Sorry. It's monstros lung and
chocolate milk stack. It does. Holy shit, dude. Are you serious? That's this 400% more. I thought
you guys were just fucking with me. All right, let's do it. I can't see. There's so much saliva
in my mouth. What? Why does so much saliva in my mouth? What happened? I don't know where that
came from. That was weird. Nice. Okay. You got plenty of hearts of Isaac, chocolate milk and
monstros lung do synergize with each other. When these two items are combined, the player can
charge up monstros lung more quickly by repeatedly tapping the shoot button, which causes Isaac to
shoot a barrage of tears in a short amount of time. This results in a very powerful attack.
It can do a lot of damage to enemies. Additionally, the charge shots from monstros lung
are affected by chocolate milk damage multiplier, which can. What's going on? Chat. GPT is say that.
Why did I leave the room? Tap. Don't hold your chat. GPT told me to tap and it's, it's more
effective. I don't fucking like this computer shit. I don't like the computers to do this.
I don't like the computers can tell us this. I don't like computers. I don't, I don't, I don't
like computers anymore. Here comes the Amish rant. Ooh, it's poop moving. I don't like that.
Hmm. Is that worth taking that? I would know the one duplicates a random pickup in the room.
Thanks. Thanks. I don't care if I get hurt. Gigachad. Nice. Is that, wait, is that tears up
again? Re-roll it. Hmm. Yeah, that's not a bad idea. Metronome. Uh-huh. Holy shit. Oh, I'm at the
tear cap. Should I get this bomb? The reroll machine. Okay. Let's go get it with the battery
max two per room. No, I think I'm just going to go for it. Only one more floor. Anyways.
Ooh. Guppy's tail as well. Throwing poop spawns one blue fly. I'm already at the. Oh yeah.
Ace of clubs turns all pickups, chess and non-boss items into bombs. Tower. This one's a super one.
The devil to whatever it is. Activates the Bible grants seraphim grants flight last for 30 seconds.
All right. I remember that's there. Where's this office still live? Oh, it's this guy.
I want full like end game legend of Zelda heart road. I don't want this. That's not enough for
Omega greed. Jesus. Where the hell are you? I'm pretty confident. We're sending so many offerings
to summon you into your Roblox world right now. I don't think I can make it. Holy shit. Twisted
pair by twisted pair. Holy shit. OP, OP, OP, OP. Huh? Wait, are we all doing the same move?
I need hearts though. This is bad. Hearts for sale. No, I need, I mean like max HP by more upside
down cards, stars, the devil again. Okay. Wait, wait, wait. I'm overwhelming myself.
Removes Isaac's oldest passive item. All right. Wait, it doesn't order. I got to do this then.
What did I, what did I just do? I'm fine. I think it's just the devil use stars right now.
What did I just get? Your oldest passive item was the key item. Really don't use it. Wait,
people are saying don't do it. All right. Uh, no, I got the devil. I'm ready to go take on greed.
Do not use it. Don't use it. Don't use it. All right. Doubters are telling you not to do it.
It really, wait, my oldest item is the nail, not the key. How that works. Nails, not passive. Oh,
what's the first passive item? Oldest passive item, ignoring starter items. Blood lust is the
oldest. He doesn't do anything and doors box. What is it? What does it do? This thing's OP.
Single use spawns rewards based on floor. What floor am I technically on for greed?
It's a chest. One coin. All right. I'm ready. Let's go. Give me the devil card. Let's go.
I'm ready. I'm not messing around. All right, everybody. This is it. We'll see. Let's see how
you voted. All right. This is kind of, I could blow it though. Uh, I think we're gonna be fine.
I'm a little slow, but it's all right. Holy shit. A coupon. What? Who cares? What? What?
Okay. Slow down. Slow down. What am I doing? I don't care about that. I should have gotten that
excited. Yeah. This is, this is for free. Sorry, doubters. No refunds right now. I apologize.
This is the way it is. All right. Should I, for a joke, should I take myself down to half a heart
to give the doubters a little bit of a, you know, just so they don't all leave at the same time?
Oh, nevermind. Cool. That was a good one. Don't patronize me. Chat carried you. I mean chat helped
make decisions. Of course they did. I don't know. I feel like you can't play Isaac and like there's
somebody, unless there's somebody sitting next to you telling you what items you should get.
And honestly, I do that for other people. I feel like I'm so confused half the time that I play
Isaac, but if I'm watching somebody play Isaac, they're getting a ton of advice. I'm telling them
everything. Oh, tainted rock over there. Uh, check the secret room, secret top right room,
probably secret room. So, yeah, it's a very backseat game. Advice from you. Nobody can't
know a thing or two about Isaac. Uh, he must've just joined the stream. Top left. So we'll make
sure you see all a hundred percent of the game. Well, somebody else did. And then I installed it
on my computer, but it's on my machine. So technically I own it. All right. That's going
to be it. I'll see you guys later. I might stream this weekend. I told you I wanted to do
old ads. That's possible. I would say if not Sunday, then maybe Monday. There's a couple of
things I really want to get situated before I stream again. Yeah, this is fun. Just jump around
playing games, slow it down, chill it out a little bit. Hope you had a good time. It's a good way to
wake up. Yeah. Some of you probably are just getting up. Yeah. Keep an eye out. I'll let you know.
That's the plan though. We'll go back to Breath of the Wild as well. Not immediately, but obviously
after we do some of this watch stuff and just some React Andy this weekend or into early this
coming week. What about the new Hollow Knight? Maybe. What time this weekend? Uh, it's usually
6 PM Pacific in the more recent months. Let me get the right music on. This is not the correct music.
Where is that? Where's the music? Where's the music? Actually, I moved it to a different folder.
Where the hell is it? There it is. See you guys soon. It's been 219 days since your last sorcery
stream. Yeah. Yeah. We'll get to it. I promise. Just can't give you a day. We'll see. Take care
of yourselves. Call your mother. Have a good start to your weekend. See you very soon. Take it easy.