What's up? Oh, should I have to mute myself in here? I don't know how to do that. Hold on.
All right, I think I know how to do it. Okay, I think I'm muted in the game. How you doing? Hi,
everybody. Welcome. Welcome to a VR stream. You know, I made a few promises, and I'm going to
keep those promises. So what we're doing today is we're going to act a little bit sus today.
Playing Among Us VR, the sus guy is finally fucking going to stream this game. I hope you're ready.
I've rebranded the whole channel. And no, I didn't put any sub badges in because I know what you
guys would do. You would you would go to every channel on Twitch and ruin the whole website.
So we're not doing that today. There's tons of BT TV emotes. Why not? Because it would be a disaster.
And on my mics, I'm still I got COVID still. So I've never played this game. I did the
tutorial really quickly. So all I know is that if I'm the imposter, I have to kill people.
And if I'm a crewmate, then I have to stop the imposter from killing everybody.
Is everybody ready to get sus? I think we're still setting the lobby up. But hi. He did the
tutorial. Yeah. And this is one day only, by the way. I'm not doing this ever again. Make sure I
tweet this. Yeah, I ain't ever doing this ever again. Every emote that you're spamming right
now, everything that you're doing, every single joke that you're making is not going to be allowed
as of tomorrow. One day only. Watch me be really good at this game. It's only a one day event. It
really is. Yeah. I have to make sure I don't show the lobby code too. That would be so the the lobby
I'm in right now. It's Kraken Vinnie Ross. There's a bunch of people in here. And I think we're just
kind of chilling. Waiting to start. I'm muted right now in the game. But I'm gonna annoy,
I'm gonna annoy the fuck out of everybody in this lobby, I can already tell you.
I think, I think I'm, is something wrong? I think I'm breaking the game or something.
Yeah, they're talking to me in the game. Hold on. All right, so it's time to get sus.
Can you guys hear them? All right, I gotta make sure I don't show the room code. Hold on.
Oh, good. We got 10 subs. We got way more than 10. Hold on. I don't want to show the lobby.
Hold on. Okay. Hey, everybody, what's going on to be the sus guy? I'm doing the Deadpool voice.
All right, hold on. I know before I just gonna make sure you can't see the lobby code.
Because that's a really important thing. First of all, I got to unmute myself here.
Okay, I'm currently unmuted. I'm currently I'm ready. I don't want to stare at a wall,
though, because I don't want to look at the room code. Okay, so here we go.
Hold on. I can turn, you apparently can turn off the hands disappearing. Oh,
oh my God. Yes, you can. Okay. All right. Hey, don't show the room code. Fucking idiot.
I can't, I can't be trusted. I really can't. I have to just look at the wall. Something's
in my eye already. How did it get in my eye? Oh, this is pretty sus.
Okay. Hi, guys.
Let's go. Okay, I don't want to see the room code. Hi, everybody. Hi, guys.
What's up? Are you ready to play some among us? I'm ready. I'm ready. All right. You look kind of
cool. There we go. It's so tiny. So how do you play? Anybody know how to play this game?
I didn't play the tutorial, man. I have no idea. Can that can you just point? You just point?
Okay. It's pretty nice. Oh, you can point. That's what you do. So you. So how do you,
how do we, is it just, do we just roll Dyson who gets to play as, you know, the imposter?
Pretty much. Ever played D&D? It's kind of like that. Oh my God. You make a triangle.
Do we get to, can we, do we get to roll who gets to be the imposter or does it just pick a random
person? I think it just picks random person every game. Picks two people. Purple is probably my top
three. How many people do we have? There's other people over here. It's number two for sure. Hey.
Oh, I just did. It's me. One day only, by the way. This is the only day. This is the only day
I'm going to allow it. Yeah. Are you ready to like get kicked out first every single round?
Because literally the only bit. Sorry. What's the point of that? Are you, are you feeling?
This thing's too tight. This thing's too tight on my hands. Okay. Yeah. It's a big in my like
handshake. There we go. That's better. Hey. Hey. Hey. Hey. So are we, are we ready to rock and roll?
Are we ready to rock and roll? Hey, I think we're ready. Are we double turns?
By the way, subscriptions are appreciated today. Look at him. He's a little shit.
I don't even know how to do this. I, I, I, I feel, I feel so fucking out of my element right now.
I'm going to be very honest. You can mute yourself if you want by pressing the little
mic button. I feel like I shouldn't be here. I appreciate that. Tell everybody. Remember.
It's true. Hey, you know what? Thank you. How about let's establish some backstory. What are
we all doing here? Thank you, Vinny. Let's start with you. Okay. What are you doing? I think I'm
sent to do the arboretum. I want to regrow the props. Very good. Would you like to join me in
this charboard? Of course. Yeah. I have a side objective though. I'm killing everybody regardless
of if I'm imposter or not. So keep that in mind as we move forward. Are we playing right now?
Establishing some like stakes, you know, before we go. Oh, I thought we were playing right.
I thought somebody was already the imposter.
We could be. We could decide who's the imposter. Regardless. Yeah. Yeah. Democracy.
I mean, aside from sus guy trying to get subs.
Do you, if you go to my story. Oh, go ahead. Sorry. I don't want to cut anybody off.
I, I'm the captain of a previous vessel that crashed and I was abandoned on a space station
and I, and I had to say goodbye to my, my loved ones and I got abducted by this one and I'm trying
to prove to y'all I'm the captain, but actually I don't have any credentials with me. So, you know,
that's the thing. I remember you. Hold on a second. I'll do better this time. Are you related to
Tinky Winky from the Teletubbies? I'll never tell. Okay.
Yeah, that looks awfully like a TV there in the middle of your screen. Yeah.
Maybe they're all just weird. And my TV is just my eyes actually.
All right. Are we ready to, are we ready to rock and roll? Are we ready to rock?
Anyone else that wants to join, they'll join in next round. Okay. Yeah. Good luck everybody.
It's going to work. Hey, be careful. If it's you, if I'm the imposter, I'm killing you first.
Wait, don't say any sounds. We can still hear everybody. Hi everybody. I'm muting. Mute,
mute, mute, mute, mute. What do I do when my screen is red and has a kill? What does the
kill button do? Hey. Yeah. Don't mind me guys. He's red. Get away from me. Oh my God. This is so
weird. What do we have to do? Oh, this mission's right. Like I'm just trying to do my task, but
now I'm tall because I'm standing, but if I'm sitting, I'm too small. Vinny, I'm coming with
you. I feel like if we're doing tasks, got a pump, pump it. How do you pump with your hands?
Don't stand so close to me. My big yaoi hands. I don't know how to do this. Pretend I never said
that. Yeah. I'm just going to go with that. I got it. Grab with the trigger and then pump, pump, pump.
I did it. Okay. Unless you're sus. No, no, no, no. I got it now. I got it. Oh, fuck. I'm muted. I
forgot. I've been muted this whole time.
So nobody can hear me.
But dude, I walked away from that corner. I said I was going to kill him first, by the way. That's
the funniest part about this. You did walk away. My first game ever. I fucking die immediately
within 15 seconds. 15 seconds. Get rid of him. Get rid of him. Get rid of him. I'm the ghost of
the fucking sus guy. And I'm going to make sure they pick you. Did I play? Did I play wrong there?
He's no way. He's going to get voted on.
Who are they voting for?
Bastards. That was so funny. That was so funny. I mean, I was literally pointing in your face
saying I'm going to kill you first and you fucking killed me in 10 seconds.
I figured the best way to get you acclimated to Among Us was to kill you instantly.
This game is kind of fun. Yeah, it's going to be good. We just have to betray each other and then
you know ruin friendships and it'll be great. Yeah, that's all right.
Who's the other imposter? Oh, it doesn't show you? We have tasks. Oh shit. How do we do tasks?
I have to like look around the corner and make sure it's coming.
Oh, there's a task in here. All right, so let's do some tasks. Let me get acclimated by this.
How does this work? Okay, so what do we have to do? Yeah, well, we're dead. We can't do tasks.
I'm dead, guys. I'm dead. What's happening? Did you vote for me? I did not. I skipped the vote.
I do it. Did I do it? You do tasks. Do tasks, people are saying. Liars. Do tasks.
I guess you do. Yeah, you can contribute. All right, I'm going to go navigation.
What happened? I'm going to do my tasks. I give up dead instantly. That's so funny.
That's absolutely poetic. All right, we're going to head this way.
That's a fucking imposter. I guarantee it. Yeah, there's no task done in here.
There's an imposter right there. Did I fail it? Oh, I see. I gotta get it right in the middle.
Done. Who's he talking to? Oh, we're all streaming. I forgot. I completely forgot.
Everybody's streaming right now. What else is there to do?
I feel like it's hard to get people alone, right? You have to get somebody kind of going down like
a hall. And you have to be the very worst version of yourself. You have to be the sus guy.
Oh, don't worry. I'm ready. I mean, if anybody in this lobby ever wants to talk to me again,
I understand. You know what I mean? I want someone to trust you, says a chat member. Absolutely do
not say you can trust me.
Become the sus guy. I mean, I kind of sound like him because I am him.
Somebody said hit the Luddie. All right. How do you do it?
Yeah. Oh, so we can sabotage when they start going again. If you use your map,
you can still do tasks because you're regular. That's zero practice, by the way.
This is bizarre. Hearing their voices like this. Yeah, it feels weird.
It feels like my head's under water.
Robert, we saw you. You poked your little head in. You saw us and then you ducked out
and then you reported it. Oh, was that what? Impostor got displeaded.
What's going on here? That's all you can do. Why are they talking like this?
Yeah, it's a little. It feels weird. Emergency meeting.
It was a little spooky. It was a little scary. All right. We were all scared. All right.
Maybe his body just did that. Have we considered that? Who is it?
Who killed you? I don't know. Who killed you?
Oh, Vinny. Maybe it was natural causes. Maybe it was heart fatigue or something.
I killed you and they immediately sussed me out in a room that's that way.
It scared the absolute shit out of me, too. I was not expecting it at all.
I was like, oh, I can trust Vinny. I'm going to follow Vinny. I was muted, but that's what I was
saying. No, that was perfect. I'm not good at this, OK?
So the check could definitely spoil things for us. I don't know where I am.
Oh, OK. Terrifying. Yeah. Yeah. Achievement. I got an achievement.
Play again, right? Yeah. Don't look at the lobby.
My only game of Among Us Impostor. I'm going to quit now.
I got my one win. No, OK. The one win. It's awful.
You feel the guilt. It's terrible. Did you hit the Yankee Splanky? All right.
I was in a room alone with you and I felt bad. You did a very good job, though.
You did an insane job because we didn't even vote to win the first round.
Yeah, I'm very surprised. How about the hit the sussy? You got it.
We're good, though. What happened to my height? Why are my hands so high?
It was cold. It sounds like I'm listening to robots. It's loud.
I can turn everything down. It's very loud.
How's that better? That sound better?
There it is. Better?
So, I only have one hand. Now imagine that.
Better? OK. Hide the room code?
I don't see people. Oh.
Thank you. The other one is like, was it on the ceiling or on the floor?
Yo, yo, yo. Dab me up. Dab me up. I could do it right here.
Bam. You got it. Yeah, good dab. Good dab. Good dab.
I got to psych myself up. OK, maybe not like that.
Oh, my God. Maybe so.
If you get imposter, you're going to fucking do it, man.
Yeah, this is pretty good. You can imposter.
Oh, I don't know what happened. I don't know. He died.
He fell down. He fell down. I don't know what happened.
He hit his head. I got it. What's up?
How are you doing over here? A little weird that you're talking alone.
I'm just trying to figure out what I want to be and do.
OK, I'm making sure. I'm making history right now.
I'll trust him. I know. I'm trying.
Hey, how do I hide the room code?
I've been looking at the ground.
Gameplay and then scroll down.
Will it show it if I look at the screen?
I like the little moving in place. It's so funny.
Gameplay. Show. OK.
OK, I don't think I showed it. I've been looking down.
I tried to walk over to my water in VR. Hold on.
No, that's not how that works. Oh, I got a drink too.
Oh, that's pretty sus.
Oh, God. Where's the my wisdom?
Who is he? He is COVID.
Sorry, guys. I was acting a little sus.
OK, hold on. Hold on. Stay back from him.
What? I mean, you have COVID, don't you?
Do you have COVID? Yeah.
Six feet, guys. What?
Hey, where'd you get that? We got a gas mask, man.
We need to spread those around.
No, I'm good. Yeah, actually, I'm good.
I've got a mask on. I can be in.
Really? It's OK.
Dude, I just today lost the ability to taste and smell, though.
That sucks.
It sucks. I feel all right, though.
If you get tinnitus, please let me know,
because I think I have long COVID tinnitus.
I hear it in my ear for the past fucking two months now.
That sucks.
It's fine. All right.
Well, how about I don't want to be like a downer on the lobby.
Like, oh, yeah, man.
Sucks so bad. Everything.
What is your body scent?
Mine's like a constant ringing.
That's right.
Is it jolly?
It's always good to be numb while playing Among Us VR at most.
Oh, boy. Are you jolly?
So far.
No, I feel good, though. I feel better.
Setting the main audio this fucking loud.
OK, I'm almost done.
Yeah, I know. I know, dude. I know.
It's insane how bad.
What's out here?
Also, your name may need your white.
He's white.
I am a bit of a white boy, which is white.
Yeah, this is jolly wanker, everybody.
So we just got to get his name proper.
I just want to see what people were saying.
What's my name?
If you open up the in-game menu thing,
with one of those little jump buttons that you'd use in VR chat.
Yeah, and like the bottom right, there's a gear.
And then you go.
I like that beak.
And then there's like a second page that you can go on to.
And there's like, hide my username.
Oh, yeah.
You can also turn off hiding.
What do you do?
There you go.
Oh, you have a little plant up.
What do I have?
There we go.
Nice to meet you, too.
We should be the first in Among Us VR to have a cool handshake.
Yeah, no.
Wait, are they doing that or are we doing that?
Wait.
Oh, I thought you were talking to me.
Sorry.
I'm sorry.
I'm almost 40.
Grand father.
How many people do we have?
One, two, three, four, five, six, seven, eight.
We got nine people.
First person to turkey in Among Us VR.
OK, let's go.
You can't hear it, but I'm clapping.
You have to yell turkey.
Oh, I see it.
I get it.
Turkey.
Wow.
Every single person over there.
You better be ready.
If I get imposter this round, first time ever,
it's going to be gun over.
How we go?
Are we good to rock and roll?
Oh.
First person to stub their toe in Among Us VR.
Who is he talking to?
I'm talking to you guys.
I'm talking to the chat room.
Why don't I just say it like that?
It's really taken over.
How many subs do we have so far?
How many subs?
Let's see.
I don't know, at least 10.
I have to update that.
Hey.
What's happening?
This stream totally isn't going the way you thought it was going to go, is it?
Well, I died in 10 seconds the first round ever.
It was not.
It's impossible to have a conversation with anybody.
Especially your chat room.
All right, we're getting out.
So what do you want to talk about in the three seconds that we have together?
All right, we're starting.
Good luck.
All right.
Oh, boy.
Okay.
Anyone feeling, anyone feeling,
admitted now, admitted now, before we start, before we start,
anyone feeling a little suspicious right now?
Not yet.
Not me.
No one?
I'll get back to you on that.
I'm taking a mental note of where every single fucking person goes.
What?
I thought somebody killed me.
I was like, how?
Who did that?
What?
I don't really have like two emergency meetings.
How many emergency meetings?
Yeah, we're using our first one for a dumb bit.
I think it's one per person.
How do we skip?
I am skipping.
I'm skipping.
I'm telling you, you got to see where everybody walks, right?
Somebody goes that way.
I'm going to just watch.
Okay, I'm good.
I'm okay.
We're fine.
All right, I'm skipping.
Hey, Vinny.
Why would I do that?
All right, in the menu, do you have your mic?
I'm going to do my tasks, okay?
Somebody follow him.
You too.
Somebody follow Blue.
Is this like a choice that you've made to be mute or is this?
Vinny and Liam, you follow Criken.
I got my eyes on Blue.
He can't speak, but I'm sure he agrees.
All right, I'm coming with you guys.
Don't leave me alone.
Why am I going that way?
Don't leave me alone with Vinny.
Wait, what?
Oh, shit.
What do I do?
What?
Okay, straight.
Oh, my.
This sucks.
Can I fight back?
Hey, what's up?
What's going on?
I've never played this game.
I don't know what room is what room.
I was going to navigation because I want it.
I'm going to navigation.
No, you guys, all two of you, come with me if you want.
It's fine.
But I want you to get in front of me.
Yeah, sure, sure.
You know what?
I got nothing to prove.
I got nothing to hide.
Go ahead.
We can watch the door.
We'll watch the door.
You take care of your tasks.
No one's coming through this.
You're safe.
It's these two.
It's definitely these two.
No, it's these two.
It's these two.
Help!
I found imposters.
I found the imposters.
I found them.
I found the imposter.
I don't know what room I'm in.
What?
No.
You don't tell anybody.
I won't tell anybody.
Just let me live.
You're fine for now.
All right.
OK, OK, OK.
We're good.
OK.
Go on, go on.
Oh, shit.
Emergency!
Emergency meeting!
Hey!
I'm back here.
Hold on.
Wait a second.
You're fine.
Take your time.
Get some water.
Did you see what he's doing?
A panic attack?
What's going on?
Listen.
You think it's him.
I was walking around.
I don't know how to play this game, right?
And fuck, I forgot their names.
OK.
So what's your name?
Green here.
And what's your name?
Green and yellow cornered me.
All right.
It's above my head.
OK.
Listen, listen, listen.
Listen, important.
We have a name tag.
They were chasing me around, screaming at me and shit.
And they were like, hey, don't tell anybody.
And I was like fucking running for my life and screaming.
It's these two.
Or at least it's one of them.
That does not sound like something I would do.
One task.
Do one task.
I went.
OK.
Are you alive?
I went to go do a task.
And they both got like weirdly in a triangle pattern behind me.
And I'm just sitting there going like.
I'm like, why are they doing this?
Why are they doing this?
So it has to be these two.
It's Charborg and Philboat.
You're making a big mistake if you listen to him.
Don't listen to where that guy's coming from.
I'm telling you right now.
I've known Charborg for years.
And he's never done anything suspect whatsoever.
No, no, no, no, no.
I'm a nice guy.
You said I was yelling at you.
It's impossible that there's something going on.
I was being chased.
If you vote one of us out and it doesn't show the imposter thing gone.
That's insane.
Oh, we got five seconds of voting.
I'm telling you.
It's these two.
What's going on?
This is insanity.
No, don't skip.
I'm telling you.
They chased me around.
It was weird.
It was scary.
Because it's funny.
Well, I'm still alive.
OK.
You're still alive.
That's true.
That's what matters.
Am I loud?
I'm going to go take care of my task, guys.
I think we're just getting bullied.
We're good.
OK.
We got some work to do.
I've got my eye on you.
Hey, I'm cool, man.
I think you might have been thinking of the other green guy.
I didn't do anything.
OK.
I'm doing my task.
I haven't run into you once.
I want to watch you do a task.
OK.
Come with me.
Let me see where we got tasks.
I'm going to follow right behind you.
And I want you to do a task.
All right.
Right over this way.
Come with me.
I know it's you.
And I'm going to convince everybody eventually.
And eventually, they're going to get on my side.
But I'm staying far enough away from you.
I am the imposter.
And I'm going to kill you.
And I'm going to kill everybody you know.
Tell them.
See if they believe you.
Can I?
Emergency meeting.
Wait, there isn't.
I'm telling you.
It's these two.
This is like fucking crazy.
Oh, why am I the crazy guy in the fucking horror movie
that nobody believes?
Vinny, Vinny, Vinny.
Listen, Vinny.
They thought it's a.
Oh, my.
It's wrong.
They're just being weirdos.
God damn it, man.
You got to be kidding me.
Why would they chase me around?
It's because I'm a new player.
And oh, no.
But it has to be one of them, right?
They're going to vote Charlie out.
Because I got my like weird fucking like maniacal talk.
Hi.
I had it wrong.
I had a dead wrong.
I'm very curious what happens here.
Why it's not you.
Yes.
How's my volume?
Should I turn it down?
Turn turn.
Should I turn me down and them up?
Yeah.
Am I good?
OK, just turn them up.
So who are they voting for?
Oh, they're going to actually get it.
No.
Oh, that's bad.
That's bad for you, buddy.
You got two strikes on you right now.
Guys, I'm chill.
German said you.
And Vinny vote you.
OK.
Yeah, German dies.
No.
I hope we can't shut things.
He's pretty good, so fuck off.
What?
German dies.
I can't play these games, man.
I get too fucked up.
Especially in VR.
I get to untangle myself.
That's so funny, though.
Yeah, OK.
So Charborg was following me around,
making like goblin sounds.
Like, oh, I'm going to get you.
And like chasing behind me and stuff.
And I'm like, what the fuck?
It's definitely him.
But isn't that your job?
Well, I'm not, I'm not.
Resident Sus guy?
Yeah, well, I have to get the imposter first.
I can't, I can't just play, you know.
I can't just play the part.
I have to be the part.
It's kind of unfair.
You're a better actor than I am.
You've successfully portrayed yourself
as a normal human being for years,
which is a real skill.
I wish I was half that good.
I love how you're just like the resident ghost.
How did you die?
I said hello to Vinny.
Oh.
I actually is right away from everyone
because when everybody's talking,
I feel like we should have some sort of conch
or something that we can pass around to everyone.
So, you know, everybody gets their two seconds
to say something and everybody's just
screaming over one another.
I guess that's what lobbies just turn into.
Oh, we have to do tasks.
So what does this do?
Oh, you can't move.
Yeah, I think I have to click on the window.
Oh, yeah.
All right.
So what happened?
Yeah, it's really weird.
So who got you?
He got me, too.
Dangerous as hell.
That's so funny.
So when you were being chased,
was it Charbon or was it Vinny?
No, it was you.
Yeah, it was you.
Yeah, I was just chasing him and screaming at him and stuff.
He was like, yeah, you and Phil Boat.
You're like, yeah, we're the imposters.
We're coming.
We're going to get you.
And they were hanging out together.
So and they did this weird triangle pattern behind me.
And I was like, it was scary.
I don't know what to say.
I mean, I was acting on instincts.
I let instincts take over and that's what happened.
I just panicked.
I don't know.
I mean, it was it was it was funny.
What you in for, man?
Oh, this is funny.
OK, I get why people play this.
I understand why people download this game now.
What's this?
They're going to get them.
Nobody voted.
Wow, two still remain.
Who's the other one?
All right, let me do some tasks here.
Let me actually do like what I'm supposed to be doing.
Well, now I'm just going to do tasks.
I feel like, OK, I feel like whoever the imposter is
wants to get rid of like the loud guy, right?
Like just like let's get rid of that guy
because he's going to like fucking freak out
and start screaming at people, right?
You get rid of that guy.
He's the annoying guy in the lobby, me.
All right.
How do I do this objective?
OK, so I got to learn how to do these.
So what are we going to do?
One, two, three, four.
Oh, so it was.
I knew it too.
No one believed.
He didn't say anything.
Why was it so stressful?
Oh, my God.
It wasn't even green or yellow without talking.
I need a drink with my drink.
You guys ready to play some among us?
I'm ready.
How many how many subs gaming?
Well, I guess we'll never know.
I guess it was.
That was amazing.
I'm going to stop talking from now on because he just won.
Hold on.
Here we go.
Yeah, it works, honestly.
I know it.
It's amazing how well you can defend yourself
with not saying anything.
He really said, and I just was like, all right, fair.
And also this as well.
Well, there's two hands for that one.
Yeah, just put them in the other hand.
It's what it's in your ass.
Wait, turn on.
OK, I've got at least five.
I was hanging low.
I got at least five.
I can hear you, Jolly.
I'm sure we're good.
That's actually the amount.
Remember, one day only, the sus guy plays among us.
The omega sub call out of five.
Then might as well play some among us.
I'm ready.
I don't think you're in the right lobby.
Oh, I didn't even take a sip.
I didn't take a sip.
Can I get my friend back in?
Well, he know about it.
Oh, yeah.
OK.
I don't want to run into anything.
I appreciate it.
Do we need to just get kicked out by someone?
Wait, Vinnie got kicked out?
No, it's the random guy.
OK.
Well, it's just the random guy.
It's just the random guy?
OK.
I think someone shares a lot of stories.
You want to lightly ask him to leave?
That's incredible.
I may have done that.
No, that dude came in and said, all right,
who's ready to play some among us?
And I was like, oh, this guy's OK.
I don't know.
It's possible that it was me.
I didn't doubt it.
Yeah, I didn't doubt it at all.
That's why I'm bad at among us.
Oh, and I could turn my mic down.
You know, they're among us.
OK.
I don't even know.
All right, so are we ready to rock and roll before the lobby
gets full?
Because I think there was a leak at some point,
so the code is out there at some point.
Oh, are we redoing it?
You can hear me.
Oh, OK.
So roll it in.
All right.
Roll it in.
OK.
All right.
Can you see the code on the big board?
Can you hear me?
No, no.
Yes.
We can hear you loud and clear.
OK.
Oh, my god.
That was amazing.
You defended yourself so well with the gestures.
Thank you.
I did it somehow.
Listen.
Vinny, I'm never trusting you ever again.
I was hiding from two people.
I know.
Dude, I saw Vinny alone in the cabin's quarters,
and he just slowly walked towards me,
and I was screaming, and no one was around.
It's so scary.
All right.
Ready to go?
Oh, my god.
I'm ready now.
I'm ready.
I don't know how to change my hair.
That's OK.
I'm fine.
Let's do it.
That's fine.
We roll.
We move.
Bum, bum, bum, bum, bum, bum, bum, bum.
I can't be doing with this.
It's too hot.
Too hot.
How are you doing?
OK.
No way.
Oh.
What are we?
No way.
Oh.
Oh, boy.
Oh, dear.
All right.
OK.
Are there any tasks?
I'm going to do my tasks.
Two hands.
Me too.
OK.
Somebody has to take care of that.
They know how to play.
Just I'm staying with somebody.
I can stay with 10 people.
I'm going off.
I'm going to stay.
It's so dark in here.
Is that what they call it?
I'm going to stay.
Stay together.
They called the lights.
You need this fail boat.
You run really fast.
Stay together.
Stay.
Why are we running so fast?
Stay together.
There's three of us here.
One, two.
OK.
Slow movement.
Slow.
I'm going.
Wait.
Where am I?
Just tap.
Tap.
Oh.
That was so ominous.
OK.
Hey, guys.
We're good.
Now, let's come back on.
I just see green.
Hello.
You get in.
I'm going to go in this corner.
And I'm going to watch.
Press some buttons.
So I've got.
Yes.
It's good to watch your back.
When you have nothing against your back.
That's right.
That's the strategy.
So we're going to get these tasks done, please.
Yeah.
I got mine done.
I'm doing them.
I'll watch the doorway, guys.
No one's getting by me.
Well, that one's not done.
That might be your task.
Is it mine?
How does this work?
Where am I?
Hello?
Can anybody hear me?
What happened?
Where am I?
I think I got like sucked into the wall.
Hold on.
Can I?
What is going on?
Fix the sabotage.
OK.
Um.
You shouldn't have asked me to do that.
Why did you ask me?
You're just leading me around the entire map.
How did you do that?
Again?
I don't know.
I tried to do.
What happened to you?
I don't want to be the imposter anymore.
I went into the wall.
It was scary.
You just walked through Hogwarts.
I went in.
I was so happy that at the same time, I just don't want to be the imposter.
What, we're going again?
Not the imposter again.
It's the imposter again.
Thanks, bro.
Oh, OK.
We're fine.
There needs to be individual volume sliders.
OK.
Yeah, I pushed the torque block.
Am I sure?
I have no idea what happened.
Um.
No, it's just the cacophony of noise.
So if someone sabotages the generator and you don't turn it off in time, then you just
wait for the video to play straight up.
I have absolutely no idea what that means.
Imposter?
Get away from me.
The generator, I was about to fix it.
And then it didn't work.
What the?
What is happening?
Why don't press it?
It's not me.
It's not me this time.
I say, Rambo, just to be safe.
What happened?
No, it's not me.
I swear, four times in a row is statistically impossible.
Four times in a row is statistically impossible.
OK?
Look, here we are.
It's impossible.
Here we are.
It might be impossible.
It is.
But how funny would it be if you're voted out and it says,
what imposter remains?
I swear to you, it's funny this time.
Four times in a row is statistically impossible.
We need to stop goofing around.
OK?
No more goofing around.
Stop goofing around.
I agree.
It's not me.
OK?
There's no goofing going on here.
There's been so much goofing around.
Why do you do this brave speech from the corner of the room?
Because people were goofing around too much.
Please.
There's too much goofing around.
The people, we have to be careful.
We have to talk to each other.
We have to fucking follow each other.
Skip the vote.
OK, we're good.
All right.
If you do it your way, gas can.
It's not me.
How would you?
I swear to God, it's not me again.
I think that hitting the emergency,
it's an emergency meeting.
You know what I mean?
It's only for emergencies only.
You're getting close.
If it's you again, I'm going to be very mad.
I'm just telling you.
I'm going to do my job.
Hey, Zamzire.
Are we skipping?
Go ahead and make your vote already so we can get the freaking back to work.
I'm skipping.
What are you doing?
What?
Where's your sense of bloodlust?
I thought my trust in you was waning.
I only have one finger.
Do an ET on me, bro.
I don't think that's all I got.
Nobody was ejected.
OK, we're fine.
OK.
Now I'm going to make a real task.
Task time.
How do you do it?
How do I do tasks again?
Jerma, press the button just to get the map and go to those locations and then just click in.
I don't fucking understand what that means.
OK.
So what do you have?
An index?
Kill him, kill him.
I can't do it.
I don't know how to do it.
Kill him.
Do it.
I don't know how to do it.
Kill him.
How do you do it?
Do it.
Kill him.
I don't know how to do it.
30 seconds before you can kill.
What?
There's a creep on.
What do you put?
What?
Oh, man.
I'm going to tell you something and you have to believe me.
Well, don't believe a fucking word out of his mouth.
This guy has killed me twice each time he chased me around the cafeteria.
He chased me around the cafeteria.
We were screaming in here.
Did anybody hear me?
No.
This sounds like a lie.
The last thing I knew when the meeting was called was there's a cool down.
I'm just saying.
I'm saying you can believe me or not, but it's Jerma.
Thank you very much.
I'm here to do tasks and we're just spending all this time in meetings.
What are we arguing about?
What's going on?
I lost your mind.
I don't know.
I've been chased around by him for literally an entire day.
I don't know what the thank you was.
Yeah, last time you got chased around, it was also a freakish juice call.
Okay?
I see no one dead yet.
I'm just telling you.
The roommate who called sucks.
I'm not going to tell you why I think Jerma did it.
Or is it?
I'm not going to say the reason why.
You're too cool right now.
Why?
He's too calculated.
That seems like a thing you should say.
He's literally calculated.
He's cool and he's calculated and he's trying to fucking get rid of me.
Counterintuitive.
Go see later on if I guess.
I mean, believe me if you want.
Dude, skip the phone.
Like, what's the point?
I like how people say things sometimes.
Skip.
I'm going back to work, right?
I don't care.
Yeah, let me do my tasks.
Somebody.
I've never interrupted my nine to five.
The spin guy's going to be right at the end of the day.
The guy who says spin.
Somebody follow him.
I'm afraid to be near him.
Why don't you follow him?
Because he's literally was chasing me around the cafeteria.
Are we all good?
Wait, no.
We're good to go.
It's not like Dundall.
Good luck, everybody.
Just don't spend too much time with Jerma.
All right, we're good.
All right.
That's bullshit.
Absolute bullshit.
Please don't listen to that.
You're too close, too.
I'm going to go this way.
I'm just going to go this way.
I'm just going to go.
Yeah, I'll stay with you.
Stay.
What?
What do you mean, stay?
Stay?
I don't want to be in a room with two people.
I have tasks to do.
Oh my god.
This isn't me.
I can't see.
It's not me.
Oh my god.
Get back here.
It's not me.
No, no, no, no.
I'm just looking to see who's around the corner.
Yeah, wait, wait, wait.
I don't like you being behind me.
I'm in a defensive position right now.
We'll all stay six feet apart.
It's OK.
Six feet apart.
We can walk down here.
I have to go to.
OK, I'm going to slow it.
You're going to walk.
Yeah, I have to go here, too.
I have to go this way.
Don't get behind me.
I have to.
I'm just in front of you.
I just have to pull this thing.
Where is the?
How do I get over here?
OK, I got to go this way.
Straight ahead, I think.
I don't like being alone.
Get him away from me.
Don't go alone.
He's going alone.
Oh, yeah.
OK, let's let's squat up then.
Let's go.
Let's go find him.
I don't like doing this.
Find him.
Let's go find him.
Do you trust me?
Pinky promise.
I trust you.
Oh, God.
Pinky, pinky promise.
What the fuck happened?
How do I report that?
How do I report this?
How do I report it?
Oh, wow.
What is that?
How do I report it?
Who did you see?
Who was there?
I saw Jerma.
What?
This guy killed someone.
He was eating a body.
We came in the room and he was eating a body.
That's it.
OK.
All right.
Fine.
What?
Eating it.
Look, all I know, it was dark.
I was with Charborg.
We were walking in the room.
I saw Jerma.
He went, oh.
And then Charborg said, there's a body.
There's a body.
And so that's interesting.
It was a yellow body.
Interesting.
Do you have anything to say to defend yourself?
You two were together.
That's funny.
You two were walking around together.
Whoa, yeah.
That's funny.
We're just trying to get.
There are two imposters that are made.
Yeah, you've been following me around this whole time
doing tests with me.
Yeah.
That's weird.
So this guy.
That is kind of weird.
I can't confirm they were.
Is that correct, Jerma?
Just give the vote?
I'm voting for you, actually, is what I'm doing.
Oh, yeah?
Well, guess what?
I'm going to skip.
I think Jerma is suspicious.
I am voting for him.
How do you like that?
I believe you.
What are you going to have?
What do you think?
You think I'm.
What do you say?
Go ahead, say it.
What do you think I am?
I think you're an imposter.
OK.
I mean, whatever.
I'm voting.
Saying OK is a good defense.
All I'm saying is that I was chased around the cafeteria
in the first five seconds of the game.
People have been fucking with me the whole.
I didn't know there was a cool down to start the fucking game.
I didn't know there was a cool down.
There was a cool down.
There's a cool down.
There's a goddamn cool down.
Face your sins.
I just hanging with the two imposters
at the bottom of the map over there.
Incredible.
I was hanging with it.
I was hanging with them too.
They stuck together.
I didn't know there was a cool down in the very.
We were chasing Vinnie around.
And I'm like trying to kill him.
And I'm like, why can't I kill this guy?
And then it's like, oh, there's a cool down.
I can't do it.
Yeah, it's like 35 seconds or something right there.
Oh, I did.
I should have done the tutorial.
You told him to stay.
You told me to stay in the medical office.
I didn't have anything.
I don't know why.
Sit right here.
I don't know why I trusted that.
It's a trusting voice.
So how far is voice proximity?
Because I was like, holy shit, there's no way anybody knows.
Wait, wait, hold on.
I'm testing.
Ah.
Oh, that's far.
That is?
OK, but if you're behind a door.
That's pretty far.
Because we were running around in a circle here.
If I go in here, if I go in here, then.
It's like, we're going to glide away.
Then you can't hear me.
No, no, no.
I can hear him in there.
Wait, what is?
Well, it's because the door's open.
Rambo, is that you?
Yeah.
What?
I didn't know you were in this lobby.
Oh, yeah.
My username is homealone.
My username is homealone2.
Holy shit.
How are you?
I forget to change it on Steam.
I'm doing good.
How are you?
That's cool.
I mean, you killed me.
So not too good.
But it's fine.
Yeah.
It's like the other side of the station.
I'm just glad it wasn't done on purpose now.
Now I know.
I can't believe you won with a sabotage kill.
That's so cool.
You don't know how.
I mean, I think it's about to happen again.
I'm going to be real.
I think it's about to happen again.
Dude, I'm going to die.
I'm going to die.
Dude, I'm going to be kidding you.
I'm going to be kidding you.
But it's not fair.
Oh my god.
What a lame way to lose again.
I'm just saying.
Who did that?
I didn't know there was a cooldown.
I didn't get there.
We'll fix the other one, man.
That's so funny.
That was a 45-second cooldown.
That was a step in the ass.
It was like 45 seconds, maybe.
You actually, that was a good cover, though.
You actually, you following, you run it.
Yeah, that was a great cover on your part.
Who laughed when I booted?
What are your hands doing?
Oh, it's Kony also.
Oh my god.
Look at his hands.
Kony Island.
What's going on with my hands?
I don't know.
I'm so sorry.
I'm OK.
It's 300.
It's fine.
It's OK.
What happens if I throw my index controller here?
What happens?
Is it just a floating hand on there?
It's on the floor.
Yeah.
Whoa, what are you doing with my finger?
It's like clock.
Can I just walk away from my desk?
Wow, look at that.
Hold on.
Amazing.
Can I just walk away from my hand?
I wonder.
Yeah, you can walk away from your hand, I think.
Yeah.
Oh no, it stays with me.
Eww.
Hey, hey there, Jolly.
Get that hand on the collar.
You give me imposter again, and I'm going to be ready this time.
Woo.
Hey, man.
A little bit of a little touch.
And just walk away.
There you go.
Just walk away from it.
But it's a pleasure to meet you for the first time.
Vinny had your back?
Yeah, he did.
You really know what's going on.
Vinny, I do appreciate the sympathy skip at the beginning.
Bad.
I like it.
I like what you've done here.
I had to call you out right away, but I'm glad that you got a chance to at least explain
yourself.
There you go.
That was one of your comedy goals.
He just puts his hand on the table and walks away.
I watch your lips.
I'm like, check this out.
Too funny.
Listen, listen, listen.
I got your back.
I appreciate it.
You can't argue that if I had to do that.
I was chasing around screaming, how do I kill you?
It's not weird.
Coney is so funny.
It would have been just like a killer chasing you.
How do I do it?
How do I kill you?
I don't know.
Do I strangle?
Should I hit you with a brick?
What am I even talking about?
It was amazing.
It was like a Conan O'Brien bit.
I love it.
He hasn't said anything in the chat.
Did Coney just fucking die?
There we go.
Yeah, I don't see him.
And he hasn't said anything in the chat, so I'm not sure.
He's probably trying to figure things out.
I probably look so stupid from an outside perspective.
I'm just going to sit.
It's kind of fun to stand and play this, but Coney had connection issues on his stream,
everybody.
Oh, no.
Do you want to do one and hopefully Coney will be back for the next one?
Yeah, I guess so.
I didn't notice who else was in the room with Jerma and myself.
Everyone make sure to stretch.
Time to go to work, everyone.
All right.
I sussed very well there.
How are you doing?
I hate being here.
I am going to go do my task, which is I have to go over here.
I was the other imposter and I was trying to tell him that there was a cooldown to kill.
There's a 45 second cooldown.
Can we all just go together?
No, I mean like everybody and go back to back here.
He's going to go together.
That's going to be hard to coordinate, but we'll try.
Okay, so there's tasks this way.
Hey, what's going on over here?
What the fuck are you guys doing over here?
I'm going to do this task over here.
I'm going to try to do smooth.
Task complete over here, guys.
It sounds like you're doing a task over there.
A lot of peeps and boops.
Very good.
Thinking about it.
It's really not great.
Oh, wait, this is the vent.
You can use those, right?
Yes.
No, I, oh yes.
What do you mean by yes?
What did you mean by yes, you can use those?
You know what I mean.
I feel like you're going to get sucked in there.
Okay, I go to the lights, I go to the lights, I'm a light doer.
I'm a light doer.
I know you are, but what am I?
I don't know why I just went.
Where did we go?
Oops.
It's Jolly and Orange.
I walked in, they fucking murdered him.
Oh my God.
We died.
We weren't there.
Jolly and Orange.
I watched them rip him apart.
I saw that, I saw that.
It wasn't, that's Tim Burton at his best.
Vinny, you and I, you and I were pretending to do tasks.
I pretended that you were winking a joke about going through the vent.
And like, wouldn't it be funny if you got vented, right?
Right.
Just let them mark it.
It's Orange.
What do you mean?
I'm walking in.
Criken, Criken, come here.
Tell me.
Tell me what happened.
There was a crossroads.
I was talking to Charborg.
I went in, I did a task.
The lights were out.
I come back out.
There was a dead body, Charborg's body.
And both Dark Blue and Orange were standing over it.
Orange starts sprinting towards me until someone else reported it.
Yeah.
It was Criken.
No, no, no.
It wasn't Criken.
I think it was Criken.
That sounded like a horseshit story.
That was a horseshit story.
That was the best story.
Because it's true.
I think that was horseshit.
All right, you got me convinced now.
I see why everyone follows around screaming now.
I'm going to join them.
All right.
But wait a minute.
What if it is Criken?
I'm scared of Penny.
No, no one emergency.
He went for me.
Jolly went for me.
He waited till everyone else was out of the room and he went for me.
Oh, my God.
Why are you lying?
Even if I was the person trying to kill you, I would have had a cooldown.
So what would have been the point?
I dodged it.
And then I, yep, it's Jolly.
Jolly was waiting at the back of the room.
Criken in his Australian accident.
And then he just starts power walking towards me.
I heard screams.
I heard some screams.
I heard a few screams.
So we finished voting out the last guy.
All right.
I was about to leave the room.
Everyone else scattered.
I turned to my left.
There's pink Jolly.
And he goes, Criken.
And then he starts power walking towards me, swinging his hands left and right
in a kind of intimidating fashion.
OK.
I run for the emergency button and smack it right before he gets around my neck.
So what you're saying is he walked at you kind of funnily
and he was kind of a goofy walk.
So that means that it must be him.
Yeah.
If you've got a goofy walk, you're probably suspicious.
I mean, but I do that every day.
But I mean, all of us are goofy walking.
You're making fun of how people walk?
I do.
I do goofy walks.
I'm not convinced.
I don't think you're making fun of how people walk.
I'm just saying that his walk had an aggressive.
There was an aggressive energy to his walk.
I think that you look kind of like Grimace today.
So I think that it's you.
No, come on.
Please.
I was right about the last guy.
Surely I wouldn't be lying about the second guy.
You've got to make the best of what you've got.
What?
OK.
Can I just please get my job done?
I'm going to laugh my ass off if it is you.
If it's really you, I'm going to be I'm going to laugh.
It's going to be funny.
Hey, if it was me, this is the bigger brain
that I've ever done in my life.
Just keep an eye on Jolly.
All right.
Why am I still holding?
Get this away from me.
Oh, god damn it.
I had a stupid fucking joke in my hands.
What are you doing?
There's another one.
Why are there two?
Oh, god.
We're going to die again.
Oh, my god.
We're OK.
Stand across the whole room and talk to me.
Where?
Stand here?
Yeah.
We should not be near each other.
We're going to decipher who is doing this shit.
It's not.
It's not me.
I can tell you that much.
I feel like I can trust you because you
would have probably killed me already.
Yeah.
I probably would have killed you by now.
That's very true.
Very true.
He just did it.
He did it right in front of us.
OK.
It was Jolly.
I was wrong.
Here's the thing, though.
That was amazing.
He could have faked his death.
But it was him.
He was talking a lot of shit.
I think he faked his death.
I think he's still here.
I'm voting for Kraken.
OK.
It was not.
It definitely wasn't.
It was not Rambo.
I'm telling you right now.
We were literally in the same room.
Yeah, I know.
We could have killed each other easily.
I think we're good.
I think I think it is you.
Yeah.
No, it is simply.
Kraken was telling the truth to me.
It's a bout of confidence that it's not me.
Jolly.
It's Jolly.
It's not looking good.
That was funny, though.
It was good.
I'll think.
Oh, we're good.
We're good.
Let's go.
Good work, everyone.
Hey, the thing is, you have to remember, right?
I was just jamming.
A lot of people like, hey, what was that whole shit with Kraken?
You shouldn't have done that.
I got you to give a real account.
You know what I mean?
Oh, my God.
Wow, you're right.
That's so brave of you to ask me what happened.
That was a.
But when I questioned you, that was a real passionate, real reaction.
That was a real reaction.
You know my baseline.
You know the baseline of what I'm lying.
Exactly.
Failboats saw it.
I ran and screamed because I was like, one of us has got to survive.
But instead of it was you that killed him.
But I was the one that took the bullet.
You could have blamed Kraken.
You guys both could have been like, Kraken, you did it.
You totally could have blamed Kraken.
But it was so clear.
Like, to be fair, yeah, we were both walking together.
You can always tell when somebody's kind of telling the truth.
People have perfected this maybe in this game.
I don't know.
But they're like, what?
They're like, what are you talking?
It's like a real passionate reaction.
You know what I mean?
I think you did it.
Excuse me?
That's how you can tell.
It was just that.
I was just a witness to murder that no one believed.
That's literally all that.
Don't worry, Jolly.
I'm not going to hold you against you.
That was fun.
I was dead, yeah.
I was.
A good detective covers every base.
I don't think I've done it in any other situation.
Did Coney jump back in?
Two other people will jump in.
No.
Yes.
What?
I think I agree.
Yeah.
Get this guy out of here.
Is this one of yours?
This is the best way to, uh.
How do we get this guy out of here?
How did he get the code?
I don't know.
He's dead now.
Yo, he joined so we could see his name, and then he left.
Yeah, what do you think it meant?
Ball fondling.
I don't know.
Like, maybe he's a basketball fan.
Oh, yeah, yeah, yeah.
Or like, movie Labyrinth, where David Bowie does the thing with the balls.
I want that guy banned in every chat.
Every single person streaming right now.
Why are you talking to the vending machine?
That's not a real person on there.
You know that, right?
You know that that's not a other guy.
No, I was just, I was like leaning over.
Oh, fuck.
Like, this is a person in the game?
Oh my god.
Are you able to differentiate the two?
He's got such bad eyesight that he just sees anything vaguely like him.
It looked like it could be a player.
I don't know.
This guy's been real quiet ever since he had anyone in his chat either.
His PC is like, bricking.
It doesn't look like he's going to be able to join.
Yeah.
That's not good.
Are we just going to go with nine or?
Or do we have one more?
I could look for another one to build if you want,
but we can also just keep going with what we got.
Let's go and then we'll see if maybe we can get someone else in here.
I can't believe I got imposter and I fucked the whole thing up.
Ross is playing with Snuffy at the moment.
Oh my god, did I knock a drink over?
What was that?
Oh no, okay.
Mike doesn't have VR, but all right, let's just go.
We'll figure it out as we go.
Hey, if we need a tent, we can get my buddy Ball Fondler.
I don't I don't know about that.
Anybody but him, Joel.
No, you don't.
You don't want that guy in there.
Everyone's sick.
Jerma's sick.
What the fuck is going on?
Oh, a task immediately.
I just couldn't speak.
Already a sabotage.
Okay.
Wait, which way is it?
Yeah, two.
Okay, okay.
I can't do this.
I don't know.
I don't know my shape.
You have to press the button.
The pattern.
I got it.
It's the zero plus.
Get out of the way.
I'll do it.
There I got it.
I got it.
Okay.
That's what your Russian got us.
Someone's died.
Wait, you're not dead.
That's weird.
He's a zombie.
Why is his name red?
What?
That means your name's red.
Wait, whose name is red?
Wait, why is he red?
Somebody donated money and it was very loud.
Congratulations.
I think that we should skip the vote.
Why did you have die and now you are alive?
I don't know.
Why is my name red?
Hey, fellas, I think we should skip the vote.
Somebody said we should skip.
Wait, can I repeat?
Someone said we should skip.
Yeah, we should skip.
Boy, I did hear that.
I think skip but plus one sus to jolly.
Yeah, that was weird.
I swear to God.
I will kill you again in a very public setting.
I bet we will.
Come again one more time.
Excuse me.
What do you mean by that?
All right, I got to take the sub goal off my stream
before I fucking puke.
What?
Okay, wait, how do you do it?
This ship is falling apart.
Match the pattern on the note.
Every single person game.
What the fuck is going on?
Wait, what's going on?
Get rid of him.
Guys, we're supposed to report dead bodies.
You can't just keep on reporting this guy
because he's alive.
I'm going to the emergency room.
Fuck this.
I think we need to save him.
We have to save him.
Stop calling the media.
Just because you want this guy to be dead.
I'm sucking us all out of here.
Please.
Why don't we follow fail vote?
Yeah, follow me.
I want to die as well, but I don't make a big deal of it.
Okay.
Is this the first time too?
We'll find the body with fail vote.
I'm going to skip the vote.
All right.
We follow you.
No, but there's a sabotage going on.
We can't waste time.
Follow me.
It's at the sabotage.
Jolly, you go first.
Jolly goes first in front of everybody.
Yeah, report your own body, Jolly.
Just stay right there.
Every single person get over here.
This is Ball Fondler's fault.
I know it is.
Let him go first.
That's how we do it.
Okay.
Where's the body?
Can any...
Oh my God.
No, there's no body.
Somebody could kill right now and we would never know.
Are you recording this?
Yes, I am.
Okay, good.
So you can show us later.
It's probably...
Yes, I can probably.
It's gotta be glitch.
Yes, yeah, probably.
Okay.
I saw my own body earlier, which was really out of body experience.
Yeah, it messed me up.
Fuck.
This game is like...
I'm still recovering SCP.
Yeah, therapy.
Yeah, therapy can't even kill that one.
Damn it.
All right, cool.
You gonna go potty?
Okay.
I voted for myself.
Yeah, how you doing over there?
You holding up?
Just so goddamn stressful.
I'm gonna put my hand on your hand.
We're gonna calm you down here.
Hold my hand, hold my hand, hold my hand.
Hold my hand.
Who's talking?
Oh, it's you.
Failboat, failboat.
Hello.
Okay, you ready?
Hold my hand.
There you go.
Patty cake, patty cake.
Bake me a cake.
Oh, my bad.
Hey, put your hand...
Ready?
Come on, come on.
We can do it.
Chuck.
You know that game, the slap game game?
Ready?
Yo, yo, slap game, slap game.
I think we should feed this warning.
Okay, okay, okay.
Go, go ahead, go ahead.
I'm gonna trust you.
We have a job to do, guys.
Okay, okay, take it serious, buddy.
Okay, let's go this way.
All right, let's...
Everybody run in the same direction.
Fucking...
Come on, everybody, let's go.
Is that all of us?
Don't forget anybody.
Are we all...
Are we gonna do it or...
I got this, I got it, I got it.
I think we got it.
I got it, I got it, I got it.
I did it, I did it.
No, we need the other one.
We got it.
Yeah, that's true.
Hey, we did it.
Good job, everyone.
Good job, good job.
We're good, we're good.
How about we just do our job?
We can just actually do our job.
You're working well.
There's a couple in here.
Let's just do the tasks.
I'll do this one here.
What is this one?
This one is downloading a little bit of data here.
That's pretty cool.
What's going on with you?
I don't know, man.
You are in a weird spot over there.
I don't know what's weird about the spot I'm in.
No, it's a real task.
It's a real task.
Why can't I speak to my friend from the corner of a wall?
My tasks are complete.
What about yours?
Finishing up here.
OK.
Being weird on purpose, I think.
Why can't I be weird on purpose?
I'm going to be weird on purpose.
Is he actually dead?
What?
I'm real.
I can't report any bodies.
I think we may need to remake the lobby.
Let's kill Philbo.
That way that'll fix it.
I don't think I have any defense on this one.
I blame Ball Fondler for this whole thing.
He's dead, people.
Yeah, we just gotta play ball fondler for this.
He's having premonitions.
It was Ball Fondler.
Guys, I can see the future.
He's going to be dead in admin in 30 seconds.
First Pink's going to die.
Then Red's going to die.
It's going to be Ranboo.
And then it's going to be Char.
And then it's going to be me.
See ya.
Get him off the fucking ship.
Get him out of here.
It's so sad.
Goodbye, premonition man.
Who walked up to me at the end?
Premonition man, that sounds like a good movie title was.
It's time to sleep with the fishes.
That was pretty good.
Except for the space dirt.
Whatever it is.
That's space dirt.
Stars?
That's not what space dirt is.
Jerma, you gotta vote.
Kill me.
Stars are going to space dirt.
Okay.
Yeah, you just get rid of Philbo.
That's fine.
Alright, goodbye everybody.
Hopefully I don't see any more bodies in hell.
Goodbye.
You know what would be so awesome?
If we had an Among Us emergency meeting button cake for my birthday.
Well, he's gone so everything now should be great.
Okay.
No, no, no, no.
Stop.
I'm just, I'm not, it's not me.
I'm just fucking around.
I'm trying to scare everybody.
I'm just, I would have done it already.
You can't be doing this man.
I would have done it already.
Oh yeah, yeah.
What's stopping you now?
It's pitch black.
Because I'm one of your crew friends.
Okay.
No, I just was doing that to freak out.
You know, like Vinny.
You know what I mean?
Hi, I'm just playing.
I was doing my task guys.
What did you do?
What happened?
I'm going, I'm out of here.
I'm going to do my, there's another person in this room.
Okay.
How do I even do this?
What, how do I do this one?
How do I do this mission?
Somebody can help me with this one?
What's going on?
Do I have to stand still?
I don't, I don't, somebody, somebody has to help me do this one.
Hey fellas, can somebody help me do this?
This is really suspicious.
But can somebody help me do this?
Yeah, what's up?
I just don't know.
I don't understand how this one works and I mean it.
Okay, which one?
This, this one over here with like the thing with this.
You just have to not move.
You have to stand completely still.
I'll watch your back.
Hey, don't worry.
No one's coming in here.
He, you're going to watch my back.
You, Vinny, Vinny, you watch Kraken's back.
Somebody watch Kraken's back and somebody watch Vinny.
Hey, don't come in.
We got a task in here, guys.
You got to be chill.
Okay.
Don't cross the little line.
How does it, how does it?
I think you just put your finger on it and then you just stay still for like 15 seconds.
Hey, don't cross the line.
There's this is a no entry.
Okay.
No entry.
I'm sorry.
Okay.
Got it.
All right.
Hey, where's the Kraken going?
I trust you now because it could, you could have done that.
He said that he was going to go over there to check to see if there was a body anywhere
because he doesn't trust me.
So yeah.
Well, where's his, where's his body now?
Where's his body now?
I don't know where his body is.
One, two, three, four, five.
I didn't make him a body.
Hey, we're just doing a group call over here.
He told people to not follow him, which I thought was.
I mean, look at the map.
Kraken, Kraken still alive.
Kraken.
He has to be.
Yeah, no, Kraken has to be still alive.
Oh, oh, Kraken.
Where did you go?
All right.
Hello.
There are two dead bodies.
Yeah.
I saw you go in there to report them.
Well, no, no, no.
You're right.
I saw your report.
Did you hear the escalation of the voice?
Did you hear that?
The rest of us were together.
Do you remember that entire show about the guy that like.
Kraken.
Tell people lied.
Kraken, I trusted you.
Would I really walk in alone to a room and report bodies if I did the killing?
What was the name of that show?
Uh.
That's a strategy.
Yeah, it is a strategy.
What do you mean?
No, he's like, you see, you see what you did with the eye there.
You see what you did with your eyeball there.
It was, it was an entire, they made like four or five seasons of this show.
I think it's not.
What was it called?
Jerma.
Lie to me.
I was with Jerma.
Sorry, he's talking to himself.
I don't think it's you because when I walked up behind you, you genuinely were scared when
there was someone else in the room when it was troubling you, which means I think it's
most likely you and you.
I think it's these two guys.
I can vouch.
I can vouch for like 30 minutes.
It's not jolly.
I can vouch.
I literally followed him.
I was about to came from somewhere that no one else was.
I traced your footsteps backwards, right?
And then I found a body with the two dead bodies.
Jolly was with us almost the whole time.
Came from the navigation panel.
I didn't even go to down.
You were there the whole time.
Yeah.
I never said where the bodies were.
I think it's him.
That's where you, that's where you were.
We saw you walk in there.
Yeah, that's where the bodies were.
And I think you fucking left them there.
I don't.
How can I kill two people?
You and the other guy.
Oh, I don't know.
I'm voting for, I'm sorry.
I'm sorry.
I don't think it's me.
I mean, you were, you were around.
I'm suspicious of you.
Yeah.
How certain are you?
It's not you.
Yep.
Yes.
Well, there you go.
I'm sorry.
I doubted you guys.
Yeah.
Thank you.
I can.
Listen, I know you went off and I, I.
You weren't moving.
You could have been in the menu.
You were in the menu.
He was the only one not moving.
He was in the menu.
He was in the menu, I think.
I'm still in the menu.
Yeah.
He's probably doing sabotage.
One sabotage.
I'll get the one.
Oh, shit.
Oh, God.
I got to get this one.
Did we get it?
Oh, don't leave me alone.
Don't leave me alone.
Did you come out of that, Vin?
No, I just fixed the sabotage.
He did.
He did fix the sabotage.
She did.
Okay.
What is wrong with you?
I'm chill, guys.
Sorry.
I panicked.
I just, I just.
Amazing.
I jumped to conclusions.
Holy shit.
Really, really nice of you to join us.
Nice of you to join us.
Hey, yes.
Yeah, where were you, huh?
Literally, everybody that is still alive is in this room.
It is nice to join you.
Yeah.
Where did Vinny go?
Let's show him together.
So I'm here, I'm doing my tasks.
I'm trying to get us to windows.
I got to do my tasks, too.
Wait, hold on.
Hey.
Does he have guns?
You got a chance.
Hey, how's it going?
Might as well take it.
Thank you very much.
Might as well take it right now.
Thank you very much for vouching for me before.
I appreciate it.
Go for it.
Let's see it.
Come on.
Do it.
Do it, then.
Come on.
Do it.
That wouldn't be right.
The comedic timing is all off.
See, why don't you do it?
Oh, god damn it.
I told you.
I knew it.
Somebody find me.
This is awful.
The comedic timing.
Oh, my god.
Well, he did it.
He did do it.
I got it.
And oh, they're going to know.
They're going to know.
What were the loos?
Did we get it?
They got it.
Oh, my god.
They actually got it.
Where is everybody?
I can't go that way.
Am I just trapped here?
How do I get out of here?
Oh, to be me, man.
I really don't want to be me.
I just taunted him.
I just want to.
I walked up to him when I was like me.
I was like, why don't you fucking do it?
I was like, dude, already.
And he did it.
Oh, I want to listen in here.
Yeah.
He's just quiet.
He's not even speaking.
He's got chocolate all over his face.
He ate the whole cake.
They're not even looking.
He's got chocolate all over his face.
He ate the whole cake and no one's even looking.
He ate the whole cake.
Yeah, it's a 3v1 right now.
To get to the task, which is a fair thing to do.
But to be fair, it seems more like they're just all arguing.
He doesn't have to do anything and he'll win.
He wins.
Yeah, he's good.
He wouldn't have to do anything.
He's causing everyone to.
Oh, my god.
You got it.
He's going to win.
I can't fucking believe it.
I missed like half of that conversation
He was in the fucking menu when we were walking that time.
He didn't leave the room.
Kill someone.
I got locked out.
I can't believe it.
God damn it.
I'm turning this off.
That was funny for an hour.
Just telling you to move.
Why am I still dead?
Why do I still have ghost sounds?
I can't believe I taunted you and everything.
The best part is you were sitting there the whole time.
They were arguing back and forth for like 10 straight minutes.
And you're just going like this.
You guys didn't even ask him a question.
You didn't even ask him a question.
He may have come from my neck of the woods here.
All right, new lobby.
What happened?
The game crashed?
The game crashed.
Oh my god, it's so funny.
I gotta get to the menu.
Where's the menu?
No menu?
No access to the menu?
I think I have to restart the game.
Oh, no, we're good.
Okay.
Be able to connect.
All right.
All right, I gotta put the screen off for a sec.
Because I don't want you to see the lobby code.
I did that last time.
Okay, give me one sec.
How's everybody doing?
Oh my god, there's like 46,000 people here.
I gotta play Among Us more often.
All right, let me please do the sus face.
You got it.
That's actually what it was.
That was actually the face.
I think we'll make it.
They're making a new lobby.
Lobby is currently going up.
Give me one more second.
It looks good.
Just making sure the stream looks good.
All right, joining the lobby now.
And he's gonna memorize it.
Is that a...
Yeah.
Okay.
You guys can't see, right?
No.
Okay.
Is that correct?
I believe that is correct.
And...
Hey, I think...
Okay.
I had to leave because everybody was still in death.
Like death.
Oh, yeah, yeah.
Yeah.
Oh, what the hell?
We have some weird like...
The colors are changed.
Oh, no.
My god.
You're red now.
You're blue now.
Oh, I'm blue.
You're blue.
Sorry if it's loud.
Twitter blue.
I'm blue.
I'm back.
I can't believe it happened.
Eight dollars.
All right.
I'm ready to be the imposter.
Hey, can you guys hear me?
You have seven people in here?
Can you hear me?
Yes.
Okay, good.
Thank god.
One, two, three, four, five, six.
I see six people.
Who's the seventh?
All right.
Eight people.
What the hell?
I don't see anyone.
Yeah, we're back.
Oh, there we go.
There we go.
Oh, I'm pink now.
The whole world is so...
No, that's correct.
This is weird.
I'm your color now.
Oh, this is weird.
Yeah, it is.
You're me.
I've graduated.
It's a bit weird.
You're playing with streamers you don't know too well.
Me and Ross were playing Amogus VR in VRChat.
We were absolutely playing with randos.
I'll tell you what, though.
I know Gascan.
I know Liam.
I know ZamSire.
I know Failboat.
I've met Failboat in person a bunch.
Kraikin's a good friend.
I know almost everyone here pretty well.
There's a couple dudes I don't know.
I really wish you could do finger guns.
Like he started to turn.
No.
All right.
Wait.
Vinny.
There we go.
Yo.
Hi.
Hello.
Oh, that works.
We combined the two.
I'm here.
We're missing anyone else from the lobby.
Wait, you got finger guns on?
Yeah.
You combined thumbs up and points.
Oh, is this the TF2 Scout?
Nice.
Oh, wait.
I don't want that.
I mean, it's cool.
It's cool.
But I don't want to.
Oh, I see what you're doing.
It's cool.
So point and thumb.
Thumbs up and point.
Oh, there we go.
That's it.
There we go.
Nah, I'm staying.
I'm staying.
How do you unlock unlocked stuff?
Don't move.
Who's moving?
I swear to God.
There's the DEA.
They've got a gun.
Hey, I don't want to be in trouble, man.
Bring out the gun.
Fucking childish.
Hey, hey.
We're out there good.
Are you guys ready?
Hands up.
Hey.
Guns are not childish.
I'll have you know that I'm being completely serious right now.
I simply will shoot you.
OK, I'll see.
I'll see Vinny.
Begin.
Yeah, I'm sitting here.
I hope you guys are ready, because I'm
going to get the imposter this time, and then you're all in fucking trouble.
Dan.
Hello?
I don't see Vinny.
Dan, can you hear me?
I hear you.
I hear everyone.
Yes, I'm sure you can see me.
Make sure you can see me.
Hold on.
Guys, can everyone see me?
My name is Ray.
Yes, I can see you.
I can see you, buddy.
It's just Dan.
He's glitched again.
Failboat.
What?
What are you waiting for?
No, don't do this.
What are you glitching about?
Why is he?
Uh-oh.
Don't press it.
I swear to God, don't press it.
You can't see me.
No, I hear nothing.
Everyone, get away from there.
If you hit the button, you're wasting a very valuable resource.
I'm going to go do what I'm supposed to be doing.
I'm trying to join our magic trick.
I'm totally blind right now.
Are you going to kill me?
Head, disappear.
I'm going to go this way.
This game is fucking glitching.
OK, crewmates.
I have the back of my freaking visor with you.
OK?
Are you guys ready to do some tasks?
Let's go to navigation.
Stop.
What was that?
Guys, I swear I just heard somebody pull a blade out.
No, I think I'm fine.
I think I'm fine.
I'm just weird.
OK, I'm going to do this task.
I'm alone, though.
I don't like that.
I'm going to get done quick.
Quick, quick, quick, quick.
Don't.
I'm going to...
If somebody comes in here...
OK, how do I do this?
I got to...
How does this work?
What do I have to do?
How does this one work?
Do I have to get the pizza?
How does this work?
What do I do?
Oh.
There's no immediate issue.
Hello.
Hey.
Hey, we never actually finished the slap game before, by the way.
Yeah.
You want to do it now?
Yeah, let's do this.
Actually, we can't see our hands.
It doesn't really work.
Oh, OK.
What's there?
I'm just getting away.
I don't know.
I don't trust anybody.
He wanted...
Oh, let's do the slap game.
Yeah, let's do the slap game.
AKA, he's going to do it.
And then...
Oh, ha ha.
And he's going to kill me when he does it, right?
Anybody...
Listen, anybody here?
Oh, OK.
I'm going to go do this.
Hello.
Get away from me.
Get away, get away, get away, get away, get away.
Get away, get away.
I'm doing it.
We already did that.
OK, OK.
We just did it.
We're good, we're good.
Yeah, me and Zam.
We're good.
Zam just did it.
OK, excellent.
Excellent.
I vouch for him.
Task complete over here.
One, two, three, four.
There we go.
What?
Oh.
You've been at this task a while, Johnny.
They couldn't see...
Oh, they don't see that I'm fucking this up.
Right, right, right.
They don't know that I'm fucking it up.
What?
I can't...
Uh-oh.
OK.
OK, task her down.
Task her down.
Listen up, everybody.
I was in electrical.
I walked past Vinnie and Charborg.
And then I heard a snap.
And Charborg was dead.
Who else was on the way down to storage?
I don't know.
I literally only saw you two.
You know who it was with you.
It was Failboat.
I've only seen Cry...
It was Failboat?
100% Failboat.
Where?
Behind you.
I can't...
There's no ghost.
There is no...
I can't...
I'm sure this isn't a strategy.
No, I can't tell Phantom.
I don't know where you...
I have no evidence on where you were even standing.
You're calling him a Phantom now?
What's going on?
He doesn't see me.
Wait, can you hear the voice?
Yeah, can you hear a ghost?
I don't...
Can you hear the ghost?
He can hear the dead.
So I don't know, dude.
He's not dead yet.
My personal assessment is...
I can hear you.
You can.
He's over there in the fucking corner, isn't he?
No, I cannot see you.
I assume you're...
Jolly!
Well, I am, but I saw you kill someone.
Come over here.
What is he doing?
All right, Jolly always never says a thing during meetings.
I can't see what you did.
Can we pause this?
I was just doing a little space, the final frontier bit.
Sure.
Yeah?
And how's it going?
Well, my...
What do you know about the body?
It's an intentional strategy from Vin just being physical to the imposter.
I can't lose.
That's the strategy, though.
If you go look out the window while everybody argues,
no one's going to point the finger at you.
Yeah, you're being awfully quiet again.
True.
Crikey, we wanted to say...
Everybody, just hear me out one more time.
Crikey reported the body, but Baleboat was literally right behind him.
I swear, Crikey and Baleboat...
Please vote Baleboat.
I follow Crikey.
Believe me.
I trust Vinny.
I can't believe you as much as I can see you.
I can't believe it, man.
Excuse me?
Oh, brother.
That's three.
That might be enough.
Later.
Oh, you got it.
Got it.
Nice job.
You sure you didn't know who was behind you?
No, I literally didn't see anyone else.
Jolly was following you.
He was ready to follow me.
Incredibly important.
Jolly just went by himself that way and didn't say a goddamn word.
He literally walked through to me.
He didn't say goodbye.
Didn't even say goodbye.
And what do you know?
What do you know?
That's a sabotage.
Who the hell would I wonder?
Let's call the meeting a meeting.
Yeah.
No, we have to get the sabotage first.
Oh, shit.
Oh, fuck.
Yeah, he took off.
Zam's got this one.
Zam, you got this, right?
I don't know what this means.
Oh, shit.
We might not have enough time.
Okay, we got it.
We got it.
Jeremy, you doing all right?
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
If I die, just let me know.
I'm telling you, Jolly walked away by himself.
Okay.
So, all right.
I'll keep an eye on it.
I'm not the imposter.
Jeremy, do me a favor.
When you go to this, can you click it?
Yeah.
Oh, my God.
Criken.
Okay.
Oh, my God.
Here's my counter-argument to you all.
If I was in a room with Criken and Zam,
would I not have killed you immediately for a fucking laugh?
No, because then Zam would have reported you.
Yeah, do you think I care?
I wouldn't have killed you.
You should have been out.
There's only one imposter left.
You wouldn't have done that.
Criken, did you not see the round where I was friends with Liam
and I just ran up and murdered some dude in Cold Blood for fun?
Look, you're a loose cannon.
I get that.
I then didn't die because you all voted for Liam for some stupid fucking reason.
Explain to us all in this room right now why you left first
and you didn't say a gosh darn word.
Bro, my hands are so big.
How come you left?
How come you left first?
Criken, it's kind of a sensory overload.
Yeah, I was going to say.
Actually, a good answer.
Fuck.
God damn it.
Look, we were as soon as Jolly left, there was a sabotage.
We all went to go fix it.
Jolly, as we were leaving to hit this button, locks the door
and both of us were stuck inside with him.
To be fair, you can lock the door from the map.
So the imposter could have been anywhere to do that.
Oh, you can lock the door from the map.
Convenient timing.
I don't know.
But also, when you walked off and then sabotage happened,
It also could have been somebody just standing in the group.
I also think it's Jolly.
We've got people to burn.
It's OK.
Yeah, exactly.
Exactly.
Yeah.
Well, I guess my...
Criken, I just got to pay you back from before.
Sorry.
Huh?
Just in case.
He voted on me.
I don't know.
Oh, sorry.
It's Criken.
Oh, OK.
I'm just going to run this way.
Why, bro?
Because I voted on you that one time.
I'm Criken.
Bro, new life rule, OK?
I did all my tasks.
I'm good.
And you reported the body as a strat
because you saw me walk in the room.
It is you who is the imposter.
Oh, wait.
Hold on now.
We can't just jump to a conclusion here.
We haven't even said anything.
I'm going to say, Criken,
it's been nice knowing you, buddy,
but you are the imposter.
What have I done?
I reported the first body and I fucking...
I think we're shutting him out right now.
Maybe you should practice this move.
Practice this one.
And then you voted Jolly.
Well, listen, if it was between you and Jolly
and Jolly was not the imposter,
then it's you who the imposter is.
So I'm voting for you as soon as I can.
100% disagree.
I do not have a single thing to say to you anymore, friend.
Vinny could have killed me,
and we were in a room alone together,
and he could have killed me.
It was literally like a straight minute.
I don't think we are after information.
I reported the first body as soon as I saw it.
And then you report another one.
You are doing 4D chess, bro.
I'm just playing a good fucking crew man.
All right.
Don't give me a thumbs down.
You're lying.
Oh, damn.
I gotta make a decision here.
I think Vinny's playing the long game here,
and he's fucking calling people out
and getting them out one at a time.
You're deflecting.
He could have killed me so many times.
I'm deflecting because my life's on the line,
and you're fucking, you're suddenly throwing me on my bus.
Vinny could have sold out failboats to game chumps,
I don't know.
There is some, your voice is doing a thing there.
It's the same thing that I did when I was telling you
the story about what happened
when I was fucking being chased around.
I'm sorry.
I'm sorry, Kraikin.
If it's not you, then.
It's okay, man.
Your eye twitched.
Gotta go.
All right.
Okay.
Kraikin, if our friendship has been irreparably damaged,
I'd like to apologize.
One more new lobby if I can't see Vinny.
Body language.
All right, where's Vinny?
We both get one.
All right, Vinny.
Okay.
Look, Kraikin.
I still cannot see Vinny.
Hold on, I'm gonna try and re-log.
Let me try and re-log here.
Oh, look at all these, look at all these imposters.
The game is tearing you all apart.
This is for one day only, by the way.
This shit ain't ever coming back.
I wish I could rescind it.
Are we making a new lobby or are we going with this one?
No, we're sticking with this one.
Can you just reach over there?
That's so sus, dude.
Bat chest.
Yeah, and Coney.
Coney, are you back?
Oh, a little bit slurry today.
Well, it's Coney back.
I think he's still streaming.
It says he's still streaming.
I'm really close to the camera.
Vinny, please re-log.
Record the Davey's Grey songs with Red Vox and make them better.
You know what?
What I should have done was just beeline it for Vinny
instead of reporting the body that first one.
Oh, yeah, yeah, yeah.
I, dude, there's, okay.
Him being an actual TF2 spy, like, I was just like,
oh, I'm gonna kill someone and Vinny's like, I've seen it.
Do the imposter dance?
I feel like it's, you point your fingers or something.
It's kind of, it's like a, something like this.
I don't know, probably.
You guys having a good time?
I know I'm not really checking in that often,
but how you guys doing?
You guys having fun?
You guys enjoying yourselves?
Well, enjoy it because it's just getting
fucking torn down tomorrow.
I was just making my stream entertaining by watching yours.
Hey, what?
You're an entertaining guy.
What are we talking about?
I'm entertaining, but I'm also lazy.
That was a weird sound that came out of my mouth.
I'm sorry.
Everyone probably heard it.
I don't have a noise gate on today.
How we looking?
Oh, my God.
That's rude.
Who are we missing right now?
Oh yeah.
Who is who are we missing here?
All right.
You didn't hear that.
Can we harmonize?
Yeah.
Do you know the Beatles?
No, but okay.
So are you, can you do low or can you do high?
I can do low.
I have COVID so I probably can't do highs,
but I can probably do like, what would you call this?
What's that?
That's like a bad song.
No, that's baritone.
Well, no, I'm just saying.
Oh, that's like pretty beautiful.
Do we, can we, can we harmonize?
Can you guys do the dumb thing that I want to do?
Tenor, you're a tenor.
Oh, that is what it is.
You're a tenor.
Yeah.
No, I'm thinking more kind of like, oh, I've got a quest too.
That's beautiful.
That's music and that's called music.
Can you go that low?
My fucking body hurts now.
That's what it sounds like.
Like the summertime out in like the woods.
It's just like fucking frogs.
Frogs and bugs.
Frogs do that.
The frogs when they do sing, you know.
Oh, have you ever listened outside or at like in the summertime in a swampy environment?
Oh, yeah.
I'll go to interview a frog just for you here.
What kind of task are you doing right now?
Um, I'm going, my goal is to go to reactor.
Oh, I'm going to a better use of my time.
Okay.
You got that one more motivated because I'm not overly.
If I'm going to spend time working on music, I'd have to be really interested.
Vinny, did you do that?
I don't fucking understand.
What's going on?
What the fuck?
Oops.
Oh shit.
Where am I?
Okay, there's somebody with you.
All right.
I am currently with Charborg and I just saw Jolly go down through admin.
Protect me while I do my task.
What's your task?
I have to go in here and flip this lever.
You do.
Interesting.
Go and do it.
Thanks.
You're welcome.
I don't know because we're alone together and I don't, I don't know you.
I don't know you, man.
I don't know you.
I'm chill.
All right, stay away, stay at least five feet away from me.
Damn it.
I knew it.
I knew it too.
Wow.
Hey, am I like we get loud when I scream?
I hope not because like I didn't do like a noise gate today.
I hope I'm not like screaming in your ears.
Okay, good.
Sorry.
Oh, I knew it was Charborg.
I was going to call the meeting next time we had the chance.
Yeah, I just lied.
It's scary.
It's so funny because you were like, oh, I'm just doing my task and there's
nothing to do in that room and I was like, wait, didn't that, I don't get it.
And he looked at the screen for like one second and turned around
I pretended to do it.
I pushed a couple imaginary buttons.
I was like, that's like that.
I don't know.
Is that even accurate?
Four out of five.
I was hitting the buttons.
I hit four out of five buttons.
It was zero, zero, zero, zero, zero.
I hit zero, zero, zero, zero.
I cost us the game.
How long have we been playing for?
I feel like time flies when you're the imposter.
Yeah, I think it's been an hour and 50.
Cool.
It's not too much.
We're still missing some people too.
It's eight out of 10.
I think we're missing Zam and...
Are we missing people?
Yeah, Zam's headset died and obviously Coney...
What?
Why does that keep happening?
Because an imposter is making it happen.
We got to fix it.
Otherwise we die.
Oh, okay.
That's the instant win button, basically.
Wait, instant win.
So if that ghost is...
What do you mean?
If you don't fix those things like we didn't before, they just win.
You're not going to kill me, right?
I'm looking for another person so we're not alone together.
Are you doing your tasks, Jerma?
I don't know what...
By the way, get out of here, you imposter.
Just fucking got you, you sus guy.
Got you, motherfucker.
Who died?
I saw...
I turned the corner.
I was standing in the hallway.
I saw Jerma go like this.
I'm going to do a representation.
A reenactment.
A reenactment?
And he killed someone.
What am I, Elmer Fudd?
I did see him run away from the body.
Fucking porcupine.
Run away from the body.
You did run away from the body.
I saw it.
You ran right into me.
I didn't see a body.
I was hoping you would call me to check if I could be like this.
In what room?
I have insane tunnel vision right now.
I don't know how to play the game.
Oh, he doesn't know how to play the game.
It's been an hour and a half.
I just had to ask Vinny.
I just had to ask Vinny before his untimely death.
Oh, the dead body?
You can't get rid of me.
I'm holding on.
I'm not going.
I'm not fucking going.
He doesn't even see a body.
He doesn't even see him.
I ain't going.
I'm not letting go.
You're going to fucking kill me yourselves.
Get him out of here.
Because I'm not letting go.
Hey, guys.
That sounds funny.
OK, so let's skip the vote.
Who knows who it was?
We don't have any idea.
Look at anybody.
I think we should skip.
Fuck this cake.
I don't even want it anymore.
My fucking fifth birthday party was ruined.
Hey, how are you?
I'm not good at this.
Did I do good?
I did hit the ball.
I hit a dribbler back to the pitcher
and I forgot to run to first base.
Oh, we have task, right?
Oh, I was talking to Vinny.
Like, what an idiot.
I can't do.
Oh, I was talking to Vinny right before he died.
I deserve that.
I swear to God, I swear to God.
Did you hear my explanation of what happened?
No, but what I did hear was you,
as you were stabbing me,
you were saying really bizarre,
like demented, like serial killer shit.
So that was cool.
What was your explanation, Jerma?
They asked, I mentioned how I had just talked to you.
I was like, oh, when I just talked to him
and they were like, what do you mean just talk to him?
Like, you were in the room with him.
I was the only one in the room with you.
That's like when I said I walked past your corpse
when I first started playing the game.
It's not a good strat.
Oh, he got him.
Yeah, I got killed.
You know, I try my best to defend myself
by screaming as loud as I could,
but it didn't work out in the end.
Oh man, this is funny.
Sorry to hear that.
I will say your meat bone is particularly strong.
Look at this thing.
Oh my God.
Wait, I can see myself.
Wait, I'm going to pull myself back together.
Do you kidding me?
This is a marketing scheme here.
How have they not done this?
Popsicle with the bone.
The bone's the stick and it's an Among Us character.
I would not want anybody.
I wouldn't want to see people eating that.
That would gross me out.
You know, like at the Boardwalk in New Jersey,
they sell bootleg Amoguses.
It's real Amogus, but it's bootleg companies
that probably don't have the rights to sell them.
Jerma, we could sell the Popsicles.
Could we?
I don't think we can.
What do you mean, like lift up?
It's just a shape.
It would just be clean with a bone.
Yeah, you should actually get like a ham,
like a big ham leg with a bone sticking out
and just carve it to look like an Among Us.
That way, it's like a little more immersive.
Do they have any idea?
I said the impression that you did earlier,
but that was so goddamn funny.
Would it be you?
Which one?
Jerma?
Oh, I was with Crockett until we were trying to do O2.
Wait, where was the body again?
He walked by me like this and he was like,
Who'd have it?
Other ghosts.
Sorry, I did a porky to take impression.
That was perfect.
That could have been me talking.
Is that Jermex as a chat member?
No, that's the sus guy.
Yeah, that's a different person today.
Okay, okay, I'm not gonna be funny and vote on four.
Because if we vote on four and we win, we just die.
This is not a little funny social game.
Are they gonna vote?
Who are they voting for?
We can...
Ah, yeah, yeah, let's be social.
We don't need to use the game's features to determine...
No, they're not gonna get it.
I can't believe it.
What, what, what, what, what, what, what?
Where was the body?
I thought we were trying to get last thing.
No, no, no, what was that about?
I can't believe this.
Voting vacuum of space is not a good party game.
It's not a funny game.
I'm not playing...
No, it was not a party game.
It was a valid tactic.
I was trying to make sure that we don't die.
I did that.
That's funny.
I just pressed that.
I did that.
It was me.
Finally.
Oh, the official sussicle.
Oh, this verse is dead.
So if somebody dies here, can they see who even does it?
Or could it be anybody in this, you know, five feet of each other?
If he kills right now,
would it be like somebody in the room or would they see it?
They can't see.
Oh, they can, they can, they can.
Tick tock.
Here comes the reactor.
Oh, he's...
Yep.
He knows it.
Oh, that's tricky.
He's a tricky...
He's a tricky motherfucker.
He really is.
I feel sorry for him right now.
Yeah, there's still a lot of tasks to do, too.
This is scary.
If you want to be the...
If you're the person, I'll give you...
I'll give you it now, right now.
If you're the killer, I'm gonna hide in the corner.
I'm gonna hide in the corner.
Let's make it...
Oh, no.
Yeah, this is bad.
This is gonna end up...
All right, go ahead.
If you're the person, you'll never find me here.
You'll never find me here.
Kill me.
Oh, no, no, no.
Don't do it, don't do it, don't do it.
Oh, well, I guess they found us here.
Hey, what's up?
Uh, I'm gonna...
I was trying to give...
Okay.
Who's doing this?
Oh, well, I guess...
He's being so obvious.
Who's doing this?
Yeah, it's Jerma.
It's Jerma?
Jerma's dead.
He was the other imposter.
I'm just pressing buttons, man.
I'm sticking around back here, though.
Oh, you catch up.
You can get that kill right there
and turn around and run.
What's the strategy here, by the way?
My streams, that's pretty awesome.
Okay, now they're splitting up.
Oh, this is it right here.
This is it right here.
You can do it right now.
I think he's doing the long con.
He's doing the vote.
He's trying to vote her.
Oh.
Oh, it's diabolical.
Wait, did you shut that?
Did I?
No, I don't think so.
Can I do that?
I think you do it through the map.
Oh, I can do it.
Jolly, Jolly, I will tell you,
your audio is a little bit low.
You're very soft spoken.
And I think maybe if you had a little bit more volumage,
I would have heard you.
All right.
No, I did.
Hey, there's someone on the other side.
I thought you were doing it.
There's someone here.
Who's in there?
It's a name.
It's me.
I see Robbo live.
Great.
You're cool.
Hello.
This is getting out of hand, man.
I won.
I had to give them a chance.
I'm like, I'm going to separate.
Oh, yeah.
Okay, I'll be with you.
I'll be with you.
Oh, boy.
No, this is the end here.
Can they solve it?
This is the end right here.
No, God.
I think it's because we can't throw our health pack.
Is it open when we go through?
Where did he go?
He's right there.
Oh, that's it.
Emergency meeting.
That's game.
Yeah, that has a bit.
I was like, just kill me so that way it can be interesting.
I love that you put yourself in such an impossible-to-find spot,
and then they both just walked in.
He's very good.
He's very methodical.
Drinking our beers, looking at them play.
Yeah.
Do I look like I know for the JPEGs?
Oh, I mean, I think Liam may have done it.
I think Liam may have done it.
I'm not sure.
I have a narrow urethra.
Liam!
I mean, I have.
He's got orange and cake over him.
Oh, thank you.
There we go.
Sorry.
That was a good one.
You did it, buddy.
That was the most stressed I've ever been in my entire life.
That was, like, really close.
Good job.
There we go.
I chose the wrong person to kill.
I definitely chose the wrong person to kill.
But then again, you two were together the whole time.
It was impossible for me to get rid of anybody else.
I was like, I'm just going to break away from the group to give it to you.
Yeah, I know it could have been you.
Yeah, oh god, no.
I should have went for you as soon as I had the chance.
Oh, that was such a good game.
That was actually a good game.
Thank you for the sabotages.
That was really helpful.
Yeah.
I was pressing buttons.
I was pressing buttons for you.
You were, yeah.
Let me just check and see if anyone's rejoining.
I'm a part of a wide network.
Yeah.
Oh, we got someone back.
I have a portable charger hooked up to my headset now.
Oh, hell yeah.
Welcome back, shit.
What headset are you in?
You played a great game, Liam.
That was, like, fantastically good.
You kept us guessing until the very last second.
That was great.
Yeah, I was like, OK, if we're all moving together,
it's a four-person unit, it's not fun.
I'm bad at this game, so that means it's still a nine.
I wanted to step away and be like, all right,
if you kill me, it's going to get real funny real fast.
Damn it.
My chat likes you a lot.
It was so, no, you were there.
You were together, and then the bite was calling.
It was like, if he's there, it's definitely you.
It was like, ah!
That was so funny.
Yeah, I love that.
I saw both of you guys.
That just tasted like a rubber tire.
That was weird.
Probably not a reason to do that.
That was a good game.
It was a great Among Us game, guys.
Some games of Among Us, thumbs up, thumbs up.
Some great, high quality Among Us games happening.
Wait, are we doing another one?
Are we all done?
Yeah.
Yeah, I want to do a couple more.
OK.
How do you turn that option off, chat member?
This game is really good.
I actually played this game in VR.
Hey, you guys want to break it in one of these?
Yes, yes!
I'm down to play more.
My chat said something like, if you could turn the option off
so that dead people don't know who the imposter is,
like, you have no idea how to edit that.
It's in the lobby.
Tools, I guess.
Lobby options.
Probably under match, whoever's hosting.
Who's in here?
In match, it just says leave game.
There's a Big Dipper.
Oh, OK.
What a wonderful view.
There actually is a constellation over here.
What is that?
Oh, is there?
You have to be the lobby leader.
All right, never mind.
Oh, there is!
I know, it's one for real.
Hey, hey, hey.
OK.
I think that might be the red imposter.
You know what I'm saying?
That might be the red imposter.
What is Robert E. imposter?
Goster.
I think that's Goster Moe.
Yes.
Someone in my chat said I'm surprised he's not playing with Jerma.
What is it?
Someone in my chat just said I'm surprised he's not playing with Jerma.
That is surprising.
I mean, who's this guy?
No, he's not feeling that well.
Yeah.
Yeah, he's not feeling good, chat member.
He's a little under the weather.
Yo, it's been cruder every time.
Every time.
All right, guys, I think there's an imposter on my list.
I'm just going to go this way.
You, that was weird.
You creeped up on me.
And I'm about to fucking do an emergency meeting.
I'm about to do an emergency meeting.
I'm telling you right now.
You step any closer, I'm going to press it.
You step any closer, I'm going to press this button.
I'm just being honest.
God damn it!
Did I get it?
Did I press it?
What happened, Jerma?
No, no, no, no, no, no.
Don't let him talk first because he's going to sound much smarter than me
and it's going to fuck everything up.
Don't let him talk.
No, no, no, seriously.
You were in the room with me.
All right, go ahead, go ahead.
Hold on a minute.
Jolly, what were you doing?
Why didn't you leave?
You were in the room and you were in the room.
I need everyone to listen, please.
And I walked this way and there was...
I turned around, crank and jump scared me.
Okay, Jolly.
No one's listening.
I'm listening.
Okay.
You know what?
You're not listening.
We're looking directly at you.
Okay, all right, okay, okay.
It's my birthday, everyone quiet.
So, by the way, can I just say...
No, this is...
No, no, we have 47 seconds.
There's only 40 seconds.
Thank you.
Yay!
Okay, thank you.
Hey, I gotta make my wish.
I gotta make my wish.
No, I gotta make a wish.
So, my wish is Criken followed me and he was behind me.
No, stop singing.
No, stop talking.
Stop it.
It's my birthday.
My underwear just came down.
I think my underwear just fell off.
Okay, listen.
My underwear came down.
Listen.
Stop.
Criken followed me.
I can't even explain what happened.
Criken, Criken, Criken, Criken, Criken.
No, no, what have you done?
Press it again, press it again.
Everyone calm down.
Please press it again.
Press this fucking button again.
Don't press it, don't press it.
What do you mean, your underwear?
Oh, God, we can't press it.
We got a picture.
He's him.
Everybody follow Criken.
I'm not kidding.
It was Criken.
I'm telling you.
The one you've done had...
The one you've done I think is the funniest fucking audio bite.
I'm telling you right now.
Criken followed me.
And you guys are saying about a great work.
I fixed it.
We all sent me pictures.
I did, I did, I did.
I did see him fixing.
Oh, my God.
Are you happy?
What's going on?
Is that a no or...
Got my eye on you.
I can see that.
Now, if you don't mind, I got some tasks to do, okay?
Somebody follow him.
I got some tasks to do.
All right.
You know, I also got some tasks to do.
I think I'm gonna do them.
Oh, we're doing funny noises, cool.
Ah, that's fun.
That's not what that sound one's...
That doesn't sound like that one.
He's faking it.
Oh, my God.
It's a fake sound.
You're doing a fake sound.
I'm singing Happy Birthday when you press an emergency meeting next time.
I'm doing a real sound.
Damn.
Hey, hey, hey.
Wait, what?
Oh, that's impossible.
That's a no.
It's green.
Wait, what happened?
You.
This green.
This green right here.
I didn't see that.
I turned around and I just saw you.
We have two dead guys.
Why did he do that to me?
We have two dead.
Why did he do that?
Oh, Jesus.
Wait, you weren't there.
I just see you like looking like somewhere else.
Or was that you?
No, it was me.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no.
I was in the little levers.
No, listen.
I don't know who to believe.
I didn't see anyone.
Why are we?
I didn't see that.
Happy birthday to you.
No, it's not my birthday.
It's your birthday.
Is it your birthday?
It's not my birthday.
No, it has to be him.
Silence in the lobby.
This has to be a room.
It was it was just Charbork.
It was Charbork.
Like literally like straight up.
Not even joking.
Look at that.
I trust you.
Implicitly.
Seriously.
A hundred percent.
Okay.
He turned.
He turned after killing and it was so obvious.
Someone is dead on a birthday.
I it has to be either.
It has to be one of you two.
I understand that.
I didn't see anything.
Vote for Charbork.
And then if it's not Charbork.
If it's not Charbork, then it's me.
Then vote for me next time.
Then it's you.
Exactly.
A hundred percent.
Just don't vote for me.
I didn't do anything.
But you did.
I didn't.
And on someone's birthday too.
I don't know who's at this point.
Why are we doing this?
I'm confused.
If it's not him.
There he goes.
See.
Now you can trust me.
You have to trust me.
And I don't know what Kraken was doing.
Because he was like following me in the beginning.
And he pressed the button.
I didn't even press the button.
Weird guy.
Weird guy up here.
Weird orange guy is being weird over here.
What do you mean?
Orange is being weird.
Whoever can hear me.
Orange is being really weird.
Orange is at.
I could kill you right now.
I could do it right now.
You made me turn.
You made me turn around.
I don't know which one is next.
And the Simon says.
Oh.
Just focus.
Wait.
This one.
Nope.
I got it wrong.
Okay.
It was down.
Fuck.
It's just the children's can do this.
Clutch up.
Are you kidding me?
What the fuck?
My controller died.
And someone killed this man behind me while I was fixing it.
I'm telling you right now it's orange.
The only one I thought was a little suspicious.
So I got nothing.
It can't be.
It can't be him.
It can't be me.
No.
I did.
Liam you were trailing behind us.
I know but you did this.
This is what you did.
Everyone look.
This is what he did.
He went like this.
He went.
That's exactly what he did.
And that's fucking sus.
There it is.
Got him.
Someone has died and you're laughing.
Someone has died.
Four people have died and you're laughing.
Are you telling me a man just happens to fall like that?
Do you realize how serious the situation is?
He orchestrated it.
It's everyone's birthday today.
It's five people's birthday today and you're laughing.
Go ahead and vote for me after.
If it's not him then don't do it next time.
Vote for me next time.
Wait you know it's not you.
I know it's not you.
There's no reason to vote for you.
You're good.
You'll always be slipping Liam.
And...
Easy game.
It's honestly an easy game.
It's just that easy.
Charlie forgot about you.
Oh my god.
I didn't run under the bus once.
What was that?
Yeah we won.
I just saw someone to kill.
I was just fucking with you.
Oh it's Charlie.
I mean it's so easy.
And you pressed the button too so that's why it was like no way man.
You pressed it so then it's like I didn't press it.
And I was trying to fix it.
I pressed it and you immediately start like fucking monologuing about how it's not you.
And it's like the most suspicious thing possible.
I'm so bad at this.
You know what?
A pretty good way of running that.
I guess.
That's a good way to go.
I'm gonna hold on.
This is great.
No this is fun.
Also I said before to Zam.
Jerma is the trickiest innocent person I've ever fought.
I'm tangled.
He really is.
On that note let me explain how I...
He's the genuine sus guy.
You managed to make it reality.
Oh no.
Because Jerma is funny.
Well no I mean hey when you walk like this...
That was so funny.
I love the fingers.
I know I know.
It was just completely sus.
I'm down to play more if you are.
Sticking out of your sussy belly.
I wish I never said that.
Oh I don't think that's a hand.
I wish you didn't either.
I'll do a couple more.
No.
Yeah I mean we need ball fondler.
Oh thank god.
Oh thank god I'm blank.
Once again.
I'm gonna go this way.
Okay so I'm gonna go...
Yeah I'll do this.
This one's taking a long time.
What the fuck?
All right I got that done.
Jesus.
Speak.
Speak if you're here.
Even though I just charted it I guess it's good to you know redo my work.
Exactly I just may have course corrected for you all over here.
Yeah yeah.
I did my task over there.
Okay there we go.
Beautiful.
That's good.
Is this one done?
Congratulations.
Thank you.
What's the vent do?
Wait why did you just look at that and then turn around?
He just went in the vent.
Oh my god he actually did.
He actually did.
Oh my god.
Report it.
No one will believe you.
Okay.
He just said no one will believe you.
You idiot.
You dummy.
You big dummy.
I was there too.
What are you doing with the little side bucket thing?
He went in the vent too.
He vented.
Who me?
Don't worry Zam.
I looked over.
You were definitely doing a task.
Wait was he the one that vented or was there a different man?
I think he vented.
Wait.
Oh shit.
Yeah definitely.
Wait who was in the room with us?
Who was in the room with us when we were?
I was there with you.
You were there.
Who else was in there?
I did see you guys do tasks too so.
Who was?
Who went in the vent?
I was round things then.
Vinny can confirm.
I was pumping.
Did you go in the vent or did you go in the vent?
We can't ask them that.
They're not going to tell me.
I know but who was in the room with me?
I don't know.
Who was in my room?
It was Rambo but he's dead.
Did we ever think maybe we should just talk?
It was you or you?
I think it's no it's you.
Just tell us.
It's you.
That's a lot of talking.
Okay.
Me and Rambo were in the room.
Somebody vented.
We said holy shit he vented.
I don't know the one with the um.
Maybe we should stick together from now on.
The captain's room or something?
Navigation?
You vented.
I saw you go in the vent.
I was over in shields.
Look is there a vent in shields?
This isn't very complicated.
Let me let me give my you know version of events.
I see I see Jerma in navigation with failboat and Rambo.
Yep.
Jerma starts saying he vented he vented
and then while he's saying that yellow runs up and kills Rambo
and Jerma goes oh my god oh my god oh my god and then I reported the body.
Act exactly.
Okay that's pretty realistic.
Fairly realistic interpretation considering how I wasn't there.
I was in shields.
Boat boat boat.
Yes no it's failboat it's failboat.
You can't see my name.
You have no idea who I am right now.
Thank you.
I could never have done that as good as you did.
You're just talking about venting for like last minute.
Yep there you go.
Oh okay.
It was very good explaining like a human.
Vent.
Yellow or orange.
One of those lighter.
I don't know.
Yellow orange maybe.
You're ignoring the fact that you saw him literally kill someone.
I just I don't know man it's stressful.
Okay well I can I can Kraken I can trust you.
I can try I'm staying with you I can trust you.
What are you doing that for?
This is is that you're making a funny thing here.
I'm in storage with Kraken by the way if anybody can hear me.
I'm in storage with Kraken Kraken and I are having a fun time.
No it couldn't have been you because that couldn't have been you.
You would have had to be in the menu.
Has the loser said what?
What is happening in here?
We got to fix this.
He's kind of being weird he won't talk.
Okay fixed.
What do you mean fixed?
I just fixed the sabotage.
No you didn't.
Yes what are you talking there's still another room.
There's still it's still counting down.
It's counting down still.
We're gonna lose.
What what happened?
What happened?
It's that easy.
It's just that easy.
I was just like what is that easy?
You guys just stood there for a second.
He was being weird.
He wouldn't talk.
You wouldn't talk.
I killed in front of you.
How did you think it wasn't me?
I don't know but he wouldn't talk to me.
He was just being weird.
He was fucking weird.
I'm sorry okay.
You were suffocating.
Shake my hand.
Good games.
Good game.
What do you mean what to see what I would do?
I'm scared.
I thought you were gonna kill me.
I was more concerned about people knowing that I was in the room with you.
I mean he's like he's like behind me like creeping up and looking at me.
That's toxic dude.
What'd you say?
You can't say he's so bad.
I'm being gaslit by my own crewmates.
Fuck me.
People are like following me and like making noises behind me.
Call 02 if you're funny.
Call 02 if you're funny right now.
If I die it's Kraken.
He told me so.
Call 02 if you're funny.
No one's funny.
Bunch of serious people in here.
Please please fix this.
Please fix.
Is it fixed?
Yeah it's fixed.
All right I was trying to.
You're the imposter right?
No I would you would be dead right now.
Kraken you told me if you were imposter you'd kill me.
I would I mean but you're not dead are you?
I mean I don't want to press I didn't want to press I didn't mean to do that.
I honestly skip skip skip.
All right what do you have to say for yourself?
What do you have to say for yourself?
This is very simple.
What was that?
Very simple.
I was hovering my hand over it because I was scared that Kraken was going to kill Vinny
and I accidentally touched it.
Skip.
Okay.
I mean that checks out.
We were in the same room that Kraken is going to kill someone.
He was just creeping around behind Vinny and I don't know.
You just think I'm a creepy guy right?
Admit it.
I followed the last round and I'm following Vinny.
That's just how he is.
It was a little weird.
I can't help the way I walk.
Well people should know as a weird walker.
That just might be the way he is.
As a weird walker.
Vinny you can take the floor here because I don't know.
I'm gonna just uh skip.
I would skip I would skip.
I didn't.
Vinny.
Me and Kraken had previous peeps.
It's fine now.
Yes.
Vinny.
Prove you're a man of love right now.
Give me a hug.
Prove you're a man of love.
Yeah.
There we go.
Alright alright that's a man of love.
I like these two.
That's a real one.
I think they're not.
These guys are sweet.
They were good.
Yeah.
We need to skip the vote.
Skip.
Skip the vote.
Oh that's right that's right that's right.
Here we are fucking virtually.
Yeah.
All we need is a mirror so we can touch our own faces while we look at each other.
Oh that would be pretty nice.
I didn't mean to touch it.
We did have VR chat.
Yeah yeah yeah.
Alright we can move.
Alright.
See you guys.
Have a good day at work.
Stay with me here.
I'm with you.
Yeah I'm sure you do.
Stay with me here.
Oh you actually did have a task here.
Wow.
Yeah.
Hey what's up guys.
What's up.
Hey.
Baby don't hurt me.
Stay together.
I agree.
Let's just go over here.
Yeah.
I'm sticking with Vinesauce.
My good friend Vinesauce.
Criken I'm sorry I have ill to you.
I have a license to ill.
Can I get behind you here?
I'm getting the silence.
Just get behind you.
I got it.
Like what.
I'm sorry man.
I got it.
All my tasks are on the other side.
This is a teleport right.
I can get quickly over there.
Can you guys just click this right here.
Just click that.
Sure.
See.
Let me give it a shot.
Listen listen.
Oh my god.
We gotta get over there quickly.
This is terrifying.
He did it.
He actually did it.
He can't kill us right.
Press the button.
Is this the cake or is this real.
That son of a bitch.
One second.
Hold on a second.
And what's going on.
What's going on.
No bodies.
Let me take the floor.
I was with Jerma and I was with Charbord and I just said hey can you guys go to the vent
and click it.
That way you can see if you're a sus.
And you know what.
Criken is the sus.
What.
He clicked on the vent.
He clicked on the vent and went inside.
Wait.
Is it these two.
What.
No it's Charbord.
Let me explain myself.
How did you vent.
Tell me how you vent.
Let me.
Let me live this.
Let me live this round.
And I will kill Criken.
That's so funny.
It would be super funny.
You know what.
Don't be funny.
No please.
It would be kind of funny.
That's funny.
That would be kind of funny.
Are we kidding.
No.
It would be funny.
Just kill Criken and we can all laugh.
I will kill Charbord because he has admitted to being the imposter.
It's him.
Okay.
I like you.
It's definitely.
It's guaranteed to be him.
But that would be kind of humorous.
Guys.
He's going to.
It's going to be so funny.
He's going to die.
Well.
He had good logic just now.
Oh.
Okay.
It's airtight.
It's actually airtight.
Well we all know.
We know who one is.
Two people and Charbord though.
Criken.
I'm coming for you.
No please.
You better run.
Alright.
I kind of want to see this actually.
I know.
I kind of.
Can we all just watch?
Let's just watch.
Let's see.
Which room would you like it to be in Criken?
I don't want it to die.
I'm coming for you.
It's going to be so funny.
There he goes.
Oh.
Now you believe that?
Does anyone know what we do?
That was new.
He's killing Criken.
We're fine.
We're completely safe.
Criken mistake.
We're completely safe right now.
Don't worry.
He's killing Criken.
Why didn't you kill my Criken?
We just chilled.
What task?
Hold on.
I'll be right back.
I'm going back by the main room.
I'm waiting for Criken.
Wait.
Wait for him to kill Criken.
I actually just forgot who went into that vent.
Charborg.
I forgot who did that.
It was Charborg.
Oh, okay.
The green one.
Someone vented?
Charborg did, yeah.
Yeah.
Yeah, he did.
And we're all just calm about it?
We're all just chill with this?
This is an okay thing?
Yeah.
He showed us.
He showed he can be transparent.
You kind of just pretended to not know that we all knew that it was him.
Don't you think that's a little weird?
What?
No.
I genuinely just forgot which green it was.
I don't know.
I'm not being suspicious.
Why are you going over there?
Go ahead and stand over there.
Don't make this a me-against-you thing.
Okay.
No, I just genuinely forgot which green it was.
I couldn't tell.
Can you stand by this vent and just press the trigger button?
Oh, yeah, sure.
Yeah, sure.
I can do that.
Look.
I'm going to press all my buttons, okay?
Okay.
That'll sound like genuine button presses to me.
There we go.
See?
I'm pressing buttons.
I'm pressing the buttons.
It's working.
We're good.
Okay.
That's fair.
He's coming at me.
Hey, how are you?
I'm watching.
What happened?
I couldn't get him.
What can I say?
He was too quick.
That was so funny.
But you're still alive?
Give me one more round.
One more round.
You're out.
He's out.
I took too long.
You're out.
No, he's out.
He's out.
Me and Failboat had a full deliberation for like a minute and a half, and you still hadn't
killed Kraikin.
You're out.
I was giving him a chance to talk, and then he just ran.
No, you're bad at this.
You're bad at this game.
I'm telling you.
I understand.
It's fine.
How did you not kill him?
You gotta be gone.
I was just giving him a chance to talk.
I ran.
You're just good at this game.
What can I say?
You just avoided him the whole time.
All right.
Give me a pat on the back.
Green gang.
Nice try.
See you.
Good try, buddy.
See you next time.
It was all right.
You are convicted, Fallen, but it's okay.
I think it's also possible to be you.
Enjoy the rest of your round, everybody.
It's not me.
Hey, hey, hey.
You're funny.
You know what?
The other one is home alone.
Don't you guys think it's kind of interesting that nobody else died because, oh, wait, we're
going to wait for Kraken to die, right?
Got him.
I have eight, okay?
It's not me.
I have eight fingers.
A guy with eight fingers can't kill someone.
Everyone knows this.
It's not me.
I swear to you, it's not me.
Please don't vote me.
I don't want to be a ghost man.
Got you.
It's not me.
It's literally not me.
Yeah, I think I believe him.
I believe him.
Why would he sell me?
Don't believe him.
I can prove it.
Okay?
I swear to you, I can prove it.
I can prove it.
Watch me do this task.
Somebody went that way.
I'm here.
Kill me.
Wait a minute.
Arnold's voice.
Stop being like a fucking weird comedian guy.
Like, I've lost everybody.
Oh, no.
Quickly.
Hurry up.
Okay.
It is...
Quickly.
Come on.
I got it.
You got it?
Right?
I did it, right?
Yeah, I did it.
I'll get him.
Weird.
Wait, is anyone going to get it?
Hold on.
I got it.
I did it.
Wait.
What's happening?
Hey, calm down.
Calm down.
Hey, home alone.
Yeah, what's up?
He's a little skittish, isn't he?
Come here.
Come to this side.
Yeah, what's up?
Okay, I got you.
I got you.
I clicked it.
See?
It didn't work.
It's home alone.
Oh!
Was it you?
That was fucking demented.
I genuinely didn't know if it was you or not, but then you admitted to it.
That was demented.
Oh, yeah, no, sorry.
Yeah, I had no idea.
You were, like, you did the click noise and I was convinced you were the sus.
I was convinced.
I just thought it'd be funny if I made a click noise instead of doing something.
Yeah.
It was good, but I thought it was a complete omission of guilt.
Time to vote.
Yeah.
Or admission of guilt.
Yeah, no, see?
I'm guilty and innocent at the same time.
You know, we could all vote for Jerma, just for shits and gigs.
They mean you could do that.
I mean, I mean, I could, but I'd like to.
It may be a little bit late.
Why would you want to be the imposter, you know?
And when you kick me out, I'll do, like, a, nooooo!
It would be wicked funny.
That'd be pretty funny.
Well, I would get a sensible couple for that.
Eww!
Yay!
Whoa!
Craig, how are you?
Hey!
Good work, everyone.
Why am I so tall?
Why does this keep happening?
In every...
I got room for one more.
One more is good for me.
That'd be perfect.
So, my suspicion about Jolly ended up being confirmed.
Suspicion?
Yeah, I'm getting a little gassed.
COVID's kind of coming up here.
And I am definitely not the imposter.
And happy birthday, everyone.
Happy birthday!
Let's get out there and have a good birthday, everybody.
That's right, that's right!
Okay, I can't see.
There goes the power.
Okay, well...
Okay.
We're headin' there.
Headin' there.
Time to...
Oh, I'm small again.
Quick light doer.
Task completed!
I've never heard my...
Congrats?
Thanks.
Okay, so, let's stick together.
I mean, like...
There's nothing better than that.
You now have concrete proof.
That's right.
We have to go out on a win with this one.
And by win, which team are you referring to?
The crewmates, of course.
Of course, of course.
Of course.
Hey.
Are we all crewmates here?
That one's easy.
You know my tasks.
Is everyone crewmates here?
Yeah, we're all task doers here.
We're all good.
Everyone's got a good amount of changes.
Just a bunch of task doers.
Okay, well...
Guys, we gotta go.
We gotta go.
We're all gonna die.
We can't let them win.
Another win?
Another win off this?
Shut up, guys.
Come on.
Get it together.
Shut up!
That's mean.
No.
I went the wrong way.
I'm going to the other one now.
Let's do this thing.
Dude, I swear to god I'm not doing this on purpose.
Okay.
I was in a room with at least purple.
I thought I saw Kraikin.
It's me, you and there was one other.
I think it was green.
It was green.
They're not gonna admit.
It was me.
It was Kraikin.
Or both.
You there?
It's one of the three of us.
I saw you.
I did it.
I killed you.
We did it.
And I did it like this.
And I'll do it again.
like this and I'll do it again look me in the eye and tell me that you didn't do
it I actually don't think it was you I do have to say though that you you are
picking like probably the worst person to like be the person to confide in on
this so I don't I think it was you hate yeah hey yeah yeah yeah you don't pick
the sus guy right to be like oh yeah yeah what he said is it accurate yeah I
mean that's it that's incredibly sus yeah
what's going on what's going on what I voted failboat it's Trubber right Trubber
admitted to it might use but he might just be being a weirdo
if you survive will you kill another person oh my god wait no oh my god your
dad I will kill again I'm killing I'm killing red next round okay that's
perfect yeah wait so he's gonna kill red so if reds dead then it's Trubber and if
not then I mean we're good right yeah the proof is in the pudding red is dead
ah yeah you guys stick together so if you die then we'll know it's him this
isn't a weird plan where you guys planned for one of you to die so you
could be the point I'm too stupid for that I think that was locked you're not
gonna die on my watch I'm just gonna follow you so I'm gonna watch everything
that happens from oh my god I just touched something that was weird I felt
like something organic that was weird that was strange I don't know I just I
tell you I touch something it was like it was like an organic feeling where's
that where's that where's that where's that where's it where's it I got it I
got it I got it I got it I got it I got it how do I do this one I got what's
going on there I walked in on Vinny and and Sam are you guys doing we just did
reactor doing tasks and finding out how we're back on or whatever yeah we're
locked in here all right never mind doing my task okay do I got a task in
here lads weird Kraken go by the way he was with us and then just kind of
disappeared Kraken was with us for a second ago and then he just disappeared
keep that in mind okay I'm gonna get the lights back lights it back we're all
alive Charborg is still alive hey Charborg have you seen Kraken anywhere
yeah what's Kraken he ran up and said some suspicious stuff and then left I
think it's Kraken he's just kind of going off on his own we just locked us
out of here hello who just locked us out of here I didn't I need to go here
though hello how do we open this I think it's Kraken Kraken is just somehow
just wait where you going I thought that was like a dramatic exit what do you see
in there no no I don't know he did it I was in the wall okay it's red I didn't
see anything I'm so I'm not gonna Sam Sam sorry do you have anything to say
for yourself I cry kid was it was running towards the body and it just
fell on the floor I don't know how else to explain it I saw Kraken walking down
the hallway straight towards a guy and then he killed him what I saw you walked
straight towards somebody but then I went into a wall and it was went all
black and I didn't see anything after that okay here's what really happened
guys so my friend Ramby was over there and he was looking at me down a long
hallway and I thought what a great opportunity to do a jump scare so I
started slowly walking towards him like this he starts screaming right he says
it's Kraken it's Kraken Kraken's coming towards me then out of nowhere
he explodes into blood and red leaves the body on the floor that's when I
reported it you can see that I reported it yeah yeah I actually can't
corroborate this because I was in the wall I saw him walk towards the whole
thing happened so you know who did it so who did it I'm not I'm not gonna say who
did it what super cool of you I guess let's all vote for who we think did it
okay that sounds good I mean I'm only going on information that I had which
is you creepin creepin so that it had to have been you it had to have been you
that imposter I'm not I'm not I'm not buddy I can't be sure which let's see if
you're worthy of doing the imposter things how like guys your story your
moral I'll follow right around the entire match if I come back dead if I'm
dead next time I'm gonna start eating crackers really loud into the microphone
somebody's gotta get rid of me yes see just just follow me I will be doing my
just following I'm worthy I'm worthy back me up I'm telling you I kill I am
I'm backing you up I gotta say far enough away just in case something crazy
happens here I got one more task we got to go this guy's gonna why are you
leaving don't what are you doing don't why don't leave don't leave are you
split up like that you're right that was weird of you to do by the way strange I
don't know why I did that very strange on impulse that was a little strange
timer is about to be up I can tell look at the way he's looking he wants to kill
he's got bloodlust in his eye in the menu by the way in the menu screen in the
menu screens oh in the menu oh in the menu I'm there you go yeah I know you
did exactly tell me have you sunk to the deepest depths of human
I've sunk to the highest don't that's weird all the way up there in not in the
vent not in the vent all right I got it I got some tasks to do I gotta go do
them I'm not going I would never think I would not in the vent or anything okay
yeah we're good we're gonna see hey look at this he's kind of looking at me look
at this you will descend into madness I did it into the Joker let me let me have
this as I was saying how far will you descend shit all right did we do it I
just did that one wait what how do we was it okay we got it good I got it good oh
we're good we're good we're good we're good this is what I don't know actually
don't know who it is yeah I it's definitely you right it has to be it's
not me it can't it's not me I'd never do anything like I would look I believe
you look at me so I'm gonna turn over here you've known each other the past
ten games I'm the gosh darn captain you remember when we when we were in
I do it was pretty cool we won that game we won that game we did win that game
anywhere you want to go before you you snap my neck anywhere you want to go
before we just happens I think Ohio okay so the course for Ohio get that going
here okay and let's get and drive and okay I'm ready here we go kill me kill
me kill me kill me kill me kill me what kill me what are you doing kill me kill
me do it click on me kill me kill me why won't you kill me kill me I can't look
I'm oh what's this like honeycomb thing oh press all these buttons dudes don't
do it already how do I even do this just kill me where's the knife just give it
kill me kill me why would he kill me wait wait he won't kill me I feel like
ten opportunities if this is him you said it was him yes you it is him guys
I saw him break someone's neck I know it's him really really I'm so tangled up
we must complete the tasks who is it then it isn't Vinny I feel like I should
be dead for like a we're gonna lose we just lost kill me kill me kill me kill
what the fuck please not me please not me please not strange things start to
happen we are damn it I'm so happy that I'm not the imposter I'm sorry I hope
I don't make anybody sick but I'm so tangled when one is not the imposter
okay I shouldn't have done that I'm just gonna do tasks you know what charge
that up okay that got that now I'm gonna go down this way it's up hey buddy hey
battle buddy hey buddy see anything suspicious lately not in this
direction about that direction on that direction good good to hear good to
ask in this room that was weird weird okay where is it where is it oh that's
far away that's far away please not again please not again if anyone can
hear me I'm doing the left one okay I'm right behind you where's the other one
okay nice okay good job what no shit fuck no stupid idiot what are you
thinking how what I trusted you but he did the task he did the task he did the
task he did the task he did the he did the task I watched him do it and it
stopped the meltdown and I trusted him I what he was oh poop I did I did it and
then the thing stopped so I was like he had to have just done it oh did he he
saw that somebody else did it he was walking around alone to say it I'm gonna
go this way oh good can you fucking believe this I mean it could have been
you too
played you like a fiddle even really I don't nobody knows either
the other one is probably cracking oh you know it was being weird you went
through eight stages of grief I was shocked I really didn't think it was I
had no idea well I'm gonna do my tasks I'm helping I'm helping download is that
one what does that one doing we can actually pilot the ship what does this
do it's kind of fun cool I know when my friend lies and it sounds the same as
when he's telling the truth I think it's cracking hey behind me you know sounding
off real quick okay I'm sure we're cool because no one's there maybe not oh this
could be acting this could be acting the other was acting too just alone just
talking this is acting I think
oh you're right now I literally just do one all right
cracking over I was not looking I'll follow you to the next one yeah I'm
looking still you can kill me and you probably get away with it because no
in the room but I'm just getting the test done ready and it's complete do you
just have to stand still for that one really yeah there it is
he was Vinny too
trickster
why am I inside this thing's like wrapping around me
excellent excellent games
yes I'm literally never doing this ever again kind of depressing I mean you
never know right you never know you maybe the sus guy could come back and
play a little bit more among us never know no this is actually this actually
was there's a ton of fun absolutely fucking fun thank you appreciate yeah
that was way more fun than I I never played this before but actually I'm a
believer now I'm an among us believer yeah that was a lot of fun thank you
seriously everybody for playing it was it was great yeah thanks for playing
thank you guys seriously it was a lot of fun let me get out of this I don't like
getting to leave the game
well I don't know how to leave how do I leave there we go oh okay there it is
all right guys yeah I probably would have stuck around how do I look see how
fucked up do I look probably pretty weird I probably look fucking crazy but
no that was a lot of fun channels gonna go back to normal but thanks for
participating everybody that was actually blast I that was way more fun
than I thought it was ever gonna be but I gotta like go chill I need to go get
COVID out of my body hope it was a good time I hope it was fun
sus guy out so I don't know the next stream I don't know what it's gonna be
probably a couple days I really I really want to get better so we'll see keep an
eye on the sus I know like the joke was that like put a sub goal in the stream
but like seriously thank you anybody that subscribed it was more for comedic
purposes but thank you I'll see you guys later have a great rest of your night
thanks everybody that played that was a good group I'll see you guys in probably
a couple days two or three days take care of yourselves there's gonna be a lot
of names here probably let's see holy shit how many people subscribed they're
almost 1,400 subs Jesus 1,400 no no no more than that almost 2,000 subs holy
shit 51 pages of subscriptions well come on at least I made a little bit of
actual sub farming I will never doing that again I trust me I'm gonna put the
headset down actually no I can't cuz I don't want to you won't be able to hear
me I'll leave the the sus branding up for a few hours probably maybe later
tonight or tomorrow I'll change everything back rip the sus you ever
gonna play this again I know I mean the joke was that I wasn't but maybe I but
without the jokey branding and all the other shit maybe yeah the thing about me
in VR though is I do it for like a week and then I put it away for six months so
I really don't know we'll see yeah good night guys see you later if I'm not like
rating anybody but there's a lot of people here so if any of the other
people that we're in that lobby is still streaming go sprinkle out around them if
they're still live because that was a that was a really fun group and I'll see
you guys soon good night goodbye take care of yourselves see you later