Hey, what is going on everybody? Welcome back to Hitman Absolution.
If you're just joining us, if you've never seen an episode before, then hello.
Welcome to an episode of Hitman Absolution. I suggest you go back and watch the first four or five episodes.
I think there's four right now. But let's get started here, escaping the library.
Gotta get rid of all these coppers, or at least avoid these coppers. Let's see here.
I actually do remember this from the gameplay demo they did a long time ago.
But I don't remember exactly how to do this, so we'll see how this goes.
Okay, what am I doing here?
Get out! Why are these guys still standing here?
Going like a coffee break. Get the hell out of here.
I'm gonna drop a chandelier on your head.
Now they're starting to move. Good, good, good.
Should be able just to chill out somewhere.
Right here seems good.
Only one dude.
Two guys over there, though.
Scaring me.
Maybe I can just go now? Let's go now.
No, not now, not now. Wow.
Wow, I almost just got spotted right there.
How do I do? How am I supposed to just go?
Hey, go like on patrol somewhere. Get the hell out of here.
You prick, get away from me.
Here we go, he's leaving.
Yeah, turn your back for two seconds and I'm out of here.
Maybe not, he almost just saw me. What's that?
Check over there. I got it.
Uh, there's a point of interest over here.
Wow, don't move.
I'm gonna try and make my way over there.
I don't really feel like going over here.
Let's see, can I make it over here?
Without being spotted is the real question.
Kind of.
But I don't like being in this position.
I don't like being in this position at all.
These guys have to move.
These guys have to move right now.
Right now.
Oh, these... I don't know where to go.
Don't stand up, that would be a bad idea.
Let me just stand up real quick. Hi.
I wonder if I can still...
Now where's he going?
Go over there. Damn it.
Ah, maybe I can walk around this way?
Is there anybody over here? No, this is not okay.
Point shooting? I don't know how to do point shooting.
Ooh, release light rig.
Can I grab this without him seeing?
I don't know if I can. I'm gonna be spotted if I walk over here.
Do I have like a distraction thing? Like a bottle or something?
Maybe he won't see me.
Oh, he didn't see... Oh my god.
Oh my god.
Oh my word.
Where are they going?
This one guy's coming over here right now.
Does he have any idea what's...
Did I go behind him?
Holy crap.
What's that guy just standing there for?
Get out of here, man. Don't just stand there.
Holy. Holy hell. Holy hell.
This guy's coming over here right now.
Holy hand grenade. Holy hell.
Don't see me.
Do you know what, man?
No, that's not what I wanted to do.
This is ridiculous.
How on earth is a hiding place right here?
Can I subdue this guy without this one seeing?
This guy's gotta move.
Okay, here we go.
Moment of truth.
Where we go, boys?
And or girls?
Come here.
Come here, you.
Get back here.
And nobody is the wiser.
Give me your police disguise.
And then you're going in here.
I'm sorry.
It was a necessary thing I had to do.
The lights are all on.
All right.
I should probably pick up his gun.
What's Johnson's gun doing on the ground?
I don't know. I have no idea.
Something tells me I don't want to just walk by this guy.
That would be a terrible idea.
Let's go back the other way.
Actually, you know what?
Can I go up top?
Would be probably a better decision.
The lights are all just blaring right now.
Probably should.
Holy crap.
That's another officer.
Why are you looking at the book?
Why are you looking at the bookcases?
This guy's looking for me in the bookcases.
Like he's looking at the books.
I wonder, he might be inside of the books.
He never can be too careful.
This guy keeps on looking over here.
And you know what?
I am going to go back down.
I'm going to go break those lights.
I remember seeing that one guy here.
I should be able to get behind him.
No, I don't even need to do that.
I can probably just, you know what?
I can probably just stand up and fake my way around.
Put the gun away though.
Yep.
Let's move back this way into the darkness.
I might even want to just get rid of this guy.
Seriously.
Oh crap.
Let's try this again.
This time let's be a little bit more sneaky about it, please.
And thank you.
Back is turned.
That guy's back is also turned.
Can I climb through here?
No, I can't.
I broke it.
There we go.
Oh boy.
This guy's coming back this way?
Damn it.
Just hang out over there, dude.
Just hang out over there.
Be cool.
We'll all be cool.
These guys have seen me now.
I might just be able to walk by.
Let's see if I can just...
No, I got to crouch back underneath here.
Wait for this guy to walk.
Is he walking out?
Go out.
Go out and talk to your friend.
That's what I'm talking about.
Sabotage the lights.
Nobody see me.
Yes.
That's what I'm talking about.
No, don't look at me.
Don't look at me.
I'm a cop too.
Good.
So far so good.
I'm going to go up the stairs now.
Both backs turned.
Yep.
Let's go up the stairs.
I'm a cop.
Don't worry.
I'm a police officer.
Just doing my job.
Looking up here.
Wow.
How is this other guy?
Still looking back there.
Man, I can't go out there.
I can't go anywhere.
You bastards.
I need to throw this guy off the balcony.
He's just annoying the hell out of me.
It looks like I could go over that way.
This guy's still...
Can I...
Maybe if I crouch I can...
Maybe he won't see me if I do this.
No, okay.
I can be sneaky about this.
See ya.
Wouldn't want to be ya.
Let's make our way.
Holy damn it.
You think you'd survive that drop?
Don't worry about it.
Just keep a lookout.
I really don't think you would survive that drop.
Just get away from the ledge.
Good slip and die.
Pull this out.
No one's going to die.
Just...
Just keep your eyes open.
You're good slip and die.
All right.
I definitely am supposed to go down this way and drop down.
Thanks for telling me what to do.
This guy turns his back.
Go look in that hole again.
Didn't it look like cool?
Wasn't it like weird looking?
Go like tell me how it looks.
Nope.
Not yet.
Man, they don't really know how to play tricks on you in this game.
I would have just dropped down there and gotten instantly murdered.
There's no way I'm going to take out that guy unless he turns around and this guy's not looking.
You know what?
Maybe I can push him in there.
He fell in the hole.
Nice.
Good.
Grand.
Great.
Wonderful.
Give me the hammer.
Don't lose it here.
Don't like freak out.
I am nervous as hell right now, man.
What's down?
Holy crap.
Get in here.
Get in.
Hide.
Holy hell.
I don't even know if I should get out right now.
I really don't know if I should get out because if I get out, he might just turn around.
Ways like the strategy guide when you need it.
Looks like he's going down here.
This might be the best time to go and see where he stops.
Keep your back turned.
Going out now.
Yep.
There we go.
Okay.
Damn.
Ooh.
Okay.
Change cover.
Go.
Um.
No.
What are you doing?
I want to like get out of cover.
Not like do that.
There we go.
It's space.
Through here.
Let's make it.
Can I climb through?
One guy.
There's the end.
Right there.
I'm almost done.
Yikes.
This is the only guy.
I'm going to go around this way.
Is his back turned?
His back.
This guy's back is turned.
Oh damn it.
There he goes.
His route looks like it goes all the way down.
Perfect.
Let's get out of here.
Seriously get me out of here.
This guy's looking this way.
Get me out of here.
Oh damn it.
Oh I don't know.
I don't know.
He's coming all the way back here.
Yeah you do know me from somewhere.
Oh I got to go up here.
Okay.
Oh my word.
This is it.
Where's this guy coming?
I don't know this guy's route.
I don't know this guy's freaking route.
Oh no.
Stop right there.
Yes.
So lucky.
I can't believe I just did that.
I cannot believe I just did that.
How did this guy not just see me right there dude?
Oh it's impossible.
It is impossible that I just did not get spotted.
Release this.
What just happened?
I don't know.
I have no idea what just happened.
But I need to go out that door.
I make it across here.
Oh come on man.
Are you serious?
If I drop down here where can I go?
It's just a question of whether or not I can get past these two guys.
I wish I had that hammer still.
It would make things a lot easier.
Let's just walk by.
And out this way.
I might be able just to tactically move around up there.
You know what?
Let's do this.
Sayonara sucker.
Nope.
Bad idea.
Is it like a book I can pick up?
These guys follow the same route it seems.
Just a question of out maneuvering these two butt heads.
One guy's here.
One guy's there.
Let's go.
I'm just going for it.
I'm going for it baby.
Oh dear.
I made it.
I made it out the door.
Now what?
Looks like I can go up top.
Nobody up here.
I can start running.
Whoa.
This place is completely empty.
Nobody up here right?
I can like walk into someone.
So what do I do here?
I have to like.
What's this?
Release the chandelier.
Releasing this will likely cause fatalities.
Well don't I want like the silent assassin?
Oh I already like killed that guy.
What if I just like walk out the door?
What if I like to say no to killing these people?
Because they're just police officers.
They didn't do no harm.
Wait a minute.
Let's see if I can just go around this way.
I can't.
I have to drop that chandelier.
I don't want to like kill these people.
The game is making me kill these guys.
I don't want to.
Oh right.
I can just walk by it.
Right.
Bang baby.
Bang.
And that is going to wrap up the episode.
So thank you all so much for watching.
I really do appreciate it.
And I'll see you guys all next time.
And if you do like the series please go ahead and throw me a like or a comment or something
like that because it does motivate me to record more of these episodes.
So again I'll see you guys all soon.
Thank you so much for watching and take care everybody.