It's not Germacraft unless you have something crazy happen, so I'm gonna go fight this asshole over here.
Get this cows too. Do I have- I don't even have a sword.
This is gonna be interesting.
I should have just made one. I should have just made a sword. What am I doing? Why am I doing this?
Why am I going after this guy right now? What is the matter with me?
You see, my brain does not work in ways that you would think it should.
I'm definitely gonna die.
This is the stupidest idea ever.
That was the dumbest thing I've ever done in this game.
I don't even have a spawn point. Oh, great.
At least there's cows.
Mountain cows.
Whoa. Where's my diving board?
Where's my diving board?
I made a diving board. Where is it?
Oh!
Coal! There's coal right there. There's coal right there.
Get away from me.
Oh, there's three creepers? What are you kidding me?
This is insane.
What the hell?
Come on now.
You can't get up here.
You know what? Blow up.
I dare you. I dare you.
Good. I'm right next to you. Blow up.
Get out of here.
Get the hell away from me.
Everybody just blow up right now. Go. Blow up.
I want to see the hole that made.
Oh, there's my diving board.
All right.
That actually looks kind of cool.
Did I make it? I made it.
Wait a second. How did this happen?
They're all here too? There's like ten people down here.
What is going on?
Oh, my God. Oh, hey. More people.
Might as well just run off the cliff.
Okay.
So I've successfully made a hole
in my basement.
Where I'm hiding from all the things
that have been just killing me over and over again.
And I'm surrounded
right now. By mobs.
Oh, my God.
Can you hear them all?
They're all over the water.
I feel like I'm in a Stephen King movie.
Shouldn't they be dying right now?
Am I missing? Look at all the arrows.
My house
is riddled with arrows.
Oh, my God.
It looks like this is like
part of the Lord of the Rings set.
Why are they not dying? It's bright as
hell out. There we go.
Now they're on fire.
Or are they? They should be.
Oh, look at that. Oh, look at this.
Oh, what happened?
What happened?
Did you die?
Why is that guy still alive?
I'm not going to question that.
Whatever.
Okay, now let me rethink
what I'm doing here. Okay, I've got to collect
some of this because I'm an idiot and I died.
Just going to get a pickaxe, go down there, get some coal.
And I should be good to go.
There we are.
So while I have the light, I need to do this.
Wait, where's my original crafting
table? What the hell happened to my crafting table?
Whatever.
Yeah, I'm crazy if I think.
Oh, I'm going to have a castle built.
I'm going to have a nice castle
built by Christmas time. Yeah, right.
Alright, let's find
some of this. There's definitely going to be coal down here.
I know for a fact there is.
They wouldn't have this much crap everywhere without coal
being right there.
At least I can get some tools, different tools.
Listen to that music.
More
caves. That's just fantastic.
Alright, no coal
yet.
There's coal right there. Found it.
I got a bunch of butt heads to deal with.
I feel
like I'm playing the drums.
There it is.
There's the coal.
That's what I'm looking for.
Will you die already?
Give me a break.
Alright, here it is.
Just need one piece of freaking coal.
For the love
of all that is sacred
on planet Earth. Just give me the coal.
Oh my god.
Finally.
Alright, get me the hell back up
so I can start to actually play this game.
I'm just
using my walls.
Oh yeah, that's fine. I'm just going to tear down
my own walls to get wood.
And it's this, right? Yeah.
Success. Okay, great.
So now, let's
do this. Let's make a little
small house so I don't get
mutilated when it becomes night time.
That's good enough.
I just need a bed.
It needs to be higher than that.
Oh god, it needs to be at least one
block higher than that. This is temporary.
This is temporary. I promise this is temporary.
A piece of sand.
Look at this mess.
This is the worst house
I've ever seen in Minecraft.
Ever.
Alright. At least I have some
light in my own house.
Gotta pay the electric bill. Well there's more coal
over here. That's definitely a start.
That's definitely a good thing.
Pick that up. Definitely.
I came over here for those,
that tree right there. But I need
this coal too. The fun part about Minecraft
is you can kind of just get distracted
and just go do whatever you feel like
however long you're doing it.
That's good. There's a little more over here I saw.
Get out of the way. Where was it?
Where was it? Where was it?
No, that's a shovel.
Thought I saw more. Oh well.
I came over here for this single
out of place tree. Let there be light.
Aim up.
Always cut down the whole tree or else it won't
disappear. That's what grandpa
told me. Cause he raged one,
he raged one time. The whole tree
you gotta cut down the whole god damn
tree Jeremy. And I said why?
Why would I want to do that?
Because it's against the law if you don't.
Yeah it's against the law.
I don't think so grandpa.
I think you're just nuts.
Starting to get dark. This is a big damn
this is a big tree. This has so much wood in it.
It's got a lot of wood in this tree.
That's actually a good thing cause I don't want to come back
and do it again. Hello, excuse me.
No I hate when this happens.
Now I gotta like, ugh. Let me get all
up in this tree. Can I put a
no I can't put a torch down right there.
There's so much wood in this tree.
It's unbelievable how much wood is in this tree.
Is that it? Oh my god.
There's more wood in this tree.
This is insane.
This entire tree is just a big huge
block of wood. Usually there's only
a few. I'm confused.
Oh my god.
Whatever. Here's the last one right here.
I'm outta here.
Give me the torch. I'm going back
home. Look at that beautiful
moon. So elegant.
Okay so I got that wood. Let's do
something with it. Let's make it into a bunch
of things.
Just shift click. Alright let's make
this into a ton of sticks.
Shift click and where's
my crafting bench? It's down there.
Alright let's at least cover this
hole up so I can not get murdered if
somebody comes and gets me. I have my house
made out of like three different materials
right now. I'll tell you it
will make progress. If you
are watching this video for the first time
and there's like 15 episodes ahead
of this, I promise this is not
gonna be this much of a mess through the
whole series. Promise.
And if it is, then
whoops.
This would be my nice little cave house
for the time being. This is it
right here. Where is my...
There we go. Let's just close it up.
No sense in just
sitting here like this. Here we
go. My house is pretty much
complete. At least my
caveman house is. Let's get in there.
Oh my god. Where's my
certificate? Where's my certificate for
first house built? Cause it just happened.
Make it... Oh my god! No!
No! No!
No!
That could have been bad. Imagine if I just
drowned myself. That would be terrible.