Do-do-do-do-do-do-do-do-do-do-do-do-do-do-do-do-do-do-do-do-do-do-do-do-do-do-do-do-do-do-do-do-do-do-do-do-do-do-do-do-do-do-do-do-do-do-do-do-do-do-do-do-do-do-do-do-do-do-do-do-do-do-do-do-do-do-do-do-do-do-do-do-do-do-do-do-do-do-do-do-do-do-do-do-do-do-do-do-do-do-do-do-do-do-do-do-do-do-do-do-do-do-do-do-do-do-do-do-do-do-do-do
Do-do-do-do-do-do-do-do-do-do-do-do-do-do-do-do-do-do-do
everything is randomly generated every single level is random wow we're moving faster oh you
can double jump z is melee oh i need to have a game pad for this maybe not x is projectile
oh because do i feel unlimited no i don't lower left okay i get it oh i thought i died in one
hit well maybe you do die in like one hit how many lives do i have who knows c is to drop a bomb
bomb that's what happened to the dragon that was just here that just shot at me
all right and space bar oh my god this is these controls are a little bit wonky okay so that's
you can do like kind of a link attack like zelda when you go down on people uh not go down uh
there's the germo there you go again like saying like innuendo is when you don't mean to
i don't have any bombs left get shiruken don't forget to read the comic okay oh i tried to drop
down on it didn't work oh my god i got a time limit okay i get it i get it i got to finish
this quick what's that i don't know what's this guy well hold the crouch button until you flash
white then push up immediately to do a super jump okay i only have like 18 seconds here oh dear
oh dear i need to put a controller in keyboard baby uh can i get up there now i got some time
left yeah all right it's three hits to do that got it you can pick up the shirukens it seems too
i got no time for you buddy all right okay control is going in after this all right so note to
those of you watching right now if you want to play this game i highly suggest you plug in a
game pad and i think there's a program i'm gonna go get i'm gonna like stop recording and go get
this thing called joy to key i love how it slows down that's pretty cool got you oh i'm dead now
i died joy to key baby i'm going to get a freaking game pad controller get attacked all right so
we're back i have joy to key set up now i can play this game and have a ton of fun let's do it
uh can i yeah i can hold this down wait no go so i guess i have to keep the time going
so i get a speed through this come on time yeah i just took a lot of damage right there so
everything is randomly generated apparently and the whole point is you got to move really fast
which i'm not really doing at this moment let's go string together combos oh jesus there's so many
people down here shuriken all right i want to get that bomb do i have enough time to get this
i want to get that too wait can i wall jump oh i can come on get up there get up there i got it
don't know what the e is but i got it time reset what's it go say hit the bombs with your hand
weapon to propel them forward okay so i can launch bombs forward let's try it okay cool it works
what what i get i unlock something yikes something else too what's what's hitting me
oh that guy was i only got three more pieces of candy corn oh time's gonna run out
no it's not hey bro hey bro rented a shurikens
see ya i think there's bosses in this game too there's money down there all right let's go bros
let me just like dive in and get myself smashed i really should not be wasting those shurikens
i should probably hold on to those spikes right there i feel like my character weighs like
5000 pounds look at he's like just like drops down oh if you get to the bottom of the tower
let me know what you find okay this bombs bombs cool all right stop the time i guess the time
stops when you're in a certain room that's cool i like that give me those so i guess it's all
about just going as fast as you possibly can i died yes we're gonna continue of course we are
oh shit we're like here how many continues do you get secret walls secret walls huh
i'm at floor 290 apparently we're going down no i never dropped down that far whoops dropped a
bomb what's that can't spend time looking at stuff i'm not a tourist is there a way you can
tell if a wall is a secret wall probably not probably not running out of time 10 seconds 10
seconds no no how did i get that why did my time reset oh i must have ran into one r so what do
you spell words too oh i'm like i'm like rage i'm like in a free i'm not in a rage right now i
gotta take this is my advantage get up there you slug give me that heart come on jump why can't
i jump what the hell man get up there climb up maybe i need to oh my god i got it i'm good i'm
good oh damn it what the hell well that guy explodes time what floor am i on i must be
pretty low now damn it i can't get hit again i cannot get hit again floor 250 oh no i'm at a boss
i'm at a boss i'm at a boss i don't know what to do mantis it's like megaman let me just say don't
worry let me just like walk into him and die instantly because i'm an idiot of course i want
all right this i don't know how many continues do i have but i just shirouken him oh he drops
bombs oh maybe i i gotta i'm gonna throw these up back up at him maybe i'll do another one
damn it damn it i'm hitting myself oh i gotta just gonna time it like now nope that didn't work
neither did that neither did that can i swing up without jumping i don't think i can oh yeah
just like just like squad on top me i'll just do that yeah that's about just keep shiroukening you
what's up punk oh you want to get electrocuted oh okay he has to be in the cone for that to do any
damage sorry i'll get him right here one more hit see you whoo stuff coffee all right let's keep
going abyss of nature a wise ninja knows that some walls are not walls at all yeah you told me that
before i don't get it though i gotta find the fake walls i don't know where the hell they are maybe
this one's a fake wall all right now for the rest of the time i'm just gonna keep going i'm gonna
run as fast i can famous last words apparently famous last words apparently well don't kill me
that's pretty brutal well this is super ninja dead monsters whatever the hell the title is
super hon let's see i got new weapons oh hold on let's look at this for a second instant attack but
has the shortest reach of all the weapons this upgrade can deflect projectiles away it hits
instantly and ping can be used to pull items towards you let's put the whip on this upgrade
makes the shirouken always behind enemies what the hell does that mean bounces off the floor
ceiling and walls until it hits an enemy oh i want that what's the other shows location of nearby
items yeah can i can i no actually i think it's already on i think it's already on oh cut hats
hats i think we found the hats no these are just suits there's a lot to this game though pretty
cool a lot of stuff going on i just want to check out these items i guess i can go to floor 250 i
can start from 250 i want to see these new items ooh simon belmont up in this bitch but that's
gonna wrap it up here guys uh thank you all so much for watching i really do appreciate it
and this may or may not be the start of sort of a new series on this channel called i mean i don't
know maybe what's on steam or something like that where i grab a new steam game that came out within
the last four or five days just to kind of give a first look and a first kind of goofy
impressions of the game to see if maybe you would be interested in buying it or playing it just to
kind of help you guys out a little bit in deciding what games you want to get on steam but i'll be
out of here now i'll see you guys all next time and of course take care everybody