No, I almost just turned off the power supply to the computer.
What is happening today? It would have just been like GOOOOO and the stream would have turned off.
Okay, I should be good to go here in a sec. At least I hope so.
And, come on. Hey, there we go. Perfect.
I gotta plug in my shit. I should be able to see it in a second here.
What did I do with this computer? Okay. Should I play online? I mean, I guess I'm gonna.
Like, a thousand of you guys bought the game. Like, legit a thousand of you guys
probably bought this game and when I played it for like fifteen minutes you're probably like, what the fuck, dude?
Alright, one more sec. I gotta plug this in.
Wheel of Fortune. Can we get the mods to change it?
Hey. What's going on with the... What did I do to my thing here?
What did I just do? Where's my webcam?
Can you guys see? Is my webcam here? Can you guys see?
My OBS is crashed. I literally can't see anything over here.
Like, full on crashed. Wait, there we go. Alright, I fixed it.
Wheel of Fortune. Let's do it. I do have to change my microphone shit here.
This has been a wild stream. I have to
stop saying that I'm gonna chill and have like a chill day. Every time I say I wanna have a
chill out day, just weird shit happens. Every time. I just
go fucking crazy. I'm not linking to the club. Get out of here.
There we go. Okay. Put it in emote only. Go for it. I'm going in
online. I'm not gonna tell you when I'm gonna go because I don't want anyone to... I don't want anyone to know
where I'm going. I apologize to the three thousand people that left over the course of the
last four hours. Considering that it was probably one of the best
ones I've done this year. No, you know what? Fuck that. I actually had a lot of fun today. So I don't
even care. I don't even care. I like had a blast today. This is like a lot of fun. I don't even care.
Alright. I'm not gonna tell you when I'm gonna click it.
For the stream sniper Andes out there. What the fuck am I doing?
What's wrong with me? What? I muted the game,
dude. I need to eat a fucking bag of peanuts or something.
I swear to God. I muted the game
and thought that was... Oh my. Okay. Honest to God.
Holy shit, dude. You've got to be kidding me.
I'm just not with it today. What? I'm shocked
right now. Honestly, I need to eat like a fucking steak.
Oh my God, dude.
Fucking Bjork.
Jesus.
Alright, let's go. Food and drink.
Food and drink. Steamed. Steamed vegetables.
Steamed vegetables. I got it. I'm sorry. That was loud.
It's vege-tables, right? Is it vege-tables or vege-tables?
Let's go.
Coffee. Something. Donut. Donut's coffee.
Donut. What?
I don't know brands were in this. That's a brand. That's not...
Okay. Brands are in this, apparently.
What?
Oh, wouldn't it be funny if you hit Bankrupt? That would've been amazing.
A place.
This is a place. France Street.
Trees. Tree stumps.
Ooh, it's a wild, too.
What? Why did I...
What? The clock ticker. I had five seconds?
Why did I have ten seconds? Listen, motherfucker, it's
train station, okay? Just win. What happened? I was like,
oh, I got a second to make sure there's... It's train station. Somebody win it.
I'm so loud, computer. I don't know what...
I did not expect it to be like five seconds. I'm sitting there going, yeah, train station.
I was like, okay. And I was like, oh, I can't... It's all vowels.
So, I'm sitting here looking, and I'm like, wait, okay,
I have to buy the vowels. It was only vowels left. And I'm just like,
I can't find them, because I was trying to make some extra money.
What the fuck?
That sucked. It was only vowels left.
I didn't want to solve it immediately, because I... Whatever.
Hey, by the way, viewers going up.
They're coming back. They're coming back.
There's a phrase? Okay. Phrase. Stop.
Stop.
Draw. No.
Stop. Stop out of...
Stop out for...
Stop. Put. It. Stop. Put it.
It's my fucking turn. I mean, it's gonna stop, right?
Okay. Okay, there's O. I'm gonna say
M somewhere?
I've never seen that be anything but bankrupt.
It's only been bankrupt.
Okay, wait, wait, wait.
I think this might be... I think I know what one of these words is.
Comfort? Stop by.
I don't know.
Comfort. Time.
Comfort.
Stop out of something comfort.
What is this? This makes no sense.
Stop out.
All I know is you guys saying his brain, dot, dot, dot, his brain.
Okay, this is a thing. Any S's?
That 10 second timer is bullshit. It needs to be like 15.
Okay.
Don't lose a turn. Come on.
Any H's?
I see an Among Us character banned that person for
one minute. Can you do it?
Something TS.
All right. All right.
Second place. And the million dollars is gone.
This could work out.
Considence? A thing.
I don't know. I have no idea what it is.
Express 1000. All right, nice. Wait, that means I have to solve it.
This timer.
I fucking hate this timer.
That wouldn't make any sense, dude. This timer is shorter than
it was last time.
Dude, three seconds to choose a letter. See, it's fucking up everybody.
Not just me. All right, land on bankrupt.
Okay. Peanuts.
Peanuts. Tree nuts.
What is this?
I don't have time to look.
What would be the first?
All the N's are freaking me out.
They don't know it either.
Nuggets? I know what it is.
Magnets. Where's M?
Where's M? It's not magnets?
Oh shit. Oh shit. Oh shit. I got time.
I got time. I got time. Ban. Oh fuck.
Oh.
Nuts. It's gotta be like nuts.
Bang nuts?
I have no idea. I thought it was...
I don't care. I'm gonna be the funny guy.
Are you solving it? What is it?
What possibly could this be?
Nuts? I was gonna say that's a word.
He doesn't know it either.
I think I know what it is.
Yeah. What is going on?
Do we really not know what none of us do?
King nuts. All right, that was a warm up.
That was a warm up.
Can I get banned from the game? Because I wrote bang nuts.
Catcher. I mean, I'm just gonna fucking guess.
One. There's one letter left.
Yadimir?
Is it Yadimir? Is it two R's?
It might just be two R's. It's either two R's or
it's Yadimir. No way. It's not Yadimir.
There's no way. There's no way. It's definitely. It's two R's.
Is it Yadimir? Or just two R's, right? I don't know.
It's not fucking Yadimir.
There's one letter left. I didn't know it was gonna be that.
This is a warm up round, guys.
Warm up, warm up, warm up.
Goat cheese.
No.
Grier.
What?
Okay, food and drink.
Really?
Fried. Sauteed.
You don't actually know it, do you?
Battered.
That's not what it is, man.
Well, I mean, now I know it's battered.
Battered fish. Battered eggs.
Stop!
Ooh, wait a minute. Battered.
It's not battered.
It's not battered. Slathered? Smothered.
Slathered? Saltered?
It's not saltered. I'm sorry that was loud.
I don't fucking know.
W. Buttered water?
Is it buttered water? Why would you have buttered water?
Buttered water?
Buttered water? Iced water? Purified water?
Spring water? Filtered fucking water?
That guy fucked me up with the battered.
Whatever. Oh, wait, they had the bonus round.
She's got the bonus round. Let's see what she does.
It's a phrase.
Engine.
I can help you out here. It's enter. Enter? It's enter.
Or it might be like...
No. What?
Day? Enjoy your day.
That's not a phrase.
That's generic language. That's not a phrase.
Enjoy your day. That's me speaking of language to you.
Enjoy your day. That's not a phrase. That's literally me saying...
That's not a phrase. It's literally just language.
I just said hi. Is how are you a phrase?
No, it's just me asking how you're doing. It's not a phrase.
Okay. That was a warm up.
I'll tell you when I'm clicking it. Magnets, I know.
We've got a level 17 here. This is going to be hard.
Okay.
Let's go.
I'm not fucking around this time.
TV title.
Saturday Night Live. I haven't watched Saturday Night Live.
Whatever. Give us another one.
People. I was going to say new sheriff, but it's a new staff member.
Wait, new staff members? Good start.
This is a phrase. The and.
And the. Whatever. 2500. Come on.
I'm going to obviously do T.
I'll try an O.
I'm going to buy a vowel.
Two.
I'll spin it again.
It's going to be a T.
It's going to be bankrupt.
One of these is probably four.
Really?
I could be a total moron and just try to do the four of and.
Okay.
No.
Fuck off.
Three letter words.
I don't know.
Two. Four. And. The. Out.
Hop.
R. It's probably a bunch of A's and E's.
Guaranteed. A's and E's.
I get an A up there. We're in E. Probably be able to solve it immediately.
Let's get an A.
Yep. Okay. Okay.
Something R. Our boat.
Our boat. I don't know.
Don't.
2500.
Look at you.
What?
I know it. Yeah. You are what you eat.
You are boat of and. Oh my
God. How did I make it to 36?
How did I make it to 36?
A boat and
R of two.
Yeah. Sure.
All right. Living thing. Wait.
Wombat. No. It's one word. How about like just
the cat. The cat. Or the dog.
I'm going to go for it. I'm going to go for it. I think it's probably the cat.
The dog. Reading the mod chat. Somebody says dude.
There's lead in your water.
All right.
Bat.
What's two words? Right? I don't know why I just thought of
Ruh-roh. That's a phrase from Shaggy.
Zdog. Scooby. Go with bankrupt. I'm still in the game.
That's about as painful as bankruptcy gets.
Living thing. But it doesn't have to be an animal, right?
It could be a plant. There we go. This will put me ahead big time. Come on.
Come on.
I could have sworn I was going to be
with an H in there or something.
Unfortunately, that's not what we need.
Lose darn. Good. Good. Good. Good. Good. Yes. Yes. Yes. Yes. Yes.
It's going to be something really, really specific that I don't know.
That's good.
Dog.
Dog. Big dog.
Big dog. Okay.
It's something dog. What kind of dog?
I knew it was going to be like the dog. It's not the dog though.
35. Come on. I don't know.
I don't know.
I don't know. I don't know. I could have bought a vowel but
I was like a new dog, right? That's what I was thinking. But
I'm sorry. There are none on the board.
My dog. Man dog.
This is not a living thing.
This is not a living thing. Not a living thing.
That's not a living thing. I'm sorry.
Part of it is. Half of it is.
Laugh dog.
I'm thinking of a certain dog breed or I don't know.
Laugh dog. Living thing.
I'm still in it.
Big dog.
F***ing lead in the water. There's lead in the water.
There's something in your water.
Nobody else got it either.
This is
my eyes are freaking out. Something in the kitchen.
In the kitchen.
Lasagna.
That was a big one. That was a huge one. Alright. In the kitchen.
Alright. Hold on.
I know. I think I know some of this. Let's find out.
Million. Give me the million.
I got it.
It's not dishes.
How is that word not?
D-I-S-H-E. Oh. That would be dishes.
Wow. Not a single one on the board.
We have one L.
There are no A's. That seems insane.
Can I play the game? I feel like I've gotten something bad
every turn I do.
Is it like a utensil or
appliance? There's going to be a lot of E's.
Delicious.
Doil.
That constant L.
Doi?
I'm going with E. Let's go.
Alright.
Embroidered.
Embroiled.
Emperors.
What the fuck is this?
Embroidered.
It's embroidered. It has to be.
Dogles.
Doil.
Doppel.
Duol.
Wow. My buttons got shocked in real life.
I'm going to cry. What happened? What is a fucking doily?
A doily is a real word?
What is a doily?
These words are fucking weird.
I hit A first. I hit A first. That's bullshit.
Yes. Of course it's grape yogurt. Of course it is.
Got it. It's grape yogurt. Come on. I'm still in it.
I can win it right here. It's going to do good.
Doilies are those things? Does anybody have a doily in their house?
Or is there one up?
Yeah, sure. Those doilies,
I thought they were bibs.
Alright. I need to get this.
I don't know.
This is a place.
The hyphen always fucks with me.
Messes with me a lot.
How is this not furniture store?
Furniture hyphen, I don't know. Furniture subway.
Furniture slash Taco Bell.
That's not...
How would that have been
furniture store?
Yeah, dude. What am I talking about?
I know it.
It's the sorting goods, sorting foods store.
It's the sporting goods store. Of course it is. I'm trying to fuck with the person that's taking the test.
The sorting foods store, aka a grocery store.
The sorting foods store. Alright, those are two warmups.
One more. One more and that's it. One more. Good luck.
That's making it so easy now.
Letters?
Alright, so it's barn leaders?
We only have a short amount of time, so go ahead and solve.
Wow, you won the bonus round. And the prize is...
Well, I think you'll be happy with this one.
The leader of the barn. The guy that makes all the...
One more and that's it. Porn letters, yeah. It's the guy that makes the animals.
Okay, let's go. You have to buy vowels. You don't get paid for...
Yeah, I know, I know. This guy's a streamer, not a novelist.
Yeah, that's right. That's right.
What am I doing? Stop. I just want brightness. Okay, let's go for it.
Dude, just play it in the dark.
Place.
Antique flea market.
I need all this money. Movie title. Come on, I should get this.
All I do is watch movies. The last movie I saw was
The Rise of Skywalker.
Did you not know it?
Manchester...
I've never heard of this movie. Manchester by the Sea?
What movie is that?
Living Things.
Shock.
Okay.
One of these days, you're going to fuck that up.
And you're going to be mad that you did. At some point during
one of these rounds, you're going to screw that up and it's going to lose you the game.
I think I know. I like to solve, please.
Yeah, I do. I can't even do the joke.
Fuck. Oh, no.
I was going to say, sheesh.
But I can't even make the joke, so now it's fucked up.
Now I have to get it right. I was just trying to make the two people here laugh.
I'm still going to win this.
I was still going to win this. Just watch.
I have to win one before I turn the stream off. I have to.
Quiet, quiet, quiet, quiet, quiet, quiet, quiet. Oh, fuck.
Give it to me, give it to me. I know it.
I know it. I know it.
I know it.
You motherfucker.
Come on.
That's it.
Come on. 900. There it is. That's a great start. S. I'm going to say T. Okay. I'm going
to say there's probably an H, but I'm going to say T. Yup. Okay. This is around the house.
Let's keep going. I'll take 650. I'll take it. All right. Like shoveling. Is it going to be an R? It has to be. All right. All right. All right. All right. All right. All right. I think I know another one. I think I know what one of these words is. Yup. Okay. All right. All right. Let me get a vowel. Really? I don't know what that word is. Give me another one. E.
Yes, we have some. Oh, let's go. Let's go. Let's build up a shitload of money. Let's run away with it. Okay. Yes, we have some. All right. All right. I'm going for more money. One more. That's it. 600. Yes, we have some. Scented dryer sheets. Scented, scented, scented.
Scented candles. Scented. I don't know. Scented something. Scented something. Scented something. I'm going to spin it again.
We don't seem to have any of those. I don't know. I freaked out because of the fucking timer.
We have one W. Scented dryer. Scented dryer. What are you talking about? Who has a scented
draw in their house? What kind of fucked up weirdo are you that you have a scented like a clothing
draw? What are they talking about? What are these fucked up terms that nobody has or nobody uses?
What? What in the name of God is this fucking product? Scented draw liners? No one has these.
No, not a single solitary fucking human on earth. A scented draw liner.
What is going on here? Scented draw liner? Old people don't even have that.
Scented draw liner. Why would you want that? What, to make all your clothes smell like vanilla,
apple, cinnamon bullshit? What the fuck is that for? I'm dead serious. Take off emote only.
Explain it to me. Take it off emote only. I want it to be explained to me in full detail.
I've never heard of them. I have no idea. I have them. They're nice. Your draws smell.
I'm dead serious. Wait, in your... Okay. It's to keep clothes fresh. I don't want that.
I don't want to have some fucking chemical ass smell in my draw. What's the point of cleaning
your clothes? I'm serious. What's the point of doing laundry if you're going to put your
clean clothes into a scented draw? It's for a kitchen. Why do you want your utensils to smell?
I don't get it. I don't understand what that's for. One million.
Okay. One million. Yes. Gee. Fuck you. Unfortunately, there are none on the board.
I'm sorry. Yeah. All these people. Yeah. All you guys in chat with doilies and scented draws.
I don't know what alien planet that you're on. Yes, we have some hearts.
Don't go and spend all that at once now. I'm going to come in last place again.
Next contestants, it's your turn. People. Okay. Well, very obviously. I know what the second
word is. Do why wouldn't they? Can they make a wheel of fortune with like Diablo two items?
Can we do that? Like I want, you know what I mean? Like I want, that would be more interesting to me.
Not doily fucking draw liners. Is there like a gamer version? Is it like a nerd version?
Scented Diablo two items. That dude, that's the virgin version. Okay.
Do we have any of those? I actually, I know what this is. So I'm going to try to make some
fucking money. I know the answer to this question. I'm going to try to make some money
because I have to. I swear to God, I'm installing the game right now. I'm going to uninstall it.
There's no risk. That's like the sixth or seventh time I've landed on that.
I've landed on that 40% of every spin. Bankrupt should not be in four spaces on the map. It
should be in literally one. It shouldn't even be on the map. What's the point of that being there?
I know that I know this. I literally would say it out loud right now,
but I still have a chance to make some money. Bankrupt. Bankrupt, bankrupt, bankrupt,
lose a turn, lose a turn, bankrupt, bankrupt, bankrupt. Yeah. Board of directors. Great.
I would have been able to do that if this stupid fucking game that has been around since like
1700 had didn't have bankrupt slots. You know, I'll never understand that these some of these
old games, there's like go to zero on the board, but then there's also things are worth five
times points in round three. What the hell are you even trying to have it be based on skill
or are you having to be bullshit RNG nonsense dog shit? Bankrupt times five points. It doesn't
matter. You get one thing right in the fucking last round. Your chance to solve food and drink.
I know it. I know it. All right, dude, you made this joke like five times. What are you me? Here
goes one last spin. How do I just keep leaning on bankrupt? I hate game shows that do this.
It's so stupid. Go to zero times 10 points. What's the point of having a fucking wheel
if it doesn't matter until the last spin of the game? You heard the buzzer. That means time is up.
Yes, we have some. Just have no rounds then. Your chance to solve. No, it's not cheese.
I don't know. No, we don't seem to have any of those. Yes, we have some essence.
Well, that is a healthy amount to add to your winnings tonight. Contestant number three,
your chance to solve. RNG bankruptcy is stupid, especially when you land on it
10 times over the course of an hour. Sleep. Time is running low. Only sleep. Sleep. I don't know.
Wait, just pass. Yeah, you got to pass. Otherwise you're going to lose points.
Oh, I don't know. Sheep. I don't know.
Yes, we have some peas. I guess you'll be paying for dinner tonight.
Contestant number two, you like to solve? What? Oh, god damn it. How do I leave the game?
My brain was just like sheep pot pie. One more and no more of this dog shit bankrupt RNG nonsense.
Would you come up with that? But that's not even fair. I got bankrupt like three times.
Our lucky contestant looks eager to start the bonus round. So let's get over there.
This should be a slaughter rule. If you land on bankruptcy more than three times in a game,
you just get like five grand. Showbiz. There are six letters we can give you. R, S, T, L, N,
and E. Let's see what kind of help we can get. Would you please choose three consonants and a
vowel? Nice scented drawers. You're having you're having general sows tofu. That's just
the kind of sounds good. Like general general gouse chicken right now. Oh, man, that sounds good.
So get ready to solve. That sounds good. Broadway writer actor. No Broadway writer.
General Gao. General so general sow general. Yeah, I know guys. Do you really go look up
that the origin of this? It's a different menu item everywhere. 10 seconds remaining.
While you got the most money, you didn't get the bone. But I think you should still be happy
at different restaurants. It's general T, S, O, general T, like sow, tau, god. It's listed
at different things. I don't even care if you stream snipe. Just go on. Let's go one more.
Yeah, there's actually an argument as to who made it up. Like, where did it come from?
Look into it. What was it? Why is everybody laughing? Why is everybody laughing?
You had to pay for a Nintendo Switch subscription with that name to get started.
Thank you for joining us today. Your outfit looks quite interesting. You must have visited
the customization menu. It says here. Well, it doesn't say much. Why don't you tell us about
yourself? Get ready for the toss up. The category on this one is free. There we go. We got these two
dorks in the Wheel of Fortune shirts. It looks like you're ready to solve contestant number two.
I would have gotten this wrong. I would have gotten this wrong. Wow. I'm so glad it wasn't me. But in
case in case he's got it wrong, I got it. It's me. It's me. I got it at the crack of dawn.
I was gonna say I thought I had it wrong. Okay. All right. At the crack of dawn.
Okay, come on. Let's go. Things. Trousers. Oops. Oh my god. Oops. I fucked it up. It's um,
shit. I didn't mean to do that. I just saw the second word. I know what the second word is,
but what's the first word? Collapsible. I don't I know what the second word is.
I know what I fucking don't care. I don't know. Contestant number three, your chance to solve
all. Columbus? Columbus umbrella? What is a Columbus umbrella? What are these things I've
never heard of before? Columbus? What is a Columbus umbrella? Okay, dude, what are you doing? Why would
you do? Um, excuse me? What? No answers from the contestants. Let's try again. Good to see our
contestants are so eager to play. We shouldn't keep them waiting. So wait, we all lost.
Contestant number one, go ahead and take the first spin. I thought a Columbus umbrella was gonna be
all right. Yeah, I'll give you a Columbus umbrella. Like, I don't know. I thought it was like a
specific kind of umbrella. Yeah, it's like super durable. It could take you across the Atlantic.
I don't know, man. I have no idea. L. Dude, you're cooked. I'd rather be cooked than raw.
Let's just put it that way. Fortunately, there are none on the board. I'm sorry.
600. Yes, we have some s's. Okay. That's a fair bit of cash. Silly songs. No H. Okay. One on the
board. See, then it sucks. Sucks when it happens, doesn't it? Bankrupt is always a pain. Sucks when
it happens, doesn't it? Yeah, it does. Let's get us a vowel here. What vowel would you like?
Something E. I want another one. You've certainly, unfortunately, that's not what we
have a idea of what that first word is. But I don't know. I don't know. I'm trying to.
I can't say the I wish I could like mute and be like in a different channel.
It looks like you're ready to solve. You're gonna solve. Really? No, you don't know this. What's
everybody just munching on the keyboard until the 10 seconds remain? Soil. Soil jug. I think,
honestly, I think the host would be like, everything all right. Are you okay? I know
what the first word is. Let's see if I can get it by playing. I can't say it. I love.
All right. All right. Okay. Come on. What? No, no, no, no. Back, back, back, back. I know it. I
know the answer. I know the answer. I know the answer. I know the answer. I know the answer.
I actually know the answer now. I want to go back. I'm literally going to quit the game if
I get bankrupt. Smiling emojis. Let's go. First place. First place. Let's go. First place.
Are we all ready to start? Yes. Fun and games. Contestant number two. Why don't you go ahead
and take the first spin? All right. Now flip it and get bankrupt. Not a single one on the board.
I don't even see what you picked. I wish he would say the letter because sometimes it happens so
quickly that I don't even know what letter it was. Fun and games. 500. M. Tycoon management.
500. That's a fair bit of cash you picked up. 650. 650. Yes, we have some arms. I guess you'll be
paying for dinner tonight. What is that second word? Trump? Oh, I'm going to get it. I just have
to be careful. I'm going to try to make some extra money here, but I do know the second word.
650. Yep. What is the first word? It's so close. 700. Okay. Is it only vowels? What?
You can certainly buy a vowel. What would you like? What kind of trampoline is this?
I got it. I got it. I got it. I got it. I got it. I got it. But I'm going to spin for extra money.
More money. Again. One more. Yep. Yep. Yep. How does this work?
All right. I'm going to solve it now. Backyard trampoline. Oh no. It's trampoline. Right?
Backyard trampoline. All right. Over 5k. That's quite a lot. This would be the one to go out on
it. If I can get it, I'll go out on this one. 700. Yes. We have some before and after. Great job.
That's quite a bit of cash in your pocket now. 650. Will we get any help? Okay. This is where I can
run away with it. Let me do the bonus round too. Come on. We're going with an H. Unfortunately,
there are none on the board. I'm sorry. This is the last round, right? There's nothing else after
this. I don't think. Ladies and gentlemen, we got a first time chatter here. Omni Jack. Welcome to
the channel. I do this for every new follower. Every new chatter. Yes. I think I know the second
word. Something. Something. Yes. We have some. All right. You're coming back. I don't like this.
Don't forget you have that wild card. Would you like to use it? Yes. We have some. That's
a fair bit of cash. I don't like this. Come on. Lose it all. Lose it all right here. What's the
first? What's the first word? Yes. We have some. Fuck. Yes. We have some. What is the fucking first
word? I guess you'll be paying for dinner tonight. Are you ready to solve contestant number two?
Baseball diamond earrings. This game is fucking terrible. What a what a dog shit game this really
is. Baseball diamond before and after before and after. Baseball diamond earrings. What the fuck are
you talking about? What does that have to do with anything?
$3,320. Are we ready for another toss up round? The amount is $3,000. Before and after.
What it why base. Contestant number three. What's for dinner? Baseball diamond. Baseball diamond
earrings. You just picked three random words. That's not a phrase. That's not a before app.
You just picked three random words and put them together and instead it was a fucking
random name. Only 10 seconds remaining. You got it. Let's get this round started.
I'll give the wheel one last pick. Let's go. Oh it's a phrase. The phrase is shoe chowder. Okay.
Any of those? No. I'm R. Contestant number one. I can't solve it with that. We have one S. Good
job. That contestant number two. Do you like to solve? We have one E. Contestant number three.
Your chance to solve. Walt Disney? Who the who what what? I was like is this a person? How do
you know that? I'm sorry there are none. I'm not gonna win. It's almost impossible. Any of those?
I gotta solve it. Yes we have some C. No small amount of cash to test the number three. Your
chance to solve. There's no way you know what this is. Camp idea. Why are you both doing? Are
these bots? Why they both just did the same exact word at the end? It's a bot. What? Unfortunately
there are none on the board. How is there no A in this whole thing? Oh so sorry time is up.
Will we get any help on this? It seems we're out of luck. What is this word man? Unfortunately
there are none on the board. What? Unfortunately there are none on the board. I'm sorry. No I'm
sorry. We have one N. Well that is a healthy amount to add to your winnings tonight. Contestant
number two. Your chance to solve. Coin? Coin? No dude it's not a coin collector.
Oh my god. Did I come in last place again? All right I'm doing one more. I'm doing a quick one.
Very quick quick quick quick quick quick quick. How did you come up with that? Fast. Very fast.
Incredibly fast. I'm doing one quick round and that's it. Let's get started with the bonus. Did
I miss any raids or anything? I was like freaking out with the song thing. We were talking about
Bjork and everything. Baseball diamond earrings? Would you follow me over here please? Oh that's
okay. Baseball diamond. Oh I get it. I thought it was whatever. We'll give you the typical. I thought
it was like baseball like diamond earrings and I'm just sitting there going why what are you talking
about? Contestant would you please choose three consonants and a vowel? Baseball Bjork. You know
what's crazy? I'm gonna go. I'm gonna go listen to some Bjork after this. Some of the classics.
Time is short so get ready to solve. Zud deeds. Do it. You do it. Do it for the joke. You won't.
You won't do it. You won't do zud deeds. You know you won't. What? No. Wait how come you didn't fail?
Why why are you not failing this? If you get it wrong you lose. What's what? Would you settle
for $45,000? I thought you if you got it wrong you lose. You can guess as many times as you want. I
did not know that. All right let's do it. We are going for it. Quick round. That's it. Baseball
diamond earrings. God damn it. I get it now. Thanks for playing guys. I'm doing a quick round. Quick.
This is the final one for real. If you lose. If you don't lose I will eat my gamer gunk. Like the
stuff only in your key. Wait what? Ladies and gentlemen. The dust. You're talking about like
the dust in your keyboard. Hello. It says here. Well it doesn't say much. Why don't you tell us
about yourself? What? That's an old meme. With like the oh all the gamers gunk and junk that
you have in your keyboard. We use the gamer gunk remover. What are you talking about? Let's go.
Yeah don't eat it. Don't. What are you stupid? All right. I was going to say beautiful senses.
Beautiful sunset. Take it.
Let's go. Last one. My message got removed. I said germa balls sweep.
The free play. You've got a second chance. All right. Vowels free.
Certainly got the money. Yes we have some ease. Okay. 700. We have. Okay. Wild. Nice.
We have one seed. Could you pick up that one and you can use it if you'd like.
Go and spend all. Looking good. 800. This is hoax. 800. We have one. It's a thing.
Well that is a healthy amount. What vowel would you. We have one A. What vowel would you like.
We have one O. We have certainly got. We have one Q. Thank god. Bankrupt is always a painful one.
It shouldn't even be on the board. It shouldn't even be on the board. It really shouldn't.
600. Can you imagine if a roulette wheel had bankrupt and the dealer just takes all your chips.
That's a lot of. No it sucks. It was stupid. It'd be dumb.
Have any of those. It's what. I don't know. Like I'm going to keep guessing.
600. Wow. Not a single one of them. 600. Yes we have. Well that's a healthy.
You're going too fast. Slow it down. Is always a painful. Yeah. What a great feature.
I know what the second word is. But what is the first word. Honest to goodness.
Well I know what the second word is. I'm going to keep going. Something background.
That's a fair bit of cash. He. He's. Tends to. Guys I have no idea.
650. We have one. Something background. I. Tainable background. That's a healthy amount
to add to your winnings tonight. What. Letters are even left. Why don't you go ahead and tell
us the answer. F. F. Elton. Is. You 10. If none of these work. F 10 sub F 10 sub.
Act in Elton's. Eld El 10. I ain't. You 10 sub. You 10. If you. Elton style.
Eld. You 10. Why don't I know what this is. 10 seconds remaining. What the fuck is this
fucking word. What is this word man. What is this word. Contestant number two. Extensible
extensive background. Extensive background. Extensive background. What drugs are you on
if that's a word that you've ever used. I'll give the wheel extensive. It's still anybody's game.
Oh well look at that extensive background. So sorry but we're out of time for this person
even playing anymore. Just screaming. I'm not going to win this and I'm going to be actually
guessing for letters. That's so annoying. Charlie's going to come in here at the very end and get it
right. Yes we have. Occupation. Your chance to solve. First time chatter. We've got it.
Oh they were deleted. Will we get any help. It was removed. Your first message was removed.
No no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no. I got it. I got it. I'm going to get it right
here. Wait what. We have one. All right. All right guys this is it. Fashion. Fashion and clothing
designer. Fashion and. Fashion and interior designer. Fuck. What is it. You're a fashion
designer. If you're a fashion designer what else. Fashion and lifestyle. Fashion and lifestyle
designer. I don't know. Yes we have. Fashion and what designer. Aren't you just a aren't you a
fashion designer. You're not a fashion and and something else. You're a fashion designer.
What other kind of designer would you be. Also a fashion and something else. You're also this.
Yes we have some eyes. Contestant number. Your chance to solve. Watch this piece of fashion and
doctor or something. Fashion and. Fashion and. Oh no. There's not enough.
There's not a word. They don't have letters. What. No. Fashion. I'm trying to fill in the
second word. Isn't it. Isn't it. Isn't it more. Wait hold on. No no no no. Wait a minute. Wait a
minute. Isn't it longer than that. It's not jewelry right. Isn't it. Is it jewelry.
That mother fucker gave me the answer. I fucking. I think we're ready to start the bonus round.
Let's get. I thought he was. Jewel. I thought it was like jewelry. Ask you to go ahead and pick
consonants. Hey. Hey. Wait a minute. They're all feeding answers to people in the sub discord.
We've got. Well we got a controversy here. We have to handle. We've got a controversy that
we need to deal with here. Time is short. So get ready to solve. We've got it. We've got a
controversy. I can't believe he gave me the answer. I thought. I honestly thought that. Oh
my god. You know it's. I have no excuse but like I thought you were fucking with me or something.
I thought it was just like oh fashion and jewelry designer. There's a controversy. They've been
feeding them answers in the sub discord. Controversy alert. While you got the most money.
I'm not done. I'm literally doing one more and I'm fucking out of here. I don't care what happens.
I can't believe they gave me the answer. See what you should have done is you should have
wrote answer and then delete it and then write it. I. Jewelry. Jewelry. It just doesn't look
right. You know. Hold on. Let me. I could write this out. Jewelry. No it doesn't. Yeah.
It doesn't look right. I thought like jewelry. Jewelry. Whatever. Jewelry is traditional British.
I'm swear to god. Right. I thought it was like jewelry. Not like jewelry. Right. That's not an
inaccurate way to spell it. It's like with two L's. Right. Jewelry is a. Jewelry is correct.
Jewelry is some. I'll take that. A great. We're ready to get started. It says it's American and
British English. Hold on. I want to look this up. Jewelry. Thank you for joining us today.
Your outfit looks quite interesting. You must. It's time for a toss up round for one thousand
dollars. The category. Jewelry. Jewelry is the American English and jewelry is the British
English. The British fucking English is the correct one. Contestant number two. I thought
there was more word letters. Undy. So yeah. I had it right. It's just another way to spell it.
What is it? Food and drink. All right. Come on. You suck. These names are killing me.
All right. Come on. That was. I don't think you're going to be. I don't think you know.
Yeah. What's the British way to spell this part? Wait. What do you. Wait. Hold on. Wait. I'm going
to get it wrong. What? Contestant number three. I pressed. I pressed the button. What? Uncle Ben's
couldn't. Converted rice. No sense in. Let's go ahead and get. Let's get. I thought it was.
I thought it was convenient. Contestant converted rice. So take a spin. Coveted rice.
Sorry. I got a little worked up. Very sorry. Just try to keep positive thoughts now.
They're cheating in the substream in the discord. Bunch of cheaters. Fine. You want to cheat? I'll
take you on right now. I'll beat the cheaters. It's fine. Yes. We have some teams. Go ahead.
What is it? With your free play. You aren't out of it yet. You've certainly got the money. We have
one. President sleeper. Stop. Will we get any help on this? It seems we're out of luck.
Stop. Ow. I unplugged it. Why would there be a fucking bee? You dumbass. No, I pulled this out
and I did. Why did that? I'm selling an explosion. Unfortunately, there are none on the board. I'm
sorry. I was ignoring answers in chat to be fair, but people were blowing up my DMS with answers.
I'm blowing up my DMS with answers. What was that? C? P. That's a fair bit of cash.
Something Pat. Pat? We have one. Go ahead and pick a card from the-
Pate. Pato. Potato. Sure, you can buy a vowel. Yes, we have some P's.
What? Pat? Ben Patty's?
700. Yes, we have some N's. It's crazy just how- This is new. What? Contestant number three,
your chance to solve. New patience? But how is that for a people? I mean, I guess it technically
is people. This is so vague. How did you come up with that? Don't skip it. I want to see it.
Let's go ahead and start the round. Holy shit. This is almost a full board. I'm going to give
the wheel another spin. I'm thinking of a person's name, right? But it's not a person, it's people.
Yes, we have some A's. Barbecue and sour onion. Pringles. How would I know?
Fortunately, you ran out of time. Yes, we have some R's. That sounds actually really good.
Barbecue Pringles right now. I actually think barbecue anything. Barbecue chips are disgusting.
To me, barbecue flavored chips of any kind are fucking gross.
Yes, we have some E's. Barbecue chips to me taste kind of like I'm smelling them. I'm not tasting
them. It's like a scent. It's not even a flavor. It's like I can smell them in my mouth. Does that
make any sense? No, no, I don't want to do that. Barbecue chips smell like coffee breath. Yes,
we have some P's. It's just like an off-putting aroma. Contestant number two, would you like to
solve? Kakarots and Mie. Okay, this is a meme answer. Josh. Kakarots and Mie Josh. All right.
Yes, we have some N's. Great job. That's quite a bit of cash. Contestant number three,
your chance to solve. I feel like the second word, we all know what it is. Yes, some C's.
Wait a minute. Hold on. Hold on. Hold on. Great job. Contestant number one, your chance to solve.
Macaroni and cheese. Macaroni and cheese. What else do you? Macaroni and cheese.
Crisps. Macaroni and cheese. Baked ziti. Macaroni and cheese. Food re-crisps. Cream.
Macaroni and cheese. Whipped cream. Macaroni and cheese. Croc. Macaroni and cheese.
Pepper and macaroni and cheese. I don't know. Yes, we have contestant number two.
Macaroni and cheese. But anytime I think of macaroni and cheese, I don't think of
four other words. Macaroni and cheese Josh. Is this this person's name?
Macaroni and cheese Josh breadcrumbs. Oh my fucking God. It's with breadcrumb topping.
No human says it like this. They say, oh yeah, I brought mac and cheese. Oh yes,
I brought mac and cheese with breadcrumb topping. No, you just say mac and cheese.
Don't say all this. This is like a word soup. Macaroni and cheese with breadcrumb topping.
You just say macaroni and cheese. So sorry, but time is out.
All right, you fail it too, so I win. Yes, we have some eyes. This is British. Contestant number
three. No, but macaroni and cheese with breadcrumb topping. To me, that's that's more than one thing
you're talking. Macaroni and cheese. Macaroni and tweez with oh my goodness. All right, then I'll
get it then guys. Yes, we have some bones. I think I still lose. Contestant number one to solve.
Macaroni and cheese with breadcrumb topping. I was thinking like with something else or with
bacon on it or I don't know or another food. All right, actual last one. Truly last one. I swear.
I promise this is the last one. I'm not doing another one after this no matter what. I promise
no matter what. No matter what. I think we're ready to start the bonus round. Let's get over there.
Please follow me over to food and drink. I think you know the letters. R, S, T, L, N, N, E. Let's
see what kind of help you can get. Stop saying this is the last one no matter what. This is the
final one no matter what. If I don't leave, I'll just say end stream. I'll just go and press it.
Wow, you made that look easy. This is it for real. I know it's getting late.
I know it's getting late. This will be it. I promise. This is it. Okay, time is limited,
so solve the puzzle. Okay, good luck. Food and drink. Something. Cookies.
You swing an axe at mail budget. No, you won't. Oh, yeah, I will. Yeah, I like I should have been
like a boxer. I wouldn't get touched once. I wouldn't get hit by one punch. It would be like
I wouldn't get hit one time. Not once. You got the most money. You didn't get the
bone. Batch of warm cookies. You should still be happy with that. If I was in the medieval times
and we were at like we were in a battle, I wouldn't get hit once.
Somebody said you're hallucinating. Dude, fuck up. You would have died of the plague,
not of a punch in the face or an axe to the head. Yeah, I would have eaten the old sandwich on the
ground and died from the plague. That would be etched on my gravestone. It says here it doesn't
say much. Why don't you tell us about yourself? But on my gravestone, it'd say here lies Sir Jeremy
Albertson, the swift. And it would say you have my record on it. It'd be like five hundred and
zero. Five hundred zero dash zero. What are you doing? It looks like you're ready to solve
contestant number three. Jeremy, you danced on stream once and had to take a month off.
No, I danced on stream and realized how bad my condition was. So then I decided to take a month
off. I could dance right now and be fine. No, I'm not going to do that. There was no accent
involved. There was no there was no battle acts. There was no sword, no broadsword, no bastard sword.
How lucky they are. Shall we go ahead and start the round? Dude, I'm going to go to like a,
I'm going to go to like a larping event thing or like a martial artist place and go there and be
like, come get me and just dodge everything. Is this going to end up like, didn't Steven Seagal
do this? He was like pushing people over. How fucking funny would it be though if I like got
a real professional martial artist facility to humor me and they just beat the shit out of me.
I was like, all right, let's go. And it was just like, oh, oh, and I was like, stop, stop,
I'm sorry. And that was the whole stream. And then I turned it off. I'm not messing around.
Okay. You're not messing around. I love how this person is communicating with us.
I'm not messing around. Smile. Okay. There you go. There you go. Why am I smiling like an alien?
What if he heard what a smile was? No, what am I doing? I'm an alien. Don't seem to have any of
those. Oh, it's my turn. Oh, all right. You're good. Pretty good.
I love all the people dancing over here. Is it the music? You're dancing to the music.
This is a fun stream. Play three games today. I usually don't do that. Maybe one or two.
I usually don't do three. This one. Okay. I know it. I want money. I know this one.
I'm going to try to get as much cash as I possibly can. This would be the Sydney Opera House
for all of you in the chat. Why don't you get home? That's a fair bit of cash.
Just no bankrupt bullshit, please. Yes, we have some wines.
All right. One more and that's it. No more. No bankrupt. No bankrupt. No bankrupt. No bankrupt.
No bankrupt. No bankrupt. Don't do it. 2,500. I'd like to solve a puzzle, please.
Contestant number or chance to solve
Sydney Opera House. I'm going to actually win this one. I got lucky. Wow. That is incredible.
How did you come up with that? Let's go ahead and start the round. Just don't lose it here
at the end and I should be fine. Give the wheel another spin by 50. What are you doing?
That's a lot of money too. It's really easy for somebody to get like 15,000 right now.
I guess you'll be contestant number two. You're not a single one on the board. I'm sorry. Really?
We don't seem to have any of those. Yes, we have some ends. I've got quite a bit of money now.
Contestant number two. Would you like to solve? Yes, we have some I. Contestant number three.
Ing ing. Come on. Sussing. Sussing my. Oh no. Okay. Elaborate. Sussing my mouse.
Sussing my mousing. Time is running low. Sussing my jaw. What's with this? Josh just keeps writing
his own name for the answers. Why? Why do you just keep writing your own name? E. Will we
get any help on this? How is it not an E? This is the best controller by the way. The Switch Pro
controller. Just kidding. Contestant number one. Your chance to solve. Is it not bad? Yes,
we have some. It's not bad. The buttons could be a little better. I like the analogues though.
I like the mouth feel. Contestant number two. Your chance to solve. Making my Christmas list.
Making my what? Making my. That's a fair bit. Contestant number three. Would you like to solve?
I still win. Making my soy list. Making my. All right. Yeah, you got it. You got it. I don't think
you win though. It's gonna be close. Making my shopping list. Will you win the game if you do
this? If you do, that's gonna be funny. You only have two seconds though. Oh, so sorry. No, I
would have won anyways. Finally, I win. All it took was somebody in chat to lose in front of me.
All right. Let's take this to the bonus round. That's it. Thanks for playing guys. Good job.
To be honest, I wasn't sure how you were gonna. Bonus round. Let's go.
I just realized the audio has been coming through the mic the entire time.
G. Would you follow me over here please? Thing. We'll give you the typical letters. R, S, T, L, N,
and E. Free. Free. Three N's. Free. We have three consonants and a vowel please. I don't know.
P, B, H, and A. Wow, you made that look easy. Free bananas. Just a few moments to solve. So go
quickly. Free man. Free. Free. Free man. Free man. Free man. Time is running low. Only 10
seconds remaining. I don't know. I actually just don't know. While you got the most money,
you didn't get the bonus, but I think you should still be happy with that cash.
Okay. Okay. All right. That's fun. This game's fun. Wheel of Fortune. I would love to see a
nerd version though. That'd be good. All right. That's it. I'll see you guys later.
Thanks for watching. We went a little late, but I did start a little late so that's fine.
Really appreciate everyone sticking around. We did a lot of random stuff today.
So the plan, I've got a lot of stuff going on this weekend. You probably will see me,
you might see me at some point this weekend, but you will absolutely see me Monday or Tuesday.
There's a lot of stuff for baseball that I have to get done. So I need to take some more time.
I think you'll probably see me on like Saturday. I'm going to try to stream Saturday.
Thanks for sticking around. Always fun. Games were interesting too. That first one was pretty
fun. Second one was pretty fun. Third one. I would like to see the rules change in Wheel of Fortune,
but thanks for watching guys. Here's your outro music.
Bring back the camera. This is the outro. We'll get, you know what? We'll probably,
I know I keep putting it off, but I just don't feel like getting scared. The next time I stream,
hold me to this. We're going to do some of the Dread X stuff. Put it in the suss so I can't
change it. There's still unpaid debt. Yeah, there is a lot of it. What's Dread X? It's a
kind of like a Jackbox party pack of horror games. They've made about five or six of them,
right? I'm looking forward to it. All right guys. See you later. Thanks for watching.
Good night. Goodbye. See you maybe on Saturday. If not, then absolutely on Monday or Tuesday.
And I'm very excited. I cannot wait for this baseball stream. It's going to be so much fun.
Take care guys. See you later.