Hello. Good afternoon, everybody. Just realized that my Wiimote doesn't have a strap.
Physically, it doesn't. I don't have one. Why? Where did it go? I gotta be careful. Don't want
to put a hole in my monitor's head. He's not using protection. Unsafe? That's unsafe. It's not that
unsafe. As long as you don't play a game that requires you to, like, throw or move really
quickly. And the only movements in No More Heroes are you just shake. You know, I, if, do you need
a strap for a salt shaker or a pepper shaker? No. That'd be kind of odd. That's the same motion
that I'm doing in this game. Anyways, we're going to continue No More Heroes. We're probably going
to get to the end tonight. Pepper shakers have a thick base. This is, like, as heavy as a pepper
shaker is. We are currently rank six assassin level. Climb in the ladder. And then tomorrow
is New Year's Eve. Tomorrow, we'll be doing a little bit of festivities. We'll be dropping
the ball Eastern time, not Pacific time. Remember, that's important. It's gonna be weird, though. I
think I did this last year, too. It was, like, 8.59 p.m. And I'm like, here we go, Ted! No, it's, like,
it's 9 o'clock, where I am. But we'll do that tomorrow. He's gonna drop his balls. I knew that
I was gonna show up somewhere. I just didn't know when. Do a countdown for every time zone in the
world. I'm not doing that. Winks are scams. Purple gang, rise up. Well, you just dropped 1200
channel points. You could have saved to get to 75,000 and got me to turn my camera on and wink.
That's too bad. All right, let's get going. Let me just give me one second. I'll be
here. I'll be here. I'm just moving something around. Maybe one second.
Yeah, that's true. Somebody just mentioned. When is the first New Year?
Australia? When is the first 2020? Somewhere in Australia? New Zealand? It's in New Zealand. All
right. So when? When? Or, like, I mean, like, relative to, like, hours from now, when is it
2020 for the first place? First time? It already happened. No, it didn't. New Year's is first
celebrated on the small island nations of Tonga. Okay. Well, happy. When is it? Let's see. I'm
gonna say, I'm gonna look up what time is it in Tonga right now. Tonga time. It is 102 p.m. Yeah,
it's 1 p.m. December 31st. Okay. We might be live when the first ever 2020 happens. It might be
possible. No, we won't. I'm not gonna be live in 12 hours. What the fuck am I talking about?
Oh, yeah, we're gonna be live in 12 hours. No way. That's not happening. It ain't gonna take
me that long to finish. No more heroes. Maybe six to seven. All right. Welcome back. Let's play with
Kat. Those of you that weren't here yesterday, this is the most important thing in the game.
Hold on. This is a one-guy scenario. I need to read this. Jerma, how do you describe a streamer
to someone who doesn't understand anything about the internet? Um, it was like four in a row.
Okay, I feel like I'm playing Battlefield right now. What the fuck was that?
So, uh, what are you doing? What? Wait a minute. Wait, hold on. Dude, um, Freddy,
Freddy, you gave 23,000 bits last night, and now you've dropped 75,000 bits right now. That's
a fucking hundred thousand bits in not even 12, 24 hours. You madman. Holy shit. That's a
thousand dollars in bits. Funding for the 2020 carnival. Freddy dreads. Seriously. Holy fuck,
man. That's ridiculous. They say, happy new year's Jerma. Thank you for making this year
hilarious for me. Freddy dread gaming. Holy shit, man. That's, all right, so that was so
ridiculous. This is fucking crazy right now. Somebody just said that wasn't even a car,
that was a weed whacker. Um, thank you. Seriously, uh, Shazzo just dropped 20 community subs
also. That was a tiny car, huge bits. Uh, Shazzo 20 community subs and fucking Freddy with,
that's, I think that's one of the biggest drops of money I've ever seen on stream ever in one drop.
We've had during the thing was another scenario where there was like five, six, seven hundred
dollars worth of bits that would drop. It's fucking, this is unbelievable. Thank you. Happy
new year to you as well. Let's hope 2020 is, um, interesting as well. That's a lot of money. That
deserves a wink. You know what? It sure does. What was that frame? What was that? I think that was,
that was, that wasn't, I wasn't naked. Hey, I can't wink. I know you just, that's, thank you.
75,000 bits equals 75,000 channel points. Give me my bike. Can somebody, was you in a tank top
looking at the camera? Can you clip that? Somebody show me what, I want to see like when that was.
Was that from yesterday? No, it couldn't have been. Oh, I know what it was. I know what it was.
I know what it was. Oh, fucking God damn it. Uh, okay. So I'm going to let me explain what happened.
Okay. This is very important. Um, that was from earlier today. That was, look at the hair. I'll
get it on stream. That was, uh, so earlier this day I got, I got out of the shower
and I said, Oh, okay. It's time. Let me set up my stream. Let me get like started here. Sounds good.
And I turned on the cam. I was setting the camera up and I realized, uh, I'm wearing the same shirt
that I was wearing yesterday, the same tank top. So I, um, I was like, people are going to talk shit
about this. They're going to be like, Oh, you in the same clothes as yesterday. And I'm just like,
yeah, uh, I have to tie hats. I just, I took off my shirt and put on another shirt.
That's what happened. But I got exposed anyways. So there you go. What the fuck is going on with
70? What the 75? What is happening today? Oh, God damn it. No, no, not God damn like
75. People are finding ways to circumvent that. All right. Uh, core monster. That's 75 subs.
You maniac. Holy shit. That is an unfucking believable guys. That's, that's too much money.
75 fucking subs from core monster right now. And 75,000 bits from Freddy. You guys are too,
you guys are too kind. You guys spoil me. I'm just going to spend it on McChickens.
That's going to buy a lot of pizzas. Well, it's, it's, I can't even believe it. I'm forever fucking
grateful that somebody would give this much money to this room. And, uh, hopefully, hopefully all
the money that comes into this channel, I can use it and try to make stuff that I think would be
interesting. That's pretty much what it is. Pay to link streamer.
Laugh my ass off. You call yourself a Jerma fan. I'm fucking loaded on channel points, bro.
Every message could wait one. Where is this by the way? All this for, uh, all this for a thousand
dollars. It's not even worth it. Try talking to chat again when you're a true fan. I highlight
every message because I just that jacked. Oh, I see. But yeah, that was a big,
huge money drops from a few people here. Um, hopefully I can get this stupid thing out of
the ground. Where? All right. Seriously, where is it? Why was my thing rumbling over there? What?
Holy shit. Freddy just gave 50. Is that person naked? Freddy just gave 50 community subs.
Wait there. What are they? Fuck their tier two. These are tier two. What the fuck is going on?
Holy shit. That's insane. 50 tier two community subs from Freddy.
Freddy Dread. You've got to be kidding me. I had a dream last night that Jerma literally. What?
What are you talking about? Or I have to. Why was that just in there? Why was that just in the part
of it? Like the chat. Why was that just in the chat? Oh, anyways, holy fuck, man. That's,
that's insane. Tier two. That's the most ridiculous thing I've ever seen. That's Freddy Dread. Thank
you, Freddy. Thank you. Evil program. Five subs. Collie Brady. Five subs. I had a dream. What was
it? I didn't. I didn't. Okay. I didn't like chill. I need to see. What the fuck? Go gaming. I had a
dream. What was it? Just somebody PM it to me. Don't PM me. I had a dream last night. Everyone was
cheering. That's so funny to me. Everyone was screaming TOS or cheering. What the fuck?
We didn't even start. I haven't even started streaming yet. Oh my God. Evil program. Five subs.
Collie Brady. Five subs. Produce. Produce. Imagine having that dream though. Like I can't imagine
having a dream like that. Produces. All right. Get it together. Produces. Produces. San. Thanks
for the five subs. Slonk. CR. Thanks for the five subs. Seriously, guys. Henry1810 gave five subs.
Jesus. I had a dream. Oh my God. I can imagine waking up from that dream. I think that's one
of those dreams where you wake up afterward. After you, you look in the mirror and you just go like
why did I have that dream? Why did I have that dream? There's gotta be something. Like there's
gotta be a reason why I'm having a dream like that. Oh my God. He watches too much. Yeah but
all right. There's a difference between watching too much and then having a dream that I'm having
sex with somebody on stream. Why was the camera on? What are you having that dream for?
Dude, this is fucked. I have to just do this mission. Oh. This is killing me.
This is killing. I don't know why this is killing me. I don't. Okay. I know this is gonna sound
crazy because it's gonna be fucked. Just like. All right. Just mute if you. Oh but seriously.
Like I just picture. I just like. Oh you know like images that like you just. Like I just see the
chat and like the screen. Like it's. We're screen grabbing somebody's web browser and it's just
that's on the video player and there's a chat next to it and it's like all my like rules are underneath.
What is this one? What was this one? I don't even remember. Oh this one. Sometimes it seriously only
takes one thing that somebody says over here and it just fucks me up for the whole day.
I'm gonna be thinking about that all day. It's gonna pop up into my brain. I'm just. I'm a very
visual person. You know what I'm saying? Like I'm incredibly visual and I like. I will see the things
that people say up in my head and I'm gonna keep seeing that until tomorrow. Until it happens.
Okay I gotta relax.
Jesus Christ. We're good.
A lot of money from this one. Welcome back by the way to this is no more heroes.
It's been 20 minutes on stream. What the fuck has happened?
Is that it? One more. Did I get it? I didn't even see that. The video on the ground.
You got like a thousand dollars and then laughed at sex for 10 minutes. That's what's happened.
Yeah that about sums it up. You're right. That's pretty good recap. Oh there's a new job. There's
a new job. Can I still vote in the poll? Yes you can. If we can get the poll in the chat please.
Check it out. You have until tomorrow afternoon to vote.
Germa NYE 19 on Serbian Monkey. That's the one. What's the new job? Mine sweeping. Oh this is not
the scorpions yet. Clean up the mines buried in the beach. A bonus will be paid due to how
dangerous the work is. We're looking for high voter participation. Actually I think I can look
and see how many people have taken it so far. And like six cars drove by. A weed whacker drove by.
Like a bicycle. Like that was a weird first 10 minutes. Where do you vote on that survey monkey
page? Should be in the chat right now. Down to the beach. Let's do some mine sweeping. How much money
do we need? 350. The unspoken rules of Santa Destroy indicate danger. No one swims on the
beach here. There are military mines buried in the sand after all. The army used the beach for
testing out new maneuvers. You won't see any girls in bikinis and you'll need a metal detector to
avoid getting serious sunburn. What else would you expect in this place? No tourists. No sunbathe.
There's no logic. The god of landmines hates metal detectors. So work persistently. How does
this work? Safely remove the mines buried in the beach. Listen to your metal detector to locate
them. Then use your beam katana to destroy the mines. Do I need my the Wiimote thing?
Oh this. Where is it?
Where the hell is it? Oh it's it that's when I get when I get close enough.
I'm like insane. I'm insane. That scared the fuck out of me. That actually scared the shit out of
me. Jesus. Wow. He's a bad gamer. He's a bad gamer. He's not a very good gamer. He's a bad gamer.
I could change clothes too. Well where is it? How much are these worth? Because I only have three.
Holy shit. It's right here. It's two thousand per mine. That sucks. I have to pick up trash.
We gotta do each one once though. At close. Where is it?
What just happened? Boomer. Boomer. Boomer. He's a boomer.
It's gonna be 20,000. I'm gonna I'm gonna get a horrible grade.
This might be the first non-placing grade of the whole entire gameplay. This is not going to even
be bronze. I might not even place. You can't get below bronze? Really? Yeah this one kind of sucks.
I don't remember this one. Let me get 10. Let me get a clean 10.
Come on. Where is it? Where is it? Where is it? Come on. Come on. Come on. Just step on it.
Just step on it. Step on it. Step on it. T.O.S. What the fuck. T.O.S. dude. Yeah that one sucks.
20,000. Gold medal. I could pick up trash and make 60. Got another job for you. Something a little
shadier. Okay I just unlocked another assassin mission. Uh noodle is bad at gaming is the one
that had the dream. They said hey Jeremy glad I could make you laugh with that remark about my
dream. Laughing my ass off. I must say it had me pretty fucked up in the morning. Happy new year I
guess. I'm just happy that I was the one guy. Happy new. Happy new year I guess. Oh that means
it was hilarious. That was like a really funny thing to read. It was just outrageous. I guess.
Not eligible for funniest one guy moment unfortunately. Unfortunately.
Kill as many as you can within the time. Mission ends so just kill as many as you can.
3,000 per kill. I'll try it. It's at the beach. 2019 snub. You said how you're not going to get
this image out of your head until tomorrow. Try to imagine what it's like for them. They can't ever
watch a German stream the same way ever again. Uh this community is fucking hilarious. Sometimes
people think I'm like fucking I'm like kidding around when I say that or I'm like making it up.
There's just like so many things. Your viewers are fucked. I don't I don't know about that.
Jeremiah had 7.5k points. Please wink. No I'm sorry. That's not how it works.
I was hoping to like GTA style. Hit that and fly over into the beach.
But there's an invisible wall. I have 12k. Can you wink for me? Does it cost 12k or does it cost 75k?
Which one? He thinks this game is as good as GTA. Where's the entry here? Is it up? What?
Will you wink at 70 at the 75,000 bit guy's wedding?
I could have just. All right let's make some money. Let's make some fake money in game.
Kill as many as possible. Let's go. Do you guys all have guns?
There he is. Come on. My weapon's not good enough.
Let's bring it together. Was it 3,000 per kill? Already better than looking at the mines.
What Star Wars game is this? I don't know. We talked about that yesterday. Did I fight
Holly Summers yet? I did. That's the last thing I did last night. Hey.
Oh, the best thing in this game is when you get like seven people to stand in a row and you do the
side swipe and you hit every single one. It's so satisfying. I only have one person left.
That's it. 20? Nuts or chocolate? Nuts or chocolate? What do you mean nuts or chocolate?
Why do I have to pick? That's a lot of money. Why do I have to pick? You have to pick. I mean
nuts are healthier than chocolate, but I think chocolate's better than nuts. But you can't,
you know what I mean? Like I think chocolate is better than a nut, but nuts are healthier,
so I'd rather eat nuts more than I would eat chocolate. What? What? What's wrong with that?
No, all I'm saying is, all I'm saying is that chocolate is good. I like chocolate.
I like to eat chocolate, but chocolate doesn't, you don't have to eat chocolate every single day.
Okay? Nuts are healthy, but the thing about nuts is they can be a little salty. You know what I'm
saying? Nuts can be too salty. Too much so that you don't want to eat them. Chocolate is sweeter.
It's a little tastier, but I don't know. It depends. Actually, some restaurants do it better
than others. Chocolate from one restaurant versus chocolate from another restaurant. What I'm saying
is like what you like. I just fucking, I just, I just fucking hit a pulp. God damn it, guys.
In my defense, I simply just looked up car crash sound, like car, and I found this video,
and it's like car crash, and it's got, this thing's got fucking 1.6 million views,
and I'm sitting there waiting for the car crash sound to play, and it took 24 seconds to go by.
That's not, that sounded like a firework. Oh shit, my wee.
No, not my center bar. I didn't have my strap.
Fuck. Okay, let's go. Let's go. I have to play. I'm all twisted up right now. I'm,
I'm twisted up. I'm him. I'm twisted up today. I'm very twisted. Let's get a new,
let's get some new sunglasses. Okay. Black, pink, pink. Yeah. Get the Guy Fieri shades.
We'll do pink. Guy Fieri doesn't have pink shades. Ooh, ooh, I like that one.
The cobra? No, that's a, it's a lion. That's a cobra. I mean, that's very clearly a lion,
but look at that cobra face. This is too much money. Ooh, I actually like that look. Black and
white. Black and white with pink shades. I would wear this out. Wouldn't wear these out. Ooh,
this matches. But there's, boy, there's a hamburger one.
I love chainsaws. You say psycho, like it's a bad thing. Yep. That's the one. No, not yet.
Give me that one. I got, I gotta get the one that's hung up in every single college dormitory.
Like on the wall. It's like beer cans and shit all over the place. Oh yeah. What's that on the
wall? What's that plaque over there? That's good. Matches the shades. What about jeans? New pants?
Now, where the black jeans? Right there. I love a good pair of black jeans. They go with everything.
I'll keep my, no, these ones are ugly. I'm spending all my money. No, actually, I don't like these
jeans. Get them off. I mean, this looks bad, but who cares? All right. That's, I do, I do like the,
the rocket popsicle. That's what that is. What is it? Is it America or popsicle?
By the way, you can't, where do you get those now? You can't buy those anymore.
Colgate. Now I see rocket popsicle. Yeah, Colgate too. Yeah. These are at the dollar store.
Wow. You're a clown. Let's get a good look. It's not bad. Although I just spent all my money.
Let's do another assassin mission. Let, no, let me see if I can do some of these because look,
it's been 20, I can, I can do some of these, uh, free missions. We don't get hit. Go to the beer
icon. You got it. Dude, does German, is German one of those people that looks at chat? You got it.
I'm going in right now. I think I do have seven, a ball in return. Let me teach you something.
Select the technique that you want. Ooh. Memory of three displays the position of enemies on
the mini map. That's pretty good. Allows a jumping slash to be performed
by shaking the nunchuck. Also pretty good. Allow a dash to be performed by pressing B button.
I think I want that one. Memory of woman extends dark side mode. Time limit. All right. That's not
bad, but I, these are all increases the range of your grab. That's good too. Earn bonuses based
on your rank. What does that mean? Allows a jumping down attack. I'm going to do the dash.
This one I can dash with B. I feel like that's like a bloodborne dash, right?
Technically, or is it a sprint? We'll find out.
Learn the technique of Czar. You got that? I'm back. I'm really tired of the pre-recorded streams
lately. Honestly, I mean, appreciate the effort, but it's just sad. I'm really tired about the
pre-recorded streams lately. I mean, I appreciate the effort, but it's just sad. Planted message.
Time for a, where is it? Let's do this one. Literally no one said that. Yes, they did.
Look at the logs. Let me take a look at his list. Which one of these haven't I done?
Bronze on this one, but it's only 30k. So silver, silver, gold, nothing in the time limit. Okay.
90,000 kill 100 enemies mission. How long will this take though? I feel like it's going to take
too long. Going to bat. I'll do this one. 5,500 per kill. I'm here for the VOD chat.
Didn't they get rid of that? Doesn't exist anymore? Doesn't. The thing about VOD chat though,
why would they get rid of it? I mean, I get, was it, were they trying to like save
data or something? Why would you have it? Yeah, I mean, I guess it's one of those things where
it's, it's just, there's no reason to get rid of it and there's no reason to have it. Right?
It's weird. Core Monster just came in with another huge money drop. Core Monster,
I have to hunt 10,000 bits from Core Monster. Another 100 fucking dollars. In bits, 10,000 drop
on top of the other stuff. Thank you Core Monster for your insane contributions. It's true that this
is a pre-recorded stream because these are pre-recorded bits. Now that would be very
interesting. That would be very interesting. How did I miss that? Fuck, I don't want to mess this
up. I have to get away. One more, one more, one more, one more. Give me, give me, give me one more.
Oh, pre-recorded stream, pre-recorded bits. How would you pre-record bits? You would have to,
you would have to sit here. That'd be really hard to do because you would have to sit here
the whole time and then wait for this exact moment where I'm about to address your bits
and time it correctly so I don't do it too early or too late.
Hmm, would be interesting. What do I got for money? 330, I need, uh, we'll do, we'll do one more trash
pickup or I'll try to get one of the, uh, you are late in addressing bits half the time. Still have
to get it close. Look at that one. LOL, he killed that guy. Don't take a single hit. This one's hard
because you have this one area and there's a shitload of people. You just have to, you gotta get
kind of lucky actually. Let's try this. I'm gonna go for this.
Oh, I don't have any battery. How am I gonna do this? I don't have any battery.
The dash? Oh, it is a run. It's a sprint. Oh, it's a sprint. It's a sprint. It's a sprint.
It's a sprint. It's a sprint. I thought it was like a hup, hup, hup, hup, hup, like a dodge,
like better than a better dodge. It's a sprint. All right, gold, gold, gold. I got gold on
everything. What's, what is the most money? Ponpon. Probably garbage, right? And plus I can sprint.
Yeah, let me do garbage collector.
Super frog. How can you not like it? Don't forget the new sword too. Yeah, I know. And I have to
train. There's a lot to do. I don't even need the motorcycle anymore, do I? Is this faster? Is this
as fast as the motorcycle? It might be. Bike is faster? All right, yeah it is. When am I gonna
get Jerma's super frog? There already is Jerma's super frog. It's a BTTV emote.
I know that song by heart.
Why is the bike so big? It just is. This actually might go smoother.
Can I sprint with the thing on my back? Find out. Jerma uses BTTV emotes because he hates mobile
viewers. It's not true. Wow, this is gonna be great. I should be able to get like at least six to here.
Hates mobile viewers. Which way? Bad route. You're playing death stranding. Not quite.
You know, it would be kind of interesting. You know, you, you, everyone makes like the,
oh it's a strand type game. That's like the joke, right? It's the strand game.
But imagine if there was a game like GTA where if you ate anything, if you actually just made trash,
it would be way worse than this. The streets would be made out of trash.
If you like ate food in a like a game like GTA, let's say you need to eat to live
and every time you ate something it just got thrown on the ground. If that went into everybody
else's game, there would be people specifically eating just to make sure there was trash on the
ground. I wonder what an experiment would look like if you had like, if you actually had a game
whose sole purpose was built around people making trash and people cleaning up the trash
and you got to pick which one you wanted to do. That would be insane, right? I'd pick up the trash
and make picking up the trash way more difficult than just throwing it on the ground.
Get to 50 please. Even with the sprint, not even good. Yeah and when you pick up the trash, you get
you pick up a hundred pieces. If you get like a hundred cans you get a new skin
or if you deliver a hundred bags of trash you get, you unlock like skins and stuff.
All right I'm going for this one right here. The game could just be called Town Cleanup.
I wonder how many different discord groups would appear to try to systematically put
as much trash down as humanly possible and how many others would be trying to do against it.
Kill him. Viscera Cleanup Detail? Yeah like Viscera Cleanup Detail but it's not a lot.
What the fuck was that lock on? What was that lock on? I tried to change the lock on and it got
whacked. Yeah but imagine that would be, I actually, I'm a weirdo, okay? I would really
think that game was fun. I love House Flipper. I love Viscera Cleanup Detail. I think a lot of
people severely underestimate just how much people like to tidy shit up in games. Or even if there
was, it was only cleaning up and rebuilding. I'm a weirdo. I'm weird. See, see this hat? Oh it's weird.
What does that mean? What does it, see this hat? I have enough money, let's go. No, I need to go
to the uh, another big bit drop. It's a money stream. I'm gonna play No More Heroes every day.
Money streams. Violactory, who is one of our resident trillionaires, uh gave another 5,000
bits. Cranberry Chocolate Sundae, fuckhead. Is that like your favorite sundae? Cranberry
Chocolate Sundae, fuckhead. Oh is that like what he literally says? It's from this, oh yeah. Cranberry
Chocolate. Fuckhead. Listening to screaming sound effects and people diarrheaing sounds. Diarrheaing
is uh really normal. I didn't say that I was normal. I, you know what guys, I am pretty normal.
I'm pretty fucking normal. I, I chores, I do errands, I go to sleep, I wake up, I do my taxes,
I fill up my gas, I drive around, I take care of, I'm a pretty normal goddamn person.
I eat, I go, oh that was, that was good. This is a good steak and cheese sandwich.
I'm pretty normal. You suck at acting normal. What a boring life. No, you can have a normal
life and not have a boring life? What's, what? Oh that's right, I did say that I did call it a
changer beeper last night and people wanted to literally murder me. You're right, I did. I know
because I, I, I saw it a million times. Strength increase, good. Well let's do the stamina. Squats.
Look at this ring. What is it? What, what, what, what, what? It's just Colgate ring, right?
Everybody, red, white, and blue lines. Everything, it's Colgate, right?
When I say it, it's not funny, but when you say it, it's funny.
What's going on there? What's up with that? What's up with that? Explain this normalcy.
Hold on, wait, I can't, it's going too fast. You gotta have context with that image. You can't just
be like, look, hey, look, this, okay, that is a pretty normal occurrence. If, but if there's
context behind what that image is. Did a live stream based around being slimed Nickelodeon style
by your audience and one of the games was trying to get the audience to say things that they,
maybe they would say, oh, you guys say diaper all the time. So I put on a diaper
to try to force everybody to say diaper and it worked. Is that, is that so weird? Is that
so abnormal? It's very abnormal. Well, all right, I gotta, how much is the new, the new prototype?
I hate absolutely everything about this game. This challenges yesterday's stream for worst of
the decade. This game, this game is really fun. What are you on about? This, this game is, I,
this is a very, I like this game a lot. This is a very, very fun game and the second one's good too.
Let's be real here. All the most famous people in history are worth weird,
really fucking weird people. Shit, it's ready. I need $148,000. I need it. I need that. How much
is it? 140. What do I have? 25,000. All right. If I do a couple more kill missions and you do them
right and not lose, then I'll get it. I've done my strength training. I've done my,
uh, my new techniques. I gotta make money. I need to make 120, $130,000. Let's go. Do coconuts. I'm
not doing coconuts. Coconuts is pound for pound the worst. What should I do? Uh, let's go to the
assassin. Kill a hundred people. Yeah, I'll do that one. I'll see how quickly I can get through that
one. Ooh, this is a new one. Pizza, but the finale. Chain restaurant pizza, but planes to open up.
That's 75,000. I did another huge bit. Message just come in another huge one. Another 5,000 bit
drop right now from snoozing coffee. Holy shit, snoozing. 5,050, 50 bits. I'm sorry. I'm not
looking at the game right now. Uh, they say at, you know, you know, at first I was going to have
this message be dedicated to make you play God hand. And I was really angry in that message
because you like this game so much with it's similar being so similar to God hand. And we
all know you would like God hand if you would give it a real chance and learn the controls.
But then you said some nice things about us, the community. So I rewrote this message,
but for real play God hand. I'll explain why in the afterstream hangout, Hey chat, God hand rise up.
I played God hand for like 10 minutes. I still own it. Rise up is a sick of play it for real.
Like do it for real. Did I hate it? Did I just not get it? Did I like not give it the real chance
play it for 10 more, more than 10 minutes. So does anybody have a clip of me playing it?
I mean, I didn't remember he hated it. You said you played it for 10 minutes. Of course,
that's not a real chance. You didn't beat the tutorial because you couldn't get used to the
controls in five minutes. God hand is garbage to be honest. He didn't beat the tutorial.
When is, um, I gotta get this off. This, I just looked over my other monitor and full screen is
this image. Get that out of here. All right. Let's get pizza. But when does the cuphead
DLC come out? I feel like they announced that a year ago. When is it? When, when did we get to get
that? It's actually going to be pretty tough. They all have lightsabers. Holy shit.
What are you doing? Trying to run. I can't run. I can't run guys.
Just stop at me. I can't get up.
Oh my God.
Oh, well that's why it's the finale.
I saw the screamer last night of Chuck E. Cheese demanding bits from the kids when he won the games.
He had a rat like grin. Oh, okay. God hand. No, let me beat this first. I need money.
The sprint doesn't work. I can't go that way. The sprint doesn't work. I got baited by my own chat
telling me to be baited by me. You can't sprint. You can't sprint and fight. It's out of combat.
Sprint only. Give me this money. We told you that. Who told me that? Crazy Ann. All right. Time to
win. I can't even sprint here. It's truly absolute out of combat. Only out in the outside world.
Dude, you have no health. This is a bad thing to do when somebody's right behind you.
I thought he was taunting. I thought he was taunting. I thought he was fucking taunting.
He put his hand up like yeah. I'm boiling. I haven't been able to do one of these
in like three in-game hours. I mean what's with the yelling I just did? He said that I was taunting.
It's not to relax. If I had anything to say to you it would be this exact message.
You're the guy that gave me less chicken than one chicken wing last night at Arby's, right? You said
your name was Jeremy something. Never got to the last name. Let me just say on behalf of the chat
could you please make an Arby's chicken wing on stream and stop slacking off at work. Thanks.
Mr. Jeremy Arby's. I'm going to kill that CEO. I'm taunting. Real voice.
Why is everyone suddenly talking about that shitty god hand game? I would hold up. After you say that
please go into the giant safe. That's like a you have to close yourself in that safe because you're
about to get like rained on. People are going to rain like rocks and fucking objects at you and
stuff. I'm still like put your shield up. I'm serious. Spam B. I can't take it anymore.
I just did. That's cool. I played this game a lot of times. I didn't know that was possible.
You having fun? Yeah. Just sucks when somebody is taunting and you get hit and you lose the
one hit mission. All right. Let's go CEO. I got to make this count. Every single person you have to
jet. I have to get in there and kill somebody. I got to get in there and kill somebody. Somebody's
like right in the front row immediately. I'm going for the not greed. I'm just going to go in. Try
to go up. Let's go. I just have to get in there and get a swipe on someone like that.
Yeah.
There it is.
Get him. Kill him. He's on the ground. He's on the ground.
Get him. And I'm not doing the extra swing. All right. Slow down.
Taunting. I was going to fill up gas. That one's so easy. Baby Jerma going to quit that mission
like he quit Godhand. Spam B. I can't fucking take it anymore. Another day. Another crash joke. No,
I just figured crashing into the wall was easy to get off the bike instantly. I'm just walking
into the thing. This is a good stream. I'm happy. Well, I'm glad you're happy. Is it almost New
Year's? When is it New Year's? In like six hours? Tonga? What's the country that gets the New Year's
first? This is the second time I've done this and I'm just realizing that the nozzle's not
connected to anything. I'm holding just a big grill lighter. It's wireless. It's a Bluetooth device.
Tesla portable battery charging. You still have time to make the worst voice of the decade.
I'm not even sure I could do that if I tried. It would end up being just a weird
mix of me trying to sound horrible and terrible and loud and I think I've probably unintentionally
done worse ones without trying. Can't talk. What? No, I'm like I don't give opinions on what's um
until tomorrow afternoon you're not going to know my opinion on any of these categories.
You'll get my opinion on them absolutely but not until tomorrow night. By the way, the nominees
are there. I want to vote on the on that but I don't want to watch a bunch of clips.
Oops. Okay, I have to finish this. Am I subbed? Ah, it doesn't look like it. 20 is good. So you're
not supposed to use your cell phone at a gas pump, right? Is that like a weird myth or is that true?
Is it true? Is it false? I've heard conflicting data on if you should use your cell phone at the
it's an old myth. It could cause a spark. Did you get that from Facebook? No.
You've confused gas stations and airplanes. No, look it up. Type in cell phone at gas pump and
you're going to go what the really what time is the New Year's Eve stream? The New Year's Eve stream
is going to be tomorrow at 6 p.m. Pacific time is when it's going to start. It's going to start
around 9 p.m. Eastern tomorrow. Yeah, New Year's Eve. That's so late. We have to count the ball
down. That's the point of doing a New Year's Eve stream is so I can count down the ball.
It's going to be midnight Eastern is when we're going to drop the ball.
If you're going to stay up for New Year's Eve, what do you? Well, it looks like it's 1120.
I think it's time to clock out. Happy New Year everybody. Just text me when it turns 1201.
I think it's time for me to have a nice relaxing day and not I don't care. No, you you you you
stand around the circle and you everyone's like here we go here it comes 10 9 somebody
gets to the front door 8 7 somebody gets to the back door 7 6 5 4 open the front door
to the outside 2 1 let in the new year open the back door let them let the old year out
and there was a yeah happy new year your family's weird I think my family's fun actually now that
I think about it your family's weird I like to just I we just silently sit in the chairs
and when the ball drops we all silently clap three times and then we all move to our designated
sleep zones we do one all right I have to kill this fucking ceo god here we go this is
fucking ridiculous
all right good fine there's a lot of money
75 000 that's right I have enough to get the new blade what does bttv stand for
better twitch btt better twitch better twitch tbt tv better twitch tv
yeah better twitch tv better twitch taunting
weapons the subaki mk2
give it to me nice now good we got the new blade there it is somebody said the f word and we don't
like I was supposed to top I was supposed to stop swearing this year yeah this year I'm going to
stop swearing I can't make any promises for the next year but this year I'm going to just take
it back a little all right I can let's go I'm good to go I got all my stuff upgraded we can do rank
five you did this joke two years ago yeah I'm sure I have I'm sure I have I've been recorded
for like 4 000 hours I'm probably going to repeat something sometimes my voice has been recorded
for like 600 000 hours I'm going to say the word the more than once let me guess you're out shopping
right hey I don't want to interrupt your fiesta who's next give me a second don't go anywhere
what huh yo what's the problem something wrong hello um squatting I'm getting a bad connection
hello can you hear me hello great let's go no what purpose should save the game
that won't happen on 5g don't worry that won't happen on 5 or 6g now once you get to 6g that
won't ever be an issue again you'll just you know you'll fold the phone up with your
17 fingers put your jeans back on I like that no hey girl it's a new one
oh no it's not okay that just got scared new cat no rank five rank five rank five rank five
uh this is here before wait what the fuck is all over the why is it blood everywhere I don't
remember this why is it blood everywhere I mean I may have done that it's gonna be just a trail
I lost the trail where is it yeah it's definitely just all the way to the fight somebody's bleeding
what happened here well we'll find out very shortly let's shake new blade new blade who this
oh yeah oh it's beautiful it's beautiful it's a quad blade who are you all right I have to
chase you down the hall this one's a lot slower it's not as quick as the last one
one
fuck ah come on
oh you caught me
oh my god I walked into it
oh
I like that one that one's satisfying
Jeremy you gotta look there's a link in the chat
but hold on I'm in the middle of playing no more heroes
the big wind up baseball swing feels so good it's a high quality link well I'll see it very soon
stop what you're doing jerma this is where it's a spoiler don't it's a spoil it's a spoiler don't
click it don't click it don't clear spoiler for what like a movie it's a content night
spoiler oh darn no we're not I don't know no no no no no no we'll be doing that soon by the way
early in the first probably week or so up in here
it's not a spoiler you eggs
what eggs no content till no content night till next year not till next year it's a long ass
hallway hit hit hit hit do it get started off
anyone who posts that links get it get a permanent ban he's never gonna beat this boss
omega low you think that jerma I thought you were good at this game all right no more chat
no more chat for two minutes no I that didn't mean literally I just meant like figure figure
figure figure figure figuratively am I saying that figuratively figuratively
figuratively is it figuratively figuratively figuratively figuratively
why can I not say that word it's weird now figuratively figuratively figuratively speaking
oh I wasn't I wasn't an english major it's a pottery miner my majors in sailboats
all right almost at the end of the hallway finally imagine not knowing how to speak your native
language no it's just english major no I'm a fucking goddamn
Travis hello continue forward and you will enter your next ranked match the fifth rank awaits you
if you win and only eternal damnation awaits if you lose how are you feeling no irritable rashes
hit the john lately taking care of the blackheads on your nose might I recommend a good hygiene set
when you're ready step inside now don't tense up too much on this one you've been slacking off a
bit you must maintain a steady tempo attacking me you know what I mean right I am so sorry to
say this but I am 1800 positive that you will die here but trust your force and head for the garden
of madness okay you say psycho you say look at me
content content here it comes here comes the big content part of the game there was let's go further
to the ice cream all right I really for some reason thought that was a pixel person holding
with their arm with a very baggy sleeve a popsicle I don't know why that's what it was
this is a bugs bunny cartoon where all of a sudden the guy the the hand starts coming down
and drawing and he's saying oh get away from me right doesn't that happen daffy doctor it was
in one of them it's daffy yeah definitely at last doctor it's time wake up ah you look good on
your rambling is excellent I think I'm going to lose the power control
it's close you the fifth guy yeah I've been waiting for you you certainly sound like you're
up for a fight I'm ready whenever you are all right then here I come disaster blaster charging
ignition ignition ready activating main engine activating solid engine
cycle ratio 50 percent cluster generator calculating four minutes protection
if I show
position
cycle ratio
this system
Travis touchdown is it not son of a bitch fucking snatcher I had him dance with me Travis
a katana this is getting interesting what do you go by Henry Henry
your instincts serve you well I I don't know who you are or what you want sir Henry
where are your manners that was my kill you naughty boy shall we get this over with
oh he's got the he's got like he's got the Kylo Ren saber fine by me after you I did it
I win I thought I thought that was things I think I fucked it up a little bit hold on
let me fix it I fucked it up I fucked it up I fucked it up I fucked it up all right we're good
stop right there the fight is over Travis you are now ranked fifth but we haven't even
we're just getting started perhaps you've forgotten these fights are an official game
if your opponent dies for whatever reason according to the rules of conduct it is
yeah oh no I remember this that's right that's the stupidest rule I've ever heard
this guy's mine and you just want me to let him go bitch rules are rules you can't have what you
can't have whatever but this dude says he wants to fight and ain't nobody gonna stop him this
ass clown right here who hey he's gone mr sir Henry motherfuckers rules what a pussy
sorry saves that aggression for your next match who the hell was that guy this guy really lives by
his t-shirt quote marvelous I did it let's shake you know at some point they were probably
programming that fight and something kept going wrong and they didn't want to give development
time to figure out how they were going to fix it so they were just like fuck it we've got four more
fights to do or we can't just just look move on something was wrong there and they just like can
it can it we got the model we have the model all done just let's do something fun with it
game had a six dollar budget that'd be pretty remarkable this is diane from b-fed videos we're
calling to let you know your overdue on returning one of our videos it's titled air force one the
first lady returns to the mile high club where why can't i watch these your uaa registration
is complete as of today you are officially the fifth ranked assassin in the united states
nice work you are on the fast track to the top keep it up and good luck yeah i know but like
if i own them why can't i just see them we don't hit the tv but i'm just saying
400 000 dollars coming up let's do 400 grand let me let me go to the video store
a new part-time job is available it sure is you don't own them you're renting them yeah but
this is still in the apartment is this the scorpions one how many mini games are there
eight nine cash what about the cat well i'll go back later there's plenty of time to pet the cat
i got four more fights to do stop what you're doing and have that cat
dogs cats dogs cats graffiti cleaning oh nice erase graffiti from the walls this is the game
that i wanted to play i probably would love mario sunshine holy shit i'm just coming to this
realization right now i would love that game it would be my favorite game ever
i love cleaning stuff why wouldn't i play that one any of the games that have cleaning as a main
component of the game it's the best mario luigi's mansion i know i can't play luigi's mansion it
takes over but the weird part of my brain that gets addicted and i can't even go in every single
room i have to clean everything and it just fucked up the whole game chibi robo chibi robo
yep all right yeah put go go to the recommended channel and put all these cleaning games in there
i crave them it turned these just around the corner your hard work can change this town
the future of santa destroy is a town without graffiti hard work will never betray you hard
work will change your future kill the god of graffiti work harder than you've ever worked before
all these basics gotta sweep sweep sweep erase the graffiti sprayed around town how
to how though like just i can't i can't do that
i get it all right that's a huge graffiti why can't i do that one
the technique here is just doing both at the same time why is cravis so tired i mean i'm
running around all over the place cleaning reverse jet set radio that's a you know it's
a suboptimal route that's okay that's fine and i just go come on where is it all right i have
stamina i just hit them together i just smacked them together the vibrations just hurt my hands
hey uh anybody any baseball players or softball players in chat here
at all yeah some yeah remember when you used to get a like a big a fastball would come down
and you'd get a nice big swing and it would hit the either the very end or right on the hands of
the bat and it was the worst experience in your entire life all right that was the worst i hated
that more than anything i would rather get hit by a pitch like i would have rather the fastball hit
me right in the shoulder than to have it hit me right on the hands of the bat and vibrate electrocute
my whole body and hurt for like no i'd rather get hit with a pitch
yeah it rattles your actual hand bones and arm bones and it feels like somebody took out your
bones from your arms and stomped on them and put them back in it's the worst
i did it all of them okay i actually did them all i thought there were more than that
that's like 20 000 we're getting towards late game here i think you're gonna give me 20k for a job
new assassin job you gotta do the assassinations yeah but you to unlock the assassinations you
gotta do these shitty little jobs you know the ones that give you 20k when you're in almost the
late game i was a catcher and got hit in between my leg and kneecap i could never play again
yeah catchers uh catchers are like the unsung hero of the whole game it's a painful job that
shit hurts all right pro wrestling contest only pro wrestling 5000 as many as you can within the
time limit 5000 that's good batting spree let's do this one kill as many as you can
5000 for a kill in the underground shut the hell up gamer you're a gamer shut up gamer
what are you talking about shut up gamer because i said the word sports i said the words what i
because i'm talking about baseball and everyone's like we're gamers here shut up shut up gamer
what's going on oh we just got raided we just got raided by joel oh that's what's going on okay
all right all right hey what's up what's going on everybody playing no more heroes welcome to the
stream thanks for the raid joel i was like are these are they bots i was like what's going on
because i did i was just talking about sports and baseball and getting hit with my pitches and stuff
and all of a sudden it's like shut up gamer gamer the gamer was capitalized so it's like oh shit
people are angry because i'm talking about like sports in the video game stream right
all right i'm looking at chat uh yeah welcome uh joel when are we gonna do no uh no talking if
everybody explodes what's the game what's that game called keep talking and nobody will get hurt
keep talking and nobody will explode keep talking and and nobody explodes what happy new year by the
way is it new year no you're not from new zealand right shut the hell up gamer or you'll explode
mission star here we go going to be funny if travis broke his gamer bone when he crashed the
bike haha yeah what do we got actually let's go run run run run run run run hurry hurry open open
open open open open open open the door go go go baseball there it is how did you catch that
i'm feeling
dude he said it he said baseball this is right i'm gonna rack up some good money on this one
actually maybe not was it 5 000 per kill
this guy's still alive
oh i don't i don't like this one this one's never that's
and it's that's 50 000 it's pretty good actually the other one's 90 000 to kill 100 people
i'll do that one let's go do that one now i should have the new blade so let me try to do one of the
ones and not get hit can you say dollars again dollars so what's funny about dollars dollars
dollars dollars again again say it again what's wrong with you guys any new uh parts
there might be new parts check check check don't lay a single finger on anything
damn it there is new parts how do i have 300 000 i got money power up for more damage and then
more battery i need 400 000 for the next fight i got money let's do it load it in i'm gonna have
to do some more work but this is another energy this is battery more battery 50 000 dollars it's
a lot of money but it's good i'll take it you don't buy them all before the next mission i'm
gonna scream i just did i just have to do the new training in the gym i'm i gotta be prepared
oh am i free next week uh yeah yeah let's do it when do you want to do it strap in then all
right yeah what do you want what new years is uh we're gonna look at the calendar we got new
years if tomorrow after new years i'm gonna take a few days off and then what are we doing on uh
we're doing on saturday we're doing on saturday what are you doing on saturday
doing anything on saturday saturday sunday one of those days saturday sounds like a date but
you have to buy me dinner may you find well whatever you want just order whatever you want
get the most expensive bottle of wine get the get like three bottles of still uh get the most
expensive steak in the whole restaurant and i will make sure to leave before the check comes
in fact you're going to look behind you and you know how a lot of restaurants have the big glass
windows and i'm just gonna put a bit i'm gonna write on a big piece of paper right outside
i'm gonna be like oh yo joe i gotta go to the bathroom i'll be right back and then i'm gonna
slap it a fucking piece of paper on the window and you have to get five minutes have gone by
you're like wait wait what what what are we doing out there it's gonna be too late paper up there
let's just say hope you have enough money lol and then i'm fucking crumpling the paper running
you know what you're gonna come catch me you're gonna get up and run i'm not gonna say that i'm
going it's gonna be written and i'm gonna have the wicked fucking mad mean face like
that wasn't that was not a sad face what are you talking about
no that's the like that's that's the very silent that's the silent but very clear like fuck you
face you know what i mean like i have to play great i can't look at the chat
my sensor bar fucked up what's going on
i didn't i never did i hated that i actually didn't like that i thought it was annoying
i'm not i'm not gonna put that on stream i was about that that's just weird it's just a scary
image no somebody has to photoshop like my hand going here i'll here i'll let you i'll give you a
photoshop ready just so i want like glass here you know what i mean like you can do like a filter
to make it look like this glass and like just here's my hand you can just like carve the arm
and elbow out you know what i'm saying and then attach it to the face i made before i guess i
could just do this now right i could just do like like like i've got like a paper in my hand yeah
like i'm pressing the paper up against the glass window derma you are so cringy
fucking can't even do this shit anymore how are you supposed to get a meat lover's pizza
uh not now never knew you're like i was gonna do a new year's yeah not in the second
year
i'm doing uh long point stocks garbage collecting yeah can we get it that's not
it's not quite what i was looking for no i've i know this image has been floating around for
a long time why am i i'm not supposed to be holding a gun why do i have a gun why do i
have a gun you didn't even um that's not even this is barely even edited
shut the hell up gamer all right what am i doing supposed to be playing i just got here why is he
pointing a gun at the webcam it's photoshopped it's not real it's fake deep fake phylactery just
gave another 50 dollars five thousand bits and they say here's a bully here's a bullet
because you're epic what he's a hold on donkey donut it's a that doesn't that doesn't work i've
read it wrong you're not epic oh it's another 50 fucking dollars from phylactery jesus
two not epic all right i gotta pick up trash yeah but joel if you're still here uh saturday
mark it on the calendar keep talking and nobody will explode easy we're gonna do it on the hard
one the hard mode he left well he knows he already knows he knows he knows he knows he knows he knows
he knows he knows he knows okay i'm i'm pointing a gun at myself here like on my
right monitor like i don't like this image like i'm looking over here and it's me pointing a gun
over here like i don't like this this you know i'm saying like it's on my other monitor like get out
of here stop get away from me it's just me looking at me all right trust no one why are you linking
a picture of a fat hairless cat what does it have to do with anything what no like seriously what
does that have to do with anything what does that have to do with anything you guys are wild
tonight people are having dreams about me getting like banned by having sex on stream i've gotten
like three thousand dollars tonight you guys you guys are are are out of control it actually is
you photoshopped onto a cat it's not a joke no it's not no it's not no it's not oh cool like
he's a cat standing on two legs that's cool yeah of course it's not all right this is the thing
there's not even the same image this is me escaping from your iphone this is not what i
was looking for turn it off turn it off i did here he comes oh god he's getting out
dude that's not edited what are you siri what was it 50 last time i'll be close do i really
have to eat a fucking meat lovers pizza tomorrow i'm gonna get diarrhea you promised all right but
what if it's a what can i can i eat like a vegan meat lovers pizza 49 vegan meat lovers pizza
walking talking oxymoron we got wait new link what is it this is
oh can i get closer can i get closer i can't can i oh well how much money do i got
do i have enough 330 i need 400 we'll do uh another assassin mission the closest one i can find
like this one over here i know it's a spinning gif yeah i know this what is this this is a different
gun image where are you what do you do this is a different and what do i'm wearing a death
stranding t-shirt oh the death star where are you guys getting these show the gift i did the gift
last night i just showed the gift it's two here now all right let me try to get at least one of
these done all right let's do it i have to do one of these all right let me let me get this one
guy to the left watch the guy to the left
god damn it these fucking missions are so hard fuck it's so hard to die this weapon is so slow
i god i god i can't do these anything i can't do these i did them in the these missions are so painful
the edit you've been waiting for it's the edit you've been waiting for
that's that's not even what what what is what is this this is like a tv show hold on i gotta
here hold on let's get it on here because i need to do again i want to examine this photo
real quick uh there it is i mean that's not what i said i wanted to say is that is it is that the
germa fear face in the reflection did you add that from goodwill hunting you swine
yeah all right sorry i don't remember every scene from every movie i've ever seen in my life
i haven't seen goodwill hunting since it came out like 17 years ago
just watch goodwill hunting on stream now sure let me please get one of these
all right watch they're gonna run towards me
that guy's a gun
it's no come on i can't do i can't do these i'm not doing them anymore why do i have two fingers
i have two fingers and a huge thumb you're alien
all right how much money do i have i'm seriously these one hit missions they're killing me i even
tried to block too and the guy i thought he was reloading whatever i don't even need to explain
it this one's right here i'm gonna try this one more time and i'll never do these ever again
this one sucks because it's in a tiny little area just don't do a big charge attack i have
to get a good swing did somebody to my left god damn these are fucking awful i know the guy in
front of me hit me i know but like i was trying to get away you come here picking up trash again
good luck paying that bill fuckhead why am i frozen it's really cold outside
and i don't have a jacket on or anything i do like the icicles off my face
and i'm just sitting in my room too all right all right all right all right no
no more photoshop i need to show this one because this is stupid okay spoiler all right if you've
never seen any more if you've ever seen infinity war you'll think it's if you've never seen it
anywhere close the stream for five minutes stupid i hate this but i still i hate this
yeah it's a glass pane in minecraft it's a glass mine that's awesome i love it i hate it though
i'm not opening up any more photoshop why'd you say five minutes because everyone for the next
five minutes is going to talk about infinity gauntlet stuff it was two years ago yeah and
people got really mad at me when i started talking about i talked about movies that are
15 plus years old before and people like dude what the fuck man i actually think i talked about
the ending of the wizard of oz and somebody just wrote dude fuck you i haven't seen that
it if you have um i don't know how it's possible if you haven't seen never seen the wizard of oz
then i don't what am i supposed to tell you that's like being angry if somebody saying what
frankenstein is dude frankenstein is the doctor and frankenstein comes to life and it's frankenstein's
monster that's on the same level as me telling you that dracula bites people and like sucks their
blood and shit what does he i've i've never seen any of that before i was gonna watch dracula one
seen that the dracula book was better the marvel movies suck though oh
i don't i mean i don't think so i think some of them i think some of them are pretty good
no not yet guys not yet there hasn't been that one thing that happens in a marvel movie that gets
memed to death and makes well actually hold on a minute here because that's how people start to
hate something it gets really really really popular and then a bunch of people meme the
fuck out of it to a point where nobody likes it anymore i don't know we're at that territory yet
people still like the the marvel memes they did that with all of them yeah but i'm not sure we've
crossed that let's put it this way i'm not sure we've crossed like the szechuan sauce threshold
for like i hate this tv show now you know what i mean it hasn't been that that catalyst
oh we're almost there almost pick it up what the fuck front of the buzzer didn't get it sorry 50
grand nothing nice buddy all right i only need not much more i'm gonna actually do one of these
out no actually i hold on i need um i didn't go to the gym yet all right one more actual assassin
mission and then i'm going to the gym so i can have enough money to uh be able to spend that
money at the gym one more assassin mission we have enough money lol i can't get over this
minecraft glass like that's that's funny let's see stadium is seven which one haven't i done
only wrestling moves if i can kill that ceo that's a lot of money let me try the 100 one
and see how fast i can do that i haven't even done it once it's 90 000 for 100 let's time it
pizza but more like pizza hut it depends on how many people are in the room and if they have
lightsabers or not what's the worst thing on the menu at pizza hut oh i know uh the cheese stuff
yeah the cheese thing is terrible um what's the best thing pizza stuff cross pizza i already know
get the spaghetti the last few times i've had pizza hut this is the worst part about pizza
for me at least personally i think that was a one hitter pizza hut always to me tastes
this is awesome i love it but i think i've gotten sick the last two or three times
a pack
this happens very very quickly 15
that's awful
most chain pizza places are off the gas we've had this conversation on screen before already
i know that some people that don't have opportunities to eat anything that's not
something like a pizza but they're all pretty bad
it's just kind of taking off my brain i don't think this one's fine for 100 000 but i don't like
this i'm starting to see something get like blurred vision from this
yeah this actually hurts my head so we're not doing this one again
it's 40 days
all right
yeah
parappa the rapper ate 50 40 pieces in 30 days
it's plenty of time
99 was 100
yeah let's not do this one ever again why is the spleen the body part that hurts the most for them
i don't know anybody have a timer for that all right 488 let's do the next
uh rank four rank four coming up right seeing a lot of purple in the chat that's so funny that
that those mailboxes are just one asset that have pasted down atm deposit 400 000 dollars
well maybe not yet did i do uh these yet i don't think i did you guys i'll give you i'll give you
credit you guys have been on point with the photoshop links these last few days but here's
the thing is this don't read this this is real voodoo you are now cursed the only way to reverse
this christine entire domino's meat lovers pizza on camera uh there's like over 5 000 people here
i mean i think did i just curse everybody i just cursed everybody you have to eat a pizza on camera
sorry
you fool i'm sorry i had to show it so you guys can see what i was talking about
no you have to eat 5 000 pizzas extended combo let's do this is another bench press
let's do it domino's is gonna have a spike in sales today papa john's pizza is actually the worst
um yeah it's like it does it does like it does like suck doesn't it um who out of all the chains
who has the best people i know that's simple that would be pappagino's but that pappagino's i think
is a new england thing so that's not technically like a like a national chain right it's only a
northeast thing so i know that counts does it papa john's
chain pizza is strange because if you have a bad chain pizza at least in my case
there's never a single solitary fucking reason to ever eat it again i've eaten papa john's
probably twice and it was 15 years ago i was like oh this is this sucks i don't like this
oh this well let me look around in a circle there's like 700 pizza places around me
oh well why would i ever eat here ever again ever again for any reason but if you don't have pizza
places like sandwich shops pizza shops all over the place then i can understand why if papa john's
is all you got then that's kind of all you got all right with any team we have pizza place but
only the chain ones deliver that's another key part of this too is if a place doesn't deliver
you know something sometimes you just wanted to sit around and have somebody bring you something
live in sweden and their pizza sucks get some of those some of these places in in new york and
in boston new england northeast east coast pizza is it can nowhere in the entire world can compare
you just can't connecticut yep connecticut pizza is fucking awesome too what about italy no
oh that hurt new york connecticut boston some places in new jersey i've heard i haven't had them
but they're some of the best pizza you can get in the whole world i mean pizza started in america
all right we got more videos oh i have to buy these there's another video this title is mask
deep panther mass didn't like master of the fourth dimension yeah how much money was that
oh right that's because i uh i already put the the fee in didn't i all right i'll get these later
boston pizza sucks no it does not what are you talking about it's on record by tons of people
huge food critics the north end in boston has some of the best pizza in the country what
boston was voted worst pizza 2019 what from like one of your friends in an instagram story
what are you talking about oh he's pissed i just well i just drove around a circle hold on
fuck gyros are better than pizza that's different that's you can't say that that's a different
completely different food i love i love gyros i'm obsessed with them but saying that a gyros
better than a pizza you that's your i look i we have to have this conversation every time i say
that word people call it this it i've heard euro i've heard euro i've heard it gyro gyro
gyro gyro this every other place you call is different i we have to do i have to have
this conversation again travis the next rank is fourth who is it come to think of it boston was
ranked as having the worst tap water 16 years in a row i'm not i'm not drinking out of my sink
it's okay a show wait this is a date right something like that why else would i be getting
an oil rub what what did you say someone's rubbing you down boston has the worst pizza that's no it
doesn't what are you talking about give me this look i'm gonna click your absolute debate link
and let's see what it says city with the worst pizza ever this is photoshop city with the worst
pizza ever let me search for it myself america's best and worst cities for pizza this is from
delish.com oh what's that uh oh hold on a minute uh the best we have new haven connecticut yes
that's absolutely correct we've got new york san francisco portland providence rod island
that's all new england the worst pizza in the country is apparently philadelphia chicago
what doesn't deep didn't deep dish like really popular i thought deep dish was people like love
deep dish piece uh detroit iowa st louis missouri put chicago having the worst pizza in the country
what i don't i don't agree with that boston best pizza in the country although uh regina pizzeria
yep top the list is the best pizza restaurant in the country boston has ranked seven
seventh on the list of top u.s cities for pizza seven it's top 10 in the country it's top seven
and regina pizzeria is number one in the whole country all right we don't have to have this
you know what get fucking cursed now you know you're gonna eat a shitty domino's pizza all right i
can't i can't say that can i all right play with cat he just cursed us
domino's i'm gonna be fair to domino's here do you remember when they had that whole campaign
on ads on tv where the ceo read all the comments about people talking about how bad the pizza is
hi i'm ceo uh kevin from domino's pizza we've seen your comments on how our sauce tastes like
ketchup and it's the grossest pizza on earth remember that go and give the performance of
your life you can do this and here's the thing after they did that whole campaign where they
and i'll give it to them i really have to hand it to domino's they did this is a brilliant strategy
they told everybody that that pizza was horrible they said our pizza sucks it's disgusting it's
dog shit but we changed the recipe give it a try everybody tried it like oh yeah like domino's
this sucks ass uh but they changed the recipe i'll order one just just from that campaign 10
years ago they made more money probably that they needed to in the next 10 years
what about you my stream sucks but we changed the camp it was brilliant it was an absolutely
brilliant campaign it was brilliant hi germa985 here we've seen the complaints about how my
stream is uh way too loud and way too quiet at the same time what we've decided to do
is try it is double down harvey moys which world is sarski you're way quieter than the ads i don't
want everyone to have a hurt ear get out of the kiosk oh my god you're annoying double down like
i make it louder and i talk quieter remember when i had subsounds that were 10 times louder than me
oh i remember i remember
i miss those subsounds sometimes i do too but as this channel has gotten
larger and the channel in the community has grown two or three times in the last three years
i it would be like having tts on screen i missed the salt and sanctuary days when
paul bearer would talk for like 25 straight i used to have a sub sound that was 25 straight seconds
i wonder what that would be like if i did that again just for like 20 minutes so you guys could
we could we could see but i feel like it would be an inaccurate sampling because i think people
would just sub to make sure that it played over and over again right am i seriously stuck
why is he not dead do it do it till the end of the decade we are not doing that oh that's
right the decade's over tomorrow that's right never mind end of the decade they're going to sleep
remove the external extension control what what the fuck are they talking unplug the nunchuck
what move special shoot sword i'm having a dream i don't remember this at all i have a sword too
he missed i was testing out the sword explode pepe what pepe i can't go over there reliably
can i just oh you destroy bullets with the sword that's how you get special
i get it what's that oh what i didn't know what's going on i tried to press a continue what's going
on do i not have a special it's not full all right that's hey i don't have a special
oh now i do i get it whoa whoa whoa whoa whoa whoa whoa whoa whoa whoa warning
okay
what the fuck fuck sorry i'm good it's not even doing any damage getting close all three destroys
all the bullets oh cool what a fun little mini game that was cute look me a a a a connected back
together okay let's go that's cute that's a cute little game all right i'm kind of tangled up though
i don't know how this happened how did this happen i fucking hate wires are you actually
playing on a wii the disc back in how are you playing with the disc out i fucked it up
you said you're gonna get a haircut before new years we have tomorrow
probably won't happen
that's actually not a bad idea i have to go soon
incredible color gradation ever i will beat it tomorrow
we're gonna be at like rank three today you are going to win with together you and me
do a buzz cut or a bowl cut and head the garden of madness a bowl cut would look so bad on me
absolutely not no absolutely not do a bowl cut for the new year stream
oh i could i can't i could never make that work i could never make it work oh no no i'm not having
those images and videos around forever like eating a mcchicken with mayonnaise all over my like face
and like hands and stuff i don't care but having a real fresh bowl cut that's i have to draw the
line somewhere new move shave your eyebrows and get a bowl cut you become a master pro wrestler
i think i'll book a match for you but first a super hard suplex satan's ferris wheel the double
armed suplex germa you were in a slime diaper that's not that's less embarrassing than having
a real bowl cut number four is it i mean i think so
the show's about to start what's with all the excitement
not every day you get to watch a big fight from bip so excited but i am most excited being with you
you're serious i wouldn't do that why were you oh shit oh shit hop back in heat baby what somebody
said elijah wood did it elijah wood makes like three million dollars in appearance
gentlemen and all killers out there it'll be a killer night so let's get so do you
oh that one actually went in
so lucky to get lucky now one of you lucky people will be chosen to be up here with me
who's it gonna be the lucky person is you wow travis this is your lucky night
me they want me serious you gotta be kidding go get him tiger no need to be shy congratulations
you nasty little boy tell the audience your name travis touchdown it's a good name don't you think
it's a fine name indeed you have your parents to thank for that my parents are dead touchy subject
a question that should not be touched upon that's okay really it is there there don't let it bother
you how's it making those sparkles and don't give up my nasty little boy thanks i'll remember that
so you came to enjoy the show damn right i did i was really looking forward to this it's the last
show right last show did i hear you right oh you heard me right harvey you're gonna die tonight
right here by my hand let's close the curtains i hope you aren't being serious that would be a
pity we still have the main event to unveil playtime is over ladies and gentlemen it's
show time oh the spinning saw blade of death
now those are cool i know where you got those you got those from dancer
it's killing time those are the coolest worst weapons in dark souls 3 all right check it out
oh yeah teleport see the teleport
what the fuck was that oh he dodged how am i gonna hit it
oops grab him i could have grabbed him idiot come on come on
you don't have a very this isn't really this barely an opportunity i have to do like that
dash around him i think like that yeah grab him number four belong down to like number like 31
oh this is why
jesus what was this oh god what does this do i don't remember this what the hell's going on
assistance now look carefully assistance it's showtime do i have to get out of this
i'm trapped in here with an animal this is so dumb i guess you have to have a few comedy bosses
right spin me back around good he's dead this guy wasn't even the chip this guy was easy
die that was the easiest boss in the game that was very easy
how would they help do that aren't they supposed to be his friend i got an s rank on that one yeah
that i two bosses go harder than that guy that's the pinwheel boss the name is travis touchdown
thank you all for coming tonight i hope you enjoyed the show i would also like to thank
you for coming this evening as a result travis touchdown is now right face and the show will
go on i hope to see you all again soon i saw the ball cut or is it that's it number four
i realize i'm the same age as travis how old is travis touchdown supposed to be
27 i thought he was older 29 in this game so does that mean in no more heroes 3 travis is
going to be 40 something he'll be like 38 or 38 he'll be like 40 that's pretty cool i like that
i'll be i can relate to him more yeah because it's 10 years or nine years right from no more
heroes 2 or no more heroes 1 10 years from no more heroes 1 i think something like that
the video you returned was a copy of one of our video titles um the best of raunchy amateur
interviews too you didn't seem to copy the whole tape though it ended two minutes into the middle
of the first interview anyway please be sure to return the original tape you borrowed thank you
i was too young to know or care good morning mr touchdown understand are you on the throne
could you have done that with blockbuster if you rented a movie from blockbuster could you have
just taped over a new tape or something was that possible was that even possible you would need
two decks right somehow 450 000 new amount of money it had to be legit well you would just you
would keep the copy you wouldn't return the copy right you would copy the tape and then give the
original tape back to blockbuster did people do that yeah probably should that would that's
probably that was very horrible that's very rampant i'd say the game all right games already
saved we need to make 450 000 new job yep yep yep yep yep is this scorpions this might be
scorpion mission time i think there's only two more missions or two more uh jobs that exist in
the game it's nine right and another five assassin missions something like that off bike i can't
believe the hoverboard didn't work yeah it'll get patched in though don't worry
meow meow capture the escaped cats use some foxtail grass to attract the cat's attention
your bike sounds like a star wars blaster does it
okay maybe a little bit i can hear it yeah a little a little bit meow i don't really
understand the unspoken rules of standard destroy trying to think a little more like a cat meow
gotta find those cats before they get busy i love meow love meow cats so much that i keep two meow
and any of them i go crazy when one of the cuties gets out if you like cats too then lend me a
helping paw the god of cats is rolling around peering happily search for them let's go save
the cats capture the cats that have fled into the town use some foxtail grass to attract the
cat's attention three two okay what i'll have to okay that's what foxtail grass is i hate that
meow he does that yeah yeah get up get up come on play it was b not a come here pay attention
fucking be again ah fuck that sucks i don't know
where are you in here where's this cat
this meow is activating your asmr
that's funny
takes too long everyone's gonna love this one because the cats but i don't think it's very
efficient for money but we have to do them all yeah oh my god not interested at all huh
you're just not interested at all you don't care about any of this got it nice oh there's one more
it's okay what is it worth garbage is better by a lot third writer another job for you garbage is
better than cats both for making money assassination mission is available and more free fights but i
have banned myself from free fighting because it's i waste 40 minutes trying to do them and
i don't make any money here we go extreme fight struggle against all odds kill all targets all
other details will be a nice surprise reward it's a secret kill as fast you can enemies are armed
with live ammo mission ends when all targets are dead seven thousand per kill let's let's do the
secret one let's try extreme fight you should drink carrot juice on camera nah well can i put
orange juice in it to make it taste better can i put 40 percent carrot juice 60 orange juice
and then shave a little bit of ginger in there we'll press some ginger in there some juice
can i do that that sounds nice it is it's very nice it's very very good yeah that's just just a
little bit not very much just like a squeeze of ginger not a lot that sounds great except
for the ginger ginger it gives it a nice little kick not too much though just a little bit
you don't want to overdo it so what's the secret
is a secret oh wait a minute i can't can i not get oh shit the these are this is reversed too
sorry left is driving right is left i have to mirror this too all right now it's working
supposed to be a problem
yeah i turned my tv upside down for you guys it is weird i'm playing in a little box over here
you mirror it i just flipped it upside i just turned your screen upside down everything's fine
how much money is this worth 70 000 oh that's pretty good that's pretty good for how short that
is i might just do that one like five times what was the last one is the baseball one i'll do the
baseball one this is fun or no we'll do that one again it's just too easy to do that what is going
on i think you guys are flipping your chat messages that's how you doing that what keyboard lets you
do that my spleen my spleen invert the chat window invert all right let's do it again it's
very it's very very simple once you do the cheat i'm holding the keyboard upside down that makes
sense uh i wonder if there's any katana parts i'll find out after this jumped it what does your
spleen do i feel like i should know this but i don't what does it do controls blood stuff it
digests hair i'm just catching what you said 70k here we come here
whoa
breakdown no you everything's you're fine just don't look at this stuff on the side of the screen
it's like being on a roller coaster you don't like tilt your head
side to side on a roller coaster same exact concept down here don't
okay that's fine and we're good i have enough of a beat well you did omega you
omega low is supposed to be upside down too why do you not do omega low hey can we do something
for a minute here please can we can you guys can we work together on something can everybody
write messages upside down oh please only write messages upside down because i'm gonna flip this
vertically and we're gonna and some people are gonna trickle in and it's gonna i'm gonna be
panicking about why what's wrong with my twitch just get get like generic random sentences
you know get like just random generic sentences that are upside down and only put that in only
spam that i don't know how it's all right well then the people that yeah just put everything upside
down okay let me do this real quick uh hold on keep it up you're doing great okay ready let's
give it a try i need to like turn this off okay here we go um i don't know something's wrong with
my twitch is everybody's getting this error there's a weird error message that's coming up
on my screen that's hard i can taste iron too is everybody can anybody else taste iron
anybody taste iron right now what's happening what are you doing are you doing this or are you
about am i are you doing it oh stop writing upside down that's funny i'm trying to spider-man kiss you
oh shit that was loud i don't know oh it's gonna have both headphones in
you should have talked upside down to how do you talk upside down what am i even wanting
what was my money 449 it's like 10-15 dollars first of all let's go check out the blades i think
there's one thing i'm missing right just play your voice in reverse i mean i can't do that without
doing a bunch of editing that was a nice david lynch twitch channel what it's like to chew
5g gum highlight that one that's great all right so though what about the part
what it's like to chew why am i still upside down i shouldn't be all right here we go what it's like
to chew 5g gum the game music the fucking game i just broke something that was the game music
fucked it up it's just playing this god damn it try it again i can't do this is what happens when
i take off my fucking head so head sounds do it again dude wait wait wait wait wait wait what it's
it's what it's like to chew 5g gum yeah it was all right it was all right it's better with the
music what about now don't count because it's not even illegal it's not even legal here's 50
dollars don't do the 5g gum joke anymore all right i promise i won't thank you phylactery 50 dollars
it was better with the music i knew i knew i shouldn't have done it again i saw do it again
again again again no no the music made it fucking fine this is the second huge raid of the night
thank god they came in right now thank god they just came in and not five minutes ago thank god
all right uh day what's it box box with a huge raid of like three thousand people welcome to the
stream thank god you came in right now and you didn't catch the 5g gum routine thank you for the
raid really appreciated box box hope you had fun on your stream i'm having fun on mine doing
hilarious jokes last joke was so absolutely hysterical you missed it you just missed it
embarrassed to be here no seriously welcome guys he's holding us hostage here what are you talking
about follower yeah i turn off i gotta turn off follower only mode turn it off turn off follower
only mode this guy's got put it on no followers only or no on what do i want to do
these guys have guns don't don't oh you're the worst you're the worst you're the worst you're the
worst they both have guns look at how many guns they have did i block them it's all right this
shit is that's too hard i want the 5g gum joke again i'm happy you know that you know when you
look at like rotten tomatoes and you see the movie for instance like cats right it's like
unanimously people like well this this movie is terrible what a shitty movie and then you go
through like the audience reviews and they're all like worst movie i've ever seen my whole life
the cg what a just just an absolutely disgusting movie and then you keep going and there's a five
star rating in there and it's just somebody that just has no idea they don't they don't care they're
just like i like this movie it was really fun when the cats were on screen and it was the best
movie i've ever seen i'm so happy that there's at least one person giving me a five star review in
here you like dumb people what what do you mean dumb but that's what makes you if you like cats
doesn't mean you're dumb yeah i saw it i went alone to the theater and i thought it was great
i loved it but i'm scared to write a review because i think people are gonna call me names
what do you mean he saw the joke what are you talking about what's going on i'm answering my
phone who's who saw it what are you talking about who it's a bad day no no no no no no no no no no
no all right no you didn't see it right
guys over there spam box bobs in his chat thanks for watching everyone see you tomorrow they all
saw they all saw what they all saw but i don't think they heard anything they did it was just me
chewing this would be it's just okay it's just me chewing all right to to any to anybody that
has no idea i'm just chewing on gum they they could hear oh wow he just turned his webcam on
oh man that's fun but seriously welcome thanks to the great seriously i hope you
haven't i hope you have a good new year too i'm just crashing all right i'm gonna make five
dollars do i have the money no go to the gym deposit or go to what should i do deposit or go
to the gym i think i'm gonna just deposit and let's go let's do it what do i need
i could you know i'm gonna do one more assassin mission and i'm gonna do a ninja warrior stream
against an athlete i would probably be okay in those i would perform pretty well although i can't
right now i would actually like to do that uh which one hasn't been done this one wrestling
moves only let's do it 2012 germa could have done it probably how many channel points for a 5g gum
joke i can not again that is really funny though that box box opens the street and said hey this
is we're gonna raid let's go and it's oh his cam just turned on i thought we were in the clear
oh well wrestling moves only you 70 000 away from a german wink save up is it only uh gun
people no that's actually sucks nice oh wait what i'm trying to
this is okay come on i wish i could sprint here this is gonna be hard to get this guy
the guy behind him get him give her this guy behind you get him this is 7 000 or 5 000 for kill
knock him out ddt that's the best move in all of wrestling it's seven night that's just that's
really good this would be all right wrong don't run don't run don't run don't run don't run don't
run don't run don't run don't uh and you've ran over here again again where's your wink
you need 75 000 channel points that's a lot oh well i think that's enough to level up
this game has worse graphics than gta 4 well this because it does it yeah this thing was on the wii
the wii was just a game cube that they injected with steroids it's not surprising let's go to the
gym i didn't mean the console was bad the wii was awesome i'm gonna make a statement here and it
might sound a little controversial to some of you guys i don't know we'll see i think the wii is the
best most appealing looking console it's like it i loved the shape and how much it weighed and how
small and compact it was i loved that just the the wii console i thought it was really really cool i
like the the top the pop the top off of the controllers i really really enjoyed the week
it was shiny sleek it was small enough it had a little tray putting discs and putting a game cube
disk in was so cool we're gonna do uh this one and that's it it was a very well designed machine
it had the virtual console it had super mario galaxy it had no more heroes it had carnival
games which i think sold better than no more heroes did in fact carnival games may have sold
better than mario galaxy it has manhunt isn't manhunt the games where you just walk up behind
people like strangling with plastic bags it is okay i'm making sure i'm thinking rock star made
it right i'm thinking the right game is this baseball arm what is this
manhunt is banned on twitch is that real i mean i i guess i can kind of understand
him i mean without that entire game is you just don't you just like hide like
sneak around and like i said flatten they just strangle people to death and that's it and like
put hooks in their heads and stuff is there is there a game to manhunt or are you actually
just sneaking around murdering people there is a flaw is there a point to this game would you
run yes i'm trying to be the number one assassin in the united states i'm not just creeping around
with a bunch of like grocery bags who's that guy over there yeah i'm gonna put a plow chugging
with a plastic bag it's not the same thing that was a lot of money let me go to the gym
and we'll do assassin number three get into the top three getting to the actual end of the game
here coming up soon the end game end of the game i know you want that right i had a dream where
jerma played manhunt on stream naked and everyone was spamming t.o.s like i wouldn't know dude hey
you're like you're having sex on stream t.o.s i what oh there's a bunch of people that probably
weren't here like four hours ago somebody explain it to him like you're trying to warn me about that
you're warning me dude you're this is t.o.s we did i would rethink this
i can't get over that this is the endurance right increase max vitality yes it's a good one
turn the webcam on to prove i don't have to do that
what do we got for a time for new year's eve new year's day for uh tonga
eight hours from now i genuinely thought my message got buried but i had a dream a couple
days ago where jerma got me 67 physical copies of terraria for my laptop each copy was the weight
and size of like a school textbook in a lot of you guys dreams i somehow turn into this weird
folklore monster i turn into stuff that you read about going through norse mythology or
something all right where's my house are you saying that you're not a mythical creature i
am saying i am i don't have to say anything you make your own deductions from them wrong place
statistically speaking you're probably at least one person's someone's paralysis demon maybe
sorry by the way i mean i'm not i'm not doing that that's just your your personification of
that sleep issue this is the big three where are you now yoga class right you go ahead and do that
thanks your next opponent is a witch she lives in this abandoned place called speed city a witch
trevis don't die okay i do have new uh tv shows to watch let's see video game the title is pure
wait i i own this now that's cool that's the one that i dreamed about a brain buster that's one
of the best moves in all of wrestling i'm pretty sure it's illegal now i don't think you can do
that move anymore hurricanrana nice on to battle number three dear travis here's a highway bus
ticket you know where the bus terminal is right take the bus to meet the witch she's got powerful
magic but you can kill her just come back alive what about the cat what about cat the cat just
got out oh no gene is going to turn into one of the cats that you have to find during the
part-time job mission almost got them all bad ending yeah i'll get that i'll be fine
oh no it's the bus driver from the other day you little bastards let me in
in
different enemy type yeah
goodbye time to get on the bus or maybe not there's somebody there oh
shit
i'll give you a nut i missed i missed the nuts guy i missed the guy i missed the nuts guy
he's only under the game for like five seconds speed city who's driving the bus me is there wheel
back here in the middle ghost bus what the fuck it's oh it's a side scroller now nice
i forgot about this i don't remember this at all i really don't
swing what the fuck was that let me up oh please i'm getting wronged
there we go three slot machines and not one all right okay god one hit killed
mess you up
i'm gonna get underneath there it is there we go oh my god finally i actually get to utilize it
it's taken me 12 hours in the game at least eight or nine do i fight on the bus
this hello next up is a win and devil's laugh you didn't dream about me i'll fucking kill you i
swear if i ever hear you say another woman's name on your sleep you'll wake up the next morning with
your joystick missing got it anyway make sure you hit the red button on the iphone and when you
change number break the phone in half move to a different state
legions of more powerful opponents out there never forget that keep your feet on the ground
your head out of the clouds i am three billion six hundred and two million six hundred thousand
two hundred and eighteen percent certain you will die trust your force and head for the garden of
madness okay is there a bathroom on the bus i don't think so bathroom out here
bathrooms on the bus are the worst i'm not sure i've ever been on a bus long enough where i've had
to use the bathroom bus reverse that you know what i mean found the cat i think the longest i've been
on a bus was maybe a few hours a couple hours maybe the longest i've been on the bus was 14 hours
holy shit where were you going from where to where yeah i've never had to be on a bus long
enough for the bus to need to get gas so and not probably less than something like that
because if you're on a bus for 14 hours doesn't that bus need to stop and get gas how do you get
did you just pull all right this is a real question i might sound like a fucking idiot
so if you're on a bus for like 15 hours you have to stop and give gas do you just pull over to a
gas station and just everybody just kind of hangs out while the bus driver gets out and fills the
gas tank is that like what happens pretty much yeah so just kind of like a highway rest stop
stay back this one's mine so there is a guy that's been training me what cat you frightened me for a
second kitty master oh i have been so i'm coming master
do not do anything stupid but i have nothing left to teach you aim for the top no remember
the exploding that was a true explosion was the cat and so freaking ignorant they never learn no
matter how old they get they never learned you are the third ranked assassin bitch
you were saying sunny i asked if you were ranked third
what what you say i said are you the third ranked assassin granny what say that again
dodged i'm kind of hard of hearing i can't hear much these days are you ranked third
like rooster gun that's right don't you see idiots all men are why should i even bother
killing you here we go even if you had nine lives it wouldn't be enough oh let's guess
she's a crazy cat lady who don't care for their own lives she's gonna fire something at me where
do i go battery i can't sprain you you can't i can hide in here can i i bet you it's a one
hit kill when i get up there oh shit and a bang left in here and get battery break the doors
why can i break the doors i'm losing health yeah i i can get up there gee i wonder i got
i'm good i'm good i get up there you're being too greedy i'm all right i'm still alive oh there's
people in here can i just bait them outside they're hiding from this lady too well why don't we work
together then don't let me let me in let me in let me in let me in why is this on the minimap
what is she saying let me in don't kill me holy shit dude you hit me like six times
everything's slow motion right what i thought it was slow i thought it was slow motion
push out
i got fucking obliterated
good i got him go i'm getting there what's in here another spot anything in here
oh this is i can walk all the way around lady you're dead this is perfect
oh i tried to do it it didn't work hit him what no battery i'm good all right here we go
straight across to have a chance full battery before i get over there
oh i'm gonna do this way can i i think oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh my god what's
run run away run away run oh my god get up travis get up travis get up travis get up travis
travis travis travis travis travis travis travis travis travis travis travis travis get it
let's go i'm going back over here
my body my body hurts okay i have to go around let's walk into the wall like five times
here we go spot to go around here no there is there another spot i don't see another spot
i'm gonna go back through here i'm gonna go around this spot this spot this spot this spot
oh shit there's people back here don't kill me don't kill me i'm dead
oh my god my tongue is out of my mouth
oh there's people everywhere is there health back here get out of my way i'm targeting the
guy on the ground it's just sitting in building she doesn't have a lightsaber right okay she
doesn't have a lightsaber all i know she wouldn't take out like a knife a little blade or something
pretty good boy damn right i'm an apprentice of the master thunder lee he was a good man and i hope
one day you'll be as good as he was count on it a little present for you farewell and good night
i mean we didn't get destroy man there you know that was a that was an honorable honorable death
we didn't get destroyed man oh i was gonna say if i missed that a fourth time then
there's no hope for me all right uh give me the katana obtained the japanese katana please give
it to dr naomi would you look at that very cool new weapon don't get to keep it congratulations
you are officially ranked third only two more to go it is really cool how they all die this
girl's freaking me out she really is i don't like this this character is scaring me speed buster
only two more to go she's basically red flag the character that's true all right number three
go to the bathroom the cat in the house
i don't hey this is diane from bped videos this is just a reminder for you to return one of our
videos it's titled 69 techniques to improve your luck making it's overdue by two weeks be sure to
return it to us soon no i i really hope or wish you know the drill that one of those would just
be a normal ass video i wish it was just a regular movie i want to just be regular five
hundred thousand dollars five hundred okay where's the cat cat's here the cat's on the fan
what do you mean cats on the fan what do you mean spinning around what are you talking about
no that's like a little goldfish what do you mean watch he's blind i wasn't even looking in this room
a new part-time job and i have to give uh the katana to naomi let's do that first
what are you spamming this link what is this link we're spamming what do we got spammers
what is it hold on wait wait wait i gotta turn this shit in first give me one give me one sec
all right what am i clicking on don't lay a single finger on anything german 95 how it feels to chew
five gum your senses that's pretty good that's funny hold on this music is good they use it a
lot it's in most of the scenes what was that why is this just immediately fine sorting algorithms
playing this is the last thing i put on stream oh where's it coming from i don't know where it's
coming from it's supposed to be okay browser source jesus christ here this is the wrong video
that's not the right video where why do somebody link that the one that somebody linked me
what's the one i just had link it i turned this shit off it's killing me
how did i fuck this up almost three times in a row i don't know all right here you go
didn't say 5g could you make something sound like cheat you know like what it would what it's like
you can probably take the ch so it's like five g five chip yeah you can do that from when he's
talking it take the ch and chew and cut that up and put it in front of five
but it's like to chew five chew yeah it would work that would it would work we haven't looked
at the t-shirts in a while let's do that let's get some new clothes something snazzy new jacket
i want to get all new clothes i got what 400 000 yeah give me some new shit here something
because this is going to take us to the end of the game what snake skin it's 177 000 dollars
the blue tiger tiger is pretty all right tan i like the blue circulates
hello what's 3000 per scorpion right let's get you actually make this pretty lucrative
don't sting me motherfucker get out of here where you go that one's gonna try to sting me
it's a gold moon it must be worth more i stepped on it son of a god damn it
pick it up thankfully it does not stack that'll be bad this shit load over here
there's a jackpot watch it don't get stung
whatever i got 22 that's like 60 what 60 66 000 i'll do that one again now that i know i know
pretty good strategy now you gotta wear all snake skin for this coming battle
i just spent all that money though i spent all that money and it's gonna cost like 300 000 to
be snake skin we'll see how much money i have after i do all the little side stuff all right
what is this kill all the enemies with the time limit mission ends when all targets are dead
5500 a kill kill all the enemies within the time limit the type of enemy you will fight is a secret
mission ends when time runs out 1500 per kill the gamble fight you have to wager money
i'll go i'll go all in if it's possible right here this is incredible i'm gonna just run over
and over again you don't have to go far it's right here or right here all right what the hell is this
okay mission start what's the gamble
gamble apparently
i should i really should just i'm gonna i should retitle this screen
i'm gonna retitle the bot calls it first links
no point
make it louder i don't think you want that
yo
shaking around right now actually the thing is as you can tell me swinging around this is what it
sounds like when i talk when i do this you understand
this could be a shitload of money this is gonna be a huge amount of this is gonna be more than
a hundred thousand dollars it's gonna be like two hundred and eighty thousand dollars
eighty eight eight that's gonna be 1500 times 88 oh my god but that's three minutes
we want snake we want snake hold on it's close though the scorpions was three minutes
so you're talking about like somewhere around 60 70 000 for the scorpion one 130 000 at least
100 000 for that and it's right here all right let's go get the new sword i probably have enough
right snake sword please please look at the gift please it's like it hurts my head i feel like i'm
looking at a kaleidoscope this one's damn good of all the ones i've made this one's definitely up
there this is 498 000 that's all my money uh i guess i could go dig up some stuff from the ground
what how much do i have i need way more than that yeah i'll get that sword that's the next
thing i'm gonna do all right what can i do in i'm just gonna i'm gonna go do that one again
snake suit and the sword well let me get the sword first because then it'll make the missions
faster i'm gonna go do an assa one of the other assassins this dude's digging for gold yes he is
yes he is sorry jeremy this is important i closed my eyes i didn't see what it said what did it say
i knew it was a image that had text on it i don't know what it said i just put it on
rather go look kill all the enemies within time with it all right we'll do this one
this one seems easy it said you can get a free ipad if you click on a link i already have an ipad
two what am i gonna do with two i'm gonna set them up on my bed so i have three monitors
get another one have three ipads connected to a device that holds them up next to each other
i would say that's probably peak fuckface i would say absolutely so i can slide from the left one
all the way to the right one in one go i can play fruit ninja across three screens
tape them together so they each other's back they're at each other's backs and
flip it around when you want to do something else
you know that's not i mean it's a that's not that's incredibly overdone but that's still
there's an application
all right
okay
minute 10 seconds left you save about a full minute or so and how much more do i get
yeah this one's worth doing time for the weapon well after when i get the new weapon i'll do the
gamble fight because then i probably kill way more people but i get 80 something last time
i probably go over 100 no more heroes part two string aka jeremy clicks every link in the chat
just hold on a second community content night yeah something like that okay here we go
subaki mk3 there goes all my money and there any parts for it there are not parts for it
it's just the best one somebody made this into a real pillow this image is freaking me out
this image is scaring the shit out of me where are you standing where are you this is a look
okay this look at this it's a table look at how high up you are from that cup of coffee
this is weird right it's it's like this that's that table look it's like almost like you're
why is that coffee so small this is not a table this is a floor that so this is just a gigantic
pillow then imagine forgetting that you put this on the pillow and waking up in the middle of the
night to go to the bathroom getting back situated comfortable and like turning your head in the dark
and seeing that that's pretty scary these dudes have never seen a rug before
i didn't expect the pillow to be that big i thought it was you look i'm working on it i'm
on the table i'm working on it i'm making this on the table jeremy's entire house is carpeted
yeah even the bathroom i want comfortable feet when i'm going to the bathroom all right where's
that one i got them i got the best weapon in the game it's this gamble fight yeah let's just go
carve up people for three minutes and see if i can make 200 000 i might be able to get more than
that how strong is this weapon strong is it equally as far distance between the third and
fourth blade it's not as strong but it's faster you'll find out oh that's cool this uh this is
awesome it's like it reminds me of a power ranger sword yes because he's walking away
holy shit okay that killed everybody rage is crazy
well this is worth it
you can't even spawn them faster if you kill them
it does take a little some of the windups take a little while here though
killing people dude yeah i know it's part of the game
ridiculous 39 what did i have 88 for
i love it i love that spin spin spin spin part of it it's great
what am i watching right now you're watching somebody farm money for the end game of no more
okay spawn me buddy let's go spawn spawn bring him over here all you
shit i didn't do it
why does it lie down
oh too many too many people one one guy
i'm killing people too fast
what a pain i killed less people than last time yeah i got only 80 i think they're dying so
quickly that it takes two or three seconds for them to respond it was less than the last time
it's actually too strong do the hot do this high charge attack oh you're right i didn't
i didn't even think to look for that let me try the heart let's try that
i say do the high charge attack in the gamble fight all right i'm gonna go for it but first
let's do this what that's an omega pog farming spot i know you already supposed to be dead
combo damn this is expensive all right combo it's probably the last upgrade maybe there's one more
after this
you're not hitting the right notes good strength and then health
so
only 15 pounds 15 30 45 90 this is like one bar is what is it how much is the bar 45
bar is 45 do i have enough to do i do the final health upgrade
i just spent all my money but i can get it all back i wait for you somebody do some quick math
here i need to get the full snake suit i need 500 000 for the entry fee snake suit was what 200
something let's do the let's try that technique that somebody said somebody in chat said hey dude
you can farm the fuck out of this place do the high charge at the gambling one with this weapon
with these upgrades you'll get a million dollars in no time let's try it
mr streamer there's a battery upgrade for the sword that gives infinite battery please get it
there was no it wasn't available i wasn't on the list when i went there
all right so he's saying high charge into the group of people
see if i can get this work low charge okay low charge to find a spot i can't see where i am
hello this camera sucks
oh it was high
all right well this technique ain't gonna work
take a long time to charge that up and look at this battery no this ain't gonna work
oh
someone getting one person wow this guy sucks i'm testing something this is not for real
oh shit this guy's so bad at this game yeah i'm all right i this is
oh he's gonna die in the gamble fight
you need to have infinite battery for it well that wasn't part of the deal
what the fuck is everybody still got 36 000 for that i think it was low actually i think
it was high actually i think it was low i think it was high you know it may have been low
oh fucking i'm just i'm just gonna do it my way i'm gonna do the scorpion mission right now and
i'm gonna get over 100 000 right now guaranteed i 100 guaranteed or what well or uh or what let's
see if i don't get at least 100 000 from the scorpion mission you know bowl cup that's too
risky i'll get a body pillow made of my face and it'll be in bed with me for at least three nights
kim is gonna think you're a psycho all right so that it's three thousand dollars per
scorpion which means to get a hundred thousand you need to do so let's say 30 would be 60,000
40 i need what 50 40 what how many 50 something 87 that's not correct let's go
come on i need like a big scorpion party ah come on by the way if i do that over a hundred
thousand you have to buy a body pillow and off my face no you don't that's fucking weird don't do
that i'm trying to get something you to do don't i don't want you to do that i don't want you to
do that don't do that nobody do that where's the spawns i'm getting screwed here this is
doesn't even count look at this where are they there's nobody here i've got there's no more left
they're gone there are no more scorpions on this map not done now this is bullshit that was like
that was bullshit that was it's actually bullshit like they would there was nobody here there was
nobody here this one doesn't count i got scammed i actually got scammed i just ran around a circle
15 straight seconds there was no scorpions i guess i the spawn rate was dog shit no that doesn't
count i died i didn't fail it instead failed well i died so that's why i failed fine i'll get it i'll
get it fine i'm gonna shred it after three nights you come here wait a minute i don't know why i'm
not doing that i'm going to the killing one these ones just these are so bad for money if i mow alone
i'll make like 20 000 i'd eat like 600 don't worry i'll i'll get i'll get it i'm gonna get it
don't worry i'll i'll i'll find a spot that of my choosing not of your choosing i'm not no of my
choosing why does that exist wait what somebody's selling this for 57 dollars what in the name of
god 57 dollars read the reviews what i mean people have bought this people have not bought this
there's a four star review it's pretty big so only buy if you want to get something that fills a lot
of space but other than that it's very good the floor pillows look excellent the floor pillows
look excellent on my floor very good the print is clear and looks awesome very well made great
pillows which are a great pillows which are a wonderful decoration accessory for every room
quality is good colors are shining bright what is good what is going on we originally ordered this
product to use as cases for sleeping pillows since the fabric used is rather rough to the touch it
is not really so suitable for that purpose however as its original and stated intended use is to be
a floor pillow case i will not count our failed experiment against that product for its intended
purpose for the pillow case is really good robust fabric keeps its shape machine washable clear
vibrant colors that don't wash out very good quality and i can definitely recommend it if
you want a shiny pretty happy case for a couch or floor pillow to lounge on and then in brackets
consider getting a filler pillow along with the case if available we didn't and it's not trivial
to come by a 90 by 90 centimeter pillow where i live printing and shipping was fast without any
issues my only request for redbubble is to add actual sleeping pillow cases made out of the
same fabric as the bedding covers of the product line up shiny happy pillows similar designs
what's the fuck let's read these reviews this is on a different product completely separate it's
just it's my it's it's the germ of fear face on another pillow we originally ordered this product
to use as cases for sleeping pillows since the fabric uses rather rough to the touch it's not
really suitable for that purpose however as its original stated intended use it is to be a floor
pillow case i will not count our failed experiment against the product for its intended purpose the
pillow case is really good robust fabric it keeps its shape machine washable clear vibrant colors
that don't wash out very good quality that i can definitely recommend if you want a pretty
shiny happy pillow case it's the same fucking thing it's the same seven reviews he's just
discovering bots for the first time this one has 53 reviews guys why would you want
my face on a spiral notebook what are these 53 reviews great notepad well received i really like
it i was surprised at first because i didn't think it would be so wiggly but i soon started
to use it for a lot of notes the artwork on the spiral is great quality and the surface and pages
were immaculate amazing the notebooks were very sturdy is there a shower curtain wait this is
shower curtain there's not a german 985 this one's fucking this one sucks what happened to
this one did you not even bother to center the image you just didn't even bother to center it
rule of thirds hold on show show all right i'm gonna show i i can't like save these images
hold on let me put this on the screen this is freaking me out i could probably spend an hour
looking at this stuff just do it i'm not gonna buy these all right hold on can i what happens
if i do this no i want a different image i want different please and thank you does this work
i can't interact with this why can't i no i have to do like hold on it's 80 fucking dollars
for what you need to get the germa cover to match what what cover jesus christ all right
this is like a whole nother stream there's a whole no no this is an entire nother stream
i i wanted before the new year's party i want to do this this is ridiculous this is what we're
gonna do for an intro we're gonna look up all the bootleg germa 985 faces on shower curtains
that is ridiculous people saying hey just like dude you gotta like take those take those down
you can hear the phrase for every door that's closed three open that's programmer lingo
for every for every door that you close three more open fixing bugs and shit that's for every
one that you get rid of 10 more will take your place we don't say that yes you do i know
programmer i know programmer and that's where i got it from they told me that's what they say
he knows a program pog yeah i know he's a toilet don't all right stop looking that stuff up
because tomorrow uh that's gonna be a lot of there's a lot of content there
i just saw a toilet lid with your face on it no more don't look up anymore
fucked up there
let them get back up no
oh
come on lock on somebody
it's been like six hours and i still can't get that out of my head
good
be big one one that goes up doesn't kill
come here
yeah the horizontal movement is the best one but it doesn't happen every time
very good 66 not good
80 again stuck at 80 forever not even 79 this is a very good stream i like the stream because it
is the one i watch definitely five stars the only thing is the stream is quite long so i'm
only glad if you want something that fills a lot of space very good product 235 000 that's enough
to get the snake outfit i think at least a couple pieces of it what about the entry fee
the entry fee guys i need five hundred thousand dollars yeah fuck the snakes i ain't doing it
if there's still all right i have two more fights to do so if after this one
welcome i got the money for it i'll get it i just bought these i don't want to do this one again
what's the uh this one's seven thousand per kill seven thousand kill all targets it's a secret
seven thousand per kill kill as many as you can within the time limit missing when time runs out
how's this one gamble fights is going to be the most efficient yeah but it's boring
it's just grinding all right fine i just saw something really funny um i can't i i'm not
going to say it until tomorrow it's so dumb i just looked over here i mean i think we actually
already saw it on screen so let's just talk about it for one second there's a fifteen dollar and
seventy six cents mug on this website it says germa nine eight five tall mug it's just a white
mug there's no branding there's nothing on it it's just a white mug just plain white it's just the
title of the listing what are they trying to say i don't know nothing probably it's probably just
a robot
pretty good start actually this is a really good start you can't even hear the music yeah it gets
ridiculous it's called the grind man
get them all on the ground uh i got already 32 is that subs coming acdc freak five community subs
thank you all appreciate it hopefully you can hear me right now that's one is there a way i can
get a right to left swing to happen more often i don't think there is i think it's random this
game is absolute sensory overload yeah these parts it is there it is come on am i out of battery
you have a lot of left to rights left right's bad it's like the worst one
up down down to up and left to right
right to left come on that's all right come on let me get more than 80 did i count 83
there's so many bootleg germa shirts yeah there are a lot how many pages existing some of these
are stickers the mk2 is probably better for this it yeah it probably is but i need to do this one
more time i'm gonna do the baseball one because i'm sick of seeing that same thing over and over
again baseball one should be about 80 000 and then i'm pretty much there okay mk2 is better
for crowds it's just bigger it's the last one right did i ever do the pizza one pro wrestling
pizza butt the finale i i'm doing this one 75 000 it's all the guys at the lightsabers but i have
a much better weapon now 75k just to kill one person i'm just gonna go in there and spam with
the katana what's going on here what's going on chat what's going on what are you guys doing
and put it on put it on single letter only mode you can do that oh wow you can go somebody spent
channel points to write h that's a that's a real hero right there here we go
do
come on
is it oh get out of here where is he 75k it's all about time but still 75k good i thought i
what is this is my thing broken i thought i was supposed to be single letter only chat what the
fuck's going on all right if i do this then i have enough to go to let's just go let me do this one
right now this one always gets me because this is right in a tiny little area i have a good weapon
come on don't get hit
shit where am i holy fuck it almost hit me what he thought it was on the ground he's done it on the
ground what that was it too it's just it didn't register when i tried to swing the second time
on the fucking old we emotes i'm doing garbage collection and i'm gonna do rank two blame
lotion yeah i'm gonna blame the motion controller from 20 years ago i will do we have two letters
now maybe it's because somebody put it in their mouth and messed it up that would that would be
a very strange person i wouldn't i wouldn't want that person near me for my family final trash
collection it's time for the second to last fight of the game it's gonna be wild i guarantee
people have a really really really great idea here well chat is doing this you can write
something somebody just wrote said hey dude when chat is like this i can tell you this
you get the chat to yourself one person just did a full sentence and i saw everything they wrote
appreciate that thank you by the way am i gonna finish this game tonight yes
after this is probably not much more after this next fight because then i'll be going to rank one
there'll be probably one more sequence after this and that will be it make sure you vote on the poll
you have until tomorrow afternoon pacific 12 p.m pacific to vote on that poll until it's closed
all this for the worst and best stuff that happened on this stream of the year we did
the same thing last year we're doing it again this one's gonna be a little more comfy than
last year's because i'm not gonna be in the studio this year i'm gonna be hanging out right here
fucking suit on maybe a large maybe a pizza maybe a large pizza maybe have a car maybe i
might have a couple glasses of wine right that seems probably it's gonna be real real comfy
tomorrow i'll tell you tomorrow's gonna be one of those streams that you just you know if you're
doing something for new years hope you have fun at least if you are in eastern time those of you
that are just hanging out put me on in the background of every party you go to
make sure make sure i'm the focus you're hanging out with your friends no no no no no me me that's
the stuff that happened all year remember and turn me up to a point where everyone can hear me
and then you can all gather around the tv and point and laugh this way who is this guy everyone
sit down for a second who's this best worst noise of the year put this on get this fucking loser off
these are gonna be worse noise of the year bro bro oh put on this on tv wherever you are like i'm
you're out no but if you're just hanging out for new years i'll be here until after the ball drop
eastern time we'll have a couple drinks watch over 20 different nomination videos i'll eat some pizza
do i have enough okay i'm just going fishing for three thousand dollars am i gonna get hammered
no i'm not going to get hammered i do want to go back to the house though well where should i get
a meat lover's pizza from a chain or should i find like a pizza place like a good vegas pizza
place make it i'm not gonna make a pizza all right i will i will get from a good pizza place i'll find
a good vegas pizza place i'll look up reviews i'll find the best and i will get it ordered
it has to be dominoes or the curse won't lift no i got that curse lifted remember i spun around
three times the chair last night and sung a song or screamed whatever it was that curse has been
lifted how many curses are on this tree two more of these
all right just need a few more one more and i can do rank two this one right here where is this
the behind here oh no that's a ball how many balls do i have don't answer that don't
god damn it i just want one more of these holes to dig here
get it 500 000 it's time to pay the fee f let me f i have zero drop frames what you guys you guys
resorting to baiting the guy that has has had traumatic experiences with the internet problems
and you're gonna pull that one on me my god all right here we go rank two what the
letter what do we got here don't come looking for me sylvia crystal some trouble at home
she quit her job what the hell is this all about the rank two match will be a destroy stadium
aren't i a hard-working girl buster not the baseball stadium again okay sylvia only two more
to go i'm going all the way that's a promise destroy destroy all right save the game make it
happen what we got 10 11 in game hours 12 oh this guy is really over the uh
how long is no more heroes average time to beat to be fair though we did stop like three times
we know more than that we've paused a dozen times to look at photoshop's of this 12 hour
playthrough maybe for at least an hour that has been flipping myself upside down and pretending
that twitch was upside down right making 5g gum jokes that nobody liked so i'm on pace
there's probably realistically another i'm gonna say this probably like another 45 minutes left
the only way that it's not is if it's like a million dollars that i have to grind
to get to rank one if that's the case then you know it's gonna take a little longer than that
jump using
why did it just want me to do that because it was full i guess i mean it was pretty cool
i gotta check how many balls i have another one right here
t-shirt it's gonna replace the cat i'm sorry what is it just a tank top well that's boring
it's just a black tank top this is the germa look kind of is that junk that
bad girl bad girl
uh like stay on this run people over let's go i should line them up should not
it's hit and run all over again there's no time limit here that's not correct
how long do i have to do this for 10 minutes no done i want that i'm not muted i'm not muted
i'm just gonna go in a circle i can't fall off the bike so who cares
i'm not just shadow band to be what the fuck you must be malding pretty hard to be this quiet
uh i'm just sitting here seething why can't i drive the car am i supposed to fall off
okay i hate the guys with guns it's the worst
that's it give me that quick does it battery is it health battery there's more of this shit
yeah who's left we good we're good all right bring it on softlock no there's just another
spawn over here that i didn't see this guy probably be it
and there's no one left very very good great there we go come here he's the walker
especially two guys yeah
all right what what how much more do i have to do i really do feel like this is a softlock
shouldn't have fallen there we go i was gonna say uh oh you shouldn't have fallen off the
bike the bike was well i got shot accidentally down there 18 hour boss fight incoming oh god
want some sugar
why do i always have to go to hell doesn't build much confidence hey if you lose you're going to
hell by the way but come on tell me you just tell me anything else if you lose you go to heaven
lose and you will float up to heaven those with guts at the glory with this your suplex rainbow
the double wrist arm salt you've slaughtered hundreds yeah but if this isn't ever well why
are we all kind of bad guys in this game everyone's like trying to kill each other
all right bad girl yes the game's called no more heroes uh this is insane this is insane
thirsty hold on a sec you're not gonna drink somebody's blood right
damn that smooth i feel alive again want a drink i'm telling you it's you think you don't you don't
hear it but it's in a lot of stuff why am i such an angry bitch seriously no matter how many i kill
it's all the same they're all going to pay yeah with their fucking lives you're a bad crazy eyes
you have no right to look at me like that it's just a job the daily grind you're no assassin
you're just a perverted killing maniac in essence they're the same don't go on thinking you're
better than me you think you're hot shit who the do you think you are all right back to swing
oh that hurt oh you can't block that one these people just coming there are people coming down
this still how do i save these people she didn't even do anything it was a bait i was waiting for
it wrestling move let's go trying to parry it she didn't even swing
look at her health she's not even closed it's a good hit come on this is gonna be long i can't
fuck this up this is attrition you can bait that out cool oh new move pretty cool didn't even get a
hit i could probably do the dark uh with that dark slide it was called like that do it do it do it
how am i gonna do this easy i still don't understand that move she's trying to bait me to swing
oh holy shit that almost that did so much damage that did so much damage that did so much damage
i could fight these people all right let's go halfway eat shit what is that she's turning
she's doing the witch she's doing the witch what do i do don't startle the witch oh fuck i thought
i could stop it i can't stop it i have to just fight them come on give me a roll give me a super
give me a bar bar bar let's see it damn it hit them back we all right i just kicked this
she just got accidentally comboed there too i think i learned that on accident hey did you
oh no she's taking out the booze phase two she's way sloppier and way easier to hit
she's just gonna be stumbling around here we go that was fairly poorly tied it's very poorly
target her hit the table what was that push yeah oh see you later number two
ain't gonna take much longer what the fuck just happened she's doing it again
what happened how do i get her off how do i get her off how do i get her off
how do i get her off how do i get her off i'm dead it wasn't greed it wasn't no what i i was
i i forgot okay listen when i was holding the button down i was gonna wait for her to get up i
didn't go in the first time no i didn't get the first time she went down i was like oh you don't
go near the witch i'm charging the charge and i forgot that it will it just goes it just swings
after a certain amount of time ready like see one two it just does it i forgot i was gonna hold it
there until she stood up and you know now we learn things and we're here at 17 hour boss fight here
we go oh that really sucks don't worry i'll get there we're gonna be here till tonga's new year
no we will not just hug that right side of that side here we go right we got very flashy very
flashy too bad didn't do anything can you imagine doing this with one of the weaker sabers and never
upgrading your saber this would actually take like four hours come on more more take a steak
here she goes she can do the thing now at least i know that i can knock him back
come on halfway almost this is it all right let me see if i can get this that's one should do it again
okay that's it bring it on take me to dodge like that that's okay that's all right get away from me
i'm not taking any chances there i'm not gonna i'm fuck that quick well she's vulnerable what the
fuck get me away from this oh my god he's terrified yeah i don't want to do this a third time send it
back you got any more music's good the music's pretty good in this whole game it's very good
could have dodged around that sorry third time how would you aim that way i'm looking at her
i still have a heal back there that i can get just don't get instant killed all right good
when you block on the jesus christ you know i'm looking over here i think i want to block on to
the person 100 and fucking 80 degrees behind you i think they're a little closer what the
fuck is going on i'm trying to time it my fucking god if i lose to this my hands go through those
walls what the fuck is going on but go do that frame by frame i would like to i want to see that
slow down to a tenth of the speed i'm getting this right now do it again would you turn around and
lock onto the person standing behind you i'm not even gonna go for it anymore i'm not i'm not gonna
go for it i'm not gonna do it again i'm just gonna try to win she was crying with two hands what the
fuck is wrong with you why you okay this is it get out get out of here let me beat this what the
fuck no my health is so no no i'm not going in no i'm not going i don't care if it's free
i don't know i can't be certain i don't know if i can bait it or not and probably can bait it
i got a fucking greasy finger right now it's slipping off just kill them
okay i'm fine
i'm not going in i promise i'm just gonna beat her with pure sword play
don't you fucking kill me you motherfucker get over here fight me i didn't even what she didn't
there wasn't even a time there was no frame data there was no frame data that was instantly
i thought i was gonna get a chance to cheat i didn't get any frame data after that oh fuck it
was instant that was instant the last time that happened she hit it back but it was like bing here
it comes what oh come on what the fuck there was no there's no frame usually just like the frames
that she has like six or seven eight frames it didn't happen that time it's happened every time
there's frame data and frame data on that one it's frame data come on get over here i'm not
doing this a fucking fourth goddamn time yeah just don't hit it back there on the fire phase
don't hit it back at all i tried to dodge kiddo i'm not doing this again no way
on a million years i'm not doing this again wow you're trying so hard right now travis yes
i'll get it just like feel how my heart i'm pressing buttons shit i tried to fuck messed it up
what did i just do i have no idea what just happened i still look a fucking cartwheel
come on i need this i need this i need this i need this get that fire going
i still have a full health over there oh all right here we go fire i'm fine
killer again i don't have it why didn't i do it
oh don't hit it back where shit they like that dodge i like that dodge
how many times are you gonna do this shit come here it's almost time this is a final fight final
swings watch the standing man i'm not choking i'm not choking i'm fine god damn it attack what the
fuck i have to do it i actually have to do that no okay i have to hit back and forth back and forth
without any frame data do something i win you're dead you're dead die just die this is it how the
fuck did i miss that
it's up to my throat naughty girls need spankings maybe you forgot i'm a bad girl
phase two
hey this is this is pretty badass i'm gonna lie
i give up you win yes i've won
the laugh oh that was ridiculous all right 330 000 dollars good no snake outfit we're going right
to the last rank i think that's the probably that's the last health increase we can get
i know that's right on behalf of sylvia crystal i'm here to tell you that you are now officially
ranked second thanks that was a close one almost didn't make it it was a fine fight sir
shit that was close so what is it is the last fight between oenstein and smog here
marvelous upgrade the sword first let's see how much money it takes so all those minus twos and
plus two referring to frame data but what people trying to tell me to save a few extra frames or
add a few frames i saw a lot of add some frames i don't i didn't need to lose frames i don't know
why everyone's saying that i didn't need to do it early it's kind of stupid it's weird why is
people saying that hi we're sorry to inform you that your video membership will be revoked until
you return one of our videos it's titled french-made cafe filled coffee please return it soon
good morning mr touchdown i wish you a pleasant journey to number one
five hundred and fifty thousand dollars that's a lot of money is there any more jobs no there's
two more right there must be two more assassin jobs then to round out 20 sure my time is running out
it's almost 8 p.m in tonga we ain't gonna see that a new there's a new job what's the new part-time
job what else is something after scorpion what's the end of the year almost almost not quite though
2020 is right around the corner almost here you always the germapillow yeah but i can't all right
can that be like an early 2020 thing i have to actually have one made i have to i'm not buying
like a 500 dollar one on red bubble whatever this thing is called you come here all right what's the
job bike jump jump your bike off the point try to fly as far as possible is this game on steam this
is not on steam this is for we and playstation 3 xbox if you live in japan this is the original no
more heroes the ps3 version sucks is what i've been told a bunch of times i'm told it's not great
i also was told that the ps3 version of this game for some reason maybe they just didn't think they
were ever going to remake the second game but didn't they put like five or six of the bosses
from no more heroes 2 in the game as just random just bosses you can fight afterwards so kind of
i'd rather just play a second no culture here nothing but dropouts and even dropouts can create
their own culture ride those waves dropouts rise those bikes but the biggest dropouts of all they
jump good jump will jump start your future it's a world that only those who experience it can
understand a wide and wonderful world the god of jumping away so you jump long and jump hard
speed up and jump from the ramp on the point but from a well-timed wheelie jump to jump further
three time there is a time limit so just straight ahead where is it how far down the road is it
here we go that's pretty fucking far okay i just jumped out of the world i jumped out of the
invisible i went past a barrier 50 000 50k for like 10 seconds let's see what the last two assassin
missions are yeah that's insane money for no time at all i'll just do that like five times
what is the final mission kill without taking a single hit from the enemy 10 000 per kill
holy shit that's a lot kill all the enemies with the time limit you'll face cloned humans
oh that's some i shouldn't even attempt it why is this one good kill all the enemies
within the time limit i mean this is the final one might as well do it
may you find 10k per kill but you can't get hit and it's probably three minutes so if you figure
if you have to not get hit for three minutes sure you might make 500 000 but you have to you can't
get it for three minutes shit i haven't peed in seven hours i probably should do that yeah after
this after this i'm gonna go grab some water and yeah i'm just gonna hydrate take pee and we'll
come back and we'll finish up the game after this though mission start so this is baseball
is it baseball it's not baseball oh no it's just no
you hear that audio too much blood he's not gonna pee till next year in tonga
that would be something now wouldn't it that's pretty crunchy can i do it 30 kills
that's really good too it takes that's one minute for 90 000 that's probably
that's probably better than more reliable yeah that's more reliable than the bike
is it 550 okay i also need to let me check the shop just the sword shop i also have to upgrade
my body yeah talk to the ball guy yeah he's right next to the get it all done here first
let's go check out the sword stuff actually this is right here isn't it yeah get this done
that dumpster is unopened bench press one more time 64 000 oh this is kind of tough now
so here we are 750 people ever recording this video 750 people are now subscribed to the channel
found the same site thank you so much it got deleted it got deleted right let me say and
squats wait i do appreciate little mini games like this like sort of san andreas style of
have an open world in a gym but i really wish that each one of these you had to do them faster
or something it's the same minigame every time wait for you it's so hard and no more heroes too
yeah that's the balls too that is you're right it isn't an open dumpster good catch
giving up on the balls i don't know
keep practicing shit do i need one more the real question is how much is the upgrade for the
katana if it's more than three or four hundred thousand i'm not i don't think i'm gonna do it
no balls if i don't do it single finger on anything something to drink all right weapons
parts well that has to be a joke 999 a million beam katana energy saving part
for sabaki mk3 set this into the heart of the motherboard inside the beam it's just
infinite battery it will never have to be recharged okay all right this one's power
uh i just i'm gonna do this one yeah this is the best one it's expensive but i'm gonna make it
one of the germa stream awards are going to actually take place
so the probably at uh the stream is going to start around six pacific so around nine p.m
eastern is when it's going to turn on i would assume we'll hang out for like 20 30 minutes
relax maybe go over some uh red bubble uh scams and probably around 6 30 i'd say
6 30 6 30 ish we'll probably start doing them probably they won't take more than a couple
hours like just like last year but i wanted to line up right when we do the last one we can count
the ball down all right i'm gonna do that mission again that fighting one because it was really
really good for some reason i we were saying gta grand theft auto and i don't know why you can
run through every chain link fence in grand theft auto and this game became grand theft auto for five
seconds i don't know why yeah no way did i just go across the bridge for no reason i did didn't i
i want a giant goddamn circle wait are we back in single letter emote only mode
i didn't even say anything we're just doing it this is 90k yeah this is almost 100,000
then after this i'll do the bike jump like a few times and we should be there
really good money 250,000 i need 550 i do have increased power though maybe i should try the
gambling one again right that sounds like a good idea doesn't it done in 20 years i will return
i love you david i can't wait for that game to come out that games we're gonna
hey prediction that game is going to be one of the best games come out in 2020 prediction
um derma i'm on a joke withdrawal i need a joke to fuel my addiction well you don't don't just
don't be don't we did it to jokes there's this two sides to the mask it's comedy and tragedy
it's not it's not just it's not comedy and comedy by the way those people just disintegrated he can't
even spawn what you're asking for is the equivalent of picking out all the grain cereal in lucky
charms not just only marshmallows man you can't just you do that yeah that's a mistake
i want to take this fully powered up sword into the gamble one i could probably get 150,000 easy
what version is this this is the original version being emulated through dolphin on his fake we
no every time every time somebody asks it's been i own it it's behind me
emulators are illegal when the president does something it's not illegal let's do a jump
how do i have the control set up in dolphin i have it actually was a this that's a great question
because anybody that's you know has you know owns a we and owns a copy of the game and emulates
their own software um the we mode is that it's kind of finicky and what i mean by that is i have
this is a we motion plus controller but all bluetooth is not made the same apparently
and even if you think you have oh yeah i've got a bluetooth it connects to your computer with
bluetooth but even still some bluetooth dongles don't work with it and it can't sync them i had
an internal i think it's actually the one that i had it was it was it was a qualcomm was the
bluetooth that i had and it just wouldn't sync with it the dongle that i have that works with it
is a targus bluetooth dongle that's the one that i'm using it right now it's like a target
targus 4.0 bluetooth dongle and it will sync if you have the original we motion plus controller
there's this one i have here usb dongle he's making up words don't use that word that's what
it's called it's a dongle it's a usb dongle i mean i guess technically it's a usb bluetooth
adapter but it's a it's a dongle that's what it is and what you do is in the settings in dolphin
there are obviously ways to connect directly to a real we mode they have it built into the software
so it's pretty good and again for some of the new viewers that might be here uh just going oh hey
he's well why is he what's he doing why he's emulating this hold on let me just fucking
destroy this um this game notoriously runs terribly on the week and the ps3 version is
not the version that i wanted to play when you have more than a few people on the screen
especially when you do the blood splatter on three or four people at the same time it can drop down
to less than 10 frames a second also all the open world stuff on the original week is painful
riding the motorcycle around town is of rich chugs chug chug chug and it runs at like 480p
so that's why i've decided to do this how much money do i have 339 all right the gambling
mission will take care of this and then it's time for the end of the game save your excuses for the
judge 17 right uh 18 you can do the secret ending um maybe maybe how much longer i i don't think
i've ever seen the secret thing is it um is it much longer after the game or is it something i
have to grind out for a while for more than a couple hours go pee or i'm gonna do it oh right
okay i'll do it after this let's see if this if i if i don't get over 80 on this then i'm gonna
be very upset because i have the maximum power upgrade tried to do it i waved just didn't pick
it up so fuck dude go pee i'm gonna be i'm fine oh no no no no it's over battery that's good you're
all dead all right line it up that's so stupid
42 i can do better than that i'm tired of my arm you know before you said that i didn't notice this
but i'm no now i do notice that my arm hurts i've noticed that now my arm does hurt
i've been kind of doing these motions for the last two straight days
there's too much key building on imagine that were real line it up yes
i might get over 100 if i'm good it's too late for 100
not even 88 126 i'm almost there it's getting late too what is it 2 a.m eastern 524 all right one
more bike jump i'll pee don't worry i'm gonna pee before i get to the last area yeah it's two
we'll probably finish up we'll finish up within the hour i can't imagine how this full area
and another boss will take more than a full hour i don't think so
i don't i need to do the jump one more time that would be 50k thermos dongle doesn't work like it
used to nice nice good good one why would i read that because my brain is a scrambled egg
and just says things out loud i don't know why i don't think nothing to compare to the dream
sequence from seven hours ago will germa read anything that's highlighted pretty much
yeah yeah i tried to hit that person and it was bad for me
nancy drew games of shovelware knockoffs of professor leighton games
i have some really bad news for you nancy drew series redates professor leighton by about
probably 25 years nancy drew and the golden shoe came out in what like 1996
oh that was a bad one 1982 yeah at least the leighton games are actually fun
i played the leighton games at least one of them whatever one they ported to the ipad i've played
it that's not a real leighton game how is it not whatever the first one is professor leighton in
the golden shoe it's one of the first ones why didn't i call this number in the first place
yes hello ask who's calling this is the assassin's association right look i gotta talk to you about
she's done it again hasn't she hey are you listening excuse me for asking but are you by
chance an assassin whoa don't tell the whole world then you have been had sir you are not her first
it's a fake association
listen lady i don't know what the hell you're talking about who are you anyway
but here's the thing if it's a fake association and you've convinced a hundred people
that they're part of a assassin association and you have rankings and they actually are ranked
do you know how many isn't it real she is a professional you mean a fraud are you telling
me this was all just bullshit she set everything up would you mind telling real fake assassins
since you've come this far are you serious what's the point this is all some make-believe charade
but a good man finishes what he started fight to the end your most formidable opponent awaits
in the castle now off to the garden of madness is it oh yeah the entry fees she's collecting
entry fees from those 11 12 15 20 potential people we still have to kill each other
and we've agreed that that person is higher in rank than us so we have actually just made an
assassin's league let's just sure the entry fee makes no sense cut out the middleman all right
gene this is the last time i'm going to be able to play with you okay let's look at the cards for
the last time cool missed a couple oh i like this one and this one and that's it darth vader
good thing i've got the dash call the bike uh now my friends has had enough of my shit
this is dumb though what's the point of doing this there really is no point in this segment here
it's just this is kind of annoying that's all oh i got how far away is that how far away is this
is it worth doing it's right there all right it's right here and then i'm gonna pee i promise
which one should i get what do you want a ball let's teach techniques displays the position
of somebody said hold c to make it go faster it's not working uh despite the position enemies allow
you to jump and slash cool okay extends your dark side now increases the range of your grab
that's pretty good earned bonuses based on now too late in the game allows a jumping down attack
probably this one grab range is good jump slash might be good too jumping slash
dash yeah let's do it technique of love
i'll be right back and we will finish up the game i almost picked up the xbox controller
everyone's scatter he's here did i get extra dust why does this feel extra dusty come on i know
what it's like when my mic is muted i can see it it's right in front of me okay here we are
fight number park store a driving segment why am i thinking it's not with the hedgehog
don't collect the boxes okay can you punch i didn't touch that guy he ran into a box i told you
don't run into the boxes i know the secret i know the secret don't drive near me
all right that guy got by that's fine how could you be fast i have turbo boost
did i get him what if i just go like this i'm just gonna block the road i'm just gonna block
the road i can't i can't stop that's so funny not enough time all right i didn't even jump it's
fine you can't lose well that's a problem between you two not me i'm gonna land on top of you
i'm gonna land on top of you the hell is that me is the old is the old lady back with her plasma
cannon there's no way i was gonna jump that take the damage shit i have to jump this i'm
trying speed up always look behind you i'll get it eventually it's the ghost of my teacher
go that way nope i'm going this way no well i got an extra health this is a maze this is a maze
segment isn't it hey at least we got to see the title of the stream one more time
oh my god freddy fred freddy another 40 000 bits from freddy dredd
that 75 000 bits earlier 23 000 the night before and that subs and freddy holy fuck freddy says beat
it faster which way am i supposed to go all right freddy i'm gonna try you have to beat it for tonga
tonight well seriously freddy that's that is a ridiculous amount of money look at open up the
thing above the chat look at how many bits that is fucking a thousand one hundred and fifteen
dolls and bits use it to buy a pillow oh don't worry i will
why do i hate tonga i'm not staying up but like what i look hey i got a bit i got a big stream
to plan and get ready for tomorrow about doing a 24-hour stream i got a big pizza eating stream
to do tomorrow i think he was pointing this way actually a big stream yeah in your office forehead
in your yeah in your office forehead there's no i don't know why that's funny it just is
okay that you can't fight jesus how do i do the jump slash oh there it is
well that's completely broken you just flick the nunchuck
and it can kill people instantly tonga is disappointed why i didn't do anything
beat it faster i there's only so fast i can go i can go as fast as i can is he alive he doesn't
look like a ghost here what does it say travis that path of men is not path of beasts you know
you know uh your edge can be poison or cure to be learned is the path and to be ignorant is also
the path your path your path is that path that no one nothing can pass yet the path reach on
devotion is only given to those who perfect single thing reward them
no reward those who do not perfect does it reward or just evil lie down your path
fight until you die travis thunder for you i left my in the laminate micky mantle trading
card in there for you it's worth like four million dollars
how much is an original micky mantle worth in pristine condition
now be honest did you really think i would let you do me if you hit number one i mean look at
yourself you are a dopey otaku assassin the bottom of the barrel dopey no one would be caught dead
with desperate bitch where in the world could you find a woman who could fall in love with someone
like you one is right here it was fun travis i love you forget to use the restroom trust your
force and head for the god end of madness okay thanks sylvia um but i'm at walmart do we need
toilet paper i just that's what i'm calling you jesus blog to me every time i call you on the
phone here we go you're in the shrek outhouse i wonder how what the reaction in this chat would
be if shrek was the last boss somehow they made it happen and it was only in this game there was
some weird coincidence two of the executives of best friends or something and what would happen
what would people do like you know how a snake made it into smash brothers one of those scenarios
funny green man and it wasn't some kind of copycat voice actor it was mike myers
with original lines welcome to my castle i heartily receive you my son all right enough with the jokes
a joke you don't remember me travis i am your true father blood does not make such mistakes
thanks you are full of it aren't you dark star it's a good story i'll give you that much
that thing's really difficult to use story that's not practical if you were my father it doesn't
matter the only thing that matters here is who's best remember son engraved into your memory is
the night when everything changed i fell to my feet right before my son's eyes do you not remember
this in my deepest memories i hear someone calling i remember it was a hot summer day
there was someone standing behind my father and mother that person killed my parents the
i can't make it out who are you remember who are you try harder i think i can see it
gamer posture now son she was the girl you loved
all right for one second i thought his sword went all the way behind him and stabbed him through
the pelvis because it was so unruly they couldn't get i told you the fucking weapon was bad at least
not anymore you killed him didn't you yes and that's why you became an assassin to kill me
now i get it all those fights it was for this
i can help you to get even she's a good con artist that's for sure she set up some killer fights
so you and i finally meet you should thank silvia jean there's just one thing i want to ask you
who are you me you don't need to know all of your trivial questions will be answered in the
afterlife answer me it's impossible impossible what do you mean it's too terrible it alone would
jack up the age rating of this game even further so what who cares what if the game gets delayed
you don't want this to become no more heroes forever just being emulated right doesn't matter
fast forward this so you can tell me okay i'll make it short and quick this ain't other way any
no it's not an emulation it's not an emulation error
maybe it had to be done but vengeance begets vengeance i hope it doesn't stay like this go ahead
all of your sorrows end today gene fuck i have to skip this cutscene we are we saw the
it's all right it's not saved right before this it's all right it's fine the emulation
oh wait we got a this is actually pretty great
they've got a big error code on the screen it says one of the following may have happened
the emulated gpu got desynced disabling dual core uh that's true and the emulator okay whoa
whoa whoa whoa whoa whoa whoa we're good wait wait did you hit the dragon or hit her
weird timing all right there's weird timings on that shit this hurts
oh she's fucking fast oh can't dodge that but he fucking swings in a row
oh shit just hit her what do you think i'm trying to do what's going on i'm the last one
phase two now i have to fight the dragon too hold on i need give me this wow you just
i don't know where damn it oh my sand slipped off the way mode too fast it's too fast
that's too fast she just beat me unbelievable shit i try to dodge it
all right phase three let's go phase three phase three do it what do you got more moves
you got nothing on me making the it's making it tighter i get it shit that hurts
swing swing oh you motherfucker motherfucker my hands are falling off the we mode it's so sweaty
jerma you're never gonna start for the red socks today stop making me laugh
jerma you're never gonna start for the red socks please why can i hit you you bitch why why why
oh shit that we watch shit check the remote
what don't you what the fuck is happening okay is this supposed to be this is scripted right
it's scripted oh no it's scripted good do it right brother please don't kill me
sorry gene this hurts me too we're both in the same business after all no we both got conned by the
same person i had enough time for you to rest gene good night travis i hope your next dream
is a more pleasant one it's over this is where it all ends right silvia you're never gonna start
with the red socks can you imagine a popular red socks starting pitcher streaming on twitch
with the we mode and he just throws his arm out the day before a big game oh that's so funny
i gotta beat this normal heroes man it's so much fun my arm is killing me though we're gonna have
to ice it dark star don't forget the bonus boss i want different music too freddy tried to get
another 22 000 bits and says go faster i did i that was first try i went faster are you gonna
do no more heroes too yes uh probably not immediately exactly 14 hours at least two of
those hours are spent looking at photoshop's return to sand to destroy or view the view real
ending i just can view the real ending real ending okay it's finally over holy shit the one can see
his dick or anything right what just happened can't this guy get some privacy at least when he's
taking a dump i'm afraid not these fights don't work like that it's time to die you gotta be
shitting me well you hurry up with that i'll be outside that was close henry thanks
what an idiot you're disgraced to yourself and all those you've killed it's the kylo ren guy yeah
okay there's another all right easy
more punish what the hell just happened right underneath that blade grab him
sure you got henry that fool that would be hurting that's a move i've never seen before
what this fucking thing doing add an opportunity damn it i missed it
no no no no no no no look at his health get away see you later henry oh fuck i'm all right
oh i did it twice in a row you motherfucker come on come on henry shit i'm all right where the
fuck am i where is he doing he's gonna move underneath that left that left shoulder he's
vulnerable in that left shoulder every time don't get stuck in the world
hmm is there a battery box holy shit i thought he was done again oh shit he's gonna dash
all right excellent bike take him out come on he's almost done i almost dodged into that yeah i
almost did see you later henry nice fight you're dead don't make me laugh mind if i ask you
sure why the hell do you call me travis travis like you're my friend or something who the fuck
do you think you are you can't be serious all this time you didn't realize what are you talking
about it's my brother yeah of course it is what the hell the craziest shit i've ever heard why
would you bring up something like that at the very last minute of the game i would have thought you
would have at least expected a twist of fate of some kind
and hey where's silvia anyway she disappeared without a trace where the hell is she
you mean my wife what wife yes you know spouse soulmate they really they really threw it all
away in the last 40 minutes here addressing the audience ten years ago fast boarding because we
were both in college at the time shit all news to me i'm gonna need shock treatment to get over
this one i'm sorry for all the trouble my wife has caused you forgive her she caused me some
trouble all right but it helped me clear up a lot of things you know how women are especially my
wife a really big spender yeah she knew my income wasn't enough so every now and then she just
disappear she's a bad wife but a good woman are you telling me that you and her oh come on
we're similar in many ways
you're right face too suddenly you being my brother doesn't sound so awkward
let me ask you how do you plan to put an end to all of this
wait a sec you want me to tie up all these loose ends i don't think so you're the protagonist i'm
just a cool handsome foil who happens to be your twin brother hate to say it but it's your job
i want to bail but where the hell's the exit there's no way out is there
no getting out right bro this is like a shitty metal gear solid cut scene
then let's find that exit they call paradise
let's go and that imagine looking out your window and seeing that yeah you look out your
window you see two guys just running by with lightsabers did they both die at the same time
well there's no more heroes too so i'm gonna have to say i'm sorry the answer is no
don't skip i'm not gonna skip the credits two is not canon i mean it is yes it is three is not
canon three is canon they're all canon even the top down one is canon doesn't the travis strikes
again set up the third game in a way i'm fairly certain there's introductions to people in them
well we're gonna have to play it gonna have to do it eventually before the new one comes out
why would they preemptively make a numbered sequel non-canon yeah that doesn't mean
travis strikes again is a half of visual novel is it i thought it was like a top down
bullet hell type game we still have a sword but isn't it really twitchy and it is top down
play killer seven as well now here you go here are the voice actors dd bradley baker told you
it was the fish killer seven killer seven's on the game cube right it's on steam when did they
put it on steam oh shit okay is it a good port or is it crappy it's good it's all right it's
good good good for it's pretty good all right i'll play it it's also on the switch it's not on the
switch as far wait iirc the port is literally just dolphin running the emulator is it really
that's pretty funny if it's that's true it's not it's not that was the trailer the footage
they used for the trailer was dolphin footage but the actual port isn't huh that's crazy
google is a powerful tool yeah it is all right everyone here we go post credit
don't you let's go gene why everybody named gene i know too bad there won't be a sequel
yes there will actually uh it never was supposed to be a series according to suda right so didn't
sort of say that this was supposed to be a one-off thing and he was never supposed to make any other
games that's actually real that's actually to be continued shit my wiimote got disconnected
oh i gotta sync this back up play the uh the other ending can i see the other ending anywhere
that's not on youtube all right also i think i've unlocked the hard difficulty right sweet mild
bitter extremely difficult many strong men await you perfect for beginners bitter does anything
change in new game plus it's just harder everything has more health and does more damage
you keep your money in your katana so what do you spend your money on on snake skin oh clothes i
guess sure i'm just curious to how hard the default enemies are on the hardest difficulty
well not bad considering i have the best weapon available but if i don't do new game plus i
actually can just start on bitter right yes you can okay cool all right well that's uh that's
going to be it kind of a long one tonight make sure you get your votes in for new year's eve
which is tomorrow that stream is going to be starting very late
6 p.m pacific we're going to start the festivities somewhere around 6 30 we're going to count down
the new year somebody want to link in the uh i think i got it right here here it is that survey
monkey link you can vote on some of your least favorite and favorite things of the year we will
count down the ball i am going to get out of here we will do the subs and bits and everything they
were they were ridiculous insane money drops tonight but also regular bitten subs as well i
want to do too thanks for watching hopefully we see you tomorrow uh if not then hope you have a
happy new year those of you that are not going to be around tomorrow for the festivities i will see
you again on saturday and i think i think we just confirmed that it was going to be me and joe
we're going to do keep talking and nobody explodes i think that's we just had that confirmed earlier
in the afternoon that was no more heroes one it's a classic it's great if you can get your hands on
it go for it we will be playing no more heroes too we'll give a little no more heroes cooldown
and maybe at some point next week we'll go back to it do the second game maybe do something else
we'll see the two worst streamers combined hey what fuck that's fucked up yeah good night
guys we'll see tomorrow and we'll conclude no more heroes one and let's teleport back
too early this evening kind of a long one i know it's it's pretty late i gotta get some food too
soon here holy shit these subs subs and bits there's so many huge bit drops
surjil but is the first one here for 250 thank you surjil but they say happy new year happy
new year to you as well thank you uh schazo ip dropped 20 community subs freddy dread had the
more than 1100 dollars tonight freddy fucking ridiculous absolutely crazy crazy i never expect
anybody to do something like that all i can say is thanks absolutely insane thank you we also had
a thousand bits from local crafts no message just a thousand bits thank you local crafts also core
monster not to be overlooked here with 75 community subs 75 freddy dread also on top of the bits gave
50 community subs a bunch of people in a row gave subs there i think we caught them all but and they
were tier two yeah they were 50 tier two community subs bonkers it's bonkers it is that's bonkers
that's almost i think that's that's close to two grand three grand in one stream freddy dread
holy shit thank you also av exe gave thousand bits part of the that insane train of money that
pulled into the station here thank you av also lucas thank you lucas for a thousand bits 10
bucks as well they just said germa hart thank you lucas how are you gonna spend your new found
earnings stuff for the stream i think the reason why i've been able to in 2019 well let's we'll
go over a quick we can talk i'm gonna talk about this tomorrow too but there were a lot of big
streams in 2019 that were that required to hire people and resources and that shit is only possible
because of the support that this channel gets that's that that doesn't happen without
this ridiculous amount of money that some people give the continued subscriptions that people have
on this channel i'm not i can't do those things without it so seriously 2019 was crazy we'll talk
about it more tomorrow but thank you again superintendent charmers thanks for the 250
uh germa erectus apparently is an emote that says there's an error we've visited it wasn't found
i'm sorry i don't i can't see your emote i don't see is it was it did i get baited
i might have gotten baited snooze and copter thanks to the 250 on top of your 5000 bit drop
here earlier they say oh yeah i also want to tell you about i want oh here's is this we're going
to get the god hand uh this is god hand uh god hand has a weird over-the-top humor similar to
this there are more than a hundred unique moves to unlock with which you can customize your move
set you can assign a move to each button basically if you want to drop kick on triangle you can put
it there or maybe on x and put an uppercut on triangle etc there's a casino that actually
functions and the composer is the same one as the one from this game the reason you didn't like god
hand is because you were exhausted and frustrated by a bunch of throwaway ps2 games that you were
rushing through that night god hand needs a single full-length stream dedicated to it back me up here
chat besides it is old resident evil controls you know the tank controls you need to get used to
it i know it's probably the only bad thing about the game please give it another chance it better
be the first stream of 2020 okay it's not going to be the first stream of 2020 that stream i believe
is going to be joel and i playing keep talking nobody explores maybe it'll uh maybe it'll be the
second stream of 2020 third stream of 2020 it'll be early 2020 i'll do it again
you really you really you jumped into god hand after trying to make the shitty tony hawk ride
skateboard work for 10 minutes it deserves a second chance that's fair oh didn't i try to break that
over my i remember trying to smash that over my knee and i couldn't break it that's the only
memory i have of that whole stream well yeah i will give it another try i promise i only want
good streams in 2020 no bad ones you gotta crack a few eggs and make an omelet comedy tragedy
hey gnarly thanks for the 250 hello it's a me mario thank you so much for playing this nintendo
game on a legitimate uh nintendo wii system you should consider streaming more nintendo games in
the future especially certain rpg a game featuring me and my brother you are a super streamer wahoo
thank you mario nintendo is one of the consoles i have neglected over the years there was that
string of wii and wii u games though i did do that i streamed wii u for a week or two straight
thanks mario but i've not played any of the main line popular triple a nintendo games on this
stream i really haven't that's right mar but mario maker is more a compilation of memes than it is
playing breath of the wild don't get me wrong mario maker is fun but that's not playing mario
galaxy that's playing a bunch of interesting compilations of people's levels dark soul thanks
to the 250 hi gap gaming here we were mildly concerned about you fucking someone on stream
but we'll let it slide since you did have all those gap socks on you did still have those gap
socks on anyway have a gap new year you're gonna get me fucking in trouble rock writing thanks for
the 300 bits rock writing germa i got your contact info from a friend of mine moira chisel i think
you did some good sleuthing work with her in scotland not too long ago for some background on
yours truly you could officially call me a locator of fine goods per se nice things get lost nice
things stay buried for a while i find the nice things i get a piece of the pie in other words
i'm a treasure hunter currently i'm in iceland in a small town called skip rot when i that's it
i kind of wish i knew what was going on there uh moira thank you rock writing for the 300 bits
thank you 25 dr peppa for the 250 show us a picture of your family dude nice nice content
monster monster rancher rap fan thanks for the 400 bits i've changed my username and given you
bits now please sing the monster rancher rap on stream i don't i don't know what that is
what is the monster rancher rap monster rancher introduction theme song
i was transported to a faraway land to the world
oh
this is your username now thanks for the 400 bits it's cool
uh oops wait what just happened what the fuck just happened oh there we go thank you monster
rancher rap fan for the 400 bits hey cad vtv thank you the 500 bits i heard this is where i
heard this is where the guy fucks on stream well you heard wrong thank you for the 500 bits future
gamer thanks for 250 you hated god hand because the tony hawk ride physical skateboard was not
working hold on this is i'm up i was looking for this earlier this is lose i i actually think it
is lost i'm so frustrated by the fuck i can't even like have fun in a video game now i want to mail
that to tony hawk i want to like cover that in peanut butter and like mail it to him then just
like he'll think it's like shit but it's just peanut butter it's not a big deal it's a hard game
holy shit what the fuck am i talking about uh all right so that's um i okay i get it i see what you
mean what a psycho um i gotta give it another chance i'll give it another chance i will
thank you for the 250 appreciate it thank you curve bumble for the five i can't do damage no i
can't what am i supposed to say to that how am i supposed to counteract that one i can't what am
i supposed to say to that well what oh well barry backtracker can't back up anymore he's
his heels are at the edge of a cliff and he turns around he's like well the thing is what i meant by
that is oh dear there's not much room back here um hey curr bumble thanks for the 500 bits really
cool to see you playing no more heroes and considering a bunch of fun ps2 gamecube era
games we'll love to see you start the new year off with that ps think you also you'd like robot
alchemic drive it's a weird giant robot sim by the edf devs never heard of it that's edf is a great
game though oh right chibi robo write that down it's a cleaning game i want in the recommended
discord cleaning games chibi robo put it in there thank you curr bumble appreciate it hey graham
thanks for the 250 hey german just got back from work and picked up a stuffed crust pizza for the
first time in years because of you speaking of i work at a family video a rental store and we do
have an adult section it is disgusting you weren't wrong yesterday also when is the next
german rumble the best part is how you said and it's disgusting the german rumble is going to be
soon but not soon as in a week or two as soon as in maybe a month or two yeah i wanted to have it
coincide with if you don't know the next german rumble is going to be a charity stream it's going
to be to help sponsor one of my good friends runs in the boston marathon and all the money
during that stream that comes in is going to go towards sponsoring his run and all that money
goes to uh i believe it's going to go to a pediatric cancer ward in boston pediatric
cancer center in boston from what i've been told so far that's the plan sponsoring running a marathon
is yeah i think the way that the boston marathon works is you uh i don't i don't want to speak
completely out of place here but i'm fairly certain it's uh you raise money for a charity
and then you run in the marathon for that charity i guess something like that i'm not sure if every
single person that runs the marathon has to do that but i know that's what people do my god's in
the chat holy shit that's that's horrible i look like i made it a raw chicken meat this is disgusting
how did this get bigger anyways uh thank you graham for the 250 stuff crust pizza it's pretty
good it's pretty good just hope that your stomach doesn't turn into a knot after it thanks for the
bits appreciate thank you bloody punker for the 500 bits hey germ i've been dealing with a lot
of insecurity and paranoia around dumb stuff like my voice as you have a background in voice acting
and bring life to countless funny characters with you i was thinking you'd be a good guy to
ask about experiences the vocal insecurity tips about overcoming it thanks pretty much that when
you first start talking to people and you hear you i'm not sure if you're talking about
referencing hearing your voice back but when anytime anybody listens to themselves back
they all you always sound a little weird you sound that's me i don't like that everybody has this
weird um sort of it not that i doubt that they hate your voice or anything but everybody seems
to have that sort of you squint your eyes when you hear yourself talking but it just takes time it
just takes a while i mean at this point you just kind of know the way you talk and after a while
if you hear yourself back enough times and you just accept the fact that that's just the way you
sound you become okay with hearing it back if you go back and watch my first maybe 10 to 20
youtube videos i was trying to sound better i was trying to sound smarter and more intelligent and
better and and and more articulated and after about 10 videos or 20 videos or so it's just like i
kind of just know the way i just talk like this this is the way that i talk and that's it this
this is just what you get this is how i speak but for dealing with the actual insecurity on
your voice i wouldn't read too much into it to be honest we communicate this way i can't think of
the last time that i heard somebody talk to me or somebody was giving a presentation or doing
vocal work and i thought even for a second about hey that that doesn't sound right no that's just
you that's who that's your voice that's you and that's good that's fine everyone has a different
voice the guy from the servers okay server germa but yeah it's that that's who you are that's how
you talk that's the person that you are you got to own it own it whatever it is you got to own
the fuck out of it you have to own it i know him from the servers don't you but i wish you luck
bloody own it thanks for the 500 dollars
own it thanks for the 500 dollars well i've seen the bowl cut yes and i've also seen the
gandalf from a gandalf face i don't know why that just looks like gandalf to me i don't know why
it does take that image that you just linked put the gandalf hat on it and add a beard you'll know
what i'm saying thank you dark soul for the 250 the one with one of my chin is down and i have
the nose uh dark soul thanks for the 250 let me tell you something crazy about crazy dough in
south boston it's my favorite pizza and i live in new york that doesn't surprise me boston has
some of the best pizza on the planet yeah number seven on earth dark soul again thanks for 250
okay but domino's pan pizza meatza with garlic white sauce is amazing also if you use the 5.99
coupon for a medium pan pizza you can choose a specialty pie customize it and effectively
just get five to seven toppings of your choice for two dollars more so 7.99 it's a fantastic
deal papa john's can go go whatever domino's pan pizza and meat sir with garlic white sauce
i might order that tomorrow this is on you dark soul if i order that this is on you
mm-hmm are you doing a bounty no i don't know how bounties work
don't as aren't bounties you you say i'm gonna do a bounty and then you watch a home depot ad
and then give you thoughts on it isn't that how it works we play a game for an hour you say hey
that was kind of fun what do you guys think about that home depot commercial are you more inclined
to shop at home depot after watching this ad with me together or did you all tab into a different
screen and mute my stream maybe eight of you watched it and zero of you are gonna go there
for all i know half of you might not even be old enough to hold a hammer how old do you have to be
to hold a hammer what would you say what age would you say is i am comfortable with this person
using a hammer i'm gonna say i'm gonna say at least at least 15 to 16
i would not be comfortable with some with like a 12 or 13 year old you with a hammer and nails
i'm gonna say like 16 dude like six not you wouldn't get a six-year-old a hammer
are you are you out of your mind if they're being supervised well 10 um i would say at least like
13 and people get their driving permits at 15 yeah so if you can't if you can drive a car
you should be able to use a hammer fuck yeah i was way off i think i'm just getting old
and 16 is like seven to me now you know what i mean it's like that's your if you have like oh
i'm 15 oh you're you're fucking just your baby i'm so old now how old is the man talking 34 35
this year in 2020 anyways you 16 year olds older than me what point is hammers are dangerous
and just be careful be at least 13 and have adult supervision streamer is lying about age to give
him pressing that he can use a hammer damn it i thought you were like 28
close enough after 28 you're the same like i told this after 27 or 28 you're the same age until you
you turned 50 why am i talking about this um somebody brought up using should kids use
hammers and i was like i don't know let's talk about it it was something like that
hey heck master thanks to the 500 bits appreciate it no message just 500 bits thank you
dodongos for the 300 bits thank you niberi for the 250 bits day germa love you streams you're the
only streamer i've watched in the past seven months just want to say thanks for the entertainment
thank you uh for the 250 hope you stick around thanks for watching dj gamer thanks for the
thousand bits dj love your streams please play disco lcm i was going to it was in the plan
it was part of the plan but then it got voted off the island for uh from the drew crew so no
we'll let me see it thanks for the thousand bits though thanks for 10 bucks appreciate that thank
you thank you zay zavier for the 250 happy birthday germa 40 is the new 20 40 is just
40 is the new 30 which is also the new 45 if you turn up 50 you're an old person done
cougar duke thanks for 300 bits we sports resort stream or riot maybe eventually heavy bin thanks
for the 400 bits speaking of germa and dreams i had one a few months ago where he was painting
in some garage somewhere drinking heavily at some point bashed his head through a plate of glass
and went to the hospital bringing the camera with him honestly could imagine him doing it going to
the hospital on stream joe that's fucking horrible i'm all right though okay the second birdhouse
stream that was just what happened to the lavos stream cyclops parker a few hours ago gave seven
community subs didn't catch it it was an individual boing boing boing boing boing boing thank you
cyclops you still here there you are appreciate that we're getting to the end here why don't we
throw the credits on and we'll change change gears here they're gonna be a lot of subs that
fly by tonight because it was shitload of community subs so many subs thank you guys
all of you from the bottom of my soul for real usb boingle germa i'm gonna dream about well noodle
that's the thing we've talked about it so much this stream you're gonna have another dream
you're gonna have another germa tos dream and you can tell us all about it when it happens
thank you some somnus for the 500 bits hey germa i'm going to nevada at the end of april
i've been on the east coast my whole life this is the first time i'm going to the west very excited
ps this is for a furry convention i hope to see you there i've already brought this up but if i
went to a furry convention you would never know if i was i could go in a full costume and never
take off the helmet and you would never know that i went there there would be no proof there'd be no
way for you to tell i wouldn't talk i wouldn't say a word and that helmet would never come off it
would not be removed until i was safe in my home i could just go i could go anywhere i could put
on a fake mustache and a hat and put on sunglasses and go anywhere and you would never know i went
everybody would know it's you how if i'm in a full costume that you don't see my face and i don't
ever take it off unless i'm in a place where i know there's no cameras or anybody how would
you know who that was just sort through the frog costumes no i wouldn't go in a frog costume i
would go i would i would go in like the most default costume possible i would try to blend
in as best as i could your voice i wouldn't talk i would do the pantomime thing the wave the hands
hands up you you know this this shit i'd do this well this is the wrong but you know i would walk
around and i would do this stuff you know i'd be like who the fuck would know it was me you you
wouldn't be somebody would say oh i really like your costume and i'd go you just gave away your
routine i'll change it germa it's a furry convention not disneyland yeah right people do that in those
costumes it's how do i know that i know i just know i might go i might you guys don't even know
i you don't think that if you tell you're talking to the person you don't think would dedicate some
time to this and go to something like this and just fucking blend in and i would never tell you
about it we'll see but thank you some for the 500 bits you would you you'd brag on stream yeah
after the fact after the fact and a full week or two later i would talk about my time at this furry
convention i was it was me that was me hey sparky your hat thanks for 500 bits just reminded that in
2020 is the year of the rat thanks for the great year of entertainment that's true
germa just is a furry i he lost a sub no i didn't tell you that i was a furry i told you that i was
gonna blend in with with the furries at the furry convention maybe when is it what day
hey pin thanks for the 250 hey germa i gotta get up for a flight in three hours could you keep it
down all right i'll keep it down thank you peaceful hayley for the 250 how you doing jeremy hope all
is well i don't really have much to say i went to galaxy's edge and built a lightsaber it was
awesome till i came back home and my lightsaber just didn't work it just didn't fucking work i'm
one of the unlucky few who just got a bad saber that's not good going back soon to get a new one
i expect disney to pay me money after this anyway good night germa yeah that's not cool aren't those
things 300 bucks they better work defective kybert crystal sorry to hear that uh peaceful
hayley that's an expensive purchase and hopefully you can get it figured out thanks for the 250
hey pin thanks again for the 250 hey germa and chad i'm flying out of state for a university in
a few hours and i'm scared do you have any advice for me thanks all a lot also go fuck yourself
pogs in chat germa venus he read it uh so for flying uh what's some good ways for to fly
if you're scared of flying the best thing for you to know and i'm gonna i'm gonna spit out a
incredibly inaccurate statement here but i know that there's an accurate one somewhere
i'm gonna paraphrase this accuracy it's something like you are 500,000 times
more likely to be injured in a car than ever in an airplane like you are more you're more likely to
get bit by a great white shark than have anything happen or go wrong on an airplane it's not that
much but the gist is true right that's somewhere in there paraphrased oh they're not they're not
afraid of flying i'm flying out of state for university and i'm scared oh fly like flying
like you're okay different topic entirely all right different topic entire so you're flying
out of state and uh don't be nervous be excited because that's a new experience you're gonna meet
a bunch of new people a bunch of new friends it's a new chapter in your book you should look
forward to reading it also you've you're 300,000 times more likely to be eaten by a great white
shark than you are getting hurt on an airplane just in case you wonder unkind thanks for the
500 bits hey germa boy i've had a really long weekend at work and now that i have a few days
off um i've done all my chores i got it on just around 1 a.m and here you still are they legit
made my day and i'm really glad that you stuck around for so long you provided so much free
entertainment here's to many more yeah thanks for stiff thanks for stopping by hope you have
a relaxing rest of your evening here wait you guys are getting this for free hey butt squire
thanks for the 250 in motherland of burger slavia this bits cost 3000 american dollars
i slaughter cowl and make burger to send you this message the local warlock want me to give you this
as burgers used to say yeah what you are now cursed thanks i'm not showing this one because
this is one really is cursed thank you butt square for the two i'm not i'm that'll actually
curse everybody here i'm not doing that you actually will have you'll have like a you'll
you don't i don't want to curse you anymore hey go dot thanks for the 250 bits hey germa i might
have a solution to your ace attorney flashing problem okay if you pirate the wii version of
ace attorney it was originally on the wii shop you play without the flashing white screens
i even tested this and can confirm that at least the first case has no flashing
hopefully this can give you a chance to play it even if it's not on stream
really no flashing even if it's not on stream by the steam version i think the steam version
still has flashing though but i interesting thought on zeroic thanks for the 300 bits
hey germa i have two questions for you two first of all what do you think is the best
looney toons character not to be confused with your favorite looney toons character that's not
what i'm asking what do you think is the best looney toons character but not your favorite
looney toons character uh probably not probably yosemite sam daffy daffy was great the roadrunner
yeah daffy roadrunner yosemite sam in that order okay what's the next question my second question
is what your favorite looney toons character is they said the best not top three daffy duck daffy
duck for both answers freddy dread thanks for the 2000 bits more money from freddy let me sponsor
the next carnival in a way you already are you just don't know it so thank you let me sponsor
the next carnival freddy dread you already are daffy duck is better than bugs bunny yeah bugs
bunny's classic but daffy duck is irreplaceable you know he's grinning so hard right now yes
he is yes he is ladies and gentlemen that is going to conclude the stream tonight we'll see
you tomorrow for the new year's eve stream let's move to the end thank you again to everybody
i really appreciate it let me see all right here ready we're gonna do we're gonna do something
tonight those of you remember uh the germa slots game cad btv cad is currently streaming right now
so i think we should go let's go let's go say hello this is the germa slots guy if you were
curious go say what's up tell him germa nine eight five sent you he wasn't wait wait hold on he
wasn't watching the stream today are you serious well maybe we shouldn't rate him at all no let's
go what's he playing finding a game buffet the wheel decides our fate all right cad let's see
let's see what you got i'll see you guys tomorrow happy new year if i don't see you tomorrow
take care have a great night