Hello. He's early, he's right on time. Welcome back everybody to this community content catch-up stream.
And I'm not talking about the red stuff. I still got it after like five days. We have a lot to
talk about today and a lot of it is going to be stuff that I don't want to say and it's going
to be also stuff that you don't want to hear. So it's going to be great for both of us but both
parties are going to be real happy about this. He's retiring and I've decided that that is it.
I broke tits too much and I'm done. Over the last week, well five days or four days,
whatever you want to call it. I've been having an internal conflict that was constant to decide
what I was going to do. I had an appointment with my doctor and people were saying plus two.
This is not a joke. Like I'm about to like really drop. I'm about to drop like a fucking
you guys not going to be happy. This is not like oh here comes the fucking punch line.
Okay I gotta I gotta relax. Here comes the punch line.
No comedy. What you're about to hear is what I'm going to call a band-aid rip.
It's going to get it's going to get long-winded. So I hope you have time.
Uh those of you that don't know over the last couple of years I've had mystery pain
that runs down the middle of my chest around to the side and down the sides of my spine.
I have been told oh you probably have intercostal nerve damage. Oh you probably have costochondritis.
Well you know you might have rheumatoid arthritis. That that test came back positive
and I've had to kind of slowly over the last two years try to figure the fuck figure this shit out
and find out what the fuck's going on and kind of keep my regular life going too. But I have
to be honest with you because I hope I hope I am you know 95 percent of things I say in this
channel are lies. So I hope you know that I'm honest with you all the time. I've been operating
at probably like a 70 percentile in two years and it became abundantly fucking clear
over the last week or two that I have to figure this out and I have to focus on it and I have to
make it an immediate concern because after the green screen stream and I talked to my doctor
he's just sitting there he was like okay because I was fucking dead bad and we kind of came up with
a treatment plan or instead of hey maybe like once every two months you can come in you'll go
hey oh we have you scheduled for an MRI. No I'll see you in like a month. I'm gonna take the next
like two or three weeks and 100 percent only focus on this with me and my doctor. That means
procedures he might want to do tests he might want to do and get actually definitively truly diagnosed
but whatever the fuck is going on because you guys don't know
I it's just been driving me crazy like I'm gonna just lay it I'm laying it all out in front of you
it's been driving me fucking crazy and I don't want it to start negatively affecting the streams
when I turn the stream on I have fun and this this stream is seriously like such a positive outlet
for me and I'm not talking about like all positivity no no I'm talking about like just
I get to come out here and we and fucking have a bunch of fun I have to think about this stupid
shit now yeah sometimes it gets in the way because when you have when you have to start to wear a
fucking back brace to sit down on a chair I think it's probably time that you like go figure this
shit out right and I've been oh maybe I'll stream three four hours a day no I'm just going to take
the fucking time and I'm just gonna I'm going off the grid for like two to three weeks and we're
just gonna hammer this out and get treated because I haven't been treated for it that's the worst
thing I went to physical therapy and the physical therapist told me he looked me right in the eyes
and he said I don't think this is gonna work for you I'm just like what the fuck are you talking
about he's like well if you have nerve damage or nerve pain if you have like an intercostal nerve
problem I can't help you I'm just like oh all right invest in a mecha spine I if I could but
it but it's not my spine and that's the problem it's like kind of going back and forth for like
years where every couple months I do another test it's like well no you don't have any spinal
disc problems okay well you're still fucking everything everything still hurts oh I see you
two months I'm not gonna I'm just ripping the band-aid off because I want to just start to
figure the fuck this shit out it could be something so easy or it could be something that's very
complicated I just need to know and I want to get it done and so does my doctor now here is
here is the plan I want it to wait and by the way we're streaming today like I'm not going to
turn that I didn't want to talk about I didn't want to do like a hey here I'm going to make a
tweet here's like 10 characters describing how I'm not going to be around and my back hurts
now I wanted to stream today talk about it today we're going to do community content today
there's a lot of stuff to catch up I'm going to hang out we're going to chill but because of my
absence that is about to happen this has been something's been worked on for a couple weeks
the second channel I'm pleased to announce is bringing on I think four new editors I have
brought on a third party to really make that process easier there are now six fucking editors
I believe for the second channel the backlog is going to get wiped the fuck out there's going
to be a ton of new content probably every single day depending how long it takes I'm not sure how
long it will be but we have brought on at least in a temporary sense a bunch of people to help
really smash through that content so although you won't be seeing my face on stream over the next
two or three weeks you'll the second channel is going to be ripe with fresh fruits I want to make
sure that was available and also on top of that there are some much larger projects that have just
got barely got off the ground are just starting to happen just starting to be talked about
and I want I got I got to get healthy if I want to do the shit that I want to do over the summertime
here at the end of like the late summer early fall I got I can't just I gotta get this shit
done I gotta just rip the fucking band-aid off let's go in a long time coming so I wanted to
tell you I didn't I didn't want to text it to you I wanted to tell it to you behind the computer
screen real life house flipper yeah there's a lot that's happening I've talked to my doctor I've
talked to my my producer my friend that's really been brought on board to help with a lot of this
I want to hit this shit hard and I can't do that right now so I'm gonna just go off the grid for a
few weeks this is all I'm gonna focus on and when I come back you I will have been at least told
definitively what my real treatment plan is gonna do for whatever this is and like I said it could
be so simple it could be so easy like this could go away in a week if I get it figured out but I
don't want to have it negatively affect I don't get long-winded here and a lot of money's coming
in right now and I want to address it but I also want to address this before I do that that I this
is I'm gonna be just fine I've I don't worry about me don't worry about financially don't worry about
giving me a bunch of money and shit don't it's not necessary don't do it it's completely unnecessary
even though you are a lot of you are it's don't worry about it I'm just fine financially I'm just
I'm just fine mentally I'm just I'm just not so quite fine physically
right don't worry give him money not so money god damn it no but we're gonna move on I want to
take the first like 10 to 20 minutes or so here to really talk about this and I I I don't want
this to turn into because this is when I first I hate talking about medical shit I hate talking
because then it's just like oh well something's really wrong with him now oh no it's oh I told
you guys I told you guys that he's wicked fucked up it's like no I I just wanted to I just gotta
get this taken care of I know and it doesn't matter what I say because I know there's gonna
be people they're gonna be like well here's what I think it is going by by uh by degree in fucking
neuroscience I think he's got three weeks to live I don't worry don't do that like I don't want to
see like reddit threads over the next two or three weeks going over like well you know I did notice
that he had a little bit of a limp on his right shoulder there in this from two from six or seven
months ago I I'm telling you I think I know what it is uh-oh no it's it's completely unnecessary
but community content night we got a lot of artwork we've got reddit doctors
my I'm on a strict no comedy diet so anytime you hear me laugh it's gonna sound really weird
I'm gonna be very very cautious about laughing it's gonna be like
I told you I was sitting there I was lying down and I saw and I'll just spoil it because it's
fucking hilarious somebody took the dinosaur walking with the Thor's hammer thing and then
and they knew how much I love baseball and they made the dinosaur just hit a like a baseball
instead that's not what I would and it like came back and hit me in the face
it was just I I gotta take a comedy vacation and not even like a medical leave or whatever
you want to call it but I know that you guys understand and I don't have to talk about it
anymore I just I don't get long-winded on it and I know I take a lot I take breaks on this channel
just like last month I was gone for like two weeks I know I don't mean to do that but sometimes
they're completely necessary and this is one of those times that I have to do it
and that's though that's all I'm gonna say so let's go through how many people have just given
huge amounts of money uh zap gave 20 community subs which is insane my lactary leech 100
dollars whatever happens derma we all hope you get better you're super entertaining
let me get back to 100 just hold on a minute just hold on let let me let me like put some
gas in the tank let's get back to 100 let's see thanks for the 100 bucks though that's a
lot of money uh jacobin thanks for 100 bucks I still don't understand how this works well you
just gave me a hundred dollars in bits I hope you weren't trying to give me a dollar
otherwise that's you gave me a hundred of them but I do appreciate it that's a lot of money
thank you for litty 20 community subs poly hex 20 community subs it's just a ton of money thank
you thank you any nep subs here smug thanks to the 10 community subs five community subs from
producers send 50 dollars from trans scout tf2 thank you you say these are not pity bits
I'm just happy you're back tonight and that you're taking time for yourself and your health
just lucky figuring stuff out and also finding a treatment that works
I made you a card too here's the link yeah and you guys made cards for me before I this has
been a long running arc here that I really can't wait until the book is closed once the book closes
oh I'm gonna be going a thousand miles bro thank you for the 50 dollars it's a huge amount of money
another huge amount of money which is completely unnecessary again I want to make you want to make
that really clear I know a lot of you guys are probably thinking oh he's gonna he's he's he's
not gonna be around for like a few weeks oh I better give him a ton of money now no don't don't
I'll be back don't worry about it please I said they're not pity bits I know they're not
it doesn't I still but I thank you I really appreciate it Jamie thanks for the five subs
Philip Rivers five subs hallowed guru ten subs Mickey music Mikey music ten subs Kai straw five
subs and then 42 dollars from clammy bob I did this for the epic badge thank you all of you
I'll be back and that's all I'm gonna say about it that's it I think I've taken enough time to go
over this really really put the point across a bunch of times second channel is gonna have
a shitload of content bunch of new editors bunch of new stuff I am going to be gone for a little
while but I'll be back hey what do you say we do some of the artwork this is community content
night and we're gonna go over community content oh by the way a lot of people probably were
what's gonna happen with the green screen stuff so instead of just dumping all of this on the end
of the another community content night when I come back no there's going to be a another green
screen just night where we just do green screen stuff otherwise there's going to be hundreds of
videos just dumped right on the end of a community content night so the idea is every time a dlc
every time a little green screen dlc pack comes out I don't know why I'm phrasing it that way
but you know what I mean we will do a night where we just do a bunch of them with rules right like
the last couple times and then that footage is just available for you to put into any community
content night video right there's gonna be another dlc pack yes yes let me get let me
get back to 100 let me get back to 100 not I can't I can't operate at 60 fucking 70 anymore
and you know what also puts more effort into this and even more brain power into this
is when I actually do start to see people ask if I'm okay you know because then it gets me
thinking like is that like people are asking like dude is he all right he kind of like
I heard he's like in pain hey he doesn't look that good like fuck man like yeah like I got I
got it like it's time you know what I mean it's time I can't just be like oh wear a brace and
scream still and go and like scream at cars right going by the rumors like I know
okay my mother would be mad at me if I continued what do you say we get started I do have some
osts here I don't want you to I don't want to spoil how many potential images there are
why would I do that but thanks for hearing me out and my long-winded my long-winded look of
a speech on the face can you idiot there actually this is the perfect hair you want to hear something
funny so before the green screen stream I actually him gave me a quarantine cut it looks awful
no that no no no no wait let me back up him gave me a quarantine cut and I specifically tried to
we were putting images up from the green screen and she was trying to like do the exact hair that
I had I think it was pretty close oh there's my handsome man thanks mom all right let's uh let's
get started this is good uh I like the line work oh here he goes again oh hey you know I like the
line work wasn't I told to stop saying things about pictures oh good lighting good line work
looks good make sure you make don't forget to fucking do that some of you guys do all right
that's this is um Dr. Jekyll and Mr. Hyde which one is the bad one is Dr. Jekyll the evil one
that like kills people or is it Mr. Hyde is Mr. Hyde the evil one they're both evil the way they're
both evil isn't Dr. Jekyll and Mr. Hyde just like the hulk but 150 years ago wait I thought Dr.
Jekyll was like a scientist he drinks a potion he becomes Mr. Hyde that's just where the incredible
hulk got the idea from the doctor a doctor just can't be scientists right here's Professor Leighton
and the mystery orb this is very this is special requested oh sorry the curious village he was a
chiropractor wait hold on kind of doctor was Dr. Jekyll wait is this a real person Dr. Jekyll
and Mr. Hyde species human Edward Hyde Dr. Jekyll hold on this is important Dr. Jekyll and his
alternate personality Mr. Hyde why does this look like green screen footage from last weekend look
at this like didn't I get in this exact costume okay no comedy holy shit oh mucka ass all right
that's bugleberry okay I'm on a strict diet of no comedy I have to go like this every time
no laughing just go over it is a laugh in my head and like go over how funny that is
I felt good okay no funny no funny this nothing funny this is gonna be hard on community content
night there's gonna be crack videos how am I not gonna laugh at crack videos I like this it's like
just finished painting and walked out in the rain that's like what I see you know what I mean like
the streaks humanity I'm not supposed to be doing this I'm supposed to say thank you and move to
the next one I'm not supposed to critique artwork doing great that wasn't a critique that's me that's
me saying like like the mental like rays of the sun or thank you thank you for a joke once man
goes to doctor says he's depressed his life seems harsh and cruel says he feels all alone a threatening
world where what lies ahead is vague and uncertain the doctor says treatment is simple great streamer
germa 985 is in town tonight go and see him that should pick you up man bursts into tears and says
but doctor I am germa 985 and there's a famous dr jekyll and mr hide thing okay stop stop stop
stop I can't fuck with you tonight oh look at that it's not dr jekyll yes it is it's dr jekyll
wait that's you holy shit this is the dream that I had oh my god this dream was insane
I had a dream that the holy shit this is gonna be crazy I know a lot of people are gonna think
I'm insane for this one I have no idea why this was in the dream don't ask me why I have no reason
for this like oh well let me interpret that there's no don't interpret it there's nothing there um
I don't know how we led to this but like but donald trump was like on the ground like a
like like crying on the ground he was like this big just like this big on the ground he was just
like like a like a hard animal or something and I walked up and I was like oh my god and I like
scooped him up and I like put him like here and his head was here and he like pushed his head and
it was just like god what happened what am I gonna take you to like an orphanage or something
I have no idea I don't I don't I don't understand why what the fuck I don't know
I told you that I don't I don't know us too if that's not a joke that's a real dream is
that a joke is not a joke dream bring me to an orphanage death stranding butt with a trump baby
a good photo speaking of politicians uh a 1991 delegates needed to win apparently I'm in the
lead uh what's going on here why have I not won my home state of Nevada what's going on there
how do you win California and Utah but not Nevada I don't understand it's not even your hometown I
know but it is now because like I live here now and all I can say I grew up in Nevada you don't
know I could I could have had an adolescent fucking child brain until like a year ago
like I grew up here I finally grew up two gamers will they ever play together again why do you have
to I why am I in the penis shirt you put that there because you knew I was gonna see it and
you knew I was gonna be like what is this why am I in the penis thing never going to play again
uh that's not true that's just we have to find something to do just wait till I come back at
100 I don't think you know I don't think you know what up what Jeremy at 100 is like I'm not sure
you can handle it you can very good we've seen it wait a minute is that what character is that
what is this is that link is that a legend of zelda rat yeah no what is it oh it's a
it's from warhammer the warhammer rat oh cool here you are I love how you have the shoe for
scale it helps I love it when you can have more more when you can have more more I don't know
it's like I'm back at 100 we'll see oh just right there we just right there oh I love it
okay excuse me can I get some this way that way in the chat please thank you that's the green goblin
this was just I just made me chuckle for a second so I just I put it on here he threw pumpkins I
thought that was the hobgoblin didn't the green goblin have those little like batman batarangs
and the hobgoblin throws the green goblin has those like green batarangs right they both throw
pumpkins so okay so what is it who what what is hobgoblin why is there a green goblin and
hobgoblin dr jekyll and mr hobgoblin right who's hobgoblin like what's the what's what's
his purpose at this point is it harry is it norman is it just like or just like like a fan
this is is it wait is it a wild fan hobgoblin was created uh by by created by writer roger stern
stern found himself under pressure to have spider-man fight the green goblin again but
didn't want to bring uh norman osborne or oh these spoilers uh or have okay these spoilers
for the whole entire series um okay so there's a it's a different person cool thanks for the photo
dr hobgoblin and mr green goblin what is this yeah how do you already have a photo like well
i'm looking at photos right now hold on give but he was it was like he was like this
like pressed here and i was like running jeez christ oh should i lost my place hold on
oh shit oh it's uh oh oh we're good where were we i lost my place i just lost my damn place
here we go okay all right here we go yeah look at this the uh germapop the uh best ice cream ever
i know some of you guys are going to say that like oh this must be coffee flavored ice cream
no disgusting get it out of here no coffee ice cream i love coffee and i love ice cream i don't
like the two of them together because coffee ice cream is just like a like a it's a liar it's a
pretender to me it's like no i i like to drink coffee i like caffeine i like to get myself going
eating ice cream tastes like coffee is a is a liar it's not going to make me it's not going to
keep you going it's just like made with some beans it's made with like two percent coffee
or something not even real or it's like coffee flavoring it's like when those when those
motherfuckers add smoke flavoring to food no oh yeah it's yeah that's a real brisket oh is it sir
smoked fucking flavoring it was he oh my god whole what happened to the music i don't know
oh this is sly cooper now okay well i'm into this this just turns into the sly cooper ost
uh freddy dread just just just drove by the stream and gave 350 dollars
holy shit can't watch the stream i hope you feel better after last stream those spins were next
level back at 100 thanks for the 350 dollars in bits that's insane that's insane that's too
much money that's 35 000 bits that's pocket change for freddy don't like don't make me laugh
i told you i'm on a strict male comedy diet and then lacronda not to be overshadowed at all i
don't want to make it sound like that that's a hundred dollars from lacronda streamer streamer
pumpkin eater but uh is that a dr jackal and mr hide reference laugh idiot you've ruined it
germa are you fucking dumb germa you're fucking dumb stop okay dude i was lying back in my bed
and i was watching the dinosaur hits the it's the baseball it back into the pitcher thing
as with the door hammer and i could feel i could feel my like bottom rib like i was horrible
what wait like i'm lying back what do you mean what the fuck did you do stop looking at us like
that well what what did you think i was talking about flying back in my bed watching the green
what were you watching this is kind of what it was like i was like holding i was holding a baby
no shirt no i did i had clothes on all right i might i'm losing my place again that's gonna
haunt my dreams yeah kind of like a fucking haunted mine what happened to my hair already
all right we gotta get back to this i've lost my place again all right no more comedy edits
no more edits no more putting my face on other people's faces and donald trump's face another
donald trump's face is no more of that my doctor is watching the stream right now and he's just
sitting there going you fucking idiot what did we talk about by the way can you fix that fucking
like weird surfer hair why is it so much longer on this side what happened here i i am like the
the hair that the surfboard goes on to have fun this should be like a little guy right here going
like oh cowabunga dude here we go look at this dye my hair blue and put a little guy on the surfboard
on it here that's a good fucking cringey photo what am i doing right oh yeah yeah yeah all right
where the fuck that's just gonna show up again i have to get rid of it for it where is that it's
gonna show up again okay get rid of this get rid of this get rid of the donald trump edits
you're gonna just randomly appear okay let's go back to what we were doing thanks for thanks for
the art thank you uh as me as uh elvis shaking hands with president uh richard nixon yes it's
real more politics is that politics how is that politics it was just richard nixon richard nixon
is not politics anymore richard nixon is it was a meme back in the 60s 70s he turned into that's
what the memes were made of richard nixon now he's a meme he's what do you mean spoilers
spoilers for american historical presidential stuff no guys it's not a spoiler that that's an
education okay uh what is this we're at a gallery here oh look at auto i see auto i instantly upvote
with the upvote button where's the upvote button where's it i don't see it oh please come on give
me that one bugleberry of course we need an auto emote oh there you got one already don't you
this is the one for bttv better twitch got tv that bttv right bt dvd how about hd dvd
oh fuck that would must suck to be one of the people that ran one of those companies
damn blu-ray and hddvd yeah imagine like you were like oh man this is for this is a toss-up
that's rough what is what's going on with the music it's just me it just sounds like a cell phone
okay that's better a little loud uh i i it could have been me i could have done this i think i'm
not clicking on any more comedy and it's not right now i can't hear it yes again get in close there
it's not comedy i was just not gonna be a comedy image you said to do it oh it's this okay hold on
look at vessel this looks like it could be this good this is a real image that looks he looks
like he's having a lot of fun tuber hair lizard hair wait till i come back and i have a haircut
i'm going back to short hair germa i'm going back to short hair germa because up here is
getting a little too thin to be long short hair germa back and we'll see anyways uh thanks for
thanks for that i keep losing my fucking place i keep adding images ah there we are oh look at
this one i'm sick herma animal crossing herma caught a rat not so giant now this is cute minus
one point for what i'm getting minus one point this is tos the image oh my bottom left stop
fucking with me oh the the pic the last pic minus one whatever oh this is a picture of a holy of
holy mac this had to include it i honestly it's just it reminded me of like a scrumptious food
do you know that you're a meme on tiktok oh wait do i wait do i accept my award because guess what
if i got nominated for an award for the most funniest meme on tiktok i wouldn't go i would
live via satellite have bugleberry accepted and i would give one sentence like the celebrities
used to do remember you could always tell when a celebrity didn't give like a shit about uh some
of the awards if they were live via satellite it was like oh uh thanks for the award i just don't
i'm not fucking going to that uh hey all you voters thanks so much for making me number one
hey check out my next movie bye thanks you could always tell i don't want to be there
fuck that wait where are they holding that i don't want to go to la no i'm comfortable here and
cincinnati oh no wait what's it it's it's it's it's for a prestigious award i'll zip on the first
plane i'll be there in a minute but not not for the nickelodeon teen choice award what's okay
somebody look this up what's the percentage of people that accept an award live via satellite
on the nickelodeon teen choice awards it's like every other person there's a hundred percent
what the fuck i'm not looking that up why why is that such a why is that such a risky thing to
search what no dude i ain't looking that up nope how many celebrities have gone live via satellite
no nope nope no that's too i'm not doing that dude where would we find that data i don't know
just go watch all of them stop imagine the person that's like you know what that i'm gonna do that
i'm gonna watch every nickelodeon teen choice awards we got what is this here it's four p.m
time for your comedy hey chat why is this why am i why did i open this what is this what i don't
i don't i don't get this i don't know what this is derma it's four p.m time for your comedy okay chat
i don't get it what is that it's a boring ruined meme it's because of dick flattening
why did i say that like death stranding did you pick up on that that was weird dick flattening
that's stranding like that's how everybody says the word that when anytime any minute
death stranding right oh i'm gonna be playing death stranding dick flattening am i going crazy
i might be but you know what i'm saying right dick flattening this music is freaking me out
this is sly cooper okay hold on what i lost my place again holy shit that just okay i just
skipped and it scared the shit out of me oh spoilers oh look at how many we have
oh no no that's you ruined it everybody knows there's like a hundred more things and i could
see what they were tabs holy shit that's what happens yeah i can handle this many tabs when
i have got a supercomputer i don't have a supercomputer in fact i have a computer that's
like probably like four or five years old five and a half years old it's a 1080 in here which
is still good don't let anybody tell you you have to oh you're gonna have one of the new ones no
you don't graphics cards are like cell phones you don't have to get everyone every fucking year
you're okay with an iphone 6 don't worry you're okay with an iphone 5 don't oh you're gonna get
the iphone x no you don't why dude do you know the rtx 2100 is coming out now okay cool you just
you bought the rtx last year don't buy another graphics card for like five years you're fine
but you want to run like crisis on every monitor in your house who cares 1080 works just fine
you can you can have 1080 and get very fine graphics and like at least 100 fps on like
almost every game you play now i know people are gonna argue this here and they're gonna go
germa you're fucking idiot and i'm gonna go whoa it stops easy you know what's with a personal
attack and then they're gonna go on they're gonna say but you can't put on like refracting lighting
and like ssa oh ssa oh a times five okay i can't even tell when that's on like when when you go
from like uh anteroscopic filtering times 16 so like times eight i can't even see i can't tell
the difference like ssa oh a o times 10 i don't even i can't tell the difference between that
and like a low quality i can't i can't i'm just i'm being honest it's not real cut his mic no my
point is is that you don't need to 2080 but play like counter strike and that's what all you play
why does everybody act like they need that card so bad you know what i mean like no i'm in i gotta
get a 2090 for um minecraft yeah okay they you don't need a 2090 to play like fucking stardew
valley there's rtx in minecraft yeah am i just i'm just going against am i just like one of those
contrarian dicks that just goes against things that are like well then it's like it's like popular
my my contrarian dickhead you don't get the 2090 rtx stupid get a 1080 it works just fine i'm a
contrarian dickhead like am i no you're just a regular dickhead dude you're so faced that's
literally the oh by the way we haven't even talked about what was on screen this is like frog me this
is i love this this is like making me happy and i'm doing that like i no no no not like
not the one where like i'm holding up like a figurine on reddit i'm talking about like the like
that is what that is how do i do that without making that what that ever that that joke that
everybody likes to make no hold on no fuck that ever that's everything guys no one can ever open
their mouth excitedly in a photo ever again you understand it's been destroyed like you you've
you got like anytime somebody is excited don't ever be excited in a photo ever if you're like
with a bunch of friends and it's like or you wow i can't believe it my friends three of you guys
like made it out to vegas and we're like oh my god we're we're out at like one of the casinos
get a photo no don't then people on the internet won't call me a bunch of fucking names like no
what am i supposed to do i'm gonna be like if i'm with like four friends and we're out
fucking somebody just hit a hundred dollars on the slot machine of course i'm gonna make that face
you can never be excited in a fucking photo ever again anyways i love this job okay the
funniest part about this one is how i had to go back i had to demagnify like four times and the
chin was still there this chin is so big that could be that could be my neck like i could be like
like smiling with my neck back but it's not it's just huge keep going keep going keep going
oh my god huge bits more huge amounts of money oh my god another hundred fucking dollars another
10 000 bits from copper coyote this time add it to the gigantic vault that sits behind me apparently
thanks 100 bucks they say jeremy thanks for being in my life all these years i've probably watched
and hundreds of hours of your content at this point that never fails to make me feel better
please take the time to get better your health comes first i look forward to when you create
after you feel better no matter how long it takes thank you i plan on getting back to 100
how well however that well long that takes from this point now until it's done because long term
i've been here a long time i've been around i've been on the internet i've been a uh it's still
hard for me to even say the words i sit here i have eclan right eclan i've been in eclan for
10 years and i'd like to do it for a lot longer i'd like to continue and i don't want to have this
fester to a point where it's like it starts to fuck up the stream starts to fuck up my everyday
life um and actually i think this is this this will be probably the first time that i've in my
own control like in my own my own reasons i've decided to like take a leave i don't think in
10 years i've ever like said i'm not going to be around for like three weeks i don't think it's
happened sure there's been stuff where it had where i've had out of my control like internet
problems when i first moved to vegas that was like a two or three week period i don't think i've
stopped on my own um maybe one time when i was trying like transitioning from twitch or youtube
to twitch but i have to do it and if this is the only time i have to do it this is the only time
i'm gonna do it the health problems are out of your control yeah but they are though they are
kind of because i can go take care of this shit like i can go do this i can go get this shit set
up and i can go get this taken care of and i haven't really been active on it i've sure oh
you went what about the colonoscopy and the and the upper endoscopy you had yeah but they would
that shit was like six months apart from each other like i could have just been like go go go
and had those tried to line those up in a in a month period you got a one man spam where
fucking go go go go go colonoscopy speedrun but this is great thank you wonderful i love it oh
look at that oh man ice man guts man cut man elect man and fireman i would play this game
i really would imagine megaman but it was like this look at this dude someone make this
well that's that's a quite a task it's just megaman but megaman frustrates me because
megaman is one of the only games that is just trial and error that i don't i
that's not true a lot of games trial i don't like to trial and error i don't like to go to ice man's
level and be like oh can i shoot him with my regular buster nope i need to go to fire level
first i've you got to play pokemon and then you have to figure out who the one guy is that can
take damage in the first level from your regular blaster just suck pokemon's fun no i'm saying like
fire versus ice ice versus earth earth versus wind wind defeats bomb right like ice defeats fire
fire defeats earth earth defeats cut cut defeats electrical because it cut the
fucking electricity wire and then wire and then electricity goes into the um blows out the candles
and blows out the bomb thanks for the art you all right no oh here's some donkey donuts because
you're rapid cut the fuse to the bomb oh you're right do the voice i can't i feel like we've
heard the same song for 30 minutes i'm gonna skip ahead here here's some burger because you're epic
this is people still love this huh yeah it activates by rib cage i can't isn't that's the
star emote that's the star burg right am i mistaken here evil i told you i don't like drinking on
camera i act like a weirdo i and i pretend to drink i do like oh i'm acting i'm like pretending
just drink i don't know why it's only when the camera's on you're a fucking alien talk show
yeah that was cool like yeah filming's going great hey what hey what what do you put in here
anyways hey what's it what do you put in this what is this anyways they always ask that why
yeah wow what do you put in this conan there ain't nothing in those cups 4 20 69 nice
speaking i gotta shave speaking of shaving i forgot that i actually did that that was dumb
that was a lot how many was that a thousand times i went a thousand times
something like that why is this a ha ha it was 550 what do you mean ha ha i don't have much to say
absolutely destroyed on red wine look at that hair kylo ren i actually was trying not to laugh
because there's a there's a couple of kylo ren's in this that are very very funny they're very
fun they're hard for me to not eat and then go cheat on my comedy diet this is great though this
is fucking hilarious okay for a second i was just like this is bad this is like naked person or
something but no this is a uh i saw this down here and i was just like this is i gotta click off this
because my face cam i was looking over here originally and my face cam was blocking it and
i'm like okay this is a bad thing guys this is murius murius what murius you know what to do
i'm gonna throw the rocket people i forgot i that was that was so much fun i love that game
he didn't mean to like throw rocks at people he was just acting out we just it's what a great
game you hate me good old murius oh this is cool somebody made this out of clay everybody actually
made a clay fireman bob for sale oh no i was like bob for scale i was like wait you're selling bob
that's really good actually scale buy buy buy buy but you know the line you know the line
when i get back one zero zero you know it see merch do more merch i know i know i know i know i just
don't i know i know i'm gonna i love this this is my i i know this is like jojo's bizarre adventure
and like oh no you as a case of jojo reference but it's me as the redler so it gets an automatic
plus one i really feel like i could be the if they if they ever cast the redler in an upcoming movie
talking to you i'm talking to you jr or tolkien if you ever cast anybody in as the redler i'm
ready i'm ready for my performance i'll be ready he's dead the wings spoiler right down my hair
black no it would look weird god no you emo hair would it be emo hair shave i will just
give me give me a little bit it would be spider-man 3 i mean if i if the if i had the venom suit i
wouldn't get rid of it let's just put it that way evil no i would be able to control it i would
control that beast i would control it and you're telling me you got i get extra superpowers
i would control that kidding me you don't well you don't well you guys don't think that like that
the venom symbiote would like attach in here and get up there and like when we're sleeping have
the donald trump the baby dream and not be like okay i gotta fucking listen to what this guy says
this guy's fucking weird and crazy and i i gotta listen to this dude now like oh yeah the the the
the dream of like when i dropped two ice creams on the ground and ate them both off the ground
like holy shit okay uh what do you want to do we're gonna be good we're gonna be good guys
and if you do anything bad then you're gonna be in trouble but i still do what i want and what i
think is right we're gonna be good about it every single person that's ever wanted to be a villain
or has talked about how they they see themselves as a villain speaks like this
we we're good though but we're bad at the same time that's a good redler and how they
play a different song was that a good redler like this whole riddler smart thing if you leave
loose with the police you're a fucking idiot what i was oh he's a million iq huh this is fucking
scary he's that's but no but i'm a good guy though forget forget that this comic book's not a good
representation of me all right more what what are you guys doing why are we getting more links
i fucking see i've seen this already uh very inaccurate because i'm scared of this
i'm scared i'm scared to do this i'll never have a tattoo i'll never have a piercing because i'm
scared of what happens here do it on stream why would i get my ears pierced on stream
wrong link what oh is this doom no it's not doom why would you think this was due don't ever be
excited again don't don't ever have any excited face somebody on the internet will draw stitches
all down your neck give you weird glasses what do i look like here this mouth in particular
this is gonna take a minute that this is a person that mouth and this like the nose
it's like a it's like a celebrity or something who is this drumpf i why did you just write
drumpf why did you just write that all right this is all right this is okay thank you for your uh
but this is community content night not whole links out of chat this is community it's community
content you're right you're right but let me go back to what i was doing please lost my place
again i don't want to give spoilers like why do you turn up i don't want you to see what's next
okay here we are all right let's go i just don't want to see what's next and it'll be a spoil
that's good that's a real picture of bugleberry quick turn it off you're losing viewers that's so
i love this i need to i wanted to have him here more way more uh tiny man's pro streamer four we
you got the the short thing in there right off the bat very very quickly the first thing this
is also i mean this works because this is the that's a look at me so this makes perfect sense
you hide anything else here ernie fireman giant rat chicken derma cheetos beer coffee chat oh
yeah okay this is all this and then chad muska he's still in the game i think actually what
happened is when they were editing this they got to this point where they did all these characters
and then they just were like damn done yeah whatever i don't i don't i'm not gonna like
mask and type another thing in here i don't care it could be chad muska that's fine
you know the best thing about art is people make you look way more handsome than you are in real
life that's the best part you know what i mean i look at this i'm like holy shit look at that guy
and it's like wow i could that's me yeah hey that's me you look like a disney villain
but i'm good i'm a good guy and i do but i might have some tendencies to do maybe my own stuff what
i want to do but i have good at heart that's what you meant to say what the fuck nice eyebrows
what's wrong with my eyebrows pores where you can't see pores on the space it's flawless
if you would if there were pores on this face that would mean that it wasn't a perfect fucking
complexion of the utmost of absolute handsome human male that one was free different germa
hairstyles we got a young germa style with like a big fucking neck i like the big neck wish i had
the big neck back i'll get it back sewer goblin style okay so that was a few weeks old haircut
style and life is pain style which one are we at now this one sewer goblin was like a few weeks
ago this is not so it's not going that's not long enough a few weeks ago yes made by germa nine eight
five i didn't do this i didn't i didn't make this also tell this person that they should feel bad
about emotes they're emoting the germa discord once he's there wow don't do that don't put
sneaky little instructions at the bottom for people don't like do sneaky little instructions
that's a pretty great animal crossing rug i'm sure it is or it will be in about 30 40 seconds
quick somebody get the qr code i think there actually is a few qr codes in the stream this
is great though all the different stages of fireman's emotions you got happy a little derpy
derpy derpy sad derpy is that a wait is it wait can you say derpy is that like a
is that a band thing now too but don't ever show any excitement in any photos and don't use words
like derpy because that's no no no no we don't use that don't use those true okay just you're
gonna be banned for two to three weeks why would i get banned i know i'm not gonna be around for a
little while but that doesn't mean that like hey guys i'm not gonna be around for a little while
um well since i'm not gonna be around i might as well uh just like sure you just can't be naked
like why would i i was gonna say something else but i probably can't say what a loaf of bread i
was gonna say loaf of bread yeah can you come to the can you figure out what he was actually saying
i have a rat shaped sword oh i was gonna say asshole oh i just said it there's a lot of people
here i can't like protect okay there's like 8500 people here it's not like i'm in a room with like
two of my friends and a fucking cat you know what i mean like i i got i got a cup of shit
no it's just me this is i love the championship belt and the pikachu socks that's a nice touch
nudes i don't even know why this is here i told you guys that i'm gonna start this they're gonna
be a criteria now for like i gotta i gotta like it make a good flow with the artwork and the videos
and i start to like kind of condense down maybe uh it i and sometimes some stuff just happens
you look like bogdanoff i think that's probably the intention that's your real face uh excuse me
me okay this is funny like this is the thumbnail oh yeah this is a thumbnail
those things don't even look real is anybody else convinced that those aren't real
there's a little row there's a little like micro machines those don't even look like real animals
don't they look like they're like they were made in like a bionicle kit or whatever those those
things were they don't this is not real have you seen these i don't think it's weird like
they have the eyes i hate these things i don't like i don't like looking at that
they're like robots prove that they're real i can't how am i supposed to do that 5g bits
all right this is freaking me out i gotta get this off i don't know i'm not sure i'm not sure
which one of these is like potentially a more scary image you know i went to an experiment
the experiment's going to be this is very high quality work by the way the experiments gonna
be we're going to go very fast at the end of the artwork we're going to go very fast through each
one of these pieces and how many of them am i in in a good mood or happy how many can we find that
are not this guy's scary and he's going to strangle you or this guy is about to throw a punch in your
face or mid-punch are there any like this guy is not out of his mind photos i know this has been
like four this is very high quality though this is great big bits oh fuck you're right oh there
is big bits hold on snoozing cop to get fifty dollars the music's off why does this keep
happening all right new ost first thing that i see is going on first thing that i right in the elbow
right in like that spot that makes your whole body tingle right in that like wedge right here
right in the fucking wedge where it's like it was like right in the fucking corner
okay uh okay first thing i see terraria okay terraria soundtrack terraria ost hey there it is
i i can't wait for the for the
this is not the song that i wanted to hear this is not the song i wanted
you're skipping skipping skip there go back go back go back all right all right all right
snoozing copter 50 fucking dollars i guess i'm swearing to it no more squares
your mouth here are some pity bits no but for real i want you to play this soundtrack i think
you'll like it let's see this is an ost this is alter ego nes music all right we'll queue it up
oh yeah this is the one that i wanted this reminds me about you like the little guys
working on a construction site like little trucks going like like you know those little guys little
mustaches and the fraggles tv show they were like moving and working and they were building like
stuff out of these weird crystal sugar structures that's what i think these guys work too those
guys well yeah the dozers the dozers the dozers yes they those structures were like made it at
such weird material the dozers all right anyways hold on wait a lot of money uh yes i know i spent
70 dollars just so you could play this on stream but i made a lot of money with my art commissions
this past month and i'm really happy about it my girlfriend got me kofi gold which was such a
generous gift and it has been really paying off so i'm just gonna use this as a shameless plug
so i get back the cash i just lost don't make me laugh red gold well thank you snoozing that's a
ton of fucking money and we will play alter ego nes music after this hey javelin thanks for the
50 dollars another 50 dollar drop just a bit you've been on another 5 000 bits just another 50
dollars just coming down uh from javelin thank you javelin they say jerma been watching you
since about 2012 long time it's not an understatement when i say that you've
quite literally shaped my sense of humor for the rest of my life thank you so much brother
you do can't wait to see you back at 100 but what my recommissions stop all right i know
what i have i can go off camera and drink and you don't even i can't i don't have to pretend
uh but seriously that's a long time to be watching anybody i'll be back i'll be back at a fucking
hundred i ain't coming back at 90 i'll be back at 100 100 anything less is is unacceptable thank
you this has just been on screen the whole time okay we gotta get this off before my brother shows
up okay i thought he was naked but it's okay uh this is i got like a hit on the am i like
unconscious am i like begging him the head go beyond oh it's the planets it's the planets
right right right right right for a second i thought like he like came behind me and like
bonked me in the head i see okay andrew jack every jack plus ultra i can't this i can't i
can't do that i got we had 100 nothing more nothing less only 100 i love this though this is good
the two rats how do they stay on your shoulder man how do you have they stay there
he said it one of us what do you mean one of us because i said plus ultra he said it again i
mean i know what it is because when you're so strong and you go over the current power level
threshold and then you can punch a guy real far that's all it does doesn't do anything else you
can't go plus ultra to like cook bacon and shit like that doesn't help it's only to punch somebody
very very far that's it you want to rake your leaves at plus ultra that's and it's not going
to utilize that very well can't drive a car plus ultra that would be dangerous can't do anything
plus ultra besides punch somebody hard in the stomach until they fly not that useful i'll take
a brain over that i'll take high iq over that one you know the riddler some things are just
accurate and can't be rebuttled or said otherwise except for this part up here that part's inaccurate
that's not right here comes a boss fight in terraria why do i have triangle hair
uh i think you should have asked why do i have a triangle face what do i mean like that i think
that's a better question are those tanning goggles it's just me in a tanning booth what is it
deus x oh deus x i never played it i never play i know people are gonna freak the fuck out
somebody just puked up their captain crunch when i just said that and like it went up your nose
and like into your sinuses and it's on fire right now and it's like holy shit that hurts so much
oh and like a little bit milk starts to drizzle down you're like oh my god and then you think
that you could like go into like putting more water in will help it makes it worse
you just have to take just a pain like a solid two minutes and then you're fine that's too
specific what are you talking about you guys have had milk go up your nose that's in every
like 90s movie like the milk coming out somebody's nose that's in every cartoon tv show media from
1991 to like 2004 you don't understand that reference too old i'm not even too old i'm not
too old you're too young don't get me screaming doctor's orders uh this is called the egg
why would you have this why would you do this why would you be the egg all these pins
this this is just you you went to a convention and this is the only booth you got pins from
like you didn't want to wait in line anywhere else this is that's all you were willing to stand for
it's like fuck man the oh and the nintendo line looks way too you know i'll take a few more of
those pins thank you the hat too is perfect i'll keep an eye on this and get it for yourself one
day sour please sour please sour please sour please sour please sour please purple purple
purple all i see is purple purple purple purple purple purple letters and numbers purple purple
purple letters and numbers purple letters and numbers purple purple letters and numbers purple
it's the dance it's the break dancing okay well i have to enable this um i can't do it right now
though i'll i'll enable i because i can't do it right now i'll i will turn this on very very
very quickly i will turn this on very quickly in fact yeah okay i'll turn this on very quickly
remember that now now now i can't do it now i can't i'm not i like i'm delogged out i can't
i can't do it right now i lost my place again all right here we go we are at the halfway mark
for art getting there this is i'm sorry mama mama i'm sorry did i do this what did i do oh
it's cooking mama cooking mama right with the hand okay now i remember it's making the the dough
balls well why would you let me keep doing it you were smashing her hand i didn't mean to though
oh here's some donkey donuts uh because you're epic people love this people can't get enough of
this shit people can't get enough of this like guy handing you an item and pointing at you and
talking to you and telling you to drink this coffee or this eat this food or drink this
beverages like everybody loves this shit this is dunkin donuts ad i like dunkin donuts i drank
dunkin donuts for fucking like 30 years he hates it now no i like dunkin donuts isn't it what's
wrong with dunkin donuts i don't like donuts i don't like dunkin donuts yeah i can buy like
four coffees for the price of one from literally everywhere else i don't like it
i got news for you they all use the same damn beans wait do you think they have special
fucking beans everywhere are you crazy no they all buy they're all like just like the
they all buy they don't know i'm gonna don't just beans are everybody else's beans they all get it
from the same fucking distributor and then they just grind it up and they add a little bit of
another powder into them some of them and like oh yeah we have a blend oh what's that let me just
like oh what's that what we got here onion powder i put it in there that's a nice fucking coffee
blend it's all the same shit i know someone's gonna clip this and they're gonna make a whole
video showing like where all these different companies get their beans from and it's gonna
be completely inaccurate and everything i'm saying is a fucking absolute farce it's not even real at
all and then i'm gonna have to make it an embarrassing follow-up to this where i go
yeah well fucking whatever i'm i'm whatever like i like donka donuts don't care and we'll shut up
and then i'm gonna move on and we'll never talk about it again and i was wrong and you proved me
wrong and um i just move on why do i feel like this i feel like this on a daily basis sometime
it's like yeah happy fucking birthday it comes with bean apology stream imagine making like an
apology video about you said that the coffee companies use the same beans everywhere
i feel like that's the thing that like a lawyer tells you to do what do you mean
dude coffee company and co was not happy about what you did go on tv and say that you were wrong
and that all beans are fucking different okay fine i don't want to go do it but you're gonna
have to find a new lawyer do you want to lose six hundred thousand dollars you fucking idiot
it's jerry seinfeld okay i have to admit i i have to admit i thought this was a big building
not a guy i thought this was a huge minecraft structure but it's a minecraft it's a guy it's
a skin but really gave it away was the big hat up here that i was like why is there a hat on that
building this is cool though it's wait it's both is it both look at the tiny guy uh yeah but this
is just like a zoomed in camera right left is the skin right is the replica this is not somebody
standing really close to the camera it is a building okay oh yeah it looks cool it is idiot
it's a skin that's what i've said you guys are just filling me with hot air right now that's the
first thing that i said handsome streamer huh change of music oh shit all right here comes
alter ego for the regular nintendo this is good this is really good okay um oh that book that they
made a movie on recently it was a horror movie and it was uh uh scary stories to tell in the dark
yeah but the uh the scary stories to tell in the dark right not lord of the rings not goosebumps
no no they uh yeah this this is this reminds me of the images that were in that book like these
this is like the the the killers and shit and like the scary people that were in that book
i feel like this is page like 16 or something this one especially do i actually make these faces
look at this one up here tell me this is not just don't belong in scary stories telling dark
am i am i a scary guy i'm not scary right no no right because there's like a you know
are you perceived online as being a scary person or like ah he's just he's just it's just he's a
comedian right right whoa that one loaded you're the friendly troll that's great it'd be nice to
have a shirt like that i'm going as fast as i can my fireman was introduced into the community
like three years ago yeah i'm going fast going as fast as i can it takes time to set up merchandise
like a couple weeks it's been three years i fucking takes time let me give that give me
a hundred percent i'll be back hurry the fuck up you're gonna pay the dude that made it
yes absolutely if there's a t-shirt with fireman i'm not gonna hey hey you know that thing that
you like made for the community yeah i'll take well i'm gonna take that and you know well
i'm gonna use that and it's gonna mine now thanks oh wait here's a few dollars
oh i already talked to him about it this is mine now that's the worst face 2020 oh yeah
you sure how about now mistake all of those you're gonna regret that
i can't do better than that not at not at 65 percent why is my face always in shadow
because i have recessed lighting and it hits me right here i've got a big ass brow bone
that shadows my face that gives me batman eyes i can't help that that's how god created me
you're really fucked up this is one i like the shading of the beard
get lights in front of you i hate that no no i don't want to sit here at my computer
and have like two studio lights blasting in my fucking face no i don't want not doing that i'm
not doing it i like if i go into this if i'm doing a production or if i'm gonna be in the studio sure
but i'm just comfortable in my own underwear i don't want fucking
like paparazzi lights fair fish shooting in my eyes while i'm sitting here playing
fucking cow games on pc no i'm comfortable in my own underwear i'm not doing that
and i know the old derby they make like the soft lights no it'll i'll look at it and then it's
it'll burn me it's all i'll see how about this when i upgrade to it and a gtx 2090 i'll get a light
that's never going to happen 1080 for life oh shit this is the garfield not this is cat from
this is computer cat this is computer cat with two um lighters you guys think it's funny that i get
so concerned about like copyright from like a cartoon character but yet i will show on this
stream full clips of star wars with me edited into them oh hey in about 25 minutes we're going
to show like a full five minutes of a star wars movie but uh no that's not that's not garfield
that's a computer cat what the fuck am i talking about computer cat for the win this is actually
i like it it's very good i love the i especially love the obi-wan kanobi lightsaber and the luke
skywalker lightsaber sorry scratch that er you're wrong that's uh flygon jin's lightsaber and obi
wan kanobis i know my lore what a redditor oh this all right okay i had trouble deciphering
if that was an image an actual real image or not it might be it's my mouth we have very similar
mouths and very similar noses he's got like he's got like a full foot on me bastard damn it was
he like six five damn it don't let it get to you what is it with the mega milk i don't i don't
even i don't even know what this is and it keeps popping up he's five five i'm five eight fix that
uh there's like over there's 83 fucking hundred people here right now i'm gonna stop swearing
there's 8300 people right now you're not gonna get don't get lied to are you a new viewer have
you just come from r slash all because that's uh now we've got new people from all from all
hey what's up uh that's don't listen to them i don't he's so cringy if somebody was cringy
would they fucking be able to look like this did you be able to nod to music like this if you were
like oh how cringy that dude is no oh yeah dude yeah talking to you hey it's glue man wow you go
big guy shit that's every scene the joker does in suicide squad god damn it i'm it's processing
well i going off the grid bye crap he p p p p p t t ah re p p p p p r k
germa is if the joker was the riddler that probably happened and in some of those universes
joker probably ate the riddler and like absorbs his brain or something i'm sure it has they've
had to there's been a lot of jokers rotoscoped germa yes i just spoken third person don't leave
please germa worst face am i am i gonna regret opening this am i gonna regret doing this
but this is edited you edited this this has been edited and listen was there glass here that i
pushed up against that i didn't see it lost my place it lost my place oh shit we're getting
there we're like at the last third here uh this just took me off i just got caught off guard on
this one boilers what wait is he naked it's not edited this is real i this is not edited
this one's not i feel like it is i feel like it is here and here somebody says a cat sneeze
no no no no no no this is this is at gym class soccer ball was just kicked into my face and
somebody took a picture right when it hit like this the frame after it bounced off my face
just like a boom boom and somebody snapped it right there it came in from this direction it
right here oh by the way right there black and white one of the greatest pc games of all time
some small movie details for you how many more of these dickas have what the fuck is this one
i don't even i don't coffee and co why am i homer simpson okay making me lose my place again
oh okay here we are and all the chat members ready to come after me
he didn't look at the pipes already forgot his own joke what was with the pipe it was the same
bean oh right right something about every company has beans it was the same beans
right something about that something like that i i know look i told you the reason why i can't
talk about this because i don't want to i can't say i can't i can't say this out loud i gotta be
careful there's 8 000 fucking people here what if you work at coffee and company and you hear this
no i can't i cannot mess up my image oh look it's a rat and that's me what image good one hopefully
still scary even in tiny print even in like small doodle and i still have a scary face
uh this is great beautiful oh look at that i think this is a emboss play
in creation magnet i think this is a magnet this is a really good magnet because no this is nice
yeah okay next uh ost we don't have we only have time for probably one more ost before we go to the
videos it's a cookie oh shit no that's not a cookie ftl you promised all right fine that's a really
good soundtrack alter ego for the nes all right here's ftl pretty good okay what's the next one
all right moving on dome dumb eternal supposed to be dumb eternal or is it dome dome dome
uh-huh funny you're banned idiot look i should bury it why am i circling everything like oh that
over here that over here who did i ban oh your mom right mom wait is this in reference to
at one time like a month or so ago when i was in the chat pretending to be you guys like parents
for like 40 minutes there was something and i yeah there was something weird right before the stream
turned on i was sitting for like a half more than a half an hour it's like acting out scenario where
i like called you guys on the phone and you guys are watching the house for the first time
because you were like a teenager i don't know something like that uh this must be me
this looks like it could be playing somewhere in time square this is one of those weird new age
cool ads or something that's playing like on one of the screens in time square it's a coke ad
take me on i'll be i don't even know the words but i just know how it sounds
something like that right the first part was pretty good that was flat was it that wasn't
in a day or two two that one is i needed one of those ding ding ding ding ding ding ding no
oh wait the echo is on whoops my speakers what happened to them wasn't that loud
i look at this dude real quick it hurts does it it hurts shit i'm sorry i didn't mean to
did you look at them hope you did uh is that one of those porn links every time i see a
series of numbers and letters it freaks me out because i think it's a porn link oh that's jex
porn code remember there was a porn code like fiasco of like 2018 whatever the hell it was
or is it well is this a wait is that a wait is this a friend code oh dude oh i don't know
if that would i don't know this was a good idea you're gonna have to make like i know
it's for the shirt okay good because like if you just put this is if that was your friend code
you you're gonna have to like buy a new switch you're gonna have to either they have like a new
nintendo account it's the code for the shirt oh and it's fucking stop swearing you're not even
cool what do you think you cool did uh i like the design of the jack shirt you're lame shut up stop
i'm trying it's i'm trying you said you're gonna stop swearing like three years ago it's a it's a
long process i'm working on it it's you know i'll figure it out sooner off that zip where
do you see a zit on this face excuse me i want to just like i want to ban that person and then i
want to take over the whole screen where is it where is it i got a wicked red face but that's
all there is to it forehead that's not as it that's that's a that's a mole guys i got i got hit in the
face six years ago seven years ago i have a permanent like you have a permanent mark right
there i got it in this face hey hey you should have seen the other guy right am i cool yet do
you like me there it is this is for germa fireman let me get it real close so you can get a good
scan on it qr codes are seriously some kind of alien technology how can like a psychology ink
blog transfer data it's it's crazy to me it's so bizarre it's so cool you're so old no but that's
you don't think that that's so interesting a series of little blots on a piece of white paper
can download fireman to your telephone like do you switch it's just like oh yeah i i hold your
phone up now i know what that is that's fireman oh how is this fireman this looks like somebody
just peeled out and fucking the wall bar parking lot just that that this is like tire marks it's
insane it's impossible coding it's crazy barcodes it's i know it doesn't make any sense
3d weeder he's pretending no that's cool barcodes and qr codes and skin like how does one qr code
device differentiate between another qr code device like it's linked together it's all connected
okay uh yeah if you don't you didn't watch um this is weed brain no this is called i'm
interested in how communication works through programming means god damn it i i picked up all
my weeds and i loved weeding joe rogan ran that's please go back to as assassins freed someday
i'm one of those losers now when i see ac i say i think of assassins creed not animal crossing
and i just proved it that was a slip that means that i think that's too bad because i don't think
that's a better game all right go is that big enough is this tv static big enough this is
jupiter no okay all right i'll go through them all this is top left it's top right wait here's
your bottom left here's your bottom right very cool thanks for those animal crossing uh player
data skins there's more there is this one this is the screaming and then gym one and this is
guy in the funny machine i mean farting i said it fine i want to say fart i hate that word the
word sucks art is such a shitty word it's just like suck it's i hate saying it fart i go fart fart
i hate that word it's like a shitty sucky word to say all right we good so thanks for these
how do you even do this and why do you have this why is this here is my first question
and my second question is it should be on the damn wall not on the ground outside
why is it out here what am i a welcome mat oh i'm a picture that you hang in the study
for everybody to come in and see i don't i don't know what this is this is auto it's auto
is this an animal crossing this is an animal there's a character in animal crossing that's
a dachshund what do they make this from scratch go back now it's made from scratch this is really
cute go back i'm not going back it's based off of a model oh that's cool no rewinds fine there five
seconds three two coming on one guy but with legs two seconds he lied
everybody gets to be the one guy at some point with legs good shit
why why am i that's freaking me out welcome to salt crest island look at this dude
good island if i opened up salt crest probably get yelled at by uh by somebody it's probably
overrun with bugs and weeds and it's probably some not gonna be good i know i i let it kim and
i were playing it for a while while we were moving my town went to shit this is really high quality
really good stuff that's gonna win probably you know but that that was not even a bad this is not
this is not a worst face this i would say this is a slightly creepy face but not the worst face
okay but when you when you hear the word worst this doesn't come to mind just because i'm holding
this up in front of my face why so serious that's not what this says that's his worst face okay that's
not the joker card with a bite taken out of it like in the new in the movies now it's that's a
that's a category for a show that i did oh look at this that's that you don't want to talk about
detail let's talk detail uh this he auto actually has this it's his winter coat that's some detail
work there he goes outside when it's too cold out and he puts on his little jacket and
because he gets cold he's a little dog fireman also this is cool fireman has the watering can
that's just detailed right there and then uh guy going to a football game okay well if you
painted this all over you and you went to like an nfl game like who are you rooting for nobody
me i'm number one i'm rooting for the clowns i wish i need 100 billion dollars but not even
it wouldn't even take that much i want to do like a it's like a sports thing where it's like the
clowns like versus the dinosaurs you know what i mean it's like a baseball game and it's and it's
just it's just a baseball game and they just play baseball like the clowns like take like rabbits
out of hats and shouldn't like like before pitches and the dinosaurs like roar and hit home runs
it's but it's just a regular game of baseball there's nothing there that's wow that's really
interesting no they just play baseball i'd like want to watch it one day yeah like yeah it would
be like like the the cincinnati clowns versus like the delaware dinosaurs people in costumes and
it sounds like fun we got more like he's not already a millionaire okay let me just let me
ask you this how much do you think it costs to rent out a major league baseball stadium
for a day how much do you think that is how much do you think that costs that's a whole net worth
of gone in two minutes it's like 100k it's probably like a million it's probably like 50 to 100k
minor league maybe 20 30k maybe but then you can hire nine clowns and nine dinosaurs
and they have to be competent in baseball i have to hire players to play well i can't just what
am i not gonna hire like 30 people to play and the clowns have to have like powers you know
if you guys have like special powers i want essentially i want to make mario baseball a
reality where like the clown like winds up and like two other clowns run behind him and they
both throw like goofy comedy balls but the one real ball comes out of the middle that's his power
i'm it'll happen wait till i'm at 100 lazy purple came in with a raid welcome everybody from lazy
purple's channel i'm germa985 you might know but you might not what's up thanks for coming
thanks for stopping by have a great day one of these days i'm just gonna have a sock puppet
just gonna be me i'm gonna be pretending to play a game they all left whatever they'll be back
when i'm at 100 how many times am i gonna do that tonight we'll see uh frozen that's your
favorite movie alienware don't buy one of those you don't need one don't need a gtx 2090 uh toothbrush
got all the dna i love it okay this was interesting this this is this big enough
this is artwork of a bunch of people from the discord all the people's discord avatars
so this is this is wild it's it's regulars in the discord from my understanding based on the
profile pictures so this is cool as shit this is awesome i love how i get a ton of space i get so
much space no no no you all have to share that corner i want at least the full quadrant in the
middle scott hall is here nice i just screamed i know but like that's so cool scott hall's at my
birthday scott hall is that adam sailor why is this your birthday i it could be easter birthday
what easter and the next one that one make sure you see who fucking made this the next one is
everybody's names this is everybody 60 people from the discord the artist nice work this is
awesome i want to see if i recognize any of these avatars i mean i recognize scott hall
that's so i love that what if it's just what if like this that's not even a person's avatar
they just scott hall's just here it makes me happy nice work this is a lot of detail
scott hall is in the discord i was trying to figure out what this was and it's just a note
like them up not put a notch on on the chalkboard for scary image of jeremy's face he's a terrifying
serial killer and he's going to kill you like he did this he's coming like the newspaper article
about like this is the guy's face that we saw and he's on the loose he sees in a he's a murderer
apparently true what true true true oh yeah yep yep yeah sounds about right oh look it's auto
on his favorite pillow that's exactly what he does he just barely fits on it and he sleeps
he loves where lord this i love this am i doing the music before the video section there actually
is only one song and it's only 13 seconds from uh that 30 day period going into uh april very good
oh hey more codes fireman creator wait what's that one orbit short sleeve t i love i i love these
it's starting to get really hot out here in vegas i'm so happy that i'm gonna be able to put on one
of those just tanks i love tanks like my favorite thing in the world so easy it's so simple i love
just tank top and shorts and flip flops if i could wear it every day i would and the best part
that's one of the reasons moving out here to vegas six to seven months of the year it's like 80 to
115 degrees i just can just wear the flip flops and the tank top and the shorts every day every
day and it's makes me so happy i don't do anything it's just like oh it's just like it's like putting
like a tablecloth on you it's just like oh that's it's on i guess i guess let's go i'm time to go
out that's a boomer no it's not no it's not excuse me please that's not a boomer thing
that's a i like to relax thing no a tank top tank top and like a nice pair of shorts
whatever it's comfortable since when did comfort become wow that's stupid don't do that
i do that all the time this is great that's pretty good it is pretty good yeah i'm
i'm fucked up in this one the hair is accurate too that's the best part not anymore though
aren't you cut what's going on in the corner down here all right i feel i thought this one was just
moving it is moving is it moving the worst picture on the internet i appreciate how much detail and
how much time went into this but it's the worst picture on the internet the thing that it is
the source the source is the worst picture on the internet not the depiction
excuse me he hates it no i hate that picture i hate i hate this photo not the the painting
depicting the photo the photo the photo of me that this is based on very well made though
everybody loves pac-man my favorite character ever and i've played one game on stream i made a video
about pac-man like seven years ago and i played one of his games oh that's my favorite thing in
the world don't you guys know that wait till we pull we got i gotta play pac-man on stream
for real that point still stands even though it's shito you haven't seen shito in a long time
either have you you know we'll be back thought it was pac-man it's because my brain was only
focusing down here like this was my eye line and i didn't even look up at all about 20 straight
seconds it's on your reddit shell yeah but i mean you haven't heard him sing in a while he's out of
batteries firma 985 rat tail lion ears wolf nose and fluff and then good wait there's like three
different animals rat tail lion ears and wolf nose there's three animals but is that what do
i do you supposed to combine like four animals you're gonna lose viewers now a hybrid animal
um i'm not drawing all the scales they say aquaman shirt evolution there are no rules
i don't know why i'm trying to follow any i'm trying to follow some rules that don't
they that aren't here that aren't real uh this is ai generated faces or something
based on that image but which one looks like we actually could be the most realistic one
from like that thousand years ago uh i got my money's on this one this one looks like it
could be real this just looks like a really bad senior photo like too much soft touching
and by the way i gotta bring this up um it's an extra like 10 to 20 dollars for them to soft
touch your senior picture but it's just a filter that they click one button why i don't understand
i never i never got that near that never made sense to me oh you could get regular senior
photos or you get the scene first with a soft touch it just makes your like face the glow and
they just blur your face a little but i want a photo that looks like me i want to bottom right
no bottom left to top right true neutral chaotic evil right chaotic neutral chaotic good lawful
good lawful neutral lawful evil pretty close neutral good neutral what is down here neutral
neutral neutral oh chaotic wait wait lawful good lawful neutral awful evil neutral good
neutral neutral neutral evil evil neutral that makes sense this whole thing work through neutrals
in the middle we made to the end of the artwork let's put on some videos thank you everybody for
your submissions that takes us up until about uh about at the end of march into the first week
of april it is now time for crack all right make sure i didn't miss any here i could have i might
have have i know these are all just added images okay moving on the first video we can turn the
this off i'm gonna get here first video of the evening is titled zooming into germa's nose
this is nice and loud zooming into germa's nose i can't that was that death stranding
was that death was that the e3 trailer of death stranding from like three and a half years ago
all right come on next this is this streamer is determined
why is this in the beginning why is this in the beginning why did you put that here
there's no reason for this this next one's called germa thinks he's one of those funny tiktoks
i remember this
this is already this is on the list by the way all right i gotta not laugh at these things
germa wins big time circus circuit come on
is that joe joe why are they all doing this wait wait wait this hold on
off to a good start i would say to a very good start this one says warning cursed shit ahead
all right i'm about this better not be a blaster if this is a blaster i'm turning it off immediately
all right this is there at least you gave a warning okay this is a blast if this is this might be a
blaster and a flasher yes be aware it might be loud it's a warrant you don't put a warning here
unless this is fucked up here we go warning i've never seen this video before in my life and i know
it's a meme i just don't know what it means slaps get it out turn it off i can't how am i supposed
to turn this off now but it's not though grab rave jeremiah harold elbertson grab rave
okay i mean i don't i it's a meme i know but i don't know for what we want a uh you want a link
yes here it is it please enable germa please please enable germa please don't i don't worry
i will the y30 way or sooner than that uh this one's cool portal gameplay let's have a look how
do you like uh wait hold on i'm seriously going to sit down on the toilet and piss up into my face
okay um how did you how did you do that how did you do that is that that's not like a cameo thing
right like a fiber thing anyways the next one's called psychotic streamer this one watch
not a big deal you're not gonna stop laughing there's so much more oh okay listen this is batman
uh spoilers for the batman movie they came out 10 years ago who cares batman spoilers
batman is in this movie and so is the joker and this is a batman the dark knight spoiler
here we go close now
not a big deal
i've been exhaling really good i've been exhaling very good
i have to see the part where he says he didn't do any damage to me
cigarettes out on my dick wait first of all i have a question why you blur out the joker's face
is that to help with with copyright or something like are you blurring out his like mosaicing his
face is it a bad deep fake it's supposed to be a deep fake oh it's so funny
uh-huh
oh okay i'm gonna relax
okay stop i know i know it's perfect it's perfect i love this video this is like my favorite video
oh jesus so good this germa goes camping in the woods what does this have to do with me camping
freshly brewed and ground from only the finest beans no i can't do that i can't the fresh ground
taste of america's favorite okay okay all right all right all right this is not all right i can't
here's some donkey donuts because you're epic i don't know no no no no that the donkey does
has nothing to do with this i have nothing to do with donkey donuts that was a parody comedy routine
this is definitely a big foot tree structure
oh
i'm not seeing anything all right let me move up get together get together
didn't we see the first wait this is another one did you hear that yeah let me take a look
listen listen listen listen listen what the hell
oh
that was definitely somebody that was an evil laugh just up ahead of us we just heard a laugh
there's no one out here i don't know if there's a big foot up there if it's a person
that ain't right that ain't right we gotta go up there buck i don't see no way out of it man
do these guys just stand there in improv stay ready guys stay tight
we're gonna go super slow here guys all right all right whoa we go whoa whoa what is this
oh no this one's moving they're everywhere what the hell does this mean this is the freakiest
creepiest thing i've ever seen what the hell did we step into when we seen those hanging in those
trees it looked like witchcraft to me and i wished to god i had a bag of salt in my hand to put a
circle around us because i was just that scared you all right was just that circle around us
because i was just that scared it looked like witchcraft to me and i wished to god i had a bag
of salt in my hand to put a circle around us because i was just that scared you all right
hey none of us all right i can't explain what we found tonight we hear something that sounds
like singing then we hear a big foot roar and then we walk up and we find these things
that are up in a tree that i can't even explain other than they look evil
i'm not sticking around to find out who dies i want to watch this show so bad
okay what what network is this on i'm serious i want i actually want to start watching this show
it's in it's interesting it's i mean i want to watch this so bad now i feel like this is gonna
be the most fun show in the world mountain monsters big foot edition on destination america i i i
cannot wait until i find i'm gonna find a way to watch the at least the first five episodes of this
show i can't wait it's on the history channel i can't wait i'll let you know my thoughts
looking forward to it this one's called amazon germo i think we've seen a couple of different
versions of these before it's just the it's the uh you know when it first arrived from amazon
i didn't know what it was yes what is it you'll see alexa what do you do hello everybody my
name is germa i'm going to start doing gameplay commentaries some people might already know me
from playing in servers awesome alexa play rock music alexa stop wait i want to try alexa what
time is it eight a.m eastern time eight a.m you actually don't have to yell at me okay uses
far-field technology so it can hear you from anywhere in the room eight a.m eastern time
from the servers
alexa how tall is mount everest the area above germa because he's so short that i have that
absolutely that's what it is how can i know so much it's so small you little shit i'm not tiny
i'm compact everybody thinks i'm like fucking five feet tall no i was like crouching down i'm
like five eight alexa add wrapping paper to the shopping list i stole that from pokemon i stole
alexa how many teaspoons are in a tablespoon 900 800 and 500 okay that's not a morning person
but echo definitely helps him wake up alexa give me my flash news briefing the local pumpkin
festival is going to be canceled because oh no it's raining outside what did the dog say after
a long day of work what today was rough minus two
alexa tell me another joke pop tarts please give me the pop tarts
seriously like
like why would he laugh please give me the pop tarts
sometimes echo helps out when you least expect it hey dad how do you spell cantaloupe
uh cantaloupe c a n t alexa how do you spell cantaloupe
q i m t u v
loves to play music the compilation of this embarrassing shit that i've said play my dance
mix the giant enemy spider alexa define annoying the indian house of representatives fasted
ville that redefined ass as eaten and with the companion app you can access echo from anywhere
he shines in the sky
that twinkle in my eye he gives me what a perfect guy
no it's not over in time or history once it's done when we're done it's over it's all right it's
over it's over looks like it's over all right it's over all right it's over it's over all right
you don't skip don't skip don't skip i skip i skip i do don't make me mad uh this is called
average germa average germa it's another movie clip there could be a spoiler for a movie
thanks yeah of course get that one
uh oh yeah there are spoilers i wouldn't even pay attention
no uh this is called a a perfectly normal video where nothing weird happens
i bet you something weird happens in this one folks this is just this is the way that i feel
like i look and feel when i have that back brace on oh well that's the default fortnight dance
right i got it so wrong last weekend uh you missed that one try another you miss that one
seriously you miss that one you miss that one you i can't shoot this
i can't fucking shoot these nice shoot okay uh this one is called germ germ and germy 2
it looks like it might be an ed ed netty spoilers for that television show ed ed netty
he's getting away follow me
yep yep yep yep uh-huh uh-huh uh-huh uh-huh uh-huh
coming up next is uh germa's streamer school
um
so what do you guys want to do i can i can barely do anything i i really don't want to lie to you
shut up i was acting i'm not a fucking woody doll you don't pull the back of the string and expect
sorry excuse me uh ma'am and sir i'm a communist and i don't agree with the fact
you have your whole entire fucking Subaru outback full of toilet paper
what the hell this is the thing i'm talking about right here no ifs ands or buts what
Peter i hear you quite the scientist well i'm something of a scientist myself
you well i don't know anything about mad donald that's okay goofy i'll take care of you all right
next one
i'll just start stream on time i want to show you something that i care about
something that i want to show that i haven't been having i had no opportunity to do it till now
that's me there we go and back to the ground who cares about this no don't do it don't do it
you're gonna get me in trouble all right that was uh the screamer school
my favorite part of the whole video is this part right here
the fuck what the fuck what the fuck okay now we have
this is the one that was lined up you saw the image to this one let's watch it it's germa
985 is the senate you've never seen star wars before and um it's star wars it's a star wars
clip it's gonna show star wars shit major star wars entire franchise spoilers okay here they come
i'm i'm trying to protect you in the name of the galactic senate of the republic
you're under arrest chancellor the senate will decide your fate i am the senate not yet
so it's pb8 unit then
so
what's going on is this this guy this was supposed to be
can't i'm sorry i don't know this is supposed to be sad
you're laughing it's the whole rest of the video i think
okay this was more than the whole i hate this video but i like it at the same time
i love this video but i hate it at the same time why that guy what why that person oh my
goodness gracious now up next we have uh this is called local streamer rated by the chat bureau
and investigation link please link please oh oh shit i think i was x out did i x out of that
oh i x out i x out of it i x out of it i x out of it oh that's not good i x out of it
go in your history uh there's like there's like six thousand videos in this history
hold on i got it okay here we go local streamer rated by the chat bureau of investigation
this might be a movie i don't know this is chat
what am i doing
could be me in the background just trying to go to the bathroom eat the shoe where we will shoot
the shoe eating stream had to be postponed i ate the shoe i ate it what's the who is that guy
the last video all right get get this too okay i gotta stop i gotta relax i actually do have
to relax i'm gonna fucking lose my mind why the two died with long endings back to back here
i already forgot the guy's name he was on screen for like 12 seconds and got insta-killed by the
senator what do you what what do you want me to do remember that guy i don't know who that was
i had no idea i didn't read the comic book uh germa pile it's a gundam uh this could be this is
like probably like the episode like 65 of like gundam wing or something just be aware every
single video you're gonna get tv shows and movies and shit are gonna be ruined for you
that's the exclamation that yeah we have to make it's gonna happen
impossible not unless we blast open side seven's hull have we deployed all combat
personnel aye sir we've deployed all units to retrieve the gundam didn't expect an attack from
within side seven oh my god watch out watch out tie fighters tie fighters coming in i'm going down
i'm going down i'm going down
look out chief denim the enemy's mobile suit it started to move and fire back
what but i thought it was all just unassembled parts chief denim doesn't seem to be functioning
very well i'll get it is that optimus prime oh come on come on all right all right you know
no more no all right no more earth bullshit no more earth bullshit no more earth bro we've seen
it no more top 10 saddest anime deaths is that who that is okay no more earth exploding i don't
don't take my shitty creative ability and no that's the word you don't want to end stuff like that
this is germa gets into a car ym germa does the ymca and then gets in a car accident
pretty specific okay it's 100 it's like 105 degrees that's one of these scary things
all right stop it do i turn it off do i do do i turn it off do i skip it veto do i veto this one
right what the fuck is going on did you just did you just take a bunch of like random clips
and just put them in the same video you know typically i i bring you the weather
daily basis at six a.m six a.m in the morning with diane carol and rick but today i want to show you
something different crack video besides the fact that first be aware we are going to have some snow
over here in colorado rockies and we threw him down into the southern part of colorado but
forget that i want to show you something that i care about something that i want to show that
i have no opportunity to do until now that's me on my fishing trip that's me and my son
it's his more his more i just wanted to show and back to the weather you have let me set some cold
from who cares about this america go out and live your lives don't worry about the weather you just
go outside and sniff you'll be just fine it's going to be cold some days it's going to be hot
some days it's just just go out there go out there and live stop diane don't go don't go oh
what the fuck is happening in this video
there's more stuff this is what this is just changing the channel on cable simulator
you know i stopped it okay that was insane that was insane comes a enemy spider video
always have to have at least a few of these because they have no they are
the best giant enemy crack true art link that one you want me to link that one
all right i was doing the thing uh where you're talking but you're doing something else entirely
i'm guilty of doing this on the phone all the time and you're just saying words to make sure
the other person just doesn't think you're insane and losing your mind that you're just silent
so you just say words while you do something else entirely and hope that you're sounding not like a
fucking moron while you talk and then they pick up on it like what what do you what does it have to
do with this and then you desperately desperately try to make the weird thing that like makes no
sense make sense for the current conversation because you know you fucked up and you said
something outrageous that you shouldn't have said anyways mega man see a lot of people didn't know
that there was a boss battle of this the giant enemy spider
there actually is a spider boss mega man spider there it is uh i have to be i have to be honest
with you i've watched this one i watched this one already and i don't understand it the person
that made this video i yeah i know the title person who created this video is probably pretty
upset that they made a karma little down dancing video when i did it last weekend this video was
made probably a month or two ago this video has got flashes in it i didn't even realize that until
right now why am i okay that's the whole video i don't understand it
what i don't get it i was partying too hard is that party too hard and died oh that's what it is
this is called germa step you know what keeps my ego in check
leave me fucking mentally unstable presto fucking majesto
put cigarettes out on my dick hello ladies and gentlemen welcome to episode one of germa crap
getting these games to run is like ripping my penis off with the other end of a hammer not
okay when did i do that all right let's watch it again
okay i when did i do that all right let's watch it again
oh
put cigarettes out on my dick hello ladies and gentlemen welcome to episode one of germa crap
getting these games to run is like ripping my penis off with the other end of a hammer
not tiny i'm compact you can eat my asshole with a fork the giant enemy spider
fuck do you eat ass life is pain i hate fuck out of here santa i know where you are santa
i was here
do another get get to fisto please that was wild
these it's like being on a roller coaster man some of these videos
germa is over is this one right it's over
i thought this was a green screen edit i saw the gray shirt and mr bean we talk about mr
bean all the time i thought this was a green screen shit it's called germa missing germa
vanishes in a in the quarantine crisis poppy cheetos chicken germa crap the four nations
lived together in harmony then everything changed when the corona virus attacked only
germa master of all four elements could stop them but when the world needed him most he vanished
i was there on the 28th by the way this is the 28th this is the 28th of march oh look it up i was
there i was there and i streamed it was guaranteed i was there 28th of march i was live it was my
birthday that's very relevant because i'm about to like leave yeah relevant it was late i was
definitely not late okay this is uh this one's called germa versus chat let's see
we've seen this i think have we seen this
it's time for you to pay yeah we have we have seen this
yeah we have seen this you're right you're right i thought it looked familiar
play it again well i mean we already started it so let's play it
that was really cool i can't wait to do the green screen dlc night that's gonna be so much fun
and i can't wait to do another one on top of that and another one and then another one and then
another one that will be one of the first things that happens when i come back because
i want to give at least a good couple weeks for people to make a bunch of stuff
all right this one's i don't know what this is i have no idea this is called mo moholland germa
i don't know what this is this is a show or a movie or something i don't know what this is
i don't get it i don't think i've ever seen this so i don't here's i don't know what this is
this is a david lynch movie okay this is just let you know this is a this is going to probably
be maybe a spoiler for a david lynch movie that's called what is it moholland what
moholland okay here we go this is called this again this is a spoiler for the movie drive if
you're in the middle of watching it on netflix right now just pause the stream okay let's go
that's my favorite thing that's my favorite video germa waiting for her meal
i thought we were going that fast and why is it a green screen what you couldn't put
like a restaurant back here or like a kitchen i would be yeah i'd be afraid of the radiation
coming off of this thing ungrateful streamer but where are we you gotta put you gotta i gotta be
implant ah i i need my immersion yes probably a meme or something i don't know what it is
this is i think this is just a clip of one of my videos if i'm this i think this is the
just a clip from a video this is not i i don't think this is a video i'm interested in the
history of this place let us go back hundreds of years it is the year 1775 or seven years
this is just a video this is just a video it's just a clip from one of my bad i gotta follow the
rules man this shit was fucking funny though this is the best part i'm gonna try that's okay
pro time crow kit no kit fisto no i really have a couple more germa's soggy feet i know people
hate when i say this but this is spoilers for the entire avengers saga infinity war end game
spoilers for all that shit i know i have to say because who the fuck knows there's 9 000 people
here i'm sorry i have to say it every single time this is for infinity war spoiler right here
right now
hold on hold on i need to i need to uh i'm gonna break this one down in my head a little bit here
one more
reversed it's reversed why that's so funny i'm so happy uh this is a source filmmaker of
when i did the toilet look at how funny i am uh april fools video here it comes
hey april fools it's a toilet you know what i mean i totally got you
uh i don't get it what's that mean i filmed a april fools video where i videotaped myself
flush in a toilet and it was like look at how funny my april fools twitter video is
and i actually really dropped the phone into the toilet not on purpose we have one more
no we don't well i do the shame in his voice wait what is this why why why are you guys linking me
a video hey april fools oh this is okay this is just the video okay oh my goodness
do grow time we're i swear i told grow time kid this still go the april fools video oh
why did i click that uh does anybody have that where is it where's the where's the actual video
i'll show it cringe is that all you shit posting all right next one i'm just clicking random links
in the chat right now where where is it i don't okay let me just let me just make this very clear
wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait hold on
important okay let me just let me just make this very clear getting these games to run
is like ripping my penis off with the other end of a hammer i'm practically insane
you get us going player one in the name of the galactic senate of the republic
you're under arrest chancellor the senate will decide your fate i am the senate not
yet i have to see it again so it's maybe a unit then
all right i'm no more no more that's it i'm not gonna watch it all
oh all right okay it's that was very funny all right toilet video is the toilet video
this is the real link oh is is it now watch it again all right everyone get your places
all right today is the big day today all right just say stop stop giving me videos that i were
not watching yet but i want this is that when i watch this is like this is upload like this is
uploaded today give me the real link who's next for a flu shot oh that's me i'm peter griffin mr
griffin these flu shots are in short supply what the what is this this game i'm just gonna type it
in the cook to google right now germa april fools video guys come on you're supposed to be helping
me out here here we go all i had to do is do it myself what we're gonna do is we're gonna we're
gonna play ah fucking spoilers spoilers you see the last two videos that's me with short hair
huge spider go back just wait hey april fools it's a toilet you know what i mean
i totally got you okay so let's i'll break this one down let me break this down so this is
real fool let's mute it so this is like look at me i'm flushing the toilet
it's so funny oh my god april fools it's a toilet you know what i mean
for try pretend to hit my face on the door that was the joke part like oh i look i'm gonna leave
now oh the door hit me in the in the face and then i dropped the phone actually into the toilet
not good not good bits within bits play them side by side that was that's what i'm doing
the idea but that this is going to conclude the community content night
uh we're gonna watch a little bit of the sonic thing this and those of you before you leave
i do let's hold on there's a lot of people here that need to hear this that may not have been
here at the beginning of the stream let's go close for this one i am not going to be around
for a pretty long time those who that didn't see the beginning of the stream or didn't see the
stream i am about to go on a medical leave of absence uh if you want to know why we there's
about the first 20 minutes of the video uh i'm it became really clear tldr if you don't want to
go back and watch any of that shit it became very clear over the last like four or five days after
the green screen stuff that i have to get this figured out and i have to whether it's do some
kind of procedure where i get an injection into a nerve or i can be going back and forth with my
doctor about some things that we want to try so the next couple of weeks i'm just going to be
hittering just hammering trying to figure out what the fuck's wrong with me um and i hate to
take more time but i have to rip the bandaid off and i can't just like stream with a chest brace
on you know what i mean like that's no i gotta get this figured out so if you want to get more
info and more you know exactly what i'm talking about the first 25 minutes or so of this stream
we talked about it extensively so i'm gonna be back at 100 i'm gonna back at 100 percent
and figure it out and do whatever it takes but that's gonna conclude essentially this
stream we're gonna do a couple more things uh let me just open this i want them side by side
let's play them both at the same time can i even can i even do that
uh hey hey hey can i hold on i have to like recapture this uh where did this go unknown
dot png unknown dot png what is this i wait look i've look if i've got hair on my head i've got hair
and one google search can show i've got hair on my head this is not this
this is the same person in the screen look this is my real hair i can even go swimming with it
not too hard all right uh let me put this up here okay now the toilet video goes over here
okay hey april fool that's that video okay let's show up for what the hell is it doing
for what the hell is it doing this is wrong oh there we go we can't see i know you can't see
i know you can't see oh we did i didn't play huge spider yet the giant enemy spider
was awesome that was actually really good i can't link to it because it's on my computer
uh it's in the discord by the way for those of you that want to make sure people see your music
see your shit it's got to be on a site like youtube or like a soundcloud or like a place
i can link to not just downloadable link we can't see we can't see we can't see i can't see i can't
see it i know trying to get this to capture two images there was fake hair um what the fuck okay
i gotta i gotta focus here we go let's open these both at the same time let's see how accurate they
are okay let's turn this one on first
you're driving me mad you're driving me mad i want this to capture it i'm annoyed
computers just don't work computers don't work uh i don't understand but i can't capture
them why can i not catch my desktop i don't understand this is a long blink i'm sorry
dad why the fuck you crying so damn loud okay was this a meme before let's see my computer sucks
was this a meme beforehand or is this something that that dude just it was funny and they just
did it it's an ancient meme is it well it's funny it's i've never seen it so it's funny
all right before we go i do want to watch a couple clips of the sonic animated remastered thing
you know what i'm talking about somebody in the community uh had a lot to do with this project
was it called sonic unleashed it's the spider no the spider was the song i just had it on my
tabs what's it called sonic remastered sonic reloaded and i did promise like for the last
year that i was going to watch some clips from this even if we only watch a few where the
fuck is it oh how am i like this here it is that's not it that's not it i don't even know
if that is i'm not gonna open that i just had it i just closed the tab stop doing bonk sound effects
i've tried to type it in oh my god i try i can't find it i'm gonna go to the disco i have to go
to the discord to find it you guys seriously he's gonna hey guys just just put anything he's gonna
click on all of them he's gonna click every single one so just put anything there he'll click it
holy shit it got on stream paper mario ost i'm not though it's the spi nest nope
i'm about to fucking get out of here play benny hill and get bonk can one of the mods give it to me
one of the mods do it please i want a mod to send me the link to this i just typed it in i can't
find it all right everyone get why you keep giving me the same video
do i have any mods that i'll doubt it mods i need the sonic reloaded animated collaboration video
there are they just don't know what i'm talking about because i'm a fucking psycho
where is it i don't this is like inside of a toilet or something i'm not here
okay okay wow would you look at this looks like it's sonic the hedgehog coming at you
holy shit this is an hour we're not going to watch an hour i plan on going skip skip skip skip skip
skip skip skip skip skip skip skip skip skip skip that's what we're going to get that's what
we're going to do five nights at freddy's this is the right video okay it's like 200 people made
this first thing first one skip wait grab a snack step so we'll make it so 200 different people
made all of it or just like pieces of it
so what did each person make a like an image or like a finally the only thing left to be done
is to capture the essential pieces of data from your counterpart everyone contributed every point
my hyper metal sonic when you awaken kill him wait that's actually like a marionette
the remake of the movie i don't think that's true each person made one thing wait it's a this is a
remake of the original i don't know anything about song the hedgehog all i know is i made that in
dreams like a year ago that was exactly my inspiration i had nothing to do with this
very pretty the 90s sonic ova oh see isn't it great the jet propelled bodyboard
but you want to try it out oh i i get it i get i see what's happening i'll go use it myself
oh sure i see what i see this is crazy little kid with his new toy so this is the whole movie
i feel like i'm watching an episode of gumball this is crazy that's the best my favorite one
that's the best one that one that was perfect i did the same thing with the shrek movie
are you all right i'm fine just fine so who's that i shot it i have some news for you
i guess so gee i hope the president and sarah are doing all right
just give us 100 times i'll stop being your hostage all right started again this is the i
what the fuck good animation what the fuck good yeah there's 200 there's 200 people that worked on
this absolutely not you should do this how when i turn a stream on and every three seconds it's
another artist depiction of the stream
that'd be pretty funny i think that's just that's the screen for like two hours
how does the movie end did i even show the ending
rat movie rebuilt every 10 minutes of a different streamer be you that's so funny
oh this is pretty sick skip it i told you guys this is like live action sonic better enjoy his
victory now because once he gets to robotropolis he'll have to fight something far more evil than
metal robotnik what do you mean are you talking about yourself you better keep your hands off my
sonic or i'll never forgive you this is with a metal guy oh boy hold on what i was saying was
i had an idea a long time ago where i was going to pay somebody that looked like me
that was essentially a doppelganger stream for like two weeks straight and don't ever bring it up
don't even mention it and i kind of come in sometimes and i sit in behind them in a chair
for some streams and just teachers aid them you know like put notes down and be like no no no no
sorry it was look at me you gotta go you gotta do it right like i'm training the next
germa to take over and they they study the way that i talk and everything that i do
and they just try so hard to just be me for a week or two straight germa apprentice you have
like more than one have like five people and then like you get fired them like they they get voted
off i mean i thought it would be kind of funny to do that at least um but then i just kind of gave
up on it it's a reality show yeah i mean sure it's on the list of things streamer school
but it's not like i'm teaching you how to be a streamer i'm teaching you i want you to be
me i'll explore it a little bit space where they would be blown to pieces this is fucking insane
gotcha that was close this took so much work wait what's this for me now that looked really good
ready ready careful fire
oh that one was made out of paper yes oh this is the best song oh yeah rolling around the speed of
sound got places to go gonna follow my rainbow already i did this joke already like a year ago
never mind delete it i did that joke like a year ago i actually did that a year ago and i'm seeing
it and i'm watching it in my own head it's a joke reuse it is hey grant dufferin i'll give you link
because that's you're into sonic i admittedly am not very much i think it's a cool character
i think it's an interesting franchise but i don't i i don't play it i don't really got into it
enable germa please i will enable germa please i will it's not right now all right guys i i'm
gonna go and i'm not gonna be back for a while put the scan lines i will be back i'm gonna try
to do this as fast as possible i'm gonna do this every day i'm gonna be going back and forth
with the doctor and i'm gonna get this shit settled and i'm gonna come back at 100
i've never tried to do like an extended break like this but it has to be done
it's long term there's a bunch of projects that i'm doing that i want to work on that i want to be
100 for and that's just all there is to it and it's it's really really difficult for somebody
like me that has been doing this and been around and cares about doing this shit so much
to be like i had to buy i'm gone and i don't know when i'm coming back a few weeks it's like
i hate to do that he's never coming back well that's what that's not true
not true uh i know it'll be fine and i'm just overthinking it like oh my god they're gonna
take like what if i'm not back for in like a month what if i have to get a procedure what if i have
to have like a surgery or something oh no i'm not going to be able to be live for like a month two
months like shit happens whatever so good i'll tweet more right i'll do more tweets uh just
it's been a hard call to to make because i knew it was coming eventually tonight we're going to
do the bits we'll hang up a little bit more uh thanks for watching and i will see you when i
get back at 100 100 on the 60 70 percent anymore none of them no more of this bullshit
i will be tweeting don't worry i'm not going to just i'll make it don't worry i'll be around
and with that i will see you guys in a couple weeks i'm not going to put a time frame on it
because let's put it this way if this could i could figure this out in the next six or seven days
or two weeks or more so i would rather just say i'm gonna get this figured out
if it's less than a week it's less than a week if it's more than two weeks it's more than two
weeks and i don't know what it's gonna be so he is a different person i'm gonna come i'm gonna
come back as a different person i hope i come back as a more healthy person that'd be great
in the meantime i am gonna set up a auto host with just a big bunch of people that i think are
really really interesting that i think that i respect that i think are funny that i think are
cool i'm just gonna there'll be an auto host just for the next couple weeks of of my like streamer
list of people that you know for you to watch if you want to watch them but let's do the bits
let's go through these don't need to go very very fast but kind of just well we'll hang out
for a little while ribbiorrhea thanks for the 250 i hope things go well me too i also hope that
because it is in my best interest to make sure that it happens no more half diagnosis no more
half well it could be this we'll test you for that oh that looked like it was positive come back
some other time no no no no we've talked back and forth me and the doctor we're doing it now
now now now now now everything hey pixel mike thanks for the five dollars here i know full well
how scary it is for the doctor to flat out tell you i can't help you i've been bouncing around
doctors for about five years and they still can't really figure it out although i've improved
incredibly it's still so unnerving not really knowing what's wrong but i think taking three
weeks of recouping will really help i'm sorry to hear that you're also having bullshit to do
and when you have some kind of underlying problem and that's the thing i i have a lot of underlying
problems i've had colitis and i've been diagnosed with with irritable bowel disease
and i've been treated for that and i remember a time when i wasn't being treated for that
and it was miserable so i'm kind of putting myself back in that same
headspace where when i was not getting treated for colitis holy shit hurry the fuck up let's go
once i started to get on a regimen that is completely under control completely i have not
had a uh a irritable bowel disease issue i've not had a colitis issue for years since i got on the
right treatment plan absolutely no problems at all it's it's it's 100 managed so i'm hoping that
same thing can happen whatever is causing this issue it's just a question of finding it even if
it's some weird condition that is kind of hard to find i'm gonna find it that's what i'm gonna do
we'll see what is the issue to not completely broken record myself i have intercostal pain
nerves that run from my somewhere in the middle of my chest around my band to my back just around
my ribs hurts all day every day for no reason i didn't get into any accident i didn't have any
problems it just hurts to move it hurts to sit for a long time and it just hurts to kind of exist
there's no real cause and it's been the the the bane of my existence for the last probably
a year and a half it has never gotten better but it's never really gotten any worse so obviously
i need to figure this out and the latest is and it would make sense but i don't want to
self-diagnose or anything but this i had what was potentially shingles a few years ago and sometimes
if you have and remember this is not this is not me telling you this is what it is but this is
just one of the theories is that if you have shingles and shingles is a rash that goes around
your it goes down a nerve and there's a small chance if you have shingles that you end up
with permanent nerve damage it's a neuralgia is what it's called it's rare if it's not that
i also tested positive for potential rheumatoid arthritis so we're gonna explore that so it's i
don't know but you can test positive for ra i've been tested for it more than once to make sure
that we don't get a false positive but it also might just be costochondritis which is just
inflammation in your rib cage i've been that the doctor said that's probably what it is there's
been like three or four different opinions on what it could be but it's time to just be like
which one which one is it which one because if it's something like nerve pain
or costochondritis i go get a small slightly invasive procedure where they inject a needle
into my rib and kind of numb with steroids the nerve and they shut it up and then for some people
you are fucking fine for the rest of your life that has been one of the procedures that i was
about to do diagnosed you have costochondritis intercostal pain on nerves we're gonna shut the
nerve down and i said no because i wanted to be definitively diagnosed so i've got a couple more
opinions on it if it does turn out to be that i'm gonna do it and that will be what i do over the
next few weeks i'm just gonna get it done but like again i this is why i don't want to to to
i don't want to tell you guys all this stuff but i kind of have to because you don't just disappear
for three weeks without me giving you some kind of reasoning oh i have a pain and uh bye see you
next month no that doesn't work like that you guys you guys kind of need to know he's gonna come back
as jex yeah i'll i'll be all right it's just something i just don't want to have to deal with
anymore like like if you were here in the beginning of the stream i'm gonna parrot what i said after
the green screen dlc it was bad it was bad to a point where i just was kind of looking i was lying
on my floor just hanging out looking at the ceiling going this has got to stop i gotta get
this figured out and that's where i kind of had the flow to the ideas around to do it why did you
break dance because i was having fun i was having too much fun and that's all i cared about and i
would do it again if i had the chance right now it wasn't that though i did that in the first
20 minutes of that stream it was just a combination of actively moving around screwing me up because
there are other times that you guys don't see where i get up and i move around and i feel all
right but if i you know if i do anything that requires me to rotate it's like oh that fucking
hurts a lot like i bet well now i'm sore now i'm sore for the rest of the day now why so it's not
just all i must have done something on that stream this happens on a this is a daily occurrence and
i don't want to scare anybody i like oh my god monger ash oh shit he's gone what's happening is
he gonna be back yes don't please trust me but we'll move on donut 500 thanks for the 35 bucks
3500 bits derma take the time you need to figure this shit out my girlfriend my girlfriend has a
bunch of mystery health issues and the doctors haven't been helpful at all uh do your thing man
hope you find you're able to find what's going on with your body i bring happiness to thousands of
gamers all around the world i plan on figuring it out i'm going in i'm going in i had a doctor's
appointment a few days ago and this is exactly what we both went back and forth it's a great
doctor they really really understand they're super on top of this and i have been told from
this doctor that we're going to do we're going to get this figured out we're going to do whatever
it takes and they're going to figure it out so i have the utmost confidence that this doctor will
figure it out hey s howco thanks for the 300 bits please please please take care of yourself
derma i know i'm not speaking alone when i say that we all care about your health i know that's
why i'm doing this i'm taking it dead seriously i am taking it very seriously otherwise i wouldn't
just kind of disappear for a while uh hey kiko thanks for the 300 bits the name game germa germa
germa boberma banana fanafo firma fi fi mo murma germa that's been a long time since i've heard
that one thank you fredol schlitz for the 250 germa post stream chat needs to know what happened
to chase fairbanks undercover idiot uh what you're probably referring to is i was i used to be on new
grounds and over the years on new grounds you know it was an animation site and we you know at
the time wanted to try to get something a comedy show on new grounds animation going this is one
of those things of the the hundred million different ideas two decades or or so almost
i can't even believe i'm saying that out loud he founded game grumps i no i didn't he was a porn
actor uh but no yeah i i i spent like i said before i've ideas come and ideas go and some of
them are better than others some of them are funny and some of them are not so funny i can't i can
tell you i could probably count on 50 hands over the last 20 years me trying to come up with an
interesting idea with a group of people and it doesn't work out and it was not funny he's oh no
it's fast i wanted to be like a voice actor i was on new grounds that's well that's not what that
what the fuck do i care who says count on 50 hands me you have a fiver account you know those some
people in five are making a shit load of money i don't i don't actually have one though show us
your old work it's on new grounds that's just not that's just there that's how i'm the guys
that's how how do you think i met blordow lord look at the screen right now the only thing that
is on new grounds is salty swamp oh i think there's a couple more things it's blordow
origins from voice acting to e-clown my ass is a salty swamp good one
yeah i mean i think you i think a lot of you guys severely underestimate just how long i've wanted
to like do entertainment it's been like it's been a long time since i was like 15 i've been around
but anyways uh let's move on let's continue you have to explain this if you if you want me to go
explain a like 16 year old like post i did on new ground i can't even remember what i had for
breakfast three days ago what are you talking about voice of one two three yeah this is all
you guys you guys this is all old shit yeah i had a voice acting page with a demo on it and
or whatever i wanted to i'm trying to practice i'm practicing how do you think i got so good
my voice can be changed to sound extremely elderly kind old man see yeah you're all right
let's see let's see what you did on you let's see what post you made when you were fucking 17 huh
that's a that's a good post i that's it was explaining who i am oh jeremy you're 17
no i i made a lot of friends on new grounds i had i had blordow is a lifetime lifelong friend
i cherish my time that i had on there as much as a fucking weirdo that i
was and you know what i don't think much has changed i think like all right i feel like some
of that shit i would say now you sound so young you hate it to anime oh what do you want to do
what who cares oh no he said he didn't like anime mom's making cookies from basket robbins is the
best flavor yeah i've what are you not much has fucking changed guys i mean i like to think
i've grown up a little and some of my opinions have matured since you know i was like fucking
you know sick like 17 years old i'm 35 this next year what do you want me to tell you
he's too old no you were not 17 you were 19 i don't know i don't know what you want me to say
i was an artist trying to take on the world that's half a lifetime ago yeah it is it is
remember is your cool older cousin that gets you drunk i why did i read that hey dark soul
thanks with the 250 what the fuck are you even talking about you do taxes yes i do my taxes so
why we've already gone over this enable this i will before i will turn that on before after
the stream is over i will turn it i will log in i'll turn it on i promise we won't wait do you
do you guys think that i have a computer or something from like 2001 or 2004 you think
i own like old computer where do you think i'm gonna get this stuff guys i don't even have
my official german 985 banner on this computer i don't i don't know where the fuck that even is
you're a fake why would i still have like any old voice acting any old footage i
dude i'm fucking 35 man and you guys have seen some videos and some animations he's still i am
still young you're right is chat saying that you're old again probably he's a young old person
stop being mean chat they're not being mean they're fine all right we have to get through the bits
when you can do a western film i wanted to make a western full motion video game
i want i we talked about it i'd like to help spread the infection yeah anyways let's continue
rosy briar thanks for the five dollars feel better soon we love you i appreciate that
it means a lot specifically because uh this is what i this is like what i do now this is
what i want to do every day projects i mean obviously we're talking about you know oh what
about like you know stuff 20 15 20 years ago or whatever this has been something i've cared about
for fucking decades so it does suck and it does hurt to be here and be like see you later for an
indefinite amount of time which and it has to be done so i can just thank everybody that's here
for as long as you've been here i get to fulfill dreams that i've had since i was a teenager
obviously judging by the last couple conversations see you in three years not that long just keep an
eye on the twitter i will update you every every couple days every like two or three days i'll
make sure i tweet hey michael smells thanks for the 300 bits i love you germa chat loves you too
you've helped me for so much and i can't thank you enough today is my last day of senior year
of high school i've known you since early tf2 days shout out to the discord subs channel you guys are
the best i'm rambling but you're just great dude thank you appreciate it the servers he knew you
from the servers yeah but anyways gnarly thanks for the thousand bits don't tell me what to do
germa i'll give you as much money as i'm comfortable yeah but it's not it's not about how much money
anyone's comfortable giving it's that i want to make sure that you're paying for something
that's worth paying for it's always been like that so obviously anytime somebody gives a bunch
of money i don't want to make sure that you're able to do it too you're able to actually give
that kind of money because i know that a lot of people maybe can't so obviously it gets to that
point where i just want to make sure that you're doing fine too and not worrying about like money
and shit and giving it to me hey just take this take this i i don't make that much money i saw
the germa census i saw it like 80 percent of the people that watch this channel don't make any
money i saw that well but it was a small sample size i did see it yes i did if you haven't seen
it people can go ahead and link it i wasn't part of it i think there was like 2000 people right
i did see it but i didn't want to turn this into a oh give me money because i'm now i'm going to
take a medical leave and i have to get this medical shit figured out now pay me and you know that's
not what the point is it's never what i want the point to be so i know i really appreciate it you
say just take it and i will but i will speak that as well i will tell you that as well i want to
make that clear uh anyways thank you too i missed i completely glazed over dark souls message dark
soul for 250 said don't believe this imposter's lies he's only taking off time so he can prefer
to skin walker abilities you're telling me this is the guy i subs to yeah i got a bunch of bright
okay hold on i gotta defend myself here i've got i have to go on defense this is this is really
bright studio lights shining three feet in front of me into my face why do you think my eyes are so
the dilation this i'm right in front of the studio lighting you look like a demon yeah i know i've
seen the i've seen the images i've seen the images you're a fucking alien well maybe i am
and that's okay right rick and morty eyes it really was that's fucking creepy hey edgy shadow
thanks with thousand bits take my money you hack i will i'll take it all right kiko thanks for three
dollars hey again germa one time i had a daydream that me and the subs discord chat robbed a bank
to give you bits but then the police started chasing us but you were part of the police squad
that was chasing us and we blew up the car you were in anyways bye
wait this is a daydream this is not a regular dream this is a daydream wait i thought this
is a real like a dream dream oh my god okay well that makes that a little stranger hey germa's the
best thanks for 250 here's to germy here's to germy's physical health all right thank you here's to
yours as well hey still best friends thanks for the 300 bits do what you gotta do i'm that's my
plan is when i'm coming back with no issues it's been a long time coming i'm gonna go for it
sticks renegade thanks for 250 germa welcome back guess what happened my neighbor's dog was
biting hard at another dog what i got bit trying to help almost took my nail off and broke my
finger have i ever been bitten before no that sounds horrible no i've never been bit by a dog
or attacked by any kind of animal or anything no never i can't imagine how stressful and
horrible that is though hope you're all right that's an insane message i mean why
hey i got bit by a dog i mean that's it's insane i mean that's a wild story it's a crazy story
hope you're all right though recover it's an oof wild hey wind are thanks for the five dollars
hey man thanks for all you do you've heard it a million times you truly are one of the best
content creators out there you're a content god i mean that i i'm glad you think that take all
the time you need a dead germa isn't a good germa not implying you would die i hope not so again
thank you you've made my life better by being someone i can look to have a smile you're a
genuine and caring person but your health takes top priority thank you for all that you do thank
you for doing everything for me i don't get to take three week breaks for my health if i don't
do what i'm doing right now you allow me to do that so thank you i'm incredibly fortunate in that
realm i'm you i'm saying three weeks i don't think it'll take that long but i'm just saying
it just to say it it's kind of the long end of the spectrum there jack the back thanks for 1500
bits love you germa everyone don't listen to him please donate all your money don't do that i
probably shouldn't have even read that thanks for the 15 bucks hey net thanks for a thousand bits
these are pity bits thank you thank you clammy bob 42 i caught it already but it's a lot of money
they did it for the badge it's so much money hey dark soul thanks for 250 again if you don't want
those bits can i take some of them back i can't there are no refunds no refunds so make sure you
get it right because i can't give them back you're my grin hey don't hit table hey kinky creatures
thanks for five dollars germa hi thanks for helping me with my anxiety here's some money for your
mecha suit it'd be nice thanks for hanging out rattus raccoon three dollars i'm super sad that
there isn't going to be a stream for a few weeks but i hope you figure out what's going on you too
i hopefully will not have to be away for that long i'm just going to go for as long as it takes
to do it however long that is focusing every day only on that donut 500 another thousand bits
you the best i'm glad you think that i'm glad you don't think i'm the worst control x thanks for
a thousand bits they say cute and all capitals all a jayden's brain five dollars i've been in
the same situation i was sick in various ways for 10 years and the doctors were useless i don't know
how much money i spent on them so i want to help you get through this as much as possible in the
end i had to figure it all on my own and i was right and now i'm getting traded hope you don't
have to go through that please appreciate video games they are the best glad you finally got to
figure it out i've got a handful of good leads where things have come back positive for things
and then now you do the next step and i don't want to wait to do them and i want to do them on
free time i just want to do them now take care of yourself thanks for the five dollars a gray angel
thanks for 250 we can rebuild him we have the technology we can make him better than he was
better stronger faster the six million bits boomer gear broth thanks for the 15 bucks
germo jumping on stream for a moment here to donate hope you feel better take care and all
the time that you need that i can assure you i promise that the next time that you see my face
live on stream i will have the news to tell you that i am getting this under control and it's
being treated and i'm ready and i'm back i don't have to even talk about i'm gonna get what i'm
gonna have to even have another conversation about this when i'm back i hope to have it pretty much
toast by then uh royal dowey thanks for the 11 dollars germa i had a funny dream where you had
gotten your hands on my credit card and you were holding it up to the camera while streaming when
i asked you not to do that you said that's ridiculous because everyone lies on their
credit card i asked how that makes any sense and you wanted a small rant about how you lied on
your card all the while chat erupted with people saying things like illegal streamer omega lul
anyways keep doing what you do man everybody lies on their credit card was it a youtube account
yeah whatever how old am i youtube i'm like 60 who cares thanks to the 11 bucks max akito thanks
with a thousand bits you're like minesweeper no not really no yeah it's cool to play for like
five seconds and then you realize that you can't play on anything other than difficulty level zero
and you have to stop it's a neat little trick every once in a while hey fishies thanks for
the five dollars germa i'm donating because i want to do exactly what you want us not to do
because i'm a rebel but for real i'm glad you're taking a break to heal and get back to 100
what's important in your life is yourself and your own health and i think everyone is is content
with your choice you've done much more than any of us could ask it's about darn time you make
some time to do what's best for you uh we love you germa nine eight five mr funny man yeah and i know
i know i know that i need to do this because i can't just pretend like it's not happening
there is no more well i can just stream for four hours a day and wear the brace and in the next
month i'll have it looked at it will keep going i really do appreciate the fact that a lot of you
guys are willing to stick to me and stick with it and of a two or three weeks a month whatever
something if anything i don't know how long there's a lot of people that are gonna stay
will people leave i don't know but i can't even that's not even crossing my brain at the moment
like well well but germa what about your growth you've had such a huge growth you don't want to
stop that now well whatever i was never one to really give a shit about numbers and how
many people were here or how much money that i take in today i don't i don't that doesn't i
don't care you know i mean i mean that's a lie of course i care of course i care about how many
people are here because that means that people like the stream and i'm doing something that i
think maybe people think is funny and obviously the more people that are here the better but i
can't let something like that take over my life and be like well who cares i'll just i just i'm
gonna keep framing every day maximize profits 100 or bust i didn't stream every day anyways
and we're still on this path right i'm gonna get it fixed a fishies wait no you didn't do twice
you just did once five dollars from fishies that's what it was and that's all it was appreciate it
uh budgie thanks for five dollars been watching the streams for a few months and i can finally
send some bits to the number one e-clown take care during your break germa i can't wait for
more second channel content is it gonna be a lot there's been a good at least three or four people
that have been brought on or they're about to be brought on there's gonna be a lot of videos on
the second channel a lot stay tuned hey pugils thanks for the five dollars hope you're recovering
all right just a quick tip from one crack head to another if a drug sniffing dog ever catches you
just say he who smelt it dealt it and they're forced to arrest the dog but um chi right
right that's actually pretty good hey red walrus thanks for the thousand bits germa it's red walrus
the one with the shoe size germa rat and the warhammer germa rat it obviously needs to be said
that i commissioned those rats from the very special snuggle bill snuggle sweet on etsy she's
super cool and would love to make more for customers she said i'll provide a link on
discord if that's okay yeah let's go for it i do not own the rats is the colonoscopy going to be
on the second channel soon uh hate sucks thanks for the 15 bucks hope you feel better boomer
thanks for the 15 dollars i appreciate it i'm gonna try i'm gonna go for it ajax the mediocre
2000 bits 20 dollars germa thank you for literally bending over backwards to make us laugh
i'll be feeling better big guy me too i hope i feel better too i'm gonna do whatever it takes
thanks for the money thanks to the big money germa fireman thanks for the three dollars they just say
fireman emote that's all that's here whimsical moose thanks for 250 i know we all will miss you
take a long as a break as long of a break as you need your health is more important than
these silly streams and we just see what's in store when you're at 100 but these streams are
important you're a major part of my life so it's a major part of the decision making when i decide
if i'm gonna do something like this thank you uh vladkovich thanks for the five dollars magic
stream was your sexiest short hair arc this is the sexiest i mean i'm probably gonna have this
hair soon hey germa 100 is gonna come back this kind of hair anyway we're talking germa 100 not
germa 65 appreciate the compliment hey douglas ratman thousand bits no message just 10 dollars
given to me and handed to my hand and i just closed my hand and i put it in my pocket thanks
for the 10 dollars this halucco thanks for the 500 bits i made the germa reddit soy face and i
feel the need to repent wait a minute why is this the germa reddit slash soy face why are you giving
me that moniker the just the germa reddit face no no no this is that this already has a name
it's not my thing this is not me that's not my thing don't bump out the the don't give me that
moniker a kill piss thanks for the five dollars germa my college roommate and i were separated
because of the virus and it didn't get to move out at the same time what we did your content was
something we enjoyed together and the space channel five stream highlights is what started
it all even though now we're miles apart your streams have been bringing us together and letting
us laugh like we're in the dorms again thanks for being a part of the laughs and memories we shared
in 318 stay safe that's what i used to do when i was in college i was just trying to make each
other laugh to make my friends laugh make my roommates laugh have them make me laugh it was
just about how they're having fun glad i can be part of that i'm glad i can be a part of that
it's important it has a 2.6 gpa yeah i didn't say i was the brightest bulb but i last a long time
i'm like a led guys am i the brightest bulb in the room no but i'm gonna last
10 years never gonna have to replace me girl all those halogens ah that bright and hot yeah okay
bright and hot wow you burn out in two years you burn out in six months fuck out of here
fluorescence oh they last a while well what's that they're full of toxic chemicals
and if you breathe in it causes diseases and shit oh yeah oh cool that good good for you
not me i'm an led last 10 years it won't be that bright where was i going with that i don't know
i was going somewhere with that he's he's losing what's i was i was going somewhere
how does that end toxic streamer a convo breaker thanks to 250 i know you said no already but
pick man one is literally a six and a half hour game you get that time spread across 29 days to
get 29 parts plus one free part on this tutorial day with no time limit in the time between days
it should be exactly two four hours dreams perfect for health and since you're a god of a gamer you
can finish before day 30 also please for the love of god add the germa please emote otherwise
your breakdancing will mean nothing i'm gonna add it i'm gonna add it i promise i just have to
log in i think it'll be the last thing i do before the stream turns off add it now okay there you go
done deal it's there hey donut 500 thanks for five here's thanks for five dollars they say here's
some funky bits because you're epic thanks appreciate it i just enabled it refresh your
screens refresh your page hey x inc thanks for the 250 did you know that bella lagasse is dead
i do i yes i know dream thanks for five dollars germa just wanted to send some love to my favorite
streamer after so many years i felt like you deserve something for all the laughs uh you
watching is enough for me to care about i'll take your five dollars though i really appreciate it
i am honored to be your favorite streamer sometimes i can't believe that that's real
shitty viewbot thanks for the 10 bucks look up germa 985 on google and go to images you'll be
surprised what the first result is will i no that doesn't surprise me i knew that it's the worst one
it's the worst image that's been there forever it's been so long that's been there for like
four years peaceful hailey thanks for 250 hey germa it's nice to see you back after you turned
into the tin man hope you're doing well still currently trying to get my shit together i think
i'm getting there anyways have a good night i'm gonna get there you enabled this emote on the
wrong account no i didn't i only have one twitch account well i mean if you don't count buying
every man zero one one one zero zero one one space zero one one of course or like all the
the 12 master of comedies that exist poor monster gave this some there was some 50
dollar drops here poor monster gave 50 dollars thanks for the stream and positive art reception
despite your onset of dementia please take care of yourself because i'm dealing with grandma in
hospice and i don't want to see you push yourself too hard and be gone too oh yeah thanks for the
5000 bits my onset of dementia i'm gonna i'll be back at 100 thanks for the 50 bucks moss lion
thanks for 250 first you break quarantine to buy funko pops and then you break it again to film
yourself making baby food on a public beach please stop you're going to get us all killed
the fake beach that was a fake beach freudian weapon thanks for 250 best of luck getting your
medical issue sorted out be safe healthy and fia and i'll see you when you get back
you funny streamer guy hey that goes for chat too right i'll pop in i'm gonna pop in from time
to time i'm not going to disappear charlie is okay thanks for five dollars just five dollars
thank you charlie no message just germa a couple of male scribbles thanks for 300 bits germa i'm
glad you liked my auto and where lord art it was very very cute also i don't know how i figured out
how to post the animal crossing one on imgur rather than directly in discord but oh well hope
you make a quick recovery during your time off take care of yourself i'm gonna try rip kit fisto
gave 20 community subs i didn't even see that thanks for the 20 subs porcupine thanks for the
15 dollars rip kit fisto and is this an ancient meme that i think is just funny now i catch all
these so late i'm sorry guys morcus porcus 20 community subs so many community subs and so much
money i hope i spend it well thank you morcus for your huge community sub drop thank you john scary
for the 15 dollars jeremy 985 elbertson i've loved you since high school please be my boyfriend
and then they say um uh forehead forehead forehead forehead i'm sorry i'm currently taken i'm taken
not bumblebuck thanks for the 300 bits i've been watching your pro gaming content for around seven
years now so here's three dollars in return now if you could do me a huge favor and read the rest of
this message with no background music it would be greatly appreciated make us big please mr
scientist i wish for 15 dollars him to be safe i am hold on make us big please mr scientist i wish
for 15 dollars him to be safe i am fast germa i am purple alien magic frog swamp witch
they say thanks i needed some voice lines for the witch's curse part four everyone can't wait to
see that one for fast germa and purple alien get into all kinds of trouble thank you bumblebuck
and thanks for the videos too hey radly thanks for the thousand bits hope you feel better
glad you're taking the time you need to look after your health thank you for all the great
streams thanks for the 10 bucks it was not an easy decision to make but it's a decision i had
to make thank you radly appreciate it we didn't watch part three don't worry we're gonna watch
part three before we watch part four cat boy thanks for the 250 you said at the start this
was gonna be bad news but we're all glad you can take some time off love from chat especially
offline chat come hang out with us in our secret hangout someday have a great next few weeks trying
to figure out that stuff stay healthy stay safe play super paper mario take care of yourself and
best wishes yeah we're gonna we're gonna do salmon mac season three never uh well bad news
in the sense that the bad news was going to lead to good news but bad as in i'm not gonna be around
i don't i hate taking extended time off because i genuinely enjoy doing this i like having fun
i might i don't even know guys i might just fucking crack you know what i mean like after
two weeks i might just crack and have to come play like incredible hulk or something i don't know
don't do it i probably won't but i won't i won't i'm not gonna i'm not gonna i'm not gonna i'm not
gonna only when i'm back to 100 you're right a poncho sanza thanks for the five dollars germa
my wife and i are in our 30s just beginning cancer treatment for stage two colon cancer
so i know what you're going through you're an amazing streamer and your streams mean a lot to
us get well soon i really hope that you that's caught early enough sounds pretty potential
one thing about colon cancer is if you catch it early enough within the i believe the first
stage or two right that it's very very reversible and it can be treated i wish you the absolute
best i can't imagine what you're going through stay fucking strong because what i'm going through
is is astronomically not even close to what you are thank you so much for the five dollars
i wish you the absolute best thank you to syrock for the 250 call vinnie he's crying
oh vinnie he's crying it was huge money holy shit it was there was a hundred dollars and then
two hundred dollars oh my god the lemmy thanks for the 10 000 bits 100 bucks germa please take all
the time you need to figure out what's going on we'll be here when you get back that's the plan
that's all they say paper is food gave 200 bucks at 20 000 bits 200 fucking dollars
that's a ton of money a year ago i started animating my thesis film so i can graduate
next week after four years with my bfa before i started production i knew that i was going to
need colorist plus music plus composition help but i also realized that i would need to budget
for the entertainment so here's your payment for entertaining me for the 12 to six hour days
while i animate my thesis since 2012 helped me make it to the end and now i have a film about
a strawberry ready for festivals stay healthy germa see you later you gotta have you're gonna
have to fill us in on what this is you if you're still around eventually let us know what it is
i'm curious now watch this clip vinnie wants to be friends with germa it'll even fucking load and
i always get really guilty about that because turn that off where's my audio like i said that
every other stream there we go and i always get really guilty about that because i like people
people like germa hey you know like for example i wish i had a better friendship with him
but i don't put the effort in and um only germa that's it one guy one guy but
you know and we we all get busy everyone gets busy but the point is like i got to
yeah i mean that's i feel that it's it's it's really really really easy to just kind of
just do your own thing and do shit and not really reach out like i do that i do it all the time i
know a lot of you guys know that i'm like i mostly do i'm a solo guy and i think then he's the same
way likes to do a lot of his stuff you know solo but you know you you can start to lose track
i've i've hung up with vinnie in real life he's a really really he's a great fucking person he's
a really good dude he is like he's exactly like how you think he is you know what i mean just like
the most chill dude the most like just he's exactly the way that you think he is he is he
tall than you no i've got at least two or three inches on him he's probably like he's like he's
like five he's like five eleven i'm like fucking six two you know it is now there's there's tons
of people that i could say this about you know about hanging out with people reaching out to
people you know you there's a lot of people that you end up talking to on a weekly daily monthly
basis i completely get it yearly but that's another thing too that i think a lot of people
need to understand is um friendships are great and they work very well especially when when
people don't feel like they're obligated to have to hang out with anybody you know what i mean
it can make it a little more comfortable when it's not like oh i have to hang out with you
because i have to but you want you do you want to and you want to spend time with this person
and you just do here comes the but no that was it that was the statement
but no i have i have a lot of friends in random various places that i've met over the years and
years and years some of them you don't talk to very much some of them you do some of them you
spend a lot of time with some of you don't spend very much time with anymore some of you used to
some you do some may be in the future you know oh well this friendship is now you talk to this
person every day now you don't there's another person that you hang out with or another group
of people it's just kind of it's kind of how how life is there are at least there are probably
at least a dozen people i can think of right now that are maybe not that maybe like six
that i will never stop talking to for my entire life those long-term just super friends that you
just talk to almost every day name them most of them are people back in massachusetts they're
lifelong childhood friends that i end up talking to i speak to not every day but you know at least
once every like couple weeks once a week the boston arc but yeah i mean i could probably
list off on my 50 hands right we're gonna move on we are going to move to the end of
whoa oh my goodness so much money oh my god it's just updated i had this like minimized
down here and i just moved it and i didn't realize holy shit there's a ton of money
i wasn't looking at like the bar over the road okay hey expanded banana thanks for the 300 bits
you're my graduate from high school this week and i want to say thanks for helping me keep my sanity
congratulations on high school completion new book opens close that old one nice work phantom
tech thanks for five dollars germ i want to say thanks i want to say thank you that's what
their message i don't know what that meant weird they say thank you uh so much for making your
content when i was in senior year i lost a lot of my friends because they graduated the previous year
and went through a breakup that year so i was feeling really useless but started watching a
lot of your videos to pass the time during lunch and really helped hope you feel a lot better man
much love from a fan thank you phantom i think that kind of goes into what we were just talking
about how sometimes the friends come and go some friends stay forever some people you're just
really excited to see sometimes i mean there are people that i used to talk to you know in
decades of time that you know i haven't spoken to in more than 10 years and these people that
i spoke to on a daily basis you know 10 20 years ago by it's like i haven't spoken to that person
i probably couldn't that person probably couldn't pick me out of a lineup i wouldn't think too hard
on it really sorry to hear about the breakup though it's never easy i wish you the best thank
you for the five dollars hey rtx42069ti thanks for the 250 about the props you used during the green
screen did you steal it from someone well you just buy it for this also what do you do with all this
stuff after the fact do you just stash it somewhere hope you're not one of those jerks who just buy
something use it once and throw it away give it to us or donate it that's exactly what happens
uh the all the props used on the green screen at least the ones that are not clothing based
you know ones like um but for instance some of the capes that don't make it very well
you know some of those costumes that get ripped or get fucked up in the process that can't really
be used again uh everything is just donated put nicely into a bunch of boxes and it is dropped
off at a center that takes them toys and models and figures and whatever it is
yeah i purchased them and use them for the stream and then i just donate them when i'm done
go goodwill hunting for germa props you probably could i'm talking across from massachusetts to
las vegas i had a bunch of donations for toys and random games and stuff and i wouldn't be surprised
if somebody one day was just like holy shit wait is this the sword that he used this is the sword
from that green screen right hold on a minute i don't know what could happen weirder things have
happened hey heavy bolt thanks for five dollars here's a couple of mcchickens thank you now you
don't need any of us to tell you this but take as much time as you need i thought about telling
you how much your streams mean to me but at this point it's all been said and i can't decide what
to say right now anyways so just thanks for everything i really appreciate that that's
means a shitload it does because i like i said i sometimes can't believe that somebody is even
saying this about me it's i don't i it's crazy for me to think about that is literally everything
i've ever wanted to do is happening now it's almost like you have to stop and look around
for a little bit and be like wait this is happening i remember that post on newgrounds salty swamp
you know like how much back then like this i was i wanted to do the same shit it's been something
that i've cared about and just been a lifelong goal since i was a teenager and i can't fucking
believe that i'm sitting here now and reading some of these comments i just hope it can continue i
hope i can continue to be somebody that you think is funny or somebody that does entertaining
things because if i'm not then i'm doing something wrong and i don't want that to happen but thank
you hey goo berry juice thanks for 250 germa i just wanted to let you know there's absolutely
no reason to apologize for taking the time off to need to fix your back pain i'm just glad you're
finally doing something about it i remember i freaked out when i saw you break dance not
just because it was pug because i knew how much it would hurt you to do it the fact that you're
sacrificing your body just to make us laugh at something that's both heartwarming and terrifying
so please enjoy your break i do have to say though i mean a lot of people are writing about oh like
the fact that you sacrificed your body to do that that's not what i was thinking i just was sitting
there and said i'm gonna break dance now that's what my brain told me to do i wasn't going like
here we go here comes like the sacrifice no this is like just do it you hey jeremy start break
dancing okay that's all that's all took his greatest sacrifice what a hero oh you broke
dance what a fucking hero god sacrificial break dance
uh
sacrificial break dance what a hero oh that's gonna make me laugh for a little while hey invaders
thanks for the 250 you're gonna miss the streams but i hope you got everything figured out with
your health streams have helped me through a lot of stress recently thanks thanks for watching
who buried juice thanks for 250 before you do that can you do one last thing for me
i need to know who did this to you who did this to you watch full the vlog three two one
go oh the little the uh who do you think that was you really need to have more than one guess
of who that is yeah there was star of course it was who else would do that who else would who
else would attack me who would physically attack me it was kit fisto please show it okay here
let's show it yeah we can see the exact the exact moment here where i was where i was attacked by
star watch for the vlog three two one go hey guys wasn't him it was you can hear him laughing yeah
he attacked me he hit me it was in the it was in the eye in the mouth with an object that could
not have weighed more than like one ounce it was it did incredible damage it was kind of like
putting my face on a pillow but it was just he attacked me is that what fucked up your nose
what do you mean fucked up your nose why are you saying i have a fucked up nose i didn't tell you
that where'd you where are you getting that from is that where you fucked up your nose from where
you get oh that's nice unbelievable uh let's roll the credits we still have bits to do but
the janitor in here is the janitor gonna come in here i'm sorry i just you know what i mean all
right so we have a shitload of subs are gonna fly by they're going to go crazy you're gonna
see them they're going to just explode are you ready here they come it'd be very very fast too
fast it's going so fast that you can't even see it it's going so fast that you can't see it that's
why can i what's going on okay now it works what why did that happen it's a lot of people
screaming by the screen thanks for the subs thanks for the huge community subs there was a
bunch of you gave a lot of them thank you it's insane i can't believe this many people are
subscribed and this many people are being given subscriptions just this list alone is just is uh
it's too many it's too many people even can't believe it give subs please jeremy i know that
guy hey niall aureon thanks for three dollars jerma it's my friend james's birthday tomorrow
can you please tell him happy birthday and that we love him hey james happy birthday from niall
aureon and friends i'm gonna miss you you silly man i'll be back don't worry platadonius thanks
for the five dollars and one cent jerma i got here too late for the proper explanation
but good luck on the subject of the reanimated thing there's been one in the works for rat movie
for a bit i think it'd be cool to see some other group could organize one for like castle griffin
steed or jerma rumble wink wink nudge nudge but for real though stay safe and take care every
jeremy yeah i've heard that floating around about the rat movie there's gonna be like an animated
kind of system like that jerma rumble will take forever yeah jerma rumble on its own is like an
hour that would be well no it doesn't matter how long the video is that doesn't mean anything
figuring these out now jerma rumble is 20 minutes jerma rumble live is 47 minutes long isn't it
46 minutes long we'll see there are other projects that are going to take precedence first
you will see them before that happens a control x thanks for four dollars and 20 cents hey jerma
it's a pleasure to watch your streams as always have you considered that your painful kidneys
are caused by your rampant alcoholism endless marijuana smoking and incessant cbd addictions
maybe lay off the crack streamer just the thought smiley face um nothing wrong with my kidneys i
had those checked already thanks for the four dollars and 20 cents kiari thanks for the five
dollars jeremy i appreciate the auto host you could please figure out a way to do twitch reruns maybe
every other day during the break i'd love to watch a vod with a fresh chat on the channel
one of the overwatch league did them back in the day but i don't know if it's still a feature i
don't think no i think i think they deleted it i don't think you can do reruns anymore right
didn't they delete it you can oh see if you can um i don't know i i don't know i don't know i don't
know if i want to do that i'm not sure i'm into the that whole thing maybe i could pick like one
of my top two favorite streams or something maybe do one of my top favorite streams and
restream them it's gonna be the birdhouse stream isn't it no let me let's that's not gonna happen
immediately let me think about what if i want to do that or not that's gonna take a long time
for me to figure out which one it is this is too many now this ain't happening this is not gonna
happen it's gonna take too long it's gonna take too long for me to figure out which one it is
i'm gonna i'll sit there for three days trying to figure that out my my phone will be blowing up the
doctor will be like what are you doing get down there for your exam sorry i'm just trying to
figure out which one of my streams is the best i've watched them all four times it's an interesting
thought though i might do it don't hold me to that thanks for the five dollars hey control x
thanks for 250 jerma it's a pleasure to watch your stream as always if what i've been seeing is not
even one percent of your power can't imagine what 100 is like can't wait for you to charge up pog
face bernie pog well it was way more than one percent it was about 70 of my power what can i
do with the extra 30 percent imagine if we could unlock the other 10 if we could unlock even 11
percent of our brain power like that movie where it happens people could control shit with their
brains we'll see what i can do hey ryu bait thanks for the hundred bucks hundred dollars for the
hundred percent man thank you that's an insane amount of money hey envy one one casting thanks
for 250 so i gotta be a little sappy for a bit sorry here it goes having to go back into my
home situation because of this pandemic nearly sent me back into a real bad depression where
your streams helped keep me feeling semi okay take as much time as you need we're all rooting
for you yeah the the pandemic has really fucked up a lot of people's lives put people into
situations they shouldn't be in taking people out of situations that they really wanted to be in
is not good but we have some encouraging data that hopefully over these next couple months
somewhere into july that we can really start to be on the down it's just the downtrend try to go
back to fucking normal as much as we can i would love to see it because out here in uh in nevada
the stay at home order is still here and it's gonna stay and we're doing this whole phased
thing where if a couple weeks go by and there's no spike in cases then we're gonna slowly go
into another phase but from everything everyone i everything i've read about this this shit's not
gonna go away it's just here and i don't think we're gonna this is might be a situation where
this is something that we have to deal with for a long time people say the word second phase but
i'm not even sure i don't even know if i believe that because i think it's just here and i'm not
even sure if there's a second phase what about just first phase that never leaves until obviously
like a vaccine right phase five a second spike is more accurate yeah i'm not a doctor i'm not a
scientist just kind of we just went that it's out of my it's out of my court for this i'm an e-clown
that dances to jojo's bizarre adventure i don't know anything about fucking medicine i'm just
going to listen to the people that do know about medicine and know how to run shit and that's what
i i just danced at jojo's bizarre adventure in front of a green screen that's what i do
and let's hope they can figure it out because this is an unprecedented thing and sure there's
a lot of well we have like we've been we potentially have been running through these
like simulated pandemics and we have some idea of what might happen and what might not happen
who fucking knows this is the first time this has really ever caused this much of a problem
at least in the in the united states can we ban sour please why what about spanish flu
well when i say that when i'm talking about is like disney world closed for more than a week
that shit ain't never happened ever uh i know like spanish i'm talking about like in it like
kind of modern times they didn't have disney world in 1918 yeah well we got it now if they
had a disney world you bet i'd bet your ass it would have been closed century mickey muz
spanish flu is modern times no when your tv could push through colors is where modern times starts
why because that's the best invention since fucking the steam engine color tv
now this is the type of shit that if i was like a real personality making these statements like on
like a real show it'd be like an article written about me tomorrow well like how fucking fucked up
i was thank god i'm not a real personality too late breaking news streamer says that color tv
was most important invention next to the steam engine listen to this here's this clip it was
it probably was no you know what the best invention in the world was glass think about that
glass who invented glass when was the first glass pane pressed history of glass
the history of glass dates dates back to at least 3600 bc in mesopotamia it's a long time ago
well that guy was rich anyways let's finish these bits up hey angry alien thanks for five
dollars the best luck to germa watched you for years and now you brought a lot of laughter enjoy
it in my life take your time we'll be here thank you cult of personality thanks for the
300 bits germa i really hate to hear that you have a pain issue i know maybe many people who
live with it and my heart goes out to them and you anyways i graduated recently with a bachelor's
in computer science you've provided me entertainment during my time studying for five years in college
and university thank you hope this donation helps you in some way good night and good luck
i will have an answer and i hope it's an easy one i hope it's just a simple thing that i can
just do and be done with it it's the best case scenario actually three bucks vibio game thanks
for five dollars germa glad you liked my dumb paintings wishing you all the best as you work
out your health stuff we'll all be here in offline chat i'll come back you'll see me i'll make an
appearance more than one i'll pop into the chat every now and then see who's around i'll help in
the discord for a little while in the general i'll be around rtm thanks for five dollars germa that
green screen stream was great i still can't believe you broke dance on stream that was a
genuine pug hope you feel better soon take all the goddamn time you need so much fucking support
like i i can't even believe it thanks guys but i'm gonna be just fine they're right yeah i know they
are and i am gonna do that grown man grown man's gonna cry i'm not gonna i'm not gonna cry grown
man cry iron chef italian thanks that's a great name thanks for the five dollars germa before you
go and become gandalf the white do you have any advice for someone that likes the idea of baseball
that has no attention span as a fellow squirrel brain also these bits are dedicated in loving
memory to kit fisto uh well here are a lot of clubs that do condensed games some of the
subscription services you can get cut out all the bullshit and you can watch a full game in like an
hour and 25 minutes hour that's been the problem with baseball for forever is some of the games
are four hours long it's three hours and 10 minutes we're in the seventh inning so if you
really don't want to go through every single pitch i know that you can watch condensed games i would
just type in like your favorite team oh how do the subscription service with condensed games
i know you can't watch it live like that but they usually go up immediately after the game is over
baseball president sleeper yeah well i'm answering his question they didn't you didn't ask it come on
you didn't ask it he did tb chamber 50 dollars 5000 bits a lot of money hey man hope you get
this thing smashed much love ps i'm working on a game with the green screen assets would this be
okay for community content night absolutely of course it would we've done a couple of those
before on the first green screen night we played a game or two yeah definitely it's a huge amount
of money apple shift thanks for 250 i'm so glad you're getting things figured out man take your
time i know that we'll be right here waiting for you when you get back you're an incredible person
and we're gonna miss you a ton thanks for making us happy and being the best eclan all i gotta say
to that is thank you i just have one of those i just put it on and squeeze it sometimes ultra
fires thanks for 300 bits jeremy my mother had to go to the hospital a couple weeks back and in the
middle of the deadlines for university that week and it was the world of stress but your videos and
streams whether it be during work breaks when i simply didn't have the will to work was a massive
light of hope during the darkness it's been great watching you over the past weeks and finally
subscribing thank you for that take all the time you need now and come back as 100 you don't owe
us anything uh you don't owe me anything either you know that goes both ways you don't owe me
anything so on a monetary sense we go back there you don't have to you don't have to do any you
don't owe me anything thanks for the 300 bits uh sorry to hear about your mother hopefully she's
okay thanks for the 300 bits colin halter thanks for the 300 bits take all the time you need jeremy
we've got years of backlog content to keep us going kick that nerves ass and come back brand
new champ i'm looking forward to it jacobin thanks for the thousand bits jerma there's a practice
that's called uh neurokinetic therapy it's supposed to help your body it unhooks muscle
tension is the short way i can explain it it sounds fishy but i've seen it work it may help
you i am i'm willing to try pretty much anything but we i do have a positive result for potential
potential maybe i maybe remember this is not a diagnosis i don't know but rheumatoid arthritis
my rheumatoid factor was high which apparently can explain a few different conditions that can
cause that and ra is one of them that was the last thing that happened and the next thing to
say all right let's get this taken care of let's get this figured out but yeah i looked into i
looked into like acupuncture and massage therapy i went to physical therapy i was told to physical
therapy this might not even help so i'm willing to try pretty much anything i will actually write
that down take a look neurokinetic therapy let's just put it in there cool thanks for the tip
hey my name bro thanks for five dollars there i had a similar invasive procedure done when i
had pain in my back a few years ago they shot some steroids in there not a way you want to
spend a wednesday but on the whole not so bad get well that's what the first doctor wanted to do
and i was about to book the procedure then i had another doctor that said wait don't do that yet
it might not be that and i'm like i don't know maybe it is not that okay if it is i'm gonna do
it if it isn't then i'm not gonna do it but it does work for a lot of people from what i've read
what i've been told if i have to do it i'm gonna do it swiggity swanky thanks for five dollars this
stream has really helped me i was in a dark place today both from overwork and stress from my
demanding boss but that kit fisto moment has literally cured me of that stress take care of
yourself first please understand that you make a difference and i'm lucky to have known you
the kid is still like slow i don't care if it's a meme it was funny thank you for the five
dollars swiggity swanky it was a great it was a great moment it was a great video
sorry joel but thanks to 250 i had a bout with a diagnosis confusion from 2015 to late 2016
i ended up having a rare thing called primary scleroserine cholangitis psc three years later
i'm one of the 400 people around the world on a study drug for my disease hope you get a
diagnosis soon and everything and getting everything all worked out before the better
holy shit that's rare yeah that's the thing about illnesses and diseases there's just so
many different conditions that you could have if you have a problem if you get like for instance
when i first went in for this problem i had a blood test oh your red counts fine your white counts
fine um your kidneys are fine your liver functions it looks perfect to me uh your cholesterol is a
little bit high but not nothing to be afraid of okay now what and then you start to it's not one
of those immediate things that people can just immediately find out and know then you go down
the rabbit hole where it's like okay so if my blood work is fine and i don't have like a tumor
or something let's spin the wheel of what the hell is your disease and i feel like i've been
in that revolving door for two years trying to figure it out can you please say penis penis
but surgery but thanks for the 250 i hope i get one soon too gay wizard thanks for the three bucks
raggo death knight thanks for the five dollars hey man good luck with everything hope everything
goes smoothly thank you one blondie thanks for five dollars germa 985 i think you are cool and
you're my favorite streamer i hope you have a good night just shorten to the point that's very just
thank you harry thanks for the six dollars harry 41 get better soon my man let's go to the emergency
robo cop body fund thank you thank all of you spiritual hog thanks with 300 bits because you
liked gotcha force you should check out custom robo for the game cube look at me it's right behind
me i own it and i'm going to be ready to play it when i come back eventually i've heard it's very
fun hey wembley t tv thanks for the 250 watching salty swamp on newgrounds even if you sound
younger you have not changed at all with your humor i'm sure i have i'm sure i've matured a little
you know i was actually talking to kim about this you don't really feel like an adult or feel like
you've grown up at all until until you you say a certain phrase out loud or you do a certain
thing that you just go i can't believe what what the fuck did that person say that's unbelievable
wait when i was like 17 18 19 i probably would have thought that was funny no i wouldn't have
not me not me i'm perfect well i'm sure i've everybody grows up everybody you know grows up
a little bit through the teens into their 20s i like to hope i've become a more mature person
in the last 20 years but i don't i i do agree with you though i don't think that i've
i don't think i've changed my approach i think that's still it's that's stayed pretty much the
same have you tried going 2 000 years into the future in search of a cure two that's a lot um
how about like 50 100 years 2 000 years i don't know if i want to step out of the time machine
the ground might be made out of liquid by then i'm not sure i want to do that
there might be a new animal that has eaten us all well i'm not doing that i'll i'm going tops 10
years in the future you go 10 years at a time don't go right to 2 000 are you out of your mind
just go five years take a look around go order a hot dog walk around some streets is it normal
okay take a look at what what companies have is there any new medical things or any new
human advancements okay this is pretty normal another five years do it again another five
once you start to see shit really fucking hit the fan i'm assuming it's probably going to be
somewhere around the one to two to three hundred year mark what that's when you start to go
backwards and then start to tell people how they can fix some of those issues like right now like
now now now no not all right well we don't we don't know that yet you don't know that
but what they won't listen they will if you can prove to them that you've seen it all you got to
do is just say like i don't know you could just you could you could prove that you're from the
future a million ways just find the hot new insane tv show that everybody's watching like a game of
thrones a cultural fucking phenomenon that millions of people care about and then watch
the series finale well i mean don't don't watch the game of thrones not not game of thrones
anyway that i poopoo that one was not very good uh you know watch the series finale memorize the
whole thing memorize the entire episode it might take you like a couple of months of really really
getting everybody's lines okay then during the airing of the show walk around and just say
every single line out loud and be like then pointing at yourself like see
no not spoil it i'm saying i'm saying like you're gonna get sued by the studio
just get it on a flash drive they would just think you stole the script what was the name
of that tv show where the guy got the next day's newspaper in the mail every day what a cool show
like that's such an interesting show what was it called there was a tv show that ran for a
little while it was called early edition this guy woke up every day and at his doorstep the next
day's paper was put in the morning on his doorstep and he had to figure out the hell he was gonna do
like what happened what happened tomorrow that i could maybe fix a great idea for a show thank
you for saying penis for me penis you get it twice see i'm a man of the people mod that guy
i don't actually do that though i don't know who that is hey vilemi thanks for the five dollars
wait hold up you hate anime i can't believe i have to cancel you jeremy i don't even i don't
fucking hate anime i watch it what do i watch it i watch maybe one a year or two yeah i watch it
i don't like love it but i don't why would i i watch it i watch it oh you like oh you do like
anime okay fine then name them all is that what you just said okay fine i'll do i do i don't know if
i can i could have pulled this from memory you wanted an alphabetical order um i don't know if
i could do that i didn't think of my uh a bridge to the starry skies a centaur's life a certain
magical index a certain scientific accelerator a certain scientific rail gun a dark rabbit
is seven lives a destructive god six and that's gonna be a lull in the sea a place further than
the universe a sister is all you need to talk to titan uh a town where you live a wind named
amnesia arachi insist back a a c a 13 territory inspection department a a celebration world
acceleration world infinity burst ace attorney ace of the diamond a action heroin sheer fruit
is that a real thing action heroin cheer fruits i feel like that's a really secure password
right like that's uh active raid actually i am wait okay the jig is up here dude he's got
anime knowledge all right let's get out here uh any nep subs here smug the stream made me laugh
harder than i have this whole summer hope you feel better and don't come back till you're 100
i won't i can promise you that hey ranger thanks for the 300 bits i love your work your visit
streams kept me entertained from the start of high school until now i'm a junior in college
you kept me going mentally when i was diagnosed with crones almost exactly a year ago
knowing you struggled with similar things and made it out stronger helped me regain focus
i'm moving into the work world soon so i don't know if i'll be able to keep up with the streams
ever probably will have to stick to highlights truly thanks so much
drones is in the same kind of family as colitis and this colitis proctitis crones
they're all in that irritable bowel disease so i i know what that's like thankfully mine's become
completely under control took me a little while though it did take a while i had random issues
with colitis bullshit for years but the one thing that i can tell you is eventually i figured it out
i got on the right treatment plan and it is completely under control completely it just
took a little while longer than i may have wanted but it's done now if you type your password it
shows as an asterisk look wait what does that work oh shit the fuck don't fucking whatever
oh fucking idiot fucking idiot hey alec keel thanks for the five dollars jerma hope you feel
well and get better rip to simon on my old dog that was my old dachshund years past thank you
so much for the five dollars hey edge wvvv thanks for the five dollars jerma i'm comfortable giving
you this money turn on smart clicks thank you i don't even have it installed i uninstalled it
not even possible i'm sorry a spectral pants thanks for five dollars been watching a long time
but you never really gave but never really give support like this take care of yourself jeremy
you've been my favorite streamer since i started watching and been watching since before twitch
thanks for your stuffs i know the future will be better peace peace to you as well rock esper
thanks for 250 hey man i just want to say anything i just wanted to say anything to you because i'm
getting kind of emotional here i've never been that active in the community i don't have time
to watch every video i wish i could participate more but i just have a lot of things going on
in life right now at all times completely understandable this stream is here solely for
entertainment it's for you to have something to watch it's for you to enjoy you're not obligated
to be here ever so don't worry but i've watched you for years your kung fu chroma key had me in
stitches and i've loved your stuff ever since you always make me smile without fail whether i'm
catching a stream or watching highlights thanks for everything well thank you rock esper thanks
for being part of this community that has grown exponentially over the last three or four years
on twitch predominantly thank you subbies well that's an old one that's all that's about four
that's a four-year-old reference right there i know what that is hey ginkgo ginkgo thanks for
the four dollars crit chance thanks for five dollars oh god that guy convinced me i can't
stop myself well thanks with five dollars sculprit thanks for ten dollars jerma this is going a while
back but i want you to know when you first uploaded your fire watch photos video i fell
asleep watching it so for a solid week i genuinely thought it was a weird fever dream that i had
was i don't know what video you're talking about fire watch like that game game you walk around and
pick up open up boxes and stuff i've never played it weird dream though man
a null dev thanks for four dollars love watching your full streams while doing homework just giving
back to the best streamer get well soon i'm honored to be your favorite streamer i i gotta
keep that title though that's what you guys don't understand you can't you can't just become
somebody's favorite streamer and then that's it okay i did it i'm done i want to continue to defend
the favorite streamer championship i'm gonna do whatever i can try to defend that title see if
i'm successful game flip thanks for five dollars hey man today would have been the last day of my
senior year i spent it sitting at home playing half-life alex custom maps that sounds really
fun just want to say that i've been watching you for almost six years i just want to say thank
you for all the laughs and all the memes for the past six years and to take care of yourself thank
you that sounds like a lot of fun half-life alex custom maps i feel like i know what that is but
i don't a la cool thanks for five dollars here's some more bits for your health i'd like to listen
to your streams while playing dark souls but sometimes i laugh which gets me killed make sure
you don't die to pinwheel everybody here doesn't like that but then you just blame it on me so then
i died to pinwheel because you died because of me while you were at pinwheel just blame it on me i'll
take the blame neon czd thanks for 300 bits say germa thanks for always providing great content
for all of us see you when you get back sticks renegade 250 what was your treatment for ibd
i have crones and had a bad flare for a year and a half ago it's in remission now but in case it
flares up again i was put on a it's gonna be too potentially tmi for a lot of people but whatever
we're talking medicine this is medical i was put on look listen if you don't you look you can't
have if you can't accept me at my worst then i'm trying to think something else besides obey your
thirst i was thinking about like go listen to fred durst but like i i've listened to fred durst's
music before the fan of his old songs and and so that wouldn't be accurate anyways i was prescribed
a uh thing that goes the other way doesn't go down goes up oh yes okay and i did that for a
while and i was on it for about two or three weeks and it just it absolutely destroyed it
and sometimes if i have a flare up which happens from time to time i go on a stint of this exact
medication because where i have all my problems is localized in the lower end of my colon
to reach talking about suppositories thank you somebody because if somebody was gonna say it
but i took a oral description for a long time it was a pill that i had to take like seven or
eight of them a day and it didn't do anything so we started finally tried to treat from the other
way and it worked perfectly but also the condition i have might not be in the same spot that you have
i was able to do it well with the other way because of where it sits the disease in the colon
so i was fortunate that i was able to do it that way there you go look i'm let i i'm a transparent
guy what do you want to say i this is real life they say this is real life right this is reality
uh we're talking reality and that's what we're talking it's all fun and games until you you go
to reality no but that's like that that sounds bad no no it's all fun and games usually but
sometimes we we're in reality we talk about real stuff there you go that's a better way to put that
a milk is stanton milk is stanton thanks to the thousand bits 1050 to be exact more than 10
dollars thank you feel better soon when you get back i've got some awesome news to share about
my life i hope i got some good news to share with you too we'll go back and forth with our good shit
looking forward to the cliffhanger a shitty view bot thanks for fun look at all this money
this has been an insane amount of money thank you shitty view bot for the five dollars take all the
time you need to think you're making the right choice here maybe this health issue is just
something small like bad gas but you made me laugh you did it bingo sunshine thanks to the five
dollars glad you're finally getting this shit sorted yeah me too bridal slits thanks for the
250 hope you feel better jerma i'm more of a recent fan but you've already made such a positive
impact these streams always make me happy and this community is basically the only place online
where i felt welcomed from the start thanks for being you love you and post stream you gotta love
the post stream and the pre-stream and the current stream thank you though uh burnt muffins gave
50 dollars and they just say i like you thank you burnt muffins for the 5000 bits for the 50
dollars i'm gonna just put that in my pocket and i'm gonna buy 50 mcchickens with it that's a lot
of money thank you seriously there's been a lot of it a ton of it an uncountable fucking amount
thanks guys there's even more reggie g thanks for the 40 dollars 4000 bits is just ridiculous
jerma i've been watching ads for two years to be able to do this and watching you since middle
school and will be a senior this year i've been around for too long been around a long time and
just want to say thanks for all the laughs and everything you do you've done so much for me in
the community hard to believe someone as amazing as you exists i don't know i don't know about that
i'm just a guy i don't know about that i appreciate it though hope the best for you
and your health take care thank you that's it's an incredibly high thing to say about somebody
but i just like to have fun and i'm kind of just a guy he's a sacrificial streamer thank you for
the 40 dollars that's watching ads for two years to be able to do that that's see that alone
is like that two years of ads for 40 bucks that's a long time and twitch what's going on with that
ad revenue two years 40 years of ads what's going on here but i can't believe someone would watch
two years worth of ads to give me money that's just i can't even comprehend that you understand
that's incomprehensible to me hey see when i get back at 100 hey see when i get back at 100
let's see what happens hey lying lying figure thanks for the free bucks i went through a period
of five or so years with undiagnosed health problems and while i was sick stuck in bed i
used to keep myself sane with streams like yours uh you've given up so much you've given us so much
take all the time you need thank you i'll be back and i look forward to not having to ever bring
this up ever fucking again you know how much i look forward to not having to have this conversation
ever again i look forward to not having to talk about this ever we just do we just do whatever
we do we do our thing i think it always was uh elemental penguin music thanks for the 10
community subs and edge wvvb thanks for five community subs princess kitty six six six
50 bucks 5 000 it's a lot of money there's been 50 50 50 100 200 200 50 50 50 50 50 100 200 200
300 300 i'm just gonna bring all this to the doctor's office and just drop it i'm gonna coin
bag all right okay all right can you let you fix me let's go it's a ton of money guys but princess
kitty they say peepee man that was 50 dollars to say peepee man thank you for the 5 000 bits
thank you peepee man 50 dollars cosmic bit thanks for three bucks please jeremy take my money
i will and i did thank you robo fussin thanks for the 250 sorry if it was already explained
but how much work went into the break dance joke in the green screen stream did you take classes
again nope i just decided to do it because my brain said do it that's all it took hey trans
scout thanks for the five dollars germa i'm going to bed soon and i'm gonna send this i want to drop
this card so it doesn't get lost take care small man also thank you for the caramel dancing it was
a moment of the century yeah looking at this card and people made a huge card with a ton of people
that were involved a while back when i was still having this problem and among other things so i
appreciate it mostly lost thanks for the 250 germa i'm really sad to hear how your chest caved in
after being exposed to 5g i tried to warn jeff bezos this would happen but he just didn't listen
anyway i just know that we all want i just know uh i imagine like what you mean by that is
like you have no profile picture on twitter and you tagged the wrong jeff bezos we have to do
something about his 5g jeff like this that's what i picture why didn't he listen to me anyway just
know that we all want you to be the best you can so get the problem taken care of so you can come
back feeling your best he just didn't listen to me i mean i wrote the tweet to him why didn't he
write back what's going on here i i talked to him why didn't he talk to me god bingo sunshine
thanks to the five dolls not to relitigate the new grounds posts but i notice that many of them
are from 2005 no one else came out in 2005 revenge of the sith hit fisto's death time is a flat circle
f in the chat revenge of the sith it's so weird because those movies that was the biggest deal in
human history some people say it was like the yankins or the mayans or the you know the the
ming dynasty would have no no no no it was when the first prequel movie came out that was the
biggest event in human history and that was the well that was the only thing that anyone talked
about that's boomer cringe i know why do you think i'm bringing it up that's unbelievable who cares
just a bunch of ships shooting at each other in the sky and the lasers with the little little laser
really more important than the ming dynasty than the than the inkins that's unbelievable
the you know the aztecs how many other nations can he name from the video game rise of nations
because that's the only reason why he's saying these hey uber morph point thanks for the 10 bucks
what would you do in the case of a trolley problem would you let a trolley kill five
people without interfering or would you change the track to make the choice to kill one person
um there are no trolleys where i live the statement doesn't make any sense to me
how big is this trolley is it big enough could i stop it with my bare hands you won't answer it
would you let the trolley so the trolley is just flying down the trolley track and i can pull a
lever for the trolley to run a guy over or let the trolley go forward and and and die or something
um well how can i be certain that i can change this track if i go over there and pull it it's
too heavy and what if it like snaps and if i what if i do it wrong i don't know how to do it
you just are i what if i can't do it that's the real question it will kill five if you don't
switch it okay no i have a solution so i'm in control of the track and i'm pulling the lever
so what i can do here is the the guy that's standing where the track is going to go i'm
just gonna scream yeah fucking right yeah i'm gonna pull it i'm gonna scream it's coming
it's coming it's coming i know i'm doing like the 15 year old screaming because you don't
want to wake up mom on xbox live i know hurry no i'd be like i'd be like dude there's a train
coming your way it's about to crash into you fuck you mocha joe it just turned into that
the person's tied down and unable to move well what cartoon universe am i in is there an old
timey piano playing in the background too do i talk and then does it cut to a black and white
screen with text on it it's a moral dilemma guys moral dilemmas don't have a right answer they're
all bad if i pull the lever he's dead if i let him go they're dead okay you're a bad person
hey uh i would pull the lever you're a bad person i would let those people just crash you're a bad
person okay so i i'm a bad person how about how about this instead of instead of answering the
question i'm just a bad fucking person that's all i need to say done i don't have to answer the
question now now you just know that i'm a bad person so and you would just let five people die
no i would yell hey hey dude pull that lever and then i would run hey dude i pull that lever
there's a moral dilemma going on it's just you it's all it's on you now pull the lever no make
a sign that says free coffee to a person that pulls the lever and then just get the fuck out
that's that's the real joker chaotic neutral way to do it so you would pull the lever no i wouldn't
i would write a note saying free coffee if you pull the lever but what i'm talking about is i'm
talking about the lever that's on your coffee maker they'd be like no i'm talking about the
lever that's on the coffee the coffee made that you pull what are you talking about holy shit are
you crazy are you out of your mind you're a bad person aren't you spending too much time on this
and i'm gonna stop it now hey nom no men see thanks for the three bucks i'm going through
a rough patch of the moment and your streams are a nice break from the world i want to say thank
you so much for your amazing streams man please take care of yourself thank you i plan on it i
wish you the best blueberry juice five dollars german you have to promise that you'll get better
not just try to get better remember it's like my favorite star wars character kit fisto always said
do or do not there is no try rip kit fisto i'm gonna do it i'm gonna do it i'm gonna do it
i can't promise you though because i i'm gonna do it i i promise that i'm gonna do it there you go
i'm gonna do it mad stormy killer thanks for the thousand bits i just want to say thank you for all
that you do and i'm really happy that you chose to sacrifice so much for twitch over everything
regarding your health goes well i don't even think i'm not even sure i would word it like that
just a guy that likes to make jokes and hang out shit about fucking companies it's kind of like a
shitty guy a shitty guy you know i just like to make jokes and hang out and like make talk
shit about companies i'm just kind of a bad guy i pull that lever we already went over it he's an
nda breaker when thank you garfield the monday killer thanks for the 250 when you were watching
the sonic rebuild thing you were singing to the music and then you shut it off right before my
name came on you noticed you did the sonic joke like right before garfield the monday killer showed
up on stream i fall the lever every time that's what i do a breezy meow thanks for the thousand
bits take it easy germ i hope you get well uh thank you for the ten dollars uh m well dough
thanks for the 250 i feel like thomas middleditch has been watching your stream because this is a
germa moment if i've ever seen one what wait he streams oh my god that's crazy i gotta hear this
i gotta fuck this in he's a funny bastard i'll tell you so look i love silicon valley it's like
i'm not a fan anymore because i'm the loser and i don't watch tv but i watched the first like four
seasons at least of that show that's a good that's a really good show like judge come on watch it
all right what do what do they do what am i on about we're talking about thomas middleditch
just did a stream and i didn't even know he streamed oh choice i did it i think i did it
i'm the most amazing boy can you believe i'm only 10 i'm only 10 i'm only 10
that's a strange thing to um brag about that is kind of a weird thing to brag about excuse me sir
yes i'm only 10 by the way uh i think his mic is being picked up by the webcam and not by the
microphone that he has plugged into the computer all right anyway here's your ice cream cone thank
you and scene he's really funny that i i i love i love his work i was a huge fan of silicon valley
the first like three or four seasons and then i'm a loser i don't watch tv anymore because i'm a
fucking loser we are getting to the end potion dweller thanks for 250 take care friend
i'm gonna miss your streams when you get back it'll be a good time hope it goes well
you too is that a lot of me too is like i agree yes me too yes yes i want to get better you want
me to get better i want to get better trust me i want to get better very much so hey rib-berry
rib-berry roria thanks for the 250 give us a thought project to chew on until you come back
i actually had one the other day what the hell was it oh god damn it it was an interesting
thought project that i had oh yeah why do cigarettes smell like raisins why do cigarettes
smell like raisins just like unsmoked cigarettes it's kind of strange why they don't yes they do
that's not false raisins yes they do yes they do they literally do yes they do yes they do
they do raisins it's true they literally don't they literally do they literally do this is
problematic no they literally do literally yes i'm going to use i'm going to say literally tobacco
is a vegetable okay oh all right i'm out of here i've only got like another five or six more bits
let's go another with fifty dollars from yeses online huge fucking money thank you yeses online
it's it's ridiculous the amounts of money that people give this stream praying for you chief
finally finished editing my greenscreen short film that i shot in vegas wait what hope you
can enjoy when you're at a at 100 smoke and sexy style levels of health well yeah looking forward
to it thanks with 50 though wembley ttv thanks for 250 also germa if you're not here it's my
birthday on the 6th of june what makes me laugh when i heard the birthday mixtape for the first
time the name of the person being said is my name so i had to put it on loop for a good few hours
during my laugh birthday my laugh birthday well happy birthday on june 6th wembley ttv if i'm not
here we'll see produces a sign thanks for five dollars after hearing about you via joel and
vinnie from vinesauce for years i finally checked you out last year and i'm so glad that i did
you give me some of the biggest laughs i've ever had seriously the amount of times you've helped
my mood from time to time not to mention others isn't exaggerated you really do make a lot of
people happy take care i can't wait to see you again i'll be back back better than ever
back i'm gonna have like a robot arm i'll do like a bit when i come back i'll have like a
fucking robot arm and i'll put a bunch of robot sounds like just trying to do and really yeah
that's gonna be a good one raid kit fisto no that's not a real streamer grove coaster thanks for
five dollars germa did you know that pac-man turns 40 today i don't have to be as old as pac-man
that's good to hear thanks to five dollars grove turret king thanks for the three bucks germa hope
this works i've been a fan since 2014 i'm still getting used to twitch i'm glad you're taking
this break hope you get well you know we love you and we know you'll come back at more than
100 only 100 let's shoot for 100 you don't want to go over 100 slug brain thanks for the five
dollars germo last year i went through a really rough time i was going through a breakup as well
as a best friend breakup as i lost my job and learned i was going to lose my apartment
holy shit man i'm so sorry to hear all that during that time your streams helped me through some
extremely rough nights i was just gonna ask i'm doing better now and i want you to be feeling
better too please get well and thanks for everything you do funny little man glad to hear it i was
hopefully you were gonna one of the sentences here would say that you were doing a little better
because that's a lot that's a lot of bad shit to happen i'm glad you're doing better thank you
slug brain i love the name too by the way speaks to me have fun on your stacom's vacation free pt
thanks for the 250 germa fuck you i hope you feel all good soon a lot of emotions in this one i
pretty uh thank you i think i'm gonna say shammy uh shimmy sham thanks for the five dollars germa
just gonna drop some love like the rest of chat big fan since tf2 as someone who had shingles at 25
they warned me about that muscular condition so it hit especially close to home that my favorite
streamer could be afflicted with it you deserve the best treatment and we will be here for you
when you're ready to come back love you yeah i i don't know i still don't know if that's the
right answer is but i can't just keep slowly punching away at it and but make no mistake
it's not like i have been ignoring this i've been going to the doctor every you know every month
every month once every once once every one or two months i am in and out of the doctor for this
but it's definitely it's not enough and i need to focus on it completely that's what i'm going to
hey nest sham nest shamatha thanks for the three bucks germa i don't know what it's like to have
ibd no i do i know what it's like to have ibd i have crowns and a myriad of undiagnosed things
going from doctor to doctor sucks but i know you will get through it you're an amazing person and
you always brighten up everyone's days thank you so much and get well soon yeah ibd is no joke
it is really really annoying it's hard to manage but once you get it managed you can usually keep
it pretty quiet please do kid fisto one more time no no i that'll ruin it for me it'll ruin it for
me we have a few more bits to do but i just want to say goodbye good night i'll be back hopefully
stronger than ever and with answers this time taking extended time off the stream and stuff
i don't like to do and i know i just moved and there was a bunch of time that i wasn't around
and this is just a lot is just but it has to be done and i got i've got to look i got to look to
the long term not the short term thank you all for your incredible support if you're taking off
you're taking off i'll see you when i see you which will be probably sooner than you think
it's not going to be a situation where i'm gone for more than a month or two that's not going to
happen i will be back within the next two to three weeks i'll be back let me finish the bits
we had five dollars from quinny thank you quinny for the five bucks hey friend not many things
make me genuinely stop being anxious and just hang out and laugh for a bit the gamer v portable
stream made me laugh in a way that i haven't felt since childhood and with everything going on with
my panic attacks getting worse that is everything thank you i appreciate you more than you 11 know
have a great night make sure you eat well and take care of yourself during the next few weeks
that was a wild one that was that was a a shitty microphone stream right i didn't i didn't i have a
um i had like a handheld mic didn't i tape a handheld mic to my mouth why don't i just
get a boom mic i don't know why i keep doing this to myself they're not even that expensive
it's not like oh wow that's expensive no just get one hey lachi thanks for five bucks germa i
started watching when i was recovering from asthma attacks the first streams i watched were you
super mario sunshine ones and i haven't missed one since that's pretty recent so i'm a noob
shaking my head uh you're a wonderful person and i hope whatever is messing you up gets sorted out
soon you're doing what you're doing you make so many people happy with your content welcome glad
you found us raid raid raid don't worry i will i will i will okay we're gonna raid all right all
right all right thank you lachi welcome to the stream well relatively welcome thanks for the
five bucks hope you kiss hope you stick around and keep watching hey a friendly spider thanks
for the sub community sub actually i just want to say friendly spider five community subs from any
nep subs here 15 dollars from ajax the mediocre i hope you take your time resting i will
oblivio thanks with 250 germa maybe 100 is too much come back when you're at 98.5
percent not a bad idea zex thanks for the five bucks thanks for all the streams can't wait to
have you back at 100 i'll be back rooting kai rep terra thanks for the three bucks just now
realized i didn't meet the bid amount to be read i did a funny joke with my previous message but
i'm too lazy to type it again sorry feel better i can tell you what the text i wrote at the top
means if you want uh this is one piece this assesses you just spoil the whole is this this
is like a spoiler placemat is this a spoiler like denny's placemat of the whole entire show
i'm gonna show this but be aware you this is a fucking placemat of spoilers for the show one
piece are you ready here it comes is this what is this it goes to the only people that have watched
the show uh you spoiled this is uh this is every character that this is every character that lives
or dies on the show okay what they said what's the what's the text mean at the top they said i'll
read it to you what is it the cover of the books oh whatever thanks for three bucks hey kitty lot
thanks three bucks germa i'm very sad to hear that you were injured and they're sending you
to the glue factory joking aside i hope the doc helps you i've only been watching a couple years
but your stream is genuinely a force for good also my robot dog says hi hello robot dog
thanks for the three bucks kitty worm club 250 thanks for the two dollars and 50 cents i had a
dream that on stream one day you explained that in real life you're a psycho and a sick freak
and that off stream you watch non-stop horror movies horror games and true crime documentaries
and the violence makes you feel nothing you said that in order to seem funny and not morbid on
stream you warm up beforehand by watching classic stand-up comedy and quoting the jokes word for
words they're delivered pretending you're the one on stage why am i such a weirdo forever why am i
such a weird scary guy nobody ever has dreams where i work in a soup kitchen you know where
are the dreams of me working at the animal shelter and saying please and thank you no no this guy's
just a sicko and he like buries bodies in his basement they're dreams of betrayal
thanks to the 250 and the wicked messed up dream hey keith king crimson thanks for the 250 love
you germa get well i'm gonna try to hey king sherbert thanks for five dollars germa do you
like larry david you guys are kind of similar i love larry david he's like my favorite person in
the world larry david is like in my favorite comedian probably he's like i think he's one
of the most smart one of the most intelligent funny i think he's great he's great he's fantastic
top five comedy writers and comedy actors done if you've never seen curb your enthusiasm
the first the first like four or five episodes you're gonna be like this is dumb it's just a
couple of fucking old guys yelling at each other but trust me get through season one and season
two and into season three four five and six season seven is the best season i know so what about
season six none of season seven is the best curb season if you disagree i'm sorry i'm not sure what
it feels like to be wrong they're all good i'm kidding what an ego only watch season seven no
no watch them all they're all good they're all okay if season seven is a 9.8 then like season
six is like a 9.6 they're all at least 9.3 all of them i do i think it's great opster narwhal
thanks for three dollars and 48 cents just saw that you enabled germa please which is good thing
good timing since i probably would have deleted it since i need more bttv slots here's some money
thanks but please i would cry for real if you enabled this emote since you say so much stuff
that confuses chat all right i just did i just all right it's there remember what yeah it makes
sense hey pretend dear thanks for the five community subs all lulu thanks for 300 bits
thank you say feel better soon appreciate it sfc 100 thanks for the five dollars germa hope this
reaches you get well soon anyway i had a dream about you buying a submarine and making an amusement
park the part i saw in the dream looked like my old high school library and it was really raggedy
but you were really trying so hey at least you weren't terrifying see you on the horizon thank
god yes i did i enabled i just did refresh aphan thanks for 250 i had a dream last night that you
are a professor in college and you got mad at the class because we didn't do your homework on
sausages pigeon thanks for the 250 rank these bill burr dave chapelle and larry david oh no
oh no that's i don't know if i can do that oh man oh no i think uh i love bill burr he's so
funny he's one of the most off-the-cuff witty people that i've ever watched but he's probably
three i mean the i i i comedian tier list it's tough though dave chapelle is
oh i was such a huge fan of dave chapelle during chapelle show
larry david though yeah all right can they be tied no they can't no ties
larry david larry larry david dave chapelle bill burr and the the difference between larry
david and dave chapelle is not even like 0.2 0.2 percent change clap clap clap you've passed the
test what how is that a test i i love dave chapelle there she feels fucking hilarious
he's just one of those just legendary comedians that i loved bell show she felt that this awesome
thing where at the end at the end i'm also at the end of streams uh the end of his stream
he would bring on musicians and they would do a musical number for every single show right they
would they would do either a video or uh in person sometimes right he always had like a musical guest
that was just on the show and that was kind of unheard of something that wasn't like the jay leno
tonight show because the format was was you know pre-recorded it was a scripted show but it was
still cool oh this guy's outro is so long he's fucked well this one's an exception considering
i'm not gonna be around but i'll see you later pigeon thanks for 250 more thank you have some
more always nice to see thank you and then you foley gee thanks for five dollars i had a dream
a while ago where i watched you escape from prison anyway xoxo thank you thank you everybody for the
absurd amount of money it was like it was how it was thousands of dollars
thousands of fucking dollars what so many messages it's like i can't even comprehend it thank you
guys i'm gonna get better i'll be back i'm gonna do this all this medical shit and see if i can
get this taken care of once and for all and not have to ever talk about it again we are going to
raid vinny he is live currently 10 11 12 1 Vinny usually streams pretty late so it's a good choice
and i will see you guys when i see you over the next couple of weeks between
anywhere from 10 to 20 days somewhere between that range i hope i come back and i hope i'm
better i hope i can tell you that good night see you soon if you weren't here but before
the second channel is going to get a monster amount of content while i'm gone
we're bringing on a bunch of new editors the backlog is going to get ripped through completely
they're going to chew through all those old streams you might not it's you're going to see
probably like one to two videos a day the next few weeks i'm not sure when that's going to start
but it's going to start fairly soon thank you everybody good night take care of yourselves
let's raid vinny see you soon thanks again