Let's see if I can do it with Samson. All fingers are pointing to no. So, let's go guys.
So, wait, what? Why do I have a spirit heart? I'm not exactly sure why that happened. Envy right
off the bat. But okay, so Samson, the way Samson works, every time you hit an enemy, you get
stronger tiers. Like every five to 10 hits or something like that, you get stronger. See how
I'm turning red? I got like a pink kind of tinge to my body right now. It means I'm doing a little
bit more damage. Every hit. But as you can tell, he has only one heart, so it's just like, nope,
you're gonna die. Why is Envy in like the first room and the first level? That's just a lot of
malarkey, if you ask me. Oh my god, why is this guy blue? That guy's like a grape. Hello from
Alabama. Hello from Boston. City of Boston. Well, I can't believe I didn't get a hit. City of hot dogs,
bright lights, and a Boston Red Sox. Well, that didn't take forever. Is it every kill? Okay,
it's every kill then. So, he can be pretty, if you get a lot of HP up, he can be pretty powerful.
But of course, we're in the spider room, so I'm probably gonna die like right now.
Oh god, this is the worst. If I die in this room, I swear I should have already been dead,
to be honest. I don't know where that spirit heart even came from. I should be dead right now.
But I'm gonna take it to stride. You know what, I got a second chance. It's time to do this thing.
All right, come on. Come on, you like cupcake. You meat cupcake. Let's get that item. Have I
met the scout in Boston? Yeah, I see him like riding his bike all the time.
He's always like riding around wicked fast, like a psycho.
Oh, so he got buffed. That's what it is. All right. Well, what about Judas? I mean,
so would you, why would you ever play as Judas now? Isn't Judas have one heart or does he have two?
Because I mean, if that's a buff, I can't think of a reason why you would ever play
as anybody else. If you go over Judas, at least. Come on, blow up the secret room.
Okay, I don't think I'm gonna make it. I don't think I'm gonna do this. Yep, it's,
it's widow. I don't think I'm gonna do this, guys. I might have to start this over again.
Oh no, no way. No way. Not a chance. Not a chance. We're gonna reach right. Okay. All right,
hopefully I don't run into the spider boss again. I don't think I will because we're not in the
spider catacomb place right now. Oh, don't worry, I'm not gonna rage. Not gonna rage you yet.
Homing shots. Good, good, good, good, good. Hey, it's always good to get your Binding of Isaac
deaths out of the way in the very beginning. Especially when you play on the stupid spider
level. That's way too hot. I think the spider level shouldn't be able, like, to spawn until,
like, the second, at least the second or third run. Because if you're playing as a character
like this, it's, there's no way you're gonna beat that spider boss with one heart. There's no way.
I mean, I guess you could if you were really good.
All right, doing much better. Let's continue down here.
Yeah, I was a little late today to the stream. And that's because I actually went out last night
for the first time in a very long time. And I got a little under the weather, as they say.
Heh. And I woke up a little too late. But, hmm, should I get the key and get the crate?
Why am I saying crate? Too many games do crates lately. No, we're not gonna do that yet.
I don't think it's worth it. Yeah, unless you're, like, a character like Kane or,
even Isaac can probably do it, but all the other, oh, Magdalen can, you can do with Magdalen.
Let's keep going this way. Get out of here, you bugs. Whoa, didn't even see that guy. That guy
came out of nowhere. I didn't even check my rearview mirror. How could you ever delete
the binding of Isaac? This game is too good. Everything about this game is good. Except
there's one bad part about this game. It has to end. Like, when you're playing, it has to be,
like, over. Ooh, ace of spades. The ace of spades. No, not doing that. Not with Samson.
Oh, let me walk over the spikes. That's a great idea. Oh, I want that chest. But I don't want
that chest, because it might be something not worth it. Decisions, decisions. Oh, you know what?
Yolo, you only live once. Let's do it. I'm opening this chest. All right, give me something good.
Oh, yeah. That was so worth it. Oh, well, you know what? You gotta take risks sometimes.
It's not gonna pay off sometimes, apparently. All right, let's go whoop this guy's butt.
All right, Mastro. Oh, two Mastros. That's not ever a good thing. And you gotta fight two of
the same Mastro. Come on, Burger Boy. Come on, Burger Boy. Oh, come on. Why did it have to be
Monstros? They're just, they're so happy. I feel like these guys aren't even really trying to hurt
me. They're just trying to like play. You look at them, they're just like, hey, I just want to
jump and throw up. Will one of them just go away? Just go away. Come on. Oh, my God, Samson, you
bastard. Why is this still two? Okay, geez, it took to like 10% health to get one of these
bastards out of here. Okay, we're good to go. Two hearts. We got it. Do I have any bombs?
I do not have any bombs, so I gotta just go. Who is Burger Boy, really? Burger Boy is one, oh,
Curse of Darkness. This is, ugh. Burger Boy is one of my real life good friends. And he's also
crazy. But that's good. That's like a good quality. Because we're all crazy.
But Burger Boy is also the egg. And there's a, uh, might be a special video coming soon.
Coming soon. Not like tomorrow, not like next week. But there might be the return of the egg.
That's the only thing I'm going to say. The egg. Best worst character ever.
All right, what's this? The Emperor. All right. Forget what you do, but that's all right.
You know, I'm actually one of those people that really liked Meet the Pyro.
A lot of people liked it, but a lot of people really didn't like it either.
I'll tell you one thing, though. I think Meet the Pyro was too short. If there's one complaint I
have about Meet the Pyro, it was too short. Because, I mean, they gave us Meet the Spy,
which was like three and a half minutes. Then they gave us Meet the Medic, which was like
four minutes. And then it's like, oh man, they're getting crazier and crazier. Like,
more cinematic and more cinematic as they go. And then Meet the Pyro was like two minutes and
22 seconds. That's the only complaint I have. Now I teleport you to the boss room. Good to know.
Good to know. Am I? All right, I must be crazy. I have another spirit heart. Did I walk over one
and just not even pay attention? Or do you, every time you kill like 20 people at Samson,
you get a spirit heart? Maybe I'm just crazy. But I mean, after the interview, I think they
could have done the interview stuff a little bit longer. You know, when the spy's like,
what kind of inhumane, just horrible, disgusting thoughts, or whatever he says.
If they fleshed that out a little bit more, maybe get a couple more characters,
like get the sniper to say some stuff. Let's do it. I'm not going in that room.
They blew the budget on the special effects. Get away from me. This guy's gonna be hard to kill
with this spoon. It's gonna, oh no, it's gonna like attack the things around him and not him.
It's all right. I can wait it out. I'm also glad that the Pyro's gender is a secret to the couple
of you guys that are saying that right now. I don't know. When you have a mystery like that,
you got to keep it a mystery. It's just like when you read a book,
right? If I read a book, and it's like, you don't know what the character looks like,
you get to make up your own kind of version of the character. Because everybody has their own Pyro.
I mean, and I'll bring up a friend of mine, Boo. You guys know Boo. Boo has like the best
perfect description of the Pyro. It's just like a cute, just like cuddly little entity that runs
around and just has fun. Like that there is no man or woman. It's just the Pyro. I think that's
perfect. The Pyro is not a man or a woman. It is a thing. It's just a mindset. It's an entity. Okay,
I'm absolutely not doing either of those. Ew, who reads books? I not miss. I gotta go. I gotta go
down. I would use the Source Filmmaker if I had any idea how to use it. The Source Filmmaker is
one of those things where you really have to sit down and like play with it and be good with it and
learn. And artistically, I was never really like an art student. I mean, I can, I went to school for
film. I could probably use it. I could probably like do like shots with it and stuff. But once
you get to the animation part of things, there's no way I would ever know what to do with that
program. Because I've tried Garry's mod, even just like do little dumb animations and little
dumb things in Garry's mod. And they always end up as complete atrocities. Like complete,
like just horrible things. Like, oh, I want to get like the heavy to smile and point his finger.
And he just ends up going like, oh, get it. Like his hand comes up. I'm just not good with art.
Wish I was though. Mini greed. Oh no, please don't kill me. Wow. Wow. I was going to say it.
There's no way I'm that lucky to dodge like five of the cut. Oh my God. Now I'm just being an idiot.
It's these stupid things that are in the way. Supposed to have homing shots. Come on now.
Oh, I hate epic hack. I absolutely hate epic hack, but I'm going to take it. I really don't
like epic hack and it's probably going to kill me. But you know what? I'm going to take it.
Let's see if I can find the secret room. Is this a full heart up here? Okay, there's two. Good to know.
Oh no, no, no, it's homing too. Oh my God, I forgot about that. Oh man, this is bad. This is
really bad. This is really bad. I'm going to kill myself with this. Guaranteed because it's homing.
Oh no. Oh no. I'm blowing this up. Cool. Yeah, this is definitely a run that is in the tank,
in my opinion. There's just no way I'm going to do this because it's homing. I will open you though.
Oh, it's over. Oh, and it's over. I'm getting out of here. I can't believe I survived that.
The only thing this is going to be good for is bosses. That's it. Barely, barely that.
Boom. What did I have for dinner last night? I think I had a chicken sandwich.
Pretty sure. Oh wow. I can't believe I got hit by that.
Hmm. This is taking so much longer because I have to keep going back and healing myself.
No super secret room there. Super secret room is probably all the way to the right,
if there is one here. Oh God. Super wrath, huh? I don't think I've never faced super wrath.
Oh no, he does not do that. He does troll bombs, like the big ones that follow you.
I guess it doesn't really matter because he's dead. Blast damage. Does blast damage incorporate
epic hack shots? Oh, I hope so. Why am I not watching the soccer finals? I'm not a big soccer
guy. I never really was. I grew up on baseball. Baseball is my thing. Versus peep. Oh, well,
this might be like good. Maybe I'll like kill him easily with this epic hack. Oh God. Yeah,
I'm gonna be good. I'll be good to go. Epic hack. Oh God. Boink. I'll take the tears up,
even though I don't really want it. And let's go. Yeah, I'm definitely dead soon. I am absolutely
dead soon. Oh, screw you. You aren't getting any of my hearts. You aren't getting my heart.
Actually, that's not that bad as long as you stay away from it. Favorite baseball team is the Boston
Red Sox. I live in Boston, so I don't live in Boston. I live right next to it. We'll put it
that way. Boing. Get smashed. Oh, no. Oh, no. No. I can't shoot this. Come on. Oh, come on.
This is the worst. This is the worst. This is the worst thing. Ah. What's this? Poison bombs. Cool.
Well, I think this is the end of Sampson. Let's find out. Unless I get a heart right here. The sun.
Okay. I'm gonna stay alive. What's in this next room? Goodbye. Sorry. I was not dealing with that.
Not a chance. I'm probably not gonna do a GTA 4 let's play or a walkthrough. GTA 5, though.
I will probably do a some type of walkthrough. Maybe a let's play or something, because I love
GTA games so much. I can't shoot that. Go in here. Of course it's greed. Wilds wouldn't be anybody
else but greed. At least it's a steam sale. Mike Lowell is my favorite Red Sox player of all time.
Mike Lowell. Epic hack. You are the worst. Oh, I want that. It's good for those guys. I will
say that for sure. Okay. No. No. No. No. Get away. Good. I'm stuck. Get. I can't hit these bugs.
Strike one. Strike two. Strike three. Strike four. Okay. There we go. All right, boss. I am
shocked that I've gotten this far. I am like legitimately shocked. You know, we're gonna do
this. Ready? Hey, what's going on? What's going on, buddy? How you doing? You want like some of my
hots? Eat this! I missed. Eat this! Run. Who's talking to me? I'm getting tweets all over the place.
All right, let's fight this guy. Oh, fantastic. Well, it was nice knowing you guys. I'm sure I'll
be like in the afterlife as Samson. Maybe. Maybe not. Maybe not. Wow. All right. I'll take that.
I'll take a swift victory. Oh, I want. Mommy. Curse of the labyrinth. That's exactly what I wanted.
That's. I'm glad. Oh, no. No, boy. Oh, my god. Oh, my god. Oh, my god. I can't even. I can't even
handle this right now. Yeah. Well, now it. Now the jig is up. Unless I pull off some real, real
ridiculous moves. I am not doing this. Oh, bombs are key. I actually would rather have that. Thank
you. This could be the end right here. I'm going to. I'm going to probably say time to be quiet.
Go to try hard mode and not scream when I die, because that's probably what I'm going to do.
All right. OK. As long as you take it slow and steady.
Just like the turtle. You don't got to be. You don't got to be the hare. OK, but now. Oh, no.
Oh. All right. It hurts every time playing this game. I might want to just go. I don't know.
I don't know. I have one heart now. I'll die. I need more stuff. That's not what I needed.
I'm afraid to even attempt to get in here. Oh, my. You know, it was going to happen.
I just. I got it. I got it over with. I got over with on purpose.
How come that killed me, by the way? I thought it only did. I thought it only did
one half heart. Why did I die from that? Oh, whatever. Let's just go straight up,
Isaac. Isaac never did me wrong. Samson, you're too hard with your no hearts. I'm going to take
this game by the horns with Isaac. Tack fly. That's a good start. I'm going to beat this right
now. You see, that just made me so sad that I'm going to beat this now. The key. All right. All
right. OK. Come on, flies. What do you got against Isaac? I'm speaking about those spikes again.
I swear that I mean, I had one heart. Why would it do more than one heart worth of damage?
Maybe they changed it or maybe I'm just not smart enough to understand. Oh, yeah. Keep throwing
your bugs at me and then you run them over yourself. Hi, Zach. Hi, Zach. Actually, I'd rather
stay up here keeping from moving around so much. Whoa. Wow. There you go. Kill your own dudes.
That's what I like to say. Now, that's what I like to say, son. Not that, though. Get away.
Whoa. Dodging bullets here. You can hit me. You can do better than that. Oh, you could do better
than that. Cuban meat. Jump. I'm smoking this game. I'm going to smoke this whole game right now
as the title character as Isaac. Screw that thing. I don't want it. I wish they would come out with
Binding of Isaac 2 and have it be like not single player. Have it be you can have more than one or
two people in the game. Oh, probably two. More than more than two would be ridiculous.
All right, let's go. Cupcake. You velvet cupcake batter. Speed and range up. And I look like a
freaking psycho. Yeah. Nickel. All right. Got a nickel. Good to go. Let's go, you uncooked chicken.
You can't kill me. I think Abu was telling me that he 100% of this game, which like that's
incredible. What a boss. It's not an easy feat to complete like everything in this game.
Really isn't. See, I use it on the secret room, which is probably right here.
Well, apparently it wasn't right there. Probably was down this hall somewhere.
But you know, I can take it. Whatever. My favorite holiday is definitely
Halloween. I love Halloween more than anything. It's the only time of the year where you are
allowed to be a freak show and like nobody cares or gets mad. Think of any other night
the entire year where you are allowed to hang out your car window as the Joker and scream and laugh
at random like old people on the street. When can you do that? And people will just go, oh,
he's just being fun. There's not another time in the world where you can do that.
Oh, you're going to curve your bullets too, huh? Curve the bullets. Angelina Jolie. That's every
day for me, mad killer. Or the Dark Knight premiere. I guess that is the situation where
you couldn't do that. Oh, welcome to the Dark Knight premiere. Oh, okay. You can be the Joker
and like scream at people. That's awesome. Man, I kind of feel like an ice cream cone right now.
I feel like a big ice cream cone. Oh, these guys aren't that bad. I can handle these guys.
I can handle these two dudes. Oh, if you're wondering if someone was asking about Team Fortress
and how come I'm not streaming it or anything, I'm still waiting for a fix. And I think
there's a beta driver right now for the 670 or the 600 series in general. I'm going to download that
and try it. It's just I didn't want to spend like an hour or two troubleshooting when I was already
like an hour late to the stream anyways. So next week we will see what happens with that.
But for right now, Larry Jr., you're dead and you're not coming back as much as you want to.
I'm sorry. As much as you want to be in your like fruit punch pool.
See, this is looking more and more like a clean run every single time.
Let's go. Four hearts, full. I got no Samsonite to worry about. You need to die. Man, you are a
persistent son of a... I kept hitting that guy in the face and he just kept going like...
He's like, get out of my face, man. Get out of my face. Do I play MMOs? Absolutely. I played World
of Warcraft for over six years. I had multiple max level characters. My main was a warlock. Well,
actually let me rephrase that. Warrior. Then it was a priest and then it was a warlock and my
main was the warlock for the most amount of time. But I had a priest, warrior, warlock, druid. God,
I had everything in that game. But then they did a bunch of weird changes. I don't know why.
They did a lot of changes. Oh, it's lagging right now? Stream's lagging? What's going on here?
Are we good? I hope so. It just popped up. Everybody was like, lag, lag, lag.
Ah! Like my stream is on fire right now. So apparently my stream is like in flames.
Try refreshing it. Try refreshing it up. Let's see. Hold on. Let's see. Just to make sure I...
Because a lot of you guys were just saying that it was lagging. Let's take a look here.
Look at my stream health to make sure it's okay. Events. I have control room. Because it'll tell
you. It'll be like, oh, your stream is lagging like crazy. It says it's okay.
So it seems better now. All right. That's good. That's a good thing. All right. Well,
I apologize about that. Sorry. Somebody just like rolled over and like tripped over my stream
cord at YouTube somewhere. And then I had to plug it back in real quick. Somebody was eating a
sandwich and they just like tripped and ripped out my stream cord.
If you're still getting the lag, try and refresh. Sometimes that fixes it.
Shouldn't be happening to begin with though. My favorite superhero is...
Ah, that is a tough question because there are a lot. There are a lot that I could say.
Oh my god, this room is full of bugs.
Man, I don't want to say like, oh, Batman, because it really isn't Batman. Or Superman. Or...
What is his name? I should be able to answer this question in three seconds. I don't know why I
can't answer this. Superhero. Superhero. Oh, Deadpool. Deadpool. There you go. Probably
Deadpool. Deadpool or Venom. That took me a long time to say that. Oh, I need more coins.
ASAP. I'm going to buy this bomb and try to blow up the secret room. See if it's right here.
But Venom is just such a cool character. I love the way like he is. He just is Venom.
No, that was the wrong place. It was up top. All right, whatever. Let's a go.
Gertie. I actually like facing Gertie. I can handle him. I can handle Gertie. Gertie, come on.
Dodge. Whoa, whoa, whoa. I did not dodge that right at all. There we go. Oh, you're too like
bubbles of puke. Gotta get rid of those bubbles of puke. I know in Deadpool, because the Deadpool
comics, if you ever read them, he is insane. He breaks the fourth wall all the time. He'll
just be like, hey, reader, if you want to like skip this part, go ahead and like go to page 14.
This part's like pretty boring. I just talked to some broad for like five minutes. I love how
much he breaks the fourth wall in the Deadpool comics. It's so funny. All right, Gertie,
that's just about enough of you and your like big smelly body. Oh, come on. You're gonna do
me like that, Gertie. I keep thinking that eye is not mine and that happens every time.
Do it again. Come on, do it again. I dare you. I dare you. Oh, he missed. You're stupid.
Go. The caves. Welcome to the caves. But down here, you never see the light of day again.
And you almost die from walking into things. What you know, Isaac. I actually, when Vindictus
first came out, I was, it's free to play, right? I actually was going to download that and I just
forgot to do it. So thank you for reminding me because I'm going to go download Vindictus
like right after the stream is done. That's the one where it's like an MMO, but it's like a hack
and slash kind of like third person. That's the right game I'm thinking of, right? I'll take that
money. Go ahead, blow up. I'll take that money. It's going here. Now, what do you have for me?
If you don't have, if I don't win this on the first time, you are dying just to let you know.
All right. I know you heard me. Do you want to stay alive? We'll find out.
Oh, it looks like somebody wants to get blown up. No, please. No, please. Yeah. Couldn't even
finish your sentence. And that's enough of that. Yeah. Definitely downloading Vindictus
at the end of this stream. And I'm going to play it a bunch. Oh, you turned into like a little
piece of jello. I feel bad for you. I'm doing it. No, it wasn't worth it for like the seventh time
in a row. It's never worth it. Me and MLC Stealth played DC Universe for a little while.
We played for like a few hours at least. A few. Oh, I'm cracking my back. Hours at least. Of
course it's greed. Of course it's greed. Why would it be anybody else besides greed? Get him, eyeball.
Show him that. So I just realized something. I am shooting a red tier every other tier. Is that
because my eye came out? Yeah, it has to be, right? Greed, you bastard. Why don't you go bottle like
Edward Elric? Like, leave me alone. Never mind. You dropped a lot of money. I like you, now.
What am I doing standing there? I need to be in the corner. I need to be in the rear view. There
we go. Don't even need to do that. Uh oh, it's super toothless Joe, whatever his name is.
These guys freak me out. These guys are scary. I've had all the Warhammer games for a pretty long
time. If you are a fan of RTS, I would highly recommend you get the original Dawn of War.
I wasn't a fan of Dawn of War 2. I'm not gonna lie. I thought Dawn of War 2 was a good game,
but I don't think it was nearly as good as Dawn of War 1. Just quit following me, dude. Come on.
Come right here. Come on. Come on. Come on. I've got like candy and soda and chips. You know what?
You're not gonna come down, so I'm just gonna kill you. We're gonna have a party down there,
but you like didn't feel like coming. That makes me sad. How much fur? There we go. There it is.
Item room is all the way over there. After this, I'm gonna have to go do that. Get to the item room.
After all these like toothless freaks. There we go. Speaking of Left 4 Dead 2,
someone just said Left 4 Dead 2. Didn't they come out with a new map? Coldstream?
Or Coldland or something? Because whatever it is, I'm definitely gonna be playing a lot of that, too.
Fork. Isaac's Fork. Okay. Oh, if you're gonna come to the party, you gotta bring like salsa.
You gotta bring dip, chips, soda, burger patties, frozen hot dogs,
a love for life, and a good attitude. That's the only way you're allowed my party.
You sack of marbles. Get out of here. Open. Open. Now open again. I'm the dentist,
and your teeth need a real cleaning.
Where's this item room? God, such a big level. This is dumb. Oh my goodness, will you just...
I need to damage up something because it's taking forever to kill any of these things.
Open. Open. Yeah, once it comes out, I'll stream Left 4 Dead 2. Once the new map comes out. Open.
Come on. I didn't even kill him. My little buddy did. Ooh, little Chad. He's so happy.
Hi, I'm Bill Chad. I'm gonna drop hearts for you. Thanks, little Chad. No problem. So little Chad,
you're gonna like tell me your life story. Okay, so I grew up in the sewer and then I pooped out
hearts. That's a touching story, Chad. Thank you. Now give me your hearts before I kill myself
because I'm pretending to be two people. Okay. Well, that's a good way to lose three hearts.
Do a little Chad movie. Pills here. No, no. That's the worst. That's the last thing I wanted.
There is a circus following me right now. Look at this.
It's like all I need now is a brother Bobby and like more attack flies and I'll be all set.
Hopefully I don't die. Oh, Chad. Oh, no. Why is he so weak? Or did it? Was that my...
What just even hurt him? I didn't do that. Hopefully he doesn't kill me. All right. Little
Chad and big Chad. This is like very surreal. He's fighting his like daddy right now. This is like
weird. Whose side are you on, son? I stand on the side of light. What's in here? I'm actually kind
of tempted to take this because I could use the spirit hearts. I think I'm going to take that.
I really think I'm going to take this right now. Oh, I'm going to take it. I'm going to take it.
I took it. Thank you. It was a decision I had to make and I made it. I needed it. Oh, God.
I'm like, why is it crashing? What? What? Oh, for a second there, I thought the game was just
crashed and done. I was just about to freak out. Did my stream die? We're still streaming,
right? Okay. You guys saw that. It was just like, you know what? We might even do it again
at some point if I need it. Oh, pro dodges right there. Pro dodging. I wish there wasn't all these
obstacles in the way so I could hit them. Oh, that was, that thing was blocking it. That was why.
Give me this. Give me that. And I'm going to blow this up for sure. Good position now. Too bad I have
stupid curse of the labyrinth. Whatever this dumb thing does. Makes it so I can't see anything.
Oh, I want to kill at least mom. I want to kill mom. That big fat...
Ugh. There we go. Let's go down. I just did this room, man. I just did this room. Okay,
I'm going the other way. I'm going around. Ugh. There's too much stuff blocking you for me to
shoot you. See, if I didn't take that guppy's hand and I didn't use it, I probably would be dead right
now. Because I've been hit at least at least five or six times. Oh, this is bad. Oh, this is really
bad. Especially this room. Don't spawn anymore. No. No. Get... Ugh. God. I hate spiders. Not only
in real life, but in fake life too. It's a good thing to take. Guppy. Die. Oh, you hairy...
This is gonna be so hard. I'm just gonna stay in the corner. No sense going out there and
meeting my demise like that. Get out of here. Oh, no. Corner's a bad move.
There has to be this many things in this room. Get out of here, you ba-bomb.
There's so many of these little guys that shoot. I hate those ones. I actually just
tried the Samson run. Didn't really work out too well. I got to, like, what, the third or fourth
run when I died? Ugh. I don't want any of your, like, cream cheese. Get out of here. This is the
binding of Isaac. Wrath of the Lamb. DLC. And this is me getting stuck and not being able to... Oh,
my God. I had to use it. I had to do that. You guys all saw it. I had to do that. I might even
have to do it again. I'm gonna have to do it again. I'm gonna have to do it again. I'm probably
gonna have to do it again. Oh, my God. I'm gonna have to do it again. Oh, my God. Oh, my God. No.
There's nowhere for me to go. Oh, there was nowhere for me to go. Oh, my God. Ugh. There was
literally nothing I could do right there besides just get hit a million times. Oh, now it is
definitely over. Oh, these... Come on. Okay, well, that's gonna be the end of this run. Hopefully,
you enjoyed this. Have fun in whatever you're gonna do and however you... What path you take
in your life. I'm silent. God. Ugh. That was the worst possible thing that could have happened.
Nowhere to run. Nowhere to hide. Nowhere to go. They were, like, engulfing me.
Ugh. Gosh, darn it. Well, that's... So now you know what's gonna happen is grandpa's gonna play as
question mark, question mark, question mark, and that's gonna be the end of the stream.
So I'm gonna go get grandpa. Grandpa can come in and he'll sit down. He'll talk about how he loves
this game and we'll see what happens. Hey, grandpa. Hey, you gotta get down here. You gotta play Binding
of Isaac right now. No, come... Yeah, come down. You're scaring the dog. Just come down. Okay,
let me just get over here. What the hell is this game? What game is this? Binding of Isaac.
What's that? Just play it. Just sit down and play. Okay, I'll sit down right here. There we go.
Okay. Hello. Let's play Binding of Isaac. What? Did I just eat shit? What the hell was that?
All right, so what are the controls in this game? Up, down, left, right. Okay, so here we go. Up,
down, left, right. Okay, good. Let's go this way. What's this? That's a spider. This game is stupid.
What a dumb game. So, you know what? You just killed spiders and that's it. This is stupid.
Why would you ever play this game? Okay, let's keep going. What's that? What the hell?
What? Oh, that hurts you. Oh, am I gonna like die? Let's just go. Okay, I'm gonna beat this
entire game right now. And let's go. Let's go down. Okay, we're gonna go down here.
Okay, so look, I'm driving like a farm right here. A pet spiders. Okay, hey spiders.
So today, we're gonna, I'm gonna feed you some little bugs and you're gonna eat them.
Again, I'm gonna shoot that. So how do I, is this like a simulator? How do I get out of here?
Oh, one of them escaped. One of the bugs escaped. One of the bugs fucking escaped.
That means you die, by the way. If you escape the hole, that means you die, you bastard. See,
these guys are locked in here forever. Can you get out now? Come on, try to get down now.
You're not getting anywhere. I'm gonna shoot the shit out of you. You can't even do it.
That's it, I got the key. Gonna go in the golden room, the golden palace,
and pick up the lazy beam. What? What does this do? Does this just shoot right through people?
So what's this button do? Oh, yeah, yeah. Ew. This game is gross. No, I take money. I love the
money. I absolutely love money. It's the best thing in the world. Whoa, that was an explosion.
We're going down to this room. Okay. Did I miss anything? Do I have to go back up here
or southward? What the hell is this? What is this? Do I go this? Oh my god, this guy. What is with
this guy? Can I help you? I'm gonna get him down. I gotta get him down off that rope. He's gonna die.
Oh, whatever. Screw you. Let's go down here. And this is the room I need to go in, right?
Oh, I have to fight this little worm. So what, do I just... Okay, so how many lives do I get?
What, I get like 10 lives, right? Like two, at least two or three lives, right?
What is... Do I have to start this all over again? You don't get lives in this game,
is that what you're trying to tell me right now? How come I don't have... This is the stupidest
game I've ever played. Why would you... This is the dumbest... You know what? I'm not gonna do
anything. I'm going right back to that same boss. That worm son of a bitch is going down right now.
Hey, worm! He's a different guy. Why is he... Where's the worm? The worm would look a lot easier
than this guy. What is... Is this whole game just like randomly generated? This is stupid.
I'm gonna like punch him in the face. I'll punch you! I'm gonna punch you right in your face.
You see, that's how you do it. That's a pro tip right there. See all those bugs that were around
him? They're not there anymore, are they? See, I'll do it again. Get rid of all the stupid goddamn
bugs. And that's how you win. That's how you beat this. And then you poo on them too. And that's
how you get the most massive points. Concentrate. Concentrate. Need to concentrate! Oh, I don't have
enough life to do the bug move again. I don't have enough life to do the bug move. And you know what?
He's almost dead. I'm gonna beat the game. I just beat the game. I just beat the game.
I just beat the game. This game's supposed to be hard. We're doing it again. We're going to do it
again. Go. Get out of my way. Get out of my way. This game is stupid. See you later. If you play
that game, you're a son of a bitch in my opinion. And we're not friends anymore. So I'm getting out
of here. Talk to you guys later. Hello? You see, did he die? What happened? Oh, I gotta put these
headphones back in. I mean, he still has a heart left. Not like he didn't die completely. Why is
he playing as this guy, by the way? All right. Oh, let's salvage the grandpa run. It's gonna be
impossible. Oh, poor grandpa. Don't worry, he'll get over it. Grandpa rages all the time. He'll get
over it. Ten bombs. And he died three times. Make it four, because I'm probably not going to make
it out of this room. Nope. Oh, there's no way. There's no way. Like, there's not a chance.
That's it right there. Well, that's gonna wrap it up, guys. Thanks everybody so much for coming.
This will all be on YouTube in the next, like, half an hour or so. So if you missed it from the
beginning, didn't really do any good runs, unfortunately. It wasn't a good night for Isaac.
But that's okay. Had fun, regardless. So thanks everybody again for coming so much. You guys all
rock and roll. And I will see you guys all soon. So take care, everybody. And let's end the stream.
Oh, and grandpa just says goodbye, too, and that he loves you all. Right, grandpa? Oh, he's coming
in here. Hold on. Grandpa, get in. You need to apologize to these people. Apologize to anybody.
Okay, I'm sorry. I'm really sorry. You know, rage takes over us all. And the game was just a little
too hard. But I love everybody. I hope you guys have a fantastic Sunday and love grandpa. And
goodbye. That's the end. Bye. Now, we're gonna eat in like 10 minutes. You gotta come up here,
Jeremy. Come on, let's go. And bring your dog, too. I'm gonna feed him.
All right. See you later. So that's gonna be the end, guys. Thanks a lot for watching. I really
do appreciate it. And of course, again, take care, everybody.