Banco cap, that's pretty cool, but we gotta go cooler than that.
Body hat, yep. Uh, little snaggletooth.
Look at it, so cute. Hi, Mr. Snaggletooth.
Wow!
Hey, what's going on, everybody? Jerma here with an on-fire gameplay commentary.
No, there we go, here we go. This guy's gonna die.
Aye, aye, aye.
Uh, this is gonna be, like, before I can not breathe.
Uh, this is gonna be a live gameplay commentary.
Playing as the Huntsman Sniper.
And as you see here, I'm gonna shoot this Pyro in the face.
I wasn't really prepared to start this commentary, I just for some reason was like,
you know what, let's just do it. I'm gonna do it right now.
And that's what happens.
Follow the unusual, just like Froot Loops, follow your nose.
This is a bad place for both of us to be, but somehow you managed to do that and get rid of all of them.
So, good job, you did it.
You are death- a big sentry, big sentry.
I'm scared.
Soldier friend, what do we do?
What are we supposed to do here?
We're supposed to just chill?
Wait for the cavalry to come bail us out?
Oh god, that was so close to being a long, super long headshot, but I'm in trouble here.
That's gonna kill me!
Medic, medic, I'm real, I promise.
I am a real boy.
Pinocchio.
Oh god, I hate when I do that.
It's just barely off.
I'll get this guy though.
Ah, no spies behind me.
Just a question, can I melee this guy?
Or is that not a good idea?
No, we're gonna do something else, completely different.
We're just gonna taunt kill this guy, because we were totally able to.
And we'll get that guy too.
And what about his, like, his best friend that's about to open the door?
At least I got him, okay.
That would be the third time in a row where that did not work, and it almost did.
Cap it, cap it, we got him, we got him locked in.
God, that would have hit him too.
Gotcha!
Bullseye!
Here we go, last chance to get it.
And I didn't get it, but we still won.
That's okay.
Congratulations!
Red team?
No, blue team?
We won!
Oh yeah, backflip!
Who wants to do a backflip?
Let's go.
Eight minutes on upward, and we already got somebody right down here.
You fell into the abyss.
That's a terrible way to go.
Shot in the face with an arrow, and you fall down into like a pit of hell.
Scared to go up that way.
That is not what I want to do right now, but I'll do it.
If you really want to, we'll do that.
I know you're going to get the health.
Shit, if I had only timed that better.
There it is, okay.
Uber, Uber's gonna end, and he's gonna come right down the hall.
The Uber didn't end!
Why did the Uber not end?
I thought I could have sworn that Uber was ending.
I don't know where to go.
I'm in deep trouble, deep trouble, deep trouble, deep trouble.
Big trouble.
Can we, please, just, I need to go in here and get health.
Coming right out the front door.
Make sure they don't get it.
Perfect.
I see blue laser beams.
That means it's a heavy right there.
You show me like the laser light show.
I'm gonna turn around and just like, just smash ya.
Crits.
The tracers on him.
Who's up here?
Anybody have interest up here?
Yeah, there is.
All right, who else is up here?
You.
You are a pyro.
Don't stand still.
You stood still.
Be very careful.
That should have been a headshot, and we all, look at, where's that arrow?
Where's that arrow?
Is arrow in his gun?
What was up with that?
I want to look at that again.
Because that arrow went like directly into his face.
But you know, whatever.
Good old huntsman.
You're gonna back up.
You're gonna back up right now.
And I didn't get you in the head, but it's okay.
That guy will finish you off.
I really appreciate the help with that.
Is there a sentry over here?
Thank goodness there isn't.
Because I would have just gone, and gotten eaten alive by it.
But you know what?
I do want the health.
It's down here.
Good show.
All right, let's keep moving.
Let's try not to die.
Try not to die one time in this run.
Although I say that now, and I'm gonna turn the corner and just get insta-killed.
So whatever.
Whatever happens, happens.
This guy right here is, if I didn't just like jump the gun right there, I would have had that.
But his sentry, no, he's gonna go down.
No, he's not.
He's just barely moving out of the way.
Oh my goodness.
He's running over here.
What the hell are you doing?
What is?
What just happened right there?
So I've just been informed that the baby, my niece is currently in town.
And she's sleeping right now.
They just put her to bed in the room next to me.
So I gotta be like real quiet.
So I moved the microphone right up into my face.
And like, hopefully it's not, hopefully it doesn't sound like Bob Ross, the painter.
Like, oh, you're gonna paint those mountains.
And you're gonna get nice long brush strokes.
But that's probably what I sound like.
So I'm really sorry.
But this is how it's gonna be for the remainder of the video.
What have we got?
Just scouts and pyro.
I couldn't even say the words.
They weren't coming out of my mouth.
But this pyro is gonna die.
No, he's not.
I lied.
That was a complete lie.
He just, you see, I got him so bad that he got sucked into the earth.
Be quiet.
Okay, don't want to wake the baby.
Don't wake the baby.
That's really important even though you just got a sick kill.
It's all right.
Just pack it up.
Get in here.
Pick up the extra health and ammunition.
Then we're gonna turn here.
And I thought I was gonna...
Oh, boy, he noticed me.
I'm dead.
I'm dead here.
Holy shit in my pants.
Shit inside of my pants.
There is just shit filling my underwear right now.
Shit.
Ooh, spy.
Got the soldier.
Two scouts just back to back right now?
We have a sentry?
Oh, that would have hit him in the face.
Where is he?
No, you're not getting away.
You're not getting away.
I hit him right in like the neck with an arrow to that first shot.
I can always feel myself like exhaling after missing one of those.
The breath comes out swift.
Anyone behind me?
Okay.
All right.
We're cool.
We cool?
No, we're not cool.
We're not cool.
We're not cool because I got shot right in the back of the head.
I'm just gonna bump into the microphone because it's so close to my face.
I can pretty much brush my teeth with it.
If I had a Colgate toothpaste, I could turn this into a toothbrush microphone.
Son of a bitch.
Oh, you had to jump.
You had to jump.
Dude, that guy's legs were missing.
That guy was just didn't have any legs.
That was very odd.
Can I make it across here?
I wonder if I can sneakily get over here and like taunt kill somebody.
Probably could have just got that guy.
Give me the health.
Come on.
Please spawn.
Hello, everyone.
It's me, God.
Just wanted to say that health doesn't spawn here.
Jerma is an idiot.
Let's get back to the video.
I will now unfreeze time.
Spawn.
Health, please.
Health.
Where is the fucking health?
It's okay.
We won the game.
All right.
Well, I think that might be it because I don't know how much longer I'm going to be able to
play like this leaned in, like brushing my teeth on the microphone.
So yeah, thanks everybody for watching.
Take care, everybody.
Goodbye.