What's up? How's it going? Oh shit. No, we're good. How's everybody doing? Good. How you been? It's been a little while.
We missed you. Hey, thank you. Hey, it goes both ways. I wanted to get back in the chair too.
How you doing? Everyone doing good? What's been going on? Anything new? Anything I should know?
I hope you're doing good. It's been a few weeks. Has it been three weeks or two and a half?
I don't know. Show us your face. Give me a second. It's been like a couple of weeks. Hold on.
Yeah, we're going to play Shadows of Doubt. I have something very important to talk about too.
I'm a little saddened to say this, but I don't think I'm going to be able to complete
Breath of the Wild before Tears of the Kingdom comes out. Sorry to all you Breath of the Wild
Andes. I don't think that's going to happen. The game comes out literally tomorrow. I don't think.
I promised. Wait, I promised. Did I? Did I actually promise to do this? Did I? Oh, fuck.
I did not promise I was going to beat this game. Did I? How deep of a promise was this?
I didn't say I was going to eat any articles of clothing, right? I didn't say I was going to eat
any articles of clothing. Or did I? You promised. Oh, does anybody have a clip? You owe me 10 bucks.
Yeah, I'm probably just going to have to play Breath of the Wild while everybody else is playing.
It's going to be so stupid. You know how many people are going to come to the stream
in the next few days and be like, dude, what are you doing? What's wrong with you?
We will forgive you if you eat an article of clothing. No, I think I'm all right.
Does anybody have a quote for me? I'm at the podium right now. Yeah, hold on a minute.
Hold on. All the reporters are taking pictures. Anybody have a quote for me saying I was going to
do that? I don't think anybody's got a quote. You did say. Well, someone will find it eventually.
But anyways, what if we just watch the Breath of the Wild story recap trailer and I hold a
controller in my hand while we watch it and I move like I'm dodging and stuff? Is that all right?
It's not the same. No. How long do I have till it's out? Is it out Friday, Saturday, Sunday?
When is it up? There's no way I'm going to beat this game. I'm just no way I'm going to beat it.
No, we're going to. Don't worry. I'm not concerned about it. Guys, the last I think I've played
maybe three triple A games at launch. All the rest I play at least six months later.
And I don't know. Maybe do I play Tears of the Kingdom? I maybe have to beat Breath of the Wild
first. I'm ranting right now trying to find a way out of this. We will finish it. How do I find a
way out of this? All right. Anyways, how you doing? Hope you're doing good. I did want to play shadows
of doubt because Taleks brought it up. Said it was great. He said it's right up your alley. I was
like, really? He's like, yeah. I said, OK, if you do play Tears of the Kingdom, I'm not going to be
around. I'm going to savor the game for myself. That's fine. That's completely understandable.
Makes complete sense to me. OK, so let me first of all, let me just prove that I'm alive.
Right. Let me just get this over with. Hi. Yes, I'm alive. I exist. Also been seeing a lot of
people talk. It's weird because seeing a lot of people talk about Pegasus King 2 and they're
acting like I didn't get an advanced copy of that game. Honestly, like really? Really? You don't
think that I already have a copy of that game? You don't think I've already played it? Kind of
annoying. I'm always one step ahead of you. Two steps forward. You're one step back. Two steps
forward. You're one step back. Nice beard. Oh, yeah. Why do you have film grain? This is there?
Oh, my God. This is actually huge. Hey, hey, I'm back, everybody. How's everybody doing?
Oh, yeah. Well, you know, I have a razor. You know, I haven't shaved and I haven't got it.
I haven't had a haircut either. I'm keeping it. I don't give a shit. I don't care. I'm just going
to grow. I'm going to grow till it's like this long. Fuck it. What do you think? Should I? Should
I let it go? Should I just let it go like all the way? I'm going to start playing with fire on stream.
All right, let's go. You've waited long enough. You've waited over two and a half weeks.
I'm here now. How's everybody doing? This game apparently is you solve. It's randomly generated
cases. Seems pretty cool. I'm going to have to pay a lot of attention though. All right. Now,
italics told me do the tutorial and pay attention. He said, don't do this. Do not play this game if
you're not ready to put real brain power into this. He's like, you have to pay attention.
You have to know where the tools are. You have to know what to say. And then I asked him to repeat
that three more times before I understood. I wasn't really paying attention to what he was saying.
So, I'm ready. I know exactly what I'm getting into. I'm going to pay attention. I'm going to...
I promise I'm going to pay attention. Here we go. I'm ready. Can you guys even hear the game?
Oh, shit. Sorry. You guys mind if I turn the fan on? Why am I asking you? All right. Should I select
the city? Generate city or select city? For tutorial purposes. What is this? Okay. North
part Sapporo. Mercy. Okay. How about this one? This one looks good.
Is this like, do you guys have my, like, this is seed or something? You guys can play along? Cool.
This is going to crash my computer. What's my player's name? Okay. What do I look like?
I don't know. What should I put the... All right. Normal probably, right? You look disgruntled.
Should I just have my, like, just have my brow down the whole time? Just like,
I look disgruntled. I think this... Wait. Gadget Lisenko. I think that's perfect.
We're good? Yo, that's my name. What the fuck? All right. Stop talking to me. I need to pay
attention. I'm serious. I need to, I have to pay attention. I need to pay attention. I need to pay
attention. I need to pay attention. Caveman Detective. Don't put ideas in my head.
Stop distracting me. You're doing it. I would need a pipe. A caveman outfit. Pay attention.
Pay attention to what? It's just generating the seed. You are literally Willem Dafoe in
the lighthouse. Damn. I feel like I'm installing windows right now. This is going to be crazy.
Simulating past events? Wait. Look out for graffiti that may give clues about illegal businesses.
I should have been reading all of this. I know that most of you that have played this before
probably just like, this is basic, like, press tab to look at your inventory or whatever. But
I probably need to know this. All right. Everybody be quiet. In Shadows of Delta,
tutorial will guide you through how to use mechanics, though connecting the dots throughout
the cases on your shoulders, detective. Help can be accessed at any time through your detective
handbook. The main menu with F1. Turn it on. It is the late 20th century. Hyper industrialization
has swept the planet. The old urban empire has crumbled, giving way to the United Atlantic States
and the first elected mega corporation president in history, Starch Cola. You have a wicked slow
computer? No, I don't. As sea levels rise, cities have become polluted islands. Workers dream of
escaping to the fields, an exclusive retirement district you will ever see. Rival corporations
have a power leased by the privatized Starch Cola enforcers. Okay, process it. Don't just read it.
Fuck, I'm doing it again. Some say justice now only exists in the shadows.
I'm trying to pay attention. Stop distracting me over here. That is a doubt. The dead of night,
52 a.m. Tuesday, January 3rd, your apartment. That's probably good, right? That's much better.
Turn it up. So cold. Turn on the bedside light. Oh, okay. What? How did I? Why would I read this
right now? I'm not ready for this. I'm not ready for this info. It's too loud. Hold on. It's way
too loud. I just can't get used to sleeping without what? He's just lying here. Get up. Oh,
turn on the light switch in the kitchen. Oh, there's like a little. This is a scary game.
It's locked. Jump. What's in there? What is this? Oh, this is a lot of reading this game. Hold on.
This is a Tennessee agreement drawn up between the landlord, Emer Jackson and me. Okay, this is my
landlord. This is my apartment. Okay. Shit. All right. Hold on. Everybody relax. This Tennessee
agreement is subject to the regulations of the Joint Corporation Housing Consortium. A copy of
these regulations may be obtained in writing from the nearest JCHC Administration Bureau on receipt
of a processing fee. The notice period will be one week on the land side of the landlord and two
months on the side. Try to write this down. 12th of the day of expiry. Financial penalty shall be
incurred for every additional 30 minutes. All broken windows, locks, lamps, sockets, sprockets,
outlets, inlets, pipes, faucets, vents, grills, and appliances must be repaired or replaced
by the tenant. Okay. The tenant shall not repair or replace any windows, locks, lamps, sockets,
sprockets, outlets, inlets, pipes, faucets, vents, grills, bras, and appliances without
express permission to the landlord. Do I have any weapons? What's up? Where's somebody talking?
Oh, I thought someone was trying to get in. Let me continue reading this.
I got more info. Hold on. The tenant shall keep in good repair all walls, tiles, and flooring.
The tenant shall not paint, plaster, paper, or alter walls, tiles, or flooring in any way.
The tenant shall not encourage nor harbor pigeons, rodents, or microscopic life forms of any kind.
All right. It's a rental agreement of some kind. So don't break anything and make sure
you register with the landlord and building supervisor. I've just signed it. Okay. I guess.
Did I? Oh, all right. Let's go. Why do I need to know all this? What's that? What's this? Okay.
It's January. Oh, I can change the date by moving it. Oh, city directory. Yeah. That's a lot of
people. Let me just do what it's tell. I just stop overwhelming myself and just turn the light on.
That's it. Don't. Why am I doing? Why am I making this more complicated? When within range,
possible interactions will be displayed at the bottom. Oh, hello.
Who's this? Ow. Why did somebody call me and hang up? What was that? All right. Search for clues.
Former police officer's welfare association. We're here for you. Free basic housing for those in
need. For more information, contact Henry. Please note, we can no longer help with money. Wait,
all. I call this person. There's a lot of, I don't have this person's phone number.
I don't know the telephone number. Call them the directory. Oh, yep. Yep. Yep. Yep. I don't know
why you would sprint across your house like that. Okay. Wait, shut up for a second. What's,
hold on. What's the person's name? See you June three or rye. See you. All right. Wait, this is,
I, this is their apartment. A lot of routes. Just go hang out. I just planned a route. Wait,
I can pin this. Whoa. Okay. So, all right. There's a note under the front door. That's not a front
door. Where's my front door? This is also not my front door. This is my front door. What is this?
When you inspect an item, it brings up its evidence window. This can be pinned to your
case board for future reference using the pin at the top. Okay. So I can pin info. Got it. Thank
God I got a beard for today's stream. Pinned items are displayed as icons that you can move
around on the board by dragging their pin. You can position these items as you wish.
Let them to bring up their evidence. You can make connections. Facts or connections are displayed
as string. You can mouse over these to see more info and use F to pause at any time to examine
the case board. Find Killian Dewitt. Pin Killian Dewitt to your case board. Pin the note to your
case board. Oh, shit. I fucked it all up. What happened? Close the case. Wait, what is this?
This is the case board, right? Isn't it pinned right now? These are all pinned. All right. Move
this out of the way. This is not, I need to find this person. Let me go look them up in the directory.
Never heard of them. If this is a job, it's a lousy way to do business. Yep. Okay. Look them up in the
directory. Okay. Pin to your case board. Whatever it is, I better go prepared. Find old detective
equipment. Oh, wait. Okay. That's map. You also have access to city district map that you can
toggle it up a little. Whatever. I missed it. What's the case board again? F? All right. I'm
starting. I'm getting it. I'm getting it. This is where I need to go. Find a route. We're heading
that way. Screwdriver. I'll take it. Exit inventory. Okay. I take snacks. It's still good.
Are they still good? I don't know. Why? Why did they let me throw that? Dish detergent. Okay. I
could use that. Give me some tissues. What's in the fridge? There's milk and there's a block of
chicken. What about the freezer? That's all I need is a detective apparently, right? Wait.
Find all detective equipment. Synthetic milk. Synth milk. Oh, a wrench. Inventory's full.
What? How do I get to my inventory? I? How about open inventory again? X. Okay. Okay. Well, I don't
need this. So get rid of this. I, I gotta turn that down. It's awful. All right. I'm taking the
screwdriver, the milk, the chicken. Do I need anything else? The key to my old police stuff
was lost in the last move. I could pick the lock. There's got to be something I could use around
here. Look for hairpins or paper clips. What about the, I can use the wrench? I don't think I can.
It's money. Money can be used to buy items in the world. Acquire genetic upgrades for your character.
Pay for information. Decorate your apartment. Really? This is, oh, wait a minute. What's this?
Final notice open immediately. How do I open it? Final notice open immediately. So open it.
This is a letter from me. Okay. I need to find, hold on. Let me do the tutorial. What? Oh, I got
Luigi. It took too long. Okay. Pick the lock. I need two of these. Why would I need two? Oh, wait.
7%. Did I open it? What happened? What did I just do? I need two. Oh, okay. What's that? Clean air
sunshine with every place and external space. Zone living areas for each family. Some opportunity
for individual expression. Fields for the happiest and best homes. Register your initial interest
today. Okay. Okay. Locked? Dude, this is my door. How am I locked in my own house? Hey, gadget.
I set the password back to 1234. Take care of yourself. This is my house. Password is 1234.
Toothpaste. Toothbrush. God damn it. I need more room. Let me fix this right now. That's better.
Oh, a paper clip. Each lock has its own strength. When you start the, this game is actually pretty
cool. I'm very interested. When you start the process by interacting with the door handle or
lock, the indicated bars will tell you how many picks you need to complete the lock pick. Okay.
So I need, would need three. You can also use lock picks to sabotage security systems. Okay.
This is a very weird toilet. I should probably drop these, right? I'm just checking and just
making sure I don't miss anything. Okay. Let's go. Don't jump. Okay. Got it. Ooh. Okay. Yep.
The top group. Wait, I got to pay attention. Let me just take a step. The top group of items do not
take up inventory space. These are for your vital tools of the trade. The lower section features
slots. They can store other world items. So, okay. It's, I got it. Drop or scan picked up items for
fingerprints. Ooh, that's cool. Assign hotkeys. Press the hotkey by hovering and pressing. You
guys just, just pay attention to this so I can ask you later. Okay. I got 30 lock picks. That was
what was in that box. Okay. I got the key to my house. The password was pinned. Select the pin.
Yep. And then I already got it planned. Unlock the door to your apartment by interacting with
the door. That's, that's the closet. Hello everybody. It's me, the detective. Here to
hopefully solve another couple of cases. You be on your best behavior. Oh, I wasn't locked in my
room for 45 minutes. All right. I have to go. I can talk to. Unknown citizen, new information.
Evening. What's your name? Have you seen or heard anything unusual? Do you know this person?
Could you provide your fingerprints for an investor? Do you know this person?
I can't help you. Evening. What's your name? I'm Jarek Lean. What's it up to you?
You got any spare change? That guy just gave me money. Thank you. That guy gave me two bucks.
Uh, what's, what's that person? How do I, this person on the board. Oh, there it is. Okay.
How do I write like a note? Very, was very nice to me. Additional notes.
It was incredibly nice and gave me two dollars. Uh, I don't think we need to remember this person,
but whatever. Is sprinting bad? This is locked. Somebody's coming to answer the door. Banker,
bar and grill? Is this a restaurant? Evening. How much for a tour of this place? Sure. I can
issue a temporary guest pass, but it'll cost you. How much? How much money do I have? Do you know
this person? I saw them today at Thompson House ground floor lobby around 2 15 a.m. Isn't that
how it is right now? What's your name? I'm CEO young. He, what's it to you? What? Let's go.
Can I get in trouble? What is this place? It's a hospital. Am I allowed to be in here? I guess
it's just a hospital, right? Leave with the fire extinguisher. Yeah. Official police business. I
need to take this with me. Uh, how do I, what do we do with this though? Depending on your activity,
different kinds of status may affect your character. Oh, wait, something's wrong. What does
that mean? What's that mean? Wet. Oh, I thought that meant I was in trouble. Why are you running?
I'm just like a fucking weirdo. All right. Let me go to 901 Royal Heights. Okay.
They ain't coming back this time. Wait, is this a trash can or is that an ATM? You know, I'm going
to have to take the plunger, right? Bists. I don't think we're ever going to get any. We're not
going to get anything done. I just want to make that really clear. I'm sorry, everybody. I don't
think we're going to solve one case. I got to, how do I put these down? Okay. I have to pay.
This is the tutorial. I can't fuck around. What's that? It's a battery. God, just draw. I need to
just go, just go up the stairs, please, man. Jim Stetter is a popular brand of beer brewed by the
starch cola corporation to prove drink responsibly. 12, uh, junk footprint. These are footprints
right here. How do I scan it? This is a different foot, size eight and a size six. What I've deduced
is that they have two different size feet. I don't know. I'm not sure what we're dealing with
here. What's up? Evening. What's your name? As if I tell you, okay. Um, I'll give you money for your
name. Do you know this person? It's not enough info for me to help you. I think it's your neighbor.
Okay. Well, goodbye. Oh my, nevermind. I didn't know that could happen. Am I alive? Where even am I?
I have a broken leg. I didn't know you could actually do that. I'm so fucked up right now.
I did not know. I thought there was an invisible barrier that didn't let me walk through it.
We're only on the sixth floor. Where's the elevator? We need to go to floor number nine.
I swear I didn't do that on purpose. It's so funny. You know, if a door is locked or not,
you must first have to try and open it. Lock doors can be unlocked by focusing on the door handle.
You have the correct key for the door. You'll see an interaction open. Okay. So this is locked.
Doors locked. When breaking into a room, it's a good idea to check for cameras.
If you're worried about them, you can turn them up by using the security breaker box
connected to the camera. This person. Hold on. We need to listen. Hold on. Are they just,
are they just watching Nick at night? There's nobody in here. All right. Where's the camera?
Oh my God. What'd I just do? I thought that, I thought, how do I restart the game?
How do I restart the game? I don't want to sabotage this. That's an alarm. What is that?
I honestly, I, where's the breaker? This is like the alarm. I owe a hundred bucks to who?
What was? Oh shit. Okay. Leave with air ducts. Hide under beds. How do I turn this off?
This is a good show. Antique vase. Bunch of shit. Hammer in here.
What? I'm drinking the whole carton. I'm going to puke. Put it down. Put it down. Put it down.
I'm just fucking this guy's whole apartment up. I drank, I drank soy milk in this person's
apartment until I puked. There's still more. Okay. I need to fucking settle down. Honest to
goodness. You got cameras in here? Oh shit. My God. Unknown citizen, new information. Dead.
Dead. A bullet wound from low caliber aim. An eight millimeter nine by 32. Wait, pin that.
I'm examining the body. It appears that the victim has been shot to death with a pistol
or revolver. I can determine the time of death is between 2345 and one Tuesday, January 3rd.
Pin this. Tall. Unknown citizen. Find a photo ID. I need a light. How do I turn the lights on?
Oh, internet works. Killian DeWitt. Wait, this is Killian DeWitt on the ground.
Connect. Okay. Put that right here. Got it. Okay. This is Killian DeWitt. Killian DeWitt is dead.
A sword. How do I pick up this? How do I use the sword? What's that? What does that mean? What was
that? What was that? Look around for a potential quick exit. Shit. I gotta pay attention. Vintage
sword. I don't, I don't know whose sword this is. I'm going to owe a thousand dollars. This is so,
this game's awesome. I'm like playing with all this guy's toys. Thank you for recently
life insurance policy. Do not meet the required social economic requirements to be approved.
Check out a range of alternatives. Okay. There was, there was a insurance policy taken out.
How do I close this menu? Oh, right here. You can travel through buildings via ventilation ducts.
Simply open the grate. Okay. So did I, this is not what it wants me to do. Look around for vents.
I just found it, right? It's still on my menu. I still have a broken leg. Is it the bathroom?
Just go in it. Okay. Well, I got info. Is it safe to go down here?
That's killing it. All right. Just search the place for clues. Well, why, why did I go through
the vent? Okay. Hold on. Each citizen has a unique fingerprint. You can scan for them using the
fingerprint scanner device in your inventory. Point the scanner where you want to scan. Almost
all surfaces can contain fingerprints. Unknown fingerprints will be found in sets with set A
being the first you find any matching prints will also be labeled to that corresponding set.
For example, if you find set A at an apartment and subsequently at a bar, you can prove a citizen
was in both locations at some point. Use right mouse button to inspect fingerprints after you
found them to pin them to your case board. They may disappear over time. Interesting.
Somebody here? Look at the prints. Turn the lights off. Print writer, prints right there,
right there. Look at that. This is Killian DeWitt's fingerprint. All right. Pin that
shit writer. Anything else? We're looking for other fingerprints. We don't know who this is.
Okay. This is type B. We don't know who it belongs to. And that over here. Very, very cool.
Okay. These prints don't belong to Killian and nobody else lives here. That's the killer,
obviously. Isn't it obvious? How do I turn this TV off? Drugs? No, it's an eraser. Is it an eraser?
Just hit it with the sword. Coin? No, how do I hit this? Shut this TV off. I can't turn the TV off.
Pour milk on it. 541-000. Last caller was telephone call. Pin that shit. 404-2676.
We got it. I was like, oh, Gregory, huh? Shut this fucking TV off. Evening, what's your name?
As if I'd tell. Have you seen or heard anything unusual? Shit. Please, no. Please, he begged us
and I flashed a light of the puncher. Please, you can have the promotion. I found the office chair
I tied him to. Uh-huh. I said, it is too late. You shouldn't have given the position to Jill.
Now you will pay. I shrieked, but I took a printout of last quarter's fiscal report.
Stuffed it in his mouth. Who's underperforming now? Did he write this? Save, save, save. What?
What do you mean save? Oh my god. Yes. Italic said, for the record, I told him to ignore all
the little detail things and just go punch people in the face. Chat, your job is to remind him to
save because I don't think there's an auto-save. Yeah, but I wanted to like, I wanted to understand
what I was doing, Italic. All right, what is this? I mean, it's connected to somebody.
Should I call all these phone numbers? Oh, this is a lot of people. Okay. Who is this? Get this
person off my bar and get this off my bar too. What's the point of this? Get rid of this. Yeah,
I already did. Get rid of this. I need to clean this up, by the way. Fingerprint right here,
put the address here. All right. Why is this so weird? I still have a broken leg. Search for
clues at the crime scene. All right, we got some clues. What's that? What's in there? What's this?
Oh, safe. Locked. Keypad. We need a four-digit key. Do I have any? What do you got here?
Doctor's prescription. Okay, this is the doctor that prescribed this. High blood pressure. All
right. You. We're calling you. Wait, I want to pin that. Here's the connection. Prescription
from this doctor. We're going to call this doctor. You sound like a tuber right now.
I'll settle down. I'll settle down. New policy, dear. Okay, do it. Thank you for recently contacting
us to request a life insurance. Oh, I already did this one. Pin it anyways. Okay. Sometimes
it's useful to search the trash. This is crumpled up. Receipt key for tax records. Banker, bar,
and grill. Call me. Not paid. Wait. I knocked on this door. So I have a tab. Well, I don't have a
tab. Killian Dewitt has a tab. Can that make that connection? Tape. A little used device containing
magnetic tape to store moving images and sounding. Okay. Okay. So code breaker. Bug on the floor?
What's wrong with me? What's wrong? What's wrong with my character? What's wrong with me? I have
a code breaker now. What am I doing? Watch this. Uh oh. Why am I shaking? Commemorative baseball?
Take this vial to a local sync clinic to upgrade one of your installed sync disks. And then what's
this? The menace of charity. What is wrong with me? Honestly, what's going on? That's a lot of
money. That's a $10,000 fine. I don't have that money. So can I sleep? Can I sleep this off? Oh,
what the hell? Don't forget who owns you. Okay. A bandage. Oh, hold on. I need that. I don't need
this. I need this though. Use it right now on my leg. Can I just eat the bandage? Remember your pass
code this time? Oh, God damn it. I just wasted that code breaker. Okay. I need to go to the hospital
now. This is kind of giving me a headache. I'm puking into the trash. I just puked in it.
Let me get my hands in there now. Key for tax records. Okay. Coffee. Hamburger. I went to the
turkey sandwich bar. Apparently this guy's eating food. Very cool. Okay. This is just a receipt.
The silent alarm has been tripped. It means what? Oh, how do I get under the bed? The dot in the
middle of the screen displays how hidden you are. A hollow circle means you are completely obscured
and others will only notice you if you get extremely close. Filled in circle means you're
completely visible. Okay. So that means something can see you. When things go wrong, you might have
to resort to combat. Punch or block, but be careful detective. Violence can escalate quickly.
How do I get under the bed? How do I get under the bed? It told me to, I said I could get under the
bed. Is a vent in this room? Oh, fuck. I, where'd I go? That was, that was weird, right? It looked
like I fell through the world. Where am I? Am I even inside of this thing? I think they're gone.
I think they're gone. Just walked out the fucking front door. All right, we're good. How do I get
out of here? Out the window? Oh shit. You can do that? I'm dead. I, what happened? What? I didn't,
what just happened? What? Am I alive? What? Am I, am I down here now? What just happened?
Oh, I clipped through the door. Oh, okay. Well, I'm just kind of bleeding out.
I gotta get to the hospital right now. I stink too, apparently. I smells. I have so, all right.
This is like in The Sims when you have like three or four different families and you just, or like
there's like five people in the household and just one of them you've just neglected for like an hour
and you don't even realize it. I am fucked up right now. Bleeding, stinky, broken leg. Okay.
Let's just go get out of here. Why am I walking by the way?
Oh my God. There's so much blood. There is so much blood. How do I get rid of this trail?
Collect a murder case resolution form from city hall. I need to, uh, I'm in, I'm hurt. I need to,
where's the doctor? I need a doctor. What's this? A cola. Is there anything left in it? Come on,
let me have a couple of little scraps. Where's the hospital? Am I picking this shit up? I'm just,
what am I doing? Where's the hospital? I'm sorry. I can't play this game. Where's the hospital? How
do I control the map? Cause like, I can't move it from here. Wait. Okay. Over here. Here's the clinic.
Okay. Okay. Okay. I'm good. I'm good. I'm good. I need quite a few things. I need you. I need a,
I need a splint for my leg. I need a, um, money in front of me. Hello. Hi. Um, I'd like to buy
something. I'd like a splint please. Thank you. Okay. Uh, what about all the blood? I want to take
it so bad. Bandage. I don't have any. Hold on. I'm bleeding everywhere. What handcuffs, sink, disc,
upgrade vial. Get rid of the baseball. I'm, hold on. Wait, can I get in the, wait, can I, can you,
I need treatment. Installing a disc. I don't have anything to do. I don't have anything to upgrade.
Okay. I am good to go now. I get this. Potential crime. All employees, the door code to my office
has been reset to 1608. Save, save, save. All right. All right. I got it. I got it. Perfect
lightning strike. What did I pick up? I picked up something else. Wait, whose blood is this?
What did I pick up? Okay. Collect a murder case resolution form. Where do I get it? City hall.
Oh, right here. Okay. Collected form. Got a resolution form. View your case objective
by using the resolve button in the top right of the case board screen. Resolve the case.
Provide answers for the following before plotting a route to the hand in destination. What is the
full name of the killer? Do you have any evidence to place the killer at the crime scene? Okay. Wait,
wait, wait, wait, wait. Okay. I got it. I got it. I got it. Juniper networks and the doctor too.
Check out the sandwich bar. I have a, I got it on the board. We don't need to do this yet.
I am going to go, go to the work. Okay. Juniper networks. Let's plan a route and we're going to
scan for fingerprints. We're looking for that one. Game is sick. It's really fun. In shadows of
doubt, there are almost always multiple ways to carry out an investigation. Here are the current
available leads. Choose one as a star to be guided through. Remember in the main game, you'll have
to think for yourself, detective. In addition, due to the simulated nature of the game, some leads
could be dead ends. It's just part of the job. If you think you have enough information to solve
the case, fill in the resolution form. Okay. Investigate the office, diner, or phone calls.
Should I just disable this or no? I think I'm going to do the diner. Okay. So we'll go into the
turkey sandwich place. Let's go find this out. Am I still bleeding? Didn't I just steal from you?
Oops. Bro, you stink. Take a shower. I tried to take a shower earlier. It wouldn't let me.
The camera's too big. All right. Let's go check this out. What's going on? Commercial properties
contain a wealth of information and probably usually I, huh. Okay. All right. So I'm going
to take the kettle off the stove, please. Fingerprint type C. What about this one? Doesn't match.
Type D. Check the booth. Type E. Type F. We're looking for B. Wait, I can eat? I should do that
right now. How do I sit down? Okay. Only his fingerprints were on this. So this thing is
useless to me. Can I sell it to somebody? Is he still the tutorial? Yeah. This tutorial is a long
tutorial. It's designed to make it so you, it's, I'm learning the game. We'll do another one.
Let's talk. Let's figure this out. What's your name? Mind your own business. Okay. Have you
seen anything unusual? No. Do you know this person? I saw them somewhere around Royal Heights. Okay.
Checks out. Checks out. Did you provide your fingerprints for an investigation?
Didn't even do anything. I just put two bucks in here. Ooh, fingerprints. Let's go for it.
This place is filthy. Am I just, oh, sentry gun. It's okay. We're good. Okay. I gotta hurry up.
Why would there be a sentry gun leading over here? How do I turn this off? M. Toilet paper. What's
this? What is that? We're going to the bathroom. I gotta check this thing for fingerprints. Oh,
we need B. Oh my God. Why did I think this was an office? I just, I'm sneaking into the public
bathrooms. I'm sneaking into the public bathrooms. Like, oh, I gotta find my way over here. Disable
the security cam. Oh, the alarm system. This is literally just the public bathroom of this
restaurant. This is just the bathroom. This is the bathrooms. There's nothing even back here.
Why did I disable all these things? I thought this is somebody's office. Oh, shit. I'm sorry.
Wait, nobody in there. Okay. We're good. Come on. I'm in here. Dude, he, and we're behind the
counter. Perfect. Okay. So let's go ahead and what's that? The note. I was in the stall. All
right. So I got, will you talk to me? Health inspector. I need to survey your premises.
Health inspector, huh? Still going to need a guest pass to take a look around. Okay. All right. I'm
paying it. Your guest pass is active for two hours. After that, you'll need to leave or pay someone
for more time. There it is. The door code to my office. Seven two nine zero. Let's go ahead.
Okay. Got it. Seven two nine zero. Hurry up. I don't have much time. Oops. Fingerprints. Quick.
Club sign up below. No, none of you. Wait, who are these people? Waitstaff. Waitstaff. Okay.
Just get, I'm getting names down here. Did I pin any of these? Urban? No. No. Janitor. Waitstaff.
Waitstaff. Retail owner. Waitstaff. And waitstaff. All right. I just learned a bunch of people's names.
Can't get in here. Seven two nine zero. How do I get in here without them being pissed that I'm
doing this though? Can I go in here? Is everyone getting mad at me? Can I do this? Just in case.
I know I'm allowed to be back here to be the health inspector, but it seems like off limits to me.
Seven two nine zero. Hunters are digital personal computation devices. They're common in most
apartments and white collar workplaces. If you know a citizen's passcode you can log into their
account. Really? Once logged in you'll be able to access vmails which are personal or work related
sent between citizens. You also build access a variety of other apps including security and
surveillance as well as employee databases. If you find useful evidence on a micro cruncher,
don't forget to print it using the on-screen print button. Okay. I don't have very much time so let's
go. First things first. Open the breaker box. Ah somebody was just in here. Camera. Yeah the
tutorial said hey open the breaker box. I was just doing what it told me. I don't know it's weird.
Somebody was in here. Did I do it? All right I need this info. CCTV cameras have two functions
to alert instance of security threat but actually capture surveillance still throughout the day.
Ooh okay. So I'm looking for somebody that was in here with this with this dude right? How can
me look like you just got back from Survivor? Okay 22 45 Monday. 22 40 22 45 Monday. How do I
change the time? Okay hold on. How do I do time? Oh 22 sitting with somebody. Open an evidence
window by inspecting their mugshot. No! Shit! Okay you were there and so were you. All right.
Interesting. What were you doing there? Interesting. Where are you? Lawrence Champion. Janitor. I gotta
talk to the janitor. Open an evidence window by inspecting the mugshot. Didn't I just do that? I
didn't just do that. I need to click on. Oh this guy just doesn't care that I'm in here. No I gotta
I gotta track down this person here because you have the guest pass. I was freaking out for no
reason. All right so I need to figure out who that person is. So I think I'm all right now.
So it was the janitor. Janitor. There it is. Okay there you are. Janitor. Are you here now?
Where's the janitor? Uh do you know this person? I work with them. That's Lawrence Champion.
Loves coffee. Saw them today at McCarthy Street around 7 a.m. To a nearby Butler Street at itself.
Okay thank you. Butler Street? So down that way. You didn't do the PC thing correctly?
What did I do wrong? Surveillance. Go to the right time on Monday. Oh I have to print it. Right right
right. Wait a minute. Print this. Got it. There it is. There it is. Use a different camera. Who's that?
What are you doing over here? Print that. And that too. Who's that? I got it. Are you pissed that I
tried to pick up your burnt cigarette? I think I'm good. You missed the girl. Well somebody was a
just a wait staff. It wasn't. Yeah this this is the wait staff right? I don't think this person is
a person of interest. No I got what I need. Oh I just want to go back. I don't want. Come on.
Store room. I got that one. Back room. Nothing. No no I got it. I got it right here. So where do
you go? You're still kind of hanging out in here. Don't just. All right you just take that photo. I
don't even care. No the other camera. The only footage of the. Wait who's this? Unknown. Print
that shit out. Did it run out of paper? Oh interesting. Pin that. Okay you. I need to
find out who you are. It's a paper jam. Dude you are so smart. It's a complicated game and it's fun.
Okay good. I think that is free. Fuck. I was just checking it. I didn't even check it. I had to
check it for fucking prints. I forgot I was on. Didn't I disable the camera? Are they checking the
footage right now? Too bad it's not anymore ink. Whatever I got 25 bucks. They don't care. All
right I need to talk to some people. Do you know who this is? Do you know this person? I saw them
somewhere around Little Parks. Interesting. Little Parks. Thank you. Appreciate it. What about you?
Have you seen this person? Little Parks. Where's Little Parks? How do I zoom the map out? Anybody
know? That's Kilian Dewitt's fingerprints on a crumpled piece of paper. Starting soon in Mercia
district anonymous work will come and share the load. Buy like turkey sandwich bar. Go to this
Kilian. You'll feel better for it. Tell them Rio Takahashi sent you. Can they print on this table?
E. Find Rio Takahashi. Okay. Hey there you are. Let's go. He's not gonna find shit. What? I have
pretty good leads right now. A sugar daddy? Okay. Sugar daddy or cola? I want a cola. Just throw
the baseball at this point. I don't want it. Can't even walk down the darn street anymore.
Okay. Let's go. I knew it was you. Anything unusual? Do you know this person? Little Parks.
Okay. Thanks for your help. Where does this person live? Sixth floor? Are they gonna let me in?
Cameras. Okay. I gotta play this well. I'm on camera right here. Here we go. This could be
the killer. I have to be prepared. Good evening. Look who it is. Look who it is. Ask you a few
questions. Excuse me. What is your name? I'm Rio Takahashi. What's it to you? Anything unusual
over the last few days? Nothing. Mind if I take a look around? You're welcome to. Come on in. Hey.
Hey, be careful. There's a killer out there. Did you provide your fingerprints for an investigation?
I guess if it's for an investigation. Fingerprints. What kind of fingerprints are they?
Shit. I was not done with my investigation. You said I could come in. Can I still come in?
Thank you. Reuben sandwich, hamburger, pepper, beer, vodka bourbon. Interesting. Interesting.
What a place you have here. Sorry. Do you like the detective routine in every television show?
Holy shit. I just, I just hit the absolute jackpot here. What do you have?
You've got beef bricks. Can I cook it? I think they're brushing their teeth.
Okay. Work. Accountant. 900 to 700. Monday through Friday. I don't know what that means,
but it's, I am just going to put it over here. This is another person. Who are you? Who are you?
Who are you? Are you another person? Oh, wait. How? That was, I thought you went this way.
Burger sandwiches. Okay. So all this proves is that you were at the restaurant. What about
fingerprints? Looking for B, right? Maybe you know who it is. You might fucking busy in here.
Okay. Can we have a compromise? Can I turn on one light? Why does this, why do you not want
any lights on in your entire house? How do you navigate this apartment? What time is it? It's
10 30. Barbecue sauce. Shit. This doesn't prove anything. I'm at a dead end. Actual dead end.
I thought that was an animal. I'm so jumpy today too. Wait, why am I still allowed in the house?
What? So can I like break into that safe? What's going on? What's happening? What's happening?
What's happening? What's happening? Hey, who the fuck are you? Oh, you think the darkness is your
ally. Where am I? Who is this person? Who is this person? Oh no. Okay. I didn't do anything.
I didn't do anything. I didn't do anything. Citizen's arrest. What? After two hours?
What do I do? Okay. You're under. What do you mean? Huh? Do you see what just happened in here?
I guess, I guess if it's for an investigation. Fingerprints. What were they? These things hurt.
All right. What do you got on you in that shit? Who are you? Take their money and take their keys.
Yeah. Take it. I'm, I'm freaking out. Hold on. I gotta calm down. Who are you and what are you?
Automatic pistol. Okay. Okay. Okay. Okay. Okay. Okay. Turn the lights on first of all. Um, um,
fingerprint. Yes. What's the fingerprint though? Is it B? Got you. You're under arrest. You're
under arrest for killing at least two people. Um, what do we do? Okay. How do I follow me down
the stairs? The victim has been shot to death with a pistol. I'm at death between 10 and 1045. I was
in the room. All right. How do I, what do I do? Is there a way I can, I can take you with me?
Just leave them there. Okay. What is the full name of the killer?
Right here. Arrest the killer. Yes. Do you have evidence that placed the killer at the crime scene?
I do. I'm standing at it right now. I'm standing at the crime scene. This has been a murder.
The fingerprints. Yep. Where's the fingerprints? Right here. Where does the killer live? I don't
know. Wasn't it on the, wait, I know. Uh, what was that? The thing I, I took the wallet. No, no, no,
stuff, stuff, stuff right here. And that I want to take the money out of this person's wallet.
Wait, I've got so much bullshit everywhere. Like arrest. Have you located the murder weapon? I've
got it. It's a gun, but I need to look at it again because I didn't pin it. Search them again.
Okay. Pin this. There we go. Here it is. Flot route to hand in. All right. You come with me.
Arrest. You're under arrest. It's closed. That was crazy. That was really, really crazy. Do I
actually have to walk with them or do I just turn it in? You just leave? I was in the, what was I
even doing in the other room? I'm okay. That was too much stimulation. I'm just going to go turn
this in. It was a box to check arrest. You didn't take it. No, no, no. I, no, I got it. Arrest.
Right here. I got it. Yeah. I got it. I got it. I got it. No, it checked. All right. Let's turn it
in. That was crazy. That was really cool though. That was fun. The thing we, honestly, we just got
into a random scenario. There is no connection between this person killing Killian. We have no
connection. We just were in the room when another person died. Just caught him red handed. Fingerprint.
That's true. Yeah, that's true. You're right. Okay. Let's go for it. Tutorial officially complete.
I think I understand how the game works. I thought I was getting shot at. Okay. Case submitted for
processing. Please wait for the results. I got five out of five. I got it. One assistant. I got
250 social credit. 2200 bucks. Social credit level up. Cool. Now what? I did it. Now you can
change your name. Change my name. Do I now just, do I get rid of all this now too? This is all
not active anymore. Upright. Archive closed. Oh, cool. So this has been resolved. Uh, close the
case. You can take a side quest now or wait for another murder. Really? I can't close it at this
moment. Why not? You don't have to wait for a murder. Murder someone then frame someone else.
I have to go back to the apartment. There's still more. Like this apartment? Wait, which apartment?
Fine. This is a mess. I know it is. Sit on your bench with your watch out. It's locked. How do I
just, where even is my house? Just start a new sandbox game at this point. The game gets glitchy
and dead of night after the murder. Okay. That makes sense to me. All right. So sandbox. Solve
and explore within the city your way. Generate a city. And Franklin's fine. Medium's fine. And
let's do random. The game should be, did you even save? Yeah, I did. Okay. Seems pretty good. Let's
go. Yeah. Uh, did I get one guide? I may have, but they said it was, um, one guy said that sometimes
it can bug out after that case. Shadows of doubt. One guy is actually correct. Okay. That was fun.
This game's giving me a migraine. Can you please turn off all the lights and watch videos of fish?
I'm sorry. I mean, I do enjoy videos of fish, but not right now. Give me one day. How big do
you think I can get this? So sandbox mode, something just happens and I have to figure it out.
Shave your face, you cretin. I'm going to try to look as gross as I can. You know what I mean?
I've never tried that before. You know, it always hits, it always hits a time when I haven't had a
haircut in a while. I haven't shaved in a while and I'm like, okay, all right. It's time to clean
up a little. Um, I think, I don't know. I just think, what if I just, just let it all go and
just, let's see what happens after like a month, two months. No, like I'm going to get a trim and
clean it up. No, no. Eyebrows. Just go for it and see what happens. Right now. Holly is probably
sitting there going like, okay, yeah, let me just look like fucking crazed. Uh, no tutorial. I just
turned it on. I thought it said no. I am fucking out of my mind. Can I, I seriously thought it
said no. It's all right. I could probably still use them. Jumpster. Crash. What's in it? Evening.
Evening. Sorry. Nothing. Don't worry about it. I just, I was trying to investigate. Hacking tape.
By default, they will be reported murder. Where, where, where, where, where, where, where, where?
New murder case. Crime scene. 1001 gray building. You also have access to a city district map that
you have toggle up with. Where is it? 1001 gray building. Use the map with F.
There we go. That's what I was looking for. Okay. Gray building. 1001 gray building. Is that a name
of street or the name of a building? I can use this search. Wait, the color. No, it's not. Context
menu. Search top left. Gray. Oh, there it is. We get out of the way. As you know, there's been a
murder. Depending on your activity, different kinds of status. Yep. Yep. Yep. I already know
that. All right. What happened? Where are you? Where are you going? 10th floor. Let's go. I don't
know what happened there. Sound the alarm. Sound the alarm. I'm here. I'm here. I'm here, detective.
I'm here. I'm a detective. Open it up. Sound the alarm. I'm here. How do I open the door? I did.
You need to get out of there. What do you mean? No. I, how do I turn it off? I don't know what,
what do I do? I don't know what to do. I don't know what happened. What's going on? What's going on?
What's going on? Help. Help. Turn it off. Turn it off. Turn it off.
Ah! What the fuck? What's happening? What? It's the killer. That's the killer. That's the killer
right there. There's a killer. There's a killer. There's a killer. Stop this guy.
Shotgun. I don't understand what just happened. I'm so confused. I saw his face. I know what he
looks like. He's bald and he's got glasses. I know. That dude shot me point blank like 10 times.
He's bald and he's got glasses. I'm going, I know, I know what he looks like. Medical fees.
Get the fuck out of here. Don't you understand? There's a killer on the loose.
All right. Where is this guy? I'm going back there. Have any food? I'll take whatever you got.
How do I buy something? I need, I need the hospital right now. No. God damn it. I just like alt tab.
There we go. Where is the hospital? Hospital. Doctor. Drugstore. Come on. Come on. Come on. Hurry
up. Hurry up. Hurry up. Hurry up. Hurry up. Hurry up. Go, go, go, go, go. Why is it? What's going on?
Where'd it go? Hey, bandage. Where's all my money? Medical fees? What are you talking about? I had
2200 bucks five minutes ago. That was a different save file. Oh, that's actually awful. Shit. Okay.
Now that's why I shouldn't have left. Shit. Um, am I actually screwed here? Or if I just reload
this, will it fix it? Just rob the medicine cabinet. I guess I could fuck off with this.
Oh, you got like trophies back here. Where's this? Where's the medicine? What time is this?
I'm just going to start over. That got so screwed up. I went there. There's somebody screaming at
me. Turn the alarm on. I turn the alarm on. A guy with a shotgun shoots me five times in the face
and then I get up. I think I'm just going to restart. I'm just going to restart. You're a
bigger public menace than the murderer. Okay. Let's try this again. That was that. That one
actually doesn't count. Sorry. I'm so jumpy. That was kind of a mess though. Give me a little bit
of slack. So in conclusion, you trespassed, started breaking a fire alarm, got shot, ran from the
hospital, robbed a drug store and gave up. There was somebody behind the screen screaming for me,
please, please sound the alarm. I just did what I saw. There was an opportunity to maybe get some
more people to help and maybe we need something happened here. I was told to do it. I pulled it
and then I couldn't turn it off. I couldn't get into that side of the apartment building
and then a shotgun was in my face. Does that mean that I get to have a shotgun at some point?
I mean, it has to imply that I can use a shotgun at some point. This game is crazy. This is fun.
I like this. I'm just choked. You sabotage the alarm. Yeah. Well, I just, I don't know,
there's a lot of loud sounds. Okay. Oh, here we go. Let's get this started. This is the real
one now. No one messing around. This is the real deal. We already know the story here.
We can just skip this, right? Okay. Here we go. 6 PM, Monday, January 2nd, Carpenter Street.
How you doing? What's your name? I'm Joanne Callahan. What's it to you? Have a good day.
Whatever. What's the world coming to? Everybody really wants to be around this fire.
Wait, there's a lot of people here. Okay. Is the fight breaking out? Somebody said I had enough.
Hey you, this street is a toll. Pay up. Get lost. You'll regret this decision. What is going?
This person, this person has a knife. This person has a knife. This person has a knife.
Help. This person has a knife. Get, am I being attacked by all of you now? This person has a
knife. Get out of the way. Are you serious? I have to run. I have to run. Somebody help me.
Somebody help. I'm being chased. I'm being chased. I'm being chased. I'm being chased.
I don't know what I'm supposed to do, but please help. Get away from me. Dude, how do I call the
police? How do I? Murder. There's been a murder. There's been a murder. It's probably one of you.
A new murder case. 1102. What was it? Bryant Terrace. Where am I? You are the police.
That was so fucked up. Why? 1102. Now I have to go to the hospital again. I don't even have any
money. I got jumped. I didn't even identify any of those people either. I was just so fucked up.
Help. Help. Help. Help. Wait. Was this the person that had the knife? Come here. Get over here.
Get over here. It was... Give me a second. Okay. I'm going to give you a second. I'm going to give
you the count of three before I drop you. Why am I the bad guy here? This doesn't make any sense.
I don't want to get... Who is this? Are these... Oh, thanks for showing up. Thanks for helping.
They went over here. They went this way. They're right here. It was... No, wait. Where are they?
What is happening? I don't know. I think they're after... I don't know who they're after. Wait. Oh.
I'm just going to die. I need to restart again. I got stabbed 10 times. No reason. Where are we?
What are we doing? Somebody's in the building. There's a murderer in the building. Are they still
here? Someone... Okay. There's something going on. How many... Why did you... I should have just taken
the elevator. What am I doing? What floor am I on? How do I get in here? How do I get in there?
All right. Let's do an investigation here. Can I come in and help? Is that the right house?
1102. One... Why is this... Why is this... There is a... Is there a... There is a body on the ground.
Oh my god. Somebody's in the... Don't... No. Wait, wait, wait. I... What are you doing? Stop.
Oh my god, guys. What have I done? I... Your... This shit is backwards. Your door number is
backwards. What? Who has the gun? Get me out. Get me... Be careful. Careful. Careful. Careful.
Careful. Who has a gun? Do you... Let me in. Let me in. I'm out on the fucking deck. Let me in.
I'm out on the fucking ledge. Can I... Somebody let me in? They locked me out. They locked me out on
the ledge. Oh no. Shit. How do I get back in? What the fuck? I have to... I... There's nowhere
to go. I have to restart the whole fucking thing. Oh my god. I... There's nowhere to go. I was stuck.
Damn it. That was so ridiculous. The window opened. You can't... WM1A murder investigation.
Yeah, but... Well, hold on though. Let's calm down and think about this for a second.
The last couple... I've tried to generate new seeds. The first seed. I just get attacked. I just get
stabbed and chased and four people are attacking me, killing me. No, that's not even the first one.
A shotgun pointed in my face. Shot. Boom. I get surrounded and attacked. I go up with the police
to help investigate and all of a sudden they start shooting. There's like... People... That was the
killer in there apparently because they went... They had like... They were firing at each other.
I get pushed out to the balcony. I'm just standing out there. I don't even know what
happened. You're a private detective? You can't be at the crime scene. You're not part of the police.
This game is wonderful. This is really fun. It's just... Things can just happen. Everybody is just
doing something. This is great. Okay. I'm getting some advice in the chat. I'm going to listen to
it. I'm going to save immediately after loading up the game. Looks good. Okay. No more insanity. No
more craziness. No more wild behavior from my end. I'm good. I am going to just simply walk down the
street like a normal citizen. I'm just hanging out. How are you? It's good to see you. It's okay.
People like it. I guess. Ain't no pleasing you is there. Both coughed. What's your name?
Keep your nose out of my business. Okay. Nobody saw shit? All right. Just running around with a
hammer. What was that? That was weird. I'm just waiting for a murder. This is weird. This game's
kind of... I'm on edge right now. What's your name? Seen anything unusual? No. When people sprint
around, it makes me nervous. He just has a knife. I think I'm going to just follow this person.
You strolled down the wrong street, pal. Give me your crows. Can I have that broom? I need a phone.
I need a phone. I need a phone. I need a phone. I need a telephone right now. Is there a working
telephone in here? You have a working telephone? You have a working telephone in here? I need to
get a look at you. I need to like inspect. Shit. I got to find a brick or something and throw it.
Give me a brick. Come on. Give me a... Oh my god. Am I in trouble? Am I in trouble? Did I kill this
person? Okay. Well, y'all, you're in trouble. There's no active case. Would you like to create
one? Yes. You attacked me with a knife. Okay. We got it. We have an ID. Potential. Fine. What?
I just took somebody's key. Wait. A knife. No. Pick up the whole toaster. How has that not been
a murder? Oh shit. I did steal this. I did walk out with the toaster. I did not mean to steal it.
Why am I freezing right now? Why am I so cold? Can I not put the toaster in my inventory? I'll bring
it back. Here. I accidentally took this. Take it back. I didn't mean to take that. I can't
go into the registers for investigative purposes. Why am I so cold? There's been no murder. I'm gonna
buy a hot dog or something. What do you got here? Can I buy anything? How do I buy food? Do you know
this person? Okay. Whatever. We'll eat some raw meat. I think I need... I only have 100 bucks,
I guess. What do I need? A bandage? Oh, a heat pack. Here we go. And then... Did that not work?
Oh, this is nice. Did I get some food too? All right. I'm gonna have something to eat.
How about a coffee and a donut? Oh, a cheeseburger sounds pretty good. Okay.
Uh, close the case. Case closed. Okay, I did it. What's your name? I'm Sawyer Barnett. Why?
Anything unusual? No? Can I have some money? Thank you. Somebody just called and said I was broke.
Well, I had 2,200 bucks. Not anymore. I solved the first case and then I had to change seeds.
Work available for a discrete individual. Business related concerns require investigation.
Significant fee available for the right person. Financial compensation. A rare sink disc.
Ooh. 1,400 bucks. I'll take it. 8835611. Okay. What was it? I already forgot. I already forgot.
Okay, let's do it. Oh, it's in... Hear about the job. Meet me at Isaiah's Cafe. I'll be sitting
with a coffee. Ask about Thompson. Make it sharp. Won't he be here for much longer?
Then don't fucking talk my ear off. This is you? Wait, are we already here? Okay. What's it called?
Thompson? No. What was it called? Oh, yeah. Run? That's so good. Doing good. Thanks for asking.
Is this you? Wait, you said you're gonna have a coffee. Who? Who is it? We all have coffees.
That has to be you. Okay. Is this Thompson? Good, you made it. I need you to steal an important
document. It'll be in a sealed red and brown envelope. The leads for the target are in this
briefcase. Take it. It's taking so much to not throw the briefcase right back at this person's
face. Okay. How do I... How do I take this shit out of here? It's already... Oh, okay. Save now,
please. Save now. I got it. He looks so unwell. Pick it up. Locate and steal the item from the
mark. A secret envelope. Do we know anything about this person? Apparently they're here somewhere.
Read their profile. There's nothing here. Short black hair. Large build.
10th floor. All right. 10th floor. I'm biting my lip. Okay. Let's go. Stop. Stop biting your lip.
Stop it. Stop. Okay. I'm done. All right. So let's get it... Let's do this correctly here.
Large. Short black hair. Size 12. He's on the 10th floor. Short black hair. Large. What do we got?
This person is naked. Okay. I don't think that was the right person, first of all. Are we good?
I don't think anybody's... I don't know which one is correct. Ow! I just went... Okay. Camera right
here. I have to get... Turn this camera off. There we go. Am I gonna get in trouble for doing this?
Turn this shit off. God damn it. Get those back on. All right. We're good. I didn't mean to do that,
but okay. Somebody's phone is ringing in here. I don't even know if this is the right house.
This is the right house. God damn it. That's so stupid. Okay. I don't have the... I don't think
I have this correct. I need more info. I'm just gonna go... I'm going back outside. This is... I'm
not... This is bad. What time is it? Can I just sit on the ground for the first guy again? The naked
guy? Close on this time. How are you? What's your name? Anything unusual? No. Do you know... I don't
care. Never mind. Fuck off. Somebody opened the door. I heard a door open. Short black hair.
Large build. I don't know. Sorry. Wait. Can I... Can I come in? What's your name? What's it gonna do
with you? Do you mind if I come in and take a look around? Jesus. Okay. I don't... I don't think it's
you. It's not you. So I've narrowed it down to two doors. The cameras are back on. Oh shit. They are.
Okay. Murder! That's literally right here. That's right here. It's in the same building. Go, go,
go, go, go. I got it right now. Before I do this, is this possible? All right. You're under arrest.
You're under arrest. You're under... You are under arrest. You're under arrest. You are. You... You're
under arrest right now. You're under arrest. I think. Um, this is a cop? What? That's a cop?
No, it's not. They're not even here yet. That's a cop. Okay. All right. Where's the body? Where's the
body? Files. Here we are. Luke Woters. Get that gone. Get that gone. You gotta find the body.
This is the wrong place. Is it? Are you sure? Why was the cop in here then? That wasn't a cop.
Am I even in... What is the 901? How do I get this guy to get out of here? What's your name?
Hello. I'm... Oh, of course. Okay. Luke Woters. Anything unusual? Nothing. There's an investigation.
Can I get your fingerprints? Thank you very much. Appreciate it. We do have fingerprints.
Type B. Just in case. I don't need this right now. Let's go. So, I need you to go away. Because I
need to get in here. Is there a camera? There is. I need you to go away. Really appreciate it. No,
you're still here. This is your house, right? That's your house. Look. There's a... There was a noise
in there. Didn't you hear that? Did you hear the noise in your apartment? This is... I heard it.
Something's fucked up in there, I think. You better go and check it out. You don't hear that?
How do I... Will he even see this? All right. Save it just in case he sees. Does he see it?
I have no lockpicks. Will you look somewhere else? You're just staring at me. You know what?
Oh my god. He didn't even go in. Dispatch, do you copy? I didn't know you had to click again.
Oh my god. Okay, for those of you that are watching at home, if you click drink on anything,
it's not just drink until you let go of click. You have to click again to stop drinking. Okay.
This is awful. My controls are backwards. I just gotta wait till everybody leaves and then I can
go in there and... Oh my god. Your drunk movement speed and control penalty. This'll disappear on
its own. Coming. What? Can I even look in here? I'm not allowed in here. You gotta be shitting me.
I'm just drinking. I'm just drinking and walking around. There's nothing weird. See? I'm just
drinking. That's it. I'm allowed to drink in my own property. No, dude. I can't walk forward.
I can't walk forward. Orsis, open up. Where have they gone? Wait, why are you opening up this door?
I was just gonna sit in the corner. I just shattered my ankle. Okay. Have you completed
your investigation? Can I go in there now? Or no? Can I not go in here? Hey! I'm just...
Damn it. Get up. Get up. When I press W, it moves backwards, by the way.
Although I'm not in any shape to do an investigation right now. Where's the body?
Oh, wait. What's this? Oh, okay. Might as well. Hey, hair of the dog, don't they say?
Was that... Where's that body? I'm gonna find out where it is. What does it say?
Who cares about this bullshit? Release cigarettes. Good. Yeah, I guess I'll take that.
Oh my god. Where is the body, though? I have to stop. What does it say? The bandit? What does it
say? It says something... Bandit? The bandit? The pin... The pinini? What is it? I don't know
what that says. Go to sleep in their bed. All right. I gotta... I gotta... Dude. I have to... Okay.
I'm crawling right now. Oh, this sucks. This hurts. How do I stop? You need to puke. How?
What? Can I... Will this help? Oh no, that made it worse.
God damn it. I don't even know where this person's bed is. Just sit down. Sit down. This is hard to
even look at. This sucks to even look at. Go to the toilet? Just... Can I sleep here? How do I
pull the watch up and sleep? There it is. Watch. Okay. How do I sleep? You can't sleep while
trespassing. Oh, here it is. No. Wait. No, no, no. I don't want anyone to see what I'm doing.
Here's the bathroom. All right. Puke. Am I imagining that or is that real?
Is that me thinking that? I gotta take a shower. Can I take a shower? How long am I going to be
drunk for? I can't turn it on. Just throw some water in my face. Oh my god. What if I... I'm just
going to turn the lights off so we don't have to suffer looking at this. I'm just going to look
at the ground. Uh oh. Use the toilet. I can't. Can I sit on the toilet? I can't sit on the toilet.
There's no body even in here, by the way. And if it's not, I can't. Press G. I can puke with G.
No, I can't. That's a lie. I am actually... Okay, I need to reload the save. Find a trash can.
Find a trash can? That's the solution? Right here. I can't puke in it. I can't puke in it.
I can't puke in any receptacle. Sit on the couch. All right, this actually is starting... This is
going to hurt everyone's brain. Go drink water. Press G on the toilet. Jump off the landing.
Just jump out and reload. Oh, it's getting better. Do a flip? Press G, dude. G doesn't do anything.
Use your watch to wait. I don't think I can do anything. Sit and use the watch. I'm just
trying to get out of here. Jump. I'm giving this 30 more seconds than I'm reloading. I actually
didn't even do that. I didn't do that. I actually just walked off there accidentally.
I didn't do that. When I press W, he picks a random direction and walks. I have a bad egg.
I've been arrested. Three stooges aren't in Fortnite yet. Yeah, it's fucked up. I've been
pissed off about it for at least a few years. Oh, I feel so great now. I can actually see what's
happening. Okay, let's get back into that apartment. I am fresh, although I should collect the thing
from City Hall, right? To be on the case. Oh, this is City Hall. Case of the Corpo Assassin.
You got it. Back to it. I got a rash when I opened my Grotto Beast pack. I don't think we had
anything to do with that. Where does the killer live? What weapon? Do you have evidence that...
Okay. Let's see if I can get in there now. Ninth floor. I know. I just want to... I have to
apologize to everybody here. Yes. I am the guy last night that was drunk and walked off the banister.
I just want to say sorry. I caused a little bit of a problem for everybody. I may have walked around
and I think I knocked on a bunch of people's doors. I was trying to find the killer, I think,
was what that was, I believe. Oh, this is my friend. What's going on? Luke? Luke is shitfaced.
Remember when I had the katana? Remember that? That was kind of cool. I know. Just take the elevator.
Okay. Just take that. Oh my goodness. Thing. I look... There's one... There's two floors up.
Why did I even get in here? Okay. It's time to start my investigation. Save it here. Okay.
Where's the body? I thought that was a knife. Oh, this is not the right place. This is wrong.
I just took his glasses. Come on. What are you doing? What are you thinking? How do I put... I
want to take... I want to put those down. Am I wearing them? Okay. That was wrong. It's this one
here. Go. All right. What do we got? Fingerprints. Let's look. There's no body though. Weirdly enough.
Where's the body? Type C. Type C? Where's the pin to pin in it? To pin in it. What does this
say? Put a pin in it? All right. I need to find the key... The keypad. All right. You got something
here. Type C. Money. All right. What is this? Probably a mine. Lots of fingerprints. Anybody
else in here? Just C for now. Cigarette. No. C. C. Where's the body? Oh, food. This is a mess. I
have to get rid of all this stuff. Why is this even pinned? This shouldn't be pinned either. This
guy has nothing to do with any of this. It's a newspaper. Why am I even... Okay. Cool. Dirty
plate. Type C. Can I smoke this? Oh, okay. Is this who lived here? Candy. Matchbox. Is that a knife?
Utility knife? Read the newspaper again. Oh, I have a knife now. Did I stab myself? No. Okay,
good. What's that? Matchbook. Soap. Find the body, please. Where is it? There's no other rooms.
Is this a clue? Put a pin in it. Hold on. Birth control pills? Okay. Birth control pills. What's
this? Oh. Didn't have what it takes. Kill to get ahead. They must earn my respect. Fingerprints
probably match, right? The wound caused by a sharp object or blade. Where was anybody? It was appears
the victim has been slashed to death by a bladed weapon. I can determine the time of death is
between 1745 and 1900. Monday, January 2nd, 1979. And that... All right. So what do we got?
Yin is the one line on the ground here. Fingerprints. Those are fingerprints. We've
got them. Type C. All right. So we know that you worked here at Revenue Tree Networks.
I'm not done investigating yet, but I know what I'm looking for. Is that it?
That's it. That's also it. Okay. So now, now what? Any prints here? Maybe this prints. Type D. Relax.
We got Type D fingerprints. And that's on the business card that says, didn't have what it
takes to... Like I'm going to kill you or whatever. Okay. We're looking for this person, Type D.
They had a business card. All right. Now what is that? Revenue Tree Networks. Yeah. Head of HR.
901 Robert Heights. Yep. That's where we are now. I'm just going to hold onto it.
And then there's a note. Yin, remember your passcode this time. Count backwards from 9.
I got to see what's in there. Take a look. 8 7 6 5. 9 8 7 6. Nothing in here. It must have been
stolen. Actually weird. Why is nothing in there? Fingerprints. Good call. Let's try it. Okay.
Okay. This is your fingerprints. No one else was in here. No. I don't think any thing... Nothing
out of the ordinary here. Oh, what about the computer? There was another name in the computer,
wasn't there? Check it out. Telephone number. Okay. We've got emails. Request of your help.
Hello dear Yin Zhu. I need your help. I have become stuck overseas after being mugged
dreadfully. I have no papers and I'm greatly nervous. Please send me one fifteen hundred
for new papers from the consulate at once via credit service. I have no other friend in the
world. You must rely the world and I have no other friend in the world. I must rely on you.
Is this from who? Who's this from? Print that out. Print that out. Valued friend, we have been
waiting to contact you with this secret and best offer on a special syncs package just for you.
Bar less than half the normal cost. Our sync disk package gives you access to all known syncs.
Reply today with your personal credit account details. Gotta get... I want to make sure I get
that. That seems like a fucking bargain. To Xiuyun Ri. Please, please give me another chance. You
don't know how hard it's been. I'm begging you. Xiuyun, this job is all I have. It's my life. I'm
so sorry for letting you down. I hate myself. I'll never do it again. I swear. Please believe me.
Interesting. Who's that? Print that out. Who are you? I wonder if you have type D.
Fingerprints. It's possible that you have type D. It's a spam. I'm sorry it won't happen again.
I swear to tell the truth things have been tough at home and I know it has been affecting my work
but I swear I'll do better from now on. I'll work overtime to catch up. Please give me a few weeks
to prove myself. Oh Detective Bugleberry's on the case. So we have some we have some people here.
Okay so this is all spam. So we need to find these other people. What do you got in here?
Employment contract. Okay let's go to revenue tree networks. All right revenue tree networks. That
is where we are going. We're going to find out who works there. We're going to find out what's going
on here. What about prints on the files? Not a bad idea. It doesn't look like it. She's moving.
You're live? I don't know. Okay let's go. That's weird. Stop biting your lip. You guys need to
tell me to stop when I do that. I'm relying on you. All right that was fairly clean this time.
Let's go to the work. I'll save it when I get up. What should I name my baby? Frank. All right let's
move. I do have a weapon though. I have a knife now. Do you know what I wanted to try? Because
I've never really had it. I think I've only had it maybe once ever. White Castle. Is White Castle
any good? I saw like this this fucking like YouTube video where it showed how they make it.
Did you guys know? Am I completely full of shit here? But they make these little patties. These
little squares. And they put five holes. One two three four five. Almost looks like a dice.
And they put it on a flat top. And they don't flip it. They don't flip the burger. They put
it on the flat top. It's so small. They put it on a bed of onions. It's on a bed of chopped onions.
They put the meat right on top. And then the steam from the water. They put a bun on top.
And it cooks the other side too. And then they pick it up weirdly. I also saw that YouTube short.
Yeah I did too. I just wanted it. It made me want it. Has anybody in this chat eaten White Castle
before? Yes. Yes. Yes. It's very bad. It's repulsive. What? It's good. It's good. It's good.
It's amazing. It's ass. It's average. It's good in a disgusting way. All right. What was I doing
going up? Right? What am I even doing here? Is this the business? Revenue Tree Networks. It is. Is
the business just in somebody's apartment or something? Or is it? No this is an office.
What um where is it? What floor is it on? White Castle fucking sucks dude. I feel like people
are too harsh. I can't imagine driving through the White Castle drive through with holding up
the glasses on the stick. The mustache and like slick back hair and stuff. Just go and eat it.
Is it really that bad? Like you're going to White Castle. You know what you're doing. You know what
you're getting. It's just it's fast food. Just like a fast food burger. Nothing wrong with that.
Okay here it is. I am afraid to open this door. Is there okay there's a sentry gun in there.
Is that a camera? All right. How do I? I gotta do this right. I'm an idiot. McDonald's is the best
restaurant in the world. Why do I feel like you were standing up hovering over your microphone
and just saying it loudly like this and then it was like ah like something you you hurt something
here it was like oh all right so is anybody can i knock anybody here there's nobody here it's
late at night i have to turn this off but how am i going to get in there without being seen i'm just
going to go for it whatever i saved it well never mind i can't break through any lockpick stuff here
buy more lockpicks at city hall yeah okay well i'll just gotta come back let me just go to city
hall use the window wait wait wait what what what it was a window it was a vent really there is a
vent is it is this illegal all right where's that vent go this is the right place i think this is
somebody's kitchen no it is okay we're good and lights off okay what do i need here this is wrong
yeah this is the wrong office well i'm not leaving empty i'm not leaving here empty-handed
i don't even know who any of these people are but oh damn it shit oh it's locked oh my no no you
didn't see anything so how do i get to the other office this way and then down maybe i don't know
wait what did i know i came from here straight and then left this is it right here has to be
yep um wait like my nose is bleeding i don't know where i'm going this might be correct did i make it
who has any idea where i even am um you're on the wrong floor now where am i on fuck can i even get
there through here i need lock picks oh my god it worked all right what we got don't be so loud
stop okay i need to know i don't know what the passwords are you got any cameras in here what
what does that mean it's hot sauce oh my guts what is this key box okay this is just like the
employee food lounge right there's nothing really here wait i'm on to all employees the door code
in my office has been reset to five three nine zero okay five three nine zero let's go all right
what do we got what do i do oh that's bad batman just diving up you know what my character really
needs just one of those party store masks they're they they're usually like purple and they have
glitter all over them you know what i mean just and they have a band that snaps and it just covers
right here i just need some of that i need one of those dude that's no not the scream mask it's a
masquerade mask okay yeah that's what it is all right let me do this again and not screw it up
a mardi gras mask whatever it is okay now what do i do about this it's connected to that
can i sabotage this here will it see me i have no lockpicks this is such a joke
office yeah i got that already sr remember your password this time this is somebody new use box
maybe in the course it is i'm just gonna put all these employees down here okay this is the
director okay so this is the director of this company i don't think i need both of this no i
don't receptionist head of hr here we go okay what about you ua team marketing it's one of these
people has to be well i have i know i know where they all are hey dude when's the next toilet water
drinking stream can you let me know you missed it by a few months okay i think i just have to
get in there i wish i had lockpicks it's so stupid to not have them here does this also work on the
computer was it five three was it it does oh it does work here this is perfect okay that's some
new info what are you doing new info all right we know who you are i want this um its telephone
number i think it's just in the notes right okay 1501 rough towers and then here's the telephone
number a little mail you're about the mail because this is the email that they had together who i
honey bunny don't forget to pick up milk on the way home interesting interesting lunch date
interesting interesting what i mean trump voice there's a person my god what's going on what time
is it i gotta get out of here okay i need to go pay a visit so we've got another person to i want
to go i'm gonna call no should show up or call all or show up what do you think there's more it
probably is more but i mean look at what time it is the day is starting people are gonna start coming
to work to show up okay 1501 rough towers i this system is really cool really fun this was
overwhelming at first but i'm starting to understand what they want you to do starting
to get it especially look at how far you can zoom up all right let's get out of here we're four
hours in you finally understand yeah but i mean it takes it takes a little bit it takes a minute
it takes a while before you really get what's going on you can do folders for different cases
that's cool it's a it's complex but it's not complicated that's a big deal this game is very
complex but it is not complicated it's really only a few different systems to learn that's good
all right here we go i gotta be prepared i got a knife right i mean don't use it now but what
but let's say okay it's in my slot 15th or this is gonna take a million years to get up there so
just close it up all the way the top can you fight in this game you can you can punch you can stab
you can swing i don't know if there's any weapons like guns other people have been using guns on me
not the other way around this is a pretty ominous apartment okay well let's good evening
good evening i'm a private investigator trying to figure out a murder case i'd like to speak with
you for a few moments if i could oh keep your nose out of my business interesting do you know
um do you know yin by any chance oh i saw them somewhere around uh mind if i come take a look
around not a chance huh i don't really know where to go at this point type e type f type f and type
e interesting type e who does it belong to type d shit shit i don't think it's anybody here type
f good evening no i just was here but i have a few other things i want to ask you i wanted to get a
look at your face that's all i wanted do you know who this is that's my partner co yun ri
interesting suffers from insomnia they live with me you're here right now can't i connect that this
is this person here i can't connect that this is uh leela i can't make this connection yet some
strings i'm gonna call them okay i'm gonna call them i'm sorry but i had to bother you but i want
to know you this person i'm gonna get really scary sorry to bother you again they know it's
me shit can i can i come use your phone can i borrow your phone for a minute how are you how
are you do you mind if i come and take a look around not a chance do you mind if i use your
phone what's your name um anything unusual maybe from upstairs no none of my business
do you know this person well then at least give me some money can i borrow your phone i just want
to call the house i said you're pathetic can i mind if i come in why the hell would i let you in
because i am you got any snacks all right fuck it i'm just my investigation is nearing complete
i suggest you and your friend in there read wisely i got how did he get up okay i don't how do i i
don't know what to do i gotta wait don't they work i don't have any lock picks that's so important
i'm just gonna go back to city hall get a bunch of lock picks i'm back up here and see if i can
i could have gone in the elevator by now have you been enjoying this granny like it's not a granny
like that's not a granny like you've got that completely wrong let me let me just correct you
really quickly i don't want to publicly correct you but we need to get some things straight here
granny like is when in this room there is a piece of bubble gum and then 500 meters that way in a
different building there is a sink that has a pipe underneath the sink that i can put the bubble gum
on and then what that does is that stops up the drain or that that allows the water to fill up
so i can get the stick that comes up then i can come back here wedge the stick into the door by
the way none of this stuff is ever explained wedge the stick in the door to open the door
and the whole time there's a monster running behind you that's a granny like and by the way
that chain of events is six hours long that's a lie it's like 40 minutes but you get it it's
literally resident evil resident evil has a map resident evil has a pretty detailed map no map
no map i won't play it that's funny if your game does not have a map i don't want to play it all
right maybe a payphone i just need a telephone any phone just give me any telephone please
is there a telephone in the hospital i just need to use somebody's phone what time is it eight
o'clock at night in the diner why is everything closed blacksmith the restaurant of the bar will
have one that person has a knife get away from me get away from me get away from me 12 bucks
you leave me alone i killed this person i just killed that person restart did i kill him that's
all right it's all right okay didn't you mean to don't you love games that when you press x
if you have a knife it goes you all know okay payphone yes thank goodness this is not your
number that's not their number how is that not you don't have any money for the payphone i got
robbed oh my god it's the part of the movie where the main character just goes
just hangs up really hard and just i'm sorry but i have to take this here's the plan
i'm gonna turn the lights off take the money and turn the lights on here we go
hello you just said your name what are you business can i come take a look around
well i know that's what that is now do you know do you know lila sherman what do they say anything
unusual have you heard anything all right we've connected the dots that's all i needed there we
are where are you there you are okay you need a drink uh i'd like to buy something uh yeah i'll
take um take some cola appreciate it thanks all right what does any do any of you know who these
people are but okay do you no go back do you know these people like do you do you know who this is
i don't know i guess i could go i said i don't want to watch your stream um well you're here
we both are we both are doing this now that body has uh whatever uh what about the other people
these other employees like for instance this person do we know where this person is
they work here i think i just have to go there during business hours and go talk to people
that's what i'm gonna do what time is it it's the middle of the day yeah okay um let's go i need
to go talk to those people i was just kidding oh okay ah the phone book yes the phone book
that's right let's make a few more phone calls and get lockpicks yes okay first of all i want
to call does anybody else have a connection to these people not that we know of let's give amber
a call okay oh they live in the okay let's just whatever i'm buying i need lockpicks where's the
um i feel like i'm really far away from anything i only have 13 bucks i think i'm i think i'm in a
lot of trouble i think screwed i think i have to start making phone calls dude where do i live
where is my house right now i started a new sandbox and you just punch the next guy you see so i can
go to bed no do you guys sell anything like this you do how many cameras you do how much are they
syringe i have to steal it if it's white text it means it's safe is it are you lying no there's no
oh i see what you mean i'm hungry i might actually be able to get in now all right what do you guys
think go to the office and just try to talk to people or wait until i can get into their
apartment and do some investigating make some phone calls first all right i'm gonna make some
phone calls person not in the directory oh no i gotta run all right let's go pay a visit i must
be on the right track where the hell am i going knife work hey if you don't solve the crime in
the next 30 minutes you have to play chess with me on stream i'm not gonna play chess ever not even
in my own free time all right here we go it's time to figure out what's going on here we gotta
talk come on what are you holding what's your name as if i tell you i well i know who you are
let me just be let's just cut to the chase here um do you know this person i work with them that's
in zoo okay they work at revenue tree networks yes i know saw them somewhere around the grove
they were murdered have you seen anything unusual do you know this person
saw them somewhere around chong building but this person i work with them that's
siu yan ri loves ballet dancing do you mind if i come in and take a look around
no get out of here i'll make it worth your while if you both at yeah are we doing fingerprints
over there almost like look at it look directly in this first i just get a good scan on you any
ghosts what i'm doing here g type h type i bastards okay i'm gonna go to that what was it baker where
is that on the map i'm gonna go scan around there what are you gonna do a colombo impression
you're gonna remember what one boss i mean the case is cutting dry now maybe a little bit
what are you doing over here oh and that guy walked over there and he said no it's not gonna
it's only one person that can sound like colombo and that's colombo there's only one person that
can do colombo's impression it's only colombo no one else can sound like colombo why would you
even ask me to do that why am i what i mean i i determine somebody that's if somebody is a good
actor or not if somebody's got a great colombo you automatically should get a sag card you know
what i mean like if you if you can do a colombo i think you should be able to automatically join
sag you automatically get to join it screen actors guild come on all right let's keep going
it's time for prints j a dude you forgot my birthday last week i've made my decision
i've made my decision you can get fingerprints from the government place
i think i'm i have an idea they i think they did it it's they definitely did it well don't ever say
definitely in the middle of an investigation they may have they might have they might have
the hell do you live where's this person live 10th floor oh the way i've got have i solved the
case so far i did i did solve a case and i'm about to solve another one right here give me
10 minutes give me 10 minutes i'm solving this case right now i'm running full speed into this
door i need to go to what time is it it's 10 30 is it 10 30 in the morning or 10 it's 10 30 at
night all right what about in the vents i guess i could go in a vent but i don't know is there an
oh it's you hi i want to ask you a couple questions i work with them that's yinzu
suffers from alcoholism saw them somewhere around yeah can i come take a look around i don't let
people off the street into my home what's your name mind your own business when do they leave
do you know luke god damn it okay i come out neither one of you has left the apartment hurry
you gotta get out of here i think the place is haunted it's it's crazy you know what no i
where's the body oh shit no why would you okay okay i i didn't want to do this but who's this oh
shit i'm jumping on your bed i'm jumping on your bed with my fucking shoes on fuck both of you
oh and by the way i stepped in dog shit earlier my investigation is going smoothly see you tomorrow
i didn't even get any prints either but i can't even i'm i gotta do it the right way i gotta do
it the right way oh this game is fucking awesome it's just i already have their prints already
i'm gonna wait until there's just no there's no other people that were connected to that
scene we have fingerprints it's not either one of their fingerprints i'm gonna go to the office
let's go to the office and talk to co-workers just threw a knife his head what's that what is
what's this what's this this is quick what do you have in the fridge quick i can't help myself i
really can't just i wish food mode existed so i could say go to the office i can put my hands up
all the fire alarm and but won't that cause a huge scene that's gonna cause a huge scene
won't everybody know i did that that's right let's see with that i need to get in there i need to get
in there okay hi goodbye thanks for opening the door all right i i don't want to do this but i i
mean i got i need to get in here so i will this actually work i don't know this is a test it's an
experiment you just changed clothes three times how do i turn it off hey we need to get in there
i i just need to know if you let's go to the office is your problem my problem is they are
hiding something and i don't know what it is but they both they're suspects you should be ashamed
of yourself i i pulled the i did he left and oh let's go to the office we'll get some more
information what time is it it's 11 why is it always 10 o'clock at night what is this it's always
11 o'clock at night it always is do i just walk around in circles till 11 every time wait it's
the morning oh is it it's 24 o'clock right let's go i'm solving this case no matter what i just
threw somebody's bike in a dumpster that was just that was there was a completely uncalled for
all right let's do it again i it's with business hours i can knock on the door
wait what's going on wait what i'm in here oh that's right it looks like an apartment
all right let's go um what's the point of using the elevator it's right here i got massive deja
vu probably because i've been walking up this stairwell 15 times and i've been in this exact
spot like five times okay wait this is not it it's up even further how far up is this place
it's all the way the eighth floor there was i couldn't press eight okay hello hello everybody
i am here i'm here to talk about uh oh i'm not allowed i'm the health inspector
fuck uh oh um can i knock good evening how much for the door codes could you provide your
fingerprints okay um do you know this person work with them okay wait that's incredibly
important information okay suffers from insomnia checks out of towers yeah what about this person
do you know this person of towers could i get fingerprints shit all right cameras are off
database search shit uh no i need to write l p wait wait what what what what what's what's his name
what's his name what's his name what's his name what's his name what's his name
prince now i e e oh yep yep yep yep you gotta find e oh oh where was this oh that's not you
everyone i gotta get your prints i feel like they're probably the ones i gotta get your
prints it's definitely you i gotta search for every employee type l nope m nope h shit uh okay i need
do we get these already type m who else i need other employees um m silva no what was it so
would you say silver you it's the person right here get out of there yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah
well i'm not what am i crazy i know who it is you're under arrest in an hour got it okay so i had
spent the last two hours being a menace to these two i owe these two a huge apology these two what
you know what i'm gonna do i think i'm just gonna tape an envelope with like a like a thousand
dollar best buy gift card to the door it just says sorry on it you know what i mean i've got to do
something i gotta do some home depot or something okay very interesting we don't know anything about
this person really though we just know they work here okay i gotta show up here between nine and
17 on monday through friday very important so what does it say didn't have what it takes killed to
get ahead then they must earn you'll get ahead they must earn my respect what do you do here
what about the lipstick that's what he would i used to be detective you need advice just ask
um first of all i that's a place of business i need i would like to ask you for help you're gone
what's that guy's name i need to talk to that person right that person needs to be talked to
i don't have very much time for that but oh there you are just needed to get changed i see okay
what's your name as if i tell you anything unusual nothing why did you tell me to talk to you is
there another naked person why is everybody walking around naked oh my goodness everybody
has to go to the bathroom at the same time something very weird is going on right now
why why are we all walking down the stairs together wait did work just get out time is it
12 30 i'm wasting a lot of time i solved the murder i just have to go get handcuffs this is
not the way out at all and i'm really sorry i thought this was an exit handcuffs where what
am i doing why do i not have handcuffs already i'm fine i need to eat though oh fried chicken
that sounds good don't eat it this place this people just throw the trash on the ground i'm
putting it in the trash all right city hall right okay arrest the killer full name we have evidence
that places them at the crime scene i don't know where they live and i don't know what the murder
weapon was but i at least i could figure out where they live before i arrest them yeah i'll
just use the record locker this is what i need 25 dollars i don't i have i need to like go steal
stuff they can't i don't even have handcuffs i need money i'll just take it from here doesn't
matter free lock picks what the fuck just happened oh my god use the plunger i can i actually sell
stuff or no poison the pawn shop you can sell wait someone's in there digging the beard uh let's
see what happens i'm curious i have no idea what's gonna happen i don't need the handcuffs but
i mean at least i want the address wait wait i could i'm gonna go to the apartment i got lock
picks i'm the murder weapon might be in there 601 let's do that i could probably get the murder
weapon right now she's work let's go after i close this case we'll do one more um we'll do one more
all right six floor let me just go one more what
you got this red door nobody understands that you you've never heard hold on you guys have
never heard anybody get called a fuck face before a fuck face a person with a face that
instantly pisses you off or something someone's stupid or annoying of course you've heard it
before what do you mean what do you mean new viewers what are you talking about you guys know
nobody here i don't care oh my look at all this red oh did i smell really bad i think i'm good
right let's just confirm got you camera goes down this hallway all right what do you got you're
gonna have to you're gonna have some shit in here we're gonna find right where's the thing that just
says i did it written in bright red ink machine guns computer i have no idea is that an insulin
okay interesting it once was an old man who had all the force of a luger but his daughter took
rain drove the old man insane and she now prices round like a cougar and made starch nothing more
than a booger where does where does this connect to that room oh this is something on the table
over there what about password oh shit oh we're gonna look jump over it okay nine eight two six
what what are you talking about what do you mean the computer the hell's the computer here it is
it's gonna be an email that says i have all the plan and everything what about uh what about
your email lunch date we might have an accomplice that's very possible reminder we're gonna pick a
milk we'll use is it reach into the kitchen it does not yes it does nothing interesting or
important yeah we know that damn it there's got to be something else here shopping list
event something over there too work we there's no um now that there's nothing here unfortunately
nothing here i just have to go and or email email email you missed an email i did what email
i missed an email so it's safe yeah i i don't know i don't know how to get in there insulin
we already have that though i think we're good i think we're i mean i know we know who it is
i just have to go arrest them i just got an insane craving for olive oil on pasta file in the
drawer where we already sold yeah i mean i we know we know everything so might as well just go for
it i wish there was some money no the other draw what am i freaking out right now what are you
talking about i didn't even see this files no there's nothing here guys this is a bug yeah
it's a bug i don't think there's anything in here what about the trash can not a bad idea
i have to get out of here though because i think she's coming back very soon i mean you bet your
ass i'm gonna drink all the rest of the mustard i have to just take insulin why doc doc please
take insulin he's dropping his calling card that's right oh i got saw on the security thing i gotta go
now it's now it's a race right now she's gonna pop up on her phone
it's like someone's in your house someone's in your house and now we just have to cue
the cue like the batman the christen nolan batman music oh my god this is somebody's bedroom
oh get me out get me out of here get me out oh my god get me out of here get me out of here i
don't want to be in here get me out here get me out get me out get me out get me out please
get me out please get me out get me out get me out get me out i'm trying to get out i'm trying you
have no idea you have no idea i didn't want to come in here i really didn't i promise this is
your fucking bathroom please just open the door i'm gonna leave right now just open the door
open the door open just open the door and i'll leave i will leave
a horrifying experience just clamoring out of the vent that would be horrifying oh my goodness
and the whole time this person is going i'll leave i'll leave i'm so sorry i wasn't supposed
to be here i'll leave i'll leave i'll leave what do you mean what are you talking about dude
jesus all right how do i get out of here i'm so turned around a 301 this better not be somebody
else's bedroom okay but it's i think we're in somebody else's house where am i oh god
get me out of here just turn the lights on so i can see where i am okay nice kitchen why can't
i leave just open the door well i didn't learn anything new but i just i know who it is full
name of the killer i did not arrest the killer yet i have evidence because we have the fingerprints
killer lives at what was it 601 it's not listed here how do i uh so one can i just type it in
601 what was it called it was what was the name of the building right yeah right do i have the
murder weapon i don't i do not have the murder weapon it's okay let's go turn it in what about
your knife okay the knife that's in my hand have i been using this the whole time scan it oh shit
that's right i've been using this the whole time no it's not accurate it's not accurate well it's
all right three three or four to five it's fine i don't have enough money to buy handcuffs five
hours to solve one case this is my second case solved time that person out but don't time them
out actually this is my third or fourth case remember the person that came up and stabbed me
and i got them and i got them all right let's see how we did got it got it got it okay how much
money do i get 1,550 bucks very nice okay very good very good very good okay now we're just
gonna do a fuck face run i am going to get a handcuffs lock pick hit wait what i just got
a bunch of shit did i why am i carrying a sponge did i get it reading fail uh let me
get okay i have one more slot here i don't need the knife okay i wait do i want that other thing
i got handcuffs poisoned flash grenade and incapacitator grenade i'm now waiting for
another case close this one right it's closed well this is the other one that i did case closed
wait oh wait i didn't do this one i got so sidetracked did the game i didn't even get
well i didn't even get in the room well i might as well just go do it what was the locate and
steal the item from the mark secret envelope is that do we know who this is correct job listing
no i don't care about this let's wait for i'm gonna close this case now let's wait for another one
i'm gonna go take a drink i need something to eat i'll take a drink is there an upgrade where
i can have more slots what do i what do i what do i put down is it weird that i just put poison on
the ground to take a drink don't mix those up i did it i did it i did it i got it does that
belong to you excuse me that does not belong to you that doesn't belong to you are you dumping
my poison down the drain still holding it we need to investigate this he's gonna poison somebody's
food gonna poison somebody's food he's gonna poison somebody's food he's holding poison
where's the poison what cough cough somebody coughed oh never mind well that was annoying i
really wanted that he put it in the food slow day today i want to how come i can't pick anything up
i want to get a matchbox i not buy matches eat pack where are they there we go okay how do i use
the matches on the cigar like can i not what's the point of buying it if you can't do it
good that's right still waiting for a crime go to the job board instead yeah i could
let's see i just had a job for sale apartment for sale good apartment low price due to odor
okay well no thank you photography skills required you got it what do you want me to do
i could gma street and be sitting with a cola okay gma street is right here with a cola looks
like a cola is this decker good you made it i need a photograph of somebody leads for the
target or in this briefcase take it deliver it under the door at 204 chong building honestly
how do i take a picture of somebody camera okay 204 chong building huge briefcase all right what's
in the briefcase 450 3022 okay i need a camera get it from city hall or elsewhere i'll get it
from city hall is that just in the thing where i bought all the other stuff probably
i don't i don't need this anymore camera there it is perfect okay got a camera take a photo of the
target interesting okay so 204 right 204 and that's chong building no that's the drop off
all right so where what info do i have bald with green hair telephone number okay i have a telephone
number let's call that number whoever this is i'm not interested heard anything unusual i'm not
telling you what's your name okay well they don't care so what are the info do i have to go on
all we know is this person is bald with green hair and they have green eyes and i did take a picture
of them i don't know anything else just look around walk around look for bald people bald with
green hair the guy gave you the address the address was not the address was a drop off
use the phone book to find the name i don't think i'll be able to do that
i don't have much to go on right now maybe i need the briefcase i think i got everything out of it
though just open it handwriting sample what a handwriting sample do you know how a phone book
works i don't think i can reverse look up numbers here it's just i think it just tells you like
weird right i don't think that's no i i can go to their location but i don't have any i can't like
do a reverse number search or something just look at all of them it's on the phone what are you
talking about identify number yeah i what's going on i'm so confused right now what is going on
numbers identify last caller um oh shit okay i'm i'm stupid did that wait
look like a psycho i what's happening right now telephone identify number okay i'll give
no i i'm trying to identify a different number what's happening just type the number what's going
on who am i even calling right now so now do i hit identify do i do this identify last caller
no identify yeah but nobody he didn't call me i call i called him he didn't call me
i called him am i this is 50 bucks every time i'll give you okay this is bugged because this
keeps popping up this is okay the guys this is bugged i'm not even on the phone with anybody this
has popped up like four times it's bugged okay all right goodbye now i'm going to do this
identify last caller i'll give you money then i know that's what i said i know they know i
every i was tell oh a briefcase there's nothing else here right no there's nothing else here you
can inspect i already did put this down yeah i i look i did it return that i can't do anything
else i can i is this is this even possible can i even beat this i don't have any info at all all
the router box i didn't get that tutorial the router box what are you talking about the router
box that wasn't in the tutorial go to the basement of i'm so confused right now why is this game so
hard well this is sandbox mode um i think that's all that exists is sandbox one of that one mission
forget the camera i have it no you have to go to the truck all right listen this is why i'm
supposed to deliver the photo he's not here the chong building second floor i have to slide the
photo underneath i'm just gonna go knock on the door and just talk to this person that i'm supposed
to be delivering this to i'm gonna be like can you help me all i have is a phone number and i know
that he's bald that's there's like a hundred there's like 300 people in this city am i ever
gonna find this person break into random houses and find their phone book i mean how many bald
people in the city really are there with green hair i feel like that's not everybody i feel like
i just don't have enough info scratching my head to figure out what i'm supposed to do here if that
if that one guy is right and i have to i can call from the basement with the router box or something
doesn't matter what building i do it in germa you're a true detective i'm i'm sorry if you
come to me and you say hey dude i need to take a picture of somebody all right how does it work
who do who you want to take a picture of a bald guy with green hair okay um there are there are
10 billion people on earth how many of them have green hair i don't know and here's their phone
number and by the way they don't even answer they don't even care they don't like you they're not
going to listen to you balls with the green hair okay i i got i this mission doesn't make any sense
i want a new one case closed i don't know i don't like that one i want a new one okay what was i
supposed to do the guy i'm gonna walk around and find something with green hair and every time i
call him he hangs up on me what was i supposed to do uh all right let me go back to where do i want
to go i need to ask questions yeah but i can't ask questions to anybody that i don't have any info
for the person i'm asking a question about if i walk up to this person i say hey have you uh do
you know this person a blank question mark image it's not gonna work okay uh let me go get another
mission it's crazy that they these are all none of this is gonna be in your game this whole thing
is generated this whole city is generated that's really cool all from an apartment then check the
building's call logs in the router box no i was never the game never told me that was possible
i never got a router call box tutorial okay let's go what is this a library i need another payphone
with the job listing uh i'm just walking in circles what the fuck am i doing okay please
all that is sacred um what's the place called press f1 and check uh f1 just opens this menu
all right give me something to do here let's do it this one sounds awesome i have suspect may be
armed in danger except at own risk let's go okay details available upon acceptance all right so i
gotta go here and i'm looking for this person i have fingerprints type n shoe size 13 all right
we're looking for a shoe size 13 at this food hall all right let's do it i i have i'm i'm ready
to go it's right here i have handcuffs all right yep um if they're here somewhere type n shoe size
13 if you are you going in the front door guys god damn detective i can go where i i can i can
just open wait no i'm a private investigator never mind i can't even do that anyways i'm literally a
private investigator i'm not even associated with it with any police office force or anything
all right how how big are these shoe prints i just want to know how big your shoes are here we go
all right i got put this down shoe size that's an estimate estimate hold on how come i have a
question so when i hit inspect i can't see info oh there we go okay all right if you click their
name no not you unpin this because i don't need it 13 i think it's i think it's martin
although that could be up to 15 though so who knows i'm gonna keep you over there for now
eight to ten i think is i think it's this guy martin vargas i got everybody right one two three
four there's one more i didn't get one two three four uh i didn't get you and 12 it could be i think
it's you let's go ask around see if we can figure anything out it's a all right i forgot i forgot
i'm not supposed to be in here how do i how am i gonna sneak by this type o type p q type o it
looks like they have it all they probably put their stick they put their stickers up here right
okay so this is he is type s i believe i can connect type s to you if we can find on the type
s that's a reach that's all i can work on right now is reaches all right what's the fastest way
to get out of here there's a vent over here is it a door right there all right so i mean if i if i
can just see him he might be here just hanging out somewhere i'll ask around first hello i have a
question for you do you know this person i saw them at obayashi parade on monday around seven
o'clock they were nearby woo parade at east okay what about you well somewhere around yep why is
everybody a snitch it's a detective game i saw them at street side pavement on monday all right
street side pavement around seven what the hell was that street side pavement where is this around
seven o'clock on monday so that's right around the corner here the job listing give you a
fingerprint uh i don't know i don't think so it did it did thanks for uh helping me play the game
it did and i scanned a shitload of fingerprints i don't remember was n one of them oh my goodness
was n one of them i don't think it was it wasn't i would have i would have remembered n shit well
then okay so we're looking for n and is right here okay they're in here right now i'm just going in
i'm going in i'm going they're in here they're in they're in here i'm going in i'm going in three
two one hi i would like to fingerprint n i would have thought they would be in here
they touched the door recently i think that's what that means all right boot size 13 do i get
your fingerprints i'll give you 50 bucks if you tell me your name final bourbon hmm okay let's
see bourbon fingerprint not sure this is i mean who else is here what i can't even arrest well i
think it's you i'm gonna take pictures shit i need to scan where what he touches just stay still for
a second i just need to see if this is you right here i can see it it wants to do it type v oh
come on so who's got the 13 and it's you i'm shutting this right in their face i think it's
maybe it is you see if i can talk what's your name okay anything unusual no and i get fingerprints
uh-huh you are under arrest get away from me get away from me i'm giving you what are you holding
you holding a brick okay i need to get out of here i did it right he threw that brick what do you
wear what is he holding it is like a piece of like a cinder block all right i got it give me my money
i was gonna say it had to have been one of the two of them right this game is great this is really
fun so the game's in early access right now i am i'm very curious how much they had because
this is already very fun case closed how much is the game um i think it's not expensive i don't
think let me see 40 30 20 it's not expensive it's pretty cheap eat oh shit sorry was i supposed to
take that really cool 20 seems pretty good well now now that's great i look forward to what else
they add to the game uh that's gonna be it that was highly enjoyable will you play it again i will
definitely play this game again i think this is gonna be kind of like coin game where when there's
a major update i'll jump in but this was this was phenomenal this was really fun this is really
funny a lot more of you are gonna do way better at this than i ever would but it was great that
was fucking awesome increase maximum health oh interesting so this is where you go to a clinic
okay yeah that was shadows of doubt it's on steam if you like what you saw definitely go get it
seems like they're making something really really cool and that's it can you throw the
grenade before the stream ends yeah why not sure okay well i didn't think it's gonna be that much
of an explosion i thought i backed up enough i went to a place where there was nobody there
and i'm like okay it's a lot bigger than i thought it was holy shit hey while i'm in here
give me a favor and install one of these things help me please come on come and get me come on
oh all right it shoots i forgot why is there a automatic gatling machine gun
in the corner of a hospital that seems a little bizarre but it's all right all right guys thanks
for watching the plan is i will see you guys on saturday we're gonna go saturday sunday it's
good to be back i am back to normal thanks for sticking around i'll see you guys on the weekend
saturday sunday i don't know what we're gonna do but we'll probably do i have a huge this was list
one out of i think 15 games that i want to play this top the list though you do omega gaming
uh no just regular gaming weekend nothing out of the ordinary nothing crazy maybe we'll play
breath of the wild a little bit maybe on sunday i don't know i'm gonna get left so far behind
with uh tears of the kingdom oh shit this is not even there's gonna be a lot of names on this list
i've been gone for a while a ton of people resubbed when i came back right now thanks guys that's
it's a lot of names here that's never uh you're never obligated to do that though so just be
aware of that thank you it's cool to just hang out too i'll see you saturday it's also mother's
day on sunday that's right call your mother on sunday i say that at the end of almost every stream
call your mother on sunday i need the music too i thought i set that back up again i guess not
sorcery that's right uh we will get a hard date for sorcery this weekend i'm not gonna play it
this weekend but i'll give you a date this weekend is that good does that satisfy you
yeah we're gonna have to do a recap though for sure where where did i put these files what the
hell am i doing where oh okay there they are hey let's play us out right at the end too
we're gonna sit here and listen to it for a minute though is the battle axe stream just
never gonna happen oh that's a good question i still want to lots of there's lots of things i
want to do hope you're doing well and feeling well appreciate that i've been doing all right
i've been doing good that was a lot of fun i got confused on that last mission but um that was a
blast thanks for joining me during that see you soon take care see you this weekend have a great
one good night