Hey, it's here. It's finally here. It's here. Let's freaking go! Let's freaking go!
Hey guys, how you doing? Are you guys ready for Elden Ring? I am. I'm very prepared.
I'm- I came the most prepared I've been to any livestream you've ever seen.
Except for obviously like, you know, the- the event ones, right?
This is the most prepared I've been for a gaming stream in six and a half years. I had a big salad
with like olive oil and radishes and lettuce. It's- I've- I have all bunch of nutrients.
I'm drinking a matcha powder vitamin b drink. It's super hydrating. I- I- this is the most
prepared I've ever been in my life. This thing is probably 40 ounces by the way. Oh, I don't care.
Hey, that's not- what are you to- no. Get in here and say, let's freaking go! What the fuck?
This is- this is- okay. What? This is like a huge deal. This- this is like- okay. You want to know
why this is a big deal? Have you guys seen the reviews for this game? This apparently is like
masterpiece. Like better than Bloodborne. I'm gonna hold my reservations on this. I'm gonna wait to
give my kind of honest opinion on this game. But people are talking about how it's- it's like
the ocarina of time of this generation. So, holy shit, that's quite an achievement potentially.
In a world of a lot of disappointing AAA releases over the last year or two,
this is a big deal if it's good. I have no idea what I'm gonna play as. I know there's all these
classes. I got a notepad here. I'm gonna have like a notepad on screen that I can- because
you're supposed to- you gotta keep track of what you're doing because there's no quest markers or
anything. But I've been looking forward to this. I liked Sekiro, but I didn't love Sekiro. Yeah,
I wasn't like a massive fan of that game. So, if this is anything like the previous kind of
Souls games, if this is like an open world Dark Souls type game, then I mean, I don't know what
to tell you besides this could be the best game I've ever played. Bloodborne is up there at like
number one or number two for favorite game of all time. If this thing runs at 60 fps,
it's open world Bloodborne essentially. Open world Dark Souls. I'm- I gotta- I have to quell my
hype here because I'm- you know I like these games, right? But I don't know. I'm very excited.
I'm incredibly excited because Sekiro beat you. Yeah. Sekiro was really hard. It was.
I remember the last boss of Sekiro was, what, an entire two streams or at least a full like
six or seven hours straight. There was a point after like hour number four or five where I just-
I was like, I'm not gonna finish this. This is not gonna happen. It will not happen.
It absolutely will not happen. I'm not gonna waste any more time. The stream is ready. The game is
ready. I don't- I think I'm gonna start in offline mode because I really don't want to uh-
I- I kind of want to like enjoy the world. I don't want to get like invaded.
I like- Balsack 500 is gonna come and like kill me in three hits. That's my opinion on the- on the
Ukraine. Uh, yeah. I'll give you one small little thing that I just- it's- it sucks. And it's- it's
really really saddening to know that, I don't know, we're still doing this shit. People are still
fucking killing each other and shit. It's- it's not fu- it's bad. And as much as I would like to
sit here and tell you and talk about it, just really hope that- I mean, uh, I don't have to be
the first person to tell you, but I'm honestly gonna just try to escape from it. That's the whole
point of this stream. Um, I'm sure a lot of you guys have been up pretty much like I was late last
night. Kind of just looking over it, going over the whole situation and going like, what the fuck,
man, what is happening? I obviously feel for the people of Ukraine, it's fucking awful.
I just really really hope this doesn't turn into something even more sinister and awful.
But that's all we can do, right? That's all we can do. So without further ado, um, we're gonna
play Elden Ring. Here we go. I think a seven's fine. Seven's good. I think that looks good.
This looks good. Yeah, I- I don't want to speak too much on it just because, obviously,
I use this stream as a way to escape myself and I've made comments about that in the past during
other kind of times of, um, of uncertainty and of real like kind of pain in the world and really
shitty stuff happening in the world. So like I've made previous comments and statements that this
stream is a place for me to get away from it. So that's how I'm gonna treat it. What fucking
class am I gonna play? I- I tried to figure this out. I was desperately trying to think of what
class I wanted to start with. I know that like all these- it doesn't matter, right?
Because I was thinking this game has like magic. It's a magic game where like everybody has like
spells and abilities and stuff. But also you can be a caster. You can be a straight-up caster.
But I don't know if I want to do that because I don't want to beat Cheese Andy on my first
playthrough. Because you guys know that with every one of these Souls games, there's gonna
be one magic move that you can get like halfway through the game that will like two hit kill every
boss, right? I mean it's the first week the game's out. That's probably gonna happen.
Samurai, all right. Let me see. Show stats. Oh, that's better. All right, where's just like the
default- I thought that guy was actually naked. I was just like, holy shit, they really don't care,
huh? Prophet? All right, so let me- let me see what these stats are. This is the faith class,
right? Astrologer is the sorcerer. Bandit. Arcane. Okay, arcane is not like plus damage to any spells
or anything, right? Samurai? Samurai? All right, what are other streamers doing? Because I want
to do the exact opposite of that because I want to be like Contrary and Andy. I want to be the guy
that's playing the one thing that everybody else isn't. So when people scroll through the like
50,000 streams of this game, I can put in my title. Bandit gameplay! And they'll come to my stream
instead. I don't want to do the- no, I'm not doing this one. No, I want to start with a weapon. I
don't want to start with the club. I haven't watched anybody, okay? Prisoner. Prisoner is
kind of like everything. It's intelligence, dexterity. That's kind of- Battle Mage?
What are the weapons there? Prophet. I don't really usually play the faith-based
stuff in any of these From Software games. I- should I just be- spell it? I should- maybe
I should be spells. Should I be a sorcerer? I feel like that's cheating though. Or should I just do
Vagabond, which is just- okay, you just use sword and hit things. Do the confessor.
That's kind of cool, but it's faith. I don't really like to play faith. I think prisoner
might be up my alley as well as- no, not necessarily samurai. Prisoner? All right,
I'm telling you, I'm leaning towards prisoner, astrologer, or bandit. I can't decide. This is
my first playthrough too. Like, this is the worst part. I don't know what I want to do.
Do a poll? All right, we're gonna do a poll in the chat right now,
because I would do any one of those three. We've got bandit, we've got prisoner, and we've got
astrologer. Again, prisoner is kind of like a battle mage. Astrologer is spells only. Bandit is,
I think, like decks? Like quick stuff? Maybe ranged? Bows? Daggers? What are we doing? Oh,
this is unanimous. Play as classic sonic. Oh, that's cheating, because the guy has a-
the guy has a- wait, wait, wait, wait, back, back, back, how do I hit back? That's cheating.
The guy has like a hat on. Yeah, the guy's got like a weird helmet on. That is actually cheating.
Oh no, they're picking the guy with like the hat, like the weird metal hat thing. That's probably
what I was going to pick anyways, I'll be honest, because I like casting spells, but I like swinging
too. All right, we're going prisoner. Let's go. A lot of decks, a lot of intelligence. All right,
let's do it. Please choose a body type. Type A or type B? What's the difference? Type A? Name.
Ooh, actually looks pretty cool. Name. Oh, we need a good name. Frogman, Frogman Jr. I think this is
going to be Frogman's legacy. Didn't choose B. I don't know what B is, but um, hmm, Flash.
Flash. That's like a, that's like a Sonic OC character name. Um, Edward. Oh shit,
that's actually an awesome name. Edward is a good name. Yeah, I think that's perfect. Okay, that's
a good- okay, body type. Yeah, that's what I want. Edward. Okay, body type A or B. Okay, we're going
to go bigger. Age, we'll do, uh, I always do Aged. Origin Pro- oh, what, what's the point of that?
Actually, I can see this better. So, intelligence. Spells are affected by dexterity as well.
Dexterity is cast speed, I think. I did my research, don't think I didn't. So, this build
looks like you want to do- and I don't know what mind is. I think mind is uh, is mana. Keepsake.
Oh, I mean none of this really ever matters in these games, but let's find out. Lands between
ruin. The gold? Grace. Shining in the eyes of the people of the lands between. Used to- okay. So,
they changed the name of the experience stuff in every single one of these games, right?
So, ruins is just blood echoes, is just souls, right? Anything that I should get? Golden seed?
It does matter. It usually doesn't. Golden seed washed ashore from the lands between.
Said to reinforce sacred flasks. I don't even- I don't know what any of this is. Imp ashes.
Old spirits within. We need to facecam? You got it! Uh, cracked pot. I don't know. No, you don't
know? No, fuck that. No facecam. You guys might give me a facecam. Maybe if you're good. If you
guys are good, then I'll turn it on. Only if you're good. Looking for certain throne items.
Two stone keys shaped like swords. Bricks. Oh, by the way, also I have this too.
Like, I can write down like, uh, found guy by tree in Anor Londo, right? Like, uh,
this game apparently has no help at all with quests. So, I need to be prepared to write some
stuff down. All right, bewitching brand. Originate from, I don't know, what is it? Five sacred
branches charged with eguiling power. Five pieces of boiled prawn. Boost physical damage. Oh,
physical damage negation. Okay, so this is like a- probably a temporary damage reducer.
Oops, I'm sorry I punched you. Notepad Andy. What? I- in case I need it. You know, this- dude,
I have been told that this is as hard to- this is like playing Monkey Island for the first time.
Before there was a game fax on it. I need to be prepared to know where like the bubble gum,
the shoe, and the combined stick and- and like tree branch go, okay? Like, I need to know what
the fuck this happens. I need to know how this works. I need to be able to write this stuff down.
Do game fax, not stop stalling. This is not- I'm- there's no stalling here. I'm trying to- I gotta-
All right, I'm picking the- I'm gonna pick the Crimson Amber Medallion, because like it's just
the- it's just the starting item that gives you a little bit more HP. You take all this shit off
anyways. Stalling. Imagine saying stalling in the first 20 minutes of any Dark Souls type game.
That's the whole point. You're supposed to make it like a character and pick- I- don't rush me,
okay? Don't rush me through this. This is a- I've been waiting for this game for 30 years.
Okay. All right, let's go with the aristocrat. All right, voice. Can I get a preview? Oh, sample.
I like this one. Uh, I think this is good. This is fine. Fine. All right, hair and face.
Graphics look great. A structure. Oh god, this- I'm gonna be here for so long. I promise I won't be
here for that long, all right? Because I- I want to play the game really badly. I think we're just
gonna do random. You sit here with a helmet on half the time anyways. How do I do the- where's
the random random random random? It's gonna be two hours of this. No, it won't. I'll- okay.
I am gonna just do the one thing that I do in every video game. All we're gonna get to is
the point where I get to the chin and the jaw and I make it big and huge. That's the only thing that
you ever care about, that I ever care about with any characters I've ever made, is just make the
guy's chin big like Thanos. That's it. That's a defining feature of every single character I've
ever made. No, we need deep, like right here. It kind of looks like me. Wait, did I- how did I do
that? It's not- my chin's not that long though. All right, that looks good. This actually- this
is what I feel like I look like in the mirror. Okay. Oh my god, that looks weird. I like it.
Okay. Contouring. I kind of like that except we'll go like this. All right, never mind,
I'm gonna stay- I'm gonna be here for a little while. Ah, hmm. Dinner? Dinner? It's shaggy.
Oh no, it is. Mouth slant. Oh, occlusion? That's okay. Mouth protrusion? This is how far out the
mouth is. Let's go right there. Out the width. Pull back. Oh, I'm sorry, I'm not gonna do iPad
photo booth guy. Nope. Or like every other filter on Snapchat. No. That makes him look a little too
normal. This feels like what every history book depiction of a peasant looks like. All right,
let's do lip shape. Expression. What does the other one look like? What does sad look like?
That's not really sad. How about this? Okay, I like that. Oh, I mean, is it funny? Yeah. But,
okay. Hold that back. Did somebody just say this guy looks like Ace Attorney? I didn't catch the
whole message. What? This does not look like Ace Attorney. Okay, cheeks. This is where it's gonna
get fun. All right, let's go all the way up. No, all the way down. Like right here. Kind of sad now.
All right, I like it. Well, he looks like he's like a hexagonal. Why is he like a hexagonal?
There's not enough polygons on this guy's face. No, that's too easy. Not that ridiculous. I want
him to at least, okay, right there. I'm gonna keep it for now. Okay. I'm gonna keep it for now,
but I can't promise it's gonna stay. He looks powerful. It does, it really does look like
Shaggy. It looks like Shaggy went to the county fair and had one of those caricatures
made where he's riding his surfboard on a wave. Or he's on a tandem bicycle with a Daphne or
something. No, that's way too much. That's way too much. We're pulling it back a little. This
looks like a joker. It does look like a joker. All right, nose height. Oh, it's not gonna be the nose
guy. That's fine. That's fine. I'm not doing anything else to it. Eyes. Okay. No, what's it?
Is this a DreamWorks character? It's like Coraline's dad. That looks okay. Goodness.
I like that. I think that's perfect. I like the wide. Wide is better. Like right there.
Maybe not so much. Like that. All right, that's a really good start. Somebody said,
Shaggy from Scooby Doo after being hit with gamma particles. Like a Hulk?
Look at this one. Brow out. All right, he's slowly turning into the bird for the Muppets.
And I made that exact same joke the last time I played Dark Souls. So you better know I'm excited.
Big forehead or no forehead at all. Like his eyebrows go into his hairline.
Forehead protrusion. Pull it back a little bit. Height. All right. Dude, my eyes are like this.
I got this huge eyebrows on. This just makes him sadder. All right, fine. All right, facial balance.
Wait, what do you mean nose size? What? I'm gonna keep it here. Nose forehead ratio.
Face protrusion. That's too much. That's too cartoonish. Like right here.
I actually think it's perfect. I don't think I need to do anymore. We do have to do something
about the hair though, I think. Well, maybe the hair is perfect. All right, so let's go with hair.
What we got. Are you sure this is Shaggy with gamma rays and not Jerma? Jeremy with gamma rays?
That's what I feel like I did. I feel like it just made me. I like that. I like that too, a lot.
I like that way more than this one. It looks like one of the, like quote,
English band members in every fucking cartoon. He has a voice like this, guarantee it. Oh yeah,
he's got a voice like this. Guarantee it. All right, 12 is where we're at right now.
Although this is really good too. I like this one a lot. All right, 12, 13. This one's like
too real. I don't like this one. No, I think it's either 12 or 13. All right, what do we think?
Is it cartoon English band member one or cartoon English band member two? 12 or 13? I could go with
either one. Yep, it's gonna be 12. Oh, it changed. It changed from cartoon English band member
to emo band member in one second. Oh, wait, hold on. I gotta change that.
I think it's gonna have to stay brown. I just, all right, this is just Criss Angel.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no. It's English cartoon band member. I mean, I could go back and
just make him a sorcerer, change his name to Mind Freak, and no, no, no, no. No, we're sticking with
what I had. Or Kiss band member. Yeah, I mean, I'm going with this. Lustre? Let's make him shiny.
White hairs. Not too many. Maybe a few. That looks all right. Make him more greasy. No, I'm not
making it greasy. Eyebrows. You can't even see them, so who cares? Facial hair. All right,
this is a big deal. Oh, all right, this is actually, actually, this could be the one.
It could be six here. I think it's six. Yep, it's six. Match hair, match hair, stubble. What does
that mean? Oh, thick. Yeah, that's fine. Eyelashes. Can't see them. Eyes. Can't really see them, but
I mean, whatever. You can't see these. You literally cannot even see them, so it doesn't matter.
It doesn't matter. You can make his eyes like green or blue or what? I don't know.
Doesn't matter. You can't see them anyway. Bores. Skin lustre. Dark circles. You can't really see
them. Make it greasy. No. You can't really see that anyways. All right. Eye patches? No, you can't
see this either. Eye patch. No, I'm not him. He's not getting an eye patch. All right, I think it's
done. I think we're ready. Now we need to do body. Wait, you can make him have a tiny head? Make sure
you have a small head? Where's all the body hair? I don't see it. Where is it? Yeah, body hair. Yeah,
I mean, it's kind of there. This is funny right now, but this is going to annoy. I'm going to
hate this in like an hour and a half. I'm going to hate this equally, right? It's too big.
No, it's not. It's not Eren Jaeger. It's not Eren Jaeger. Okay. It's kind of close. I'll give him
kind of a big head because I want to be able to see the helmets because it's cool. All right.
That's fine. That's fine. That's fine. I'm done. Done. It's over. I'm done. I'm done. I'm done. I'm
done. Okay. Save it. Was that it? Save to favorites. Save. Reset appearance. Yes. Okay. I think we're
good to go. See, look it. He's got the... You guys made me do all this stuff to put this fucking helmet
on him. All right. Are you guys ready to go? Wait, what does he look like as other characters?
Fuck. It's perfect. No. How many times have I said no in like 20 minutes? Relax. I'm going to get my
ass kicked. I'm doing... We're going to go with prisoner, but I'm going to take the helmet off.
All right. Are you ready? I'm ready to start Elden Ring. That's just a Titan. You can probably
hide the helmet. All right. I am ready to play. I've been waiting for this game for 100 years.
This is it. Let's go. Are you ready? Let's go. I'm fucking excited. I'm ready to go. I've been
waiting for this. I'm going to get a nice sip of my matcha green tea. All right. Cutscene incoming.
Let's go. Oh, yes. Pale blood, you say? Well, you've come to the right place. For the great
Elden Ring was shattered. Fuck. In our cross the fog, the lands between Queen Marika the Eternal
is nowhere to be found. Godwin the was first to perish. Come on, Godwin. New meme. New meme
unlocked. Marika's offspring, demigods all claimed the shards of the Elden Ring. Taint
of their newfound strength triggered the shattering which no Lord arose. A war
leading to abandonment by the greater will. Oh, rise now, ye tarnished, ye dead who yet live.
Call of long-lost grace speaks to us all. Poor alone, chieftain of the Badlands,
ever-brilliant gold mask. Fear the deathbed companion, the loathsome dung-eater,
and Circadian Ophnia. We all know it. I have no idea what the fuck any of that was. I couldn't
follow any of it, but its art was really good. I should be writing all this down. No, I got the
notepad, but I'm not gonna. The only thing you had to write down was dung-eater. For the Elden and
become the Elden Lord. All right. All right. Let's go. All right. New the Ring. Okay.
Just like, okay. What do we got? Let's test out the moves for a second.
Okay. Oh shit. This guy's a fencer. I don't want to play a fencer. I'm gonna get my ass kicked.
I don't play. I never play with the fencing ever. Kind of restart. Oh, this is bad. Praise the Elden
Ring. I actually did not mean to rate that poor. I tried. I thought start was yes. I'm the one
person. I'm what? I'm such a contrarian. Well, I don't know that yet because I haven't played the
game yet. So I'm not going to praise it yet. Dislike tarnished, wisened finger. Okay. What does
that say? Well, the path be broken and uncertain. Claim your place as Elden Lord. So I'm supposed
to be a Lord. All right. Be wary of message. Oh shit. I'm online right now. Is that bad? Seek
life. Okay. I'm gonna, I gotta play offline because I've quite look for secrets. Wait,
there's an actual jump button. No, there's not. Five fingers, butthole. Oh yeah. Great. Thanks.
What does this one say? I tried poop in face. That's it. There's a jump sprint. All right,
let's go. Whoa. Well, chapel of anticipation. What's over here? This door is blocked shut.
All right. Wait, wait. Okay. Where's my, with my mouse door next to spawn. Where am I?
Door next to spawn is blocked shut. All right. That's all I need to know. What do you mean
cheating? No, what you've like, I, if I was this character, I wouldn't walk around with like a
pen and paper or something as I had ink back in like the 1200s. Okay. There's nothing wrong with
what I'm doing. Necessary item ahead. Is there actually, can I go down this ledge? Why can I
do this? I can walk over here for some reason. Why nothing down there? What did you do? Everyone
just walks off here and dies. I, okay. I'm not doing that. I'm not going to have the first fall
joke be an intentional fall joke. All right. Let's go. Camera controls. Yep. First off,
good luck. I keep saying poor and I'm trying to start should be yes. Wait, what's this? What's
that? What's down there? What's over here? All right. You will fall joke. Yeah, but not like right
now. Is there a lucieri walls in this game? Praise the roll. Okay. This is really pretty.
This is beautiful. Really? Can I, well, there was a, there's a way to jump up the ledge.
Is there a penalty for dying like in the other games? I hope not. All right. Let's go. Let's go.
Let's go. He actually did it. Well, they put a jump in the game. There has to be something over
here and I'm going to take my time. Retrieve law. Oh, okay. From software doesn't just put stuff
like this for no reason. Is this just here for no reason? I'm going to miss something. All right.
Don't die in the same spot again. I'm going to try one more time. All right. For what? What does
this do? There's nothing. Okay. There's no reason to do what he just did. Let's go.
I like the compass though. That's very helpful. All right. Oh, all right. Is there, is there a
champion Unger? No. What's his name? Ingir? Ingman? What's the guy's name at the very beginning?
Amphion Bunger? No, no, no. What's the guy's name in the beginning of Dark Souls three?
Ing... Gundyr? What did I say? Ungir? Undyr? Not Bunger. Gundyr. Gundyr. Unger. Undyr. Whatever
his name is. All right. You're distracting me. All right. There's nothing over here. It's just
pretty. It's really sucks that I have this fencing weapon though. I have like this dung eater. Cool.
All right. Let's do it. Wait, what about over here? Barbecue, bacon, Bunger, Bunger? Nothing.
I know completionist Andy. I know, but I need to see what's over here. I like the statue.
This is definitely a... Yeah. I knew it. I knew there was going to be... I knew there was going
to be a Bunger. I knew it. How do I cast spells? How do you cast spells? It's not that one. All
right. How do I cast spells? Not like that. I'm dead already. Oh, that's supposed to happen.
I don't even have a heal. Cool. Ooh, that was a bad voice crack, but I'm very excited. It's the
horse. Nice. The Elden Ring is kind of a powerful thing, but you get it and you become a lord or
something. I'm like that, I would assume. I just realized this helmet never can come off.
Your head can't come out of that hole. What? The Lask of Crimson Tears. All right. That's
definitely the Estus. That's just like in Dark Souls 3. Here's the two. There's the magic one.
Brave Tarnished, take the plunge of learning and remembrance. Oh, I was about to jump off.
Recall the arts of war and your warrior's blood. What's that up there? A blood display. Wait,
you can... Whoa. Wait, how do I do that? That was interesting. Impaling thrust. What does that mean?
What? If only I had a pickle. You hold it. That's weird. That's kind of weird that it turns it off.
Okay, if only I had a pickle. Whatever. Can't get up there.
Oops. And go up. I don't think I'm going to go down just yet. Free thing. You hold tree. Praise the
tree. Write that down. No, I don't have to write that down. Are you ready? But wait, am I taking
the plunge? I'm actually really glad that I accidentally just did that because I probably
would have got hurt a lot. Okay, cool. I think I would have died. All right, I'm going to use my
fencing thing. This is a cool looking cave though. Sites of grace. Resting at a site of grace will
restore your HP. Yeah, so this is bonfire. Restore his flasks. Yeah, most enemy. Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Is there fast travel between them? Very little fall damage. Think secure. Really? Okay, that's
good to know. Pass the time. Oh, that's right. There's a full day and night cycle where different
shit happens. Wow. Okay. All right. Well, here we go. Rest the camera. Do I have a parry? I don't.
How do I- Okay, that spells. Thank you. What's it doing? That takes a long ass time. Okay, how much
mana did that use? Is there a- Can I turn- Hold on. I know I'm going to break immersion here,
but is there a way that I can just make it so it doesn't turn the HUD off? Yeah, yeah, yeah. It's
on. Keep it on. Yeah, I much prefer it like this. Sorry for your immersion. What is impaling thrust?
Why is it on my HUD? You can memorize sorceries. Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah. Must
have a staff. Uh-huh. Weapon art L2. All right, I see. I'm not going to use magic on these guys.
Why would I? Yeah, I know how to play. I just took- Okay, the tutorial did the thing and I had-
That's actually a really cool move though. From software, why did you- Hold on. What are you doing?
They're doing the thing. They're doing the pause mid-swing tutorial. What happened?
Oh, this is fucking beautiful. Who's that? I can do that too, you know. Is that going to hit him?
Oh, wow. That's good. Let's go. You have to drop something, right? Change the button prompts in
the PC. I actually don't mind why being- I think it's okay. You went down the combat tutorial hole
and you're complaining about tutorial. No, I'm just kidding. I'm actually just kidding.
Yeah, you can do it with two hands. Wait, what? I can't hold this in two hands.
I'm gonna hit him in the back. Oh, hell yeah. Swing. Swing. Swing at me. You dick. Really?
Wait, oh, I have a shield. I do have a shield. Okay, cool. Swing at me. I always hate fighting
the guys with big shields. They're annoying. I definitely want to- How do I- Because I do
want to hold this in two hands. Sometimes. Let me do that. Hold on. I know how to use the menu.
What does this do? Use to write me- Ah, I see, yeah. Y and RB. RBY. Oh, okay. Because it was
just Y in the other game. I'll tell you right now, that is going to fuck me up big time.
But I'll get used to it. Let's go. Take the helmet off. No. The backstabbing? Dude,
they brought backstabbing back? Are you serious? That's such a fucking shit thing that they brought
back. That's so annoying. I really thought they were going to get rid of that shit. It's so annoying.
Makes the game so easy. Not missing anything, right? No. That was a minus two joke. I'm just
kidding around. I'm very excited. Let me be excited. That's actually really good. Should I go down?
No, this- Okay, wait. This is where that guy was. The bow and arrow.
That uses magic? It does, you're right. How fast is it? Rouch. Rouch to make it harder for enemies
to discover you. There's a stealth? Wait, they added stealth. Wow. Okay, that's cool.
That's really cool. So I'm imagining if you're in kind of like tall grass like this.
Oops. Well done, wolf. Ramped area ahead. Yep. I wonder what the range is. Yeah, the stance
breaking. Yeah, yeah, yeah. You want me to go ahead and do it? Is there no jump attack? Usually
it's what up and- You will never use stealth, I'm sure of it. You can't be that positive about it.
It's jump and right trigger. Oh my goodness. Okay, there's a dedicated jump button. That's right.
They actually added a dedicated jump button. Tutorial boss. Soldier of Godric. Let's go.
Hard counters. Yeah, yep, yep. Wait, you can perform a counter attack immediately after blocking
an- Wait, what? Was this in the other games? Right trigger immediately after blocking an attack.
Block in R1? What does that mean? Is it just a parry? Is it just a parry? It's different? Add in
then- Right. I hear something walking around. Okay, cool. It's after you guard. Right trigger,
not right bumper. Okay, cool. It's a held block parry. Does the shield even do it that I have?
I feel like this kind of shield would not do that.
Parry the platypus. Shield will do it. Okay, I gotta- There's the item I couldn't get.
Strength, new. Knee mode? That's it? You didn't do the voice.
I actually need to practice this because it'd be embarrassing if I get it wrong.
All right, well, that was cool. Let's go. It's like, oh, parry the platypus. I'm going to take
over the entire world, parry. No, it's me doofus. But that was actually really, really good and I
would say that was probably the best one you've heard anybody do. I'm not sure that you could
probably find somebody on Twitch right now that could do that better than what I just did.
I have to give myself a little bit of credit. Uh, well, I have the bonfire now.
Use tarnish-filled fingers. Yeah, this is co-op. I'm not going to be really doing it.
What's this? Use stone sword key. Do I have one? Write that down. Whatever this is. I need a stone
sword key for the bonfire. What's this place called? Here it is. Okay. Why is it so spaced out?
All right. Gamer notes. I always forget this stuff and I never remember where it is and I will sit
here and I will beg you guys to tell me where the gargoyle statue was and everybody was going to
laugh at me and then you're going to send me in a completely different place. What's this?
Lever ahead. Yeah, you're blocking the lever. I can't even do the thing.
Can't even. They're blocking it. I can't even activate it. Is that supposed to be happening?
What a liar. There's no path here. Elevator. What about back here?
Oh, okay. Let's go. Do you like video games or are you a liar?
Playing a video game right now that I really like so far. You'll see after I die like five or six
times to the first actual boss and I tell you that games aren't really for me anymore and I'm
kind of done. Nothing here. All right. Let's go. Dude, the feeling of... Wow. Wow. Wow. Wow. Wait,
wait, wait, wait, wait. Guys. Oh my God. This is unbelievable. No way. Look at the tree in the
distance. I can just go anywhere now, right? That's the whole point of this game. Elden Ring,
you can just do anything. This actually looks fucking crazy. Didn't expect gorgeous view.
Look at that over there. This is insane. This is actually crazy. I'm going to go around the back.
What? Oh my God. There's more stuff over there. How do I get there? How do I get over there? I'm
going to go that way. This is going to be so bad. I am controlled in From Software games because
there's only one direction you can usually run, but this is going to be a disaster.
In every corner of the lands between you will find fruits and flowers,
mushrooms and butterflies and various other useful materials. There's a crafting
row of fruit. Dude. Wow. Those, oh, those are hostile. These bald eagles. Wait, am I high
enough level to fight these two bald eagles? Are they hostile? No, they're not. But do I need them
for anything? I think I needed to do that for some reason. Poor toad. What? Oops. Oh my God. I feel
so, I feel awful. I didn't want to do that. I was just testing my woof. I didn't want to do that.
What about the, they were like friends or they were friends or siblings or lovers or I don't know,
one of those things. I'm really sorry. I didn't mean to do that. What is that? There's just random
animals. What? Okay. This is crazy. I forgot where I was. All right. Let's go over here.
There's a crab down there. Do I have the horse yet? Or no, probably not.
Okay. So I don't see anything over there. I'm going to wait. There's more materials.
Herd leaf flower. Somebody over here. I'm just going to go this way. Wait, there's a person.
Roots. What's that? What's that? Oh shit, there's a person. Okay.
Guidance of grace. Grace exists to guide the tarnished and lead them along the proper path.
Even now, some sites of grace retain that power. Their golden rays will guide you along your way.
This is pointing in the direction that I have to go? That's it?
There's just a person pointing in a direction? Use your map to check your current position as
well as the terrain and surrounding structures. You can update your map with new information
by finding map fragments at Steeles along the road. You can also use the map to freely place
beacons of light to serve as landmarks. Okay. So you're going to find map fragments and you
can place markers. Oh Jesus. With the map menu, you can check your current position and terrain
and buildings in the surrounding area. You can also place beacons of light to serve as a landmark.
Lastly, for your map, you can select any site of grace that you've discovered and traveled there
instantaneously. Really? Oh my goodness. That's awesome. Cool. And it's pointing this direction.
Are you getting this? I think I'm getting this. All right. So what if I place a beacon
over there? Does it show up? It does. How many can I place? Okay. You can place like,
you can place like step five beacons. I don't remove these. All right. I'm going to have to
write down like beacon one. Cheshire Trest. Can't open yet. This is going to be the best game I've
ever made. Okay. Let's go. Hail Vlad. I told you someone was going to do it.
What? Why do you say that?
That guy's scaring me back there.
You may also behold its golden rays pointing in a particular direction.
This is such a good looking game too. That is the guidance of grace. The path punished must
travel. I'm so excited. Relax. Grace's guidance holds the answers. It will lead you to the path
you're meant to follow. So, okay. Wherever this thing is pointing is where my like a current
objective is. L plus ratio plus maidenless. Such grace. Yep. It's okay. The grace and we
got to get grace. All right. Do you do anything else? Is this a vendor or something? Or should
I just just literally go back behind this guy and shove my sword through the back of his neck
through his throat? Because I mean, you might watch other streamers that play these games one
way, but I kill every NPC. I don't know. A lot of new viewers might not know that. I kill every
single NPC and my character stays at like level four. And then I quit the game in like two hours.
So if that's what you don't want, then I'm actually just kidding. Don't leave because people
probably just like, Oh, fuck this guy. And they left. Don't click the X yet. I am kidding. I beat
Sekiro on stream and I was a fun game. Let's go. All right. We're going to go that way. I got to
fight this guy. Very obviously the guy on the horse was this. Summoning pools? In each area
you may find effigies of martyrs. These effigies are summoning pools. You'll find it easy to summon
other players at these locations as co-op and hostile summoning science created. Okay. This is
like the summoning zone. I don't need it. There's only one boss that I ever summoninged. And that
was the big dragon from dark souls three that we like Mario partied and beat it. I'm saying that
like anybody remembers that when that the channel had like, I think like 1500 concurrent viewers,
like when I played that game, why am I saying, do you guys remember that? Maybe somebody do.
All right. Um, I'm, I'm, I'm going to, all right, I'm going to shoot this guy.
Let's go. Didn't miss. I sneak up and backstab pre sentinel. All right, let's go. What the fuck
just happened to the game? Why is the game like slowing up and speeding up? What the
fuck is that? 30 and 90. The game like slowed down and then sped up and then slowed down again.
All right. On dying, you'll be revived at the last site of grace that you visited.
It was drop any runes. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. If you die again, they're gone. Yeah.
Compass will show you where the body is. That's actually really helpful. That was weird. Is that
the kind of bugs that people were talking about? There's like video problems. Oh, hopefully that's
not that prevalent because that kind of sucks. You can jump. Whoa, dude, what the fuck? That
actually is like hard to play with. I get it. I didn't hit him. Oh shit. I don't think I can
fight this guy right now. I think it's too hard. You know, way too long. Is this hitting him? I
fucking hate the stupid fencing weapon. All right. Breathe. Wait, wait, what was the comment?
Lower the graphic settings. Is that sort of actually do something to help that? Yeah. So
like every so often, the game will like slow speed up. Is this something I should turn off?
Turn off auto adjust in settings. Whoa. Okay. Advanced settings. Wait, I know it was right
there. Auto detect off. Oh, no, no. Auto adjust. Where is it? Is that what you mean? Is a different
one? There's bullet time. It's the auto detect. Yeah. It's not in here too, right? Motion blur.
No, let's see what that helps. I mean, it only really happens in the first 10 seconds, 20 seconds
of a fight, but that's still kind of horrible. I can kill this guy. Let's go. Although I'm just
going to be, I think I'm just going to cast at him. Did I pull him somewhere else? I mean,
the game's too pretty. All right, let's go. Oh, that's bad. That actually is why I got hit.
Back it up. Oh, fuck, even one hit. Ah, shit. Oh, that's like, that makes the game even harder.
So that's what they wanted to make the game more difficult. I'll turn the graphics down.
What do you think is doing it? I wonder. Reflection quality, shadow quality. This is AO. Try that.
All right. It's on medium. Oh, but look, it's ugly now. Let's see if that does anything. Fight
him up on the higher hills. Don't fight him down here. Whoa. Oh no. Is that coming through? You
guys seeing that too? Or is that only coming through on my screen? Like fight him over here?
Let's try it. It feels a little better. Yeah, that feels much better. I waited way too long to swing.
Yeah, that feels a million times better. I'm out of MP. Whoa. Oops. Oops. Come on. Geez, Andy.
What's that? What does that mean? Yeah. I'm out of magic ammo. Fuck. Okay. I got to pay attention to
that. I got to pay more attention to that. What is left bumper in circle? Okay. I got it.
Oh my God. I suck. All right. So I got to fight him up there. All right. I get it. He was doing
this weird like shield move. I got it. It's Y and right bumper is to do that. Okay. I got it. I got
him on a half. Get more mana flash. I got this. I got this. We don't need to level up. I don't
have to do shit. I got this. Get better magic ammo. All right. I got this. I got this. I got this.
I got to fight him up here though. This is awesome. This is really good. I'm really. Oh my God. I
can't wait to play this. Is that funny when you feel like that? When you're already playing the
game. All right. Yeah. That stuttering is kind of a problem, but I'm willing to look over it.
This is okay. I got to go this way. Remember this is called buyer's remorse.
What? This is fantastic. Oh, hold on. Get that V sync. I mean when I fought him over here,
it was fine. There's another bonfire there. All right. I'm going to do that bonfire because it's
like right. That's really close. Screen mode is put it on exclusive full screen, not borderless
window. I think that'll help. Then I can't easily tab over to my notes. It might help it. See.
That changed. That was, that's weird. What happened here? Oh, oh shit. Okay. See if that helps.
I have a 1440p monitor. Yeah. Put it in offline mode. Let's see if that does anything. We're
going to try it until I get it right. See if I can get it. All right. Everyone quiet.
I have an idea. I didn't know. Wait, what? He's springing three moves together. What the
fuck are these moves he's doing? He's just bringing this shit together now.
Oh my God, dude. I don't think it happened there though. I think the full screen thing fixed it.
This guy's OP. Oh, I didn't touch the thing. All right. All right. My plan is I want to try
to bring him down to like half health without using magic and then just dodge around and use
the magic and kill him. You parry that? You might. I don't know. I need the horse.
All right. That didn't fix it by the way. I probably can come back and kill this guy,
but I'm like so obsessed with beating him. You only have 12 gigs of RAM. I have way more than
12 gigs of RAM. All right. Fuck. It's still happening. I'm going to go. I'm not going to
fight this guy right now. I don't think this way I can fix it. It's just this area. Well,
then I'm going to let me play the way that I was playing before then because I want the
borderless window because that didn't fix anything. And then turn the quality back up
and let them turn this up to high. Okay. Let's go. All right. Put it back at 1440. Yeah. I can't
even do exclusive. All right. That looks better. All right. I'm just going to, I'll come back to
them later. This is actually a very common bug with an easy fix. Simply close the program and
wait for the devs to finish the game. I thought you had an actual solution. All right. Through
your map, you can instantly travel to any sites of grace that you've discovered. Yep. Very cool.
Go offline. I do that from the menu. Play offline. I think I have to restart the game.
I don't think that's the problem though. I think it just is like a current bug in the PC version.
Strengthening. At a smithing table, you can spend runes and smithing stones to strengthen your
armaments. Somewhere in the lands between you may meet a black with who. Yeah. Yeah. Okay. Cool.
Everything's stone. That's just like the titanite shards with the app. Yep. I don't want to upgrade
this dumb ass weapon. Tarnished. I can see it, but I can also see that you're not after my throat.
Then why not purchase a little something? This vendor. Cool. Okay. Ooh, what do you got?
Throwing dagger, telescope, finger remedy, crackpot, crafting kit. I don't have any souls.
They're all gone. Cookbook. Oh man, this is cool. Okay. Cool. You only have four bitcoins.
That's not what that is. I gotta get my souls back. I don't want to fight this guy. I just want to
pick up the souls that are on the ground over there. No, get away from me. I don't fucking
have any. All right. I'm just gonna go. I'm gonna go towards the great rainbow thing and just play.
Ah, wait, what's over here? I'm going to explore a little. I'm tired of your behavior. I didn't do
anything. And what is it? Nope. No door ahead. Okay. Do I discover anything? Will I get removed
like the fog of war on the map if I discover stuff? Oh Jesus. Those, there's penguins. What?
Why is it every animal on earth here? Is this such a regular enemy or is this a boss or something?
Um, uh, oh man, I'm not supposed to be down here. Oh, he's so slow.
He's got a big sword on his back. I thought he was going to go faster.
You know, it's all right. It's okay. It's okay. Holy shit. Oh my God.
No, we're just like the little shitty skeleton enemies. It's just big scary people. I, all right.
You're dying to trash mobs. This is crazy that this is just everywhere. All right. Where I got
to find like a bunch of shitties. I'm going to follow the grace of whatever this is. I feel
like I'm missing a couple of important items. Maybe I need the horse. I don't have the horse yet.
It's all so much to take in. This is, this is insane. I'm not, I'm going to be playing
this for a long time. He hasn't killed a single enemy since the tutorial. Well, I've only seen
two enemies. Huge guy with huge sword and huge guy on huge horse. I haven't fought a guy with
a torch in his hand. This is the first guy that's just a regular dude with a torch in his hand.
I'm going to kill him. He's not going to do any points of damage. I've only fought huge guys.
Ooh. Nice. Lucrease. The stealth is actually a really cool mechanic.
There's a patch out to help with optimization issues. I think that probably,
that's the day one patch, right? I think that already came out. All right. I'm going to,
there's a little bit of stuff to explore over here. I'm going to keep acquiring materials.
What's the backstory for your character? Oh, I don't know. Yes, we'll play that song. Oh, yes,
we'll play that. Rune fragment. I wonder what these, um, oh, I was going to say, what are these
little skulls? Rune fragments, Rune fragments. Cool. It's up here. Okay. I'm going. All right.
I think this is the, this is the destination right here. I'm going to put a marker here
because that's where I'm trying to go that way. I was making that sound. You hear that?
What the hell is that? Tear drop scarabs. There are both crimson and cerulean teardrop scarabs.
Feed them to replenish the flasks that match their type.
Something else I'm noticing too is what's going on with the stamina bar here.
I, I don't, I'm not using stamina. That's interesting. It just refills your estus. Okay.
It only happens in combat. Okay. This is where I need to go. But all right, let's just see what
happens. That is so pretty refills. So I don't have to go to like a bonfire. That's kind of cool.
Eight front ruins. Oh, all right. Wait. All right. The dog didn't, I didn't hit the dog.
I'm playing this on hard mode for myself because I sincerely hate the, uh, the fencing weapons.
It's a challenge. I'm for it. Oh, they're fast. Get a new weapon. I will in beast bones.
The crafting seems pretty cool too. I'm really interested in how that plays out. I'm gonna
stealth. What the fuck am I doing? I'm not a fan of this game. You know why? Cause like I can't
go over there and hold my binoculars up and just scan and just have like seven or eight squares
show up. Like I know exactly where they are. Oh, what's with that? Come on. Oops. You can't block.
You can't block magic. Can you? Oh, you can't. I'm going to forget to stealth a lot of these
times too. Oh boy. Look at that guy. I think I can kill that guy in one hit.
Did he go over there? What? No way. How did you, how did you even see what I was doing?
I went right by his ass. Come on. Watch out. A guy coming down. Come on. That's an alarm system.
That's an alarm system. That's an alarm system. Uh oh. Uh oh. Oh no. Okay. That's not, that's really
bad. That's really bad. That's the entire camp. Um, I don't think I can get, I don't think I can
get out of this. Hold on. Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait,
wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait. They got something back here. I'm going to like open the
chest and leave. You guys have to have some bullshit over here, right? What is this map?
This is a stupid idea. I'm just going to leave. What is that? That's my marker. Just like taking
all their food. Wait, I think I despawned everybody. Remind me, can you parry people
with a spear? I forget. Dark souls. I think you can. I've got no magic left in this thing.
Open up. Open up. Fine. I'll just kill you. That's fine. I'm going to just, I'm going to thin
them out. I'm going to take out the whole camp so I can just walk around and collect whatever I want.
Still no giant. Oh, that's where it wants me to go. I'm not done with this place yet though.
We're going to go through and we're going to stealth kill like all these people. Watch this.
Everybody else here, right? He hates jumping. It's such a new concept to me in these games.
I have to get used to it for a while. The fact that jump, like just regular jump exists,
it's, that's going to take a minute to hear how jumping, but secure played like a completely
different game than this. To me, this feels more like dark souls than secure. So to me,
it's like kind of a dark souls game in my brain. Can I open this video games are video games. Yes,
that's precisely what I'm saying. Butterflies and then say something about these smoldering
butterfly. I won't. Oh shit. Okay. Well, hold on. I think I'm going to come back here because I
have 1200, um, souls. I guess saying jump, jump, jump. Fine. That actually is very useful. Wait,
does jump have invincibility frames? That's a huge fucking deal. If it does, it doesn't. Okay. I just
needed to find out. I needed to know. Wait, I can go up there at the chest. Get the chest up.
Um, hold on. Oh wait, this is a chat. I thought there's just a wagon. This just looks like a
wagon. It looks like the back, like a bumper. Oh, oh my. What 18 decks. Oh, I'm going to be a flail
guy. I can't wait. It flails. There's never been an item like that. Holy shit. I'm so excited. This
is awesome. Okay. So I got a flail and there's a guy on a horse over there. Take off the helmet.
I will eventually. I need to explore. Guys, this is not going to be like a, like a four hour and
25 minute stream. Don't worry. I'm here all night. I'm not stopping for a long time. There's a chest.
I don't think you can open these. Did I miss anything else? I can go down there, but I feel
like that's kind of scary. So let's just go ahead and do it. I'm not reading any more notes because
they're spoilers. This is too perfect. Is it too perfect? With a whetstone knife, you can use
ashes of war to grant your armaments new skills. An armor can only have one skill. Any skill it had
will be removed permanently. Adding affinities. With a whetstone knife, you can use ash of war
to grant affinities to your armaments. Okay. I know it's like lore definitions, but armaments
just means weapons, right? That's not some other thing. This way you can alter like weapons attack
affinity. Okay. With attribute scaling and more ash of war storm stomp and a whetstone knife.
Jesus Christ, man. Go offline already. Like what the fuck? I'm not, I don't want to play online
anymore. I've always hated that. Okay. I think I've done everything here. A new map has been found.
Lynn grave west. It looks like sorcery. Oh, there's another wagon here too. What was it?
Not that one. There's another one somewhere. Where? Hey. Oh, there's two guys here. Really?
Yeah. Vanquishing an enemy group will replenish your flasks. The number and type of flasks
replenish varies. Enemy group? Wait, does that, so that means I cleared this camp?
Oh, that's kind of cool. All right. Just got to open up the back of this wagon over here.
What do we got here? Lord sworn's great sword. I definitely can't use that. Is this snow in this
game? If it is, it gets like a full letter grid and probably does have snow. I know I want to go
in there, but not yet. Okay. Maybe I will go fight that boss. I need to use a weapon. I want to use
first. I wonder where the level up person is. I could sit here and do a new weapon art. Oh,
hold on. The 18 to put the flail on. So please remind me of that. Greetings. Traveler from
beyond the fog. I am Melana. I offer you an accord. Have you heard of the finger maidens?
They serve the two fingers. Night time. Offering guidance and aid to the tarnished.
But you, I am afraid, are maidenless. Can you stop saying that? Like stop. We have to keep
reminding me. I can play the role of maiden. That guy's kind of rude. Turning rooms into strength
to aid you in your search for the Elden Ring. You need only take me with you to the foot of the
tree. All right. So we're going to go to the tree. Does this matter? I mean, I kind of,
I want to be able to level up in the game. Okay. I'm not going to do like a hard mode run
to turn rooms into strength. Another matter. I bequeath to you this ring.
It's the ring. The spectral speed. Okay. Now I have the horse. I can. Okay. I was trying to
fight the horse boss over and over again with no horse. That was probably pretty stupid.
All right. Use it to traverse great distances. It torrent has chosen you. Treat him with respect.
Level up. Shall I turn your rooms to strength? Let my hand rest upon you.
The samurai is ruining my cut scene. Get out of here.
Okay. This is important. All right. Vigour is health and fire resistance and immunity.
So that's important, obviously. The mind determines FP. FP is mana and also affects focus. What is
focus? Your resistance to sleep and bouts of madness. The higher the number, the lower your
susceptibility. Okay. Endurance is stamina like every single other game. And equipment load.
Robustness. What's that? Blood loss and frostbite. Ooh, there's your snow area, by the way.
Strength. Yep. Dex. Yep. We all know what that does. But hold on. Arcane. Attribute governing
discovery. Holy defense, vitality, certain sorceries. Arcane is luck. Okay. Well, I mean,
it's 18 to have the flail. So I'm going that. I'm doing intelligence and dex. It's expensive.
Dex. I'm going even into dex and intelligence. And it's probably going to make me impossible
and softlock me from completing the game. But I don't think so. I think it'll be okay.
18 for the flail. Yeah. I'll go for 15 first. Or 18 first. Add charge to flask. Use... Whoa.
What? Use one golden... Do I already have one? Hold on. This is different. All right. I want two
and two. I already have one? Oh, right. Okay. Oh, ashes of war. Grant skills and affinities.
All right. Didn't I just get one? Storm stomp. Strength scaling. Do I consume this stuff?
Is this a bad... If I put this in, is it like gems in Diablo 2? Am I never going to get this back?
I don't know. I'm kind of scared to do it. No. Okay. Quality or standard? I mean, it's going
to be quality, right? Because... I mean, it's got to be standard because of the dex scaling.
Oh, wait. Let me see what that does. Use the spectral steed whistle to summon and ride your
spectral steed. If your steed dies, you can summon it again, but it will cost one flask. Oh, shit.
Really? That's... Oh, no. Pouches. Oh, it's just items. Yeah. How do I call the whistle?
What do I do? Left? Where's my steed? Emery. Okay. So, I just have to do this.
Oh, it's a jump. Yeah. No, shit. I fight the horse guy with a horse. Okay. I need two.
It wants me to go this way. I'm going to go... I'm going to fuck that guy up.
But first, I'm going to get a couple more points. Can I stealth with the horse?
Is it double jump? What? How fun is it to be on the horse and stab people? That's not the
button you do to do that. I don't know. I hit X. Cool. All right. Really cool. How much did I
need? 800? Can I not cast spells from the horse? Whoa. One, two, three. Cool. 800. I think it was 850.
Golden rune. I like that you can pick stuff up on the horse. That would be awful if you couldn't.
Okay. There's a sprint. Damn. Okay. Cool. Let me get this queued up. That should be enough to put
one more point in, and then I'm going to go try to kill the horse guy. The staff in your right hand.
Really? Can I actually cast from horseback? You can. Can you drink flasks from horseback? You can?
Okay. Awesome. Get to 16. So I'm imagining that she just is at every place. Okay. Yeah.
Let's go. All right. The horse guy was back this way. I got to start remembering where the hell
this stuff is. Horse guy was down here. I'm just going to follow the road. See if I can kill him.
Wait. I got to go to that one. Wait. Can I fast travel? Yeah.
Can't rest right now. Who are you talking to?
Pleasure to meet thee, tarnished. I am the witch, Rena. I'd heard tale of a tarnished
hurtling about atop a spectral steed. Wow. This planet. Upon looking into the matter,
the talk I surmise is of thee. Any spells? Thou art possessed of the power, no? Call forth
the spectral steed named Torrent. I can call the spectral steed. As I had hoped,
I was entrusted this for thee by Torrent's former master.
Wow. Spirit calling bell? Lone wolf ashes. Tis a bell calling forth spirits. Summon them with it
from ash and return to the urtree. The spirits will obey thine command but briefly.
As they recall battles past. This is another one of those kind of weapon art things. As thou
wishest. Summoning spirits. With a spirit casting bell, you can use ashes to summon various spirits.
Summoning typically consumes FP, right? You can only have one spirit at a time. You cannot
summon spirits during multiplayer. We got more stuff to look at here. I have to equip it?
Okay. So I have this like horse, I have this wolf move? Forgive mine intrusion, tarnished.
I doubt we shall again meet. But all the same, learn well the lands between. So did they
remove? Before the tarnished tire of obeisance to the two fingers. So back in the other
From Software games you had consumables like grenades and throwing knives and stones to throw
and coins and is this the replacement or is that stuff in the game too? He's gone. Those are still
all here. I have to really condense what's going to be on this bar down here because I really
foresee a problem where I'm just like okay that's what I want. I have to actually equip the bell.
Is it a where is it? Is it where is it? The second tab on the menu. Oh equip that bell icon.
It's on my oh it's like wait I can't do it. The bell stop saying that.
Equip the gauntlets. Oh yeah I got to do stuff didn't I? It's not gonna be too heavy right?
27 and 49 still rolling fine. Okay well I'm just going for it. There he is.
Yeah no I haven't equipped already. We talking. All right dude it's time. Let's go. Holy shit
what's happening? I can queue them up like that? What? Holy shit that's so that's overpowered.
That's absolutely broken. What? Okay hold on. That just freaked me out so much. You can just
spam it? All right all right all right I'm ready. I'm ready. I'm ready. I'm ready. I'm ready. Let's
go. Let's go. Let's go. I'm ready. You just got hard countered. Yeah I'm the dickhead that's playing
against the fucking Lucario. Just sitting there spam spam spam spam spam spam and finally he catches
me and he KOs me. All right it's gonna be hard to not spam though because I'm fucking stupid.
All right let's go. Patience I'll kill him right now. No this weapon actually probably isn't that
great for when I'm oh man that's slow down. Um please fire at him like what the fuck I couldn't
I couldn't shoot him. That was actually kind of unbearable. I couldn't do anything. I tried to
like press right bumper and the game like hung. Maybe I shouldn't go around that fast. We should
fight him like this. It's his frame rate aura. Turn the grass down. All right grass the grass is
on medium. I have to go to the main menu for that shit. Oh god damn it whatever. So is there eye
frames with the horse dash or anything? I'm trying to understand like how this kind of work. Is there
eye frames with the horse? No it's not okay. I was just testing just testing. I want to see if the eye
like that little dash that he does his eye frames. All the jumps have eye frames? Lowering the grass
can improve it by about five percent. I feel like five percent's really not that much.
It would need to be like 80 percent for me to notice it I think. What do the wolves do? Let me
try it. What? He's just running over trees. Do they fight? They're actually kind of good.
All right let's go. Holy damn it. Oh what? Not good. It's empty. That took almost my whole
fp bar. Holy shit okay. Whoops I thought I had the other weapon.
Shit hit the horse. Oh my god this guy. Fucking oh my goodness. This is such a new concept.
This little sword. Yeah I need I need like a huge lance. Okay so that takes up the whole fp bar.
Did I unlock the flail yet? No not yet. I might be able to two-hand it though.
I feel like the horse is making it like a hundred times harder.
Did I just fight him? I don't know what to do. It's probably like a rhyme or reason to how to
actually fight on the horse and I'm just kind of running around just like freaking out. I can get
off the horse too right? Yeah you might be under leveled. Oh I mean this guy's kind of just like
an optional encounter it seems. Let's try it. Let's see if I can get him hit. Okay that goes so far.
What happened? What happened to the horse? Where's my horse?
What the fuck's happening? Did he kill the horse? Um okay let's just see if I can do it like this.
Unfortunately I have can I put this in the other hand? Shit god damn it. Oh my god.
I don't think I'm supposed to be fighting this guy right now but he's definitely doable.
You better without the horse. Yeah way better. I'll come back later.
He's definitely doable. Yeah he is. Wolves and magic?
I used the whole bar. All right I'm going I'm going I'm going one more try. One more try.
I need to actually equip the shit on the right bar. It's like it's different on the horse
like that okay. All right I'm gonna let's see if I can do it. I'll try it one more time. Last try.
Should I try parrying him? I mean he can kill you in one hit so I feel like I just would rather
fight him. Okay here we go. I thought he was gonna swing wrong button. Oh shit look at this.
They can tank. Yeah I'll come back later. This is way too hard. I can die in one hit.
He kills you in one swing. Remember the quitter? Fine. Fuck that. Last try. Last try and I'm
and I'm gonna. All right here we go. You have to get good. I'm I'm gonna get good right now.
How am I frozen? Hold that. I oh what the fuck. I'm still alive. Ah god damn that fucking move.
All right that shield move is almost a 100% one hit kill. He queues it up. He dashes really far
and I'm telling you right now forget about magic here. Absolutely. Wait I'm doing wolves twice
and melee. No magic. Come on. Come on. Come on. I got it. I got it. Let's do it. Oh yeah wolves
twice. It's a big distraction. He's gonna do this for two hours. I'm probably gonna do this for a
lot longer than that. The thing that's the big killer is the um when he queues up the shield
and he goes wham and dashes forward. You gotta wait for it. It's hard to be patient for it.
Let's go. Just just co-op him. He can't hit us. He really can't. I don't think he can hit us.
You know what I mean? Oh fuck off. He bumped me. Hey. Ah. All right. Is there another horror? Nope.
Oh what was that fucking move? What the fuck was that? He like just slipped his hand down
and scraped the ground. Come on. I don't think I've even seen him do that yet.
I'll get him. I'll definitely get him. That's the strat. Dogs twice. He's got all these little
nuanced moves. All right let's go. I can cast one spell at him. That'll change. Here we go.
Is there a timer on these things? I don't think there is. I got lost in the goddamn push.
I gotta turn the music down too. It's like I'm like a fucking rave right now. I can't concentrate.
It's so hard sometimes when he just leans over it's hard to tell if he's gonna swing or not.
What? Did I only do that once? Shit. Foolish. Oh man. Stop using the silly blade.
I can't equip the other dex item yet. No spells wolves only. Yeah I know it's just so easy to
stand back. All right. I definitely can do it. I got him down to like 30 or 40 percent. I'm
certain I can do it. Yeah you know I have to get rid of this stupid silly ass blade.
Like it's I hate this fucking thing. This is the worst item in every fucking sperm software game.
It's the worst. It's so stupid it sucks. It has one point where you can hurt somebody.
I'm deleting it. I gotta find a new weapon. I have to beat this guy on principle only.
And stop screaming. What is this? Am I making a YouTube video? I mean I probably will.
Let's go. That stupid bump is the worst move. It's so hard. I'm fucking. I'm balding.
That little tiny little bump that he does with the horse. There's almost no telegraphing.
He just goes like bump. All right if I don't do it this time I'm leaving and I'm gonna go
find a new weapon that's not the worst weapon in every from software game. Okay good. Sounds
like a plan. Oh my god. Fuck you. What? No. I'm getting out of here. I'm fine. I'm doing
something else to do. I'm not gonna fight the guy that's like the optional fucking boss that
requires like 500 more decks than I have. I'm leaving. Fuck it. I don't even care. I'm going
back home. Good luck wolves. Fight him. Is he still aggro? He's outside. Does he come inside?
Wait. Oh my god. This is scary. He just sits out here. Oh my god. He's gonna knock the whole
building down. Holy shit. What happens if he knocks the building down? Can he kill this guy? Oh no.
I don't want him to kill the NPC. That would be horrible. Don't hurt the NPC please. I don't want
to restart the whole playthrough. Fuck this guy. I'm gonna move on. I'm gonna get the flail and
I'm gonna come back. I'm gonna get the flail. I'm gonna come back and I'm gonna kick his ass
after one more attempt. It worked. It didn't work. I don't think you can parry. That was actually
perfect. That was a perfectly timed parry and it didn't do anything. Okay. Well I can't beat that
guy. I'm not supposed to fight that guy. That guy is like... I come back like four hours from now
and fight that guy. Oh fuck it. I'm leaving. If it helps I've been playing for 13 hours and I didn't
even know that was a boss. Finally. Finally. But I had to like try to prove my like gamer skills,
right? Fight the optional guy that is hard and now everyone's gonna tell me about all the other
streamers that beat it and I didn't do it and now I have to come back and cheese him with like what
is the equivalent of Dark Souls 1 lightning. Okay. Sorry. Sorry. I'm gonna come back at level 100
and kill him in two hits. Okay. Let me explore. What's over here? Your build is not good for
killing him immediately. Yeah I know. I'm just messing around. I'm just kidding. It really would
have been really cool if I used this piece of fucking trash. Right. Never mind. Don't get angry.
Get even. I wonder what these fragments do. You're boiling over with rage. Oh no I am not.
I'm actually really happy that I can't beat that guy. It's just more content.
You know what I mean? Like I could stream this game for like the next three months.
Urba. Oh what's this? Mushrooms? This is a little cave over there. Mushrooms. Oh it's in here.
Oh shit. Where am I? Do we have face cam now? Yeah. You've earned it. Like 20 minutes.
Okay so I need I need to put the flasks back. I turned on face cam and like my brain just
started to blink. All right what's down here? Proper death means returning to the urd tree.
Have patience until the time comes and the roots call to you. Okay so I have to go to the tree
eventually. It's like a little dungeon. This is cool. Okay. That guy's behind me. Hey what the
fuck are you throwing? Wait a minute. Why do I feel like I okay I have a ton of stamina. A ton of
stamina. That's kind of weird. How many times can I swing and dodge and stuff? I'm just noticing
right now that that was only half the stamina bar. Root resin. You know what I'm saying? Like that was
you have more stamina in this game like per swing. Vinny killed him with your sword. Brave
glove wart. Fucking Harry Potter teacher name. Oh co-op. The summoning pool is now functional.
Why do I feel like there's a boss in here? No no no. I ain't fucking around. I'm casting spells
at this guy up there. Where the? I like that you can actually do that but it's going to cause me
a lot of problems. Why am I throwing up? What's over here? Brave violet? Secret passage. They're
probably not even in the game. Water? Is that rushing water? Oh dear. Hey that's not fair.
One two three four. It's gonna be close. Dude why are you crouching? What the fuck?
Is something behind there? Oh shit there is. Good. All right what is it? Paddling plate hello.
Oh is that the hello? Oh my god go. Where's the very edge? One two three go. Don't go yet.
One of those guys is gonna jump from the ceiling and try to kill me.
Where is he? Where is he? Is he gonna? I knew you. I saw you. I knew you were sitting there
waiting for you piece of shit. I knew you were gonna kill me. That guy was pretending to be
one of the pots. Oh my fucking what the heck is going on here? What the heck's happening here guys?
What the heck's happening here? What the heck's happening here? What the fuck is happening?
God damn it. I mean I gotta go down here. I can't just not go down here. You dodged into it. Yeah
it's called panicking because it's scary. What even is this? Blocked by some contraption.
Probably you probably open it and leave. All right uh I can I don't need to I'm not gonna waste
magic. Actually this is the perfect time to use the magic. Although I feel like it's a waste.
It is. I can fight these guys without it. Unless they don't fall down. Does he jump?
I don't think he does. Back to that fire room. There's gotta be something at the end of this.
Something good right? Oh my freaking god what the heck? Oh what the heck's going on here?
All right this guy up there. There he is. They're doing the stupid thing that is in every horror
movie. They're in the corner of the bedroom and they they their head cracks and they look at you.
All right here we go. Holy shit I did I timed it right. Okay here they all come. Just I I have to
do this right. Oh my god how did I not see all these guys on the wall? How did I how did I not
see those guys? They actually fooled me. I was completely fooled. Ready? Ah I'm scared!
Okay they can they climb? Oh shit he can climb. How do I knock him down?
How do I do the thing that they do in PvP? Fuck no! I like forgot that you could like kick down.
I didn't know if you could climb or not. God damn it I'm like purple. What happened?
Oh I'm purple. Why am I purple? They're gonna die by the fire. It doesn't matter.
All right let's get out of here. Give me my lost souls. Get up. I would turn to the camera and all
my facial hair and my eyebrows would be gone. I ain't moving until I'm certain what's going on
here. I'm not moving an inch. Yep all right bud. First off down then lever. First off down then
lever. Oh that's kind of cool. Not yet. Are you kidding me? Stop throwing those! Is he still alive?
They're not gonna fool me now. Somebody right above me. Is somebody actually in this room?
They're all gonna climb out of these little divots. Wandering noble ashes. Oh that's a new move.
Destruction. Okay that's pretty cool. I got what I wanted. It's a new summon. This game's really
good. This is just a random dungeon. Just a random little spot. This is really cool. This is awesome.
Okay so I can pull this lever though. What does that do? Put them down here? That's probably for
the door. Yep lever. Somewhere a heavy door is open. Nice. Is somebody behind me? That would have
been scary if I had even seen any attention. I was paying zero attention. Zero. Okay so that door
opened. I'm gonna go sit at the bonfire. That's that new move. What does it do? It's like a stun.
Okay that's cool. I'm gonna do a little bit of gamer exercising. I'm turning off online seriously.
I keep thinking it's somebody. All right I'm sitting at the fire. I think I have enough to
level up. Can you level up at any bonfire? Holy Mike is it off? Because I almost just walked into
fire probably. All right where's the- there it is. Because I'm close to the flail. Oh that's really
awesome. You can do it anywhere. All right 17 we need one more point in decks and I can use the
flail. Level your chin up to level two. Good. Is this game like LA and war? Yeah it's like exactly
the same. Each one of these enemy encounters it goes like a zoom in to the enemy's face and
you have to decide whether or not you're gonna like trust them or not. Well they go like this.
This is a boss. Entry burial watchdog. What the hell? Okay. Holy shit that that extreme action
figure. Press the button on his back. What the fuck dude? His moves happen in one second.
He's like a GI Joe. How does this- does this hurt him? Oh that hurts him a lot. Let's go.
Spam. Oh get cheeseballed. All right this guy- this guy wasn't that bad. All right that guy
wasn't that bad. Enemy fell. Noble sorcerer ashes. That guy wasn't that bad. Ah weak foe. I did it.
You know what? That person could be- you know you did do it and I rated it poorly again.
That guy- who knows? That person could have like just bought the game from like Walmart today
and I just like- I keep- it's not- it's start and then whatever it's select. It's not start.
Turn to entrance. I'm gonna look like such an asshole. You know now I understand why- oh now
I understand why some videos just have like like 10 dislikes randomly. It's probably because they
just like press the wrong button. I get it. I think that's it right? That's- that was cool.
That was a fun one. I just like all of your videos. Find the party. Apologize for what?
Oh it's flail time guys. Finally. All right. This helps my casting too because it's casting speed
so that's good. What we got? 109 plus 21. 106. Yeah that's better. FP cost? Okay that's spinning
chain. Let's take a look. Oh that's cool. Nice. What's the uh chart? That's awesome.
It's kind of slow but I think it'll be all right. About two handed.
I love it. What about the weapon art? Let's see. Holy shit that's awesome. What does that do?
Is that a block? It takes up uh FP. I wonder if I can- can I attack out of this?
I can. All right I think I'm gonna use this weapon. What's FP? FP is mana. It's the blue bar.
Very cool. Well that was awesome. I'm gonna check it out. What is it uh- I gotta buy that
crafting thing. Can I still kill people with like with a stealth? All right it's a little loud for
me. Music at least. I'm gonna turn the music down just a little bit. Just a little bit. Okay
that's it. Only one notch. So that was here. That was it. Okay that's cool. I wonder what that is.
You might as well spit in the- nevermind. I love this weapon. It is so much better.
This is running away. So this is de- the scaling on this is not great though. Probably gets better.
Can you zoom the map all the way out? Uh I think this is what we have here.
Unless there's more. Is there more? Or is this the whole game? I don't know. There's way more zones.
Oh my god. Uh I see that statue and I raise you going to go see it. This is literally the tutorial.
This is the tutorial. This is so cool. This is so good. Wait let's check this out. I might be able
to kill that guy now. I want to go check out that uh statue up there. Oh wait this is like
another catacombs. Kind of looks like a catacombs. Where's that statue? What's this? Whoa.
Ultimate nerd neck. Dude I'm just saying put your monitor up a little higher. So many people the
reason why they like this is because their monitors- put your monitor a little higher
so your eye line is here not here looking down like this is your monitor here you want your
eye line to be right here okay i don't think can i do anything with this holding something
that's where that's the okay that's where i was before let me let me do the crafting thing
it looks like the ice cream lady from spongebob i don't i don't know what you who you mean but
weren't you you're back here to buy something
yes this thing enables the practice of item crafting
oh i could buy these too a lot of money wait note waypoint ruins note flask of wondrous physique
what is this i'm just gonna buy it
so
it's raid who's reading he's on them guys get raided by g4 tv like g4 the g4 what's up
playing some elden ring what's happening holy shit well hey welcome everybody from g4
my name is germa and we're playing some elden ring uh i got to warn everybody here though
i'm pretty new to the souls uh games i haven't really played very very many of them
so i've this is about our number like three or four um i i died to the first boss uh i'm
just still trying to find out how to like swing the weapon and stuff and combo moves together
um people are telling me i need to equip something called like the estus flask i don't
know where that is maybe some of you guys can help me when you come on in here but thanks welcome
everybody um i'm still kind of learning yeah so people are saying that this thing here
does some kind of heal is it a heal over time because i have two of them i don't know what the
other one does i don't know i i'm probably gonna stop playing this game after like a few hours
i just i'm not like i don't really get it i don't even know why people play these but
what is it welcome everybody still going to purchase something all right i'm gonna buy
what do i buy i was seriously thanks for the g4 that's i i used to watch g4 when i was a kid
it was like permanently on tv all right i want to come back and buy this stuff because it's just
easy to it's like in bloodborne you buy the hunter's outfit all right where we're going
should i kill the okay here we go hey new viewers not a big deal i don't know how to fucking heal
i actually probably could kill him now whoa what happened why am i back here
use those summons oh i did get some new stuff man let me check stomp all i have only i only
i only have is i only have stump or the other ones didn't i get them it's in items summons
five wandering spirits summons noble sorcerer oh hell yeah wait why can i number held and why
can i equip it why are you in normie dark souls streamer guys i'm gonna watch infinity war when
it comes out okay i'm not gonna not watch infinity war like what because i know i don't want to watch
that normie movie every single person seen infinity war if you're over the age of 12
you've seen infinity war at this point i don't think this is a person on earth that hasn't seen
i'm gonna play infinity war okay how do i equip this i actually don't know i'm sorry g4 tv
why can i not how do i take this off discard i feel like they would throw it away
it's on your actual item bar oh right okay that makes sense i want to look through the sorcerer
see what this guy's like noble sorcerer ashes and i use it is it not equipped i don't get it
you can only use it oh i can't okay all right let me travel over there let's go for it
let's go let's go let's go oh i don't i'm so used to traveling like that in the other games
you can just do it from the map okay it's time we're gonna use the old noble sorceress and see
what happens and i'm gonna try to kill the horse guy again let's go for it no more messing around
i'm sweating all of my brand new xbox one controller it's a good controller
all right let's go old man what does he do
what the monitor up all these guys playing fortnight all day does he follow me
watch out he's so slow
nine fucking damage holy shit you're awful dude wait can i can i i can't even summon him again
fuck you so stupid it's like a little like it's just like just do it already stop fucking with me
okay that that guy's not that what's the other one noble wandering nobles this is five people
i'm gonna try these guys they're already good we're just gonna swarm them at some point we're
just swarming them five people let's go where'd he go where'd he go hey there's just five out
there's six people in my party why are you only going after me why do you have priority
kill the caster priority you got six people in front of you last try last try last try
last try and i'm doing something else i'm not supposed to be here collision you can bump into
these idiots oh get the same stupid one two three ran into a fucking tree i just i just i don't like
the guy he can move around too much i want i he can move way too much i'm fucking going right now
killed the horse he's supposed to swipe he's swept the horse under his legs getting greedy
oh i'm gonna fucking just i jumped off the horse i gotta rebind that i gotta rebind that because
i'm sorry when you move around and you are like gaming hard you're gonna press the left stick in
i gotta rebind that i think that's gotta get rebound all right i'm not messing around
anymore i'm beating him right now we're gonna summon like the weird townspeople to come like
just be people to just shoot out or whatever whatever the stupid shield he's gonna just shoot
his shield out well like he does and he's gonna fucking what if i just run him off the edge will
he just walk off the edge and die it's so hard to get so his weapon is so much bigger than mine
i didn't want to jump off the goddamn horse stop just have patience this bro's weapon is
way bigger than mine it's not fair he's like broke my spine i did this like they do back in
old england where they just drive by each other i'll be back i'm done with this guy cast a spell
at him what are you doing dude come on dude what the fuck don't put let's go all right
this there's something in my mouth i don't know what's in my mouth that's fucking gross
just burger boy him dude how am i supposed to get away from that he goes so much faster than me
dude it's so hard to tell when he's gonna do that fucking move
i need i need so much more vitality do you understand i have like five percent vitality
that i need to have to fight this guy did you get it okay i'm right now the wolves were way better
all right anyway and yes i'm sorry i had my shirt on the coat hanger for too long and it's
ruined now okay let me just get it out there first oh my fucking god you stupid game
i have no health left what i dodged the exact perfect time
what am i supposed to do you can't dodge it he doesn't scream just like this like fucking sonic
blast i didn't think i would be this like fucking malding at this point new strat new strat new
strat new strat i'm gonna calm down just relax i need the extra health we're gonna summon dogs
once and then i'm just gonna get good this guy's fucking hard come on this guy's hard
that it's a it's teaching you this whole new bullshit of mechanics like ride your horse to
fight him i'm not gonna do that i'm not doing that it has not been seven hours has it holy
shit this game's amazing let's go fuck that move that move sucks have you tried turning your
monitor on uh you know you know i don't know i don't know i think it's been on this whole time
all right i can it could definitely do it maybe one more point in decks i'd say i keep bumping
into these rocks and this these fucking things get in the way they really do okay come on this
is it yes dodge it's the stupid bump when he's just like here i go i'm gonna i'd say fuck you i
didn't wait i don't telegraph it's just like here he goes he's yeah yep like what the fuck is that
shit okay i'm i'll come back later again fuck this guy i first tried that other stupid action figure
boss i'm i'm killing him right now i'm very angry but i'm gonna slow down and i'm gonna get
three four free hits i'm so far away oh shit we're in lag city right now
i gotta back it up we're in lag city back over here come on come on stop i need you to come back
here i'm this is lag city down here i can't play here oh god it's gonna this is gonna ruin
everything that move it's gotten me every it's impossible it's impossible it's impossible
it's not possible it's possible if you're very good at stuff but it's impossible if you are not
leveled correctly and the guy's an optional encounter you don't have to even fight this guy
i've been wasting five hours just trying to come back to fight this optional golden knight guy
and i don't have to do this but i'm gonna do it again how long has been like two hours
i i've consistently been getting him lower though i got him down to like 30 which before i could
all right no more fucking around let's let's relax every time i think i can oh fuck you if
it's chaining that shit together lag city oh my god his moves patterns are just so all over the
place i've had it you know it'd be great if i put one goddamn other point in fucking vitality
and instead i have and i have the same amount of vitality that you start with as the naked guy
all right i'm fucking out of here i'm out going this way don't call me a quarter i'll go back
fight him on the horse the horse is like sloppy for me i gotta get used to it first
all right we need to go over here i'm gonna put a marker here i never took you for a quitter
that guy's hard all right let's go i don't have to do this i can just teleport who is that guy
that guy was cool all right here's the thing though let me explain why this game is awesome
so i i can't move on from that guy like i know i'm like not supposed to be killing that guy right
now oh you could you know if it's just really good and you just dodge everything you get
everything right yeah of course sure but it's this is crazy that i can just sit there for like
couple hours and just lose i like the optional stuff all right come on and he shoots that
that's good um let's go ahead and get on the horse with this he's shooting right in the eye
that's not the button i wanted to attack him it's been a while since i've played up from software
souls i'm x i'm hitting x to swing on the horse not right bumper all right i'm still like i'm
still like tapped out from that fucking goddamn horse asshole okay get a fucking way from me
all right that's not how you're supposed to do this i gotta like get over there get off the
horse and kill them i'll get it oh this is this is tricky dude he's already here
horses assemble i pressed x to attack on the fucking horse again i don't know why i just
but i'm so used to playing like i don't like dynasty warriors or something why do i think
i'm playing like dynasty warriors what game do you use x to attack on horseback
holy shit there's so many people i've oh shit thanks jesus i need my magical stay
don't go towards the huge guy go away from the huge guy the entire fucking village is here
is there should i just go run away or something because like what the fuck am i even here for
oh shit he can kill him all right all right all right all right all right
i think i didn't want to swing yet you're a quitter i'm still here dude he's going so fast
all right let's go my chest i'm fine all right take his legs out watch out for the sonic blast
don't get cocky don't be an idiot i gotta queue up like the wing wing wing like that get out of
here motherfucker i'll get him oh shit this is bad new move set i forget what it does
please jeremy what are you doing i i i'm dead i'm dead i'm dead i'm dead i'm dead i'm gonna die
right now i'm dead i think i'm dead here oh i'm watching like a scary movie i have to run away
i can't kill him right now i don't if he hits me one more time i'm dead
just run quit coward dude don't call me that just stay way the fuck away from him
then he gets really he gets really up on you he gets really up on you
oh that's okay i need enough i gotta take him outside all right no more like youtuber screams
okay i gotta take him outside don't i no i don't want to go outside there's people out there
get back in that gate all right get out get out get out get out get out get out get out get out get
out get out don't aggro all these nights i didn't think he was close enough i thought he was far i
thought he was too far away to do that use your magic because i used the wolves and it went to
zero and i yeah it's magic andy time all right where what is this last where am i going which is
the last gravesite right that was a goofy reaction yeah i like whoa and drop the controller
okay it's magic on this guy and i thought i could get him with the melee shit
i yeah this is fucking crazy oh man i gotta fight all that shit again but i don't have to i could
just go through it but man do i want to try that's like how's your day it's going it's going good
just kite him outside it's actually probably a better idea to do that probably making this way
more difficult than i have to how's your day is your day good i hope so all right so these people
here i don't it's gonna take a while i think i could fight him out here and plus he'll kill
those guys yeah he'll kill those guys gamer exercises hold on we're good yeah i wonder
if i can let me just get him to come let me just get him to jump down and then i'm just gonna run
out and i'm just gonna run around him and i'm gonna cast my magical spells that's definitely
the strategy for sure don't even go near him unless i have to two at a time two at a time is
fine this is not going to bring him to zero i'm okay i gotta remember he does that this actually
might bring him to zero fuck you yeah i'll get him here i that made that so much more difficult
on myself than i had to holy goodness you're dying got him that was so much easier than i made it
oh geez okay that was way easier okay now i can go take those guys out and be able to be clean
i have some pre-recorded gameplay of me beating this boss if you'd rather just use it
it's not a boss this is a regular guy this is not hitting it's hitting for fucking three oh my god
get off the horse get off the horse it's just what what am i what am i holding this stupid
fencing weapon again can't see your souls oh shit i'll move it he's still alive holy shit
i thought i could get it back stuff it's a mistake don't be cute about it just kill him
we're good everything is fine i can now explore a little bit make sure i get all the items that i
need put on the actual weapon that i should have on and that's kind of cool okay okay so now
i still have a heal which is good you should have been cute about it
no i got the crafting thing i don't know what i should do with it though
i wonder if the big guy respawns you look like a ps2 sopranos character golden rune i don't know
why what does that even mean i i actually kind of don't know what the hell you're talking about
what does that mean ps2 let's move the camera up where should i put it up here here somewhere
in the middle top right top right or kind of middle right yeah that looks good well what do
i have for notes wow great notes actually kind of good notes because i wouldn't have remembered that
all right onward erba mushrooms all right there's a motherfucker right here
actually the bow might not be a bad idea because i'm doing a lot of decks a left bumper for
right to adjust rb arrow one arrow two i mean the game wants me to don't do that
they just blocked all that damage good will you get the fuck out of here
i didn't even get a chance to put the bow on oh nice okay i cleared a camp right
a little bit of me a little bit of me why are you saying that wolves actually have been the best
the sorceress guy was probably might be good later i would imagine might be pretty good later
on let me put the bow oh i don't have strength um they changed the way that rolling works
my equipment load is 33 out of 49 i'm still rolling
they changed that kind of feel like they did all right where are we i gotta head this way
break the skulls on the ground break the skulls you mean like those big skull head things
where are they i'll find them later continue i need another uh bonfire
my voice is so junk at the moment i've just been screaming no more screaming i just like i'm i'm
like i lean back and i make like weird sounds that's really cool looking storm hill oh this
is uh estus thing i know this way let's try over here i'm gonna check this spot over here
i think there might be something over here if we're gonna drink water yeah i'll get a refill
old tinged excrement okay so i'm currently in this little forest area
can i go over here kind of what was that would this be a lovable sort i like pet the owl i don't
know okay i can't get out maybe i can get over there from here gotta be something over here right
it's like jellyfish things up there are you serious what are you thinking uh i can go around
i'm looking like another one of those dungeons all right all right i'm in the jail i'm in the
jellyfish i need a place to octopus ahead yeah okay i see it are these hostile that's not an
octopus by the way there's a squid they're not hostile i see an item mushroom anything else here
new weapon oh shit what's this i was hitting a to dodge but a is jump they've added more buttons
to this game it's not just dodge and attack this like dodge this jump there's wolf move there's
ride the horse oh shit i need to get those that's bad i was like two or three thousand
this guy's back oh my god he is i am not i'm not fucking around now i don't care go ahead blow
the horn just don't walk off a cliff nope can't do that maybe i can nope go the right way
got zero swag i don't care i don't why do i need swag i don't need any swag
okay watch out for those weird hollow skeleton people where do they even come from how come i
only oh fuck that's right forgot okay i only have one estus allocated what else is over here yeah
funny oh no another pig skeleton skeleton yeah yeah yeah yeah i failed don't you what
is wrong with this guy okay you have to kill him twice got it he's message marvin it's day one i'm
i want to read what people have to say i'm gonna kill one of these things that all right it's very
angry is it gonna explode i think it explodes oh they're all they're all angry okay so they've i
turned them all red interesting i don't think i can it's metroid they have a lot of health
they don't drop anything really so i don't think it's worth killing everybody
is he gonna come back to life yes he is do it required ahead and then try critical hit
material ahead yeah i already got it that wasn't a fact that necessary item all right well i'm
leaving bye it's kind of cool kill them kill them all i don't i don't need to kill every single enemy
so let's go from here it's definitely this bridge that's the bridge right there kill them all kill
them all wait until sans makes you answer for this kill kill kill kill them all oh kill them all later
don't don't don't wait there are more how come these ones are lit up but these guys aren't
oh godric soldier why they why they all congregating over here is there a reason
why they're all congregating around the six stone are you slow as hell they're all right again excuse
me hey kill before he comes back please they get full health when they come back that's
fucking awful okay it's the slow motherfuckers are driving me crazy the guys that take like
a hundred don't fall okay i'm safe guys that take like five seconds to swing the sword
you get me a guy that swings every half second and i'll beat him all right so let me get back on the
road this is probably something i can do there later that's a weird place i have to get to another
bonfire because i need to level up bad this is back on the road okay that the golden trail is
going this way nice okay awesome beautiful okay what i need to put my points into definitely
i need health it's just a fact uh i'm gonna use this brush these i'll get the 12 health no
this is my health is so bad do the crafting oh that's right thousand all right sort chest
oh okay that's cool add charge to flask i have a golden seed
awesome it's very that's very important i'll do four in one
so now i need to do how do i craft oh i gotta go to that workbench right let me do that
just started the stream have i missed much um maybe a little nothing too crazy it's been
really fun so far though i'm gonna upgrade the well you missed him
layling at an optional boss for three hours he killed five bandits and died a hundred times
all right let's go i do plus two now i need it more i definitely i need to do more damage
we're gonna go i'm gonna go for the horse guy again
um
i gotta like run around when he does that oh my god that stupid little move that stupid little
like wait come on man what the fuck i think i probably could do it oh that was so dumb it's
like i'm on the side he just like flicks his why not magic spam i tried that already
he just moves too fast they don't hit him i'll give it one more attempt and i'm gonna keep going
yeah i gotta get him i gotta get it back up you're you're in such a weird position here come on
that's such a weird spot come this way fingers are so greasy i wouldn't have missed that if my
pants didn't slip my god he just moves around so fast i need to get on the horse these three more
tries all right oh my god how the fuck are you doing that you just glued to me huh excuse me
oh my god you're fucking magnet dude i jumped over that shit head i i'm out of relax
i got it i'll get him this time we're not doing wolves i'm just gonna okay i got it i got it i'm
just gonna be patient we're gonna do just a horse fight one-on-one that's it horse fight
is your name jeremiah no can you shit on me can i do a weapon art on the horse yes okay
um hello yeah nice job nice game you got here that was fucking cool teleporting jumping lag guy
i can't see anything yeah watch that stamina i'm in i gotta take it back up this is a bad
place to fight him back up here up up up up up up up this is the this is the part that actually
lags oh shit oh don't be stupid okay we're all right we're all right you're good you're good
we're gonna get away with the building get away from the building good night god i was playing
this game so fucking wrong i was playing the game completely wrong like the whole time i
playing the game wrong i was playing the game i was playing the game wrong golden halberd what
is that golden halberd that's kind of cool strength though not enough scales with faith that's so weird
i want to put it on see what it looks like all right so i was playing the game wrong that's all
right holy shit this thing's huge wow this thing is crazy look at how majestic that is
the raid we did have a raid dog doug dog doug with a with a big we have a couple of big
rates today thanks dog doug apparently enjoying elden ring i've i lost that horse boss like 15
plus times uh i just beat him if you don't know who the horse boss is and you haven't purchased
elden ring yet let me give you some tips don't uh fight him uh with a flail on the ground is it
that's probably the best tip i can give you i actually really like this what's the weapon art
what you just go like hooray oh not enough mana okay what does it do no that doesn't do anything
what's its weapon arm i don't think it has one you need faith to use it okay all right well i'm
that's way too much equipment load cool all right well that was fun that was cool this game is
fantastic i gotta stick with what i'm doing here though i'm going with point intelligence the
spells uh i'm gonna go kill like one thing oh crafting right how do i do that we're gonna do
the crafting thing end of the stream voice what do you know we're not even close the shattering of
not even close not even remotely
who keep things from drying up entirely let's say you're a very welcome customer crafting items
so do i it's not the smithing table there's a bug in my room i'm too lazy to get rid of them
any suggestions um yeah what's the bug just well just open up your window and like lead and like
eventually the bug will fly out the window maybe we'll get the breeze of the air and we'll
find its way out i got a new one of these not storm stomp where is it
didn't i get a new one i did godric soldier asked two soldiers to try it
okay cool very cool i'm gonna go to where i was going before killed mr horse man have you seen
my pickle messages in the game yes i actually have yeah it has like 5 000 upwards interesting so it
needs me it wants me to go this way have i even fought the first boss yet or have i just killed
two optional bosses has it even been a boss no nope really this game is boring like any souls game
i i'm just telling you man like you get i would just you saying that is that's like
you gotta be careful with that take oh stone sword key gargoyle statue tutorial bonfire let's go
see if i didn't write that down i wouldn't remember that let's go i'm going there right
now dude no it's in four hours it's in here right i'm taking my time through this this game is so
good it's so fucking good can you be a reference for my job application what are you talking about
no what do you mean d face why are you doing the d face all right here i actually think that um
the person that's out applying right now uh hard worker gets things done on time and work well with
others and has um pretty good head on their shoulders i think they're honest they're um
they're they're pretty pogchamp they're if you don't know that's what we do here at twitch.tv
my name is germa985 by the way uh pogchamp means very good very good uh very cool very awesome
excitable and i think they deserve a salary of 185 000 a year starting base salary by the way
um what else i got a big zit back here i don't know if you can see it actually hurts a lot and
i try to get rid of it bad i'm sorry what do your eyebrows go dude it's dark in here they're right
here man look look it's just the lighting in the room and i have a big eyebrow bone turn on the
ring light i'm not gonna turn the ring light on and sweat my ass off in here i'm not no i'm
not turning on the ring light i don't want to i want it to be like dark and mysterious not like
look i'm in a studio no taking away your reddit shelf privileges uh congratulations on the job
by the way or whatever it was okay here we go use the key yes i mean not enough how many do i need
i need more it's two well okay let's we'll keep that written down does anybody in chat have a pet
shrimp pet shrimp all right we're going over here it looks like if i go up that way oh all right
when you're with a party of like three of your friends walking through crossroads and wow
and a level 60 is just a dickhead and doesn't give a fuck about your fun time with your friends
oh let me do you one more i'm not going to leave this spot for an hour a full hour is going to go
by and i'm not going to leave why do people just hate when other people have fun like just go
fucking go herbalize or something man big castle oh cookie bug wild strikes what is that you doing
that let me try trebuchet oh shit this is bad oh shit okay all right all right get up get up get up
get up get up stop crouching not what i wanted to do but that's okay people are you gonna have
like there's no mana what did i spend it on shut up i'm so sorry these games just fuck with me
i'm probably so loud and irritating i'm sorry i know it's late too is the game too loud it
looks like it's a little loud is it too loud not really okay who's still fighting me where i don't
know who's fighting who's attacking me oh golden okay that's how you get those all right i feel
like i need to be picking this stuff up every time i see it i don't understand who's doing that
who can see me from this far away where's it coming from the guy in the back just looking at me
all right i guess i got him oh boy watch out oh my god all right just charge at him and just
dodge every one two three that is such that travels so quickly this spider's in my hair i think this
bug's in my hair oh can i shoot it oh fuck don't do that if you don't know what it does yet
oh goodness i just he's right behind him just standing single file behind him all right we're
good there are bugs all over your skin okay so i could probably explore a little bit i mean they
kind of are bugs all over you is it like dust mites they're just literally crawling over your
entire body why do people think that's i mean does ever do people just go to every wall in the game
and just say hey look this is a secret here you're wasting my valuable time i should put one down
all right let's go um going in here a big ball is gonna roll down this hill it's gonna be a pinball
i'm gonna turn around i'm gonna have to run for my life i'm telling you something's coming down
there it's gonna roll all the way down i don't know i do okay i don't know what i should be
doing here should i do one in endurance probably i feel like i'm not having a stamina problem
maybe intelligence or keep doing decks i should get it to 12 i really should 11 is probably way
it's too low lol he doesn't know about el ballo that's what i'm saying why is this golden
summoning sign summon holy shit wow okay i just like el ballo oh yeah that that guy el ballo
now this is boss all right sure i'm not sweaty even like just get so aware of your blinks
all right here we go uh marget the fall omen okay we got magic too okay
so he's a slow motherfucker as well see you in another four hours he's got a slow wind up all
right well thankfully it's right here i could just spend uh a hundred hours here how much damage
you want to hit him that's a lot it's worth it holy shit that fucking wind up oh my god the
wind up dude holy shit my whole body itches holy smokes all right
he's just losing the home run bad on me and it's just so hard to know when he's
doing it okay i gotta start memorizing his move set skillfully back it up okay with this little
ding ding okay holy shit man can you stop attacking for a sec oh he's doing so long
out of mana already damn okay well let's go two handed i cut his tail off holy goodness
oh holy fucking stop attacking i think it's all about distance with this guy
oh come on really i don't think you want to get away three out of five what you should
you should rebrand as the penis genius i don't know what the fuck that's supposed to mean
but you made me chuckle for a second okay all right keep going i'm thinking that you get a
couple attacks in and run away like just get away yo let's get oh yo all these guys penis genius
i fucking hate that and then you want to get the hell out of here i'm thinking one attack and then
you get back back up that was stupid wait till he's done swinging attack and get in there and just
this i am not even playing the game right now what what was that what what was it saying
oh i had that selected looks okay all right actually that's not a bad thing to do at the
beginning i will tell you right now i don't think i would be betting anything at the moment i don't
know if you should be betting anything i'm going to probably die like 30 times before i get him
here okay let's go easy easy don't be an idiot i hit him in tail just run just turn
around and run oh you that fucking wind up you killing me here man what the fuck it's like the
the changing patterns of just like a quick quick slow so quick oh i'll get him no breathing room
will gamble when he rage quits the boss and comes back in an hour no that's not gonna happen
i'm gonna get him should use the wizard i'll try all right let's try one more one more time with
the soldiers of star fucking dunked on oh you bro oh he just pump holy fucking moly man
okay i don't have to dodge that when he does the big wind up holy what am i hitting there's a
fucking wall somewhere oh my god don't dodge it um the problem with these games is when you do the
i just jumped onto the ledge as super mario but i immediately jump again and fall to my death
even though you made it to the platform uh i call it mario ledge syndrome um happens all the time in
this game i messed it up i just killed me just fucking run off the edge run off the edge run off
the edge fuck this guy i didn't i waited too long let's make fun of the vod watcher so they
skip this part what other hold on maybe the dogs are good here or the spell caster guy
i'll try it noble sorcerer let's try it and then wait why this is here now fire pot
feed to restore hp to torrent rainbow stones or reveals co-op and hostile summoning signs okay
cool we cracked pots let me try the old man see if he does anything interesting all right you any
good i mean i just walked into the fucking these these things in the ground of collision of course
they do they're like a fucking gas coin again walking into gravestones 11 damage this guy sucks
this guy's not doing anything if he could heal that would be great when he does the huge swing
just run like i go oops let him come to me don't just be an idiot here let him come to me
you gotta run around him when he does the long lines up
i gotta get behind him it's so difficult when you're locked on it's a business of wash this one's
over maybe not i can do two damn it man dude ah when he goes in the air like that and you're
locked onto this motherfucker your camera goes like this and if i want to try to dodge through
me i go i gotta fucking not lock onto him because then you're gonna walk in the way that he jumps
over you and yeah there's a jump is you and you understand how long it's gonna take my brain to
understand that one whoa whoa oh fuck off with that bullshit there's a hammer right i'm barely
fucking hurting this guy what the fuck did i just do to fucking god just can you give me one
second to fucking do anything i got a bleed off oh okay i'm just a training dummy for this guy
you can't be serious not fair you tell me oh you guys told me to jump you said
jump you have a jump i jumped to make it so i wouldn't get hit by it i jump up and it hits the
ground and it did i get hit what happened to me i go like this and he lands and it still hits me
you guys do jump attack oh that's what you said okay oops fucking god damn all right i got it
i'm i'm improving i'm improving oh just walking over the edge you're a mage yeah i know but he
moves around so fast i i need the health what do you want forgive me i've been testing you i'm
kind of busy whether or not grace truly does guide you whether you are fit to face the challenge
it seems my worries were unfounded torrent had your measure from the very start whereas i merely
pretended i was joey i was just pretending i can do to offer you guidance what i can take you to
taste this champion why would i want to go there guided by grace what was your s.a.t score i'll go
to where are we going so am i getting luigi'd did i get luigi'd why did it why did this round
table hold it's okay you can't fight in here i mean i'm i'm fighting this boss in
china okay i'm the last time i do china's your senior i bid you welcome it is safe here
you have any spells you may let down your guard only a word has your senior you are a mere visitor
to the round table nothing more a house guest yet to earn their keep remember your place
newcomer a great voice
there's nothing left to say be at your leisure there's nothing left nothing so where why am i
here i see you've just arrived welcome to the round table hold i teach this head stuck in a wheel
the strength granted us by the two fingers and explore the secrets of the golden order so that
one day if a tarnished of the round table hold should become it's a ring light i might
counsel them ensuring order regains its proper form fighting rule over men do you still see it
the guidance of grace how come nobody's done how come nobody's gone like this after a dialogue
option i'm kind of disappointed uh i don't see it that is unfortunate cause for despair
it's likely a temporary condition i'm told for whatever reason it happens from time to time
just keep your chin up and stay the path well that's not gonna be too hard guidance of grace
returns to you oh this guy the faith person has the guidance of great i see it most tarnished
are blind to it these days you are something of a rare breed what do you say care to learn
an incantation of the two fingers incantation of the two fingers study incantations oh okay
yeah so this is uh this is faith i'm like pyromancy right i'm not faith right urgent heal
yeah all right where's the um sorceress may the golden where's the sorcerer sorcerer sorceress
where are they hello he must be new here just call me dialos the honor of one's
household's little import in these lands it's a cool place have you met a young woman named
laniya on your travels she's my servant but fickle as the wind take your eyes off for but
a moment and she's good as gone we just got a forced break please be sure to tell me i lost
like too many times at the boss so the game said hey why don't you go check out one of the other
areas bro there's all the stuff to see be sure to tell me if you meet a young woman named laniya
looking for laniya write that down okay that all right be sure to tell me if you
wish is a servant she's been like i've lost count of them honestly there's so much blood down here
invaded oh shit i got invaded mad tongue alberich this is pvp this is bm this is not pvp right
fuck you god damn it oh dude 16,000 440 points in pac-man are you kidding me
i need to stand up i'm having too much fun oh no how do i get back there i've died 55 times
really let me try this again is there a bonfire i can sit up i don't think so is that a huge bonfire
this is fucking ridiculous i fucking hit him with it can i not do that
i parried that shit i actually did put it in two hands i'll get him if he drops something cool
oh i know what to do when he spawns just spam this lala i have a feeling i'm probably not
gonna kill this guy i got if i can get a parry i'll be okay oh my god i got it that's i'm not
gonna fight i'm not gonna be okay as literally this is literally impossible literally impossible
actually impossible all right well here's what we're gonna do i'm just gonna start swinging in
this room no uh what else is in here there's a few other places to go cool time to spare
what do you mean a house guest are you aggrieved oh she knew about a visitant here then you would
do well to remember the first words of grace given to you stand before the elden ring the
elden lord if those words help any meaning to you follow the guidance of grace lay low the shard
bearers for yourself the graphics are incredible they really are the game just looks absolutely
phenomenal and the doors to the receive the wisdom the two fingers once the wisdom of the two
fingers becomes your own are to you a proper welcome this guy doesn't care member of the
round table i have hopes for you i'm sick and tired of them these namby namby tarnished think
us no more than a shelter from the rain we've spoken long enough we've spoken this guy's got
such bad nerd neck i really thought when we came in here i thought he was sleeping i thought his
head was down and i thought he was sleeping on the desk oh okay that's like a 500 years of history
i'm just destroying a wild animal okay cool so we're gonna i can't do anything in here until he
until this guy respects me i can't do anything i gotta get the two fingers come back where's the
sorcerer there's definitely a sorcerer purchase great rune that's the aid of a hunter summoning
increases memory slots stone sword keys all right this is where i have to make a decision
whether or not i'm gonna stay with the flail the short spear might be pretty good
i don't want to use this cemetery might be good too i feel like the flail is gonna be fine
pick on appearance of a host of fingers pick on appearance of a cooperator what is this do
deceives invaders this is just a mess with somebody that invades they offer a bell bearing
behold pear oh hello okay uh edge can i talk at all oh that you're cool looking the skeleton
really cool i need to drink some water yeah i'll take we'll take a minute here let me just see if
there's a the sorcerer's person is here or is blocked did not go this way though you and i we
get each other oh blacksmith actual blacksmith okay hold on ashes of war wild strikes okay
definitely the it's got to be the standard one right ash of war duplication they put on more
than one thing i see you've noticed the chains nothing special i'm a prisoner and these are my
chains i'm trapped in smithing for you fools that's all there is to it you're a prisoner
don't read too much into it well no grudge against you my being a prisoner is no fault of yours
besides mind smithing despite my differences the weapons get stronger all the same
even time technique never fails besides it helps me forget all right gotta find the sorceress why
is it always door oh wow sorcery the cosmetics oh you can redo your character that's interesting
greetings great champion called by grace i am fear circumstances have compelled my stay at the
round table hold your spells on you would you allow me to hold you every time we hold hands
we teleport to a different place some of your life figure and your stout-heartedness doing so
will grant me the warmth of a champion and you i am sure will bear a baldekins blessing
blessing vulgar perhaps where i come from it is a sacred act okay um i guess i'm gonna let you
just do this great champion is gonna grab me you are very warm what you felt light up inside you
was a baldekins blessing though it is but a fleeting thing i am afraid come back to me
should you require another i will take you in my arms as often as you need a buffer or something
what does it do where is it all the kin's blessing uses fp to temporarily boost poise
if ever allows one to forget any aches and pains in death there is only peace for in death there
can be no sensation so what i use it it has one use and it makes my poise go up so i don't get
you need that hug after dying 50 times with the horse guy okay interesting please to see you
again would you like me to hold the blessing is still a flame in your breast would you like to be
held regardless and good day to you i want you to teach me i want someone to teach me spells
one more place i didn't go spell crafter ah utility guy with the wood circle on his
neck uh that guy is i just used it was in here stone sword key was lost with its use but i just
opened oh no it was this bad there's a chest in here oh fuck it's a time for us to do a little
bit of a pivot here i need strength now the ghosts are other players yes they're in their
own universe oh great that actually may have been a waste i just got a crossbow for it that
that's not good i can buy them from the vendor though over there all right well there's no um
there's no sorceries so that's kind of annoying probably to go find them somewhere
okay unless somebody in here does it they didn't talk to i think i talked to everybody all right
so here's what i'm gonna do i'm gonna go pee i'm gonna drink a bunch of water i'm gonna come back
and i'm gonna keep going because i'm it's cool it seems amazing really fun i'll be right back
i'm gonna go pee and we're gonna play by the way a new song uh from lord i got a few more
let me know let me know how you like this one i'll be right back give me like two three minutes
so i am back i've got a huge water i've got a crunchy uh peanut butter
cliff bar you better believe that we're not even close to being done i peed i stretched i'll eat
that clip bar over the next hour and a half and we can get uh we can get back into it and turn this
off i'm into the music or the music turn off oh that's weird it stopped did oh i didn't put it
on loop that's my bed all right let's go let's uh continue
i shouldn't have fucking looked at the preview i shouldn't have looked at the preview god damn it
oh i fucking ruined everything shit i looked over at the preview and it was just
my fucking god i was god damn it i've ruined everything it's fine
uh i it took so much effort to try to not make any sound there it's just so it looks so bad
it doesn't it looks weird i look like a fucking cartoon character
actually it looks like good what the fuck no it doesn't all right i don't want to say anything
okay there's gonna be people over the course of the next like six hours i'm gonna be streaming
for like another like at least three four hours so over the course of people are gonna come in and
just think holy shit this dude's got like some really vibrant eyebrows whatever it's staying on
it's just fucking weird enough where it's very bizarre looking i think we're gonna go for it
i'm gonna go here i want to investigate this
so
in like 15 seconds how did you fail immediately because dude i look over and it's just like it's
such a it's so jarring let's check out over here uh i've got to kill that first boss today
maybe the flail is not the way to go i'm kind of committed at this point at least temporarily
all right so this is kind of the broken area here something here yes there is okay very cool
look like an impersonator i really do look like somebody that looks exactly like me but it's not
me okay uh let's check over here really come on i can't kill it now i can't kill it now do
we like the unibrow guy from jimmy neutron i don't know who that is all right what's this okay
i can read your fingers okay all right down
all right no don't touch me somebody all the way down oh nomadic warriors cookbook
okay oh oh shit this ain't on the map guys this this ain't on the map
you're kidding me don't go that far uh there's a little cave right here weird okay i thought the
tree was a monster this is we're going a ways away right now hopefully i get one of those uh
transports what's that okay there's a lot of hold on pretty good thin beast bones this is an hd
texture pack derma i feel like something's gonna jump out and attack me somehow i'm gonna get off
the horse this has been way too quiet of a ride oh man that luverina of the lakes oh that's my new
weapon arm wild swings right look over the ledge why is it always don't you dare where am i applaud
this message sure all right this is just still going more fruits break it all right we're back
in ooh golden thing is over here it's actually pointing over here oh no it's not it's pointing
at the other boss all right well i found one of these that's cool and your brain works andy touch
grass this is crazy look at this was i just there i was just over there this is absolutely beautiful
i kind of feel like this is a high level zone that i shouldn't be in or something of that nature
church of erith whoa ah finally sacred tear i'm gonna upgrade the flask perhaps you could spare
some rooms believe it or not i studied glintstone sorceries at the academy of rea lucaria for a
small donation i'd be happy to share my knowledge ask you what hand is it you're a true saint
my name is tokes presumably you're interested i can teach you sorceries as promised only
none of them are particularly great what all right give me a sec hold on there's like something
on my face that's better oh glintstone pebble listen arc starlight magic projectile horizontal
widening magic arc i gotta get some stones do i have any things like those crush things
not enough okay well i remember where this guy is he's here at the church
why is this guy sneaking up on this dude okay well i got the estus thing which is a huge deal
what's that there's so much to do so many places just to go look at and explore
okay well i know what that is now um okay where do i go oh this is interesting
get oh my god oh my god i should have done here are you going for the chewing world record
it's a cliff bar they take 40 minutes to eat i want to i still want to do it let's go back
that there's something there academy scroll cool i'll get stuck you don't know i want to fight these
guys i want to be able to buy a sorcery thousand runes to buy the thing that i and the thing is my
favorite part about being on toy story was the fact that i was constantly constantly asked questions
about uh tom how do you do it how do you actually get in that booth and and and be woody and uh my
only thing i would say is i just got in there and tried my hardest and that's what i would
think everybody watching right now should also try their hardest too everybody needs to try
their hardest and do their best there's no reason not to ever not do your best and i kind of don't
want to die right now yet because it's gone it's gone it's so i when you get the tom hanks for
meeting you get to have fun for like 15 seconds and then it's gone it's kind of like lucid dreaming
if you are if you are aware of tom hanks in your voice you'll lose it okay i gotta pay attention
before i lose those souls you guys are just casting no no god that dex strength and it's
strength come on all the cool things that i found have been i can't use them this thing's awesome
okay well i don't think there's anything else here i got what's that that academy scroll
where is that give to a learned sorcerer to acquire oh oh that's huge oh yeah did i beat
uh margit i did not i got the lady came over and said this game's too hard for you and she put her
hand on me and we teleported to a banquet hall all right i need more than that i mean this they
want you to do this right why would it be like this well done no i mean like but why would it
be like that they didn't want you to do that it's like a unibrow i can't get on i've spread it
around hold on all right that's better i fixed it somebody said burt and ernie no i can't do burt
i want those sorceries and i want them right now do you guys understand how
fucked up i'm gonna look when this is off it's gonna i'm gonna look weird i'm gonna look awful
it's gonna look jarring okay i'm gonna give this scroll to him okay study how do i give him the
thing
okay so i gotta go there
you might have guessed the seals are still active making entry to the academy impossible
without a glintstone key okay so i'm stuck here i need a glintstone key
oh the glintstone key
and if you find an extra glintstone key an extra one
once you've tied up all your loose ends would you consider donating to me can i give them the
scroll where are you in the game i don't know i just went in a random direction i don't think
i can give this to him but i really want these really badly which one of these is which one is
good horizontal arc that spreads outward this force me to cast repeatedly and while in motion
this is just light and this i think this is the
from the original game right this is a universal first step on the journey of true knowledge i
this i like this one the one you have now is it glintstone pebble no it's not i have magic
glint blade probably looks like the grinch all right well i can't really do that it wants me
to go that way but i'm gonna go over here or here yeah let's go here put a marker i'm going
over there i don't understand how this is accentuating your chin it's weird i don't
know notepad notepad i'm begging you what what should i write on it but i need glintstone key
okay hey somebody said it looks like you're wearing fake teeth huh fake teeth it's because
this looks weird together all right this way let's get on the horse is that area over there
with the big giant people i'm going that way yeah let's go because i can reliably kill them with
uh the sorcery now yeah these guys are not a problem now although i might need uh i'll get
this guy at least i might have to run around him a little bit all right i'm out bye oh shit dodge
thousand and is that it should play worms armageddon i don't know maybe maybe one day
not i actually am not good at the worms games i'm pretty bad at them oh shit okay this is pretty
open coliseum where's the horse i can't have the horse here oh no that's bad where is he
where is he no horse allowed either oh my goodness gracious all right i can beat this guy
that's horse shit i hit him i can get burnt by that fucking lava all right he's dead you
no all right invader defeated summoning other players use her calling finger remedy to reveal
summoning signs gold sign indicate an ally red signs are an adversary sure hammer talisman
hammer talisman what's up i love you germa just kidding i'm sorry what did you say
i'm sorry it's it's always going to be funny to me is it an item oh enhances stamina reducing
attacks against blockers i feel like it has read an ai sentence enhances stamina reducing attacks
against a blocker so it makes it easier to break guards okay i kind of
i'm gonna keep this on i think all right oh somebody here competitive multiplayer small red
pg whatever this is like competitive pvp all i wanted was to fight to fight as a warrior to
the last so why why oh guidance and grace but this door not open i don't know man so this is
what like the pvp zone what about over here oh i thought i had to get off is how okay door ahead
door ahead hidden path ahead you know what's really kind of look at this somebody did the look there's
a secret door here like that's already here door ahead and looks hidden path ahead don't you
you're stealing this person's joke and then this person is like hey by the way there's nothing here
just want to let you know it's like i feel like i'm reading a message board 29 okay he did it but
he did it louder yeah oh this is kind of cool it's that thing these like slugs fire slugs
i like come over here oh fuck i think it's gonna explode why is here rave violet smoldering
butterfly oh there's a bunch of them what i got like i just hit like the jackpot all right cool
wonder what i can do i'm gonna go i'm gonna go to that like kind of beach area here where those
giants were but i need to get some i need to get some more mana oh stop you're killing them
i have enough to get the sorcery but i'm not gonna do that yet in fact no no no no no no no no no no
did you see the sea of thieves update yeah dude it's fucking crazy
no sit back down green's here that's better is that area with all the giants i feel like i can
get some good experience there that was like here right oh i can change the marker that's very very
useful okay you're gonna play deep rock galactic i don't know maybe probably not though i never say
i will not huh who's that there's so many wolves everywhere oh my god i can't
i didn't want to hit that one that guy's got health see it's like a rare spawn oh all right
clean him up what was that all about that's it nothing you didn't drop anything damn really
that was a cool encounter too okay another statue over there oh hell yeah this is the game everyone's
hyped about yeah i'd say so this is that game gonna go by the sorcery very very soon and i mean
incredibly soon i want to see what this is a geyser well i die if i go down there this is
weird and it's weird enough for me to want to do it this is weird right like this is weird that
it's here there's got to be something down here there is yep raise the rat all right no
oh holy shit this is so pretty i can't get over it okay what about down here
you know that's one of those that's a slug that i can't hurt yeah no please poison bloom oh man
that's this bad don't while on horseback ride it's current into the air yeah we gotta go um we gotta
go i'm not messing around here what is this place this is another dungeon oh i love these i love
okay i'll be right back i'm taking this off i look like a fucking idiot you're you're my
comfort streamer oh you have a white pair let me see thank you gotta tell you you've all you've all
just been had yeah now look how weird i look when this is off oh no i'm like ugly oh no what
happened i had the gigachad filter on i was thinking about taking another break and filling
in the beard and like giving like really long like angry eyebrows but it's like it's like 10 o'clock
that was a joke for like four and a half hours ago okay that's good enough oh shit look now i
look like i don't look as good i need i'm gonna start doing that save the stuff all right let's
go oh i love these these are like my favorite part of the game so far what's he doing
oh my god we're both so awful aren't we why am i just can i might i might can i not hurt you
dude i hear something lumbering around you're annoying you know that i'm gonna bleed
the brows back on oh i'm not putting the brow back on all right left or right i'm gonna say
i'm gonna say right first that's a pressure plate i'm gonna step on that and the thing
something's gonna shoot at me what happens shoot them shoot them shoot them shoot them shoot them
it's so fucking dark i can't see anything all right well i was trying to get him to get killed by the
thing did you take the wig off now i'm getting gamer elbows you guys ever get that where you're
like been your elbows have been on your arm rest for an entire day i don't even give him a chance
just go just kill fight fight fight did i not pick up my i would have been a shame if i didn't
get those okay this time don't be stupid they fire straight out just don't step on it use your
casting abilities to take out these shitheads back is there anybody this like this ceiling right
they're gonna be behind me yeah i even knew you were there too this is another door all right so
that's very obviously that's where the boss is a little whatever the little mini bosses
right i forgot you dude now don't step on the pressure plate all right so we got smithing stone
very cool i need those root resin again and now we can open up this thing cool cats slow um i think
if i you know this i would imagine a lot of people are potentially uh potentially have this stream
in a tab on a different monitor while they are playing through elden ring at the same time
that's what i would do that's what i would do that maybe you got me onto the background
maybe you're playing you know you're probably busy and every so often you're looking over here
to see just how much further you are than i am which i hope you're doing i hope you're doing a
good job gaming uh i think i'm gonna reset it because that's definitely a boss i actually
think i'm gonna go buy the new sorcery thing and level up once because i'm kind of terrified of
this i'm smoking crack fuck video games well i've been okay all your time yeah you shouldn't be
doing that i'm gonna level up uh intelligence it's not gonna be enough i know i'm not traveled to
site of grace from this location can i travel back here if i'm outside the dungeon gonna
teleport inside the dungeon okay i can just making sure in there i'll buy the i only have enough for
one which one do i want do i want the default spell or do i want the arc spell i don't know
ours a horizontally widening magic arc this one has more intelligence required 130 in the morning
you're still going i'll be going for at least another i'd say at least another probably hour
or two at least can i afford both i want to level up though yeah i guess i'll just get whatever
and now i have to go tune them right come back let's get to a bonfire
i will carry for a bit it's fast and spammable oh you like the game i think it's absolutely
phenomenal so far i keep finding new things to do try this spell i sort of just keep finding
stuff to do that's it has nothing to do with the main game okay let me see yeah this is the this
is that spell the original kind of just little cat and it's quick too so now i can actually use
this oh you kidding me i wish i had this like an hour ago what about this one wow that's good
oh yeah okay now uh now we're actually working now we're actually playing the game now
i want to allocate more mana that move is really good all right let's let's go go back i forgot
that they dropped down which what direction am i firing this nice all right well wait a minute
didn't i um oh i can use the tier use sacred tier to increase the amount of hp and mp uh whatever
yep very very important all right this time don't mess around damn it's good it's good i
think we're doing a hard pivot back hard pivot to casting i wanted to do astrologer at the very
beginning and i think it was the right call but i do like the ability to be able to use my melee
too let's go ahead and open the door please don't step on that
oh i could just run by these guys well let's see if i can kill this cat right there
all right let's do it brave warden duelist whoa whoa what hit me oof oh i'm out of juice
all right let's see he's not bad he's not bad it's not bad so i like wasted a lot of
i wasted a lot of shit on that okay so i'm we just run we're just going to sprint over there
forget about these guys just a waste of time this way okay let's go oh you go please
let's get it right off the bat wow that hitbox is crazy fuck you oh he's in he like does this
like fucking overwatch ult where he like jumps in the air and he stays up there for way too long
instead of coming like jump down he goes like jump down it's a devin chat
that'd be that'd be insane hey you back you can backstab him oh okay i'm just getting too
way too uh jumpy when he goes in the air you gotta wait oh you gotta be kidding me oh bad move to do
that right now i'll see you later so casual man casual mancy i hey i got in there i had to dodge
your shit a lot of times i hit him with my flail at least like 10 to 20 times too bad i got another
weapon that's probably incredible that i can't use look at all this cool shit that i can't play
with it's a weapon art oh it's that this is so heavy yeah but that was awesome um i could eat
my soul strength getting all the cool gear again you have any souls dude just chose the caveman
no i mean the battle kind of battle mage stuff is really cool i would like to get a dex weapon
that i think is a little more comfortable to me open this people need to get out of the strength
or dex build mindset um i mean i'm trying to do kind of a half and half casting and dex dex
increases your cast speed so it's gonna be pretty useful okay well that was cool what platform is
this is on pc pc uh i don't know if the same is on console but pc currently has kind of a weird
problem where um sometimes a game will just hang and slow down and speed up i'm imagining that over
the next maybe even a few days or week or something maybe they'll figure that out but regardless of
that it still is really really fun i'm gonna do the next point into uh vitality and then i'm
gonna try to fight that boss again going for the boss again reduces fall damage and sound animal
what is it animal rainbow alleviates blood loss okay so let's head back to i want one more point
in vitality and then i'm gonna go kick the shit out of this guy i haven't been down here yeah i'm
gonna go that way just for a minute how come everyone's playing elden ring um because it's
i don't know we only get one of these every like three four years i think i'm i don't want to do
that though this probably such a there's probably a better staff i don't want to do that it's the
olympics of video games yeah i mean it's just every three or four years they make one of these
and they keep making them more and more interesting so i'm gonna do three and two let me see if i can
beat him now i'm just gonna go for it that's a cool lake over there and there's something cool
here too but let me see if i can beat him are the cats in the game oh well maybe wait no i'm not
ready for that yet let me let me level up uh vitality one more time oh okay this shit's
fucking insane i'm gonna be able to clear whole just waves of enemies really free and beast sir
code oh it's the thing that they weren't still rolling just fine i keep hitting select do that
definitely these okay versus physical that's way better i can't wait to take off this helmet i hate
it all right that's enough to do vitality and then i'm gonna go for it i hope he hasn't had water the
whole stream i hope that salad was what he is all he got wait what thanks for the reminder
you look like an 1800 scuba diver
all right vitality very good do you know how much i can cheese the hell out of this
i can summon the soldiers and just sit there and just spam cast spells at him would you guys call
me a bad gamer if i did that let me see if i can do it without them yes but it would still be kind
of cool let me see how how much how well this plays out without them i think we gotta build
that we're gonna be able to work with here let me tell them i just don't know why this is gonna
take away your first try jevil card that's not fun come on i'll get him i don't need any more help
you go dodge dodge dodge dodge dodge swing swing swing back up i hate that fucking move so much
i'm using it as a truck right now i'm using okay sorcery is awesome but sometimes when you
start to play with like a sorceress you just kind of go like this oh right i have this is a game i
can't get hit the two or three times that i played through dark souls one and dark souls three with
sorcery i remember getting to bosses getting them to like five percent health and just getting
lazy and just still spamming and just losing it's you gotta pay attention still
all right it's he just moves in fucking slow motion it's so annoying i fucking hate this guy
i would rather have to have to dodge 50 attacks a minute than have the guy go in slow motion
smash i'll get him it's just like i haven't been here in like an hour and a half
i just like gotta it's like i gotta get back on the bicycle i told you sorcery fucks
okay please
i had it it's just like dodge dodge dodge dodge like i'm trying not to dodge that much it's just
like sometimes your brain just goes like do it again do it again do it again do it again and
i'm just like no stop don't press that fucking button a third time all right okay what is the
gap close use the weapon art like sucks asshole he hit me he hits me with that little swing every
single time i'm just he takes forever to do fucking every other move greedy too greedy
and i fucked it all up you punk this like hurt my voice somebody said something stupid
somebody said did they say bro look at the hold on bro look at that boss's toes what's
what's wrong with them what are you talking about i gotta just be patient man
it's the slowest attacks whatever the next boss is if it's even 10% faster than this guy it's
not gonna take me that long god damn it i'm dead need to jump more stop telling me to jump
because the last time i did that i got killed i'm gonna beat him tonight i'm gonna beat him
before i go to bed you bet you bet your ass i'm gonna it takes so much fucking longer i keep
trying to wait so long oh my gosh i fucking hate this guy it's like one two three four it's like
god damn it i that was a good start too this guy's f-tier like on the very bottom of the dark souls
boss tier list he's literally f- he's f-0 f-0 plus dude you're turning blue you were better at
this game with the eyebrows god let's go i'm beating him right now this guy gives me so much
trouble it's just all the speed changes oh i'm installing it is it too is it too i can't do a
refund it's the it's the speed changes and it doesn't matter how many times i see it i think
it's faster than it is so look at me listen to me wait another full second before you do
fucking anything his swings are always a full second you understand it's like full two seconds
longer than you think it is it's a full count more count more i want to punch this fucking guy
in the face in real life if i was there if i was there i'd kick i would kick the shit out of this
guy i'd just get i'd get up on him right i'd get up on him and just like like i'm just fucking
flurry this guy with a bright red face i would have a bright red face and i would just be like
i keep getting to like 50 i can't i keep getting to like 50 what is this fucking travel
let me fucking give me a second
good focus on the tail that's how i beat him first try you're a liar you didn't beat this guy
first try when he gets to this phase two and he does like the six fucking moves in a row it's
just like one two one one two one two throw throw throw one two one too greedy yeah i know how many
tries until you win i don't know i probably should have fucking threw this flail into the ocean
because like what fuck all it's doing me here that's the wrong button what a disaster
oh my god i'm so fucked here i didn't i couldn't dodge hard your spells for more damage
i wish i could just move around faster magic is no magic is good i keep getting to like 50 to 40
health and then i just i just fall off because i run out of mana and i'm using a fucking like
a pencil sharpener for a weapon get away from the wall what the fuck i dodged what the fuck man
i got him 40 like 45 like 10 times in a row i am gonna javelin this fucking flail as hard as far
as i can when i'm done with this my fucking hair is in my eyes just kill me kill me and i'm bringing
the boys next i'm bringing the boys next i'm i'm bringing the fucking boys i'm like
okay you know what i'm throwing this old guy in the ocean too all right let's go boys you know what
to do stand there and get hurt while i cheese the fuck out of them with magical potions now
i gotta stack the bleed too oh get him stab him in the mouth all right boys stack on him
stack on him don't let the fucking raid leader die don't let the raid leader die
hey let's do the rest of this with my fucking eyes closed don't make a joke stop
oh my god what am i doing how did i do that why did i do that i was gonna make like a joke where
i was gonna close my eyes and cast a spell at him what the fuck are you doing what am i doing
would i do that why would i do that what was the point why would i do something like that
why would i do that why why i was over i fucking beat him it's not you're not funny okay you're
not funny you're not funny just beat the fucking boss just beat the boss like nobody would have
laughed literally you're not funny nobody would have laughed at you all right bring out the boys
again let's go are you kidding me i'm so stupid i'm so stupid why why yeah i've played these
games so many times you can't be a cocky dick and ruin everything like you you do that you
celebrate after the fight not when he has one hit left you don't go like oh look at this
i'm fucking hilarious what a fucking idiot i'm so mad at myself that was truly the stupidest
thing i've done all year it's probably like the last year and i'm like full tilt now like i was
i was doing so well i dodged like 10 of his attacks in a row what i really have to unbind
fucking crouch and dismount from left stick that's such an awful place for that to be
nice job boys nice job can you not get hit by that fucking move i feel like that move is like
if you're near him you just get hit no matter what i'm so fucked i'm so sad i can't fucking believe it
i could buff the staff no i i can beat him i just put on the tier list
look at how funny this guy is over beating the fucking goddamn boss jump off the cliff
and reset your karma just pull over and ask for directions okay all right this is the one right
now no more fucking around i'm not gonna be a dickhead i'm gonna beat this stupid ass guy
i gotta build up the bleed on him fuck you
dude fucking leave me alone for one second you got another guy next to you you know
maybe parried i mean that's a great question but i feel like maybe i'll try it okay how i staggered
him before i think i hit him like three times in the face i can't fucking believe it oh that was
weird man come on come on come on come on come on come on come on come on don't go off the fucking
cliff no why is b don't i pressing b and it won't fucking do anything i'm getting like weird input
lag so fucking dead here oh yeah i can't i'm so fucking annoyed i can't fucking believe i haven't
killed him yet okay what when he does that move when he does like the swing swing swing stab
into the ground he hits me with it every single time he hits me every single time like i'm trying
dodging left dodging right like dodging away he still hits you with it and i swear to god
sometimes i press b and dodge and i don't move i just kind of stand still it's weird really how
did i not dodge through that poor shit i'm trying to stagger if somebody said i could a heavy attack
will stagger what a bad fucking time to heal idiot shit i think that's staggered so you know like how
do i i can't get away from that okay again oh my god why is he giving me so much trouble
you've seen me play through sakiro dark souls one dark souls three i i want to fucking throw
this guy over the edge of the world this is the i i don't know why this guy's doing it to me
am i under leveled i don't think so i did a lot of the side stuff i blew it already i'm all right
damn it dude fuck off i'm telling you right now i press b and i didn't dodge
start again we're just gonna do it change spells i only have three more more hopping
it's because you have the worst weapon yeah but i mean i have spells change the spell to this all
right if i don't beat him in the next like three or four attempts i'm literally gonna eat this
fucking flail on stream and then i'm gonna get a new weapon i think this is no i'm gonna keep
pebbles better oh shit i wasn't paying attention all right i pay attention pay attention come on
come on seriously this guy's not that hard he really isn't i just i'm just i just can't get his
pattern down my brain just cannot do the two speed changes it's making me want to fucking
just chug this as fast as i can charge the spells i don't think i can charge the spells there's no
there's no card except no i i have played through all these games without summoning
anybody with the exception of one or two cases i ain't doing it i'm doing it on my own
i'm doing it on my own yeah yeah i can't charge this uh hold on let me start hold the button down
that's what i was just doing how much mana does that use it uses a lot more the boys are
terrible i would have been i would have literally been in the next area by now
if i make another joke at the end of a boss fight i will gift 50 million subscriptions
i will gift 100 trillion subs if i make a joke with one hp left on this guy again
there's 100 damage okay there's a lot of mana i'm not sure i like this
i wonder if it's better to actually just try to use the use a melee weapon right i'm i swear
to god what the fuck man why am i running out of stamina i'm not just noticing that that's weird
wouldn't be because he i can stagger them you really have to wait to like literally press the
button to attack me all right hold on so let me get this it's not a bad idea it's not a bad idea
it's got to have to build up right god damn it i have no my heels either uh something's i swear
to god something weird is happening i just tried to dodge and it didn't do anything he didn't even
move he didn't do anything what the fuck what's going on that makes no fucking sense i had the
same problem oh i'm i am i am not fucking this is not copium i swear to god like sometimes he
just doesn't dodge what i mean i'm plugged in i'm not i'm not wireless it's copium i swear to god
it's not copium it's not even input lag it's like it just doesn't work like i'll go dodge and he'll
just he won't move i had the exact same problem but it was only with this boss really magic has
end lag i don't think so i didn't cast a spell that was weird i have i had a full bar of stamina
all right how many attempts have i had on this boss this is like insane like this is crazy have
i just been so far out of the game with the souls games that i'm just so rusty that i can't beat the
first boss all right let's go i hate it this is the one
it's happened again what the fuck is happening is that all right don't let fuck no fucking around
is that actually a problem at this guy like i swear to god like 10 percent of my inputs are not
being uh not being done on the dodge it's weird what the fuck's happening is it where the terrain
is sloped i don't know sometimes it's just like when he when he like goes in the air i don't even
like attempt to dodge every jump attack the frame issue i i mean it's weird i promise i'm not making
it up to make it look like i'm not fucking terrible at this game just jumped backwards
i it's but you heard it you could fucking hear me click it twice twice in a row you heard it i
swear to god what the fuck is happening you heard me click what it's doing it again
this is a big problem i now i'm realizing what the fuck's been happening this whole god damn time
my dodges aren't happening crouching i don't think so get an on screen i'm about to fucking
sit here and show you like it's just that like that sometimes he just doesn't do it
need to resupply the copium i'm fucking not fucking around your v-sync is is doo-doo
you don't have to beat him yeah i mean that's a huge problem if that's what's actually been
happening because like i feel like i shouldn't be getting hit like half the time is it actually
the terrain like i'm getting stuck on like a cinder block or something but you won't even do
the input get his ass get his ass why are the sticks everywhere look at that fucking muscle
it's bigger than anything you've ever seen guys guys i can't get up my arms are too weak
oh the dodge is fucked and i'm not kidding the dodge is fucked the dodge is fucked i'm not
kidding i swear to god this input lag caused by forced v-sync capping your fps under 60 should fix
it oh thanks for the copium man appreciate it that guy was fucking crazy but i swear i don't that
probably wouldn't even have been that bad if that wasn't happening i wouldn't have died like 40
times with that guy if i didn't have like like 10 to 20 percent of my dodges actually where the
input was there you know what i mean like that's that's great all right i got a ton of this game
is really good this game is really good fuck that boss throw him in the ocean uh okay so this game
is good it's very good so oh i got a lot of level up to do you just suck so bad all right fine
yeah uh oh you think i just suck so bad oh yeah yeah you can do it too wait you said you would
what what did i say he wouldn't have died so many times if you didn't try to be a funny e clown i
that's what i know trust me dude i am internally i am i am going to i am internally punishing myself
right now for that bullshit because like like 10 to 15 more attempts were added because of that
this person said uh you look like you're having lots of fun back there you said you would eat
though your flail if you died three times when you're gonna eat it okay so just make sure
everybody knows uh so i said if i made any more jokes i'll give 100 million subs
but that was just for that boss that was just for that encounter and it doesn't it's not any
other encounter like i can make jokes at the other stuff if i want to it was just for that boss i
wanted to clarify that all right so do i just dump points into endurance and call it a day
and just never do it again or should i 20 look should we spread it out maybe some more mana
us two being bad at game thanks for the content it was the dodge it was the dodge it was the dodge
it was the dodge i'm gonna say let's get this to 15 and then i'll do that looks good to me that
looks good to me what how long have i been playing for eight hours i want to keep playing though
how is it it's like midnight but i i'm not done what's the most attempts you ever had on a boss
uh the last boss in sakiro took me i think six hours it was i believe six hours
it's beautiful holy shit actually looks phenomenal bring some water i got a huge one right here i've
been drinking it the whole time i've been watching someone try and beat the tree sentinel literally
from the moment that you beat it it's fucking not easy man it really isn't don't let anybody tell
you that these games are like well you see it's fucking simple what you do is you just have to
go do this and this and instead i i beat him on my first try and by the way jerma like i beat that
guy in my first try too i turned around in my chair and i beat the guy i actually beat him
with my fists like these games are hard okay so if anybody ever tells you that first of all say
you're full of shit because they're full of shit and second of all see one because that's all that
matters what do you want for dinner um i don't know of a snack i i had a crunchy peanut butter
bar um i'll take another break in like another let me get to like the next section here and then
i'll take a break um yeah give me another few minutes you know there's probably people that
actually can do all this stuff in once like without any problem at all but they also get to see the
world at like you know point point 0.5 seconds better than everybody else like i told you this
theory that i have that we all kind of see the world differently some people see the world like
0.2 percent like 0.2 seconds slower than everybody else some people see the like perceive the world
0.2 percent faster than everybody else right people that can play games like this i swear
to god they have like this 0.010 millisecond like slow down that they get to experience
like i i just don't understand how it's like that reaction time yeah like the world is is like a
little bit you take it in a little bit slower so you can react faster things it's an alien rant
no it's not it's still stuck at the tree sentinel yeah keep at it but just don't okay here's what
here's what happens if you guys are new to playing these games which maybe some of you are
you just watched me um go through about four or five stages of like i would say grief it's the
weapon this weapon sucks something's wrong with the weapon yeah fuck this weapon this boss sucks
this boss is impossible this boss is stupid you know what maybe i can't do it maybe i'll just go
do something else no you know what i can do it no i can't no fuck this game the game sucks why
people play this this is the best game i've ever played in my life i i want to tell everybody to
play this because it's seriously like it's a 10 out of 10 fuck this game i'm refunding it this
game sucks delete it throw it in the ocean that's literally how everybody plays these games
every single person is it delay on the webcam it shouldn't be but at the end of the day if you
continue to go forward and you end up doing it all the copium all the anger all the annoyance
all the frustration all the my controller is broken in quotes you get this intense feeling
afterwards of that was awesome i accomplished something crazy because this game is really
fucking hard and it's really really interesting and then you go back to like okay what's next
that's why these games are so much fun
really i don't know if i trust this dude use the main gate or sneak around
i think i'm just going to the front door what do you think looks like a trustworthy fellow
no i'm using the main gate
when you approach the gate it's only your neck on the thank you idiot uh so here's the main gate
open the gate this is the main gate hello open the gates that was much easier than i thought
it was gonna be golden rune blister bolt i feel like i should have probably gotten hit by that
i thought he was gonna let me in i thought he was letting me in i'm jumping on the legend mario
i'm safe he warned you yeah but what i mean i'm okay i'm here i was supposed to just fall
and r1 him i thought this was a different guy that would have been very bad that would have
been not good i don't think and i use the horse yeah somebody hurt him what just happened what
the fuck happened boys let's go that's those scared sounds
oh watch out get him get him get him get him get him do something
all right boys get him we gotta go get rid of the ballistas that's important they do
just kind of stand here they all fucking terrible hey what's in the telescope what are you looking
at maz smithing stone nice hey i need i need you guys to come up here we're gonna go around the
anybody see a gamer anywhere i can't find one up top really i need to get up here wait really come
on i gotta get you from what happened to you all right all right boys send them back wait they're
still alive oh shit what happened did he just die oh my the final the final boy just died what
happened well you see you don't understand i tried to breastfeed i got stuck my controller doesn't
work this game fucking horrible this game sucks fuck this game i should uninstall it i'm gonna
throw it into the ocean what i'll just tell you relax it gets a little bit funner and you keep
going and eventually you're gonna beat that boss you're gonna beat that guy and it's gonna be a
lot of fun trust me man trust me it's a really fun game you should keep playing all right so that
the ballistas are all gone i don't think i need to do anything else i think i'm okay this is the
anti-game journalist game there's no more ballistas right check this out i'm gonna see
why you play sorcerers i was thinking i could get him all in one hit oh wow wow wow what is it
has he done the bit of yelling harry potter spells when he cast magic yet no and that's a
that's a big mistake i'm actually kind of annoyed that i haven't done that yet so
where is it where's the other um is a goddamn thing it fired at me from over here where is it
where is it i've heard it i'm gonna get hit the head by a stray arrow and die oh looks like a
little magic user doesn't have any more mana folks let's see what happens when he gets a little
bastard oh shit stop being a fucking little weirdo please i have zero health this is bad
somebody just needs to come over and touch the back of my head and i die i think this is the
only enemy that's left in this area so i can't screw this up i just can't
it hurts i got it i'm so overreacting it's so bad and you all know it but it's so hard not to
is that it i can't get hit once oh shit there's a guy there wait maybe this way oh man oh man oh
man oh man oh man oh man go back go back go back go back i have so many souls holy shit okay it's
gonna wait it's gonna resurrect everybody why did he hear me all right all right all right all right
i'm just gonna go spend the money i'm gonna spend the money oh my god get in the room please
get in the room i was kidding around i was messing around uh-huh you can't come in here
this is a sanctuary just like in world of warcraft come on come back up here i want to get stuck in
the door oh fine whatever please jeremy jeremy jeremy this joke this is not a joke i was gonna
try to get him stuck in the doorway so i could get him in the head all right i'm thinking yeah
intelligence no i need mana i need more mana wait a minute i have kind of a crazy idea what if i
pass the time to nighttime will they all be in bed nightfall that makes sense right now it's
harder for me to see the gates are open it's only your neck i'm thinking about killing this guy
that's not fourth grade logic that's that actually makes sense dude that makes sense friendo
so this is the side entrance okay another smithing stone i don't make sense i make
dollars time the person up for an hour and then reduce it by 45 minutes oh there's another
bonfire over there i think i hurt me a ladder or something climb hope this doesn't kill me
oh fucking rare bald eagle all right um where's the or i want to keep playing but it's it's late
it's late but i want whatever i'm having fun i want uh all right in i'm coming back tomorrow
but keep playing i'll take another break and then maybe i'll eat a little bit because i don't know
um this is i'm just awesome it's too fun go ahead is that is that the same person that said that
they did that in the chat pickle this is you this person said they were doing this like throughout
the game or something right yeah this summoning pool is now functional let's head up this way
and i'm gonna let's get some more blasts what do you say making a nice round 10
i don't know we'll see i'm gonna be up left tomorrow essentially i'm gonna do is i'm gonna
go sleep and wake up and play the game like that's essentially what's gonna happen here
not dealing with that we can throw him into the ocean get up did he get it off no he didn't
i thought that was me screaming i mean that's i do kind of don't you think about falling off that
edge don't you think about falling off that edge don't even think about blowing that horn either
where's my spell oh my god you idiot you're not even funny i did i sat there and was like you're
not funny you're not even funny it's like i'm looking in the mirror it's like oh i'm like i'm
like psyching myself up you're gonna have a good fucking show today you're gonna be fucking funny
no you're not funny you're not even funny prove them that you're funny prove people that you're
funny you're not funny what the fuck was that horse shit it's like uh like fucking uh taxi
driver like what am i doing i can't reach him from here i hear a patter of little footsteps
in here i just looked at how weird i looked on face cam like that's why i don't even ever use it
that's not what i was doing visions of a hidden path there is no hidden path
could this be item no it's not let's go down first let's get to that
oh fall from the ceiling hook claws what holy shit he's ugly
oh okay that's actually kind of good i think it's a weapon art does it have one
can i do this in two can i hold my hand and do oh i can it's a dash i think this might be a good
idea what's the scaling on it how bad is it xc and it has lead build up how much is the flail
lead 50 so it's flail does more damage but has worse scaling i don't know i'll try it for a
little while wolverine mage i'll try it for a little bit why not nothing else clearing a path
very good very good very good i don't have no health push as well that's not good oh right like
holly was talking about dinner i don't know when i uh um when i go on break figure out what that's
going to be something really interesting about this game so far it's something that seems to
be missing from the game that's in every single one of these games pretty much besides i don't
remember being in sekiro maybe not it's a shortcut so you don't really need them anymore because
there's an open world game this person's freaking me out so smoldering butterfly
i had him over there he's gonna have a 2 a.m dinner oh i this might be one of those weird
like my energy is still at like a nine i feel fine i feel great i don't feel fatigued at all
like actually at all i got a lot of these oh shit oh we gotta go back up you'll feel it tomorrow
yeah but what was okay since all of the medical bullshit when was the last time that there really
was like an eight plus nine plus ten plus hour stream it's been a long time and i mean if you're
only gonna get these every so often then why not this is i'm very invested that's adrenaline
speaking i'm all right i'm telling you i ate a big salad today what the fuck just happened dude
holy shit dude i can't lock on to him why can't i lock on to him i can't lock on to him
yeah i thought i could fucking parry him i just didn't get it off i thought i could just go wham
i thought it looks like i looked like i got it i mean all right get back up there that's so far
away i can get back up there now i know that's what that's what's happening
finally i can take this helmet off you know i'm gonna save my magic because i feel like i'm
really gonna need it i'm already kind of screwed here um jeff wordy i gotta get out there i gotta
parry that dude i really i gotta get in there parry his ass give me the shield i'll get it right
now i love sorcery so much you call me cheeseball all you want it's so it's so much fun although
sorcery like i was saying in the middle of my rage induced bullshit sorcery is cool but there
are some bosses in this game and all the other games where you just cannot do it it the fact
that you need the standing still for that one second is enough to die but it's great for like
85 percent of the entire other the rest of the game which is why this is actually good to do kind
of a battle mage because i'll still be able to use be able to actually fight things with my hands
all right let's go parry oh you thought the darkness was your ally boy you were blinding
i don't even know i don't know how i don't know what the lyrics are
the lyrics what the fuck am i talking i did it so good where is he come on dude don't just get
stuck in the fucking door holy shit he's right there what are you doing get the fuck out of the
way come on out oh you chump are you really gonna do this all right fine cheese's ass
it won't go through the door come on i have to run in there one two three go oh are you immune to
magic you didn't have anything on you a rusty key okay there's a chest here too
curved sword talisman really what does that do i'm safe in here right i can wear two of these
enhances guard counters i don't know that i don't really know what that means
guard counters i don't think i've done that once we tried holding the attack button
power attack with sorcery yeah it doesn't work yeah look holding left uh bumper
you can't uh charge it maybe i learned that later okay cool that's a cool thing to get it's for
shields um i might actually go back to the bonfire but maybe not see if i can keep going
i go through this shit saint trina's arrow oh is there anything else i can do up here
i go up there well we'll find out i'll come back if i need to
um get away from the edge i left i just i'm gonna fall off what's down there what's that
i've been there before yeah l plus ratio fell off what's the point of that how do i get up there
oh that's the key all right locked door yeah that's cool i thought that was for some reason i
thought i was gonna have to bring that somewhere i wasn't here you need to go to sleep i will very
soon i knew it i saw the things on the ground i should have known better i'm in trouble here
this is bad all right let's just take a look over here what else okay i'm just gonna jump
behind the boxes right last shard and silver pickled foul foot a pickle thing okay so what's
out here further up or i'm gonna go the other way there's another place to go this way
somebody on the ceiling right i'm so paranoid hurry up hurry up hurry up it was almost a disaster
okay fire grease how do i get that shit i jump up there i don't think so oh no way you definitely
have to fall in there somehow we have a little fall joke as a treat i can jump from here to there
okay hold on i definitely can make that and i do not yeah it was a little fall joke it was a little
bit you know the eu people up if they oh the e that's right what time is it it's like six it's
like seven or eight o'clock in the morning eu this is finally an eu stream i just had to sit here
for long enough all the na crowd uh went to sleep already which i'm surprised that there's um i mean
it's it's like 12 30 this is crazy i'm surprised that the amount of people that are here all right
i'm going up no i'm not i can make that jump i'll try it one more time est is waking up est has
probably been asleep for the last two hours i wasn't even looking i wasn't even looking i
wasn't even looking i wasn't even looking you better still be alive when i go to sleep um i
eventually i'm gonna go to bed okay so let's go here maybe a running star do you think it matters
there you go stop hitting me with your goddamn shield dodging is death here by the way dodging
is death i'm running okay that's it oh i just it was the panic i i can get back up there god
that's unfortunate that's unfortunate but it's okay it's okay we're just gonna speed run this
but he's gonna speed run it i'm gonna run up there and he's gonna blow the horn but he's
gonna run right by him it doesn't matter actually we need to kill this guy i don't want to actually
don't want to blow the horn throw it please you didn't even blow the shit up that's how i go out
like that after getting all the way through it after going all the way through that's how i go
out and i lose two thousand souls that's how it happens we're going for we're going for a record
here well now it doesn't matter so now i'm just gonna run up there uh it does sound like me you're
right i can't even fight that there we go that's better throw another one already hey you just
killed all your friends fuck just go go go please i need a pee break all right when i get to the
top of this tower we're taking a break we're taking a pee break holy shit i forgot about that guy
get out of here oh fuck this guy i'm fucking snapping this guy's neck sorry i had to get my
revenge i got a salad did i have i gave me superpowers i swear to god i don't understand
it was radishes lettuce parmesan cheese croutons oh no it was this thing okay this like
this actually gave me superpowers this is a peanut butter cliff bar that and a salad apparently
gives you un uh unrelenting energy oh dude wait a minute no what i drank that matcha green tea
thing it was the green tea thing probably right well that worked was it a chicken parm no it
wasn't chicken parm it was like okay i had a salad of like a matcha green tea powder like drink
this is the guy that just okay you're annoying it was a salad the green tea powder and that
flip bar okay i've made it here this is where i died last time interesting brick hammer is that
dex because that's kind of cool oh it's strength now this is the real caveman weapon yeah it's just
like a it's just like a block of cement with some rebar i actually i think this item is in dying
light i also got this too this lord sword great sword this is a little bit more strength too
it's kind of like a long sword it's really cool it's nice looking it looks cool
i'll go i'll stick to the claws they're fast claws are much faster than the um the flail so
but that's what was up here so now where the hell do i go now i can't really go up from here
oh yeah i can this is where i was before though how do i go up from here there's the stairs you
didn't want to oh that's right okay yep that makes sense i fell off accidentally i'm on pst and i
want to go to bed um yeah but elden ring hogchamp it's all right i'm gonna be playing this all week
so don't worry and i'm not gonna rush through the game this is the most focus i've ever seen
you in a game ever i mean the from software series are some of my favorite games ever so
i i love this this is so i love getting angry at games like this i love getting super into it
i love finding things i love scavenging i love and this is like the ultimate version of that
because it's open world and i don't even know what direction i'm going i'm just going in one
and i will be very honest because i have to be it's real close to being at the same caliber
of the first like five to ten hours of bloodborne for me i actually think it might have an edge
just simply because i you don't have to go in a certain direction it might have the edge but
that first real boss made me want to gouge my eyeballs out don't move when he can't see you
man you're slow as shit too aren't you holy shit man you're so slow but your weapon's like
this big on the screen if i only i probably should have powered him i'm gonna i know roll into him but
i rolled to the left because i just my brain just goes left throw it throw it throw it did you die
your eyebrows is making me feel insane because i can't tell if you did oh yeah here i uh i wiped
it all off earlier but you can see it you don't oh yeah i'm supposed to say no i didn't oops i
need something gamer cushions here let's try this again i'm gonna go for a parry i think parry is
the way to go here that didn't work did i get him what what are you doing in here yeah i know
yeah i'm fucking fighting a guy in dark souls 2 yeah yeah sorry bro sorry bro yeah
sorry bro you're not getting the controller no no i don't fucking care i don't care i don't
care get off me man you can't you're not gonna be able to do it no you're not gonna be able to do it
go buy it you have ps5 get out of my room get out of my fucking room why are you insane
i'm not i was gonna yell mom but i don't know i didn't want to like freak out holly be like mom
should be like what is happening in there like that's even that big of a deal
think of all the weird crazy shit i've been screaming this whole day you get out of my
room dude all right we're going double claw it's the only way oh no it's not this is not the only
way this is the way can he fall down there oh this is gonna be some fucking doritos nacho cheese
there oh get out of my room get out of my room get out of my room get out of my room
why is he so much faster than me it's not fair bro bro why are you wearing a suit of armor
get out of here oh fuck he's got so much reach all right give me this thing stop stop i got him
where are my souls here oh they're there okay wait what wait what that's death don't be an idiot
i only had a lover did you miss a death um i don't i don't know i don't think i died did i
feel like somebody's hiding back there contraption does not move come on really
raw string fire grease um okay well there's up there is this way let's go this way first
oh hell yeah thank god but wait i don't want to respawn that guy so let me just take a little bit
around real quick it doesn't move either that's kind of stupid both of them don't work we get a
mechanic in here then check over here just in case something cool uh i'm not even kidding
i'm going i'm going and i'm gonna i'm gonna go buy like 10 packs of that like fucking matcha powder
i didn't even i just kind of had a little bit it was i feel great it's not like energy drink
bullshit it's just like green tea oh man i feel good i need to take a look at some armor too
uh can i this is stupid this might be stupid i made it that's it it feels like kind of dangerous
but nothing oh never mind can i walk on that i think i just almost just killed myself there
okay we're good all right i need that bonfire this is going a little bit too far my liking
how can you still be in orlando i'm fine never mind are we gonna get a break um all right i'm
done that's it i would keep going but i'll just get up and go right back to it i'm gonna sleep
for as much sleep as i need and then i'm gonna get up probably somewhere we don't want to keep
playing all right it's for the best but before i go i want to look at some stuff that's fine
this is light damage yeah this is magic resistance maybe we should put this on i'll put it on just to
look cool don't look cool all right how about how about one more oh i want to how about one more i
just gonna peek i'm just gonna peek out here and see what's going on i'm i'll be i'm gonna stop in
like just a little bit but i'm pretty much done i just want to peek and see what's out here i
promise i just want to see what's out here this kind of looks better than the unreal five thing
that they showed it's unbelievable okay i i just want to take a peek and see what's out here
hey there all right these birds that throw grenades okay all right all right all right all right it's
all right okay all right uh that's it what are we at nine hours well i'm gonna we're gonna go
right back to it thank you for watching everybody it's been the first part of elden ring i just
forgot the name of the game and i will see you tomorrow i'm very excited i think it's really fun
what time tomorrow that really depends on when i go to sleep i need to eat relax go to sleep
and wake up and get to it so i'm gonna try to get up in the morning maybe at like
i don't want to start too too early because i i don't know somewhere around like between one and
two p.m maybe three p.m just put four just put four just no all right two p.m tomorrow is when
we're gonna start two p.m if i get up really early then maybe we'll start a little bit earlier but
i'm gonna try to go for two p.m that's not morning yeah but i i was thinking about streaming at like
10 11 o'clock in the morning but that would require me to get to sleep soon which i might
not i might still be up for a little while so i will see you guys tomorrow round two-ish and
we'll keep going i'm not gonna play without you don't worry i promise this is a very very good
i love this area in particular this one right here all right guys i will see you later let's
get the credits up see you tomorrow take care of yourselves good night goodbye see you soon
it's very very late oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh
oh i gotta save my notes right i gotta save the notepad where the notes look like so far
door next to spawn is blocked shut do stone sword key gargoyle statue a tutorial zone bonfire
looking for lanya send back to the main character of every anime what does that mean
blendstone key for sorcery guy and to open seal to academy okay um i think i know where where i
need to go um you know that i'm having a good time with this game when i'm just like obsessed
with it it doesn't understand any of his notes all right let's raid let's raid uh we're gonna
raid atriarch also playing elden ring i don't know how far they are so i i i don't i'm not
gonna be watching i'm not gonna be seeing it so i don't know how far um they are just be aware
that um you're playing it as well i wonder should i should i give it like a quick peek
and just see where he is no no spoilers all right just be aware i mean everybody's playing this game
so whether they're five to ten hours ahead or five to ten hours behind we're all playing the
same damn game the next like week straight so just be aware of that i'm gonna queue it up
i'll see you guys tomorrow uh atriarch's a good dude he has uh he's shown this channel a lot of
support uh he's rated the channel i think a few times too so let's uh let's send the love back
to atriarch good night goodbye daily why is it going so fast okay i always it always does that
i always think it's gonna happen in like five seconds it's not thanks for the subs as always
see you guys soon take care of yourselves good night goodbye have a nice day because it is a
day for a lot of you bye