Hey, what is going on, everybody? Jerma here. Welcome to Enlighten.
It's been a very long time. For those of you that subscribe to this channel because of my first couple episodes of this,
I deeply apologize that it's taken this long to get another video of Enlighten up.
But it's back, it's here, it's gonna be every other Wednesday.
And we're going to start, well we're not really starting, I've started this a long time ago.
We're going to continue this series with arguably my favorite game ever made in the creation of all video games of all time.
I know I've said that probably about a couple other games, but there's really a top 3 or a top 5 when it comes to my favorite games ever made.
And this is definitely one of them, Super Mario RPG.
And because it's taken me this long to make a new video on this, a lot of you guys probably have no idea what this series is.
So in 10 seconds or less, I'm going to explain this.
Enlighten is a series where I break down an old game.
And one of my favorite old games, I guess it doesn't really have to be one of my favorites,
but one that I used to play when I was younger, and I explain exactly why I'm in love with this game.
With that being said, we're going to get started.
Super Mario RPG Legend of the Seven Stars.
So like in typical Mario fashion, the game opens with the Princess being abducted by Bowser and being hauled off to his castle.
You go on an immediate quest to save the Princess, call Bowser an asshole, and blah, blah, blah.
You know, every Mario game ever made.
That's the first five minutes.
And then the game goes completely bonkers.
A giant Pringles Man sword crashes through the castle, destroying everything inside,
leaving you, Bowser, and the Princess to fend for yourselves and escaping.
Turns out that sword was a real pain in the balls for the entire world, because he broke through the Star Road.
If you don't know what the Star Road is, it's in pretty much all the Mario games.
And they actually go into much more detail with what the hell the Star Road even is in this game.
And you learn, after playing for a while, that the Star Road is kind of this middle ground for people's wishes,
and without it, no wishes will ever come true again.
So of course, as Mario, you have to do all the dirty work, because you can jump real high.
Never understood that, by the way.
Why does Mario have to do everything?
He's like the savior of the world, because he can jump higher than Michael Jordan.
Like, why is that a thing? Whatever, we're going off track here.
Repairing the Star Road becomes the main plot line of this game.
You are aided in this by a bunch of different characters that were specifically developed for this game.
And I'm about to go off on a complete and total rant right here about a couple of these characters,
because here we go.
Squaresoft developed this game, correct?
Squaresoft are the guys that made the game, they made everything.
They created a couple of amazing characters that were never used again in any other Mario game.
The main one I'm talking about here is Gino.
Gino is your guide of sorts.
He's the one that fell from the Star Road, he didn't fall from the Star Road.
He's a star that comes down and takes control of a wooden doll's body, and has superpowers.
He can shoot friggin' laser beams from his arms, he can shoot rockets out of his hands, and bullets out of his elbows.
Why would Nintendo not put this guy in a different game?
This guy is way more interesting than Yoshi's, like, pink, blue, and orange cousins.
Like, who cares about those bastards?
Okay, I'm getting pissed.
But anyways, Squaresoft owns the rights to these characters, apparently.
This guy Gino, the character Malo, the character Kroko,
all these amazing, awesome characters that were developed for this game,
and they were never seen again, they were lost in hell.
Actually, Gino appeared in one other Game Boy Advance game,
but I could go off on that for a thousand years.
So anyways, we'll move on from that now, that was a complete rant, completely off-topic.
Let's go into the gameplay.
So the gameplay is like many other RPGs of the time.
You take turns selecting moves and abilities, attack the people, and the people die.
You get experience, which levels you up,
and there are many items and armor pieces throughout the game to improve your character.
The game also introduced something called Timed Hits,
and Timed Hits became something that a lot of other RPGs would later refine
to try to make RPGs less boring,
because of course, they were just back and forth,
ding, ding, ding, ding, ding, for quite a while before this game.
And essentially what it was, it was just you selected a move, you did the action,
and when you got to a certain part of the animation,
you would click the button again, and it would do a stronger attack,
or in reverse on defense, it would do stronger defense.
You kind of put your hands up, and you block the move they were throwing at you.
One more key thing about the gameplay that's really interesting to note,
this was the only Mario game in existence that ever allowed the player to control Bowser.
Bowser actually joins your party at about the midway point in the game.
He's pretty emo throughout the whole game, by the way.
He cries a lot. I don't know why he's crying,
but Bowser is a playable character.
One of the cooler parts of this game, having him in your party.
Princess Peach is also a party member as well,
so having the three of them lined up in the three-party system
is pretty entertaining, to say the least.
But now we're going to talk about the fun factor of this game,
and the reason why I am so in love with it,
and it's actually a pretty personal story.
So the reason why I love this game so much,
and the reason why it's one of my favorite games of all time,
is mainly because when this game came out,
it was a pretty rough patch of my childhood.
I was having a lot of issues at school,
I was almost failing every single class at one point,
when I was in like the 8th grade, I think, or the 7th grade.
Whatever it was, my like 8th grade through like 10th grade,
or 11th or 12th or something,
it was just about when I became a junior in high school.
I was having a lot of issues in school.
I mean, I was little, I would get bullied by people,
I wasn't the smartest kid in the class,
it was a lot of things depressing me when I was younger.
And the character specifically, Geno, that I talked about before,
contributed to a lot of my loving of this game,
and specifically because he was a small character,
he was a little wooden doll that got possessed by this greater power,
and he had such a large destiny,
and the ending of the game is just so uplifting and so sad at the same time.
There was a lot of reasons why this game pretty much helped me through my childhood,
and I will never lose this game from my brain ever.
I'll probably be 80 or 90 years old on my deathbed,
and I will be looking at the ceiling,
and I'll just be thinking, man, I remember that game Mario RPG,
that really was a great game,
and it helped me through when I was a depressed little kid.
That's gonna happen, that really will happen,
because it happens now,
and it brings me to the last point I want to make about games,
and especially this one.
Everybody has a connection with a certain game.
Everybody has a certain feeling they get when they play a certain game,
and most of them for me are gonna be pretty old,
because I'm a lot older, I'm 27 years old,
so most of my comfort games, I guess you can put that in quotes,
are back when I was 14, 15, 16,
and a lot of you guys are at that age right now,
and you probably have that game you're playing right now
that you will keep in your head forever.
So as the video ends here, as we end on Mario RPG,
and we talk about some things,
it's really a shame that Square and Nintendo
really lost touch after this,
and Paper Mario was actually supposed to be Mario RPG 2,
but it was right at that point when Sony came into the picture,
and N64 came into the picture,
and Square and Nintendo started to absolutely despise each other,
and it never happened,
and that's why my gut sinks whenever I think about this,
because of these things I talked about previously.
But to wrap the video, to close the video,
I do want to say that Mario RPG is a fantastic game.
It's one of those games that if you have not experienced it,
you have to experience it.
You have to play this game by any means necessary
if you are a big gamer.
It's something that has its place in history,
has its place in controversy as well.
This is not, you know, peaches and cream type game.
There was a lot of problems after the release of this,
with, like I said, Nintendo and Sony,
but it has to be experienced, guys.
It is one of the best games I've ever played in my entire life,
and hopefully this has enlightened you.
You like that little outro? Sick.
Anyways, guys, I'll see you all next time.
Thank you so much for watching, I really do appreciate it,
and I'll see you all next time.
And of course, take care, everybody.