It's a beautiful day today. Did you see the sun?
I can't see the sun because of my cameras facing the stairs.
Oh, well, you know, just sitting on this staircase with you makes me just remember the days when I was younger.
There was all kinds of fun things we used to do. I used to come to the-
Oh, my head, Jerma. Is this what you used to do in the old days?
Well, I didn't think we would ever be in outer space together, just floating around.
I don't know what to say. This is too dumb. Whoa, where are we going?
I kind of want to just- I want to see what happens when I try to get out.
This is so awkward looking. Good thing I'm like riding you.
This is just a piggyback.
No, get out of my way. It's my friend. No, I want to get in. No, I'm in. I can't. I have to drive it.
These guys are too dangerous, yet again.
No, we don't want you to drive the car. You die.
It's going too fast.
You're going to make me sick.
We're going to the water.
This is so stupid. I'm going to hit my head on the-
This is real. That person's head would have just censored great.
Okay, here we go. Here we go. We're doing a revert ramp.
Oh, yeah. Tony Hawk's pro skater.
Except with bikes, so completely different.
Damn, that was sick.
200 points. 300 points. You are a rock star.
150 points.
How many points, Jeremiah?
Didn't kill me.
Look at the two ostriches in their natural habitat.
I want someone to walk by and see us like this.
And just be like, what the fuck is going on here?
Get in the car.
What about these dolls that are just standing upright?
This larch-looking son of a bitch is still standing.
Look at this person.
She has just moved.
Look at the way she's holding the gun. Look at her shoulders.
She's hunched over. She just doesn't care.
I thought she instantly died.
She had enough.
I'm not sure what's happening.
Oh, this is so stupid.
Can we move on from this?
What? Why?
Why did that happen?
Why is it not letting us go over this?
What is it?
Are you dead?
I don't know.
Apparently, if you stub your toe, you just die.
You know what? I think I was dead in midair,
and it just didn't say I was dead until I left.
I don't have any words for this.
Did you see how we were jello-jiggling down that staircase?
No, I just instantly died and was gone.
That was jello.
We were just jello sliding around in somebody's cup.
Do you eat jello out of a cup?
Yeah, you can.
I mean, you can, but would you?
Don't hit me over here.
You'll never get me.
What?
I got you.
How did this even happen?
No, the tire.
Something tells me that's not going to work.
That's not going to work.
You're going to crash your game.
You just wait until one of them spawns up there.
The balance.
I could not replicate that if I tried.
I just love how you keep ditching different cars
and trying other things.
Okay, I got it this time.
For some reason, I don't have hydraulics,
but I'm putting the hydraulics on.
God damn it, that doesn't work.
Ditch it.
Try the helicopter.
No, let's try 14 garbage trucks.
Come on, do the thing.
I know you're going to do it.
No, get away from me.
No, no, no.
Get me up.
You made a staircase of garbage trucks.
You ought to do some platforming.