Hey, whoa, daba, atibatabo, ho ho.
That's our family, let's see my armpits, so I'm not lifting my arms up.
Yep, these, what are we gonna do, what do you say like with the lip I was just doing, I'm just going.
Just a little too big, can't breathe without these, what are we gonna do, say like with the lip I was
just doing, I'm just going.
Just a little too big.
Welcome to the stream, everybody. Welcome to the stream, everybody, it's me, Jeremy985 here.
Just getting to my house that was just recently fixed and upgraded, hopefully.
If I put too much pressure on it, it just, ow.
How's everybody doing?
Hopefully everybody's okay, hope everybody's feeling okay, hope everybody's doing okay.
I am not doing okay, this is probably the worst I've ever felt since,
I don't know, I don't have an oberometer for this because this is the worst ever.
Oh yeah, let's, what do we got up here, what's this, wait, wait, I got trapped in the wall,
I got trapped in the wall, I got stuck in the wall,
I can't, there it is, okay, I got stuck back there, I got stuck in the wall.
What is this? Ooh, I didn't know about this, this looks like a staircase.
Oh this is, I really like what they did here, ooh, second floor, wow, interesting stuff.
I didn't finish this one, this one wasn't finished, I was gonna hopefully do some of that
today, some work, but I don't feel like doing any work right now.
They told me that I could finish it however I wanted.
What else is up here? Oh yes, the stuff I bought, bed, another bedroom,
oh, this one gives me less comfort than this one, I look like Clark Kent, but if he was smaller,
didn't go to law school and never went to the gym, I look like fucking Otacon.
Yes, Snake, what you need to do is, but I'm not smart enough to be that guy,
I like this bedroom though, yay, ow, so if you guys knew that weren't here yesterday,
uh, the old house got kind of burnt and we got some insurance money which was immediately used
to fix the damage and to upgrade the home. So now we have two floors, we've got a DIY room
and we've got all the other rooms that you've seen already, thank you, oh my god. Now the
thing about these stairs is they go down pretty far, this is a very high, this is a very far house,
so it takes a few minutes to get down the stairs, takes about 10 seconds, a very big house,
that was just huge, that's not the bathroom, that's not the bathroom, I went to the wrong door,
that's the wrong door, I gotta go to the bathroom real bad, thank you,
get out of here, I don't even want to use it,
I don't think I've washed my hands in a week and a half, ow, ow, ow, ow, ow, okay, is it healed yet?
Let's find out, I feel better, can I get this off too? Oh shit, this is clipped on,
this is clipped onto my body, it's gonna stay, they just have bird shit on me, oh thanks seagull,
oh, and by the way, I know you like the robe, I know you do, but, but I, it's too hot up here to
wear this 24 seven, I'll put it on at other times, okay, they really have a huge bird shit on me,
can I put this somewhere, it's way too hot to wear this, do you know how hot it is,
I can't put this on, and by the way, these don't fit, I was so concerned that these were gonna
get picked, because they don't fit, it was, it's a disaster, so I'm gonna be walking around like
this is a diaper, what do you mean, wear the robe or no food, wear the robe, I can't see that today
to take my glasses off, no robe, no food, fine, what did you hear, here's a souvenir,
all right, I'll put the robe back on, but if there's like an article written later this afternoon
about like streamer dies of heatstroke on stream, remember whose fault it was,
I guess I'll have a cookie, fresh baked cookies, fresh baked cookies from eight days ago,
pretty good, it's not even good, you're like, this is like dad, you have like a sleepover,
like you come up and like, it's like two o'clock in the morning, you come out here,
you're getting a snack for you and your friends and I'm dad, like oh, hey son, what's going on in
there, you guys supposed to be asleep, I keep hearing noises in there, you gotta cut that out
son, I got a big thesis coming up next Monday, do you want some milk, of course you don't,
that was a good cookie, I love how cookie equals entire meal, one thing I had to make really clear
is eating on this stream, eating on stream, right, I can't eat like a full dinner every day,
I can't, what you want me to eat like a full plate of steak or something, no, I'm gonna eat
a cookie and I'm good, and I'm like, I have to finish the cookie, right, I can't just throw
like a quarter of a cookie away, give me a shower, oh wait, wait, let's go for a shower,
with my glasses on, hey, hey, I'll ask Reddit, what's something you do in the shower that like
people know and it's like we all know, oh man, I go in the shower with my glasses on all the time
and they fog up, oh me too, 10,000 upvotes, oh, oh, you know, I don't think there'll ever be one
stream where we don't like do like the fart is funny joke, you know, I thought we could get,
this is the third one, this is day three, but like look, if you get, whatever,
how do I even describe, explain myself here,
at least I feel clean, oh, I need to go, I want to go to my bed, I want to go in my bed,
oh these stairs, I don't even want stairs, I wanted a flat house where I could walk around it,
oh, this is going to be fun, but I don't want to do it, what's that, what's that,
I said jorba.net 5.com, jorba.net 5.com official merchandise, don't go and don't, don't go,
let me see if there's any butterflies, let me see if there's any butterflies,
oh look, there goes one, oh wow,
wow, this looks like I'm trapped in here, like hey, excuse me, I'm locked in here,
can somebody help me, can you catch me a butterfly, I have to go outside,
I'm too tired, I can't catch butterflies, I just got my robe got stuck,
all right, I'll go catch butterflies, sleep would have been a great option,
you know, go to sleep, but fine, I'll go in and catch a few butterflies, like I care, whatever,
I can make it, I can make it, I think I can make it, but no, of course not, I didn't even show you
outside, I didn't even show you, but we can look at something else too, we can look at the pool,
I have a pool now, I almost fell over, I had to just ground myself for a second,
ground myself for a second, otherwise I would have puked, we got a pool, and oh cool, oh yay,
ow, arm, oh butterflies, oh my god, this is a huge net for a butterfly, what are we catching, mothra,
for a fucking Godzilla, oh I think I got one, I think I got,
I didn't know that was still turned on, oh cool, butterflies, what songs do butterflies like,
one bit me in the neck, ow, that's a pool, there's a fucking other one, get a big house,
I gotta get to bed right now, I'm so tired, just I need one night's sleep of good rest in a bed,
that's all I need, that's all I want, oh the bed is calling me, it's screaming at me,
I feel great, what a good night's sleep, holy smokes, oh man, I feel like I could write a book,
I feel like I could write a play, I feel like I could write a novel, I feel like I could go
for a jog, oh I feel fucking incredible, damn what a good night's sleep can do for you,
and a good food, all that good stuff, it's coming off, it's clipped into the microphone,
at some point we're gonna have to actually do something about this, oh I feel good though,
what a day, oh projects, mystery box, what's in here, why is there a mystery box up here,
sounds like a pretty good day to check the mail, I got up a little too fast and I almost just burped,
I created a bunch of gas when I just came up really quickly, and uh yeah, I almost just
burped on camera, let's check the mail, I feel so good, I could probably even come out backwards,
I can, why don't we do it here too, I bet you I can come out backwards,
that's new, whatever it is, there's a piece of mail in here, well this,
it's probably one of these kids in the neighborhood, what does it say, it says,
Jerma, thank you for involving us in such a unique experience, we have had the time of our lives,
the crew, they actually wrote that, they actually wrote that, that's actually really nice,
without a crew like this, this is not possible, this is by far one of the coolest things I've
ever done, and by far some of the best people I've ever worked with in my whole life, and I
really mean that, all of you, there's tons of people back here, tons of people backstage,
you can't even see them, but uh, but clean this shit up,
oh a unicorn, wow, oh it's huge, oh dude, stone cold, oh stunner, don't hurt him, don't hurt him,
I'm not, he's fine, cool, I can't wait to potentially go swimming in that pool with
absolute water in it, you know, fun fact for those of you behind the scenes stuff,
there's supposed to be water in there, it's supposed to be a full pool, but last minute we
decided, what an absolute dangerous hazard considering there is a transformer right there,
all right, I love it though, I do feel good though, this is a good day,
hey, go to work, you got it, I'm in such a good mood, oh hey, can you cue up, can you cue up
like if somebody gets like fucking speared sound, can you cue up like if somebody gets like shing,
like speared sound, could you get that like right now, okay, I want like a skewed up
spear sound, somebody gets hit with a spear and they get like ah, I know, I, hold on, I'll be
right there, hey, hey, hey, thanks a lot to the crew, I'm coming, thank you, eventually I will
get a car, I promise, one day, I don't know when, thanks for the ride, oh shit, I hit somebody,
oh my god, I actually hit somebody with the fucking javelin, are you all right, I mean I
threw it as hard as I could, I didn't know you're gonna be that far away, is he all right, is he
okay, somebody, it's, I see a lot of blood coming out of here, it's like, it's profusely,
what was the medical on him, are you sure we can, is it all right, is he okay, okay, I mean why would
you stand in the way, I mean I knew I had a good arm, but I mean, you know what, but I'm cheating,
you know what I mean, that's a classic fucking comedy joke, all right, that was a good day of
work, I am kind of gross, I mean look, I've got a pool back here, I don't even need your choice,
I want to go in the pool, look, we got it out here, I'm gonna use it, it's been a long day at work,
I'm gonna get in the pool, just turn it off, otherwise I fucking won't stop touching it,
okay, I could wear my, I could wear the same clothes, it doesn't matter, a little cold, cold,
what's the thing, you just gotta go right in, okay, I'm just going in, that feels good,
ah, oh, butyl berry do one of these, I think so, ah, right there, that feels good, oh, you know,
something about cold water, that just really gets into your, gets into your head, it opens up your
blood vessels, or closes them, I don't know, either one of those two things, it does one of them,
all right, what happened, you feel like I was still alive, but something happened there,
I feel like, that was a long day at work, that was really weird, I kind of like just,
it felt like I stopped, my head, it was like a split second, my head felt like it was,
like my head froze, but it was only like for a second, I don't know, but where's the ladder,
what, I'm actually having fun though, I'm having a fun time, what happened to the ladder,
where's the, where's the ladder, um, where's the ladder, I have to get out of the pool,
I don't want to be in here all day, I've got shit to do, help, somebody help me, somebody help me,
hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, come back, come back, help, help, help, help, help, get in the pool,
get in the pool, that's a police officer, get in the pool and help me, get in the pool,
get in the pool, there's someone in the pool that needs help, there's, I think they took the
ladder over there, fucking idiot, AI piece of shit, hey, hey, don't eat anything,
don't eat anything, what's he doing, is he going, is he in my bathroom,
no, still drinking beer, I can tell, that's all people do in my house is drink beer out of the
fridge, put the ladder back, put the ladder back, you can put the ladder back if you want,
you should put the ladder back, I want to get out of the pool, I want to get out of the pool,
I want to get out of the pool, put the ladder back,
well, well, has someone gone for a little swim without his floaties,
it's me, your old friend, death, who puts the fun in funeral, come on, it's time,
oh, yes, it's time for the midnight train to the long farewell, no, no, what,
you killed me, why did you take the ladder out, that's a, it's a funny joke, isn't it,
until it's dead, are you blaming someone else when you decided to get in without a life jacket,
oh, you're right, calm down, okay, am I dead, am I dead now, oh, you're very, very dead,
oh, wait a minute, I could have just gone like this, oh, unfortunately, no gives these backsies,
have you made all of your preparations, I have, and I just,
you look wonderful today, can I just tell you that, the scythe, the uniform, something about
the way, the mysterious, the dark, mysterious stranger, you know, usually when people flirt
with death, it's something simpler like blowfish sushi, right, this is a bit complicated, are you,
do you mean it when you say that, or are you saying that because you saw me,
I mean, I mean it, I do, I think that I, would you like to come inside, maybe,
do we have to go immediately, or can we have a drink, can we hang out, you know,
this is kind of, listen, I have a hot dog eating contest, and I've got three souls to take in about
20 minutes, okay, it's unconventional, but this once, I'll allow it, okay, great, come on in,
I feel, is that normal, should I be doing that, that is normal,
usually it's a bit more crying, screaming, I've been crying, it feels like for fucking three days,
that's all right, time to see your uncle Ted, isn't that fun, after all, I didn't even know
that, I thought he was dead, like, I've already got a spot picked out for you, okay, well, I do,
I really do think you're a very, very, very handsome death, oh, stop, stop, you don't mean
that, I do, I do mean it, come on in here, why is he in here, hey, I just want to let you know,
it's probably, but thanks for the help, by the way, you did a great job, by the way,
officer of the law, of the court, keep doing as best as you can,
making, making good friends in the neighborhood, are we, yes, we are making very good friends in
the neighborhood, if you're like, no, we can't, that's, that's a, there's a garage back there,
sorry, I don't want you to see my garage, it's full of filth, are you trying to waste my time,
filthy thing, come on up here, into my, into my room, death, I'll show you my poster, I got some
pretty cool posters, oh, watch your step, though, wow, little dark back here, it is kind of dark,
yeah, I got to get some lighting, I just moved in, I just moved in about, today, yesterday,
actually, boy, quick turnaround, huh, yeah, it's great, you're right, you can tell I'm going to
be making more than one visit here, an entire stairwell and no lights, I'm death, of course,
he doesn't even feel pain, he's death, what do you think about this room, you like it,
it's a little minimalist, well, it's gonna be upgraded, it's gonna be upgraded really soon,
probably in the near future, interesting decor choice, yes, if you'd like to look at the bedroom,
it's up here, I can give you a full tour, that's a work in progress, it's a work in progress,
yes, so in here, this is, I've got two beds for fun, I don't know, they decided to give it to me,
so what was it, what was your last, where were you before this, right before this,
yeah, like right before you came in and got me, carnival ride accident Kentucky,
one of those small card roller coasters, they tried to fit four people into one,
you know how it goes, that's unfortunate, two people choked on churros,
wait, in the audience, oh yes, interesting, dead right away, I feel like you've got a lot
of places to be, oh, I've got appointments all day, so no days off for death, how many people die a
day, how many people die a day, that's classified, okay, it's probably, is it, okay, I'm gonna give
you a number, is it more or less than a hundred thousand, yes, okay, it is more or less than that
number, okay, so outside, you can see we've got a pretty good view, a beautiful view of the outside,
oh, lovely, yeah, it's pretty nice, are all those butterflies common in this area,
they're actually huge, I don't know, but you can make yourself comfortable, I mean,
if you want a snack or something, there's plenty of room to hang out if you want to, snack, I'm
actually, I mean, I'm just trying to, when do we go to the other side, oh, very soon, very soon,
very soon, okay, well, I'm, it's the what scene, it's the what scene, it's the, it's the, you said
a W word, W word, oh, okay, you got, death, I don't know how you feel about potentially,
have you heard the word, word woohoo before, woohoo, you and I are potentially on a date here,
I can't say that woohoo is a part of my normal vocabulary as death, not a lot of woohoo in the
underworld, it's more like, generally speaking, oh, so would you like to spend an evening together,
would you still respect me if I said yes, absolutely, I guess we're doing this, shall we,
shall we, allow me, I'm going to put the robot, I'm going to show you the time
of your life, okay, that sounds good to me, so how is this going to work, you're not going to,
do I like die, am I dead, I'm going to tell you right now, it's something you'll never forget,
okay, all right, I'm into this too, death, you know, I've been known to go for at least
two to three minutes, wow, record breaker, this is nice, this is nice,
come on, dude,
that was wonderful, somebody's here, stay up here, stay up here, don't make yourself a known,
I can't go back to bed, I can't, just get under there, get under there, stay under there,
okay, just cover yourself up, quiet, quiet, quiet, just be quiet, just cover yourself,
I'm in, ah, bedroom, who is it, Jerma, I'm in the bedroom, oh, um, I guess, okay,
you come up, it's through the hallway, hey, hey, Amelia, sorry, what, Amelia, how are you,
who is that, that's just a bunch of pillows, that's just a bunch of pillows, it's a collection of
moving sentient pillows, no, it's nobody, this is a standing pillow now, no, am I meant to believe
because I'm a stupid maid that this is a sentient pillow that's dead, no, no, no, no, no, of course,
oh, he's got a side, what are you doing about that, he's got a side, he's got your side, why,
did you stand me up on our date and now this, you have, look, you have no idea, my life has been an
absolute train wreck, people come to the house, organ players, I've had like police here three
times, a police officer was here like an hour ago just drinking on my couch, this sounds really tough
for you that someone was drinking on your couch, no, you don't understand, it wasn't even my decision,
it was easy for me to get stood up and I can't believe this, you can take this, you can take him,
you shitter, no, no, I hope it was Amelia, just wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, no, no,
you missed your chance, you don't know how high I can fly, how high, listen, Amelia, this has been
great, it's just a little tense for me, I've got that hot dog eating contest, listen, I'm just gonna
go, you don't call me, I'll call you, okay, just gotta go, wish I could talk, have to go,
so nice, I actually don't want you to call me, I want you to lose my number because I don't want
to hear from you because that means a bad thing, oh don't worry, I'll come calling, you just won't
know when, Jesus, um, I got my life back, I feel like, I feel like I've had a big life but I gotta,
hold on, I need to, Amelia, god damn it, I didn't want to stand anybody up, it's not even my decision
if I stand somebody up or not, did you understand? It's not my choice if somebody's,
Amelia, Amelia, just wait, I, Amelia, hold on, it takes 30 seconds to come down the stairs,
Amelia, oh no, Amelia, crap, oh crap, Amelia, oh, that was a voice crack and it was bad,
that was the worst one I've ever done, what a disaster, what a day, oh right, I turned it off,
right, that's not, I didn't want that to happen, oh damn, what a wild day, well, here's some,
something for you guys, if you kill me, you need to be ready for the consequences,
catch butterflies, I don't even know, I threw it at somebody, is he all right, can I get it from,
can I get it from his, can you give me the thing that I threw at the crew member,
yeah, just toss it over here, yeah, thank you, thanks, appreciate it, catch butterflies,
I'm falling full, I can't get out of there, did I get any, I don't even know, I don't like everything,
I don't know what they look like, I'm so tired, please send me to bed, thank you, oh, it's so far
away, it's so far away, it's so far away, why do I have such a big house, it's too far away,
I can get there, I can get there, let's go upstairs, okay, two, three, four, I can't,
oh, oh, that's been digging into my neck, oh, it's been digging into my neck the whole night,
one of these staircase things, oh, there's this like deep purple blood here,
what is that, why is it like purple blood, oh, my glass is on all night,
ow, I'm gonna have this permanent just kink in my neck, and remember, Germanite85.com,
if you want to get your visit, I don't even care, I don't even want it, I'm gonna, I want it,
you can decide for yourself if you want to go to Germanite85.com and get merchandise,
especially specifically for this show, I feel awful, I just feel like this sucks, oh, yes, oh,
it's a dachshund, oh, it's Otto, it's an Otto, oh, and it's my ladybug friend from the first,
from two weeks ago, I'm gonna say first stream, because then we're gonna do continuity,
oh, I love them, I actually love them, and wait, is this one of those things I can go like this,
what, holy shit, get this on fucking camcorder, you kidding me, are you kidding me,
are you kidding me, I love them, they're fantastic, oh, they're so cool, they're gonna go
in my bed, they're gonna go in my bed, in my bed, I don't want to go too far,
wait, this one, wait, look at this, it's a magic trick for you, oh, oh, I'm starting to feel that
up here in the throat, I have to pee so bad, I'm going to pee with or without the rub,
I'm just, look, I'm just saying, I'm just saying, hot dog, I'm just saying, fine,
if it allows me to go to the bathroom, I'll put it on, hold on, let me go down the stairs,
I'll put it on, it'll be on by the time you see me next, I promise,
uh-huh, put the robe on, get heat stroke, we want robe or no bathroom, wrong door,
this is the one I'm supposed to go in, okay, who is calling me, who is calling my phone,
hey, this is Jason again calling from dealer warranty services licensed representatives
of car extended vehicle purchase points LLC calling, looks like you've been dodging a couple
of my phone calls, we sent you a bunch of things in the mail, a couple emails, a couple fax machines,
even got your grandma in on the thing, but for some reason you just don't seem to want to get
back to me about your vehicle's extended warranty, are you trying to drive on safety, do you want
your car to explode, at this point I'm starting to, I'm starting to be a little concerned,
that's enough of that, you know phone calls are starting to become like email, have you noticed
that, when was the last time you answered the telephone, if mom wasn't the contact that came
up, I have not answered my actual cell phone unless mom is on the goddamn fucking thing,
okay, it's becoming spam email now, nobody answers their phone, nobody checks their email,
how do we communicate with anybody, I wasn't done, I wasn't done, hold on,
I'm gonna need a little more than that, I'm gonna need a little bit more than that,
I'm gonna need a little bit more than that,
okay,
yes,
show up, my voice is fucked, this is from screaming for three straight days, show up,
get those bars up, otherwise I'm gonna be in trouble,
oh hey, glasses, reddit, 10,000, upload,
and you know the pose we're doing, fooled you, fooled you, I'm hungry, very hungry,
exceptional, I gotta clean this up, what happened here,
look at this, what a mess, this looks awesome, awesome, looks awful, make food,
but I have to have the robot to make food, well can't we just say who cares,
and I can just do whatever I want, can I break away from their control at some point, okay,
sure, put the robot, this is so hot with this on, can I go like this, no, no, it's just a snuggie,
oh yes, snuggie, oh my mic, I gotta be, hold on, I'll go like this, I feel like this is like a
fashion trend right now, right, is it like a dress that people wear that looks like this,
with like a halter top and it's like this, right, don't you think that'd be huge,
and it goes into a dress, I think I found, look, if you're a designer and you make this,
I want 10%, it goes around all the way back, yeah, all right, food, making food is just annoying and
I'm not doing it, it's been three days, so we're just eating a cookie, not until I,
I'm not dealing with this shit until I eat, we're here on behalf of the king, on what king,
King Elton McCartney, the conqueror of the fifth, as you are new to these lands,
you must read the scroll, I need to read the scroll, do we expect you to pledge fealty
to the king, if not there will be dire consequences, I don't know what drugs are
going around this neighborhood, but it's something hard, pledges fealty, or you'll be severed,
so you're gonna, you're gonna kill me if I don't pledge fealty, what's fealty, pledge fealty to
the king for 500 shillings, 500 shillings, is that money, the youngest king Agatha,
huh, she needs braces, you know enough, let's do that, okay, wait, well just say that one more
time, my daughter needs braces, I've been on this job for a fucking long dude, okay, you know,
it's my fourth appointment, I'm gonna cut your break, who sent you here though, like it was like
a joke or something, no I'm here on behalf of the king, and the thing is if you don't pay,
I gotta sever your head, I don't know if you ever used one of these, it's kind of dull, it takes a
little bit of time, that hurt actually, I've done three today, I'm fucking tired bro, just pay me
like 500 shillings, that's like, you know, 20, 21, 200 bucks, you look like shit, you're not even that big,
I can literally cut your fucking head off right now, and I don't want to, my arm's exhausted,
got a torn rotator cuff, I know, but you look like shit, and I fucking, I could probably beat you up,
I could probably punch you in the face and kill you, loser, loser, that poked me in the eye,
you're most really gonna do this, can you just cut me a fucking, how much money do you need?
I told you it's five bucks shillings, who is this, who is this guy, don't worry about that,
it's not your concern, are you gonna pay or not, look, if you want 500 bucks from me,
then I'm gonna have to hear a goddamn song from this motherfucker right here,
you want 500, you're not in a position to decide if, who play it, the flute if, I want to hear a
song, don't it end everybody else, my music sucks, you both suck, you're both idiots,
you both, you both, you both like probably, you probably both stupid, you probably fucking have a
30 IQ, very well, all right, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, I was told to do that,
somebody said do that, who, there's no one here, yes there is, they're up in the sky, I see if
no one is, play, just tell him to play again, okay, 500, 500, will 500 get you to leave,
okay, get some music, get some music before I look like an idiot, is it decided, yes take 500 and
leave, then we're in an alliance, we're in an alliance, you're not gonna hurt me, are you,
yeah, let's celebrate, what are you doing, you know, you can't just take beers out of the fridge,
what is it, what, this neighborhood, I swear to god, everybody is on fucking hard drugs,
what are you doing, I toasted the king, no, there's nothing, there's nothing left, this time next
year, yes, this time, watch the phone, there's nothing left in here, he drank it all, he's just
the guy that comes in, he's the guy that comes in and drinks a beer really fast, that's his thing,
that's his thing that he does, hey, do you know a guy that can drink beer real fast,
ah, yeah, yeah, I know a guy that can drink beer real fast, this thing is gross, I'm putting this
in the sink, and you left my door open, pledge fealty to the king, well I hope your daughter got
the braces, unbelievable, they have a cop here, I think the cop is on drugs too, literally nobody
here is, nobody here is sober, okay, there's like a bunch of people doing drugs, I'm the only sober
one in this whole neighborhood, well that's not actually accurate because I've had like three of
those, can I get the bread off the ground at least, what is the king doing here, why is there like a
flute player, hey, do you know a guy that can drink beer real fast, what is this, oh, he left it,
I'm watching some TV, I'm gonna put the tube on, all right, what do we got on TV, don't show
the TV yet, don't show the TV yet, don't show the TV yet, I wouldn't show the television yet,
I think I need to hit the input button to get this to the right channel,
okay, I gotta make sure, look, I just got it installed the other day,
all right, what's on TV, let's get ourselves on, that's a lot of feedback from a microphone,
what we got, what's on TV, what's on TV, channel change on here, turn it on, it's a weird channel,
you guys can call 1-800-SEXYMAD, that's S-E-X-Y-M-A-D, we ran out of numbers,
to get my service, it costs $2,000 per cleaning, or $2,500 if you want me to wear cat ears,
or $150 if you're a giant piece of shit named Jerma, change the channel, change the channel,
I don't want to say that, change the channel, what's this?
Now future recent events will also be roaming the neighbourhoods and helping out those who are in need,
when we replace homes, because we've heard there's been a lot of un-things happening,
fires and drowning, well then there's this main incident, everything that could just be-
Change the channel, change the channel, change the channel, change the channel,
giant piece of shit, he's a big poopy, I hate him, I hate him, I hate him, I hate him,
change channel, change channel, nothing on this one, there's nothing on this station,
there's nothing on this station, or are they just doing dead air on this station,
change channel, I gotta go, this thing's messed up, there it is, oh back to-
So please make sure you give us your credit card numbers-
All right get that off, I don't want that fucking TV, TV off!
He's screaming, he's screaming, man TV is weird out here,
there seems to be only two or three stations, it must be an antenna, I- what happened to this?
What is that? There's three channels on that TV, I don't even want to pick it up, and I'm not
touching that because there's poopoo on it, oh my god there's like beer everywhere, this is actually
kind of a disaster, this is gonna get actually cleaned, oh interesting, here's the beer stein,
whatever you want to call this, let's rinse it out, yuck, disgusting, I'm going up into the bed,
I want to sit down, there's just a soda, there's a non-descript soda over there,
I want to check out the DIY room, because what does that mean? DIY room, do it yourself, DIY,
I don't want to stream right now, I've got a lot going on, how am I gonna stream on Twitch?
Um okay, where's the mouse and keyboard, where's the key, okay there's the mouse,
am I still banned on Twitch? I don't think so, all right starting the stream, I gotta apologize to
everybody, let me go live, it's been like three, it's been like four or five days since I was,
I got banned like twice, let me, I gotta apologize, make sure I look okay, I have to look like,
I gotta look hot in this video right, because that's what matters, not the apology,
I gotta make sure I look good, okay let's go live, and live, hey what's up everybody,
Jerma985 here, I know for the last couple of weeks I've been live um only a few times,
and it's been for only like two or three minutes, and then I go BRB, I'll be right back, hey everybody
it's Jerma985 here, I just want to get some good comfortable clothes for this stream,
because you know it's important stuff we're talking about here, I have to apologize real quick
that I've been I've been I've been away, and I've been not good to you, and you may have seen some
things on the stream, me sleeping, you may have seen me shitting on stream a few times and going
to the bathroom on stream, but I want to say I don't condone going to the bathroom on stream,
I find it disgusting and repulsive, and that I find that anybody that would do that would be
completely out of their mind, I don't condone it, and it's not me, it's me from a while ago,
it's a past me, I just want to say that I'm sorry about my past me that would have actually gone to
the bathroom on stream, and that would have gone BRB and gone to sleep, that's not me,
that's not me, I would I mean that's not me as of a week ago, that's not me, I'm a new person,
I mean it was a week ago, it was a week ago, but it's not me, that's not who I am,
I also want to say very very much sorry to Al Migraine, to Amelia, what? I want to say sorry
to Amelia, because they didn't deserve that kind of treatment, and I really feel like that they the
that I really just want to say sorry to them, they saw me having sex with death in my bed,
and I just want to say that that's not me, that's not me, that's not who I am, I don't have sex
with like three different people and like lie to everybody as of a week ago, it was three days ago,
but that's not me, I'm not that's not who I am, I woohooed him, we can't say that word,
or can we? I woohooed, woohooed, it's not the same, it's not the same thing chat,
woohoo is a different term, although I just really screwed up and said something else,
woohoo is different, it's different, we woohooed, we both said woohoo, we had a great time,
and look I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm apologizing for that, let me apologize for the apology too,
I'm very sorry about that apology, how I said something else that wasn't what we did,
we were upstairs, we rolled around, we went oh woohoo, and that's it, that's all that happened,
that's, so I'm sorry, I'm really sorry for apologizing for the apology, this time I mean it,
I know you might, some of you might think I'm like a shitty person, but I don't care, you paid me a
lot of money, so I don't care, but like you know, I'm just gonna do this to make sure everybody's
happy about it, I'm sure everybody's happy about that, I'm sorry that I said the S word,
the S word, S-E-I, I can't even say it, oh it's not me, sorry I'm not that person,
S-E-I, oh I can't say it, you know what I mean, like that's not me from yesterday,
from when I went to sleep that time, I can't even say that word, oh I can't even say it anymore,
it's disgusting to me, but yeah I'm really sorry about that, and what, I've been permanently banned
from Twitch, permanently, indefinitely, but indefinite means like, no, I'll just record
an apology video and then I'll send it to Twitch, I gotta record an apology video, hey get the OBS
out, get over here, no not with a toilet, I'm gonna be stupid, don't be dumb, oh yeah sorry
Twitch, please appeal the ban in front of a toilet, pink is, pink background's fine,
hey Twitch, it's me Jerma here, I just wanted to appeal the ban that I had,
I was on a lot of drugs and I didn't mean any of those things, no, delete that, here we go, hey,
delete it again, start over, hey Twitch, it's me Jerma985 here, just want to make sure I check
in with you and see that I got a permanent, indefinite kind of ban, what you saw the last
few days, it's been kind of crazy, a gladiator came in and was like threatening to kill me,
and I'm gonna start over again, again, one more time, make sure it looks taller and bigger because
the minion will be able to present and get the robe off too, hey Twitch, it's me Jerma985 here,
just wanted to give you a quick update of what happened over the last few days and appeal the
ban, I was attacked by a bear a couple times, I don't care, whatever, fuck it, I'm banned forever,
don't care, whatever idea, Twitch I got hacked and somebody posted on my behalf and it wasn't
even me, so I'm sorry about it, send that email, send, send, I'm gonna take a shower,
what am I gonna do about money, what am I gonna do, why is the water not working, fuck,
how am I gonna get paid, oh, what am I supposed to do, I brush my teeth in the shower
every day, that was a quick shower, what was that, you know the move, you know the move,
my arm still hurts from the window, from Twitch, it's not even funny, it's not even funny,
I want to watch TV, that sounds like a plan to me,
what's on TV today, journal on, and good afternoon residents of dollhouse, we have an emergency
announcement, there has been a gorilla reported on the loose, after speaking with the gorilla,
we did get some information by the motive of his escape, after dispute with his mother about not
liking his girlfriend, he has decided to escape his enclosure, here we have Randy, our specialist
in the area on gorillas and bears, Randy do you have any advice to offer citizens if they
encounter this gorilla, well the first thing you have to remember is you're dealing with a wild
animal, you're dealing with heartache, so first thing you need to do is make sure that if you are
going to approach these animals, make sure you take somebody slower than you, because you want
to be able to outrun them in case you get attacked by that animal, the gorilla, second of all,
don't forget to play dead, because then you'll know what it's like when they kill you,
and then I would advise against pepper spray, bears love the taste of pepper on human flesh,
I would suggest rubbing your body with steamed broccoli before going out after these animals,
wonderful thank you so much Randy, is there anything else you would like to say, did you get
any more information behind the motive from this gorilla, no really, just the whole conversation
was it was just bananas really, and I it's just crazy, I'm not okay okay, what we're gonna do,
that was fantastic, that was a great segue, tv has been turned off, a gorilla on the loose,
okay, I don't have broccoli, I don't have whatever else it was, yeah really,
right after the segment on television, I want to move, I want to move, I don't want to live
here anymore, why does it feel like everything is coming to get me, and there are my glasses,
that was loud, there's my glasses, everybody's coming, everybody's trying to kill me in this
town, how could you possibly live here for more than a week, what the fuck, I'm not going out
there, you saw what happened last time, I'm not going out there again to get attacked,
I'm gonna call a bear, call a bear, what does that even mean, call bear, call bear, I don't have a
bear's phone number, do I, I guess I do, my hand is doing it, hello, I'd like to, I'd like to call
the bear, a bear service to come attack, to help me, I guess, this is real service, okay, thank you,
how much does it cost, that's too much money, but all right, god damn it, god, send him, send him it,
what the fuck, hey, hey, it's a gorilla in my yard, it's a gorilla in my, shit,
did somebody just say red rum, are we all right, oh that's a quite a mess out here, nobody here,
okay, a bear, how much does that cost, a bear service, that was the bear that was here before,
but he was, he was friendly this time, what does that cost, I'm, the maid's gonna have to, I know
Amelia, I, Amelia, I'm still paying for your service, so that doesn't mean you don't come
anymore, 250 dollars for a bear, was it 2500 or 250, I was gonna say that's pretty cheap if it was
2500, good thing it was an extra zero, get this back over here, where it belongs please, this sucks,
this actually sucks, it sucks living here, I fucking hate living here, I actually don't like
being here, it's a nice house, but what is this neighborhood, bears, gorillas, people that aren't
drugs just attacking you, we're like church groups that come into your house and just don't even
knock, the police just sit on your couch and drink sodas and stuff, people drink beer out of my fridge,
mess, not today, not today, tomorrow, tomorrow, but tomorrow, why can't you just do tomorrow,
showed up like this, I'm gonna look, people are gonna be happy about it, hello, I'm going to work,
fine, just wait, I'm coming, that looks like a full car today, do I have to sit in the middle,
no, I don't want to sit in the middle, what, fine, just move, that was a long day,
this is because I sit in the middle because I'm the smallest one, I know I always put it up for grabs
and I always say I'll do it, but that doesn't mean I want to, maybe like next time I can get in the
front, like just once, just one time I sit in the front seat, sit in the middle, sucks, I know I'm
like the smallest guy, but whatever, whatever, whatever works, thank you, see you on Saturday,
if you get a fucking invite,
was that a, was that like a fun beep or was that like a you're mad beep, I can't tell,
you do that all the time, you do that like every day,
I don't know if that's like a you're making like making me look like an idiot,
hi Edna, how are you, hi, hello, good day to you, good day, how are you, I'm doing well,
world treating you treating you well, very good sweetheart, it's a strange world out there,
okay, see you later, okay, a lot of people in this neighborhood,
I gotta take this off, I'm gonna get more comfortable, but oh my brain, my brain,
I need to probably play a quickie keyboard, did that cost money, I mean, the maid has not been here,
I don't know where the maid has been, but look, I know we have like an issue, but like it,
you're still a maid, I pay for a service, was the maid here, was the maid in the house,
did Amelia take these, that's uncle Ted's stuff, oh okay, so you were here, oh I get it, I get it,
oh I'm mad, because she, because you woohooed with death, so I'm gonna take Ted's prize possession,
okay, real funny, we'll see if you come back again, I'll make sure I get you, I'll get you
right in the eye, I'll look you right in the eye, I'll tell you get out of here and you're fired,
unbelievable, unbelievable, it was, that's money, I pay for a service regardless of if we have a
problem, it's unbelievable, take things from my goddamn house, because like what, because we had
a problem, we weren't even, we weren't even like, hold on, here's the worst part about this, but I'm
not even, we weren't even, we weren't even like doing anything, we would like, we had a date that
was planned, one date planned, I need to, I'm gonna get, can I dust my fingerprints, hold on a second,
we had one date planned, I have to pee bad, I'm starving and I'm tired, this felt right today like
this, looks good, I'm hungry too, flush, don't just not flush, come on, what is this,
I still have to record the apology video, for the apology video, for the apology video,
for the apology, wait, hold on, did you take anything else, you took Ted's spoons, did you
take Ted's furniture too, I'm hungry, nothing missing from this room, Amelia, give me a break,
give me a break, all right, let's make some food, then hopefully I feel a little bit better, oh
what, oh my god, a coffee maker, I didn't even see this, oh my god, I love coffee,
that's perfect in the mornings, that's perfect, thank you, it's a little dirty in there, it's a
little dirty, that's extra dirty, but oh coffee, all right, food, that's good, that's good, that's a
good baked roasted cookie, anything in here, it's in here, why are there almonds in here,
look at this, there's a shitload of like pecans in here, I'm tired, I'm very tired and I'm not
having a good time at all, contrary to popular belief of me you have laughing, make the bed,
okay, I'll eat the rest of that cookie later, I'll eat these cookies, I'm like a six-year-old,
I want chicken tenders, french fries and cookies, can you even live off of pecan sandies, how long,
what, somebody look this up, when do you die, at what point after eating just pecan sandies,
I'm gonna make my bed, it's just like sugar, bread and like flour, can you live off of flour,
I think you can live off flour for at least a week, I hope so, sorry, I took a multi-vitamin,
you just don't see it, you want one of these, you want one of these, you want one of these,
too bad they're sold out, I actually think they are, German at 85.com, make the bed, hi, we were
just doing my in my bedroom workout, well, I mean, you know, you left your front door unlocked, so
we were just, I have a very, very, very important quick question, yes, do you both have a house,
I have a condo, it's my mom's condo, it's just a temporary thing, how much, how much room is in
the condo, it's a one bedroom, okay, small, about the size of a phone booth, do you have a house,
condo, rent, anything, rent, rental, Gladys, I think it might be time, I'm feeling a little overheated,
how long have you been in here, you know, it's, I never really time my workouts,
when my body says it's done, I know it's done, but you have to do it in somebody,
somebody's bedroom in the neighborhood, wherever there's free space, we figured you're new to the
neighborhood, we can get you into the, remember the 60 mile run, remember we're gonna, well,
I don't want you to leave, oh, I don't want you to leave, in fact, I want you to fucking,
show me some workouts, you'd like to do some workouts, I would love to do some workouts,
well, someone's had a change of attitude, okay, this is a nice shirt too, oh, you like that,
you say sweating, sweating, you know why, because the secret's in the sweat, and I think that is
very sexy, if I can be honest with you, oh, well, that's, that is sexy, and awesome, and I am,
I'm very, I'm very much into it, oh, well, it's a little, a little forward, I think, I think,
I think you're wonderful, listen, someone's got a silver tongue, okay, so here's the first
exercise, glattis, try to keep up this time, okay, just perfect, hands up, we've got spirit
fingers, okay, spirit fingers, I'm really tired, so we're gonna do something light, okay, something
light, okay, we're screwing in the light bulbs, screwing in the light bulbs, we're screwing in,
we're screwing in, we're screwing in the light bulbs, I find you very, very, very handsome and
attractive, oh, that's not part of the workout, but that's just gonna pretend that, that just
didn't happen, okay, so now what we're doing is we're gonna do the sprinkler, okay, follow me,
it goes, no, I don't want to do the sprinkler, hey, hey, I want to hear a better hey, hey, hey,
yeah, that's a bit better, that's a bit better, now here's, oh, like that game Dark Souls, that
game Dark Souls, let's just, we'll do it again, okay, all right, here's the next one, okay,
yeah, there's something stuck in the fax machine, there's something stuck in the fax machine,
oh, there's something stuck in the fax machine, get out of there,
something stuck in the fax machine, something stuck in the fax machine,
you all right, you're gonna be okay, screw you dad, hey, would you look at the time,
I think it's bedtime, I think it's time for me to go to bed right now, okay, come on, Gladys,
close that door, Gladys, oh, I heard, I heard something last night, oh, that was a very weird
dream, oh, it's, it's Otto, wait, hold on, there was an explosion last night, it sounded like a bomb
went off, I don't know what it was, I mean, something just followed me, followed me through
here, it smelled, what was that, is it a gas line, holy shit, that's not me, is it, oh my god,
I think it is, you want one of these, sold out, what is this, oh, cabinets, the stool's in here,
and I'm not gonna show this, because I know, I know what you're gonna do,
I'm not gonna show it, because I know the audio guy, I know what they're gonna do,
in fact, audio guy, I don't want you to play the sound that you, that you want to play,
play something else, oh, there's a poop emoji in there, okay, what else is in here,
these are so heavy, oh, the stool, wow, we had a lot of these, and a smiley balloon,
oh, I kind of don't, oh, that's sad, that's really sad, nice cabinets, what a waste of money,
you could have bought literally anything else, what am I doing, decorate, decorate this room,
let me first of all do this, member of Jeremiah5.com, if you want some merchandise from this stream,
it's all sold out, but who cares, decorate, it's probably actually a pretty good time to do this
room, I think so, we'll do this, I don't like this being open, I don't like that,
I don't like that one, I like this one, I like that being open, this fell, get this out of the way,
this is the DIY room, and if you don't know what a DIY room is, do it yourself,
so we're gonna be you and I, of course, gonna be painting these rooms, maybe, pick a good color,
I hope you do, hey, want to see something crazy, I command this to go into the bathroom,
did it go into the bathroom, it did, I have magical powers, all right, let's move this,
I get this out of the way, this is so fucking heavy, my god, what a waste of fucking money,
okay, that's not gonna work, that's not gonna work, nothing else is gonna,
what do you have back here for me, what do you have, what the fuck, what, why,
I can't even move these, they're like in 10 pieces, okay, I don't, get all this out of the way,
out of the way, out, get this out of the way, open the door, so I can see what I'm doing, good,
all right, what do I want to do, number one thing I want to do in the DIY room,
I think we take out one of these walls, yep, this is a sledge hammer,
what do we got here, all right, this is good, this is a saw, I'm thinking right here, I think so,
what do you think, ready to get some wall, I think so, right there, I want an open bedroom
concept for my VR room, can't really, what happened, what, why does it not work, it's plugged in,
what the fuck, the saw is not working anymore, what happened, I think there's an electrical
problem, the saw doesn't work, the saw doesn't work, oh shit, that scared the shit out of me,
I can't get the saw to work, I'll try to figure it out, let me see if I can get this to work,
somehow, I probably lead to the fuse box, probably, that's probably what's going on,
where does this go, this goes somewhere, it's taped down over here, but
why would it stop working, I plugged it into the base downstairs, I have like a whole unit
that's down there, there's like four or five extension cords that go out, I don't know,
I don't get it, what is going on, what is going on, what the heck is this, who are you, I'm your
neighbor, I'm Jim Matthew, I live next door, what are you doing, what are you doing my electricity,
I plugged this in downstairs, my unit downstairs, what are you doing, no way, that thing's coming
straight from my house, you can follow it down the street, listen, when I grew up, that's called
thievery, I don't know what you think that is, well, I saw a place to plug it in, I plugged it in,
I didn't know if it was yours or not, you didn't check first, no, I mean, electricity plugs are
just, I can just use them, what is this place, this is your plug, yes, my plug, that's okay,
which are you, 9-8-0, 9-8-2, what are you, yeah, 9-8-0, 9-8-0, I live down past Edna,
oh cool, yeah, you met Ludwig, yeah, it's crazy, this many people live here,
it's weird, dollhouse lane, listen, I'm gonna need that back, I'm working on a project up here,
working on a project, yeah, it looks like it, you have no clue what you're doing, do you,
I don't really, I mean, that is not the right tool for the job, I gotta tell you that,
I tell you that much, that's not the right tool for the job, that's for sure, okay, well,
this is more confusing than a fart in a fan factory up here, all right, well, excuse me, Jeb,
oh lord, hey listen, I tell you what, that's your electricity, yeah, electricity, so I've been,
haven't been taking it from you, have I, I mean, we'll have to see, my bill has been exceptionally
high, but I thought, how high has your bill been, I mean, a couple extra hundred, a couple extra
per month, listen, my son, he's been doing some weird things on the computer, I figured
there's something like that, but you never know, okay, all right, Jeb, oh lord, so, I tell you what,
you keeping those, you keeping these, no, so these, these appeared last night, I don't even
know where they're from, okay, I mean, because I don't mind, maybe just to pay for the electricity,
I can bring them back to my place, well, I don't actually owe you any money, considering that,
well, the electricity, I mean, the electricity's mine, that's the thing, do you know how, I tried
to get this to work, the saw doesn't work, okay, the saw doesn't work, okay, basic safety, yeah,
yeah, yeah, that's a good idea, let me show you a couple things, okay, let me show you, my daddy
taught me this, okay, he taught me two things, NASCAR and how to fix stuff, well, you're not,
you know this stuff, exactly, exactly, holy smokes, okay, the two are pretty synonymous, by the way,
so what, what, what can you tell, what, what, what, what should we do in this room,
uh, okay, well, are you, are you like a handy guy, oh, for sure, yeah, absolutely, absolutely,
I mean, I would, I would start for sure, you got to get some paint up on the walls, okay,
probably move some stuff around, it's pretty dirty, tripping hazard, interesting, do you,
do you know this guy, he looks a little, I've never seen him before in my life,
no idea, that one guy's lovely though, I've seen him, let me see if I can see who this is,
the, is that you, Kiteboga, Kiteboga, whatever, I don't know, I don't know if you've ever heard
of those people, German985.com, they're all sold out, okay, I mean, yeah, it seems like you have
literally no idea what you're doing, what, what do you, would you think we should start with
painting, is that what you think, well, I mean, the first thing we're gonna have to do is paint,
absolutely, okay, have you dusted the walls yet, uh, I've, I've pre-dusted, have you checked for
prints, I've checked for all, yes, yeah, because, well, you never know, did you build this house
yourself or you move in, because you never know if it's like a crime scene or something,
I, I, I woke up one day and I had a sling on my arm and I walked over here and this was just here,
so, I just figured it was mine, a sling on your arm, yeah, I got a broken arm and I, I went through
a window, uh, a few weeks ago, um, you went through a window, were you here when the fire happened,
were you, you, I heard, I heard some siren, actually, I think I called the fire department,
is that you, I think I did, thank God for you, because I, I shattered my arm going through the
window, but I'm fine, though, I'm all right, you mind if I, uh, let me show you something here,
okay, so you got the stools, how about pink, you got the stools, does pink work for you,
pink, I mean, I don't think it'll look good, but that's what you want, if that's what you want,
what wall do you think I should do for pink, what do you think, what wall, yeah, what do you,
what do you even do, what are you even doing in here, is this like your, well, this is gonna be
my VR room, I wanna build a jump around in virtual reality, VR, what on earth is that,
virtual reality, virtual, you're getting a headset now, it's gonna be my VR room, I swear,
you kids have no clue what's going on, virtual reality, you called it, what is that,
by the way, I know you probably smelled gas coming up here, gas, like gasoline, it's me,
I just wanna make sure you're aware of that, no, my, my smell ain't that great, but,
gasoline, so you wanna paint over all pink, I wanna paint pink, virtual reality,
it's not quite sure what wall we're doing pink at the moment, okay, I mean, what about,
you got this wall here, that's nice, this pretty sturdy wall, back wall, all right,
how about we do pink, I need a tool to open this, have you tested these walls for stability,
oh good lord, sorry, I just like to do that, okay, let me get this paint open, you have no,
you have no clue what you're doing, do you know how to open paint, I've opened paint, I feel like
it's a tuna can, I've opened paint, I've opened tuna, you did both, I sure have, you live in the
United States, we had tuna sandwiches every day when we were kids, okay, pink paint for virtual
reality, why is that, I just wanna make sure I wear this, I would probably take off my shoes,
if you don't want them to be covered in paint, you want me to take, so let me get this straight,
you steal my electricity, this is not stirred, by the way, how do I stir this, listen, sit back
and relax, this stuff's easy, okay, it's all intuitive, it's all in your head, okay, you know
what you're talking about, Steve, I don't even know your name, Jeb, Jeb, all right, let's get that pink
up there, are you a painter, of course I am, okay, good, that looks pretty good, you like that, yeah,
so how long you lived here for, oh, you can't even get on my floor, I'm sorry about that, okay,
listen, I told you I know how to paint, I didn't tell you, I knew how to be
cleanly, all right, so we just dump it in here, yeah, dump it, are you a handy person or are,
I got hands, yeah, we'll make this work, all right, we'll make this work, what wall are you putting it
on, huh, on the back wall, the back wall, okay, east face and north face and south, I don't know,
I don't have a compass, you have no idea, it depends on where the moss grows, you know what,
by the way, you're a mess, excuse me, you're a waste, I'm sorry, did you say a waste, you're a
big fat mistake, I don't understand, listen, my mother told me I fell off the ugly tree and at
every branch on the way, but I have never been more offended by someone I've never met in my life,
okay, I'm going for the back wall, and now you're painting, you're just gonna paint now, yeah,
man, I have half a mind to leave right now, okay, he's painting, you're painting,
okay, you got to put more, do you think it looks good, you got to put more paint on them,
okay, why don't you grab a brush and help me, why pink again, why was that, why pink, why are you
doing pink, uh, because the demons in my head told me to, okay, you're talking about Satan,
well, it could be, I don't know, I haven't figured it out yet, you want to do nice,
you got to do angled lines, like, do you go up and down or do you go side to side,
you got to go side to side or angles, better coverage, by the way, and I really do mean this,
and this is not a joke, this is not a joke in the stream, this is not a joke for anything,
this is real life, uh, this is the first time I have ever, in my entire adult life,
in my entire childhood life, have ever put paint on a wall, ever, congratulations son,
congratulations, hey, there's a first time for everything, uh, I don't think we're, we need to
ladder, to get the top of this, by the way, is that, is that why you, is that why you picked
pink, because you've never painted before, or does it have something to do with virtual reality,
oh, I just thought it was a cool color, I thought it would look nice, okay, that looks pretty good,
you met my, you met my kids yet, same, I smell, I can't, I, I'm, it's making me gab, it's making me
gab, I'm gabbing about it, it's smell, I smell so awful, smells like my bass boat, I'm sorry,
I really apologize that I smelled this awful, oh, it's fine, it's, it's, look, it's the wood,
the wood has, emanates like a disgusting onion and like taco smell, I mean, it definitely smells
like something living, it's coming from something living, I'm really sorry about this, I really am,
I don't usually, I usually bathe at least once every day, so you live here alone though, yeah,
no one to help you paint, no one to help you do nothing, no, I haven't bathed in eight days,
eight days, eight, is that right, yeah, I'm sorry, I have to tell you that,
that's okay, the pig's back in my yard, don't bathe either, oh, I could be like, what are your
piggies, what the fuck would I say that to somebody in a public setting, we still love them though,
what, is it pink or pink, is it pink or pink, we're talking about pink balls,
you picked the colors, I was like, why are they saying that, I think, that's how we say it around
here, pink balls, well, I, excuse me, Jeb, I appreciate the help, I really do, thank you,
thank you, how do you say milk, how do you say milk in these parts, you know, if you're going to
drink a glass of milk, say that again, if you're going to drink a glass of milk, what do you call
it, you know, you know, Jeb, I think, I don't, I'm not really a big fan of the pink, if I'm honest,
no, I'm actually a pretty, I'm a pretty big fan of a black wall, if you wanted to help me paint
the wall black, I got a couple more minutes, a couple more minutes, yeah, I don't know what
you're doing today or tomorrow, but I really don't like the pink, the pink doesn't pop,
yeah, I mean, I don't think my wife will miss me, if I'm honest, well, you live right at 980,
you're okay, yeah, okay, we need to paint this black, it is getting kind of late though, you're
sure, yeah, I mean, we'll just, we have in a few minutes, you got food or nothing, there's no, like,
you don't have a pizza, this food downstairs, I know you came in my house, I'm completely
uninvited, yeah, no, because you stole my electricity, just to throw it out there, I didn't steal
anything, actually, that's okay, I plugged my house into an outlet that was on the street,
I thought it was a city outlet, you thought it was a city outlet, you pay taxes, no, I haven't paid
taxes, yeah, okay, and you think the city is just gonna give you electricity for no reason, we need
another one of these, jeb, I'll just pour it right in there, okay,
that's where pink comes from, here, let me help you with that, I need the screwdriver, you know,
you do have a stench to you, I'm sorry, they won't let me take the shower for some reason,
who's Dave, what are you talking about, Dave, the people that are here, there's literally no,
I know it's just you and me, but there's like 60 fucking million people that are watching and
having me do something, what are you talking about, oh, okay, you're one of them,
you mean like they're sent me in the walls, yeah, I've been thinking there must be something,
I need to have another way to see what I'm doing, okay, you ever wake up at night and like just see
random things, like the things flying in space, is that what you're referring to, or no, yeah,
jeb, what are you looking for, I'm looking for the screwdrivers, they're helping us,
oh, they are, they are, okay, so you're saying you moved in, I moved in, your house could be
haunted, have you considered that, I don't know, jeb, do you, like, I get a very serious one-to-one
you and I, like forget about anybody here, there is literally no one here, it's a wall, you don't
even have a window right here, one-to-wub, one-to-wub, you and me, jeb, are there, is there like drug
problems in this neighborhood, drug problems, yeah, you're talking about like what kind of
drugs in specific, like acetaminophen, or what do you talk about, I don't know, I just feel like
people are on crack in this neighborhood, can you, can you move that box out of the way, jeb,
yeah, sure, what's in here, what do you want me to move it, just kick it forward,
just, just push it forward, literally, just, yeah, just throw it off into the bathroom,
okay, just push it over, just kick it, doesn't matter, wall here, I don't know, jeb, this is green,
this isn't even black, this is green, this is green paint, I told you, you ain't good at this,
she really ain't good at this, jeb, okay, god damn it, is that black, excuse me, can you check,
we don't, we don't use words like that, I'm sorry, jeb, I have, hold on, you really are,
you really are, you really want to take care of that stand right now, so you don't shower
because people are listening to you in your house, like, well, I don't shower because they don't let
the ghosts tell you, the ghosts tell you not to take a shower, I don't even, I don't know, ghosts,
people, you want to appease the ghosts who think you're stinky, jeb, let me ask you another question,
do you just wake up with furniture in your house, no, I pay for it because I have a job,
you ever thought about getting one, where do you think I got a house like this from, a good point,
okay, fair enough, you paid for it or, excuse me, excuse me, of course, no, I don't have any money,
I'm sorry, so you're saying you want us to paint black over your pink wall right there,
that's what I've been told, okay, from the demons, jeb, I'll take care of it for you, all right,
why don't you, why don't you just clean up a little bit of your stain or something,
just a tiny bit, please, can you guys please do me a favor and just make it so we don't have to
talk about this every five seconds, I'm filling the house with like, human gas, like, please,
just pick shower, we're painting the walls like pink and then black and whatever, please,
just pick it, so he doesn't, he's disgusted, okay, so listen, I told you, I know how to do stuff in
a house, I am not an interior designer, so what do you, what do you expect me to do here, you want
me to kind of just, black on the back wall, dip it in there, yes, just dip it in there, black on the
back wall, okay, you know, my wife makes a mean turkey casserole, she just takes mayonnaise and
pretty much that's it, that's it, yeah, I'm sorry, you just ruined the floor,
hold on, you make, that's a turkey casserole, this is a very significantly watered down version
of blank paint, I hope you understand, okay, I just want to get curious, I just want to make sure I
caught that correctly, you had a turkey casserole and what's in it, yeah, listen, we're a big fan,
you can make a casserole out of anything, a casserole out of anything with mayonnaise,
well, I just did it way worse, jeff, I think you made a new paint,
okay, okay, listen, this is easy, this is easy, all right, we'll just run back and forth, well,
don't come over on my domain, it is kind of fun though, don't you want a lot of, we need to get
off there too, I mean, it's not bad, that's not bad, look, you can even draw on it, what's your
name again, jeff, my name is jeffrey, jeffrey 900, jeff, r, j-e-f-f-f-r-e-e-a, f-r, thank god, e,
j-r-f-e, good luck, just keep doing what you're doing, I'm sorry, what, I just have to, I have to
shower, just do what you're doing, this ain't my house, excuse me, hello, are you coming back or
you're gonna get like pizza or something or like mayonnaise, okay, all right, that's the wrong,
that's the wrong door again, that's the wrong door again, there's the right door, taking a shower,
he's coming around the turn back out there,
do I brush my teeth four times a day,
okay, we don't need the pit stop, we're on nascar list, we're on nascar list,
ah, it's so much better, oh my god, I can't smell, like a dirty, gas-covered,
I'm just embarrassing myself, people are embarrassed to be in the same room with me,
people are embarrassed, oh, okay, not bad, my god, I can still, I still feel like I smell,
you know when you take a shower, you feel like not showering for three days, and then you smell,
you can still smell your armpits, it's like, god, I need to do that every single day, put me down
by the river, Jeff, Jeff, Jeff, I'm nascar list, that looks great, thank you, that looks great,
thank you, is that all you wanted, I mean, this place don't look much better than when I got here,
I feel like, Jeff, I think it looks good, I kind of want to move this out of the way, yeah, that's
probably a good idea, again, I'm not like, I almost just bent my ankle, I'm fine, I don't know much
about safety, what do you think about this wall, Jeff, I mean, it doesn't look good, I want to get,
before you came into the house, I wanted to get rid of this wall, oh, you're talking about that wall
right there, I don't like the cotton of VR, yeah, that's the northeast south-facing wall, okay,
north-northeast south-facing, I mean, you could probably get rid of it pretty easy, you don't want
to take care of something, you don't want to paint it or nothing, just give me a second,
let's get a cup of this, okay, no, I don't want to, I want to get rid of it, it's a VR room,
okay, you got a lot of paint around here, you know that, Jeff, I gotta go get my robe on,
your robe, can you please bring me some sort of food, I mean, I've been here for what, like three
days, I'm just kidding, do you like cookies, three hours, cookies, do you like cookies, yeah,
pecan sandies, what you got, let's get my robe on, sugar cookies, molasses cookies, chocolate chip
cookies, mayonnaise cookies, I like every kind of cookie by the way, what am I, like a 1940s billionaire,
like what are you talking about, put your robe on, put your robe on, what are you talking about,
I don't know where it is, where is it, let me see what he's got around here,
must have taken that wall down, huh, I'm like a playboy, all right, I don't, I don't even know
where my robe is, all right, hard day's work, that's what I'm talking about, hard day's work,
I don't know who the robe is, all right, oh, where's my robe, excuse me, Jeb, yeah, yeah,
we're right back, you say you want to take that wall out, huh, I, I want to take it down, you want
me to get started on that or, um, I, are you literally gonna do anything, there are safety
glasses there Jeb, safety glasses, I would put them on, I want this one, so let me get this straight,
you have safety glasses in this house, yeah, but demons keep you up at night making you not
shot, it's like you're prepared for certain things, yeah, it don't make no sense, do you
want to help or do you want to go home, now listen, I don't think you have any clue what you're doing,
I don't, oh, you ever demolish something before, get these off, no, never, never,
I've done a thing or two in my life, well, because if I do VR, you got to stretch first,
I don't want to bump into the wall and like, and, and, and like, oh, I'm doing VR, oh, shit,
I hit the wall, I think it has to come down, okay, let's see if I can get it down, Thor's hammer
over here, are you gonna help me, you look kind of funny with your robe on, I'm not gonna lie,
see what I can do, you're for real, you're taking that wall down, yeah, I mean, it's got to come
down, all right, hey, hey, hey, you, you ever thought about like, pretending like you're on the back nine,
like a golf swing, yeah, I might get a little bit of power into it, sure, that's not quite what I
meant, that's not a golf swing, my friend, that was a golf swing, let me show you, let me, let me,
hold on, let me get one more, I'm gonna just step over here for a second,
I just bounced off, would you like to try again, let me at least show you a little,
yeah, show me how you do it, I'm talking, I'm talking about pretending you're on the back nine,
and you don't want to get back home, okay, you don't want to get back home, because you
got a lot going on, yeah, let me just light up my shot really quick, okay,
okay, okay, are you, are you a putter, or are you a driver, you got another hammer or no, no, I'm just
watching you do this, okay, you see that, that was actually really good for not very much effort,
very easy, hey Jeff, let me see that for a second, let me show you something,
Jeff, hey Jeff, get along with it, more afraid in my life than right now, I may have just sold my
pants, hey Jeff, you want a swing, I may have just sold my pants, it's gonna be more than one
person stinking up this place right now, I'll tell you that, if we go for a swing, Jeff, I mean you
won't take the whole wall down, I want it down, I don't want it there, are you sure about that,
say good, how many more swings, I don't, I want to do all the work for you, I don't want to do
everything, do I want a big one into that right wall, okay listen, you take that part down,
that's for you, that's your house, you hit it right up there in the quadrant,
Jerma, you give me like two seconds just to hide, okay, Jerma you're short, Jerma you're like five
five, no I'm not, fuck you, you're like five six, I'm fucking five seven, idiot, shut up,
fucking idiots, are you talking to me, yeah, excuse, you're really digging that wall down aren't you,
yeah, you get it up right now, I think, yeah, that's right, that's what I'm talking about,
you work out, not in like, not in five years, no, okay, let's get this out of the way,
let's uh, can you get that out of there Jeff, yeah, man you really are stinky, or is that me,
I think that's you at this point, because I took a shower, that's not me, I mean I did, I did, I
did soil myself, so I tell you what, why don't you hit it like, you hit around here or something,
okay, give it the sweet touch, right here, yeah, you want to do it, no, it's all you, it's all you,
it's your house, okay, how about right in the middle, right there, I feel significantly unsafe,
is all I'm gonna say, what's it, what's it, Mario, you played Mario, whatever it is you're doing, I
don't think, oh so long, get out, get down, you mother fucker, that's one thing, you got a bunch
of studs there, are there studs in the wall, Jeff, yeah, what do we do about that, you're gonna have
to take those down at some point, let me use my hands, why don't you take a swing Jeff,
why don't you take a swing, oh that's perfect, yeah man, oh wowee, I'm strong, wowee, you did
that all by yourself, hold on, let me, hold on a second, oh sweet lord, yeah, I got you, I got you,
oh lord, I'm gonna be feeling that for a while, all right, okay, that ain't hard either, what is,
what's left, what the heck is that thing, what is this, a painting, yeah, you could probably get
this down if you need to, can I get this down, hold on, watch out Jeff, no please don't, okay,
I'm at your house man, yeah so that's meant, that's meant for structure, I don't think that's,
I would probably use the screwdriver, yeah, you want to do that or, I would, I would do it,
by the way, I asked for a cookie, you're right, he did ask for a cookie,
okay, I'll get him a cookie, okay, he asked for it, fine, why is that down here,
make no sense, just bringing him up, weird, just bringing him up, you want a cookie, you want food,
of course, gotta be neighborly, gotta be a good neighbor, gotta be a good neighbor,
Jeff, how are you, how are you doing, I've got some cookies for you, thank you, you make those yourself,
yes, I did, it kind of looks like my mother made those, would you like one, yeah, I wouldn't mind,
it kind of tastes like sand, I just didn't want to touch it because I've been touching the ground,
I don't know if I should, I'm not sure if I should eat with these hands or not,
could you feed it to me, you want to just smell them, yeah, does it smell good, yes, they smell
great, I'm sorry about that, oh lord, let me ask you something, you built this house yourself or
you bought it, what's that, you built this house yourself or you bought it, I bought this house,
it was upgraded a few times, but I, okay, because this, this is strange, okay, there's no reason,
there's no reason to have this in a closet, okay, and listen to this, right, yep, you see,
this is not mine, look at this, look at this, holy shit, that is real weird,
there's something behind here, by the way, we might be able to take this down, but I am not sure,
oh okay, I'm just going to step over, get this fucking thing down, we can't get the door frame
down, I'm not sure about that, you know, there's a painting in here, Jab, let's look at that,
really interesting, do we have it, I want to see what's back there, that's why, I don't know what
that is, I mean, the weird part is that whole painting is kind of like stuck to the wall,
why is it, it's like glued, it's like the previous owner put something there,
all right, hold on, let me see, can I cut it, how old is this house,
hold on, can I cut through it, you got to put a little more effort into it,
have you ever used that in your life, I've never used one of these before, I mean in real life,
either, okay, first time for everything, that's all right, okay, why would there be a painting
back here, I mean, I guess it could be some sort of shrine, you did say there were demons in the
house, okay, you did say there were demons in the house, maybe someone was trying to do some
sort of, you know, Jab, give me the sledgehammer, okay, I'm gonna walk away now, you can give a
little force to it, okay, you're not really good at that, this is definitely something back here,
Jab, what do you think's back there, why is this made of steel, are you kidding me,
holy shit, there are screws here, hold on, okay, there's that too, I mean, you really can't cut
that, I'm scared, have you ever been to the dentist, Jab, I have never been, no thank you,
no thank you, all right, what is the, I don't understand, why is it here, it's the wrong way,
how do I get to go, I'll tell you what, I bet you could cut through it if you'd like, would you like
me to cut through it, how do you get this to go in reverse, okay, let me see, you go ahead and try,
I'll take care of everything for you, can it go in reverse, yeah, this is the wrong thing,
that ain't gonna work, okay, I'll tell you what, where's that knife, where's that knife,
Jab, be careful, it's hard to cut through, I'll be careful, all right, I'll be careful,
be very careful, I promise, it's a very sharp knife, thank you, thank you, my liege, thank you,
be careful, so you moved here, yeah, how long ago, a week ago, two weeks ago, okay, you married all,
no, you're not married, I've never been married, not married, okay, why not,
because it's not, I'm not ready yet, you know, somebody asked me the same question
a week ago, the same exact thing, the sleep demons are telling you something,
no, somebody that may even be part of your family, I don't know, excuse me,
I don't know, just focus on that, it's a very sharp blade, sorry, I've done this a couple times,
unfortunately, this is the most sturdy painting, there's been a few times in my life where I'd
have to take down a painting, we're almost done, I'm gonna let you do the, you got it,
I'm gonna let you do most of the work, here, okay, looks good, you seen the fitness,
the instructor, yeah, you might want to do that, has he gone in your house,
oh yeah, he goes in your house too, all right, why do you let him do that, that's like his
home invasion, you didn't sign the HOA, no, what HOA, okay, all right, let's see if we can
get in there, let me see that knife, okay, you want the knife, yeah, there you are, I just,
I want to get this away from everybody, oh, I understand, okay, can we get in there,
yeah, let me see, there's something back here, I think, here, there's something, good lord,
holy shit, what is that, what is this, there's a safe back here, what is that, okay, and you said
you bought this house, I bought this house, okay, oh my god, it's a safe, you know how to get that
open or not, I don't know the code, hold on, let me try it, okay, let me just double check,
have you ever opened a safe before, because I'm finding there are a significant number of things
you've never done, I watch YouTube videos that can explain it, you listen for the little, okay,
do you hear that, right there, do you hear, right there, okay, yeah, I don't hear nothing,
I can't get it, you could sledgehammer it, I mean, maybe, I do know a guy, this is, I swear to god,
this house was built, like, five days ago, that's weird, okay, I may accept you, I know a guy,
if you need help, I know a locksmith, we could call, you know a guy, I know a guy, I got a guy
for everything, we could break it too, you want to try, we could, listen, I'm gonna say, I don't
have a significant amount of confidence, so you're gonna be able to break that safe, if you couldn't
break that wall down, but that's just me, I mean, is that like a joke or something, I've been proved
wrong before, but that's all right, if you want to give it a shot, give your guy a call, okay,
all right, can I borrow your phone though, because it's downstairs, it's downstairs,
it's down in the kitchen, okay, yeah, well, you know a guy that can come do this, yeah, yeah,
give me two seconds, okay, two seconds, he knows a guy, okay, to open the safe, I don't know what's
in it, because I, this is an upgrade, I didn't, I didn't know this was even in here, was this part
of the foundation, well, the foundation is on the ground, so, German, what are you stupid,
we're like on a second story, he knows a guy, call him, I think people like tools, because of the
sounds they make, you think that too, you guys think that too, you know what I mean, just like,
it's like, oh yeah, let me get my tool, it feels like, it feels very like manly, like, oh yeah,
how you doing man, yeah, okay, you're not busy right now, listen, I got a thing or two, we could,
we could get taken care of, we won't come on down, get him down, yeah, come on over pronto,
I got a little bit of a situation, I could use your help with, okay, yeah, no problem, okay,
America, all right, I can't get it, I don't know the combo, I don't know what to do,
hey, can you get the door, yeah, I got you, I got the door, if it's your guy,
I don't want to pretend, I don't want to greet him, you know him, come on in, come on in,
hey Jeff, hey, how's it going my guy, good to see you, oh you are a blue collar as always,
come on in, come on in, listen, if you could keep this on the down low, all right, I got a safe
situation up there, I need, I need someone to crack it, I want to make sure that, I'll make sure
you get paid, if you know what I mean, sure, yeah, all right, let's head upstairs, anything for you
Jeff, thank you brother, it's not your place right, down the street, oh no, no, no, not for sure,
keep going, keep going, this is confusing layout, I'm gonna tell you right now, that makes no
fucking sense, this whole house don't make sense, that makes zero sense, he's trying to paint his
wall pink and black, what, pink up there, that sounds dumb, you can go up the stairs, it could be gems,
oh stairs, okay, jewels, gold, there might be gold in there, gold still expensive, if it's gold,
that's awesome, who would put a safe in a wall, that's ridiculous,
why would you put a safe in a wall, unless it was to hide something very, very important, hey, what,
what the fuck is this, a little bit of a war zone up here, we swear we come in a room, okay,
all right, this is my guy, that's your guy, he can take care of pretty much anything, what's your
guys name, what's your name, what's up, what's your name, I'm a locksmith, he doesn't need it
now right, no, okay, all right, you're good, okay, we have a safe here, okay, that we, I didn't want
to break it, didn't want to swing at it or anything, all right, but it's here and I just,
can you get into this, for the record, have you tried to get into it while I was going,
I tried, why would I know what combination it was, I don't know, the sense you're saying,
it should be pretty standard, okay, was it behind anything, it was a painting in a wall, he's a
neighbor, yeah, religious, does it mean anything, does it mean anything, can you just let me,
okay, all right, you can stick the painting, something, I don't know if it's a code word,
listen, do you, that's a hot locksmith, I just want to make sure that's clear, that's all,
what's up, beautiful, you called over one of the most attractive locksmiths I've ever met in my
whole life, I just want to know, he's a good looking man, but can you not come on to me,
I'm trying to do my job, appreciate that, just keep doing what you're doing, that's like an
ocean violation, he's very, very, he's really, really sweet and he's very sweet, how many days
I told you he can get in anything, ride the boat, the rain, how long was the rain, a week,
the rain, 40 days and 49, 40 days and 49, what's the time frame on you getting into that,
the safe, are you rushing me, no, I just was curious, I don't know how long it took,
I mean, the bench, okay, well I hope he gets it, I'm gonna ask you, I'll ask you a quick question,
yeah, are you familiar with the idea that nine possession is nine tenths of the law,
you're gonna have to say that again and like explain like I'm five, okay, position, they say
position is nine tenths of the law, you understand that, I will explain it, okay, so conceptually it
would mean, okay, you know what nine tenths is, it means nine out of ten, yeah, I think that,
hold on, how many percentages is that, I think here's the point, whoever has what's in that safe
owns it, you understand, you're just making no sense to me, okay, I can't get it, what do you
mean you can't get it, I'm fucking with you, I'm the best, okay, all right, you want to get in there,
well you got it, what's in it, whoa, what's in it, okay, okay, oh, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait,
wait a second, wait a minute, wait a minute, wait a minute, well we have to have a conversation about,
no, no, no, no, no, let me see that, I don't know, position is nine tenths of the law,
no, I have no clue, that's good, you got the safe open, well, you know, it's a pleasure to
work with you as well, it's, you got the safe open, okay, take a couple, you got the safe open, yeah,
thank you, let me see what's in there, well, what if we just figure out payment, let me see what's
in the safe, get downstairs now, okay, why are we going downstairs, because I don't, I want everybody
out of this room, because I don't want to be up here, get downstairs, you might want to pocket
some of that, it's my goddamn house, whatever's in the wall is mine, that's absolute bullshit,
ton of money, I don't, I'm not comfortable with you touching all of the stuff that's in a, in a
wall in my house, you, you didn't even know it was there though, it's my house, so you took it from
my house, I mean, but he didn't build this house, private property actually, he didn't build this
house, hallelujah brother, let's just, hold on, let's wait, let's just go ahead, let's get an ad
break, ad break, I want to get this sorted, I'm sorry, what did you say, a what break, just go into
the kitchen, what is this guy talking about, ad break now, hey, we're going to sort this, thank you,
don't hand people money that didn't do it, I want to take a quick second to go over a couple things,
kind of off camera, with just no, no jokes or anything, I want to talk about the show
and how it even was able to happen in the first place, Coinbase came in at the last second
and let us be able to do this show, and when I, when I say that I mean that, all the things you see
back here were really only possible because of this company here, and I really mean that, I
wouldn't say it if it wasn't true, Twitch came in and gave us a bunch of money, Coinbase gave us a
bunch of money, what you see here is only because of those two companies, and I couldn't afford any
of this stuff, there's no way I could have done any of this on my own, and when you talk about
like sponsorships, talk about sponsors, you've seen the show, you've seen, they've let us do
whatever we want, we didn't have to do anything, Twitch and Coinbase we had, they just let us do
what we wanted, I've used Coinbase for the last five years, those of you that know this channel,
I used to have an Ethereum address that you could donate to, it was real, and I have to thank them
because without their support the show doesn't happen, doesn't happen without them, and also
there's so many people to thank, we're not going to have that much opportunity to thank everybody,
but seriously I'm going to take the opportunity now, but seriously if you're into cryptocurrency,
if you want to learn more about the space, it's a great place to start, and they gave us a
significant amount of capital to make this show happen, so thank you Coinbase, thank you Twitch,
also while I have a second here, because this is the finale, JK Productions, Community Jake,
this is impossible without these people, Andy Mark, Ghost Commander, Criken and his team,
this went off without a hitch, it's seriously like, sure this is the idea that I came up with,
but you can't do this without a ton of dedicated people, the glass breaking, when we did that,
Andy Mark, the engineers and Andy Mark came up with all this stuff, there's so many people,
Ludwig, Kit Boga, Milton, there's so many people back here that you don't see, I wanted just to
kind of address it real quick, because I wasn't going to have an opportunity to, but again I want
to like, we'll focus on, there's so many people to thank, there's so many people that made this
happen, but Coinbase, go check them out, please do, they gave us so much money to do this, and it's,
they just wanted to make a good show, they wanted to make a good show, and I think it has been,
I think it's been a lot of fun, so that's because of Twitch and Coinbase, thank you both of you,
we'll go back to the show, I've actually used Coinbase, I really have, for five years, I mean it,
and I'll go back to the show, let's break the fourth one, what's going on in here, I thought
that was a bug, hey, have you guys heard anything in back, I was just kind of back there, just
messing around a little bit, sure, we were just talking, I mean, yeah, you've got quite a bit of
money here, okay, you've got quite a bit of money, so, hypothetically speaking, we were thinking,
we could make this whole thing go away, that's a, that's a, can I hold that, well yeah, I was
talking to Jeb, and I figured we just split it, you know, maybe three-way, yeah, me, Jeb, and he has a
actually a dog named Buck, you're gonna do a three-way split, between the three of us,
it's in my wall, but he wouldn't gotten in, all right, let me count how much money this is,
I mean, hypothetically speaking, if we were to have taken the money and walked away, no one would
believe you, that we were honest, it's 1200 bucks, so, that's pretty bad math, it's 1200 dollars,
when you were gone, I got something in your hat, listen, I didn't get much beyond the sixth grade,
and I can tell you that, hey, that's 1200 bucks, from what you've done, blue-collar-wise, you seem,
it seems slow, what, you know, the painting, you seem a bit slow, I'm very fast, let me show you,
toy boat, toy boat, toy boat, toy boat, toy boat, toy boat, toy boat, toy boat, toy boat, toy boat,
that's actually impressive, that's very impressive, admittedly nothing to do with blue-collar,
that'd be crazy, that'd be an extra violation, just to do that, toy boat, toy boat, and I figured
out that great white-collar, so, you know, I got a lawyer friend, okay, I just call him in, we just
square it away, he's got a guy, I don't know why we need law in this, this is literally my house,
I mean, what do you want, you want me to just give you a hundred bucks, and I'll give you a hundred
bucks, how much is your fee, zero change, my fee, yeah, it's not, it's not flat, it's percentage-based,
and then there's a finder, there's a finder's fee, a finder's fee, because I find it, let me just call
him up, let me just call him up, oh, finder's fee, my giant dollars of bills, call your lawyer,
sure, get a lawyer in here, you realize you never would have found the money if it ain't for us,
is this stevenson, stevenson, stevenson, already, you just need a lawyer down here,
weirdo at nine eight five, nine eight, why don't we just take this and put it like, yeah, there's
beer here, that ain't your money, that ain't your money, you might want to put it down there, but
yeah, if you could just come down, we just got a dispute really, you mind if I have some of this
bread, go ahead, yeah, he's being kind of a dick, yeah, so, I don't know if we can just figure that
out, that'd be great, I'll see you in a bit, is that all you got in this house, this bread, this
mac and cheese up there, but it takes a while to make, just forget it, could go for a homemade
cookie, yeah, just eat a cookie if you want, so you know a guy, he knows about finder's fees, he
knows about your percentage, oh, I'm so tired, get the door, by my house, we're doing everything
for him, he's like, he doesn't do a lot of work around here, he wants to keep the money,
hey man, you see that over there, hey, how you doing buddy, how's it going, come on in, come on in,
wow, this is quite the establishment you got here, yeah, well, it's not mine, it's this guy's, but,
hey, hey, how's it going, hey, oh, I know you, you play on the same softball team,
that's right, hey, who's this, is this the homeowner, this is the homeowner, he's a bit erratic, a bit,
I just don't think he's mentally fit enough to be able to handle the situation, well, nice to meet
you, but, hey, it's Bob, Doug, Stevenson, part of Stevenson, Stevenson, Stevenson and Randy, it's
been a long day, I'm tired, okay, well, hey, I'm here from the property management law firm of
Stevenson, Stevenson, Stevenson and Randy, yeah, and I was called down, well, first of all, this
is quite a nice place you got here, just want to let you know a couple of things, zoning rights
that we have, okay, all right, now listen, what's, what's the pickle we got, I got $50,000 in, it was
in my wall, and they want money, okay, so here, let me get, let me get it right, okay, he was stealing
my electricity for a significant amount of time, I'll make that very clear, the only reason I was
in this establishment is because he stole my electricity, back in my day, we called that
thievery, oh, thievery, 100%, 100%, that's a sin, that's in the Bible, then I called my guy here,
I called my guy, so it was a finder's fee for me, I think that's legal, I think that's legal,
he's for, I get money, that's right, I call my guy, he takes care of everything, right, I mean,
look at him, he can take care of anything, you know what I'm saying, hey, ain't that the truth,
if you lock, I'll open it, you know, we don't have a slogan yet, but we were shopping that one,
my wife was saying the same thing, she said they're locksmiths, hey, so what are we doing here,
this is what we're dealing with, well, we need to disperse the money, okay, so you found this money,
we found a saint in the side of the room up there, okay, fucking, there was smithy granite,
well, now, you say we found the money, so you mean, it wasn't just you who found the money,
was there some, which one of you, which one of you, we found it and he helped, oh, I mean,
I found it, 100%, okay, at least nine, well, nine tenths of the law, not possession is nine tenths,
you know, have you ever heard possession is nine tenths of the law, did he just fall asleep,
hey, is he, is he literally sleeping right now, is that, does that mean he doesn't want the money,
you think, is that legal for, maybe we'll just, okay, here, I'll tell you what we're gonna do,
okay, here's a little bit above my pay grade, I'm gonna have to go in, I think maybe what we should
do is give him some equal representation, I'm gonna call another lawyer in, okay, why don't
we do that, yeah, that sounds great, would you like a lawyer, yes, I'll call a lawyer for you,
okay, yes, I would, all right, just give me, just give me one second here, okay, take a quick nap
or something, yeah, I'd like a lawyer for me, all right, this guy has no clue what he's doing,
yeah, he's a bit distraught, all right, yeah, it's Bob Doug, yeah, yeah, we got,
got a new, I'm gonna make you some bread, oh, please, you can't just walk around my house,
turns out he's a real, you want a beer, you see what we're doing right now,
no thank you, maybe set him up, yeah, I'll take a set up, let's do it,
I found some money in the wall or something like that, you can't just walk around, he's got a
half-eaten piece of bread just sitting there and, yeah, can we get to, I appreciate that, thank you,
you might want to microwave that, give it a little bit of, yeah, of course, can you microwave this,
yeah, I would not do that, all right, you can't just, you can't, get Doug Bob over here, extended
can't, okay, that's how good it is, you can have, you can cut bread, of course, it's bread,
okay, we got someone coming in who's gonna give you your representation, I thought you were a
lawyer, listen, I am here on behalf of Locke Smith and Jebediah, okay, Jebediah and I go way back,
get in, get in, come in, come in, come in, get in, hey, don't open, open the door, not bad,
it's not bad at all, it's not bad, that's not bad, hi, hello, I'm Doug Stevenson, I'm Stevenson, Stevenson, Stevenson and Randy, hi, how are you,
hi, I'm your representation, mine, yes, right, that's correct, yes, you will be representing the
homeowner, uh-huh, yep, good, why the hell does his representative have a big book and you got a dumb
hat, okay, I don't appreciate that, we're gonna be respectful of all lawyers, I complimented you,
first of all, I do, I do appreciate that, but we're gonna be respectful, thank you, sir,
my big book is underneath the hat, huh, right there, okay, that's not, you're my lawyer,
that's not my law, okay, so he came in, and hi, my name's Jeb, I'm the one who found, I found the money,
and then my guy came, oh, well, I'm gonna ask my, I'm gonna go ahead and ask, can she do that,
like that, I don't think she's allowed to do that, I'm just gonna let him introduce you guys,
can you please step in here, oh, what, listen, that finger getting a little heated here, okay,
let's all just, I understand, let's all just step back for a minute, so they found some money,
behind a wall, I found the money, they, plural, the three of them, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no,
no, no, technically speaking, you didn't buy one, technically speaking, I found the money,
I did all the work, did I not do all the work up there, we split the work, what type of work
did you do, what type of work, handyman work, listen to me, we paint the wall pink up there,
listen to me, you shitty idiot, everybody in this room, everybody in this room is a stupid or shit
idiot, sir, you're as stupid as the rest of them, defamation, you're dumb too, you're dumb,
you're dumb, defamation, where'd the other one, where'd this one go, okay, you know what,
you're wearing sunglasses inside, it's loud here, I'm fucking an idiot, I'm calling Michelle,
call Michelle, okay, what do you call who, I'm calling in an additional lawyer,
because you're dumbass, I don't want any more lawyers, hey, Michelle, you're wearing glasses
inside, what are you, fucking Tommy Wiseau, let me just give me the money, it's the only guy that
called that off, the person is unbecoming, did you not get, where's the rest of it, what happened to
the rest of it, if you could just get over here, look at me split, that would be so lovely, position
is non-tensile, no, position, position, oh what a spin, what are we doing, spin that one, give me
that money, so much, holy hell, okay, so technically if he has position does that mean that he,
well, it's, it's only, I'm hiding this out of a fucking mattress, everybody has 30 IQ,
hide that, so you're suggesting, don't let anybody see that, don't let anybody see that,
hide that, I will give you a percentage, hello, you asked for a Michelle, yes, another lawyer,
great, I think that was okay, I got the stool samples, so wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait,
Michelle, Michelle, okay, I'm glad you're here to help us, so you're, you're their lawyer,
you're my lawyer, and that's your lawyer, correct, yep, yes, that's correct, Michelle Stevenson of
Stevenson, Stevenson, Stevenson and Randi, that's right, pleasure, Michelle Stevenson, Bob Doug
Stevenson, Doug Bob Stevenson of Stevenson, Stevenson, Stevenson, and Randi, I hate everybody in
this room, I hope they all would come, okay, well sir, that's unbecoming, you are on a stool,
it's a legal thing, it is not, all right, now listen, we got to get to the bottom of who's,
are you going to catch me up, there's a way, you don't have to catch me up, what's going on,
I'm with this guy, this gentleman and this gentleman in the locksmith hill, sure,
yeah, I think I deserve, hey, I'm going to like that, I'll need something back,
and then how is he going to get it, if we put it back in the same, and that's like, I can tell,
all right, under the bed, I can see it right here, are things getting, I'm gonna have to call Randi,
he's gonna be real mad, I'm gonna have to call Randi, this is, I'm sorry, all right, don't worry
about it, you type on your cell phone,
your shoes untied,
that is eating the middle, is eating the middle of bread, without eating the crust, a fucking
offendable offense, I think it is, while it is disgusting, it is not illegal, which one of you
did that, probably, if I could take a quick guess, could I see what you got in your hand there,
Mr. Locksmith, let's take a quick little look, oh mommy, cut the crust off mommy, he is a great
locksmith, he never said he knew how to cut the crust off mommy, right, cut the crust off mommy,
fucking loser, I think you should try and settle down, you should also conserve some energy,
maybe if you just had a seat, why don't we just have a seat there, hey Jerma, fuck you, how do you
know that's my name, oh god, oh lord, what was that, what was that over there, nothing wrong with
eating the middle, hello Randy, hello Randy, thank you, what was in the door, hi, who are you, Randy,
you're Randy, Stevenson, Stevenson, Stevenson and Randy, okay, is the whole family, yes,
yes, we are a family, can you tell, she's got my eyes, he's got my build and gets the beard from his
mom, come on, let me explain, let me explain, let him talk, let him explain, I came into this
household, I had no expectation of anybody, I helped the guy out, helped his whole room, I get my guy to come in,
he opens the safe, all right, he opens the safe, he has a fee, he has a fee, I charge, that is an
honorable thing, everybody knows that, he's got a fee, yeah, send him back, he called, we call a
lawyer, I don't care how much it costs, give me five grand, I don't care, ten grand, that was me,
that's fine, thank you, I tried, you got the address already, yeah, it just, just, just calls a,
calls a fucking ruckus, doesn't matter, I mean, pretty much the whole thing can be solved if you
just give me the money, that's all I'm telling you right now, what's the role in this, well, I open the
safe, sir, hey, this is my mom on the phone, okay, all right, okay, is this normal for you,
uh, no, it's all good, what's, what's the verdict here, what's going on, what's your role in all this,
so, I was the, uh, well, first of all, I'm the homeowner, yeah, let me just, quick, why is he
opening the door, I just opened the door, because I feel like it, because I want some fresh air in
my home, I'm the homeowner, the windows are just fine, sir, I don't think you want to open that,
uh, we, as, as you're, you should not do that, how about you step over here, we get this solved,
give me this, let's just do this, all right, so this, from what I understand, this large sum of
money was found in the wall, in this, on this property, and you assisted in tearing down the
wall, and you assisted in opening the security device in order to obtain the money, that's good,
okay, thank you, all right, so, here's, here's how, I, pretty much, knowing the law like I know the
law, because the law is the law, and the law is the law, this is what we are going to do, I know,
said that three times in a row, did I, did I, does that affect how, did I, three times, all right,
so, here is how, this is how we're going to distribute the money, this is how it is, now,
I believe you had some electricity stolen from you, sir, really quick, sir, I got a quick objection,
he literally, he may have just kissed a bear, that is, that is a violation in this state,
I'm allergic, I'm allergic, I'm allergic, no, I'm allergic, I've got allergies,
yes, so, this is, this is pretty much what, this is how I'm going to rule on this, all right,
so, here, here it is, did you have electricity stolen from you, absolutely, I think if we pay
you fair kilowatt hour rates, and I think time in, time in, also, you were doing some handiwork up
there, emotional damages, well, were you very happy about this, yes, okay, emotional damages,
too, I think you are, you think you're allowed that amount, where, were you, I open the safe,
were you open the safe, did you have to drive all the way over here, yeah, and did you have to use
tool time and talent, it's a pleasure to meet you, all right, you got all those things, you know what,
I think you get, you get that amount, have a good day, and you know what, that's some gorgeous hair,
go buy some more hair product, too, why don't you get that taken care of, that would be nice,
that is awesome, where's the bear, I have not seen you two in a while, send the bear back,
send the bear in, don't forget to call your mother, okay, make sure you're there tonight for supper,
absolutely, and then, I'm gonna go ahead and keep this for lawyer watch, thank you, not like
paper clips, I need the bear to actually open the door this time, I think this is done, let's go,
I need the bear to open the door to the house, I don't think I've met you,
what just happened, why they all leave, where's the money,
where's the money, why did the bear not come in the house, I looked over, okay, I looked over,
there's a guy with a fucking bear hat, this is human arms, how much money did we lose,
they took everything, there's a guy, they just like didn't plan that,
a guy with like a big bear head is right here, uh great,
I'm trying to get in the house, but if you got in the house you would have like mauled somebody,
okay, get that out of my way, what, I lost 50 and then 15, why do we have to have five lawyers
come in, like lawyer, lawyer, lawyer, lawyer, and then the bear comes and just sits in the window
and gives me a high five, I went like this and he just ran away, that safe was in my house,
why would that ever make any sense, okay, fantastic, fucking dumb, the bear is in the window,
how would he have gotten in the window, how much money do I have left, how much money is left in
the bank, we're good, we're good, we're good, don't go that way, wait, it's this way, I want to see,
hold on, let me take the safe out of here, no, never mind, you know what, I don't feel like
doing that, I feel like watching television, yeah, I feel like watching TV, that sounds like a better
idea, I love television, I do, especially this fucked up network, which we see all kinds of
weird people, TV is now turned on, let's see what's on TV, hi, welcome back to another episode of all
the days of the week, Red in Order, Monday, Tuesday, Wednesday, Thursday, Friday, Saturday, Sunday,
Monday, Tuesday, Wednesday, Thursday, Friday, Saturday, Sunday, Monday, Tuesday, Wednesday,
Thursday, Friday, Saturday, Sunday, Monday, Tuesday, Wednesday, Thursday,
Friday, Saturday, Sunday, Monday, Tuesday, Wednesday, Thursday, Friday, Saturday,
Sunday, Monday, Tuesday, Wednesday, Thursday, Friday, Saturday, Sunday, Monday, Tuesday,
Wednesday, Thursday, Friday, Saturday, Sunday, Monday, Tuesday, Wednesday, Thursday, Friday,
Saturday, Sunday, Monday, Tuesday, Wednesday, Thursday,
Friday, Monday, Tuesday, Wednesday, Thursday, Saturday, Sunday, Monday,
that sounds like it was inside the house, something in the house, it's not a bear or anything,
it's bears, gorillas, these people, I lost all, whatever, what was that, what was that,
what is going on out here, somebody in my house, hey, what are you doing here, oh my god,
it's a person, you know the date's 2020 on this right, there's a person in my house, oh I gotta
need to get that changed, what are you, what is going on, you know, it's, you bastard, you're
gonna steal from me, Vietnamese toilets, you're not gonna steal from me, I see you're a burglar
and you're a big trouble, oh yeah, what did I steal then, you stole, what did you, I don't
know, what did you steal, did you steal anything, what are you doing in my house, oh my eyes,
oh, can I get a push, oh, you want a push, okay, I'll get you a push, here, I'll get you a gun,
all right, there you go, there you go, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, get back here, my eyes are blinded,
he's got a gun, he's got, oh shit, he's got a gun, do you see this, there's a person you can call
to, to do deal with that, what did he take, did he take anything, oh my god, why, he like shot me
the head with like a laser feasting, what the fuck was that, what was that, what, no, you are not,
I'm calling fucking cops, hello, yes, it's an emergency, yes, it's an emergency, there's a burglar
at my house and he keeps on coming to my house, send someone, I don't know, I don't know who they
are, I'm just, I'm not having very much fun, I'm sorry, send someone, thank you, god, see the thing
is, when I was a young kid, baseball team, okay, baseball team, I just got the call for that,
I would go quick, okay, okay, thank you sir, I really appreciate that, hey, this is the police,
space would be so interesting, we got you surrounded, but, oh just get in there, he's dangerous,
okay, I'm coming through, I'm coming through, life is so interesting, I'm trying for this,
how can we even get to space, it's crazy, the front door might have been open, hello, space,
it's Sheriff Tony Andrews, as data from Star Trek used to say, that's all I think about things,
that's how I feel, that's how I, excuse me, huh, it's a burglar, it's a burglar,
I've been told, I've been told you were burgling in here, what are you doing with that flashlight,
all right, put your hands up, put your hands where I can see them, what, hands where I can
see them, you own this place, you own this place, yes, this is my house, what are you talking about,
this is a house, this is a house, what do you want, this is a house, okay, listen, I got a report,
someone called the police, you called the police, I called the police, there's a person out here,
who's that guy out front then, he was stealing my jewelry, he didn't look like he had nothing,
he didn't have nothing, you don't have nothing, he had nothing, who stole something,
I don't, he was here, breaking into my house, I really don't appreciate, I really don't appreciate
you waking me up in the middle of the night to come down here, because he's a burglar,
and you got nothing, he's got nothing, great, it's a complete waste of taxpayers money,
you understand that, okay, you think that's funny, you think there's some kind of joke,
I don't think it's funny, because it seems like you think it's some kind of joke, no,
I don't think it's a joke, I mean, you might see some, I'll make a lulls in the chat, but it's not
me, okay, hold on a second, hold on, let me get this other guy, I don't know what's, other guy,
I thought I saw someone around, that's the person that is in the house, are you out of your mind,
are you still out there, listen, I don't think, did you come across a person here,
can you prove to me that something has been stolen, it looks like you literally woke up from
like a terrible nightmare, and it's just, you don't even take care of them, like,
what has been stolen from your house, I got a massive headache, um, what has been stolen,
I don't know, I have to take a look, I don't know, and if somebody broke in the house,
and they were attacking me, they shot me with a square gun, you want to look through the house,
you want to look through the house really quickly, yes, yes, I don't know, I wasn't upstairs,
okay, you give me you, okay, come with me upstairs, okay, do you feel safe right now,
no, I don't, and I don't even, with you here, I don't either, okay, you don't feel safe with me,
well, hey, because I don't think you're gonna be doing your job correctly, so, okay, well, after
you, go ahead, after you, up here, I'm gonna have you go first, just double check if there's anyone
up there, okay, I don't know, that's why, I heard noises, were you sleeping, I love this uniform on
you, it's just like, it's nothing but a police officer uniform, it's just sexy to me, I really
appreciate that, I really appreciated you saying that, you know, yeah, I think, I think it looks
good on you, looks like you've been working out, looks like you filled it out too, oh yeah, well,
I had a lot of years of training, you know, have you been training a lot, oh yeah, I'm the only
sheriff in the town, so, I mean, you got, you got these broad shoulders, and I mean, I love that,
this looks like a mess, oh, you got a safe, is that what they stole from, they stole from the safe,
they didn't steal, they didn't steal a safe, I had a problem with that earlier, come to the bedroom,
see if anything, this is a disaster in here, you gotta take care of your place, just come in here,
hello, can you just check and make sure there's nobody's in the house, you're really just going
in there, you think someone's in your house, and you just walk in the place like this, officer,
it's my house, you want me to check under the bed for you, yes I do, make sure there's no scary monsters or something, okay,
I'm gonna have to charge you for this, check out the bed, hey anyone under there,
I think I hear something, that's real funny, is somebody under the bed, what was that,
is somebody under the bed, you look under there, I don't, that's your job, I'm not supposed to do that,
what are you three years old, get down, get, come back downstairs, for the love of god,
there's no one in here, all right, there's no one in here, you're fine, you're fine, thank you officer,
appreciate it, probably, by the way, have you been to Germanin85.com, what the heck is that,
it's a place where there's a merchandise, some of it's sold out already, I like merch, I like that,
is it very, is it creative, what kind of colors you got, uh blue, black, anything else, green,
green's not a very creative color, is it is, yeah I don't know about that, green's the smartest color,
Ben Stiller told me that in a movie like 10 years ago, listen I tell you what, I'm gonna have to
give you some kind of citation, all right, why am I gonna get a citation, you don't just call the police
in the middle of the night for no reason, okay, we're busy, we're taking care of people, we're
keeping them safe, we're checking for monsters under the bed, why don't you go first, okay, I'll
go first, do you, do you hear that, was this, do you hear anything, something in here, there's zero
chance, there's zero chance, where is Amelia, I'm gonna just fall over, listen give me uh,
you give me a drink or something and I'm gonna head out, give me a drink, you want a drink,
let me give me, give me a glass of water or something, you give me, I'll get you a glass
of water, where do you keep your glasses, where do you keep your glass, like a glass of water,
get you a glass of water, Jesus, okay, oh how about this, right there, okay, get a glass of water,
can I drink this, is this portable, I wouldn't drink that, okay, all right, well hey listen,
you have any more problems, you give us a call, all right, okay, okay, thanks for doing absolutely
nothing and absolutely not helping me in one bit at all, thank you, you sure you're okay,
I'm gonna be fine, all right, but hey, if somebody's in the house and kills me,
you know, hey, good work, excellent job, call us back, all right, give us a call if something
happens, I want to sleep, what a crock of shit, I need to sleep, I need to like do something fun,
I'm so, I'm not happy at all, I feel awful, everything about today was horrible, everything
yesterday was horrible, sorry, one second, my night goggles are on, I couldn't see you properly,
I heard something in there, are you looking slimmer or is it just your, thank you, you know,
I thought I heard, your uniform, I really appreciate that, you sex machine, thank you, I do have broad
shoulders, put it there, gotcha, have a good one, I heard something in there, did you hear something,
you hear a lot of things these days, right, the news, you leave the door unlocked,
hello, any scary monsters, all right, that's fine, get a load of this guy, I can't believe that,
all right, no, no, I'm not gonna, go to the bathroom, I don't care, I don't care, not today,
don't care, kick it, oh, it's light out, I don't, I need blackout curtains, why do I keep sleeping
my sneakers on, it's gonna come off, my glasses, oh, funny anymore, it wasn't even funny the first
time I did it, four people probably thought it was funny, oh, okay, what is this, get that off,
I'm going outside, I just don't have any fun, I need to get stuff that's fun, not stuff that's
like practical, get me a fun toy, give me like a basketball or something, give me a break,
how, have you not figured out that you need a basketball, oh, look, a mystery box, oh, cool,
mystery box, the stools in it, I think, oh, look, good thing you got a mystery box, I can't,
it's a little better, hey, you're, you're in big trouble, aliens, oh, aliens, what the heck,
aliens, oh, that's kind of funny, aliens, oh, I feel better, that's a little fun,
good thing you taped it, otherwise we wouldn't know what it was,
okay, it's a bar, all right, all right, what can I get you, what can I get you, oh, here you go son,
oh, what's that, oh, can I get you over here, what can I get you, vodka tonic,
fuck off, what can I get you, oh, oh, cool, there you go, I'm having fucking fun, I don't want to
answer the door, no, I'm not answering the door, this is fun for me, this is fun for me, somebody
calling the house, hello, yeah, hey, it's Josh from Car Dealer Warranty Services USA, I've been
calling you for a couple days now about your extended warranty, but you haven't been returning
my calls, I was wondering if you had a second to talk about your car, truck, van, maybe your mini
van, SUV, anything like that, hello, are you out of your fucking mind, is there someone, are you
out of your goddamn mind, no sir, listen, I'm just calling about your car warranty, do you have
anything else to do, like go mow your lawn, go like weed your backyard, sir, sir, we actually
can insure your mower, do you have a lawn mower sir, is that something that I can help you with,
I don't have a car, why do you keep calling me, okay, no car, why is this the thing that people do now,
do you have a truck, I don't have a truck, I don't have a car, I don't have anything, I barely have,
I barely have a trash can, yes sir, are you sure you don't want a car warranty, are you sure,
because your extended car warranty is expired, that could be very very dangerous, I could get
you in a great policy, I'm gonna hang up now, if you're my front log, I'm gonna give you a fist in
the face, just letting you know, excuse me, hello, oh yeah, oh yeah, oh yeah, oh yeah, oh yeah, oh yeah,
fuck is this, oh hey, looks like I finally reached you about your car's extended warranty, is this
the homeowner, get out of here, oh my god, hi, how's it going, my name is Justin with car dealer
warranty services LLC, yeah, yeah, can I get you to sign right here, we can get it, we can get you
into a nice pack, get you to leave, it's pretty inexpensive, yeah, does that hurt, come on, it's
fine, so what do you want me to do, go ahead and just sign right there, and what does this do again,
985 dollhouse lane, 985 dollhouse lane, your car warranty is expired sir, okay and how much money
are you looking for, just go, how much 500, a month, we'll get you into a good package, this will take
care of everything, bumper to bumper, windshield to windshield, wiper to wiper, everything,
called bear, excuse me, I'm just saying, I got hair, you know the bear, I got big, what do you mean
bear, we do insure bears, do you need a car, a bear insurance warranty, do you insure yourself
from being attacked by a bear, I would have to check with corporate, but I would be willing to
bet, so just sign right there, you want my social security number, sure, social security, my social
security number is 111111111, that sounds pretty fake, but I get a commission either way man, so
go ahead, can I ask you what the commission is, nope, thank you, you gotta just, right there, I
don't want to sign, thank you, look how about this, I tell, what, how about this, sure, if you help me
clean up this house, I will sign the document, and I will, you can take it, you can do whatever you
want with it, yeah I'm definitely not gonna be able to do that, say there's a lot of people that I have
to call, they've been expecting my call, I really don't want to let them down, when you call people,
yeah, and you annoy the fuck out of them, sure, and you annoy them all day, I think, and they
hate answering your calls, do you think it's not worth like five minutes of your time to clean my,
I don't experience the same thing you do, you don't, yeah, I'm pretty sure that is completely
made up, so just sign right there, interesting, so do you ever hear about HIPAA laws, HIPAA, yeah,
no, I'm pretty sure I have insurance for that, HIPAA, like a, like a, yeah, it's like a medical
thing, I'm just trying to scare you away from my house, what do you have a party or something,
I don't know, I had, look, let me show you something, I tell you what, if there is going to be
a party, I could help you clean up, maybe I could sell some insurance, stay here, okay,
I'm all yours, man, stay here, I'll sign that, okay, wait, you haven't signed yet, no, not yet,
just stay here, hey, yeah, I'm gonna need you to come over now, and bring, bring your claws,
I do sell a refrigerator insurance and warranties, yeah, that's fine, okay, cool, just bring,
I'm gonna get a couple, get some more paperwork for you, okay, man, that's fine, yeah, by the way,
there's somebody in a pink shirt, not the black shirt, I want you to tell the bear, this is gonna
be a sick sale, not a black shirt, because I got hurt last time, okay, a house warranty, yeah,
somebody in a pink shirt, well, it's kind of like lavender, yeah, yeah, they're here now, red, just
don't go off to the person in the black shirt, black and gray, great, sounds good, okay, sounds
good, how are you, how are you, I've been waiting for you to call me back, yeah, so, so, I'll sign,
I would actually prefer to do this over the phone, if that's all right with you, you want to do it,
I feel a little bit uncomfortable not having it be over the phone, even if you just held it,
if you just held it, you don't even have to call me, yeah, yeah, okay, so, if you could just sign
on the line, okay, that would make me feel great, the bottom one here, yeah, do you like helping
people out, I don't like when people take money from people that don't deserve to get stuff taken
from them for no reason, see, this protects you from anything that might happen to your car,
I'm actually gonna put a house warranty on there for you, you got a house warranty now,
phone warranty, this covers everything, thanks, I appreciate that, thank you, is this fake,
no, that's a real signature, I mean, either way, I get the commission, that's a real
signature, I'm gonna hang the phone up because it's weird, okay, have a good day, is there a party,
you're not invited to, if there is a party, you would never be invited, okay, nine,
you're sleazeball, okay, man, appreciate you, you're, no, don't go, because you need to get
mauled, is there, excuse me, you have a mall, have you seen the mall, where is that, do you see
the mall, there's a beautiful mall that's down the street, do you need a warranty for that,
I could use a warranty for you, because eventually you might not make it, I actually, to the mall,
I might be able to sell you a warranty against me calling, that is actually a really good business,
can I ask why you call so much, it's my job, it's your job, but why do you call so much,
like every four hours, well there's a couple, there's actually a sweet old lady who loves
taking my calls, like literally we just talk, right, all the time, okay, let's, these aren't real,
these aren't real, he's lying about that too, they are, they are glasses, there's nothing,
there's glass frames in here, not even real, yeah, did I ever tell you that I have wore
prescription glasses, Jerma, your name is Jerma, right, that's the homeowner,
okay, that is the homeowner, that's what I wrote on the paper, I wrote Jerma on the paper,
okay, listen, I tell you what, I thought that I could, I could quit my job,
I could quit my job, if you help me out, hey, I'm going on in there, if you want, it's all up to you,
hey, hey, okay, if you want anything, there's some food here, okay, all right, I picture,
okay, okay, can you help me, please, yeah, sure, I'll sign, yeah, I'll sign, I'll sign for it, yeah,
there it is, there's the signature, there's the signature, hey bear, hey bear, if you want to get
both signed, it really doesn't feel good though, it really, it doesn't feel good, it doesn't feel,
thank you, thank you bear, thank you, you piss me off, wait, wait, dude, why are you,
you know how to get out, he doesn't know, no way, it's right here, the door handle's here,
it's just a demonstration of how good our warranties are, I actually hired that guy,
can I get you to sign or, I would love to, I already signed it, you can take it, all right,
man, hey, thank you, yeah, absolutely, very good, very good demonstration,
anytime, I'll give you a call, okay, thank you, I will not answer if you call ever again,
how long it takes to get somebody in a bear out in a bear costume,
takes about five to ten minutes, he couldn't even find the door, he couldn't find the door,
he got like stuck over in the corner, that was fucking crazy, oh my god, I'm gonna pee,
mystery box, I'm gonna pee my pants, if it's not, if it's not sorted out soon,
it's been scrambling backstage, bear costume, I have to pee so bad, call a, call a friend over,
okay, who am I calling over, call a friend, I have lots of friends now, I've met a lot of people in
this weird neighborhood, there's a lot of interesting characters here, um, where's the
phone, there it is, hey, I don't know who I'm talking to, but I'd love for you to come over,
I'd like to invite over, um, I'd like to invite over, hey, they can bring, by the way, they can
bring a plus one, uh, I'd like to, I'd like, I'd like Edna to come over with a plus one,
and in fact, you know what, I hope the plus one is, um, is death, by the way,
I'd like death to come over with Edna, please, thank you, good luck backstage,
because now they gotta go all out that, how about we go to the bedroom, that would be Edna and death,
I want them to come over, I want to hang out with them, I feel like it'd be a fun time,
you know, maybe I would even throw like a, maybe I would have like a party too,
good time, I want to have like a party, I'm thinking about a big party, but is the place
even ready for a party, how many people should I invite, if I have a party, how many should I
invite, everyone, I did say there was a party happening, a week ago or so, I want to get as
many people here as I can, because I want to show everybody that I'm the cool neighbor, I've got a
cool house, I've got a cool party house, and I want them to know, I'm about to piss in the bed,
I'm just gonna pee in the bed, I don't even care if they voted for it, I'm peeing in the bed,
I'm just gonna, I don't even care, they don't have to vote for that, I don't care,
oh, this place is a mess though, can I even like do anything up here,
I can't, I can't even move anything, this place is a complete disaster, it's a disaster, hungry,
I need a shower, I'm having friends come over, god damn it, I love the pillow set you gave me
though, it's beautiful, can I take a shower, please, look I pissed my bed, that's enough for
you to choose shower, thank you, why is it, I'm just, whatever, I'm throwing this out,
it's not staying in it, right, it's not staying in it, get me ready for the day,
okay, okay, good, we farted, we farted three times in 15 seconds, great,
turn that off, don't do that again, if there's a fart again, I'm gonna be very upset,
actually upset about it, oh it's not there, okay, okay, oh what an absolute mess, I wish I had a
maid that could take care of this, oh Amelia, who opened this, I didn't, disgusting, revolting,
where's my trash, oh it's over here, I need to clean it before anybody comes in,
can I at least be responsible for this junk, it looks horrible,
all I smell is like beer, there's just a beer stench, get rid of this, okay, sit that there,
put this back, whatever, good, that looks better, not as horrible looking, there's something about
like bit pieces of bread that just annoy me, they look, this looks awful, clean up, okay,
should I just drink one of these, how's that, does it look good, call the what, clean the house,
I'm trying, I'm in the middle of cleaning up the house, if people are gonna come over,
I want it to be like a dump, there, hey how about some coffee, let's make some coffee, on,
okay, coffee's brewing, coffee's brewing, I think,
is that a horn, wait what was that, hey sweetheart, hey, I brought a few friends over, you said plus
one and I improvised, there's a lot of people here, yeah, that's quite a few people, yeah,
well, you know, you said plus one, so, plus one, plus one, everyone brought a plus one,
hi, how are you, oh you got some punch, I called for Edna and death to bring a friend,
not for every single person to show up,
Amelia, looks like shit, yeah, see you didn't really clean up much,
no, because you didn't, you haven't been here, yes, I haven't,
enjoy the house, hi, it's good to see you again, good to see you again, look, if I could just talk,
please get away from us, I'm trying to talk to him, thank you, thank you very much, get away from him,
yeah, he hates fun and happiness, look, I just want to say sorry, and keeping promises,
I just want to say I'm sorry about everything that happened, I didn't expect you to come over
today, because I called two people over, but in this university called two people over,
there's been 10 people come over, so you didn't want me to come today, I thought you were going
to apologize, I mean, I did, it was a mistake that I'm here, but the, in the way this game works,
when you call someone over, 30 people show up, this isn't a game to me, death's got a pizza,
you want some, you think I want something from him, how about you two, make more pizza together,
okay, just enjoy the house, enjoy the place, let's have a party, is this stereo system,
who brought that, can we get some tunes, I'm gonna walk around and see what you've done to the place,
I just, there's no CD in here, can we get some tunes, let's get some tunes going,
all right, what a depressing life I have, okay, cool, well it looks like everybody's here,
which is weird, because I actually invited over one person,
it's actually kind of fun, what is the bear and gorilla doing here, that's what I want to know,
hi, how are you, um, please don't do that, please don't do that, please don't do that,
that's a, that's toilet paper, I have to pay for that, that's expensive, that's expensive,
I don't want to have to pay for that, that's, you have to, I don't even know who you are,
I mean, I'll have a bite, I've been seeing you people in my dreams, by the way,
you two have been in my nightmares for the last like five weeks, I don't want that,
hold on, what's going on upstairs, hold on a second, whoever's upstairs, I want to make sure
you understand that I, thank you Edna, hope you're having a good time, I didn't want a party
at all actually, hey, how are you, lawyer, nice to see you again, hey bear, hey,
hey, hey, hey, hey, thanks a lot for that, wow, yeah, well, okay, thank you,
how you guys doing, you just joined the, uh, the impromptu party that I didn't know I was having,
we were not talking, nothing, what's wrong with that, oh, she's great, she's getting out there,
a little bit, but she's gonna die, what, no, she's gonna have a great time, don't get carried away,
what are you doing here, here to bring the fun, everyone knows death and clowns work together,
great, you two have a good time, I don't care, you as well, great, I'll see you real soon,
I would like it if you put that back in your car, I thought it was an accessory, a banana,
all right, that's what I'm talking about, all right, yeah, I thought you were a dick before,
but now, let me help you, hold on, turn around for a second, no, no, wait, no, no, don't do that,
turn around for a second, turn like over here, let me just give you a hand here, uh, I need,
I think I need, I need to zip you up, because you're like, underwear is showing, let me like zip up
this costume, because his underwear is showing, he's like unzipped, I need to zip his costume,
stay right there, okay, I'm gonna, I'm gonna zip you up, if I can find the zipper, wherever it is,
of course, oh, it's buttons, so, who made a costume like this, like buttons,
of course, you're a gorilla, what am I talking about, pop a squat with me, I have a couple
questions for you, there we go, all right, I got that one, that's all you need, that's all you need,
have a good time, have a good time with the party, have a good time with the party, I don't know,
I'm just kind of, you're good to go, he kind of, all right, that's right, all right, yeah,
good time with the party, this is good shit,
I got it, I got it, I actually got it, it came down, hey,
I thought someone was calling for me, sounded like heavy machinery being used without protective
equipment, yes, it was, take a look, I got it down, look, see, we were trying to do it for less than
four hours, great, no, go ahead, go by, that's fine, all right, I'm gonna get help cleaning up,
right, yes, that's great, they've been here a few times,
I'm downstairs if you could, that'd be great, yeah, down here is good, down here is good,
just make your way over here, I got this beers in the fridge, there's, um, I might need that,
oh, hey, hey, hey guys, um, nothing, I was just talking to my lawyer friend,
and he had some interesting information, uh, if you wouldn't mind, this is, you're talking
to the lawyer about what, just, just some interesting things about this house of yours,
what's, what's wrong with it, I don't feel comfortable, I'm not a lawyer, what's the party,
we're having a good time, yeah, looking at the county records and looking at the property maps
and things, apparently this house was built on, uh, somebody else's property, maybe somebody built
on somebody else's property, somebody else owns this property that this house has been built on,
somebody owns this, okay, yeah, so technically, it's probably their house, their property,
how is that even humanly possible, I've built, this was a house that was built,
these are the county records that I've obtained, well, how long have you lived here,
a two, three weeks, not very long, not very long, are you a 985,
yeah, because I heard someone lived at 983,
okay, Jeremiah, what do you mean 983, oh, what the, I'm Ludwig, what the fuck, yes,
this entire time, well, you've been, no, no, no, no, no, we're talking, the land you built on
is 985 and maybe I passed an eye this whole time to your discrepancies,
what are you talking about, no, but after I walked in on, oh gosh, after I walked in on you
and that cretin, is he gonna be okay, well, I think he'll be fine, it's not like he can kill
himself, I don't, wait, wait, wait, come over here, I need to talk to you, show him the deed,
show me the deed, what are you talking about, I, this house has been built, I didn't, whose name
does it say there, whose house does it say, it says 983, I've been building, I'm in, I'm in
Ludwig's backyard of 983, this is, 985 does not exist, this is an official document, it's accurate,
well, how does it make any sense, you've been, Amelia, you've built on my land without asking
and I passed a blind eye because I liked you and I thought we'd get along great,
what are you talking about, how are we supposed to, how are we supposed to deal with this,
what are you talking about, you can deal with it pretty simply, deal with it pretty simply,
it's called you get out, get out of the house, it's how about you get out of my house, no,
you get out of my house, your house, look at this paper, that deed is, actually, that is a legal
document and Ludwig owns the property and the home, what the fuck are you talking about,
so you just got invited over as a party, you're my friend, the law is the law and the law is the
law, no it's not, this doesn't make any sense, how about you get the fuck out of my house,
you don't own this house, I own this land, 985 Dollhouse Way, I was having a party and I
invited everybody, actually I invited two people but you all showed up because everybody in this
neighborhood, well I thought you wanted to hang out with me, maybe apologize, everybody in this
neighborhood just cracked apparently and everyone's on drugs, first thing you said to me when I walked
in is you didn't clean the house enough, I didn't even know you were Ludwig and then you took the
mask off, does that matter, does that mean you need to treat me with respect if I'm Ludwig,
okay, it's great, sounds great, that's impossible for me to, that makes no sense,
don't log into my account, don't stream on that account either, come on let's go discuss this,
no, what do you mean evict me, I'm kicking him out of this house, no one's evicting me, this is my
property, I live here, is the sheriff here, no one's evicting me, hey I need your help, Ludwig don't
let him stream on my account please, well I'm not worried about him streaming on your account,
follow me, I got banned from, hey can you help me, I got banned from Twitch, I need some muscle,
where's the sheriff, I can represent, can you represent, yes I can represent, Stevenson, Stevenson,
Stevenson and Randy, I got banned from Twitch last weekend, I'm gonna need you to help me, I can,
could you follow me, yeah I could follow you, this is my kitchen, yeah your kitchen, oh now you feel
bad, it's my house, it's not even your house, it's my house, you built up my property and maybe if you
treated me nicer this wouldn't happen this way, I don't even know your name, oh there's the sheriff,
what do you mean the sheriff, get off me, where's my bare friend, he's the only person I like here,
well he's hopefully not here, oh that should be officer right now, thank you, it's my door,
I'll take it, yeah, oh sheriff, what are you doing, I'm trying to help, I'm, hey, but we gotta follow
the law, we gotta follow the law, he's trespassing, what's going on here, he's trespassing and I want
him out of my house, who, this guy right here, you have proof, book him, yeah I've got proof,
let me see it, right there, that is a legal document I obtained from port, well what do you
think it says, okay, I mean it says you, I, well okay, because it's my property, it's your property,
my property, listen, I'm sorry man, you gotta come with me, it's all legal, listen, it's legal,
put your hands behind your back, it's not legal, what the fuck, all right, oh I'm actually hurting
real life, there you go, that's right bear, book him too, all right, all right, you're coming with
me, all right, man, listen, all right, calm down, all right, calm down, boo, fine, I'll go, fine,
what the fuck is this, I'm so sorry about this nuisance, I'm sorry about that, come on, can you,
can you rep for me and just say, what's wrong with you, you're stealing some of the pranks,
you can keep the punch, welcome to Ludwig's dollhouse, housewarming gift,
that's a great part, it's a good time, hey, welcome to Ludwig's dollhouse,
you got him off earlier, sorry if that hurt, are you spiking the punch, all right,
you're just gonna leave after spike, thank god I'm a maid, all right, my house now, what does it
smell like cigar smoke, what the zuck happened here, oh it's terrible, should I call my own maid or am
I my own maid, why is there, okay, I imagine that doesn't belong there, all right, I'll ignore that,
it still smells like cigar smoke, god, I can't clean this, how do you even begin to clean this,
there's no trash can for giant drywall, that was covering the paint, okay, right,
clean that back up, I think the posters are sold out but we could maybe sell that one and I'll take
that cut, oh fresh baked cookies, well that's ugly, oh this is a fashionable robe, okay, it's really
wet, okay, that's kind of gross, well that's kind of gross, I'll just take the cookies and be gone,
gone, having less autonomy is just a living hell, oh now I get to make the bed, okay,
that makes a lot of sense, clean and make bed should be symbiotic,
do I have to make the piss bed or can I sleep on the children's bed, you know what the worst
kind of people are, the people who buy sequin pillows and do this, like what do you think you
are Houdini, it's just a pillow, relax, what does he even do all day, I'm not gonna bother with this
room, German must still be home, I should kick him out, oh god, smells like shit in here, right,
that's, that was the laugh track moment, maybe he had some, it's a little late, shower time, okay,
uh how would I do this, let's just, you know this is not my first time doing this live,
okay no peeping toms, you know what the worst thing you can do in a shower is, piss or shit in it,
it's like other people might use it, you know, I'll do it sometimes but still pretty deplorable
of me, you know, nothing wrong with pissing as long as you don't shit, all right, that's enough
shower, that should be, I feel clean enough, there it is, is there another maid service in this town
or am I the only maid, why are there so many stools, okay, uh what was the point of kicking out
Jerma, I have two houses now, I could have just charged him rent, I mean at the end of the day
all he asked me to do was just go on one date, it sounded like we were dating,
he deserved it, oh it's gonna be tiring, you know if someone really wanted to,
they could have me take a nice bed, I've seen how you make Jerma act, you don't have to act
the same with me, we can have a good relationship, you know, actually follow through with love
stories and not just burn them to the ground by having sex with death, just an option I guess,
what's the point of parties, it's too many people to even have a conversation with,
every conversation is dull shit, seven people told me they're gonna go to Japan but COVID hit,
I don't give a shit, maybe I should call him back sometime, I'm tired, go jogging, go jog,
so it doesn't matter who's in the titular role, people said oh no it's just because it's Jerma
that we treat him poorly, but perhaps really you just treat everyone poorly who comes into this
room, even given the pope you'd probably still make him go jogging as he's fatigued, who do you
treat nicely, oh jogging, oh hello, are you doing jumping jacks and cigar smoke, is someone ready to
get fit, are you ready to go for a run, let's jog together, okay let's go, come on,
high knees, get them up, okay, there we go, we're yummy mummies, okay, we're yummy mummies,
can we turn around, can we turn around, I'm a bit tired here, are you winded already,
I'm just a bit tired, okay let's do a cool down, come on, just maybe a cool down, you're looking
great, thank you, knees up, let's go, these are high, yummy mummies, knees are high, well I'm
getting tight in the tummies, aren't we, oh gee, oh,
yeah Christmas, this is amazing, is it even Christmas time, it hasn't even been much colder,
but this is great, wow, that doesn't seem festive, but maybe for birthdays, why are there so many
cigars, now wait a second, it feels as though it's a bit short, maybe for the previous tenant,
make sense, go back outside, go back outside, okay good, garden the flowers, I feel like I've
spent a lot of time in here, the flowers, these flowers, garden, okay, they need rich nutrients
and maybe some water, oh hey, how are you, I'm looking for, was it Jeremiah or, what was his name,
Jeremiah, what do you have there, well listen, I felt kind of bad the other day, we had a little
bit of a run around about something, I wanted to give him 100 bucks, you know, oh, you seem really
nice, did you, nice to meet you, well you know what, he just left, okay, but he said you'd stop by,
yeah, I want you to know, I really like what you did with the place out here, it looks real nice,
thank you, you picked that yourself, yeah, I would have gone taller, but you know, how about you come
in, okay, how about you come in, I mean, I didn't want to stay long, so you own the house now,
you know what, yeah, I own it, but he comes in and out, so you know, I'll just hold on to it for you,
I mean, listen, I was gonna give him 100 bucks, and listen, I'll give you, you know,
you know, okay, camo, it doesn't really work on you, because you stick out, like a sore thumb with that
okay, beautiful body of yours, I really appreciate it, I'd suggest other clothing, I am married,
okay, married to the game, I am married, so, I'm physically married, I'm just going to, yeah, I'm
gonna give that to you, well hey, you're a looker, but don't tell nobody I said that, you know,
yeah, if you're ever interested, okay, 985, 985, and 983, I actually own both, okay, yeah,
I love what you did with the place, thank you, you look great, yeah, legal dispute, hey, anytime
you need electricity, anytime you need electricity, there's an extension cord already, and I can just
use it, it's yours, okay, that's convenient, I feel like it'd be a huge headache, okay,
pee-pee, poo-poo, or eat-eat, we gotta pick one, because right now it's, well, it's a little all
over the wall, it seems gross, but they kind of look appealing, oh, clean, yeah, I'll just, this
seems to be somewhat stereotypical, feels like we could have respected maybe the job more, and
and been like, oh, maybe that's, that's, that's what they do day to day, so perhaps,
you know, they could take care of the rest of what they got going on,
but I'll clean, I'll clean, I've cleaned this place before, and do it again,
admittedly, all the utensils were me, so I can't be too upset, what is this, small pinata,
does this have actual pizza in it, what, why is it so red, how do you get pizza that red,
is it made with beets instead of tomatoes, it's so, it's a week old, why would you put,
I would have eaten that, okay, I get the white bread thing now,
there's so much alcohol, does he ever drink water, is there a way to drink water in this
house, or is it only unmarked sodas and unmarked beers, oh, sorry, I'm not allowed to do that yet,
okay, but if anyone wanted to feed me, that's what I would do, but for now, I'm staying hungry,
had someone wanted that to happen, that's what could happen, but we'll never know,
well, this room's not bad then, I'm anxious just being here, I have to work, why am I being cold
by Elvin men, I'm a maid, is this for the king, you know, it's been a pretty long day, I had a few
different things to worry about last week, I had a couple of payments that I was a little laid on,
it's been kind of a difficult time, and I'm wondering, I think looking for a rail, this is
the only job I had, this is cleaning this house, whose house am I, did I say it, oh gosh,
uh, just on my way to work, how's it going, peasant, well, good day,
Ludwig or Amelia works generally, but thank you, good day to you too,
I own two houses, it doesn't make a lot of sense to go to work,
I could just rent out a house, doesn't add a lot of value to society, but
it's a good way to accumulate wealth, but nothing over 2.6 million, that would be too much, frankly,
all right, why did I leave it open, if you leave both open, it kind of ruins the illusion,
never mind, but do people just come to my house, let me take off my work uniform,
okay, can we do one thing that's good for me, all right, shower, piss, eat, sleep, I think all of
them would be pretty helpful right now, play outside, yeah, that makes a lot of sense,
no, I have to piss, oh yeah, play outside, hey, whoa, does this get us in trouble,
oh, it's fun, good performance, can I do something good for me, I don't want to be outside,
I'll just, I'll hover near things that I would like to do, and maybe, maybe, you know, it's like a
hint, didn't close the legs then, didn't mean to do that, it's more looting, okay, there's already
a lot of piss in the bed, oh, I feel like having a bedroom through a room with a reciprocating saw
and a sledgehammer, and a knife that is far too sharp, and a bunch of broken drywall isn't the
safest way to live life, wow, look at this, maybe still available, I don't know, all right,
what are you doing in my house, you're gifting me cookies, no, stop gifting me, okay,
you didn't trap us in here, you sit on the stool, what are you doing in my home, oh yeah,
no, no, no, no, force, it's you,
you couldn't even be a proper man, a shadow boxer, you know how hard it was, to get
involved in that group, what is it like, they're auditions, what do you mean, no,
just hold on, delete, the save, delete, there's a save, file, you need to delete, we're
gonna start it over, what's, delete, the save file, we're gonna start from a new house,
delete the save if you could delete save file oh delete the save delete it right now we're gonna
start over i can't do this anymore you can't only be in my house not gonna happen no way
not a chance at hell am i gonna let this happen you don't live here but i i earned it you can't
just redo it no i can redo it because then i'm gonna redo the save and we're gonna start a new
game starting right now it's a lot of piss hello production production i'd like to start a new
save file please what no i get to keep it no you what's your big plan now again run the poll again
you can't run the poll again run it again run the poll again this is my house is my domain
this is my house what are you saying it's it's rain you're just gonna run the ball again okay by
the way let me see you do this let's see how fuck let's see if you deserve this house beat you to it
you did you did beat me to it you did oh do it again ready one two just delete the save no i'm
better than that ross delete the same file guys i won't call you anymore if you do you can come in
you can come in i won't call you if you delete the save file we're on the pole again we're starting
to save file over i'm not doing this this is my house this is my you can delete the same file
ready if you want one two three
i'm literally erasing your names from my call list if you delete the same file you can come in
okay there's a wall but perhaps he heard through the wall thin walls i can you're inviting me into
your home okay come in and we need to start the save over can we start the same start the
no again one percent voted yes and the one percent runs this just like it should be
delete the file guys run it again run it again until he says it's within one percent it looks
like 99 percent said no i am literally deleting all of your names off of my call list if you
delete the same you need to restart the game because like it's all look i need control again
for goodness sake people are just coming in the house and i didn't even they i don't even know
they were coming in you think it's worth restarting you think you could change things
i think so well i can help you run things so far last two days it's not easy is it no i couldn't pee
or shower exactly or eat it sucks i think they're trying to kill me they are they did kill me they
already killed me once he's gonna delete the same what's the issue why are you deleting the
save file they're gonna delete the same file i don't know how you open it here what's the issue
the issue is hey gg hey hey uh what's going on here i forgot your name i just
delete the same i literally don't delete the same why are we deleting i don't know why they're not
deleting are you gonna cheat on me this time no of course i would never do that to you again
delete the save file i would i would appreciate it if they deleted the save just delete the save
we can get out of this place they said no again why are you keeping us in this prison
why i'm trying to release everybody but they won't let us go i'm happy to rerun it if you
don't screw me over delete the save file delete the safe just delete what if you guys pull like
a rock paper scissors rock paper scissors deleting the same okay okay yeah okay please come on one two
three go that's a bang right that's a bang right that's illegal that is a legal win that's a legal
win who is that we're trying to get him to just turn the save file
you can just come on up be a yummy mommy and just delete the save file it's not hard that is
i mean what if we just do aerobic workouts until they i'm not gonna work out to the
movie we're all just be here all day until they delete the same file done these enduring events
it should go about a month don't you want that could be you if you don't delete the save file
delete the safe i don't know if you should threaten them that's true i meant that metaphorically
speaking hello come on shaders clogs can we end it now delete the safe just delete the safe
what's going on please come on i want to give a little bit of a move to production here if we
should give them the choice again just yeah give them give them the choices should we let them do
this again yeah just delete it just end it should we just should we delete it can i just veto and
delete the game they have to vote it they have to vote yeah okay let's go to be democratic you
have battleship bloodlake or uh i have some battleships downstairs so oh my god i thought
that was a knife holy god i'm just here to fix stuff you know hey how did he get in here you
guys want to say something cool how did you even get in here check this out uh don't worry about
that oh it's so cool watch this you know the kitchen down there yeah yeah i'm gonna blow your
mind yeah how yeah it's called super mario mark magic someone's got a loose stool
that is good this sounds like your friend's here what's wrong with his head why does he
have like a bunch of tape on his head i think he had a hat before oh yeah is it like a new game
plus option new game plus new game plus save file oh we need to restart start hit yes speed
how would you do things this time yeah anything different i would hopefully i would eat more i
would jog more i would go to the bed in the bed more often how would you do it different how would
i do it differently yeah i'd add i'd add another room another one yeah i'd add another room story
or add on to the second i would go to another room you guys deleting the same yeah we're deleting
the same now right yes it's been fun guys save us from this prison i feel so bad for the person
in the bear costume because they have they've had to change like 12 times are they deleting it
do they do did you do it oh oh a mailbox
yay whose house is this this is my house let me give it a check hey in there hello can you hear me
why don't we give it one more check i'm here that was a voice crack in the first 10 seconds
hello uh i just want to say real quick that on august 30th at 4 p.m pacific we're going to do
behind the scenes show so those of you that want to watch it if you want to see what how this kind
of played out over the last uh like six seven months uh it'll be on my channel we'll see you
on august 30th at 4 p.m pacific a lot of people over here that worked on this and i can't be
happier i'm very proud of everybody it's such a fun show we'll see you on august 3 everybody get
out get in here why not just nobody hurt me please this is what this is the kind this is the amount
of people it takes to make this show happen you understand these are actors these are people behind
bring it all out take a bow all of you and look at that screen
every every every single person here had an incredibly important role and without them
without every single person here it doesn't happen thank you to the sponsors thank you
to twitch thank you to coinbase we'll see you on the 30th see you later i just kicked the ball