What? Oh, right. Look, I cannot be responsible if you're going to bet on this shit.
Uh, hello. How are you? Good to see everybody. Where's my coaster? I have a coaster or something.
There we go. He is responsible. Hope you're doing well, everybody. Let me tweet this.
Let me get this frog out of my throat. Okay, so today we're going to complete Pikmin 2.
I'm going to finish it. We're going to go over a few things. Some very important things.
3.6 million points. Half of you guys are going to be rich and half of you are going to be broke
in channel points. If this keeps going on the way that it is. 22,000 points. Omega low.
But anyways, we've got a lot of things to talk about. Streams are going to be a little different.
Not anything major. Just something a little different. So for the next...
It's today. It is the 12th. For the next three weeks, streams are going to be shorter.
We're going to pull back the streams a little. Because on March 6th, it's going to be a very
major stream. I can confirm with 100% certainty, with absolute certainty, the archaeology stream
will be happening on Saturday, the 6th of March, at 1 p.m. Pacific time. That's true. Yes, the
archaeology stream is happening before the Catboy stream. You don't have a date for that one. I'm
not giving you a date for that one. You're just going to have to be watching, okay?
That is not a Catboy stream. I'm going to make that very clear. It's not a Catboy. No Catboy
Archaeologist. No, that's not happening. That's a separate stream. So there's a lot of stuff that
we're doing. There's a lot of work that we're doing on this. It should be a lot of fun. I hope
it is. But got to put time into it. So I'm still going to be streaming, but just not the same
amount of time. We'd rather... What were you saying? We'd rather longer streams than four hours of one
gimmick stream every six months. That's what you want. What about what I want? Is this your channel?
Do you run the show here? Do I give you the keys? You want the keys to the house?
I'll give them to you. You want them? Here, take them. Run it. Man, you ain't getting these
fucking keys. They're mine. It's going to be a lot of fun. You have several billion dollars in debt.
I think we own this. No, no, no, no, no, no. The collateral for that debt was not the channel.
It was my Funko Pop collection. That was my collateral. And when I went in and got the loan,
I told you. You got just $62 in collateral for your $5 billion. How's that? No, but in all honesty,
yeah, I'm going to do what I want to do. That's the way it is. That's the way it's always been.
You might be a new viewer. That's the way that this has been for almost a decade. Not sure how
long you've been watching, but that's how we do it. I was going to scream. Let's go as loud as I
could. Let's go. This guy spent almost $100 on Funkos. Oh, God. Can you imagine? He wants to be
a cat boy. All right, you ready to go? Are we ready to play? I'm not doing this on camera ever
again. I promise you that. All right, let's get it over. Whoa, I almost turned the stream off.
That would have been bad. It was not on, right? All right, where are we going? Where were we off
to? It was on. No, it wasn't. Shirtless Andy. How close am I to the end of the game? Am I almost
done? A few hours or something, right? I drained that pool the last time, right? I'm not putting
the face game on. No, I don't care. You're not getting that. There's a whole post-game area? Oh,
cool. All right. All right, so I want to go to that pool that we drained. I'm going on an adventure
with blue because somebody said that it's all blue, right? Blocking the goddamn Wiimote sensor bar
with a cup of coffee. You look less handsome today, Jerma. No, I look great today. You know
how I know? Because I got one of those apps that scans your face and tells you how hot you are.
I got an 8.5. I'm going to go on a grind mission today. I downloaded this app called
Are You Ugly or Not? It scans your face. You hold it up to your friend and it goes
across the forward-facing camera and then it says you're ugly confirmed. They look at the camera
and they're like, what? It takes a screenshot of their reaction. It's fucking hilarious. Okay,
where am I going? And then they go, what's this app? Is this a prank? Where am I going? All right,
shower room. Is that a spoiler? I need to kill stuff. I need to grind to pick up some blue guys.
That's a good place to grind to get blues. Anybody know? Just kill animals, right? All right,
pull back. Blue, put it to blue. You're going blue, right? I want blue. Not here and it's not
a good place to do it. Grind? They all live? Yeah, what do you mean? They're fine. What are you
talking about? All right, I want blue on there. How many blues should I get to go into the shower
room? Does it matter? No, I want the good red. A little Pikmin chant noise has been what?
5k Andy. Shut up. Whatever. The fact that that person voted oh, megalul after that. It's like,
come on, dude. It's like, look, I'm going to be really honest. I think that's funny every time.
I don't know why. It's like rude. That's wicked rude, isn't it? I got only five. I don't know. I
don't know. I think it's funny. The submerged castle in the shower room. All right, well, hold
on. Let me. I need to get all blue, right? That's what you guys told me. You told me that you need
a blue for that one. 5k Andy. That's wicked funny, dude. Oh, shit. Maybe 6k Andy. Castle is blue,
not shower. Okay. So the shower, I can just go with whatever I want. Well, I got some blues.
That's good. I need a different team then. Who the fuck is Andy? Well, look, you got like five
straight years of like Twitch dialogue that you have to go through. I'm not going to tell you all
about that. I'm going to take 25 blues. I can't wait till 50 years in the future go by. And there
are historians that are going to have to be like memeologists. That won't be like a weird thing to
say. 30 red. How many yellows do I want? Some of you guys are going to be fucking 80 years old
on like the history channel talking about like Kappa and like explaining what it is.
It's called a historian. Well, yeah, but like that's not what you'd be called. It is. It's not,
though. You're a memeologist. You're a meme historian. Yeah, whatever. Okay. I want to go
to that shower. It's over here on the right, right? Yeah. Wait, isn't there... I saw eggs.
Fuck it. Who cares? We'll get those later. 98. What do you mean 98? Get over here. Get over here.
Meme historian. Yeah. Okay. Meme historian Andy. Yep. So you'd be like Jeffrey Anderson and
underneath it would say meme historian Andy. All right. Nobody's going to die from this, right?
Okay. This is... I should be good. Whoa. Whoa. Whoa. Whoa. What do you mean 63 out of 100 entering?
What are you talking about? Get over here. Why do they stop? Why do they stop? What are you guys
doing? Get over here. 90 out of 100. What? Guys, why are they detaching from me?
Come here. Oh my god, you idiot. 85. What are they doing? What do you mean 84? What are you
talking about? What? Why did I just lose another... What the hell is going on? What happened to the
other ones? I'm so confused right now. I don't understand. I had 100. Where the fuck did they
go? Okay. They're just buried into the corner? That was really bizarre. They're just stuck in
this corner, deep buried into here. Oh, fuck off game. Give me a break. Yeah, of course. There
you go. It was a bunch of small blue Andes. Okay. Whatever. Sorry. All right. So this is the shower
level. I'm looking forward to this. Wait, wait, wait, wait. Whoa. Back up. All right. I got to...
All right. We need... That's fire, right? Whoa. I'm resetting. I'm resetting. I'm going to reset.
I'm going to reset. That was fucking bullshit. He killed almost every blue Pikmin. I'm resetting.
Okay. I'm resetting. We're resetting. That's a reset. I'm just going to turn the console off
and we'll come back. God damn it. Hold on. Just here. There's some cool... Look at this artwork.
Look at this artwork. God damn it. Really? The first thing I do... All right. If he didn't kill
almost every single blue Pikmin, I wouldn't have cared. But like that was... He wasn't... The guy
wasn't even on screen. He was off screen when he did that. That's fucking horseshit. No, I'm not
living with that one. I don't care. It's dumb. How come my Wii pointer's not working? The hell?
The Wii pointer doesn't work anymore. What the fuck is happening? I actually cannot... The pointer's
not on the screen anymore. God, how much was this thing selling for when it came out? I hope it was
like 50 bucks. Not like 500. How much fucking was this console? What the... Hold on. Let me pick up
my brick over here with a screen on it. Let me go over... Hold on. One sec. Wii sensor bar settings.
Give me the... Hold on. Wait, wait, wait. How's the sensitivity? Why did this thing change sensitivity
randomly? This doesn't make any sense. What the fuck is happening? Oh, the ooey gooey. This doesn't...
I don't... I have no idea what's going on. Why is it doing this? My Wiimote doesn't even work anymore.
I'm not even kidding. I swear to God. The Wiimote's not even showing up on the screen.
What the... Where's the Wiimote? It thinks I'm holding the Wiimote upside down.
What the hell are you talking about? This thing better have been fucking less than 40 dollars
when it came out. This is a 40 dollar machine. At most, by the way. At most. The Wiimote upside down?
No! What the fuck is it doing this for? I'm gonna take the batteries out. There's usually... The two
dots are side by side. Why is it... So I'm tilting the controller. It's 30, 40 degrees sideways now.
I'm gonna just... There's supposed to be two dots right next to each other. I just did this before
I turned the stream on. Like, I literally just did this before the stream turned on 20 minutes ago.
Fucking 40 dollar machine. Look at some artwork. I'll be right back. Sensor bar below TV.
Repair this fucking thing. I don't understand. Why is it doing this? Because I turned the console off?
Check the TV for more information. Some explanations can be scrolled using this. No,
I don't have any info on the TV. I think this Wiimote just broke. Dude, this Wiimote just is
bricked. It's not even turning on anymore. What? Why? How? What? What? No, it's not. All right,
hold on. I've just received the batteries. What the fuck is going on? Dude, it's... This thing is broken
as hell. This shit's broken. I don't know what to do. What do I do? Let me try to read. This is
ridiculous. I have no idea what's going on. I seriously have no idea. I don't know why it's
doing this. It's not like Cheeto dust on the front of the camera or something, right?
Put in new batteries? It was at like 60%. Let me see if it works. It won't even show up on the
screen. I'm sorry. This is just bizarre. A $40 console. This is the longest fail bit ever. I wish
this was a joke. It's a... No, it's not a joke. It's a $40 at most console. Would they sell this for
fucking 500 bucks? The Wiimote's broken. It's actually broken. I can't use it. I actually
cannot even point at the screen anymore. Whatever. Me turning the console off and turning it back on
bricked the Wiimote. Let me get new batteries. Give me one second. This is stupid. I'll be right
back. Okay. So I did the tried and true method. The tried and true method is I smacked it like
three or four times and now I have two dots. I don't know why. For some reason, I thought
it was a really dark camera and you could see me. I was naked in front of this or something.
All right. Let's go. I didn't want to cancel that. Three nipples? What? Get out of here.
Those are my nipples. Okay. That's best one guy. That's best one guy moment of the week at least.
All right. Let's go. Just moving around. Oh my fucking god. This fucking console. I swear to
god. What is it doing? Leave me alone. I don't want to log back in. Go to the Miiverse? No. Go
to hell. How does that sound? I don't want to go to the fucking Miiverse. Get out of here. Okay.
So, hey everybody. Welcome to the stream. Today, we're going to be playing Pikmin 2. I'm going to
be jumping back into Pikmin 2. I'm going to finish the game tonight, get to at least a place where
I get to the end game, mess around for a little bit. Oh yeah, by the way, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah,
you guys real quick. Streams are going to be pulled back a little. Streaming for like only make three
or four hours of streams instead of four or five. Working on a couple of big projects. You just want
want to let you know make sure you got those dates saved March 6 by the way if
you don't that's the first one there'll be other ones right after that too
pretty soon after that I gotta buy got a whole baseball stream to do which I
can't wait for mainly because it's already it's already done just couldn't
do it cuz of COVID that's what that's gonna be my favorite stream I've ever
done by the way I'm gonna make I'm gonna make that really clear to you guys
whenever the baseball stream happens that will that's gonna be my favorite
stream I have ever done I'm serious that's gonna be my magnum opus it will
alright now don't die to the giant fucking frog that will be my favorite
thing I've ever done I don't even care how bad it is it doesn't matter alright
let's go watch out for the frogs what about Shpee you know what you're right
it'll be close it's gonna be very close to Shpee you're right put it in there
peeked at Shpee yeah I'll find it whatever everybody says that like
Seinfeld season four is the best season right they still made four or five more
years of that show and everybody still liked it so it doesn't matter don't
throw the flowers in wait they don't come out as flowers oh shit okay I
thought they came out as flowers if you threw a flower in it's my bad that's my
bad I didn't know all right let's put this up here I want all the more to get
yellow here all the more and then I want I want Louie to do red okay what's over
this way electricity you hang out here go take care of the electricity that's
fire over there when you electricity break this down fire going after anything
else in there all right get the fire he is a he's a blue nose that's water okay
he's got that's a guy he's got a blue nose never mind come back everybody I
thought that was a fire guy we need water this guy is gonna piss me off I
need I gotta kill that guy like now I have to kill that guy right now with
purples I hate these guys I'm freaking out everyone run run run run run you're
fine you're fine fine fine fine fine fine you're fine you're fine you're
fine you're fine come back come back come back you're fine he's not fine he's
dead get this stupid thing out of the way kill it kill punch him all right good
all right now it's your turn get in there break up separate get out of the
way mega lol you didn't say the o part you got that wrong all right do a jump
and then we go good good I've been told somebody told me that these the guys are
the hardest ones in the game they said that the poly wogs are the hardest it's
a German be careful you're gonna rage the poly wog and I'm like I probably I
probably will I don't know that went a lot smoother than the last one he
doesn't know mega well okay everyone else can come through now we're just
writing omega low why is everyone is writing mega low streamer is unaware
oh that's what that's a what is that that's a juicer it's like a lemon
squeezer let's get the light lemon squeezer crew go for it
oops I think everyone alright where the juicers juicers you're not you're not
gonna you know the banana bros that's not who you guys are I'm sorry you're
the drew crew yeah or at least another couple few months ninety nine thousand
you can't juice a banana um no no you I guess you can't you can though I guess
if you juiced a banana if you just ran a banana through a blender and like
strained it and pushed on it and through the strainer wouldn't like you
wouldn't water come on there's some this water content in banana yes there is
it's the same thing yeah that's just that is the same thing why is that
person saying that then that's it for so why this is protecting nothing here
banana smoothie yeah somebody said you can't juice a banana but juicing a
banana is just like a banana smoothie it's just like the like the water
content and the pulp and sugar content inside of the banana you can pump any you
can pump any non viscous liquid for anything you wanted just call it chunky
juice yeah it's the same shit I need some of the gas and yeah I need a gas
guzzler no not you guys just the gas guzzlers please and don't wake that guy
up should do the GTA role-playing stuff you know I've always kind of wanted to
do that but I just really never understood or knew how to even start or
would even talk to or what to even do you guys should know this by now getting
me to install even a patch for an old game to make it work better is like hard
for me to do like installing a full like complete conversion mod to a game or
something or sir I don't know I don't know how I don't don't even know where
to start and but I wouldn't do it long term though that's the one thing if I
was ever gonna do like a GTG TRP or something would be I would just be like
grandpa for a weekend and then I don't know hopefully so hopefully somebody
would just kill me I don't know like I would just want to get hit by a bus
after a weekend of doing it and this is never come back all right this guy's
gonna be a problem in GTA yes in GTA I don't that's a that's a new enemy I
don't know what that is can they get what do they get it okay I gotta be
careful about this shit ready watch out for the meteors you woke up where they
going okay good oh shit battery yeah that's exactly what's in here right now
Duracell I have Duracell's in the Wiimote right now and I think it's so
holy shit there's a lot of treasure hey get out of here or please don't walk out
in front of a bus that's a really I'm not I'm talking about like my character
getting hit by a bus in GTA I would just do it for two straight days or three
days like Friday Saturday Sunday or something like Saturday Sunday not this
coming Saturday Sunday I'm just saying like in general there's a lot of money
plus aren't a lot of these servers are hard to get into like it's not just a
question I can't just be like hey I want to stream I'm streaming on GTRP see
you tomorrow thanks for the invite it's not how it works
you're a 7k Andy it'll be fine yeah I'm but that I would rather not I would
rather like okay if somebody really was into GTRP I would rather them get the
spot then then then fucking 10k Andy over here just being like hey let me in
tomorrow yeah I'm gonna like me a grandpa for two days he wishes he was
10k excuse me 7k yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah everybody back up I want to get
rid of I got a lot of money this one I like this one careful down there no my
point is if I was gonna do RP I'd want to just kind of have fun with it for a
little bit and I don't want to like hop in front of somebody especially if
somebody was way back up back back back back back back back back back back oh he
killed him okay hold on shit sorry eat him that's fine he'll die whatever what
was I saying yeah well I don't want to like just jump in front of a line or
something if it was possible just because I wanted to do it if there were
people that actually like our paying and stuff and I don't know like German on a
fire just fucking rolls on it and says I'm gonna play tomorrow rather somebody
like that actually wants to do it and is into it really to get that spot you know
don't crush any fucking pick many swear to God there is no line oh okay oh no
treasure yeah I'm good I don't know what that thing is but we're just gonna leave
I don't know that is but we're gonna leave don't ever do GTA RP well I
haven't done it because I haven't and never had like really the real I never
I don't know I just did I wasn't really that into it before it could be fun to
do for a little bit those guys look like their electricity I don't know but I'm
gonna say they are and make myself feel better by using electricity guys to
fight those all right what are you what do you do are they friendly back up back
up back up everyone follow me who's just going over here okay I'm I guess I'm
gonna take the yellow over there just to see you electricity I feel like you
it's a they're jellyfishes I don't know what do something what are they moves do
a move they do a big suck that is they just do a big suck that's it they don't
have electricity it's a big suck okay I guess they're not electricity all right
well we got a I got I got a I don't want to fucking kill everybody come on turn
turn turn in let's go everybody let's do it follow me we're going in do please
don't kill everybody please don't kill everybody please don't kill everybody
hi oh my god I know where they are he died I got back up back up fuck I'm missing a few
people where are they oh fuck where why are they just sitting around stop
sitting around they're dying whatever eat it and die get a bad stomach ache
okay I'm gonna weigh it down weigh it down weigh it down weigh it down weigh
it down overwhelming power overwhelming numbers good there we go okay now this
is safe hey bring that guy back bring this guy back we're looking for treasure
spun out of control that's a bigger one that's literally that's a German 985
enemy I don't know what it is and it's freaking me out I in fact I think that's
on my old logo on YouTube I think that the exact creature okay it just has a
mega suck that's all that's what it does so we have to overwhelm it I guess it's
a mega suck I don't know I guess I'm just gonna go for it watch out he's
gonna mega suck he's gonna do the mega suck everyone run okay now go what move
move he's gonna mega suck kill it okay oh shit he dropped a nice all right we
got two treasures here we got a makeup kit and she shells this one's kind of
big all right let's take this down what's over here
oh there's like a tin can in here little you go collect everybody do it she sells
seashells by the seashore she sells seashells by the seashore she sells
seashells by the seashore she sells seashells by the seashore oh good there
I almost lost it a few times I almost lost it twice come on Louis get it oh
that's cute I love that I love how that's just a top of a soda this person
there I really enjoy your content even if your IQ is room temperature at best
but in loving your material I've come to realize it's not about you because who
cares about you really it's my birthday so yeah you should kind of like um I
don't know maybe wish me a happy birthday oh you guys it banned that guy
we got like a couple of bands today going around what's going on here why
won't he say happy birthday cuz I I get to decide who I say happy birthday to
this isn't cameo whoa where's everybody didn't kill anybody what he didn't kill
anyone I think I just got glitched I think I just got saved by a cutscene the
cutscene actually saved their life Wow that's unbelievable okay cool all right
we're good happy birthday okay so that's good oh wait wait wait wait wait was
there's an egg here I want to have people drink I need I want something to
slurp because I want where was that I saw there was an egg somewhere wasn't
there let's show up on the map the egg show up on the map no where was it
isn't there an egg am I losing my mind was there an egg you dick
okay there's another there's another suck demon in that other room yeah there
is I swear to God there was a I'm going crazy uh well whatever let's just go
do I have to go across the water whatever I guess I wanted
oh my god guys I tried to separate them I'm so glad they fixed that in
Pikmin 3 fuck I have to bring them over here over here come get me these guys
meet me can I make it if I throw them and I throw the purple guys this far I
can all right so you guys just you guys take care of this shit
catboy what are we gonna get catboy turn sir and you're gonna be kept or
sir sir give us a date I only have one date to give you and it's March 6th and
that is for the archaeology stream that's the only data I have for you right
now you need to reschedule it I'm working then um it'll be available when
you can play slime rancher we're playing slime rancher tomorrow tomorrow is slime
rancher I pull this out I don't like this camera someone's gonna jump out of
the I'm gonna get jump scared but they would definitely not be this long of a
hallway but something's gonna jump out and attack us I'm getting the purple
ones ready I know it's gonna happen I can maggot lair I'm gonna run right into
a bunch of those big swarm bee things this is a hold on wait I'll be doing
this but where they're going where you going wait wait wait wait wait wait
wait don't just go don't just run around without where are they going okay they
drop down here the flowers give you just cash oh cool all right
oh nice drink up this game is really fun all right so this is yellow I think it's
just changing colors okay what do I need more any blue get rid of some red I
want I want I need blue oh god fucking damn it I let go prematurely holding
down trigger with my index finger and holding down a with my thumb and like
aiming forward I just let it go I was like wait I did this stupid thing where
you Google fucking authenticator and you just you you think you have time to type
it in yeah whatever that's in the code changes I don't whatever it's fucking
dumb I got somebody that was just stuff doesn't haha so fast about that I all
right don't fuck that one up of that if I fuck that one up again I'm gonna be
upset it's gonna be very bad I want we're going to throw a red one in here
cuz we just got a major surplus of red Pikmin look it up there okay thank you
plant 10k added to the debt for every Pikmin dying what do I get out of that I
just increased my debt I don't get anything out of that okay now we need
wizard I'm with the rest of the crew you go get go get them shit I gotta go all
the way around wait what this sucks 30k remove for every treasure no that's not
worth it I'm gonna be losing I'll be losing way too many picking you didn't
get anything with the initial bet either well I did I got absolute total
narcissism and just just being a facetious asshole that's what I got out
of it okay we're all together again got free content for like a year yeah I
guess that too and is this technically water they don't drown in this right
you're not gonna drown in this are you okay oh the leaf in there is it it's a
marijuana leaf this is like a joke it's like a funny Nintendo put that really
huh okay well let's keep going come on out guys you can do it is that it that's
all that was in here no no way something's buried actually that's
actually a marijuana leaf a burial flippery no of course there's another
something in there of course there is what was the point of this room this
whole level was just nothing okay not weed oh no you say a prayer um I wish
you the best I wish you will all right let's get in the corner we've got fire
water fire and water so far we need some do not get burnt by that please okay
Louie you so glad I have a noise gate that was a huge awful like burp that I
just swallowed okay there we go no I don't want any yellows don't get them
okay easy is more fire over here I know it fire over here
watch out for falling stalactites do not engage do not engage the enemy stay back
it's a treasure found in Pikmin 2 oh was it marijuana got people's having whole
books in here no you fucking boomer hey cut that out I'm gonna start making me
really upset at you treasure right there now we're gonna go the safe in here all
right we just good look oh that's a big snuffle off of this thing okay I gotta
be ready for that the rest of you get over here if this right did they get it
on their own right good go get it I gotta take out the stuff off I guess it's
too in here okay interesting go back what what oh my god thank God they got
out alive we're okay right all right we're good it didn't get out there
inside them well we'll get them in a minute we'll take care of them don't
worry they're in the jellyfish he ate some all right I'll get I'll get it I'll
get it we'll go we'll go look rescue mission here we go
weigh him down don't get mega sucked kill it before it sucks yes saved him I
think they suffocated inside of his body they're dead well I'm sorry you can't
save every pigment I need more you don't have me spray all right where I'm
gonna have to go on a spray mission next tomorrow tomorrow the goal is to get at
least two or three sprays or something I need to get the half my team is default
the tea leaf I need flour okay watch the fuck out watch out watch the fuck out
good okay now weigh him down why did I not have purple selected I thought I did
why did I not have purpose like that I had purpose like that what the hell was
that because they're all so damn slow they're all so slow it's unbelievable I
got rocket boots and they don't have rocket boots run oh my god this room
sucks get up here run run run run run run all right well he's in the other
room I was our opportunity to kill these guys one by one okay honestly I'm in
with the Wiimote seriously like it's okay you know like this console aiming
like analog aiming like console aiming this is like a next level version of
console aiming it's because my brain knows exactly where it wants to go and
it's kind of like a mouse the code control is kind of good but it's almost
like there's like a person in my brain and in my arm like holding my hands back
and my stick again it's getting a putting a wall up in my brain it's such
like a horrible in between of like console aiming and mouse I'm pretty
fine we're not running out of purples am I I let them bait it out go ahead all
right get in I had purple selected I like like is there a way that I can make
it so it does not select another pick but I can lock this shit in it's so
annoying I don't even care if I don't have enough I know it's because they're
not behind me but I don't want to select another one and throw it get to the
don't miss the first row I feel like I'm cleaning somebody else's teeth okay
that's how I've always felt using a Wiimote with a game that requires this
I'm like a fucking dentist holding my hand up like aiming leaning forward with
a little device have to be very careful very intricate lean forward move twist
small wrist movements and I can't put it on I can't rest my arm see this is a
mouse if I could have like have it on the ground and moving around like why
can't I why can't it be mouse mode the Wiimote should have a mouse mode convince
me that I'm wrong they would have sold billions you're just doing a Trump voice
why was was I I don't I wasn't even aware of it kind of was I literally no
oh but that was good go this way no I is there a dig I feel like there's
something on the ground here yeah there is right no all right up there get over
here why do you all have to do that I can't just run over here I'm here you
getting stuck in the sand yeah if I pick the olomar and Louie run too fast now
ever since I got those boots upgrade I don't like the boot upgrades I take them
off I'm running too fast I'm just losing the Pikmin how come they don't get the
speed upgrade hey careful he jump I was gonna say can he jump over the fence
that would be horrible it's fire all right well we got fire and I get to fire
and one poly wug odd he's gonna jump over that fence and I'm gonna be so mad
all right pull everybody back here I don't want to kill everyone hang out
back here hang out back here we're gonna do purple and red that's the only ones I
want okay let's try to get through here I'm so concerned about this dude mmm
pull them over here come on dope come on you can do it see it they got they're
gonna be burned by this guy if I throw them over here he's gonna kill them
cuz he's gonna jump on them all right come here just kill it yeah I don't
want all my purpose to get burnt to death I'm trying to get them down the
hall there we go all right there we go you got one you crushed one it's okay
and I will lose one red to get rid of these things all right now we're gonna
go easy watch out kill kill one for the kill good nice work guys excellent job
and deal don't throw all the reds cuz I'll actually good it's potty humor in
chat well I'm gonna tell you disgusting how dare you okay there is a treasure
up here buried I know it at this process cool I lost one guy that's good this
chat is sometimes so goofy it is yeah the way that I see it is I'm kind of
like a gremlin that got wet after midnight or 8 after midnight whatever it
is you guys kind of just sprouted out from that I think like I've said I've
said the words like poopoo and stuff on this stream so I ate like a bunch of
nachos after midnight like I've done that before I know I have say it again
again again do it again I'll do it again you want to hear it again I'll do it
again I promise oh it's just the water okay there's no I can't dig well we're
just gonna throw them over come on up here blue go get it say it okay I'm
gonna say it and then I want everyone to relax you guys gonna relax if I say it
no then I'm not gonna say it then if you're not gonna relax is German a good
boy I think so I try to be I try to be a good boy I don't think I've ever really
tried to be like a bad boy which I think you look I think you try your best
right everybody wants to be a good boy you just try just try to be a good boy
what is it I bet what about when you murdered random people in Red Dead
Redemption so what why what a specific thing to say that's oh like what like
you're a good boy you murdered that guy in Red Dead Redemption um I guess like I
may have like killed like a civilian in Red Dead Redemption and you've got even
on that even stuck on that for like a year two years you think you're such a
good boy what about that time that you shot that guy in Red Dead Redemption I
haven't forgotten you have oh yeah when you were playing Grand Theft Auto that
time and you drove on the sidewalk accidentally and you hit that
pedestrian don't act like you're so good mr. Albertson we know okay you're
gonna do a personality test on stream uh we did that not that long ago we did a
whole bunch of quizzes and tests um few months ago I mean do more I want to do
more tea I love tier lists I've done so many tier lists but I think there's so
much more things to rank you know saying I love doing those it's so much fun just
white flower okay the Pikmin tier list okay sure I don't need a tier list for
that I can just tell you right now um I kind of need a look at them any good
look purple s purple s yellow a red and blue B and then white like C or D tear
yeah that makes sense to me speaking of red let's get a red in there the maker
has spoken about the bulb men's I mean those are s plus but they're not a
Pikmin I mean if we're ranking just Pikmin characters just Pikmin monsters
or just any character in Pikmin then sure the bulbs would be up really high
hey hey get that back I don't know if this thing does but get away it's
poison thank God I've ran everybody away holy shit I just saved everybody's life
you see that that was very very lucky I thought it was purple Pikmin I thought
it was super strong or something I almost had a Snapple wait does it have a
joke come on it has to have a piece of life advice or a joke underneath get
gone what's over here another wall um what's the point of this okay uh yeah
okay it's one of these guys holy shit nice don't let him get away get it again
oh my god he's gonna feed the whole whoa is everybody all right I whatever I
don't care they already drink it I think that much I've already drank the
other ones okay nothing's gonna be buried in one of these I mean that's a
fact right it's just a fact watch out oh it's an electric bug it's an electric
bug I think I don't know kill him okay
don't steal anybody I don't did he get anybody it's I it's so nerve-racking it
really is this is the most nerve-racking game is you don't want
anyone to die but you know they will get him get him get him surrounded big guy
over there all right now where's the treasure it's buried watch out watch
out watch out watch out watch out do not fight do not fight do not fight do not
fight run away it's a bomb that's a bomb that's a bomb Jesus where's that guy
all right that's gas excellent job birthday's tomorrow Oh teeth please
turn into a funny voice to chat please no I'm not going to do that I don't
just get to demand stuff from me that's 10,000 I think I got it
behemoth jaw I got $10,000 I got I have enough to pay off the debt cool all
right so let's get that paid all right we got this big guy in the way we've
got to overwhelm him with purples in one two run away fuck oh my god I couldn't
throw him above his head I was trying to get people to land on his head way he
catches them in the mouth or something I thought the purples were didn't matter
the purples were too heavy and if you hit if you I don't know I thought if
you get hit in the face of the purple then it's just knocks you out for a
sec you have to actually land them like on top of their butt not like on their
head oh well well I'm okay I wouldn't be I don't think I could even attack that
guy from the back look at how small the hallway was he would have just woken up
maybe should have put poison in front of him how was that I hate those things I
would love it if this thing I'm holding it so steady it's braced against my
fucking chest damn it watch out move out of the way this controller I swear to
God is shaking just to piss me off now oh my god why put up two birthday candles
and throw this like 40 cent piece of plastic they put in the fucking box in
the trash that's what I should do but I won't just gonna complain but how bad
the tracking is on this thing I'm just gonna whine about it and just be whiny
and say oh why is the tracking so bad there but just put up two candles no
that'll probably fix it I know no I don't wanna okay well then stop
complaining about it no I'm gonna I paid for this it's I use my good money to
buy this okay you did a funny voice we win were you betting on that I didn't
even notice was it a prediction that will I do a funny voice in the next 10
minutes hey that's not a bad one to do okay let's go what are you willing to bet
on that can I not do a like jokey in quotes voice for 10 straight minutes
what do you think is it what something you want to bet on that's easy money I
don't know is it though ten full minutes let's do it put it on put it on there no
emotion for 10 minutes no it's no jokey voices for 10 minutes define a funny
voice okay a funny voice is defined as one that is very very far away from my
speaking voice one that is so detached from my normal speaking voice like this
like okay yo I was stupid although the Wiimote sucks it's not we want a piece
of shit that's like normal right I'm talking about like by the way this
hasn't started yet I'm talking about like and I said that the infrared
technology was the best and they were wrong they were completely wrong so like
that would be a jokey voice right I guess if I was gonna do like an impression of
that no it hasn't started no no I said it hasn't started yet it starts when I
say go so it's when I say go it starts we're talking any jokey kind of voice
that's that's very detached from the way I'm speaking normally okay we're gonna
begin this after the betting starts by the way what I'm not gonna do this till
the betting is closed yeah it starts when the bet closes will he do a funny
voice in the next 10 minutes god I don't know I'm not okay it starts the second
that I say go not yet not yet I'm gonna try really those even a betting with me
I'm gonna try trust me I'm gonna try as hard as I can oh nice okay remember this
is my speaking voice I can get loud and I can be annoyed I can say like I fucking
threw the purple Pikmin on his head what's going on here that's not a funny
voice that's my normal speaking voice but like a little elevated you know what
I'm talking about killed him okay here we go ready it begins now I'm looking
over I'm seeing people really desperately trying to get me to do
stuff not gonna happen I'm just a normal guy I'm just a regular person just like
you well I'm just hanging out we're playing Pikmin Pikmin 2 actually you
and I are just hanging out together you and me are in this just hanging on the
same chat room just watching TV together and hanging out that thing is gigantic
whatever that is very large I don't know what that thing does but I think a lot
of people are going to die I have to okay he's got a he's got a red thing on
his tail I hit the red tail I think is he fire I don't know he's got these
weird eye things alright everybody stay back Lamar go check it out all right
what do we got one yellow he's tracking he's tracking he's tracking he's tracks
them and then what does he do he's doing his tracking beam so he does a tracking
beam okay then he gets really angry and goes forward what about Jake on his
head and they land on his head they cannot and they cannot hurt him what
about how do they get how do you injure in his eyes okay well he got one it's
got to be the button it's definitely but not the bus how do you fight this guy
lame don't why I want to land on his tail am I just missing what the fuck
it on his tail this seems insanely difficult to do this I'm actually
trying so hard to get it on his tail oops you got him okay um oh no he's got
literally open his mouth I don't know what to do overwhelm his his tail he's
gonna skewer everybody now that shit ain't oh whoa whoa he's buddy he's gonna
have help now it was because they ate the white Pikmin oh my god don't come
down here that doesn't count I went whoa and my normal speaking voice do not
skewer all right just eat them I don't understand this guy just have that eat
those don't come down here eat them he's healing okay honest to God I don't
understand this guy nobody can do anything to him he follows the captain
you're controlling but he's well now what do I do oh well what what no get
out of here come look at me let him eat Louie look at me look at me I'm over
here look at me look at me look at me look at me look at me look at me keep
looking look at me look at me this boss is stupid
dead that doesn't count that doesn't count doesn't count that doesn't count
that was not a funny voice that was a screaming voice was it a funny voice
maybe it was a little funny but it wasn't intentional funny it wasn't
intentional funny was not intentional funny I wasn't trying to do that my does
that count it counts but intention cannot be recorded it but I don't know
we need some deliberation here was that die that wasn't a voice was it not a
voice I don't know just I'm so sick of this fucking boss all right I'm good
what do you got a plate a bowl who was nothing it doesn't count okay does it
not count what what do we think I don't know I need some deliberation is a weird
scream a funny voice or is that a weird scream that does not count no I I'm gonna
I'm I don't need any more deliberation that does not count that was me
screaming weirdly me doing a voice would be like me saying you know put on a
thing right okay does not count that was a weird I was me screaming weirdly by
the way I don't what what is this it was a funny scream funny scream I don't
think it counts though is it on technicality does that count it's a
speaker oh just refund it all right refund it refund it out refund it we're
gonna do it again we're gonna do it again this time this time if that was
that was a scream that was not a funny voice a funny voice is me like
impersonating somebody like doing somebody like I'm doing somebody's voice
a scream me screaming weirdly it's not a funny voice it's a me screaming
strangely so I'm gonna help we're gonna here's what's gonna happen we're gonna
refund it we found those points we can do it again and the next one is going to
be this is a funny voices just don't scream you shouldn't be able to be the
one that decides well but people what you want the people to decide they're
gonna vote based on how they bet that you don't go to like a bay a table in
Las Vegas and have it land on a table have it land on like red to and have
them guy okay guys it landed on red too but we're gonna vote on the table on
whether or not I should we should be paid out or not shouldn't have landed on
red to what do you guys think the one guy that when it landed on red to the
one guy the table is gonna be like yes apps a fucking Lutely it landed on red
to I want to be paid out and all the other dicks at the table are sitting
there going no no no it doesn't count no no I refunded fuck I'm so bad at this
all right no no no no no I have refunded it was over right no I've
refunded it by that point right I said we hadn't started it we're doing it on
refunded it's been ten minutes wait it's been more than ten minutes has it been
ten minutes already oh okay all right all right okay so we're good we did we
refund my point is is that everybody at the table that didn't bet on red to you
got a guy with five grand that he put on black one yeah yeah I think it was a
scam I think it was bullshit oh yeah let's I vote no that it doesn't count of
course he does of course he didn't bet that all right let's do it again this
time with real rules screams should alright we're gonna vote on this should
a weird scream count as a funny voice we might wanna make sure I get this right
this is very important so you're voting on should it count if I do a weird
scream is a scream like weird a funny voice we're gonna get this correct oh
man this is actually pretty split I'm not on a timer right now yeah and by a
weird scream is like like that's a weird oh wow weird scream like whoa did that
count as a funny voice why the fuck is it 5050 really guys did you not decide
is it this hard to do but all weird right it might not be a funny voice not
all funny voices are screams but all screams are funny sounds which all
screams are funny voices what I'm so confused you guys obviously can't figure
this out either I'm having trouble too 51 49 I gotta keep it open okay this is
getting close I'm gonna give it to you again if you haven't voted you have a
very this is important it's separated by like 15 votes funny sound does not
equal a funny voice interesting theory that's right but the shme shaping my
vocal cords to make that funny sound is me making funny sounds with my voice so
therefore it could be a funny voice I have no idea it's tricky are you guys
deciding are you getting close all right I've given you the reasons for and the
reasons for not that's noise does not equal best impression good point okay
it's he's tricking us no I'm just telling you what people would say about
it all right okay okay I'm about to close this poll there's your last chance
I'm gonna give you I'm gonna be a 10 20 seconds last chance does it count does
this is a weird funny scream a funny voice damn it it's so it's too close it
wouldn't let me vote I I can't close the poll until it's very clear what the
fuck close it I can't close it look at it look at this it's separated by like 10
people it's never gonna be clear this sucks I'm I'm trying to be democratic
about this but what the hell I should have just flipped a coin okay all right
I'm in 10 seconds I'm closing it 10 9 8 7 6 5 4 3 2 1 it counts it counts all
right it did counts that's when I closed it it counts a funny weird scream counts
as like making a funny voice okay at least for this particular stream let's
go do it again I should just flip the coin by the way this does not start
until the betting is over yeah to be clear okay I almost just leaned into the
mic and did Obama the you know let me let me be clear right I almost just did
that I was leaning into dinner I was leaning to do an Obama impression I
almost did that and but it wouldn't even counted it hasn't counted yet so I can
until the vote until they're all in all right let's go just don't talk all right
you need a colonoscopy bro I just had one like six months ago it's a little big
haul today okay I'm almost ready just don't talk no I have to talk that's not
fair I'll give you guys some incentives as to being on board or not on board
this I have to talk I cannot go more than I cannot go more than 10 straight
seconds in silence otherwise it nullifies everything right hold on is it
not yet there's a cutscene doesn't not starting now I want to just do these
characters right now but I can't okay it's start it's now we're starting now
ten minutes starting now I can read these in my own voice probably should
have put this on the pole should have asked about this is doing car engine
noises considered a funny voice or is that me imitating a car engine probably
I put a Louis okay congratulations German the best part wait what I thought I
was I didn't beat the game I mean I guess I just beat the game that was a fun
game but there's more right I wanted to so badly I'm just putting a I'm just
having to self just sit her and shut and quiet I wanted to say Monka s in the way
I can't I have to it's just weird to do I'm always doing just weird sounds and
stuff you left Louie behind so is that so Louie stays on the planet and
continues to do stuff well this is real imagery and spongebob vibes from this
when they put just real stuff I'm not gonna skip the credits I know everyone
wants to see them yeah I'm not done I'm gonna keep playing you have to save
Louie cool I've seen everybody writing doi doi doi oh my goodness the urge to
do that right now the urge to just put my hand up to my mouth push the pinky up
and just do it as hard as I can is there is hard it's hard to avoid that I can't
like yeah I want to do it right now well I can't wait till 10 minutes is up and I
can just doi doi doi with like five straight seconds as hard as I can into my
head cool Pikmin lost in battle Pikmin lost to fire is zero that's pretty good
but I want to can I go through these myself I've been born 550 yellow Pikmin
blue Pikmin born total playtime 11 hours and 41 minutes cool that's cool what okay
I made the most red Pikmin I want to do it so bad so 550 were born 339 died
that's not bad you must resist it's eating weight and it's only been two
minutes it's been a little longer than that resume the expedition and return
to the planet yes thanks to you our company has been saved hurrah what
there's still more treasure if we collect it all will be filthy rich Louie
where's Louie what you lost him in that case I shall go oh okay ooh new this is
new awesome let's check it out but wait I want to make sure that I check this out
over here I can throw carrots at these guys do any of them like carrots this
one explodes that was a wild I can't believe what I just saw okay this looks
very this one looks very very interesting to me I want to read the
notes greater spotted jelly float cephalus vortex a jelly float family
vivid pink coloration is the most noticeable characteristic of this
floating life form pretty cool all right continue to area selection you can
express emotion no I can't I don't want to I want to land here and check this
out because if I put a motion on I might go into the Adam Sandler voice honey man
monotone I I'm trying to win oh he is with us now I want to do I wait that it's
trying to get me to do it it's do it right do it it's trying to get me to do
it do it do it it just made the doy doy sound it's trying to get me to do it
once we do it so bad I do too I'm gonna do it I'm gonna do it if it's calling to
me I have to do it it's really tricky they're not okay hold on we must we
shall make pocketate freight the golden indisputable king of deep space long
hall freight then everyone will be godly clad in gold like me no I am unique and
beautiful yes Oh Lamar I must ask that you take extreme care so as to not
insult or endanger our president for now where could Louis be to be stuck on an
uncivilized planet with no food at all I am concerned you must waste no time in
finding him how much time do I have three minutes easy done let's take 30
blues 25 I don't I only have 13 13 yellow we need for 40 these and then oh
my god I'm almost out of everything you're so close I know I'm gonna get it
I'm gonna get it you bet you that was a not a good bet to bet against me I'll
never bet against me again notice how I didn't lean into the mic and do a lower
voice with a little bit of gravel on it I just said never bet against me again
they're normal person don't eat everybody please thank you very much
don't eat them okay cool there it oh that's a big dumbbell that's a really
cool-looking dumbbell I need 1,000 Pikmin to pick that up that seems
incredibly hard to do how am I possibly gonna have 1,000 Pikmin out that's not I
don't think I can do that I'm not sure that's possible it's 100 purples very
very interesting I'm not sure I'm gonna get that not on at least on this game
session that I'm playing now I need yellow where's yellow no no I told you
no don't get I'm okay this isn't germo this is not how this is not you dude it
is me desperately trying to win a game of chess with everybody times it right
now oh yep did I win no not yet one minute okay one minute we'll get that
alright watch out for this guy you dickhead get on top of him and get him
down surround him swarm him make sure he doesn't do anything stupid excellent job
got him I want yellow to pick these up please thank you very much yellow pick
that up need two more of these yellows over here and a yellow on that one too
okay great watch out there is something up there this voice is funny time time
oh is the time yes oh look what I can do look what I can do now don't get
crushed by this thing don't get crushed hold on look what I get to do it's me a
Bernie Sanders and I'm gonna say I can't believe that Jeremy actually did it he
got to the other he got to the other time good for you hey thanks hey thanks a
lot Bernie appreciate it man let's kill this guy oh no oh yes I feel fucking
fantastic right now oh my god that's fine perfect ending perfect ending to a
fucking incredible show oh my god I'm annoying I must be like annoying this
is me know my normal speaking in my normal routine am I the annoying guy I
might be the annoying guy oh wait yeah we could go out we could go out to eat
with like Jeremy but man like he just he's always like moving and talking and
making sounds um I'd rather hang out with your mother I'd rather spend time
with your in-laws then go to dinner with Jeremy yeah you know he like picks up
the handkerchiefs and goes like and he puts a knife he puts a butter knife in
the napkin hides it so when he blows his nose he tilts the net the knife up so it
looks like the air is going up really really hard into the napkin and he
thinks it's funny every single time he does it but which I'm just like annoyed
it well I buy it by this point I don't want to see it anymore
well he keeps doing it every time we go out to eat he picks up the nap it's in
the night because I've got a little bit of a cold and no one laughs he just does
it every time no one laughs and then he just keep we just keep having a
conversation is he figured it out yet that we don't think it's funny but it's
like not we don't laugh at it there's the other five you are the one
guy and when I lose these guys over here let's do a double or nothing but no
double or nothing doesn't mean double or nothing we're talking about why does it
look so weird you don't double or nothing with bets I mean well you don't
it's time to 20 minutes how about this let's get the predictions off I mean you
could look you can predict on this if you want but how about this you guys
willing to put up a billion dollars and we're dead if I cannot do any like dumb
funny voices for 20 minutes no screaming and no funny voices for 20
minutes can I get that we go for it no this is gonna be really boring it's
gonna be really boring if you do all right well I'm gonna kill this guy come
eat a white one eat eat mountain eat a wooden idiot yeah I wouldn't idiot that's
me laughing I have wouldn't able to do it for now my I don't know like freaking
out now I'm like a soda can because I was like shook up a shitload only funny
voices wait only funny voices for 20 straight minutes I don't know if I can
do that only funny voices for 20 minutes only oh god oh my god um do I get any
time do I get a time between that sounds like hell that sounds like hell I get
one five minute break okay I think I want to do this okay all right and by
the way funny voices cost no breaks oh my god so no breaks and no Bernie I don't
I was just gonna say what if can I just what if I just do Bernie for 20 minutes
does that count no breaks and no Bernie what that's not fair at all
Bernie is fine Bernie please Bernie counts okay all right are we doing this
we're doing this we're doing this right now new poll 20 minutes of only doing
voices I cannot speak in my normal voice for 20 straight minutes yes or no for
for one billion dollars off the debt tell me this is gonna this is the one I
just I just cannot speak in my normal speaking voice for 20 minutes let's I
want to get official for for no normal speaking voice this is actually gonna
suck I'll be honest with you people that come into the stream that have not been
here forever but that may be new viewers or something they're just gonna think I
so fucking hard like I am just trying so hard to be like funny and shit like
Jesus man like come on really like you just you just a doing of voices for 20
minutes yeah for like 10 minutes straight like I look funny I get it like
just relax didn't just play Pikmin like nobody cares we don't like people want
to hang out and have fun you don't have to try this hard by like just doing like
Bernie Sanders for like 20 minutes I was walked everybody into that this is
unanimous all right we're doing it 20 minutes if I do not do it if I speak in
my normal voice one time then oh god what happens does that we add a billion
it adds a billion okay all right I'm gonna have to take a break before this
though I'm gonna have to take a break and go piss and get ready you have to
add another day of catboy no all right yeah let me go take a quick break when I
come back we will do a three two one and then I'm just not going to speak in my
normal speaking voice for 20 minutes under any circumstance all I'm just
imagining I'm imagining me getting like a call like a very important call that I
have to take mr. Elberton this has been an accident it's been an accident okay
well let me just make sure that everything's okay like no I'm gonna
lose mr. Elberton is yeah it's us it's it's it's you have not paid your
electric bill not pay my electric bill what would you look at that sorry about
that I all don't work on that I'll get better at that I promise
hey scam that's not part of the deal we don't like why are you mocking me now
mr. Elberton no no I promise this is not me mocking you it's not a buck it's
absolutely not a buck I just I have something going on here that it your
muck stop doing that voice I'm not dumb try I'm just about how I speak a scam
I'm not putting on a face game no I'm not putting a face game on no no face
game you're not getting I gotta go back look we did a look up we got a look we
had some we got wasted an entire day a scam how is that cheating cheating what
do you mean cheating you hear me talk you're listening to me speak where's the
last one but me having a face cam on is people just think I'm a fucking weirdo
it could be pre-recorded no it's not pre-recorded people I'm just gonna I'm
gonna be sitting there they're talking in voices like this to help with the
fucking face cam on this is gonna be so embarrassing if I hold on fine fine if
the fate if I turn that face cam on for 20 minutes and we do 20 minutes of
voices and you have it on the whole time proof I want another billion off the
debt if I do it another full billion is that we got a you're not wherever you
anonymous that you know you know I'm just I'm that I don't think I need to
have full all right I have to go put on clothes all right I'm gonna do it I'll
do it fine fine sure yeah all right fine two billion off the debt if I do this
for 20 straight minutes I cannot speak in my normal speaking voice two billion
off of that sounds good to me that's what it is zero treasure all right all
right well I'm gonna get this ready let me go pee let me put some clothes on and
we're doing two billion and we're gonna vote for two billion by the way I'm just
telling you this is what I this is what I'm putting up if this is a no by the
way face cams not going on I want to make that very clear face cam not going
on if this is not agreed to for two billion with face cam on and I was the
outside a timer on my phone while I am taking a pee and just grabbing another
water it's coffee not a water I lied about it again I don't know why I'm one
of the big make you think I'm drinking water I am but why would I lie about
that with face cam for two billion yeah with face cam for two billion off yes or
no and again the face cam does not turn on if you say no to this it only turns
on if it's two billion that's what I'm putting up I'm not going any lower all
right here we go I I'll be right back and I go take a quick pee
why is everybody laughing everybody's laughing their ass off why I just came
back and it was a wave of omega lows what happened gotta get ready for this
okay oh hold on I want to let's get a longer look at that one I don't want to
cut it off all right somebody did somebody get robbed why did I cut one
off one of the picture pieces glitched and couldn't see it all right well we'll
put it back on we'll figure we'll get it back on pro spore streamer and a stream
voice at space stage it plays on normal unironically cheats optimizing factories
playing on hard maxis would release sport to any moment now dad's computer
at age 10 and 80 yeah I mean whatever oh my god okay all right all right all
right all right all right all right all right all right all right all right all
right oh do I even look like today I don't know shit no I look all right I
look at hello okay I look all right all right I look all right I gotta get ready
you're gonna get my voice ready so let me get this clear it can be so Jeff
hold on wait is it delayed come on I have to delay it just all right just so
we're clear just so we're very clear I cannot speak in my normal speaking voice
can I laugh in my normal laughing voice is that okay if I laugh I have to put
like a jokey laugh on it or something yes yes yes okay look at this hair this
piece just like wants to be whatever I don't even care let's go hmm I'm ready
I'm ready I'm ready so I'm gonna show do a countdown here I need to I get I might
need a timer on my phone 20 minutes putting a timer on 20 minutes begins so
I need stopwatch all right timer 20 minutes the timer begins with the timer
on screen I don't I don't think I can do that I don't have like a plug-in or
something I could do hold on that's actually a good idea hold on give me a
sec I could probably just capture like a window hold on yeah give me one sec
timer now I'll just use like I'll just use Google timer thing 20 minutes 20
minutes 20 minutes we get that done let me capture that window I'm setting this
up I'm making sure this is done right hey lock that this is for two billion
guys I need to get this right okay window capture where is it come on right
there right you see it you can't see it why not oh they go okay all right
Zorn leaked there you go 20 minutes is on the clock I am ready to attempt this
ready in fuck it's not not until I did not until I say go so we do a put it
predictions fiction please prediction please all right well let's get that
going before I do this some president you are I just got back from vacation to
find out you're on a treasure hunt well don't bother coming home until you found
every item on your list no predictions um we could but if we do predictions I
gotta yeah you know forget yeah forget it we don't need it all right here we go
I gotta pick out some from ones I can do for a while I could do I could do this I
could just talk like this in for a while I don't know what this is but I had
something it's something that is not my voice I don't know I don't know but it's
not my normal voice okay three two one go okay so where do I want to go first I
think we're gonna go back to wistful wilds I think that's a good place to go
I've seen people say that don't burn it but that's I don't know what you're
talking about okay how many pick me do I want all
I'm trying to do voices I think I can do this one for a while okay there's two
Otto plenty plenty of these guys and printing nine of these guys and then
maybe 30 or 40 every these guys look at 40 okay so come over this way I can't
pick that up I know I can't pick that up it's too heavy okay so I go this way I
wanted to go over this way with blue guys I almost talked in my normal voice
for a second it was very close I almost just talked in my normal speaking voice
so we need I'm gonna do is do I need I need one two three four of sixteen
these guys I'm not even it's 18 more minutes okay I need you guys to go over
here and pick this up open this thing up and get the treasure inside watch out
for this guy watch out he's getting ready to shoot you oh this is this is
actually pretty easy I can do this for much longer than 20 minutes you guys I
think you guys got scanned it's a raid oh no is actually a raid I hope there's
not a raid I hope there's not a raid raid song no no there can't be a raid song right now I
don't I hope there's not a raid is there a raid I have there's not a raid I don't see a
raid I do not see your raid thankfully I don't see one over there
okay we're fine we're doing fine he's gonna go this way watch out for this
guy watch out for this guy kill this guy no much more worse way to face Kim on I
hate it on I want to I think I need to I need some yellows over here to get those
I take that with yellow that would be good oh actually that could give me some
that could give me at least a few extra blue guys which I'll take I'll take the
blue guys come on you little bastards pick it up at least try to pick up this
one okay so how am I supposed to put how do I take everybody should I throw
everybody over there would that be better I think that's a good idea that's
for them yeah I think we go over here that guy's got a cannon watch out for
that guy that guy's got a cannon people are saying you can laugh normally no I
cannot laugh normally I can't laughing normally is gonna get me out a lot of
trouble I cannot laugh normal I'm sticking with this and I'm gonna try to
stay as long as I can as long as I possibly could do now they they are
going the way that they're not supposed to be going they're supposed to go a
different way I'm a little concerned that these little guys are gonna die
they're almost good it's very close it was incredibly close somebody died where
I did anybody know where the purples are where are the purples I seem to have
lost my purple guys oh they're back here I think actually getting harder to stay
in one of these voices they drowned what are you talking about they didn't
drown you have no idea what the fuck you're talking about I think they're
still alive we've got to overwhelm this guy I'm gonna try to overwhelm him as
much as I can it's very difficult to do this and still play the video game at
the same time I'll tell you it's not easy all of my concentration is
completely just front-loaded into the top of my head to only talk in a weird
way I don't I have no idea I've got my time and trouble playing the game it's
already halfway through the day so I can't get that treasure but I can do
what else is left to do so I can turn around and go the other way which I can
do that I think I think these little guys I'm gonna take him to get the egg
that's what I'm gonna do they're going to get the egg I love eggs they're my
favorite breakfast in the entire world everybody drink up we've got many many
nectar french fries excuse me do watch out stop do not go near them don't touch
them do not dare don't even think about it it's stupid don't touch them we're
gonna try to land on their heads very carefully very carefully very strongly
good good good good good good now put them up and bring them back to for a
snack yes I'll get to do and nobody can say minus two nobody can say minus two
right now who's ready for an adventure I can do so
finley margolton as long as I want I hate this fucking voice this voice sucks
I hate it I don't it's stupid but I get to do it for as long as I want who's
ready for adventure okay so I think what I have to do is I have to cross over
here for the blue guys how long is it how long has he been I have to do this
for 10 more minutes okay oh what's up with this big bug there's a big bug over
here and he buried into the ground okay that seems pretty easy we just need
everybody to go over there I just whack it with their heads oh they just got
absolutely whack so this is really stupid and fucking hard to do I don't
even know where to go I'm supposed to kill everybody over there I did slip a
little bit it was really close but I pulled it back very close I fucking
hate this this is the worst thing I've ever done on stream this is the worst
thing I've ever done well I do believe that we can very simply pull over this
guy Bart take him over here and jump on his head and then eventually we'll cross
this river I said I've wasted two full days Brian I've wasted two full days on
this Brian I know it would be great if I didn't waste two full days Ryan good
job guys you got out of your water I'm stuck I'm stuck I'm stuck I don't I don't
know what to do I don't understand I don't know it's very hard to do this
it's incredibly difficult to do this that guy over there is gonna die I
three-voice Andy three voice Andy I don't care I need purples I don't have
any purples
I can't just stop please kill him kill that guy he's idiot okay quick oh no no no no no don't do that
please I want everyone to know that we meet Otto kill this guy please thank you
I only have to do this for five and a half more minutes say something funny
I'm trying I don't care how funny this shit is I don't care this could be some
of the most ridiculously unfunny stuff you've ever heard in your entire life I
don't care I just I'm trying to keep my normal speaking voice from coming out at
all I don't give a shit about how funny this sounds I don't care about what I
look like on stream I don't give a shit I don't care and are you thought that I
almost slipped but what happened was I fended to a German guy Louie we
suddenly stopped hearing from you is everything okay if things get tough you
can always come home I'll suck up all those pit-pits
cabbage is a cheap love no no no is my favorite noise my favorite weird voice
this is Bernie this is Bernie if it Bernie is morphing into a bunch of
things but it's morphing into German guy again Bernie is morphing into guy that
speaks like this I'm getting close to losing I am that was not asleep that was
not a slip that was me changing to this guy that was not a slip absolutely no
sleep somebody just wrote God dot dot dot dot they must I must have I must this
must be so fucking annoying I'm so sorry I'm so sorry I really am so sorry but I
need to take this debt down I need to get the debt to come down very very
quickly as fast I can I'm so sorry he's getting desperate yeah yeah this is what
desperation looks like cuz every time I try to do this and try to shave off the
debt it never works and I always look like a fucking asshole every single time
I just look like a fucking idiot it makes me look really stupid I want to go
to that place that had only blue Pikmin in there now that blue Pikmin in there
I'm heading over that way to the blue Pikmin Center but I have 86 of them now
how do I have to go up north now north north which way is north I don't know
which way north is two minutes and I can finally turn this shit off I'm gonna
turn this stupid fucking thing off and just be done with this just go up okay
should I take any purples or something with me I would take no do I need any
purples no or it only has to be okay well let's just take some blue stuff
only blue Pikmin okay so let me get to 100 blue Pikmin okay one minute and 20
seconds room temperature IQ and the E clown
now let me think and I wasn't gonna be able to do this let me be perfectly
clear I could and I did I did it well what are you talking about not a slip
this is non-slip this is rockabama that's not a slip not sound sort of like
the way that I kind of talk a little but now I know you make me go I'm gonna be
in debt forever um let me explain what happened I started to do Barack Obama
started doing Barack Obama everyone said slipped slip slip slip slip slip slip
slip and then I struck and then I started to make Barack Obama's voice
sounds fucking horrible so I didn't want to make it sound like I was doing a
really shitty Barack Obama so I was correct I was telling you guys that oh
look at how bad my Barack Obama sounds now no slip what do you mean I won I did
it did I actually do it watch the clip and pull it all right let's watch the
clip I'm slipping I think a lot of you guys just fucking feel bad let me hear
it let's say I'm gonna I want to hear it where is it
we said Obama slips let's see no and I did let me be perfectly clear I could
and I did I did it well what are you talking about not a slip this is
not slip this is Barack Obama that's not slip my sound sort of lack the way that I
kind of talk a little but now I know you make me go I was Bernie Sanders into
Mario getting his ass lit on fire I kind of talk a little but now I know now
night and not now I yeah that was Bernie Sanders then turning into Mario getting
his ass lit on fire go I know you make me go I but now I know you make me go
now you make now you make me go on now you make me go on that's not a slip
that's Bernie Sanders I think we're good but now I know you make me go so in
question is was that a slip fucking stupid thing I've ever done let me give
you let me give it to you again so you understand what you know what you're
doing here but now I know you make me go on the slip was that Bernie Sanders
just just seamlessly going into a loud funny like Ren and Stimpy scream it was
seamless it was seamless Bernie Sanders now you make me go loud equals funny
exactly absolutely you're right absolutely loud equals funny 1 billion
1.5 billion compromise I'm sick yeah we got a vote this is a no-slip by the way
alright that's a 1.5 billion compromise I'll take 500 we'll take 500 million off
the debt for me maybe maybe an awkward transition between Bernie going into
Mario lighting his ass on fire alright deal deal deal alright let's go I'm
gonna play the game now I'm getting a fucking face cam it was so painful that
sucked that was the worst that's oh yeah is it worth like the potentially okay
yeah I get that compromise is it worth you'd shave 500 million off that one
point five billion compromise that's fine you know how many people left the
stream because they couldn't take it anymore and they probably won't come
back I just lost out on people gained viewers yeah but how many did we lose
getting to viewers all right let me get a where is where we at
bang go this way now you're gonna lose viewers yeah that's probably oh well
okay 83 how many do I have now double or nothing absolutely not I absolutely not
going to double or nothing I'm taking that as I can get it 98 out of 100
damn it me two more and then I'm going in that one that's all they need all
blue this was fun though Pickman's this is I love my fun with this and I thought
I was gonna know you heard me complain about how desperately I hated the Wii
motion controller and what I saw I called this like a what a $40 system or
something and what I call the Wii U I made fun of the Wii U a bunch I was
really mean to the Wii U really mean I said it was like a $40 console like how
dare they sell this more than $40 right well whatever all right pick it up blue
we need more blue the 2 billion was added we had a vote they added the debt
no we had a vote we had a vote that it wasn't a slip that it was a 1.5 billion
it was a 500 million compromise they fixed it all right good oh man okay here
we go I got 100 blue Pikmin so where is it it's up here
Citadel spiders Glutton's kitchen or shower room so it's Glutton's kitchen
that's where we have to go no it's past that okay no we'll get it we'll get it
there is a blue sitting around somewhere where is he on my Wiimote
tracker is fucked up okay 100 let's pass that kitchen you say get spray oh shit
you're right yeah should we get a bunch of spray I just just burn another whole
day doy doy doy doy doy doy doy doy doy doy doy doy doy doy doy doy doy anymore
purple juice is really important here more apologize for what whoa I'm now
going to sing the Super Mario one one level in this in like the sultry doy
voice on planted let's go is that a threat don't just wrote I'm good thanks
you guys are fucking funny I'm good man thanks I got a spray well I need more
I feel like I want to get these guys to mmm I don't know let me just see what
this place is so if I go across the bridge I go past the Glutton's kitchen
okay am I gonna have enough time to go over attention attention remember don't
bring a hundred attention I'm gonna bring it on you need purple spray where
do I get the purple spray attention gamer attention gamer bring 80 attention
gamer what the fuck all right fine 80 is fine all right attention gamer only
bring 80 and bring okay it's the bulb men okay where hey where do I get the
purple spray up your ass ha ha ha fuck no no I don't I want the ones of the
flowers on them I don't want the ones that I want only flowers their way can
separate them how do I I only want the guys of the flowers but all the way then
take them only to okay I'm gonna time anyways I need way more I don't have four
purples that's fucking horrible it's purple fruit flowers all right well I
where's the best place to get those I need to stock up on those Louise out
here dying and you're struggling to count to 80 there's a German you but you
didn't get my message but I'm glad I caught your stream today I've been
watching you since your TF2 days years ago you've been a source of laughter and
entertainment for a long time this week I'm going into quarantine for two weeks
and I'm joining the USMC I'm a little too old for it a little old for it 26
years old that's my dream you've been an inspiration in a weird way to have some
bits and buy yourself plenty of Mountain Dew as the elite gamer that you are well
thank you good luck good luck to you thanks for sticking around you sound a
little old for it you're never too old for anything thanks for watching I wish
you the absolute best of luck who died for how did I have four Pikmin what
all right I am going to go into the water dungeon at the beginning of this
day no I'm not I'm gonna grind purple stuff where's the uh what's the thing
that it was the purple flowers was the best one where's the best place to get
a purple flower you don't need it I will fuck it I don't need it I don't need it
I'm not doing it I don't need it I don't need it I'm gonna go destroy this place I
can't believe I was just on camera for 20 minutes going like this and this is a
high guys oh my god all right so you say just take 80 all right I'll take 80 so
you saying if we're gonna go this way so go all the way up through Glutton's
kitchen oh you're gonna get bald men all right right right right right right
right right right right right right right right right right right right right
watch out for this guy this guy's a dick you're not jump don't jump don't jump
don't jump don't we have Baldwin it doesn't matter wait secret I thought I
could go across the bridge fucking crazy up this way this Glutton's kitchen in
there this guy this fucking stupid polywag is gonna kill everybody run run
run run run run run run run run mods mods mods mods help mods what hurry
before this guy gets over here hurry before he gets over here please
distract him oh my fucking god don't do it will we get the fuck out of the way
you're just getting crushed all right leave wait oh the president whatever no
no oh my god I just love these characters don't even matter all right I
am gonna send I want more blue Pikmin bring this back no I don't I don't even
do I fucking care I need help with my Spanish homework okay
de-soberante that's deodorant they want and say that means hurry up all right
now we go through here just don't just run just run on the just hang the edge
hang on the edge don't even get attacked run run run run run run run run you are
too slow it's so annoying okay now where I see something over there is that it
that's it over here I'm ready here we go don't call them annoying deeper sections
of this whole scene to be submerged in liquid sadly I am a delicate piece of
machinery that is sensitive to water you too must go alone it might be
Cheshire trusts down there why do you look at me with such sworeful of
whatever captain crunch cereal voice Kevin crunch cereal fuck I did the
drunk guy thing again all right what is this are they breaking weird who this
that too hold on yes hitting but why they do that oh whatever 13 treasures
that seems like a lot blue Pikmin only red Pikmin this fire everywhere how am
I supposed to do is the blue Pikmin I get it just run them into the water grab
this oh yeah well they ate it wait kill it well it's kill it while it's not on
fire good job yeah on the water we're good all right nice nice nice nice I got
whatever this is like a scraper wheel emote only please why emote only for
what history wheel oh that's cute let's keep going okay still treasures on this
level check this out we're gonna overwhelm it well it's not on fire kill
it come on come on come on good very good very good very good you idiots you
making me very upset at you wait punch it why are they not doing it punch this
I demand it I don't know why they were taking so long okay that's a safe
trip through here through here where's this other treasure oh shit okay it's
over there that's a huge guy though I don't know this is worth it maybe I'm
oh fuck I don't know if it's worth doing this he's asleep though but that's not
worth it I don't care no definitely not worth it no way just getting the hell
out of here you're a coward that's all right whatever you know for a fact that
at least 10 to 20 pick them we're gonna die right there if I was doing that
and under that control we mo to only that's pretty good oh yes give me
friends ah that's a lot of new friends that's a very large amount of new
friends and he had a cookie wait easy give that shit back right now don't let
him burn you don't let him burn you don't let him burn you don't let him
burn you run away run run run run run run run run run run run good all right
let's get everybody pick them all up I love the little bulbies it's so cool I'm
glad I got him who stole the cookie I mean I just got to do Otto's Pogtastic
adventure and that's pretty much gonna be gone
comfort cookie cool oops no no no break this down with the Captain Crunch boys
again no what you got a no interest loan here there's so much cuter too they
instead of going are they go hurry I love the little bulbies now the question
is where's the other treasure here mmm dangerous hole dangerous hole oh but
but hold on everybody relax I don't want to do this yet until I there's probably
a sleeping guy is there nothing here something's not gonna jump out and attack
I know there is right yeah of course you're right here these guys don't jump
down so I'm sorry I think can I get it fuck oh well let's go around okay pick it
up I got everybody on it 26 of you I lost a few but it's okay hey in the in
the world's and then the words of Albert Einstein one to skip a few 99 100
yeah everybody I think it's all right I don't see
anything no monster has attacked yet which is kind of scary something over
there the guy with the balloons monster ranger what is this I can see it with my
optical receptors but my sensors cannot detect this steamroller could its
physical form be anchored in another dimension attacking it is futile if only
we could force it to take on physical form but in its current state no danger
it's a steamroller all right well he's all the way in the water put this up
first is this cheese or tape oh infection hoop oh my god he's coming up
here it's fast too um come on come on come on hurry up hurry up hurry up can
he go uphill come on come on guys hurry go go go go hurry card go go go oh no oh
no oh no oh no he's not down here yet wait we can hide in here he can't get in
here come on everybody in everybody in everybody in everybody and we good
everybody in we're good he can't get in here everybody in get in get in okay
we're okay you're not pushing them out
there's too many people okay you can't I'm going I'm ready I'm ready I'm ready
let's go this way we slide down here now we have access we can run this way we
have to use the tunnels I have to break this what the fuck can I that's a bomb
I'm fine I'm ready get out of the way can he blow him up get out of the fucking
way go go go go go go go go go go I'm alright oh shit that's how I can't get
the doughnut how am I gonna get the doughnut where is he okay look this guy
I gotta kill this thing this is gonna ruin everything now have him blow up by
his own balloon now that okay good where is he can he fit through here why
is he not coming down here he's not I lost him he's good I'm good just get
that doughnut in there let's get the hell out of here oh fuck is that him okay
hurry up hurry up hurry up hurry hurry hurry hurry hurry hurry hurry hurry oh
man oh man come for me come for me look at me look at me look at me look at me
look at me look at me over here okay all right all right all right follow me no
no follow me follow me follow me where's he going where's he going what the fuck
can he turn down there guys it's time to run in the all for two doughnuts sub
level three does he follow down I only have 29 wait oh here we go come on give
me some more friends there's so many right here okay here we go ready I'm
gonna just be Bobby only there we go we're fine that's the cutest thing I've
ever heard in my whole entire life listen that's so much cuter of a song
then the Pikmin one that's so much cooler electricity I want them to drink
someone must I want the bulbs to drink Jesus yet fucking Wiimote the fucking
goddamn Wiimote you piece of dog shit $40 fucking console what the hell was
that William down all right I want them to drink I just want the bulbs to drink
come on over here yes so yes isn't big over there this is dangerous
holy shit that's what they did that was when the machina first came out
people went on their private servers with like 15 of their friends and just
man can we line everybody up and just see get it shoot through everyone yes it
can oh my god this is a disaster well it is a
bulby run now because I can't get anything else reset actually no I've no
I can't I can do it with bulbies trust me okay holy shit we're getting more
bulbies aren't bulbies stronger I just need like another 20 30 of them they're
immune yeah they're fine all these can handle like
electricities too you reset when you have 10 die to a frog but not when you
massacre a hundred well I mean I didn't know what the steamroller guy was this
guy's really cool I like it I highly recommend it you had 80
sure what the fuck did he come from you just fell now actually reset that's a
well I'll try that again that's why is he there that's stupid you shouldn't be
there you can press the home button and reset yeah but it feels more like angry
it feels more angry if I am you know but if I do it and hit mash the button on the
console to make us mad he's emulating he's angry when he said hey German I
showed that clip to my little bro he started giggling like crazy he just
can't believe someone makes much make such a simple mistake I asked him what
he thought and he's just you play an easier game like Yahtzee are you little
brothers an asshole what why am I seeing D face he didn't say hey my little bro
who is also six his little bro could be like 30 just because somebody somebody's
little brother doesn't mean they're like five like that guy could be like 40
years old all right let's go honey fireman so I gotta I gotta move faster
than this this is is this the hardest man 11 in the game I guarantee it is I
don't really want white this we mode is I don't know what is it why you freaking
out we don't stop that okay okay am I emanating a 2.4 gigahertz signal out of
my teeth or something I just reset the console and the it's I can't pick it up
anymore I don't get it it's way worse now I didn't do anything it didn't change
anything it's like just moving around like crazy the sensor yeah I'd recalibrate
it every time I turn the fucking computer on you're radioactive these guys
remind me of I do one the remote you have seems really funky yeah I mean it's
official this is an official Nintendo we vote storm get him swarm of swarm
Pikmin use swarm Pikmin use tail swipe because watch that show I agree I'm just
fucking around didn't I say that I was gonna stop pretending to like hate stuff
I think I made that statement I was like you know I'm gonna stop like pretending
that I think things are stupid but I hate things is people that might be new
here I yeah I did mention that didn't I like two three days ago I need more of
those bulb guys aren't they a couple down here we won't please when the
pretender is strange came with you guys if you guys have given me such a bad
name with that meme by the way you know you guys know how many people hate this
community because of that meme yeah it's that like that's that germa guy yeah
he's a fucking loser he's an asshole who's that who's that suss guy oh yeah
fuck that guy oh my god I almost lost don't please god Pikmin is too hard he
just ate somebody I'm gonna rage quit again I'm rage-pitting again he's just
fucking snacking like god those things how the fuck he's supposed to kill those
things reliably what do you he shakes him off and he goes in here and crushes
them I have less people than what what you lose the treasure wait no no no no
reset reset reset reset reset yeah I forgot I thought I would have just
walked in the thing I would have walked in the thing that shoots you up I thought
if you said escape that it meant okay I know it said I did said that didn't okay
well hold on let me reset it is it too late to reset are you kidding me oh god
damn it no it's not don't save shit I'm to play Yahtzee now whatever it was a
cool place and I know that's the hardest level in the game I know it's endgame
hard level one of the hardest I've heard so somebody said it was like hey dude
that's a really hard level and I don't worry about it
Jesus I do want to make sure I reiterate this again because there's just 10k
people here what it was until I just failed that level miserably and 500
people left because that was an embarrassment and they couldn't stand it
but you know whatever it's still this close 10k March 6th is it gonna be a
pretty big stream I'm gonna be doing an archaeology adventure mm-hmm I'm very
excited about it at 1 p.m. Pacific is the start time on March 6th bring your you
know bring your shovels bring your eye be searching for all kinds of wonderful
things all right where have I not gone in here I want to go to the glutton cave
Lutton's kitchen yeah I don't want to go to the submerged castle that one's too
hard if we are to do Glutton's kitchen no we did I loved that place is there
nothing else here that's worth doing there's definitely treasure somewhere
hold on I'm just gonna get like a treasure on the map I cleared it right
right yeah so the truth there we go all right this is a bottle opener right
there cool I want that that guy's got fire run everyone's good uh we'll do
some collection but I don't want red to get those I want blue to get them
because we just but first of all this guy's gonna he's gonna mess everything
up yeah we go what are you doing the hell are you guys doing oh my god this
Wiimote is gonna make me scream into the microphone as loud as I can I want I
want yellow or blue to get these and then yellow you get the bottle opener
these the purple ones pretty cool if they were just saying I reach it from
here I cannot and I reach it we're gonna reach this from up there get it I swear
to god I'm my life my farts must be fucking 5g I swear I have no idea why
this is doing this and I have farted a lot the last couple of hours like I
don't know why this fixed signal is so fucked up right now I didn't do any that
didn't change anything yeah bottle opener change your batteries these are
brand new batteries and I've recalibrated the controller like two
hours ago I must have I seriously must have like 2.4 gigahertz breath I was
another treasure it's in the open at the Wii motion plus I think this is yeah
this is Wii motion plus inside yeah I got it of course I do think I'm not
gonna do nothing I'm gonna spring for the Wii motion plus controller more
more more no cuz only 12 games use it wasn't that standard in controllers
after a certain year after like the consoles up for a little while go to
that drained lake yeah hold on let me see what else is in here there's another
treasure on the map somewhere well Jeremy we've been trying to reach you
about your car's extended warranty well leave me alone I don't want one over
here any treasures over here ah it's hold on one of these assholes is over
here though hold on I need purple run run all right jump remember drives a
dirt bike I drive a lawnmower don't pass why I almost just blew that so bad
dress a dirt bike no I don't have a dirt bike I'm scared to drive a dirt bike
dig something to dig something to dig something to dig something to dig how
many white Pikmin there we go yes jump don't kill that guy all right now back
up dead hurry up get it go go go go go go go go go go go go go go go hurry hurry
what is that oh it's like a conch shell we're good we're good we've got enough
people on it right yeah it's just right here they got it it's gonna be close you
took that real wide turn real wide corner there you didn't have to take it
that wide three get it in get it in one well I know where to go fuck games
addicting by the way I just want to make it really clear I'm not I don't hate
Pokemon Pokemon school it's an interesting concept I think the show was
interesting I like I thought it was interesting that was cool it was a cool
show it was worth watching I would say I want to make sure I go back to that
because people were pretty probably upset about that I don't mean that I
do that sometimes that's what we do they make up fake scenarios oh yeah oh yeah my
allowance doubled and it's all thanks to my papa after all he's a great captain
he's a great captain but when in the world will he be able to come home yeah
all right I want that thing both they're buried up it's probably worth a hundred
two hundred bucks it's worth it so he's gonna go dig it I need some
white I only have six white Pikmin that's horrible
Pikmin's cooler than Jerma I mean there's some facets of Pikmin that are
cooler than me I still think I had my coolness factor is a little bit higher
than Pikmin by just a small amount I think so I'm more red coolness factor
all right not wasting time let's just get over there and do it don't lose
anybody come on don't walk into the wall either somebody did I'm here at CVS
yeah yeah I'll get a coconut water this thing's really good
was it over here over here okay no water yeah guess I like coconut water it's good
stuff I really like it I was 20 years older than me yeah it's it's kind of
crazy yeah hey what yeah I can I said I've wait like 10 12 5 15 the nectar in
here right now what do I want here I'm looking for other treasure that's out in
the open I need more treasures I want more out in the open treasure or ones that
can be done needles moving needles moving a little bit you see that it's
bouncing a little bit ooh I see one any thoughts on baked ham that's good it's
good I think it's worth eating and what is that oh that's not treasure okay it's
good no give him back everyone's do 25% more damage right you submerged castle
no I'm not doing that again that ones I just want to collect treasures for a
little bit us we got we got eat we got yo eat we got EOTW we got EOTW coming up
EOTW slower so it sounds better EOTW V and of the no EOS EOST EOW
what's the W end of this world stream there's still shit out here that I need
end of the world voice well you know guys I'm looking out my window right now
there's a huge burning red circle above us it's huge and it's getting closer so I
mean an end of the world voice I guess yeah we'll be back tomorrow though
tomorrow we're gonna be playing slime rancher it's another highly requested
game you want my final opinions on Pikmin 2 it was good it was very good I
liked it a lot I see why people love this series I see what people like the
game very stressful very hard submerged castle one of the hardest levels from
what I've been told I think it's really fun though I like it finish it then I
did I paid off all the debt I'm doing extra content we saw the credits land
on his head you didn't get to the true ending people drowning get out of the
water where's this last piece of treasure sir dog it's a hot joke
well let me get him he wants to come in he wants to come in but he's he's he is
staring at me he's just like he wants me I think he wants me to do something for
him what's what is it what's matter you just want to stare at me do you like
Pikmin yes I would eat it did you eat one of these Pikmin yes I mean he's like a
bulby he's one of those bulb things oh I need to get up there he did he didn't
say that he didn't say that wrong button you guys are a press with the
minus button on your Wiimote and doesn't do anything I think I just hate this
control I think I just really hate the Wiimote and nunchuck I think I hate it
what okay what's the um did I put this on a tier list have I ever done a tier
list with the Wiimote on it with game controllers I don't think I've ever done
it I think I have to do that this would be somewhere at the bottom all right
treasure come on secret treasure I think yeah I have I think I have oh here we go
where is it huh shit okay hold on okay this is gonna be really difficult I need
just yellow only that yellow is the only one I want we're gonna go very slow here
you have to wrap around it's gonna be really difficult no it's not can I throw
it up there can we reach from here ooh got it nice okay so how do they bring it
down hell yeah we got it you need to save Louie do I though he's not even in
the third game Louie in cannon there's not he's gone he's only in the
multiplayer mode and Pikmin 3 isn't he I get more people on that faster
Hermes bored none no I'm just like chillin you understand I did I had to sit
there and just do 20 minutes of annoying voices fuck that's like I did that
already at them but I'm using that as an excuse as to why oh I'm good just
relaxing I run like this for 20 minutes oh boy
elastic pickle cool it's still other treasure here it's probably buried over
here it was something to do over this way wasn't there remember I was like
throwing people up here but now you want to get out you need to go outside hmm
okay you want to go outside he needs to go out he's giving me those eyes yeah
he's giving me the eyes all right let me out let me take him out and well I'll
come back well I'll do yeah I'll do one more day I'll do one more one more day
and then we'll call it let me go let him outside though I'll be right back okay
hello sorry that took a while what is that some of you need Jesus okay let's
do one more day and then I'm gonna go some of you need Jesus and what does
this say it's pain no not that this what about Louie Louie is gonna be fine cat
boy of Wall Street spam I am so lonely I want a friend that'll listen to my
troubles I want to meet someone like you contact me at Nintendo comm who's that
supposed to be what's the silhouette all right the last day I want to go over
here I want to just look around this the this is the new zone I only was it I
went here once okay I want some stray treasures I want to look around too it
was twice but you ruin the stream oh yeah this is where like the do the voice
for 20 minutes thing came from right oh yeah I haven't even looked around forgot
about that you're right I get more as you forget well I didn't forget about
that I just forgot that it was here let's get more yellow I have a lot of
yellows don't I yeah whatever it's a little blue yes mobile go to the dream
den it's the final boss I don't know what that is dream den let me explore
some egg we're gonna get there's gonna be collapse upon thing here these eggs
are not real six whites and four purple he's ready I have I would be very
surprised if you were not kidding there's no way I'm ready you need a
hundred purple Pikmin for that fight I I'm definitely not going to do that
that's right the bridge right here but this is like weird guy all right I need
to get blue don't go in the water everyone relax blue needs to take oh god
oh my god oh my god oh my god oh my god run run run run run run he shoots bombs
okay he shoots out bombs if I get rid of him I got it tonight bait him I throw
them across and then fight come on get over here come on get over here can I
make that I'm afraid to throw because he the hill just get it they'll get attacked
all right good bait you come no oh wait wait wait wait hold on almost there come
on come on no no no turn around turn around turn around turn around why not
that's what I didn't want to have happen right exactly what I wanted to
not have happen oh my god the games lagging is it's just around everybody
you know all right fuck this just come over here get over here no you dummies
everybody get the fuck back here toxic well I mean this is the endgame theater
okay you please move out of the way and none of these gas Pikmin I don't they're
all gonna die from this is there another way I can get everybody across not
having to do oh my god and there's one of these assholes too oh fuck this place
that's I hate this place this is the worst level in the game I like the water
level of this shoot him shoot him oh my god kill why did I kill him no get all
right I'm done I'm done I can do be the full letter grade just dropped this was
like an 80 like this is like an 87 as I was 75 just because of this part right
here look at the remote look at just look at look at the remote that I'm not
doing that's not me doing that and look at those huge guys in there this is a
gauntlet everybody get out of here I'm going the other way this is for him be
careful give me a break from all appearances this is particularly
frightening crevice the data is horrifying courage is one thing but
recklessness is something else perhaps we should turn back can we just can I go
in from here or do I have to get hit by this still wish to enter keep your
daring and check okay that's one I want to see that the the space so you all
right so you're telling me that rock went through here didn't hit me or this
the boss guy wrapped all the way around and then spun around run everybody over
why did it not hit this with this or me or here or here or how why was that so
perfect it didn't what it didn't hit the edge of the cave it went all the way
around and didn't hit the wall and they came all the way back around and rolled
over everybody fuck it's 71 oh wait but the ball what the bulb creatures were in
the game it's all right it just went up to 78 that's right that's right that's
really important well I need to more Pikmin we're sitting here rating a game
all over the place what about the treasure I yeah I know I need more
Pikmin to get over there I have something in front of the sensor bar yeah
like toxic air criticizing a 20 year old game omega low no I'm putting myself
back in time when I had a Wii and I would have been sitting on my couch at
480p saying the same shit only this time I have like a pair of cocky's on what's
this that's one of these guys hold on back it up back it up back back back
back sacrifice you look at how scrumptious he looks I know sacrifice a
blue one oh no let me look scrumptious there we go get him not why were there
this motherfucker just said cookies no I didn't I said cocky's khakis what I
really want come out and get him pants like cocky's khaki pants khakis I can't
kill this guy like just come out I want I had my fucking cocky's on right now
man I would throw this we vote into the drywall it's way to God like what the
fuck come out and come out just get out no no no no no no no no no no no no no
no that rolls up here this game gets a five okay get up pick me not just
bullets you can carry I wouldn't call them bullets where's my Mario 64 camera
what like hitting Z think like was his resident evil fucking for give me a
break like why can I just I just want to turn the camera drain that water
quickly I think I can do it he's gonna burn everybody he hasn't decided who he's
gonna do it to yet burn me burn me instead burn me burn me instead he's in
water it doesn't work was that nothing there's no cave there all right well now
I can do that next time and his electric fan all right I'm giving it one more one
more day one more day one more day that was bullshit one more day they're not die
if they're in the squad they're fine as long as they're in your party or in your
team right I didn't get this far in this is kind of all we've been doing eat the
last three streams Louis are you eating well when were you when you were bored
you were quite skinny so I made you clean your plate be sure to cook
suspicious food before eating it reply we have no idea where Louis is that's it
look he is dead sorry or just just ignore just act like in wrong number the
Louie and there you know Louie here you might have the wrong email I have the
wrong email Louis Smith at Hoka Tate industries.com this is his email I think
you might have got the wrong guy wrong email all right 94 to this is bad no
Louie here just ooey gooey here I'm surprised you knew the name of the
industry the industry okay look I might have like ADHD and I might have like a
lot of attention problems but I mean like that's I've been playing the game
for like 14 hours if I didn't know what Hoka Tate industries was I feel like I
wouldn't be paying attention to anything in the game I mean anything
drink up all right good good good good good good good good I'm ready I want to
go back that way we need to run oh this guy's hitting himself wait we can drop
death from above here we go all right I'm getting at least one treasure from
here you better believe it it's a thought there's a fire guy over here
there's a there's a one fire guy take care of him the water guy over here take
care of the water guy and then the electric fence needs to be taken care of
by the electric guys all right let's go you guys good you guys all right wait
what is going on right now who's doing that what is killing them what's going
on hello yeah I couldn't even see that like blending into the ground they
should just make the ground concrete in this game like it's so ugly just kidding
I'm sorry oops all I'm saying is it should have been a cartoon like what
would it come on this is a perfect cartoon Hickman 1, Hickman 2, Hickman 3
where's the like animated series that'd be so awesome is art isn't it oh they're
animated shorts are they really come here guys there is that's cool I would
love a little cartoon Hickman the animated series would be awesome come on
hurry up why get in there and do something watch the shorts on YouTube I
don't know if I can I'm kind of scared to do that am I is it really gotten to
the point where I'm afraid to like watch a YouTube video of like a show or
something it is technically Nintendo video right Nintendo doesn't fuck around
anymore no entertainment is illegal didn't you know that yeah well I know
people saying what about Bionicle yeah Bionicle is free to watch on YouTube
that does not mean it is free for me to distribute on my stream there's a thought
of legality there oh my god I need that pinecone I do not have the broadcasting
rights to the Bionicle movie it's how this works just because something is
free does not mean that I can just do whatever I want with it just hold up a
controller and pretend it's a video game didn't somebody do that at one point for
like a Super Bowl kill kill kill kill kill kill kill hurry hurry up please
we're good it was UFC that's so stupid that's
unbelievable but now I I cannot just stream the Bionicle movie I do not have
the rights to I don't have the broadcasting rights to Bionicle which I
need to be able to show that on stream and is it correct me if I'm wrong here
but Bionicle is Disney is it not I don't think that's gonna happen isn't that
underneath the Disney umbrella it's a Lego hold on Bionicle Bionicle who owns
Bionicle Lego would never be able to watch it it's Lego wait Lego is
Bionicle but isn't who owns Lego is Lego just Lego and somebody own Lego is a
Warner Lego just is Lego but who has like who has like the rights to like the
Lego movies and stuff and Lego media TV shows and stuff John Lego I thought it
was Disney I thought Disney had like the broadcasting rights to like Bionicle or
something I don't know why I thought that I know where I got that from what I
get that from they do okay so I was right this present be extremely careful
all the more your job is to protect his life at all costs
hello it's me mr. Bionicle Jerva go right ahead thank you mr. Bionicle I
really appreciate that okay I got treasures over here but where is it oh
fuck run away holy shit there's too many things over here yeah the Lego group is
owned by a certain company but the dish the distribution rights to the Bionicle
movies I don't think is Lego so I'm trying to say run run run run run run I
think I'm just dead here it is Disney people saying no it is I think it is
though I actually do think it is it's distributed by Buena Vista which is
Disney right yeah I had it right there's so many enemies here it's just just a
mess this is a mess right now didn't I drain this water already I thought I
already drained this oh whatever this place is cool but not really I mean
Disney does not have rights okay regardless if it's Disney or Warner or
Buena Vista or paramount whatever it doesn't matter it's not me I don't own
the right can't stream it buy out Windows Vista no Buena Vista okay I'll
add I'll see you guys tomorrow buy them you millionaire listen even if I let's
just say I had let's just say I was right let's just say it was a millionaire
you know how much it's gonna cost to buy Bionicle probably like more that yeah
gotta probably add a zero or two it's probably quite a few zeros to buy
Bionicle to stream it the one movie I guarantee it's least it's at least 10
million to buy the rights to Bionicle and that would be a steal I got some
treasure though ask them nicely you know I did who knows I we that we I've
reached out yeah I got a guy working on it we'll see probably not though don't
get your hopes up okay if I do if I ended up ever getting the rights to
actually broadcast that on stream you do understand that to be able to do that I
probably have to sign an agreement that means I cannot I probably can't like say
like dog shit on stream anymore that would have to be a very I think family
friendly stream if I was given the rights by whatever group owns it to
distribute it on when watch it on stream okay we're back and I'm back to this
bridge will stay but wait sorry whatever I'll see you guys tomorrow I got a new
cave but now yeah that's it that's it we'll see you tomorrow signed off it's
still playing no no no no I got my fun out of it I have my fun in Pikmin so the
amount of times that I said I hate this controller versus this was a really fun
game that was a cool thing I just saw what's the ratio there four to one five
to one it's at least like five to one right I give Pikmin to a 76 and then in
brackets plus five with GameCube controller does that sound pretty good
score it is I enjoyed it very much so all right I'll see you guys tomorrow
we're gonna do slime rancher tomorrow which is just another Pikmin there's
just another cute little blue red yellow purple orange monsters that you throw
around is it a completely different game we'll see you tomorrow have a great rest
of your night let's do the credits what time 2 p.m. Pacific time 2 p.m. Pacific
same time we started today if you're gonna be around maybe we'll see you if
not then have a great night thanks for watching as always this has been Pikmin
2 I now have access to a Wii U so if there's something that is worth playing
on the Wii U and I do have it and I don't think I've ever really streamed
anything on the Wii U I did a bunch of Wii stuff but I don't think I've ever
really done a Wii U game do Pikmin 3 I don't know it's a literally only Pikmin
3 is the only one we'll see I'll give it a look all right here come the subs
thanks everybody it's insane how many people have subbed to this channel still
I don't I sometimes I just I just wonder why stare at the ceiling and I'm like
how can this many people want to give me five dollars a month I don't understand
but thanks I really appreciate it nonetheless it's a Plants vs. Zombies HD
they really kind of ruined that franchise didn't they that's weird that
went completely 180 real quickly didn't it I went from one of them was most
beloved everyone at PAX has the funny mask on and the cone on their head to
this is the most disgusting awful shitty game shitty practice ever by a company
ever and no one cares about pick I was at portal to Pikmin 2 what plans for
zombies 2 if you want to see a total 180 of community engagement versus
hatred of an entire franchise look no further than plants for a zombie 2 I
remember playing plants for zombies 2 and I was my base melted off
essentially with how I could not understand and I was just flabbergasted
what you needed to pay fucking money to like do well in that game that's all I
remembered I remember it was I got like 20 30 levels in or something oh this is
kind of fun but then it was like you like you're getting overwhelmed unless
you like use the super electrocution devices and stuff so what ended up
happening is I just ended up having a bunch of the electrocution like super
killed all that just wiped the screen things and I didn't play the game
anymore I just opened a level waited for enough stuff was to be loaded onto the
screen and then kill everything with the electricity I didn't even play the game
it was horrendous that was one of the worst games I've ever played and I'd
really mean that that was like one of the most that was one of the stupidest
things I've ever played I've ever played it's insane how bad they fucked up that
first game is unironically fantastic oh yeah well a lot of the pop cap stuff
was unironically fantastic it was just egregious horrendous business practices
and notice how you did they even talk about plans for zombies they have that
garden warfare game but I'll be honest I don't I don't care at all about that I
doesn't I wanted like a plans for zombies 2 or plans for zombies 3 or
something I've actually heard that it's not bad I've heard that garden warfare
is actually pretty fun that's to me to me that's the that's the side series
right that's the that's not the main series they've got plans for zombies
plans for zombies 2 plans for somebody's garden warfare cool it's a really kind
of fun an FPS game go check it out maybe but I want it I want like a main
plants for zombies game that's not just I on the app store dude move on no I'm
not gonna move on this is incredibly important topic to me I'm not gonna move
on this is this is like move on move on Jeremy just go move on all right I'm
gonna move on because this thing just beeped at me and I got kind of scared I
got heard something in my ear I heard and I thought that somebody did
something all right I'll see you later have a great rest of your night see
you tomorrow I'm gonna play slime rancher tomorrow good night guys take
care of yourselves we'll see you soon Wednesday archaeology stream March 6th
and 1 o'clock Pacific I'm gonna be digging up all kinds of interesting
things probably get your shovels ready we'll see you later good night