I want to read this one. Viva Pinata ran its course. Resident sleeper Drew Crew is out in full force.
Oh, so we didn't run Drew Crew's course with like five streams and like 17 hours of gameplay?
I think you- I think you're holding on to something there. It's been like three and a half hours of
Viva Pinata. Do you guys act like I've streamed this game for the last like four years straight?
Holy shit, Viva Pinata. It's been 75 hours of this game straight. I played it yesterday for like
three hours. I need to check on my animals and that's what we're gonna do. Check on your animal
crossing village. I can't. It's not here. I got- my girlfriend needs something. I gotta have something
to do. She's playing animal crossing. I'm playing my version of animal crossing which is animal
related and it's called Viva Pinata out of control. What am I supposed to name the game?
Trouble in paradise. That's the one. It's the animal crossing wannabe. They both came out the
same time. I'm opening it up. We're going. This is what I want to play. This is what we're gonna play.
Where's my headphones? What the fuck happened? Where are my headphones? Why am- why are my
headphones not in this room? Wait, they were connected yesterday. What? Hold on a second.
Why are my headphones not here? What the fuck? I didn't take them out of here. This doesn't make
any sense. I got them. They were wrapped up in the bottom of the chair. Okay, we're good.
No, it wasn't Kim. It wasn't Kim. All right, I got them. We're good. Imagine that. All right,
here we go. Did we just get bits? We did. We did right now. Very nice. Gave 20 dollars in bits.
Can you guys even hear this? Yeah, you can't hear. 20 bucks in bits. 2,000. Love you,
German. Always stay safe, bro. That's been very nice. Well, I think that's very nice. So,
thank you. Don't mind me just passing through. All right, what were we doing? I wanted to get-
Okay, here we go. Oh, yes, there they are. It's been so long since I've seen you two.
Wouldn't they just drown? Wait, wouldn't that frog be like in- like swallowing water? Wake them up.
All right, so let me- okay, right, right, right. That's what I was gonna do. I got a plan. We're
gonna get cats. Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah. Cats eat mice. Mice have sex. Mice make more mice.
Feed cats. Cats have sex. What do cats need? We'll find out maybe eventually here. Okay,
give me my shovel. I need crabs too. Wait. All right, send that person off in a cannon. I'll
level up if I do this, right? Yeah. Anyways, I didn't do an intro. Hey, guys. Welcome to the
stream. Fucking cool. Where's that? Where's the cannon box? That was lame. Do it again.
No, I already did my intro. I don't know. This isn't like 2012. I don't need to be like, hey,
what's going on, everybody? It's Jerma here with another stream. No, where- this is 2020.
That was better. He's unprofessional. Gameplay. In that way, how come it's not shooting at all?
How many do I need to pack in here? Did I not pack it? I did. So why is the cannon not shooting?
Like my post if I'm here- if you're here from the discord. I got it. I am. Has to be a new- oh.
So did I just remove that person for no reason? Kind of annoying. All right, what's most- whatever
I want. Like my post if you're here from the discord. All right, what do you think? I'm
thinking sand. I'm thinking sand over this way. Yep. That looks good to me. I don't want that
much sand though because I- don't the snakes not like sand? Fix the noise gate on your microphone.
Don't worry. In like- in a week, I won't even be in the same place. We'll fix that some other
way. Why is the sound fucked up? I mean it seems like it's working. No, there's this-
like what's wrong with it? Yeah, it's working. It's working. It's fine. Do a stream from the back of
the moving van. Like I'm just sitting back there. Just like sit at a desk trying to like stream
something. What happened? Like why- why don't- why- why's my right analog not work now?
What the fuck? Why can I not- up and down on my analog doesn't do anything?
Okay. What the hell is going on? What's that? What's that mean? What's that? What's that mean?
Battery? Well, why can I go forward? Wait, there's no battery going to the right analog?
Battery going to X? What? Hold on. I do it. He's orange. Stop. I just want to play with my animals.
Why does the right analog not fucking work? What does this take for batteries?
Two double A? Got it right here. Oh, right. Okay. Oh, surgery. Surgery on stream. I didn't even
sedate this guy. I didn't even- I didn't even get anesthesia. Sorry. Which way does it go?
Which way does it go? Wait, did you take- you can't take that serial number and like fucking
like do anything to me, right? All right, let's- where's uh- how does it go? Wait, oh fuck!
God damn it, they're all the same brand! And I just dropped them. I think- wait, I don't remember.
I think this is it. My brand. Why are you orange? Because this fucking white balance isn't set up
right now. I don't know. What? Okay. L. The triggers don't work. The bumpers work. B doesn't work.
B doesn't work? What's going on? Those are the right batteries. Okay, up and down works. Start
works. B does work. So why does the right analog not work? The triggers don't work either. Hold on,
I gotta- I gotta restart the fucking game? Smash the controller in the closet. No, no, no. Let me-
Hold on. This doesn't make any sense. Controller style? What? What? What the hell?
Why would they do that? Why would that even be an option? Simple controls. Well, all simple
controls does is just remove the function of half of your controller. All right, where- okay, let's
go. Okay, I want to do more- I want to do more grass over here. This dude does like a dirt over
here. Get the crab? I'm gonna. I'm gonna. I'm trying. I'm just trying to make this look a little
better. I just got an expanded- I got an expanded ground. Cheeto puff controller?
Let's do dirt. Yeah, over to here. Getting rid of this- yeah, that's like a little beach. That's
fine. The snakes don't like this though. I'm gonna- let me change this. Turn the orange cam back on.
It's fine. No, I don't like this because you can see my fucking red eyes from like sleeping
two hours a night. No, I don't like that. You guys can see my like my fucking like two hours of
sleep eyes. You should wink. I'm not fucking winking. He's high. Please. I'm trying to make
this place look better. What shit are you wearing? What shit?
It's a Pac-Man t-shirt. Are you out of your fucking mind?
Look at how messed up this is. Let me plant down- it doesn't matter. I'll fix it.
I just don't want this to look so shitty because this looks awful.
Look at how much cleaner this is gonna start to look now.
How's David doing? I don't know. I don't know- I don't know who David is.
All right, that's better. We got a little pond over there. Now let's put this away.
Now I'd like- why are you- what are you doing? Why the fuck is she doing?
It's the guy you stole the Xbox from. I didn't steal any Xbox actually. This is- this was- I
bought it. All right, now we need a little bit more. We'll do desert over here. How do I get
you to get in here? Just eat one of these mice. Hurry up. Let's do desert over here. You bought a
stolen Xbox. I don't- I don't think that's what happened. I think I made that name.
I don't know why but maybe- I don't know. I did for some reason. I can't think of a reason why.
That's a liar. I don't know. Maybe I'll check and see what David's like play history is, right?
All right, that's good. All right, this is a daisy. I need some more. Look at this. It's starting
to come together. What's in here? What the hell is this? Oh shit, it's another- another water
tube. Wait, what happened to the other water tube? Did somebody eat it? Who ate it? Did somebody eat
that old water tube? Oh, it's like a little lily pad. I did. Well, you fucking shouldn't have done
that. How much water can the watercress take in? Too much. Okay, so we get the- this is good.
So what does it take for a crab again? We need much more water. So I'm thinking- so we got a
little sand portion over there. We need more sand. I'm thinking another sand portion this way,
right? Because this is- we could bring the crabs in over here. That's what I'm thinking.
You're right, I shouldn't have done that. The streamer is pissed. Why am I pissed?
Is it because I'm like red?
You know what we're gonna do tomorrow? And for the next 30 to 40 straight days, this.
I'm gonna play Viva Pinata every single fucking goddamn day
the rest of my life until I'm 100. Because I'm- I'm- I'm making it to 100, okay? You know how
many green vegetables I eat on a weekly basis? Not enough. Probably like one serving a week,
which is bad. You should be- you should do like a green serving of vegetables every fucking day.
At least every other day. But now that I think about it, I'll probably- nutritionally speaking,
I'll probably make it to like 61. So that's why I gotta start now. I've got to start eating green
vegetables on every meal. Oh, seeds. When my mask gets broken, I fix it with flour and water paste.
You gotta start like 20 years ago, dude. I actually- I actually eat very well. I eat at least
one green vegetable at every meal. Can I even do this with a straight face? Oh, the trick stick.
Let's try that. Tahini- I have tahini paste at every meal. Uh, plant dried out. Didn't I just
overwater this like five fucking seconds ago? Oh, the $20- a $20 donation just came in a bit.
From Very Noise. Another one. 2,000 bits. Thanks, dude. Thank you for that. 40- that's 4,000 bits
total in the last like 10 minutes. Thank you. The Cheez-Its have made him orange. Should I fix it?
You want me to fix it so it's not orange? You want me to put like a- like a handsome filter on?
No. What? Why? Put the handsome filter on? Hold on. Wait, this is wrong. What? Hold on. Something's
wrong here. I can't get- it doesn't- it looks wrong like this and it looks wrong like this.
Okay, here we go. Right? All right, we'll put the handsome filter on here in a second.
I could- I could be- I could be anything. You can imagine the rest of my features.
See how handsome this is? What's going on? No, fuck! You know what the worst part about this is?
You know when you're watching a streamer and they have autofocus on, which by the way,
you want a streamer tip, turn autofocus off because what happens is it gets like this
and they don't even know it's like that and the camera is fucking struggling so hard to just-
please refocus it and it could be like this for about two to three straight minutes.
But we're going to keep it here for five straight minutes. Wait, how else can I change this to make
it- how else can I change it to be like, hey streamer, something's wrong with your webcam?
How about this? All right, this is- this is- I just plugged it in. Yeah. This is- I just plugged
the webcam in and didn't even do one setting. I just turned the fucking stream on after- this
is not even default. I just plugged it in and turned it on. No, actually that- it'd be more
like this. This is more accurate. If you just plugged it in for the first time and didn't even
fucking do any settings. Let's make me a little bit more handsome though. Now this is- this is
just the- this is the side image for every copypasta villain or monster you've ever read about.
Like, yeah, like turn the blur off. Yeah, it has to be forward and like eyes wide open and mouth
wide open. We can do a better one, hold on. Really close too, like- can we be dead? This is actually
scary. It's delayed. Oh, whoa, look at that guy. Kind of looks all right. I'm scaring me. All right,
get this off. Go shave. It's a process, okay? It's a- you know, you know when Jeremy goes like this
and he gets like right into the fucking camera and he goes like, keep the cam on. No, all right,
I- people- animals are over here. What? Oh shit, real face. This is what I really look like.
Fuck. Come on, man. We can't do that.
Here we go. This hurts my fucking eyes. I'm done. Oh, there he is for real. Now let's go the other
way. Oh, this is what I look like. Oh shit. Oh, fuck. This sound is freaking me out.
What's- my skin doesn't look like this. What's with my lips? All right, I've just burnt. I can
only stream for like three or four hours and I've already burnt like- burnt, burnt. I've already
burnt. Say it. Do it right. I've already burnt like 30 minutes. I just burnt it. Nothing's real.
Nothing is real. Nothing is real. All right, what the fuck was I doing? Sounds fucking with my head.
All right, let's go. I need a surfboard in the garden. You got it. Where do I get it? Who sells
a surfboard? It's desynced. What the fuck are you talking about? What are chocolate coins if not
for spending? I'd spend- It's not desynced. Better value. It's not desynced. What? It's not. No,
it can't be. It can't be. I refuse to believe them. Don't believe them. All right, so we need a
toy surfboard, right? Toys? Woo woo train? Where do I get a surfboard? Toad voice. It's horribly
desynced. Okay, I don't believe you. The camera is set to be- Hold on. No. The camera is set to be
delayed by 650 milliseconds. The microphone is 650 milliseconds. Ready? That's- This is how you know.
I do know because they're both set for 650. Yes, so now it's 650. My mic is 650. You're burning time.
You guys are burning time. I've got three hours. You're burning time. My voice is early. My voice
is early. This happens before the mouth moves. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yep. Yep. I already said
fucking go. No, they're right. They're right. Okay. I need a surfboard. Do I not have access
to a surfboard yet or what? I can't- I don't have a surfboard. When do you get a surfboard?
Does anybody know? Stop sign. It's going to be in the toys. They probably don't have it.
This is some kind of currency thing. No one plays this game. This is such a- People love this game.
You guys are being mean to this series for no reason. It's- This is like a fun game. Like the
piñata animals. Like, come on. What a fucking idea. A new piñata has been spotted in the desert. Ooh,
let's go. He's scared of the duck. I don't know. I can't have a surfboard. But piñatas. Like,
that's so- Look at how cool that is. All right. You got to explain to me how catching fish in
Animal Crossing is pog. But watching frog in lake is un-pog. I need an explanation here. Neither are
pog. Neither. You tell me that serpent one is un-pog. But if I- That was pretty un-pog.
Okay. So let's go over this again. So this is un-pog. But if I took the head off
this snake and put it on a standing body, gave him a shovel, and had him go like this.
That would be pog. I just want to make sure I get the facts correct with my brain.
Yes. Yo, that's pog. Why does this guy hate Animal Crossing? I love Animal Crossing.
But I don't- I refuse to believe that this is an un-pog moment right here.
That was not a good example. I like them both. And they both are fun. And I can't wait for Viva
Piñata 3. On the road again. Coming soon for the Xbox Scorpion. I'll be the guy that plays it.
All right. What does this person want? All right. You guys, I know what you're doing.
So fucking tactful. You're distracting me and derailing things so we can- You're burning time.
Fucking smart. Real smart. Pretty good idea. And I get it now. I'm very easy to- I'm very
manipulatable apparently. It's still working. All right. I'm going to go back to what I was doing
in my pog experience. Digging holes in this game sucks. But if you dig a hole in Animal Crossing-
I can't even put it there. I want to put two images side by side. I want to put this
with resident sleepers and then I want to put the Animal Crossing dig with like a bunch of pogs.
Somebody get on it. Somebody get on it. Oh, this has to be desert, desert, desert, desert, desert.
Yeah, yeah, yeah. That's a terrible meme. It's not a- I'm not making a meme. That's from my
personal collection. I'm going to have that playing on a Roku stick behind me in a frame
for the next six weeks. Where does this go? What the fuck is this thing? Doesn't this go in the
desert? What's this? This is not the right- Oh, does this have to go in soil? Oh,
forever sucks at this game. It's a reddit joke. I have a feeling that all the people that talk
all this shit about reddit have like a post history. It's like 30 pages long. Fucking redditor.
I can't believe he uses reddit. And then you go to the like- you slash- whatever the name is.
Here it is. Like 10 pages. Like r slash smash brothers. They've been on- they have like 600
posts. And they're all at least a paragraph each. That's un-pog. All right, I gotta go back to the
desert. I want to find the new- good work. You're doing a good job. Look at you guys. Look at you
go. Look at- look at- look at you go. Uh, no, I don't want to go to the Arctic. I want a gecko.
Yes, I do. I don't think I've been here at night. Irma actually made me have fun. How
does he do it? What do you mean I made you- what? We're just hanging out here, man.
We're just having fun, man. You're forcing fun. What did you guys think? I have some like fucking
streamer playbook on how to like- we're having fun in a jail cell. I've never heard of a Java- Java
prison system where the doors are all unlocked and you can leave the prison at any time.
Yeah, sorry, you're sentenced for 20 years in prison. By the way, uh, you know, the doors are
all open and you can just- you can leave whenever you want, sir. This is a- what do you mean prison?
You can just walk out of yourself, walk out the door, and go to the nearest Wendy's and
order a fucking number four. What are you guys doing? I love the 4% battery. All right, I need
to lock this fucking thing in place. All right, let me ask you a question. Would you- would you
swipe left on this person? Wait, is it right? Would you swipe- all right, would you swipe right
on this? Yeah, I think this is one of those cases where you go, oh, I mean, it's all right, but
you got any like other pictures? And then the next four pictures are me, like, with my face
blocked out like this, and this is another person, and this is another person, and I'm like-
I'm like peeking through like this. This is where they are. It's like this.
I'd fucking- I- why would I- I'd swipe right on that person because that person's me. If I was on
tinder, it'd be like, oh yeah, that guy looks all right. I'd fucking hang out with that guy.
Gecko alert! Gecko alert! You're an egomaniac. Set off early and catch some good stuff. I like
your style. Some of the- some of the smartest people ever were, and the most successful,
and the coolest people ever were egomaniacs. Like, um, who's like an egomaniac that was
really successful that now everyone doesn't look back and go, oh, that person sucked?
Is that gonna happen to me? In like 40 years, are you guys gonna be like in your 40s and 50s
and look back and be like, oh wow, that guy sucked? Shit. All right, we're gonna dial it back.
I'm like a- I'm like a- look, here's the safe way to answer any of these questions.
Oh, what do you- how good looking do you think you are? I'm like a seven. I'm a seven, I think.
And then people are like, okay, that's not too high, but that's not too low. You got like some
confidence. Yeah, all right. I'm a seven. Just say seven for everything. Oh, I just- I just- that
was a home-cooked meal. I just cooked it for you, and I- what did you think? If you didn't like it,
that was like- I'm a seven. I was into it. 75. Sounds pretty good. Or if you are reviewing- if
you're reviewing any movie, TV show, video game, or book, just do that too. It works everywhere.
75 is terrible. 75 is not terrible. 75 is- I thought this was terrible,
but I didn't want to tell you that it was terrible. Fuck! Don't listen to that. I've done this like
10 times already on this stream. Uh-oh. No, now everyone's gonna go back and look for all the
sevens I gave to games. Oh, shit. Uh, what have I done the two recently? He gave a seven to Outer
Wilds. I did not. No, I did not. I gave that an 89. Get out of here. I did not give Animal Crossing
a seven. I did not. Outer Wilds was an 89. He hates Mario Sunshine. I didn't even- I didn't even
score Mario Sunshine. What are you talking about? He gave a seven to that ninja game. Oh, okay,
this is the image I was looking for. Rate Animal Crossing. No, I can't. Because if I give Animal
Crossing a score, it's either too low throw rocks at his house or it's too high. That game's boring.
What an idiot. This- I don't think I can take a position on there. Get the rocks. They're in my
eye. I'm having fun. It doesn't matter. It could be anything in the fucking screen right now.
All right, what was it? Here. I like Animal Crossing. This is- this is just a little, like,
this is just a little shtick, you know what I mean? But it's- I like- I really like- I really
like Animal Crossing. No one- wait. Why is there- why is there- why is there dialogue in the left
one? Why is there dialogue in the left one? Who's Lily? Lily, League of Legends team? What the fuck
did you get this from? The Legends team. What did you get this fucking image from? All right,
anyways. What was I just saying? It's a random screen cap. Oh yeah, I need a trap. Business
edition. That's not necessary. You are a boomer. All right, that- what do you want me to say? Yeah,
yes I am. Yeah, yes I am. I'm a boomer at me. Like, how do I respond to that? What's the proper way
to respond to somebody saying that now? All right, now I need a- what do they- they want a snow thing?
They know. I don't even know- I'm- that's- but that's the thing, I'm not even. All right, come on. No
snake. You go get this. I won't- look at- look at that, look at that, look at that, look at that,
look at that, look at that, look at that, look at that, look at that, look at that, yep, look at that,
yep, look at that, got it. Resident sleeper, resident sleeper, resident sleeper, resident sleeper.
You know, I'm gonna record something right now and then when I- the more- when I see them, I'm
just gonna- hold on. Yeah, let's go back. Well, not- there's a cooldown on it. I know you guys are just
doing it for fun now. All right, where's my- let's go get it. I finally am gonna get a gecko.
We're not. This is boring. I'll press it right now and it'll- you'll be- wait, this is not even
centered. This looks fucked up. What did you guys do? Well, hey, what the fuck did you just do?
What did- what did you do? What did you do? I'm sorry! All right, here we go. You don't like the
frogs. Frog at the bottom of the sea. There's a- there's a frog at the bottom- there's a leg on
the frog at the bottom of the sea. There's a leg on the frog at the bottom of the sea. There's a
sea, there's a sea, there's a hole at the bottom of the sea. There's a ward on the- ward on the leg
of the frog at- ward on the leg of the frog at the bottom of the sea. There's a ward on the leg on
the frog at the bottom of the sea. There's a hole at the bottom of the sea. There's a fly on the
ward of the leg of the frog at the bottom of the sea. There's a fly on the leg- there's a fly on
the ward of the leg of the frog at the bottom of the sea. There's a- there's something down there
at the bottom of the sea. There's a hair on the fly in the ward of the frog. There's a- there's a
hair- there's a hair on the fly in the- there's a hair on the fly on the ward of the leg of the
frog at the bottom of the sea. There's a hair on the fly in the ward of the frog in the log- fuck!
You guys didn't go to preschool? How many- what- you guys how- ow! What you made me do? I'm not
American. What you guys didn't have like the- there's a this, and a this, and a this, and a this, and a
this, and a this, and a this, and a this, and a this, and a this, and a this, and a this, and a that,
and then everyone's like laughs, and has fun, everyone's like moving around, and cheering,
and stuff. What- what- what- what happened? You guys didn't do that? You just don't remember you
did. I do. I remember everything. Nobody had that. I feel bad that you didn't have the fucking this,
and the this, and the this, and the this, and the this, and the this thing. It was so much fun.
I actually did. Yeah, I know. Good. What are you doing? Look, all right. I'm gonna- okay, I'll get-
I know- I- I know that there's- I know that about that chocolate factory. Okay? I know it- I know
that the chocolate factory is- I know that's a chocolate factory. All right. What are you guys
linking? You got- I'm- but wait a minute, but I'm running out of time here. I hate that I know
what you're talking about. See? I knew it. What? What's wrong with this? You guys- here's the bad
meme you asked for. Wait, did- we already showed- wait, have you been gone for the last like 30
minutes making this? Somebody did it already. Shit, I'm sorry. I'm sorry. But this one's good too.
This one's also good. This is seven out of ten? Hey. Hey! Hey! No, this is- I would give this- I
would give this an eight. Okay, here we go. What the fuck am I doing? I want- where's the gecko?
Did you guys make me lose my gecko? I think you actually made me lose the gecko. I think he left.
You gotta be kidding me. I can't believe it. I can't believe it. Gecko's gone. Play- play
Tokyo. No. I'm gonna play Ikaruga. I'll play Ikaruga tomorrow. I can beat that game in like
two or three hours. You guys don't think I'll be able to do Ikaruga? Oh, you've got something.
You'll see. You should play as a guaranteed no. You don't have to beat every game in one stream.
I mean, Ikaruga's only- I looked up time to beat and it said an hour and a half.
I think I could do it. Here, this is important. Please, can you pretty please get me a kitty?
Yeah, sure. The cat doesn't want to come over here. There's plenty of food over here.
All right, now I- where are the ducks? Ducks need to eat crabs. I need a taffy.
I'm starting to loomer. Sorry about that. I've played Resident Evil 4, god damn it.
Is this- is this- is this just shout games that you like our- is this just yell games that you like
the hour like Gex? Oh, shit. I have a 3DO. I have like 15 3DO games and I have a 3DO.
I was supposed to do that very recently. I was supposed to play a 3DO, but for some reason,
I did not do it. I said I was going to do it like next week, but I didn't do it though.
Weird that I- weird that- weird that I- kind of weird that I- kind of weird that I- kind of weird
that I- okay, what the fucking happened there? I think I messed up. Kind of weird that I bring
that up because I was supposed to play Gex like three weeks ago. Real voice revealed.
Fuck, Eagle. This game's boring. Play Fortnite. I'm never going to open Fortnite on this stream.
Ever. Ever. I will never open that video game on this stream. I got- I got real close.
Those of you that know what the Fortnite stream was going to be, it's the only time I was going
to open it. That was going to be the vape pen stream. Remember? I was going to be in like
stunner shades and like really bright colors and just smash on a fucking vape pen and I was going
to have, over the course of like an hour of playing it, I was going to fill this room. I was going to
have, well not this one, but I was going to do somewhere that was safe to do it and have
fog machines just fill the fucking room with just vapor and I was going to sit in there until I
disappeared completely. There was going to be like a- and I was going to still just be fucking
doing it and still talking and like just like going for like fucking a shot. That stream was
going to be like 40 minutes long but I didn't because that means I'd have to open Fortnite.
That's- that's a struggle for me. That was going to happen like two years ago.
I just never did it. Someone's just going to steal that joke. I hope it's funny.
Here are four- ah! I have to play fucking Viva Piñata! This is a comp- this is a comp stream
with the- this is a comp stream with a video in the background. You don't even want to play this,
you know it. No, you are wrong! You are wrong! You're wrong! I think this is fun and I think
it's cute. He's not even playing. I- what do you mean not even playing? This is- look at the title
of the stream. This is like looking at an aquarium that you've like reached in sometimes.
This is an interactive screensaver. I- why am I playing? Look at how much fun they're having.
All right, slow down. I can't believe that you guys aren't getting behind like- I can't believe
like Quack Crew is not- where's the Quack Crew at? Where's Quack Crew? Can I manufacture one? Can I
like force one of these? I don't think I can do that, can I? Where's the Quack Crew? No, it's- it
doesn't work that way. This is like when some like company on social media desperately tries to make
their own fucking version of a meme and everyone's like, wow, that was fucking stupid and lame and
shitty. Yeah, I can't. Quack Pack! Yeah, where's the Quack Pack? Look it! Uh, guys, where's the
Quack Pack? Wow, nice game, Omega Low. You didn't just think that that was fucking cute when he
just drank the water out of the dirt there, like he just like licked it up off the ground. It was
like cute. He like was laughing up like a dog. Like, fuck. Grimp. Grimp. Grimp. Grimp. Grimp. Grimp.
What? But that's not how that- what that noise makes. It's like,
that's not grimp. Gramp? Grimp? Stop distracting me. Okay, I gotta- I gotta water this. Is it
already watered all the way? It's sitting in water. I already got stupid. All right, kill this. He
sounds like a sim. Jeremy, are you okay? Yeah, I'm fine. What? What? What? What? Shit! Put this down!
I'm fine. No, guys, I'm not gonna like after this- I don't know, some of you guys think I like after
the stream is over, I like go and take a hot shower and just like scream into the water. Like,
like, I don't just fucking yell in the shower. I mean, I mean, I do- everybody does that though.
Who- all right, let me ask them. Who doesn't fill their mouth with water every like 45 seconds in
the shower and then just go- just spit it out. Everybody does that. Everybody just goes,
fills and then just goes- if you don't do- you're a liar if you don't do that. That's a lie.
Everybody fills their mouth with the fucking water every like minute and then just like
just flushes it off there and out of their mouth. Yes, you do. I- no way. Oh shit. I don't like
people watching me drink water. It freaks me out. I admit it, laughing my ass off. Good. You-
seriously? Yes, you do. Imagine- can you like imagine lying about if you put water in your
mouth and spit it out in the shower into the ground? Come on. I'm sorry, we don't- I don't
drink it. I just- you go and you go- who goes like this? Everybody does. You get in the shower and
you go, yes, you do. Yes, you do. You get in the shower and you go like this and like it does- yes,
you do. Everybody does that. I want- next time you take a shower, I want you to be very aware
of what you're doing so you don't even realize you're doing it. You get in and like the shower- you're
waiting for the shower because you're blocking the shower might not be hot enough or too cold
or too hot so you like just getting it ready and then it- yes, it is. I want you to be aware of it
next time and then you're gonna go- you're gonna get in the shower, you're gonna be like, that guy
Jerma is a fucking idiot. He's so fucking weird. He's like the weirdest guy I've ever known in my life.
He was right! And then you're gonna come- and like in a week, you're gonna fucking come to the stream
and you can say, hey man, I've done a week of showers and you were right and I'll be like, I know,
welcome back. And then you're gonna do something that I don't even do. You're gonna go like this
and then you're gonna be like, whoa, I do disgusting shit in here apparently
and oh oops oh yeah that's- oh no but I- Jerma's the weirdo. Jerma the weirdo. He puts his hands up
and like puts water in his mouth. Hold on a second. Unbelievable. Unbelievable. It's- it's
unbelievable. My dad does that and that's- and that's where you get it. You get it from your dad.
It's in your- it's in like your DNA. Wait, why?
I'm playing an animal. This is not Animal Crossing.
It's okay. This is the worst stream of 2020. No way. No way. No way. No way. No way. No way.
No way. We're not even- we're not even into fucking April. You got way more nominees.
You promised me a kitty. I can't just fucking- I gotta wait for one of them to get in here.
I'm actually having a lot of fun. I don't know what you guys are talking about. I'm having like
a ton of fun. Can I like nominate this for like most like fucking quirky stream of-
Oh, there's no cat. Get back here. No. If you didn't like, no, I'm Petula. My runs used to run
this shop till the- I suppose you better select a piñata to give this to. Oh my fucking god.
First select where the accessory should go on your piñata. Oh, that's good. Oh, that's so funny.
Should I give him German hair? How about the wizard? Okay, what about eyes? No, no glasses.
No glasses. A nose ring? Oh, I could do a clown nose. Holy shit. No. No, I don't want that. I don't
want that. I want little shoes though. Is that the only shoes? I want like little sneakers.
What about this? What about the bow tie? No, I don't want- I don't want the hair. I want something
on the head. Look at that. So cute. Clown nose over riot. There's like 10 animals to do this to.
This. Okay, that looks all right. Good choice. Well, now we need- now we need to do it to the-
look at- look at how cool he looks. I don't want you to have anything. I'm always a frog. I want
the frog to have something. The snake. Yep. This is real exciting. Can somebody link the other
Animal Crossing shovel image again, please? Oh, I love the hard hat. It's perfect. Oh, the wizard
cap. Yes, the hard hat. Hard hat and like glasses. Oh, they- they don't go like this? They- shouldn't
they go like that? Click that link. What do you mean me click that link? This is for you to click.
German, what the fuck? This is like- okay. This is what it looks like when you go back and look at
like history and paintings and shit. This is like a historical painting of me. If I was- if I was
like some- some like fucking senator from like 1402 or like 1400. But like I actually look like this
looking at a mirror in a dream. Yeah, I was gonna say this is like dreamy person. Let's see if I
can match it. There's no difference. Yes, there is. There's a fucking huge difference. I need this one
to be moving, though. You guys gotta tell me which one's real. You already fucking know. What
are you talking about? It's like before and after. Yeah, it's before and after I get like
cosmetic surgery. Hold on. Wait, wait, wait, wait. There. All right. Yeah, that's like before and
after. I go- I go get like some work done. I'm not growing out my beard. Wow, he fucking hates this
game.
What are you guys doing? What are you doing? Stop. You have less than two hours to play. I know. I'm
sorry. I'm trying. How did I bite my lip? Fuck, did I bite my lip?
Why, what the fuck? We already went over this.
We've already talked about that. Remember kids, everything you write is saved forever on the
internet. Don't forget that ever. I wrote this like a year or two ago and it's still here.
It's- I have what? Okay. Okay, cool. I will do one more. Let's do the frog.
Okay. I suppose I'll pick a piñata. Sure, how about you?
All right, the frog's gonna have a big top hat. Yes. Oh. Oh, you could marry. And a monocle,
of course. Yes, and the monocle will be bright. And is a piece of Professor Clown,
Professor Clownsworth. This is just Mr. Peanut. Mr. Peanut. What the fuck?
No, no, none of this. Wait. Yes. No, it's- Thanks on behalf of my absence. When you get back to
your garden, you should like think about me. Okay. I won't say bye because you'll probably be right
back in here really soon. All right. Now, what's it gonna look like? Let me, let me, let's see.
What am I gonna do? Let me just fucking, let me just. Come on. Come on. Hurry up. There's only like
this. I got eight more seconds before this doesn't work anymore. Okay. I'm thinking about, let's see
what I want to do here. Come on. Big spin. Big spin here. What do we got? Big spin. Yeah. I don't
care. I don't care if you didn't like it. I don't care. I think I'm gonna get some yams.
Okay. So what do I need? I was gonna buy a reminder. Stream ends in one hour and 40 minutes.
Fucking god damn it. Do I need to put more time on this shit? It's been an hour and 20 minutes
already. Fuck. Okay. I want to do some paving. Ooh. Ooh. Ooh. Ooh. Stone. Stone. Insert another
coin. Put more quarters in. Where do I want to put the stones? I think I want to put them over here
next to the snakes. Yeah. Like this. A little bit here. A little bit like over here. Okay. I'm bored.
Let's play Mario Yahtzee. No. You look better. I don't, what are you doing? Why are you, why are
you linking this? Why are you linking? I don't know what this is for. 2015. Okay. So this is,
this is the, the day that Battlefront came out. The original Battlefront.
How else do you want me to explain this? This is me pretending to be really excited for Battlefront.
You knew I needed to explain this? You sure? I didn't play Battlefront. You need me to explain
this? You can't get that from me. I don't have one minute in Battlefront. I need to apologize for
this. You were 30 when you tweeted this. No. You just did the same thing. You just did the same
fucking thing. This doesn't work. This does not work because you did the same exact thing. It did
not change at all. This doesn't work. Paul, the only thing that happened was I was ready for the
picture on the left one and I wasn't ready for the picture on the right one. This is like the
30 selfies you take and then you delete 28 of them and you pick the one that you're like, wait,
whoa, I look like a fucking weirdo in that one. You know just how much your face can fucking change
in, here's an experiment. Okay. So we're going to do this. Here's an experiment. What I'd like
you to do is we're going to, remember, I remember I'm taking selfies of myself over the course of
three or four seconds. I would like for whoever wants to do this to take a frame, every frame of
this, and we'll go over them and we're going to see how shitty half of them look. Are you ready?
Here we go. Click, click, click. Okay. So at least 40 of those 50 frames were terrible.
They were terrible. Every frame is bad. Why are my eyes so huge? What? You have big, I've got big
fucking eyes. There's no filter on. T minus hour and 40 minutes. I know, I know, I know, I know,
I know, I know. Alita Battle Angel. They're not that big. That looks nice. That didn't even look
good. All right. Look at me. I know everything about paving. That looks good. Yeah, that looks
good. All right. That's fine. Somebody just said you're surprised that I know what Alita
Battle Angel is. Do you think that, okay, so after every stream, after every single fucking stream,
there's just sand outside and I just, I'm like, all right, I'm done with the broadcast today.
It's been swell. Okay. Good night, everybody. And then 12 hours go by. Oh, fuck. That looked really bad.
It looked like it was fake. Oh, fucking god damn it.
Stop playing. We're in it. No, we got an hour and a half left of this particular broadcast.
We're all in at this point. I'm making at least one more duck. Worst hair, worst hair. Fuck. It's
all right. Whatever. It's not going to win. Don't worry. I'll have a greasy ass head in like four
months. What is this? What, do you guys think that changing the game is going to change what's
going on in the chat now and what the stream is derailed into? This is not, this is what we're
doing. Why can I not open this image? It's Bill and Ted hair. Wait, somebody, wait, what? Bill and Ted?
Why could I not, I can't even connect to the internet. Does somebody have a comparison?
Bill and Ted. Why can I not connect to the fucking internet? Am I stream still on? I can't open up
any of these links because it's on, is Discord having problems? Nice link, dude. What? This is,
what the fuck is this? You swapped my eyes? Hold on. Let's go. I need to go over this. So this is
normal eyes. Hold on. Normal. Right eye and right eye. What? Who looks better?
This is left and left. Left and left doesn't look good. And this is eyes swapped. Which one looks the
best? All right. Bottom right and bottom left look fucking awful. Top right, I think looks the best
to me. What do you think? Oh, okay. If we're going to, if we're going to rate these on like on order,
okay. Number one is top right. Number two is top left. No, all right. Fourth eye swapped is number
three. And at the bottom is left. And my left eye is not the strong eye, huh? This eye is not the
strong one. Look what top right is looking. I don't get it. Left and left is himbo germa.
No comments. What do you mean no comments? Where's kitty floss?
Oh god damn it. It's like the same face. It's the same, the same energy is coming off of these images.
Same actor. Okay, that's enough. I'm done with this. Grow a beard? I can't grow a beard.
You think I can grow a beard? This is the extent of what I'm capable of. You don't want to get it
up close and personal here. You're gonna see all my nose hairs. They need to be trimmed. They're very,
very long. They're very long. You don't want to see them. I don't want to get that close so you
can see them and you can count how many. No, no, I haven't had time to do any trimming or any any
any of this stuff. There's a spider on the ceiling. Oh wow. There's a spider on the ceiling.
Get a hold of this guy. What the fuck am I doing? I just like stopped. Did you see that? You just
watched the train leave the station on camera. It just like I was just here. I stopped. It was
like the eye halted. It was like his brain was empty. All right, time to fill my brain with
knowledge. What was I doing? I have no fucking, oh this has been no experience gained. Nothing's
happened and I've and we're like halfway through the stream. What? No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no,
wait a minute. I gave them funny hats. So that's excuse me. This dude's high as a kite. I'm not
at all. Why are they all hanging out over here? Why have none of them been eaten yet?
I feel like this is one of the Muppets. Next resident sleeper. There is no next. There's a
next tomorrow. There's an Ikaruga tomorrow. Not right now. Let me at least do the one thing I
wanted to do. Please, please. And that one thing was, okay, I got the two ducks. They need to eat
crabs. I need a crab. I need a surfboard. First of all, Odama tomorrow. I need to say this on
camera because people don't would just apparently don't want to get this solidified into their
brains. I will, why am I blinking so much? I will never play Odama the GameCube ever again. Okay,
I need a house. I need to get a mouse house. We have, uh, I need these two birds are still
hanging. They've been sleeping for like four days. Let me go to, I need a gecko. That's what I want.
Gecko. Go get one. That's the ice place. Go to the desert. Actually get a gecko. That's what I want.
A kitty floss. Will they have to show up? Is a gecko in your mailbox? Well, I'm going to get two of
them. You missed like three. Show webcam. We want to see your face. Show webcam. I'd recommend that.
I don't like the, I don't like the frog that talks. It takes away my version. I give them
their own voices. Like for me, that's like, not like this. You know what I mean? It's like,
oh, it's fucked it all up for me. Okay. We need to get bait. Uh, come get it. I'll get two.
Voice is wrong. We demand orange. We demand orange. There we go. This is exactly what I was
talking about. This is the exact thing. Yep. Why do they all look like this? Why do all the
paintings from like the 13th century, 14th, why do they look like that? That's how people looked.
What? This is not even, you just like made my nose a little more bulby. But this is, what the
fuck even is this? I'm going to show this on stream. Yeah. And that's not even an edit. That's just me
going like, ah, let's head back. Now let's make the geckos happy. Very happy. Did I bump you? I'm
so sorry. Okay. Go to the post office. Gang, gang, gang, gang, gang, gang, gang, gang, gang, gang.
Sorry. I have to do this every time. Some of you guys weren't here yesterday. Some of you guys
weren't here yesterday. There's a thing, talk about the mouth flap hitting hard and it's chasing you
in a nightmare. This is like literally yesterday. I had a dream last night. It was crazy. It had
something to do with Twitch. What was it? Oh my God. What was it? I remember I was like, ah, maybe
I should fucking like say something about this. Fuck. What was it? I don't remember. Damn it.
Yes. A little gecky. Okay. Now how do I get you to stay? You need to eat a flutter scotch. There's two
here. Eat one. Eat them all. Flutter scotch. Eat that one. Isn't there like three flutter scotches
just flying around? I need to put a light in the garden. You got it. How do I get that from that
store? This is like when the, this is like the part of the movie where the caveman guy comes into
society and they're trying to teach him how to count to 10 and they're trying to teach him numbers
and squares and shapes and shit. This is part of, that's part of that movie. They've done this like
10 times now. What movie? There, it said they're like a bunch of movies. We need a lamp. There we
go. Firebrand. Name one. Uh, the, what's the movie? Movie with um, the movie with uh, the movie with
Brendan Fraser. What's it called? Brendan Fraser. Uh, he's like the, what's it called? He's like the,
he's like the caveman, right? There it is. Instino Man. Done. Oh, name one movie. Got it. How am I
gonna put this? Yeah, like right here is fine. We'll do like two of them. This happens in Toy Story
2 as well. Okay. Done. Two. Somebody said it happens in George of the Jungle. Okay. Three.
Fuck out of here, snail. That happens in Spider-Man. Okay. That happened in the beginning of your online
career. It's how I started. What's that? Germa. Circle. Circle. Circle. Almost. Pizza. Pizza. Yes,
you'll get pizza, but circle. What is this shape? What is this? Pizza now.
Can we get another pizza here? Domino's. Yep. Can we get another pizza from Domino's in here?
Extra pepperoni. Okay. But you can't say circle, huh?
Where's the flutter thing? There it is. That's an ad for Domino's.
Whatever. You eat Domino's. Eat it. It's fucking down. It's all right.
Do the whole scream in that voice. No. What? Oh, Chadbird incoming. Chadbird incoming.
I need three corns. Oh, that's not Chadbird. Did I lose the gecko again? I need to bring in...
What do they need? This and something else. Let me take a look at the encyclopedia. Let me actually
learn. Hulk waiting room. You're gonna be waiting for a little while. When can we expect a movie?
When can you expect me to make a movie? Okay. White flutter. Does it matter? White flutter scotch.
Okay. Up here I have one daisy in the garden. No, it's the other ones. It's a regular one,
right? When are you doing the chocolate factory tour? Guys, we thought... We brought this up
yesterday afternoon. It's not just like, okay, time to go to the chocolate factory and broadcast
from a chocolate factory. How do I make the regular flutter thing show up? It was... I need...
What was it? It was the... It was the torches and what? Do that tomorrow. I can't go... All right.
That's enough. That's enough. That's enough. Mods. Mods. Start mods. Oh, okay. There's one.
But how do I get the other ones? You all right? Oh, you're on fire. Here. What are you doing?
Backgammon waiting room. I don't know how to play backgammon. You're going to be waiting
forever. I... How? I need ducks, but they need to eat crabs. All right. I'm getting a cat.
I'm just buying one. Can I buy a cat? I don't... I don't know how to play backgammon.
I don't have any money. I can't even buy one. Gekko was a resident already. I don't see him.
Where? I want to hear a story. I don't really have many stories. Where's the Gekko that's the
resident? I don't see a resident Gekko. Oh, yes. Okay. Now what do you need? I need to eat a moth
drop. All right. You'll stick around though. Look at how cute he is. I knew people were going to do
resident Gekko with the resident sleeper. I knew you were going to do that. All right. It's time
to start selling people. Sell. Sell. Sell all the birds. Sell the birds and sell the bird.
If you're not a duck, then I'm going to sell you. Play Resident Evil 4. I'm going to.
I'm gonna play Resident Evil 4. Just not in the next 20 minutes. Good. Now I need a Gekko house.
Ooh, cool. Somebody said Resident Evil 4 sucks. Do you guys understand there's no way I could ever
make all of you happy? Even if a majority of you guys want to see Resident Evil 4, somebody just
said Resident Evil 4 sucks. You know what I mean? Like, what do you want me to do? Pizza. Pizza.
Pizza. Pizza. Pizza. Pizza. Take off your shirt. And that person actually for like at least five
minutes. All right. I need to do Gekko house. We're going to put it over here. Where's the door?
Yes. Yes. Yes. Yes. Take off your glasses.
Fuck. I hate this. I hate this. But I'm going to show it anyways. I hate this. Build it. All right.
That looks good. I'm going to buy a couple more of these. I'm going to buy like four or five
watercresses and put them along the edge here. Do I have enough money for that?
Do a voice. I can't do. Oh, fuck. He's on fire. Why the hell burning?
I think we have to be careful. We have some more. Hold on. I think I get it. Just give me a minute.
I think that I like, I think that we can maybe get some quality entertainment here school.
Oh, yes.
Like maybe we should stop streaming school. I think maybe that's a good idea.
Don't say I didn't fucking try. Come back soon and try again.
Okay. Scooby-Doo isn't a Yoda horse. Um, what the fuck are you talking about?
Yes, he is. Scooby-Doo is can be absolutely described as a Yoda horse.
Are you serious? Yes. Are you kidding me? It's true. Why are you don't you? Yeah, you can't.
Yeah, like, like, like, I almost got it. I'm close. I'm really,
if you give me like four or five hours in the mirror tonight, I'll get it.
I've never tried that before. Don't I have another gecko?
Please buy a milk bottle. People happy. Kitty floss. I'm crying. There's not going to be a
kitty floss because there are no kitty flosses that care about my house. They don't care about
this place. Oh, look, a Gekki. Eat that right there. Right there. There is no, that's a fox.
This is a fox. I don't want one of these. I had them last time right there. I see one. No,
you don't. That's a lie. Oh my God. You're not a liar. Okay. Come here. How do I do this?
Direct a mouse over here. Come here. Oh shit. He's going to eat it. Yeah. Now I have two geckos for
residents and I'm going to give them hats. Stop eating this food before you get, I'm going to
sell you if you don't cut the shit. Break the shit. Break the shed. Break the shed. Wait,
isn't that from Courage? Cowardly Dog? Return. What is it? Return the slab. Return the slab.
Super dog. Yes, Gekki 2. All right. Let me see what the house looks like. Oh, Courage. Be careful
out there. Don't go out too late at night. You're putting too much effort into this dumb dog.
Oh, does she have an Irish accent? I don't know. She doesn't? She's Scottish. Oh, well,
this is nice. Look at this place. How is this a gecko house? Okay. Now for them to, I have two.
They both need to eat a moth drop. How do I get a moth drop to come stay? Permanently. Let's look
it up. This is a baby game. Play Dead or Alive. Does anybody actually play that game? Like,
do people play that game? Isn't that a fighting game? Did they just give up and just start making
fucking like beach simulations? Do they still make Dead or Alive the fighting game? Isn't it good?
Isn't Dead or Alive a good game? Like fighting game wise? Isn't it like a good game? It was.
The old ones are pretty good. Yeah. I'm just saying what I've heard. All right. I don't think
I even have any info. How do I attract one? There we go. Moth drop. Peer requirements. Night time
in the garden. All right. But have a light in the garden. Night time in the garden.
How do I make you stay? Wait for night time. Play Dead or Alive. I'm not, I don't play fighting games.
No, I don't play them. It's not even just like, oh, I don't stream that. I, that, it's just not.
I just don't. All right. There's a moth drop right here. Has eaten one bluebell flower. Here we go.
Check this out. Bluebell flower. Plant them. Put a couple here right in their spot that they like.
Well, this is so POG. This is an, this is a POG only stream. Okay. I'll do fertilizer on these.
Does it matter? Just blue fertilizer, right? Kind of POG, I guess. POG only. So let's do a fertilizer.
Plant a bunch of shit and then get a bunch of fertilizer. What should I do first? Plant first,
then fertilizer. Was it fertilize first and plant or plant then fertilize? Fertilizer goes on
afterwards, right? I know. Like you, you smeared my face up a little bit. God, I'm so, okay.
Very on POG of you. I hope the same people doing Resident Sleeper do the same thing for
Animal Crossing. People happy. Um, I think that half the people doing that are doing it because
they just, they, they just want to cause chaos. They just want constant fucking conflict.
I know. I saw it. I saw it. It's fertilizer after, right? We're doing, we need bluebell.
Do I not have it in my bag? Fuck. Ah, mean flower. Just watch Family Guy funny moments. Why would I
do that right now? Why would I watch Family Guy funny moments? There's no reason for me to do that.
All right. I need bluebell flowers. We need to feed these people and then they're going to go
and they're going to, we're going to have gecko. They're going to have gecko babies.
Watch TikTok compilation. All right. Fertilizer and seeds. I need seeds first, then fertilizer.
No, no, no. I mean, where's bluebell? I don't even have access to this shit. Bluebell.
You need to react. Uh, what I need to do is, holy shit, he's zooming around. You see that? Look at
them. Look at how fast they're running. Well, don't touch it then. Don't touch the fire. What
are you stupid? All right. Here we go. Plant. Fertilize. Action. I'm going to play my favorite
game. All right. On sub. Good morning. Can I interest you in something seedy? No, I don't mean
like that. That's, that's what you could title this stream. I could just change the title of
this stream to Jerma play the game I like or on sub. I could just change. I could be the title
today. All right. We need blue fertilizer. Fertilize. Fertilization. Didn't get this one,
did I? Yep. What about this one over here? Did I get this one? Yep. Okay. Water. He's not playing
farming simulator. I am. I am going to lose it. A monkey Island. I am going to lose it.
Play Toho. Until like four days ago. I didn't even know what that was.
It's, can I, give me a second. It's really good. All right. It's like, wait, why can I not do this
anymore? Wait, here they go. All right. Blue Bells are up. This is like you recommended a movie.
Hey man, you should really go see Star Wars, Return of Skywalker. Okay. Yeah, that sounds
like a good movie. Maybe I'll check it out eventually. Maybe I'll do it. Yeah, I'll probably
watch it. No, go right now. I don't want to go watch the new Star Wars movie right now.
I've got some stuff to do. No, go right now or I'm not your friend anymore. Can I just give me a
couple of days to figure out? I got to look at movie times. No, there's one playing at 5 30. Go
now. Here, let me help you. And you start like pushing me out of my house. Let me help you.
Just go out there. You open the car door. Get in. I don't want to go see the movie right now. Get
in and drive the car now. All right, fine. Jesus. And then you stand there like so like you stand
there straight in the air like a pencil till I come back. And I get out. I'm finally, I'm like,
God, I get back in the movie. You're still there. Like, and I pulled the car into the fucking
driveway and that the lights hit you and you're fucking still there standing staring. And then
the door opening was that best movie you ever seen your life? Um, well, I yeah, I know. I like
the two. It was my favorite movie ever seen my whole life. That's your favorite movie you've
ever seen your whole life, right? Sure. I thought it was great. Cool. What do you do tomorrow? Um,
I don't know, man. You should go see this movie. I'll stand here. I'll be ready. I tried to kill it
in time. Did I get it? I did. Can you stop with the movie recommendations?
Never. He hates it. Why were you friends with person in the first place?
Why were you friends with this person in the first place? Because they were a pretty normal guy
until the subject of movies came up. Kitty, please. I can't. Look, the kitty is going to come
eat. The kitty is going to come eat a bug if the kitty wants to. Oh crap. I still can't get a surf
board. Here we go. All right. Where's uh, where's my, where's my gecko friends? Four daisies in the
garden. Oh fuck. You should play Roblox. And that's another one, right? Like Roblox is so
much shit. It's like the Roblox is not like the game Roblox. It's the infrastructure Roblox. And
I've seen that often too. And that's the equivalent of not telling me to go see a specific movie.
That's telling me to go just spend my whole day in the movie theater, right? And just, hey, can
you like pick a cool movie to watch in the movie theater? I, I guess. What do you do? You're not
even, you gotta live here, man. Go watch all the Star Wars movies. All right. I need to wait till
nighttime. Are these ready to be harvested? Choo, choo, choo. Honda. Chota. Chota. Chota. Honda.
Choo, choo, choo. Choo, choo, choo. Let's get some info here. Okay. He's eating one moth drop.
I gotta get the moth drops to show up. He never went back to that game. Yeah. Cause I bought like
a bootleg copy of it and it fucked up. Do I have my sneeze button still? Uh, I don't know. What is
this one? What's that doing? No, I don't. Actually it's gone. That's sad. All right. Here we go.
Here come the moth drops. Eat these bells. Hurry, hurry. I'm only 400 pounds. Hurry, feed me,
feed me more. I'm only 350 pounds. I think that's the, the thing in the arcade from like 20 years
ago that then you throw the balls in the lady's mouth and she gets fatter. Come on. What? I'm under
wifi. Something like that. Yeah. All right. Where are the fuck are these moths? Look at, I got
everything they want right here. You promised me a kitty. I can't unless the kitty decides to come
over here and eat one of the mice. I'm trying to make the geckos do the gecko dance cause I
want to see it. Cause that game used to terrify me as a kid. Yeah. It, yeah. It was fucking crazy.
Check its visit requirements. Yeah. It needs blue. It needs these bells and needs these lights.
This is nighttime. So where is it? Excuse me. Are you here yet? Moth drop. Eat a blue bell flower.
Look what's over here. Eat it. Yes. No, wrong image. Uh, yes. This, uh, it's big Bertha.
And what you would do is you would throw balls into this. There was a little ball thing that was
underneath down here and it was like the little tray and you had to throw the balls into her mouth
and there was an inflatable thing underneath where her, where her shirt is. And every time
you put another ball, a ball went in, it would inflate a little more until a big got huge.
And, and points were weight. And every time you'd get like two or three, four or five balls in,
she'd say like, I'm only 200 pounds. I can be much fatter than this. And then it'd be like,
I'm only, you'd cut it off sometimes. So if you, if you had like three or four friends all doing it
at the same time that you did, it was like, blah, blah, blah, blah, blah, blah, blah, blah. It'd be
like, I'm only, I'm only three. I'm free. I'm 400. I'm only 500 pounds. You can do better.
And then the timer would run out and then she would laugh. And then you'd put
25 cents in and you would do it again until you were out of money. And then you'd go buy
four tootsie rolls at the counter with the tickets you won. Did I get a moth drop yet?
Bingo. Bingo. Do it. Please. Eat one of these. Eat one. Yeah.
All right, go. Now we have our resident moth drop. We need another one. And then we can feed
the geckos. He's still playing piñata. Yeah. I mean, for now, for now. Yeah. And I'm probably
not going to play this tomorrow. I just want to make a couple more geckos. I'm playing
Icaruga tomorrow. Oh, they're actually kind of cool looking. He hates the piñata. He hates
the piñata. No, no. You hate the piñata. You hate the piñata. Not me. These still need to be
a plant dried out. What? Stop fucking touching this. You're going to get hurt. Come here.
All right. Now I need another moth drop. You need to eat one of these moth drops, but not yet.
I need another moth drop, two moth drops. We're going to have moth drops and then we're going to
have a gecko baby. Why are your lips so red? They're not. They're not. The white balance on
this camera is tilted to a point where it's all red. My eyes are red though, because I've only
slept like two or three hours a night for the last five straight days, but that's accurate.
Patch here. Where am I needed? I'm ready for healing and stuff. That's an exaggeration.
It's probably been like four. It's probably been like four hours a night, maybe four and a half.
Oh my God. A liar. It's maybe like three or four plus maybe four and a half or stop streaming and
go to bed. I'm fine. I'm all right. I've like, I've had four plus hours a night. Oh, there's six,
six to ten. Turn off the torches, please. The piñatas are burning. Bluebell. Dink, dink, dink.
All right. I'll turn the torches off. He sleeps 18 hours a day. He'd probably puke. If I slept
for 18 hours more than, I'd probably throw up. I'd wake up and I'd feel like shit and I'd probably
puke. Turn around, you bad streamer. Oh, here. Look, I can't, there, I can't do anything about
this. They have to come eat a mouse. Look, he doesn't even want to come over here. Bad. He
doesn't want to come over here. He has to eat a mouse mallow. He doesn't want to come over here.
Buy milk. Oh my God. Go buy milk. Milk, milk, milk, milk, milk, milk, milk, milk, milk. All right,
get milk. Cats aren't supposed to fucking drink milk. Birds aren't supposed to eat bread.
This is ridiculous. This is a thousand dollars. Uh, no. Uh, you want to spend a thousand fucking
dollars on milk. Can I, I can't sell you. You don't, you don't, you don't live here.
Selling a mouse and selling two mice. No, I'm not. Fuck. I don't, I can't sell anything. I don't
have any money. Let me do it. I don't. Uh, fine. I'll sell a mouse. Fine. Get back in there and buy
that milk. It's a thousand dollars. Sell the seeds. Where is he? Where's this weirdo? March
in there and get that milk. I can't until I have a thousand dollars. There goes the cat. No, no,
no, no. I want the cat. No. Oh, moth drop. I'm so mad. Look, he's pretending to fly.
Did you see that? He had his arms out and he has the, the helmet on. Oh yeah. He's mocking us.
Was I? I don't think, I don't think I was. You won't come here without a surfboard.
Okay. How about, um, I need to sell. I'm just going to sell.
Uh, I have to sell a mouse. That's just what's going to have to happen. I'm selling a mouse
and I'm going to sell a couple of flowers. Make an OnlyFans account. How would I do that?
Oh, I don't have a reason to do that. I'm selling a mouse. You and I'm going to sell some of these
flowers. Daisy. All right. I need five, nine, 70, 981. Okay. I can get the milk. I'm not going to
buy it yet until the cat comes back. I'm supposed to get distracted. I've been distracted for almost
two and a half straight hours. I've, I've been distracted for as long as a, a like Christopher
Nolan movie. Okay. So we, I can start to play now. All right. We're looking for more moth drops.
Turn these on. Back away from this. Back away. Back away. Back away. Back away. You're going to get,
whatever. Attention. Attention. Look at me. Attention. Okay. Cool.
It's worth showing this one. It's worth showing this. This is great. This is very good.
This is my favorite of the whole night. I think this is very, very good.
Any more moth drops. Come eat and then I'll, I can make the geckos breed. This one's better. I
promise. Oh, that one. Whoa. Wow. That's way better. No, it's just, you, you, it's a smudge tool in
Photoshop. You. Howdy doody. Howdy doody Hummer. Howdy doody Hummer. Howdy. No, I can't do that.
That's not, I'm not good enough. If you tuck it. That's different. What's that one? I don't think
you. Oh, that's like, there's a bit. When my mask gets broken. I can't. How many do you have? All
right. What is this thing? This is a question mark, question mark, question mark. Mystery seed.
Let's try it. Where's it? What are you doing to plant it? Just right over here. It's a mystery seed.
Let's check it out. It is a doesn't go. No. Gooseberry bush. Whatever. Fucking controls.
Fucking suck. Fucking controls. Stupid fucking controls. Hey, time to silent. Nobody's in my
room. Be mad at something. The fucking controls are fucking stupid. Dumbest fucking game ever,
man. Such a fucking stupid game. So fucking stupid. Fucking dumbest fucking thing ever.
Fucking be in the game. Fucking. What is this? Is it a tree? Dude, it's a hazel tree.
Hmm. This thing take a lot of water. Nice and this. Um, hello? Look at how much water this shit takes.
Fuck this. All right. Another one. The show was better than the game. Oh, squazzle. Oh, wait,
there's a hazelnut tree. That's how you get a squazzle. This game is fucking so bad.
Why would anyone play this for more than five minutes? It's opposite day. Just kidding.
Oh, fuck. Is that another one? What is this one? Is that too close? An apple tree. Oh, shit. Nice.
Is this too close? Actually, that kind of look that look good. That look kind of good.
All right. What's the mystery one then? Just in case something big. I'll put it over here.
Something dried out. Where? Oh, this shit takes a ton of water. Oh, gooseberry bush.
I just walk into fire. These things take so much water. Holy shit. Stop walking into the fire.
Oh my. Aye. Okay. Well, I know what it looks like now. Big bits. Big bits. Fill this up with
5,000. 5,000 bits from Titan Claws. 50 bucks. Thanks to the 50 fucking dollars, dude.
And Titan Claws says, uh, girlfriend of five years broke up with me. Then my father passed
away unexpectedly two days later. Holy shit. I'm so sorry. The past two and a half weeks have been
the worst of my life, but your streams and highlights have helped me more than you could
know. Thank you. I'm really sorry to hear about that shit. That's pretty rough. Back to back
like that. I can't imagine what you're going through right now. Try to keep your head up.
Hang in there, buddy. Yeah, for real. Because that's two, that's just two things back to back
that nobody wants to that shit to happen. Especially like that back to back like that.
Let's hope when the page turns here, take as long as you need to grieve for all this stuff
that the page can turn. Thank you so much. It's completely unnecessary to give me this much money.
Take care of yourself. I wish you the best. Thank you so much. And an award for, oh, did I level up
finally? It took me like three hours to do that. Come on. Yes. Level 13. In no way unlucky, I hope
Petula has a new wig and Lottie has three new items to dress up your garden. Most importantly,
you can buy a new seed packet from Lottie that will give you more options in your garden.
Because I wasn't doing anything. There it is. How many times do I have to get a shovel upgrade?
You've reached the stage I got to on my third day. Well done. This makes your shovel stronger.
So you should be able to deal with some of the more awkward things in your garden. Thanks for
the info. I don't know what that means. Stupid idiot. Hi, these are all ready. This one needs
some water properly. Whoo. It's going. It's going. Attention. I'm not gonna say that.
I know it's drying out. I'm trying. I'm working on it. Happy birthday. Cool. So we have,
we need to get them off. These ducks are still having fun. Having some fucking fun. Sick. Sell
you. And buy milk. Screamer. Attention. Buy milk. Buy milk. Milk, milk, milk, milk. You need milk
for the cat. You need milk for the cat. You need milk for the cat. I know, I know, I know. There's
no cat in sight. PS2 emulator slow down. Do you guys remember that shit? What game did I play on
that PS2 emulator? It was that news one, right? Something with the CPU cycling was wrong. And it
kept going like that. Yeah. What was that? Michigan report from hell. Yeah. Didn't I beat that whole
game to putting up with all that crap? I was waiting for them to come in. I got the bad ending.
Whatever. Shit. Where'd that go? I gotta get rid of this. Where is it? It's in here. Get rid of it.
Stop. I can't even select it. Tell it. Quick. It still needs water. All right. Time to turn
this shit on. There's Mr. Cidos. Oh, I didn't even plant this. What is this one? Let's see what it
is. A tree? It is a tree, isn't it? It's a blackberry bush. How much water does it need?
Or it's too much? That's probably good. That's good. That's good. That's good. All right. Looking
for the moths. I need another moth. Are you a moth? No, you're an ant. I don't really care about the
ant. Wait, they want to eat it? I think they want to eat this. Cat. The cat's not here. There's no
cat. I can't get a cat. Cat has to come on its own when it wants to. There's no cat available. See,
I looked all around the whole perimeter. No cats. There is. No, there's not. I don't see. There's no
cat here. That's a fox. What are you doing over there? He's over there. Then find one. All right.
I will find one. Just attention. 28 minutes remaining until the stream is over. I'll find one.
I'll just have to... I'll get a... All I have to do is just find... Yeah, I'll get an upgrade for it.
Thermo monkey has thermo. 28 minutes. Oh, fuck. Is it really? Where are these fucking moths? You
can't turn the stream off till we have the cat. That's fair. That's, that's fair. No, the stream
can't turn off till we get the cat and I breed the geckos. That's just the way it is. Where's this
bat? Attention. Use hunter. I can't use the hunter until I have a resident sleeper. Moth drop. All
right. There's one. I need another moth drop. Moth drop two. Oh. Yep. Okay. Eat a blue. Eat a
flower. And then finally I can breed the geckos. Over here. Come over here. Check it out. Can you
breed the moths? I think I can, but I got to see what it takes to do that. Come on. Come over here
and eat one of these. Come over here. Come on. I know you want to do it before the time runs out.
Please. No. Is it leaving? No. No. Don't leave. No. What the fuck? No, please don't test it.
Badgicle. Didn't we already know this? A badgicle has appeared. The garden has a blackberry bush.
Then a badgicle won't be far behind. Didn't we already get introduced to a badgicle?
Eat it. It's going to eat it. Come on. You're right there. Eat it so we can keep this going.
Please just land on this and eat it. Come on. Do it. Why are you doing this? You're teasing me.
You must be a chat member. Will you just eat it? Oh my god. Just eat it. You've already
have to fly around like this. Just eat this and then live here and then I can make a moth house
and then I can breed you and then we can breed the geckos. Eat that. Eat it. Please just eat it.
Just eat it. Eat. Weird owl ripoff. That's a weird owl song. I'm singing the weird owl version. That's
not me singing that. That's a weird owl song. No, it's a Michael Jackson song. That then turned into
a weird owl song. That then turned into me referencing a weird owl song which references
the Michael Jackson song. Sorry. I win. Now I can build a moth drop house. Two moth drops.
Now what does it take for them to breed? Has to eat a hazelnut tree seed. Oh god. Do I just say
fuck it? Hazelnut tree seed. Somebody just gave 5,000 bits again. Another one. What's with the
all right turn this off. That's another 5,000 bits from phylactery lich phylactery. 50 bucks 5,000
fucking bits. Thanks for the huge amount of money as always. This is an actual important game tip.
Okay. Thanks for the huge amount of money first of all. Second of all,
once you breed a species the first time you can just go buy romance candy and feed it to them
to make them breed again. You don't have to keep feeding them moth drops.
Wow. Holy shit. Don't dig a pond. Well, thanks for the tip and now let's do that. Okay. So let's um
you know what I mean? We're gonna look for a seed, right? No seeds are gonna fall. Fuck. Okay. So
let's do romance candy. Wait. Let me read that again. Once you breed a species for the first
time. All right. So just eat the moths. Where's my uh geckos? Gecko one. Eat this moth. Gecko two.
Where's gecko two? Gecko one. Gecko two. Eat moth one and then breed. Where's moth one? All right.
Gecko two to moth one. Gecko two to moth one. Over. Where's moth one? Gecko two to moth one.
This is big business. Um seriously. Where's the other moth? Is he in the house? Wait. What?
Moth. Eat moth. What are you afraid of? Where are they? I'm gonna start. I'm just gonna start
massively selling. I'm just gonna sell a bunch of marshmallows. They're impeding on my gecko.
Come here. Go eat this. Eat. Go for it. Got it. Wait. Don't both of you do it. Wait. Can you both
just eat it together? It just dropped a peanut. Come on. Eat. Maybe they don't have. Maybe I'm
gonna keep that one moth. Eat this candy. Come on. When? Really? This fucking squirrel is over here.
Get out of here. It's not yours. Get out of here. It's not your food. All right. Where's moth? That's
not the right moth. Why do you not live here? Are you? Moth? No. This is not. This is not even the
right one. Where is this motherfucker? Did somebody help me out here? Where's this other moth drop
that moved in on the sand building? Oh, I thought that was part of the fucking-
I thought that was part of the decor- the design. All right. Let's go. Eat. Eat. Eat. Apples and bananas.
I like to eat. Eat. Eat. Apples and bananas. Oh, all of a sudden, all of a sudden, you do
baby bop and people fucking want to leave. Wow. Whoa. Unbelievable. You do the fucking
Barney the Dinosaur character and everybody decides it's time to go now. He's actually mad.
All right. Let's do it. Are you ready? Did you even eat yet? Eat. Dermot, you should be worried
about the people that stay. What? He's view pandering. I just started singing the Apples
and Bananas song from Barney the Dinosaur and then you think that's me pandering views.
It's time to see what this sex thing is. What are you- are you saying that the audience is like
10 years old? What is that thing? Sour Profitimel. You have attracted a sour profisimel, I'm sorry.
Well, just hit him in the head with the fucking hammer, whatever this is. Hit him with the face
of the shovel. He'll go away. Where is it? Are you guys ready to see the dance of the geckos?
You ready? This is gonna be sick. Here it comes. We've been waiting two days for this. All right,
let me see. So we go bottom. I don't know. Who cares? This is really hard to control. It is.
Trust me when I say that. This is very difficult to control this. It's very, very sloppy. Change
camera. You can now press the Y button at any time. No, no, no, no, no, no, no.
During the time, I'm fine. All right, let's see the dance. Let's go.
Watch out, watch out, watch out, watch out, watch out, watch out, watch out, watch out,
watch out. I gotta get back to the house. Oh shit. Oh shit. Oh shit. She's coming over. Oh my god.
Oh no, no, no, no, no. I gotta make sure. Is the bed clean? Does the bed smell? Oh fuck. Is there
trash in my fucking counter? Shit. Yeah, just one second. Throw it on the fucking ground and
push it in the corner. Where's the Febreze? All right, we're ready. Come on, come on in. Fuck.
Come on in. I love this one. That was great. That was awesome. I want to see what the duck one is.
So bad. What about this? Can we see the snake one at least? Egg delivered. Maybe we'll get to see
the cat one. New seeds. A new pinata is in the desert? A new pinata has been spotted in the
Keen Arctic. Let's go check it out. Wait, evil. You're my cursed dog PNG.
At last you have a shovel worthy of a real gardener. There isn't much you can't do with this now.
See the jagged edge on this shovel? That's so you can cut down any tree that you don't need anymore.
That's pretty cursed. You're right. Now all we need this to do is we need this to move. So the mouth
is constantly moving forward and another head's coming out of the mouth. You know what I mean?
Like those weird images that just keep going forward at you. Or keep going backwards or
whatever it is. That's a Jojo reference. Oh, sorry. Sorry, I just gave you a Jojo reference.
I'm waiting for him to come in. He'll come in in a second. Right when you cross that line,
that's it. That's it. You crossed it. You crossed it. That's the line. You're off sides.
If only you'd stayed over there, I wouldn't have, I wouldn't have hit you.
God, fuck. There's another one? What the fuck? This reminds me of a song. I want attention.
Only 11 minutes remain in the stream. Only 11 minutes remain in the stream. I have no,
what's wrong? Oh, I got it. My phone just started. Oh, I got a notification. Okay,
I only have a little bit more time left. I got the notification.
11. That's it? What the fuck? I thought I had more time than that. That's weird.
All right. Oh, what was I doing? I need that cat. A cat has to show up. Wait, isn't that a cat?
This is a cat. This is your cat right here. No, it's not.
Ooh, apples. He's not selfish very much. Just keep him. Hazelnut seed. Who wants one of these?
Oh, there he is. He's so cute. Put a hat on Gekki. Yup. On a little Gekki. Absolutely. Whoa.
Fucking holy shit. Can I put it on? Do they have to be an adult? Yeah, they have to be an adult.
Okay, what about for a hat? Anymore? Oh, there's new stuff. Hold on. I mean, perfect. Fireman,
right? Ooh, football helmet. Hmm. I think I want the bonnet. Or the fire helmet. Yeah, that's
perfect. I love it. I love the eyes. Superhero mask. Eh. Eh. Nah. Nose. A gas mask? That doesn't even
fit on his face. There's nothing more than these teeth. Funky. Ooh, a tie. Or a spiked collar. Okay,
the collar is kind of cool. Or the tie. So I like the tie. Collar is cool too. I like the collar.
Sweat bands. What about shoes? Yep. But all of his feet are on the ground. All right, I like it.
We're good. Yeah, selling's good. Means you do most of the work. Won't say bye because-
Put a tie on the duck. Yup. Couldn't have thought of anything more perfect than what you just said.
New resident. A taffy? When did I get a taffy? What? I need a taffy. What do I need this taffy?
Somebody has to eat this, right? I think, what, a snake? Who eats the taffy? Burn it. Set the
taffy on fire. Come here. Do it. Do it. Touch it. Touch it. Touch it. Look at him. Oh no, I'm the
fireman. I'll put you out. When do I have to, when do I put it out? There we go. There it is. A super
taffy. Evil candy? A ruffian is on the way. Oh no, a ruffian is on the way. They're experts
in spiteful destructive behavior. Okay, now sell. For 2,200 bucks. Done. Okay, now,
hey, uh, hit him. I gotta hit him with the shovel. Um, I can't even hit him. I can't hit him. He just
throws up a candy and leaves. What is it? I think there's a candy. I think I know what that candy
might do. 5,000 more bits from Filashulich. Holy shit. Another 50 fucking dollars. Feed a gooseberry
to a duck for a special surprise. Yeah, but what does it do? Oh, thanks for the 100 bucks.
Feed a gooseberry to a duck. Okay, let me, I'll do it. Do I get a super duck? All right, here's
a gooseberry. Hey, you. Not into it? Not into it? Not into it? Yeah, that was blackberries. Oh,
was it gooseberry? I gotta look at all this fruit. Okay, gooseberry. You.
Eat that gooseberry right there. What does it do? Oh, it turns up in a squidward.
God damn it. You know, there are some people like myself who can help you with your more mundane
tasks. For example, you should let a springling like me come water your plants for you. Oh,
you do work for me. Good. But I'm worth it. You can find me an arfer in here if you want to take me
arfer. No doubt. How many people live in this town? Seriously? Hello. If you have problems with
garden visitors, we can make sure that only guests on the list get in. I'm just going to have a
couple of drinks and I'll be ready for work. Welcome to level 16. This level has a new helper
to make life easier. Lottie has some very special fencing, a new item, and a-
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah. I can buy the surfboard now.
But I don't have a duck. I have a duck and like a juicy duck. They can't- can they breed together?
Can I do that? Does it have to be duck and duck or can it be duck and juicy duck? Can I do that?
No, I can't. It's got to be duck and duck. And now there's no other- just buy a duck.
Should I sell juicy duck? That's a lot of money. But does juicy duck sleep in the same house
as regular duck or do they need a juicy duck house? This is- no, okay. All right, I'm gonna
buy a duck and then I'm gonna buy- okay, I have some things to buy. I need- I'm gonna buy another
duck. It says goose. Goose. Okay, where's duck? $2,000 fucking dollars for express delivery.
Get the fuck out of here. Come on, man. Standard delivery. Yeah, thank you.
You're leveled up. I know. We're looking for- we have the- all right, I think it's time- I
can throw this- I can- I can cannon this Gekki, right? I think it's time to cannon the Gekki.
Because I already- I have two. He's gonna go to the- have a party. Yeah, we haven't done this yet,
so we'll be able to send him to the party. Yeah, we're gonna get a lot of experience for this.
Fire him away. Reward for sending to a party. Yes, more, more, more. Level 17? Where's my pop-up
window for 17? Juicy goose. Gekki 1 is ready for liftoff as well. Should we send Gekki 1 to the
party? They come back, right? They come back. They come back. Send to the party. No, they come back.
They're just going to the party. I'm gonna do- I'm gonna sell these things. Sell. Sell. No, don't sell
this. Okay, sell. They do come back. Going to the party means you get your guts- what? Anytime
these things are within two or three pixels of each other, or like 200 or whatever they are,
it's so hard to select anything. There's napping in the game, and it just- it's very- it's wonky.
Cat alert. Milk time. I did promise before the stream ended that I was gonna go get a cat.
Attention. Chat has detected cat. Milk. No, milk is not a vegetable. Milk is not a vegetable,
as much as the American food pyramid would like for you to know and believe. Bone. 14 fucking
hundred. This is so much money. You- I hope you like this. Get rid of this shit. Hey, fuck. Get
out of here. Don't- Juicy goose. Don't eat that food. It's bad for you. Do not eat that food.
Leave it alone. Don't touch it. Nobody touch this food. It's bad. Poisonous. What is this, a mushroom?
What is this? Is this live? Oh, I don't know what it was. Okay, now these apples. Who needs to eat
one of these? Somebody has to eat one of these. Where's my duck? I need a crab too. I need a
surfboard. Fuck. Okay, surfboard. Boys. Boys. No, there's woo-too train and woo-woo train. There's
no- What do I get it? Garden item? Surfboard. There we go. All right, good. Now I can bring crabs in.
Evil bat. I know. I see him. Go to the desert? I will after I get rid of evil bats. So I have
two apples that I think I can- Attention. You have over five minutes of your eluded
minutes allowed on stream. Each minute after this momentary interruption will cost the streamer
$15 per minute. The clock is still here though. That should be fine. Got to text. I don't know
who's texting me right now, but I'm getting noticed. I don't want to fucking even see it.
I'm streaming. What the fuck? Where's a cat? Where's a crab? Oh, a duck. Fred, we're gonna- Oh,
come here. Hey, come here. Make more goose. I can do two goose. The bread's in the water.
Does it matter? I have another- My delivery is ready, right? Oh, super goose. Geese. It's geese.
I know. There's a quackberry. Where? Collect? Yeah. Thank you. All right. Nope.
Omega lol, two goose. Omega lol, two goose. I mean, you get it. Did you eat that bread yet?
You didn't. Why? What am I doing? I'm waiting to tame a cat and I'm waiting for a crab to show up.
When a crab shows up, I can breed the ducks, play Lisa the Painful. What on earth? What? All right,
we're gonna get the camera off of this one. I probably will never play Lisa the Painful on this
stream. I've got to make all these statements today. No, I said probably. All right, I said
probably. I gotta fix that. I will never play Lisa the Painful on this stream.
There you go. I have to- Sometimes you gotta just pull the bandaid off. Go to the desert or riot.
I'd like to see you try. I don't see anything new. I see Chadbird. I see everything that I've seen
already. Where's the new pinata? The box. The box. What box? They were telling you to play desert
bus, not go to the desert. I already did play desert bus and I gave up after about 15 minutes.
I did desert bus vr and I was like, oh, this is kind of- I'm done.
Wait, let's really reload the area. Why won't you play Lisa the Painful? Because I don't want to.
I don't want to play that on stream. I don't- I'm not gonna. That's all the reason I need.
I have to give you like a written essay as to why I'm not going to play Lisa the Painful on
this stream. Is that my homework for next time? Wait, nope. Go to the Arctic. Lisa's like Dark
Souls though. No, it's not. It's not. It's like an RPG. Like a top down. It is not. Yeah,
nice try though. That could- you would have got me to play. Oh, penguins! It isn't top down.
My whole world is upside down. Pengum. I kind of wish I'd, you know, made a-
Really wish I made a kind of an ice place.
What are you doing here? What should I bring? Will a penguin be able to exist in my land?
Maybe I should get him. All right, let's get him.
All right, what is he like? Something hot. Something hot. All right, I can do- how about a-
is it holly berry? What's hot? Is a holly berry hot? Is this hot? No! Hey! Get out.
You idiot. And now they're running away. Just- where's- where you gonna crab? Juicy duck having
a fun time? Seed guy? Come here. Gold. Gold's more valuable. Gold is. I'm just saying something
that's stupid. Is this a yam? Fear tree? Punish him with a shovel? No. You guys are twisted.
You guys are twisted. You guys are so fucking twisted. I can plant some more of these trees.
Uh, how about over here? I'll do some more of these trees. Why not? They look nice. Cat? Well,
there's milk just sitting there. Look, I can't- what- what's that I was saying? You can- you
can lead a horse to water, but you can't make him drink. What do you want me to do? Stop being so
cool and go over here. Get over here! Come visit me! Hurry! Look what I have for you!
He just stomped all over it! Got it! Okay, and now we eat. What did you just eat? He just ate
something. Mouse. You. You're on the menu. Come on! A new taffly resident. No, you just drank my
milk and you're fucking off? That was $1,400, man. You smug bastard. All right, well, how do I- I
want cats to do this shit in real life. Yes, they do. Okay, is there another fad seed here?
Okay, we're good. Fill this fucking hole. How do I- what's the requirement to get a frog to show up?
And why have I not seen any crabs in two fucking hours of game time? Oh, 3.17 hours of game time.
Shit, you're right. I want to plant these. Jerma, it's time for bed. Uh, you know, you're actually
right. It is. Thanks for reminding me. I gotta get off this computer soon. Very soon here. You're
right. No, you're right, guys. You're right. How do I plant this? What the hell even is this thing?
Where do- I can't plant this anywhere. What is this? Hazelnut. Oh, it's- I can't plant it. It's
just the nut. It's just the hazelnut. All right, where's that goddamn cat? And no crabs either.
Unbelievable. Where are the crabs? The same crab showed up five times. And now that there's a surf
board here, he doesn't want to show up ever again. And we got him. We got him. There he is. Get over
here, ladies and gentlemen. We got him. I didn't even mean to do that. Is he eating the apple?
Okay, everyone inside. Come on over here. That's a gamer meme. I don't want to. Everything is here
that you want. Everything is here that you like. Come spend eternity here. You just have to cross
that line. Just cross that white line. And you will- you and I will be friends forever.
You can do it. Just cross that line. Paradise. Water. Sand. There's a cool surfboard. Just walk
over that line. That's all you need to do. Just cross the line. And there you go. Your signature
is right here now. Excellent signature. Yes. Yes, it's very nice. Welcome. Welcome. Now stay.
No, no, no. You can- you don't- Why is he leaving?
He doesn't like the juicy duck. Okay. Well, at least you'll come over here. Eat a taffy.
Taffy. Eat it. Second frog. Yeah. Second frog. Incoming. A crow. I kind of want one of these,
as a friend. You need a dock patch on speed dial? All right. Eat this and then we can have a
frog dance. I- Where's that cat? Seriously. Oh, look. Instant money. The piñata is ill.
What is this guy? Sweet tooth. Oh, they're so cool. It's like a beaver. I gotta get this dude.
Wait, what's wrong? Who's somebody sick over here? Oh, no. Taffy ate some bad candy. No.
He ate rotten candy. What do I do? He's dying. What the hell on earth? How do I help him? Call
the doctor quick. Please help him. All right. Get in here. The two frogs. Okay. Romance time.
What do I need for them to romance? Green flutterscotch. Good fucking luck trying to
figure that out. Will you get in here? This cat doesn't give a shit. All right. What do you want?
Three fur cones. Okay. I got those. Right? I have a fur tree. What do I plant? Where's the fur tree?
Where the fuck is the tree? I just planted one. Did I just plant one of these? He's good. He's good.
Where did I plant that fur tree? This is the right there. Holy fuck. This thing's dying.
He ran him over with his car. See, he's back to normal. Flying around. Having a good time.
I need cones. Can I knock some cones down yet? All right. Just plant this shit. Fuck digging. Who
cares? And we're gonna eat these. He's lazy. Yes, I am. Just go in the water. Go in the water. Go
in the water. Go in the water. In the water. Get in the water. Stop flying away and get in the...
I can't even put you out. I can't put you out. Get to fly in the water, man. Into the water.
Fly in the water. Fly in the water. Into the water. Into the water. Get in the water. You're
gonna die. Go in the water. Are you drinking? Get... Okay. You're good. Oh, I want to do some more
dressing. I want to do some more dressing up. This is moldy bread in the water. Fuck. All right.
We're gonna make you look absolutely fucking wonderful. What plant dried out?
Oh, will you fuck off? Is there... What plant dried out? Marshmallow three is very unhappy. Well,
Marshmallow three is going to be food very, very soon. So, um, I'm sorry, but that's just the way
it is. I need that cat to come back. And wouldn't there crab somewhere? Get out of here. No, fuck
off. Get out of here. I need a kitty, you promised. I'm... I've actively been trying. You've seen it.
Dear me, it's been three hours. That's all right. How much... What do I owe? I owe like $400 something?
Whatever. I'm gonna get this cat. I need that cat to come eat a mouse. And then they'll be the
resident. And then I'm gonna put a funny hat on them. And then I'll see you tomorrow. But I do
want to do this right now on you. If I nod off, I suppose you'd better select a piñata to give this
to. Here we go. Kind of like the ultimate creation. Should it be... Should we do it like a British
bobby hat fruit hat? I mean, that's absolutely... That's wonderful. Bottles, glasses, caterpillars?
Okay. Ears. Mermaid earrings. Jiggy earrings. Puzzle piece earrings? Well, no, no clown nose.
Big jolly lips. The teeth? The teeth? No. No, that doesn't... The lips? Okay. Neck. A stethoscope!
Oh, it's perfect! I'm out of money. A yeehaw saddle. Oh my god. I don't have any money.
I need shoes, though. Kazooie talons. Like Banjo Kazooie. It's the same company. Fuck!
Good choice. If you see my parents, tell them I do actually need...
You... I don't know. What do you... Why... I'm... Let's take a look. All right. Cool. I like you. You have fun.
Look at that hat. Okay. Cat. No cats. This is rotten. What are you even doing here? Get out of here.
All right. Where's that taffy? There's a moth coming in. Where's that taffy?
Get this fucking bat. What am I hitting? Hit the bat! This is so fucked up. Where's the kitty?
I don't know. I... I tried. Where is it? Is there one? Oh, come on. Are you dead? All right.
Where is that cat? I need the cat to eat a mouse. Big time. Where? Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah. All
right. Get over here. Eat a mouse. Come on. Wake up. Wake up. He's gone again. Gone again.
Gone again. Cat might not come in since there's no milk anymore. I'm not going to sit here and
just drop thousands and thousands of dollars. No. You promised. Yeah, I know. I'm going to try. I'm
going to try again. Fly into this so I can get 2,000 more dollars. Got it. All right. 2,000.
Oh, you're ready to go for a party. No, I want the camera. Don't pour it on him. Come here.
I think the badger got in there.
Ah, just me and the crew. You know, no big deal. All right. What's... I think they... Let me go to
the menu again. Give me the cyclopedia. We're looking for the cat. What does it take for a
kitty floss to show up? We're just going to appear... I have two resident mouse mallows in the garden
and it's nighttime. I have one bottle of milk in the garden. Three resident mouse mallows in the
garden. All right. I need three mouses and I need milk. I can do that. They just need to... I need
to breed a mouse or just buy one. What does it take to breed? I already think I already have a couple.
They need to eat a yam. We can do that right now or just do romance candy,
but I think yams are probably cheaper.
Romance. Ah, romance candy. Yeah. Bye. Go for it. Romance candy. Eat it. You. Romance candy.
Tell this shit because it's just stinking up the place. Quick. Don't let him eat it.
I just sprint around. Okay. Let's get a third one and then I'll get some milk.
How could you not like it? I thought this was Animal Crossing. Some people wish it was.
Sorry. I was looking at the chat. I mean, this doesn't have to be... This doesn't have to be that
good of a... We just need one. Wait, there is three. There are three. Give me some milk.
Play something cool with blood tomorrow. That's so funny. Dude, play something with
blood and like... Shoot people and like... Axe and hit people in the head with a fucking axe.
Play that one. Okay. Play blood. There's no blood in this one. I'm playing Ikaruga tomorrow.
All right. I've got milk. I've got three mice. It's going to be night time. We're getting that
fucking cat. The new resident. Where? The cat has to eat a sparrow. Well, we'll go get one.
I'll get one. I'll express deliver it.
Yup. Yup. Yup. Yup. Yup. Yup. Yup. Yup. Yup. Yup. Yup. Yup. Yup. Yup. Yup. Yup. Yup. Yup. Yup. Yup. Yup. Yup. Yup!
Mouse, get up there. Come on. He's visiting. Watch out. Watch out. Watch out. Watch out. Watch out.
No. Don't sell their egg. I would love to select something besides... Get out of the way. Get out
of... I can't even select you. Get over here. I can't even select this motherfucker. Come in. Go
get that milk all right i please this is this is the person greeting no you
motherfucker get back here you are stubborn oh
shit he's on fire oh my god oh okay to hear some hunting
story no no no i can't wait to see you again
do we need a separate menu for every single time i press a button
like come on you guys made fucking banjo kazooie
come on come back when you know here we go i got everything that this cat wants
there's milk over here there's mice there's birds
there's all this shit it just doesn't want to come over here
by the way what the hell is that huge blue hippopotamus thing up there
what is that did somebody drink the milk don't touch that milk squirrel
it's not for you they're all existing together having fun
it's so dumb like why they dress like that then one of them dresses a firefighter
nighttime here we go this is it i've got milk
i've got sparrow i've got mice come over here please beaver
uh i mean there's a squirrel running around the beaver come in
i saw him jumping around a little bit oh he's over there what does he want
he's thinking about it i need three fur cones let's go
i should have the least few of them oh yeah let's go
knock these off all right no fur cones on this fur cone tree
be serious it's not ready yet shit we need to water it again
all right nighttime what's going on oh fuck
breed taffy's um shit it's blending with the apple
it's blending with the apples i'm trying to i'd love to select it
with it cat nighttime please come visit me and come eat all these
animals get out of here shit i missed big bits oh fuck i did
from a couple minutes ago another 5 000 bits another 50 dollar drop
which is crazy this is happening like five times tonight
thank you all of you especially thank you to the
cube overload thank you the cube the cubie overload that's 5 000 bits
they say love this game when i was a kid love you here's a little something have
a great night stay safe and well in these troubled times you as well
take care of yourself make sure you guys are following all the necessary things
that we need to be doing to get this shit out of here take care
of yourself take care of family take care of friends
and cat what more do i need to do to get you to walk in here
oh i got a new resident i didn't mean to come on don't you do it just drink out
of the fountain and that you get in here still i have to kill this bat
excuse me he's sucking on somebody's blood
he's feeding he's feeding on that tally get over it
no is it the same one the same guy the same tally is getting
fucked up oh i'm so sorry like what did i do to deserve this
why did it have to be me again i didn't do anything
okay uh doctor help happily for again cat the cat don't give a fuck guys
oh okay the cat doesn't give a shit the cat i've tried
how many times do i have to try to bring the cat over here the cat doesn't care
dastardos fuck this guy let me introduce dastardos
he loves smashing open sick pinata and stealing their sweets
wait a minute this thing's infected and it's in and it hurts it's in
it's in pain he's gonna come and rip it open while it's in pain
that's not gonna happen right all right come on doctor fix this
plus one letter grade i know you said that that's not me
dude there's just bad shit everywhere i can't even buy a cat
i can't i'm gonna piss my pants this game ramps up in difficulty good luck
this is a screensaver game oh i didn't get a look at you let me see
oh you're kind of cool okay remember the lizard is sick
what you didn't prepare for late game is this what you guys are talking about
and you're like oh he's fucked he did he made that so wrong he's so
fucked is a lizard sick where's there a sick lizard
oh no he's like i don't know what to do um all right i'm gonna call the doctor
right okay call the doctor that's not a doctor
that's not a doctor that's not a doctor
no that was i really liked that one he smashed him he smashed him and
exploded him why are you all standing around like nothing just happened
no i feel terrible now and now i'm sad and i want
i'm i'm done i'm done well that made me so upset
no cat he exploded him that was so fucked up at least we have our funny
juicy duck you're still okay and you're
2500 dollars okay it's all right and we still have
sir clownington whatever his name was here but this game's actually kind of
hard this is somebody was saying well it's
fun i'm just gonna plant this i want that cat
where do you put this fucking thing all right what is this
sad oh wait funny juicy duck people happy he's in he's in he's gonna get this
mouse right here get him get him eat somebody
do yourself it's not smelling the air with like i feel like you're gonna start
floating because there's a pie on a windowsill come on
eat no eat wait you're not gonna eat the juicy duck are you okay please
this milk everything you want is here lead a mouse over there i mean there's a
bird there's mud they're everywhere eat them
come on oh please he's right you just don't care
you don't care shit well no crabs either everybody hates my
house everybody hates the stuff i have here well
oh well this is a cool game buy a crab i don't think i can
can you shuffle quackberry to death uh yeah um
yes operator this guy what the fuck are you talking about
uh i know but i can't force him in here he needs to come in he needs to come in
any estimates he wants to you want he's gonna want to be he look he wants to be
a resident but he won't be a resident he's like this
looks like a good place i don't want to live here just get in here
and enjoy it like get the ducks out of the way all ducks
move away he needs to be comfortable juicy duck out get out of the way
he needs to be comfortable find this one little spot like right all right
there's no ducks in the area we need sand right here he's gone
he's gone he doesn't fucking care no one wants me
no at least i had my ducks that's all i cared about
to be is our last shot here the garden is full
i mean the garden is full what what do you mean the guy i can have a full
garden stay here he goes stay in here okay eat
mouse eat that mouse eat this mouse right here right there
just leave here we go it's happening it's happening it's happening it's
happening it's happening it's happening it's happening it's happening he's
ready he's ready i'm gonna pounce on him
it's happening oh you can't be serious oh get the fuck over there
oh my god this thing's gonna this thing's gonna kill him
yes all right now what do you need eat a sparrow mid all right
get that bird over here where's that bird you get over here
the pinata is ill who's ill who's ill somebody's ill
where where where where where are they where where's the ill where who's ill
this is very important i don't want him to die were they ill is it you no you're
sleeping you're sleeping you're sleeping oh shit it's big bird i
gotta i gotta i gotta fix big bird right now
quickly hurry please the cat leave how many people are ill
oh shit okay get the doctor over here get the doctor over here quick all right
eat the sparrowman eat the sparrowman ladies and gentlemen
we've got we've got a resident cat i did it
you're welcome i'll put a funny hat on him then i'm going home
do the bathtub i take a bath they eat like
pizza hot or whatever uh whatever the joke is kitty floss got
there you go okay and everyone's fine there we go
let's put some funny clothes on this cat and that's it
and then i'll see you tomorrow iccaruga i did the joke
did the thing we just have to make sure we make him nice and stylized
you should choose what's next why is this weegee boarding
beef floss all right this is important it's
it's so cute football helmet yeah i think i like the football helmet
okay i get orange now we don't need anything on the eyes
now we don't need that anything on the earth but the nose
definitely clown nose uh big jolly lips
funky tie yes what what how about the teeth the saddle
we need cool shoes there we go five out of five
are you serious i need the sneakers here are the teeth
i want those sneakers well the bird feet which ones
sneakers his dad would say no you can't afford that
i know the feeling but rules are rules i need won't say bye i have enough money
so there he goes what does it take to romance for a cat
has eaten a canned dairy nothing else well i want to wake you up because i
want i want to get a good view of you
this is fucking just bizarre okay name the cat and the cat what
what save that name the cat fart sure here's the best part about this
eventually uh if somebody else if it gets a hold of
this xbox for any reason like if i get rid of it or i don't i
don't like forget to wipe the drive or whatever
someone will be able to actually open this if they have the piano
you think i'm gonna delete save why would i do that
there you go there's this part the cat can i get like the band of all like the
weirdos come here what the fuck now what it seems very
professor pester and i'm here to educate you
you will learn how to make me happy it's time to see me
all right i want to take a good picture of all the weirdos come here
wait what are you where are you going oh no world 15 is one that's sick
oh cut cut no no bark bark i have a dog and a cat
i think the bark bark is withdrawn to your garden by its rival
i mean rival you have puzzle gums to scare the ruffy in a way
have a kitty floss in the garden so how do i make him stay
oh no he's sick too call the doctor i need a bouncer it's a don't worry i
whatever i'll see you guys tomorrow oh there he is
what do i do how do i take care of him what does he do
no i don't want to hit the fucking duck he's like a boss
did you shit his pants what do i do about this
i don't really want to get close enough to add to he just
this dude just fucking runs on my up on my shit
all right who's the bouncer that was the cat
i'll see you tomorrow god damn it whatever the guy did i save it before
that who cares fuck i didn't he's
inhaling the candy he's inhaling he's inhaling fart
oh that's that's where we end it good night goodbye
see you tomorrow we're gonna play ikka ruga tomorrow holy shit
all that just to have him be instantly killed that's fucking horrible
all right let's uh let's do the bits and hang out for a little bit see you guys
tomorrow for ikka ruga good night everybody
let's go back in time too early today we had 250 from sticks renegade they say
hey everyone germa here just bought this new clown car here it's
fun to drive up here in las vegas strip but you know that
you know what i like more than materialistic things german knowledge
okay in fact i'm a lot more proud of these seven new shelves
that i had to get installed to hold 2 000 new bottles of cvd oil
that i bought from my boomer back like the trillionaire barry
f bugleberry says if you don't have linkedin you got to get on
linkedin cvd oil what the fuck what's ikka ruga it's a bullet hell game
it'd be really fun thank you trans scout for the 500 bits
germa tell us about the cat you mentioned having also thanks for playing
viva it's nice to have a chill stream in the background while writing
uh you're referring to young soy which is kim's
cat or it was kim's cat until it was given to one of her friends because we
moved and uh didn't really have the opportunity
to bring the cat to las vegas and originally
that was kim's kim sort of got young soy it was sort of
i think from my understanding it was she was taking care of
that cat temporarily because that was not really hers to begin with i guess it
was like a stray and she was just doing her best to take
care of the cat until i figured out what we were going to do
would you ever want a cat i've had lots of cats before
my family had at least six five or six of them
one of my old cats was actually in a video
and uh i mean that cat has since left this earth but i've had cats a lot
at least five or six of them over the couple decades where i was in my
parents house you know update the wiki the purpose we were trying to we were
trying to get young soy a good permanent home
that was the plan what video uh what video was that cat in
his voice germa's voice higher than usual wait shouldn't be
how's that it was in the egg video what it was in the egg video oh
fuck i completely forgot that the egg video was not an
it was not the egg video it was here's a setup video
right it wasn't half that video i was like so scared to upload like a weird
fucked up video so i was like this is a setup video here's my computer here's
the specs and uh here's a wicked fucked up video
now right that was back when i was scared to show
you how fucked up of a person i really was
yeah that makes sense yeah that makes sense
but thank you to invaders for the 250 it's been a minute since i've sent a
rat update rat update we ended up putting
all four of them in a huge rat condo together they're very happy
but since all this pandemic stuff has been going on i haven't been able to
visit them at my sister's house anyway thanks for
keeping my spirits up while i waste away at home here's a cute pic of the rat
boys oh wow look at that they're all chewing
something that's the best part look at this every single one of them is
like i'm gonna chew this i'm gonna chew this one this is mine
everyone get here this is mine okay everybody has something to chew i'm
chewing on this ball i'm chewing on this thing i'm chewing on this over here
oh these are so awesome they're so cute pretty sick rat update thank you and we
had uh alex gave 500 bits no message just
alex 92 500 bits uh very nice gave i think almost 100
dollars here total 20 dollars in bits
three or four times in a row they say one more for the road thanks for the
huge amount of money it was very nice thank you uh i i missed
big bits here from freshly brewed cider
uh that's 50 dollars that i missed a couple hours ago
i'm sorry that i missed this but you got a great name
uh thanks for the 50 dollars hey germ i've been watching you since the tf2
days and i want to thank you for the hours of laughter
here without a doubt the best e-clown the world has ever seen
i'm glad you think that by the way bugleberry is an amazing character and
anyone who says anyone who says otherwise
couldn't recognize genius if it hit them in the face
what a fucking intelligent person you know what i mean
just you can get the smarts on this one seriously
thanks for the 5000 bits thanks for the 50 fucking dollars it's a lot of money
thank you uh germa stole my 360 thanks to the 250
hey germa the joke was funny at first but my mom is getting mad
i don't need my xbox back soon sorry david
now here's the thing you gotta type that in to log you gotta log in every day
with that name germa underscore stole underscore my
underscore 360 you gotta log in with that every day
freshly brewed cider another 50 dollars and they say how could you ignore my
bits you hate me streamer makes me sad fuck i'm so sorry
i don't know what was happening but something was happening that's a hundred
dollars and i missed you completely and that's on me i think i
was like zooming in on my face on the webcam and i've lost track of all things
in the world thank you freshly brewed cider for your
insane auto he's like let me out we'll get out of here hold on
show auto no i'm not showing auto he wants to get out of here you want to get
up come with me all right give me one second
i'll be right back come on oh yeah thank you freshly brewed cider
for your huge contribution hey butt fangs thanks for the 500 bits
hope you're staying safe and having a good day you're my favorite orange
streamer i'm happy to be your favorite any streamer so thank you
super bruce thanks for 500 bits germa i've seen a lot of recognition to
groups like the quack pack the drew crew the bugle bunch etc but
when will you acknowledge chat's original fan group
we're still here jeremy the floygan flock does not forget we demand floygan
brothers no okay uh so go get a dream cast and
go buy floygan brothers and play it i'm not playing that fucking game i'm
sorry like there's no i have no reason to ever
open that yeah like let me tell you you could play
floygan brothers if you want to if you're part of the floygan flock
to go just get a dream cast forehead just get floygan brothers forehead
and just play floygan brothers forehead right something like that
i played floygan brothers for like 40 minutes
not even like 35 minutes there's not enough time for you to make a go crew
about it quack pack i mean i've streamed viva
pinata like four times now okay right that makes sense drew crew
we've played through at least two full drew crew games
and like another six five or six streams with the drew crew
moocrew i played both black and whites at least four or five streams of black
and white that i mean but like the floygan flock
i that's like it's like 27 minutes of on stream camera time
wink dink citizens okay maybe but that yeah
because the winks were a thing for like two months it was fucking gold
all right okay i'm not gonna play floygan brothers again
no if you excuse me i'm gonna slam this water we want floygan
no i'm not playing floygan brothers but thanks for the five dollars though
hey noodle is bad at gaming thanks for 250 not gonna lie i do the shit you said
in the shower thank you on a separate note how do you
feel about a stream where you hire an actual therapist and
get group therapy for you and chat i don't think i would want that i don't i
don't i don't think i want to go to a therapist on stream
because i don't want to sit there and have them analyze me
and then it would be like what if they come up with some fucked up shit
you know what i mean like i don't want to do that i feel i feel like that was
like that would be out of my comfort zone i think
like what i don't what if they're like let's talk about your childhood or
something and i'm just like i okay how many people are watching super
bruce thanks for the five community subs as well as your bits
fucking ego maniac you guys already know that you guys already know this shit
ego ego ego ego fuck i really am gonna piss my pants
i didn't let me can i go to the bathroom i'll be right back let me just go pee
oh boy okay you know when you pee and you pee a full an entire piss
you drain your your bladder is completely drained and then
four or five seconds go by and then you just did your hair here you go again
here comes again it's round two but i've been like three times
like i've pissed storage somewhere else where
if you do a full piss and then you do another full piss
where where's that coming from do you have how many bladders do you have
doesn't make any sense the p comes from okay yeah i'm sure it does
i'm sure it does hey yen wen thanks for the 250 yen wen wen
uh i think we have a a new finished picture from my understanding
let's see it says this artwork i've done was
probably the most difficult for me to complete no matter what i was doing my
mind wasn't happy uh now because of all the virus that's
going around all the schools are closed that's right
i forgot about that all the schools are closing and shit
uh this meant my training provider suspended me from teaching
a lot of free time now because of this and i would admit being shut in all the
time by the government is getting me down here
is the artwork it's fucking crazy it's awesome
this is fucking unbelievable i'm sorry solidified in history is an image
what is an image of me eating a rotten turkey sandwich
it's it's solidified in history now it wasn't even rotten it tasted fine it
just was probably bad that's fucking incredible as always
they say also i can confirm when i draw you i always initially draw your eyes
too small your eyes are huge dude are they
i don't are they actually they're not though
do i have big eyes this is fucking fantastic though
like everything else you've done it's 10 out of 10
holy shit thank you again for this fucking ridiculous
incredibly detailed piece of artwork makes me want a turkey sandwich actually
really bad frame it in your house imagine how much
of a psycho i would be if i had just a bunch of framed
paintings of me all over the all over the whole house
that'd be so that'd be scary people would come over and be like dude
are you like you really like you huh like yeah i mean yeah i like me
you look at me do you see me we have a clip here this is uh hold on
hold on a second this is uh swiggity swanky gave
250 they say flushed flushed i don't know why they said flushed we're
about to find out let's see yes kiss me kiss me kiss me
kiss me kiss kiss me kiss me kiss me what the fuck was that
what was the what was that what was that what is this from what was that i don't
even know what the context could be for that i'm searching okay
um thank you for the thank you uh gnarly thanks for the 250 you must
have taken crack before the stream started you should
keep doing crack before streams because it makes for good content but i
don't do crack sorry very nice thanks for the 10 more
dollars thousand bits why do i look so scary i don't understand
i said this is a scary person it is i've said that at some time
that's a that's a scary person as a person that like if you you like on the
subway and you look over you're like i'm moving five more seats to the right
this is that i don't know who that guy that guy that guy scares me
thanks hey jason thanks for the 250 jason
and it's and it's another like i'm gonna make your mouth huge and your nose big
photoshop thank you appreciate it uh thanks a lot
pluto passing by thanks for the 1500 bits they say pog i guess why pog i guess
pog i guess what happened show the other image
what show the other image what other image
it's two oh there was one underneath it oh i didn't know there's two
yeah but this is this is just me opening my mouth this is not even edited
this is just a like this is that's just my face
this is that's like an image of my face that's not like
smeared or like smudged or is it it might be
wait is it that's not no that's my face that's not smudged or smeared
that's just my real face that's okay but thank you pluto passing by for the 1500
bits appreciate that 15 dollars is a lot of money just to say
pog thank you avery drop dead thanks to the 530
bits hey e-clown can you do an impression of a gorillas
character yeah
there you go why is why how many how many times right
there you go thank you uh embedded dan thanks for the 300 bits
thank you for the years of entertainment in the past in the past i
subbed seven months thanks dude also played resny before
i will i will just not today not tomorrow
maybe someday soon we still have to do normal heroes too and
both beautiful joes those are very very fantastic
incredible video games that i want to play and we're going to play them
hey goiki thanks for the 1500 bits 15 bucks you can't disagree with me on this
because i'm right but this is 100% a crack stream they
always happen during games that chat sees as boring
the other crack stream being hidden folk anyway the worst hair bit made me cry so
thanks um i don't i disagree i disagree
we had a very recent crack stream that had a very very very
fast-paced action-packed video game in the background that everybody wanted me
to play you know what it was what was it it was not
odama it was mario sunshine that's correct uh at least one of
those mario sunshine streams was a full-blown crack stream
and that was like two weeks ago so that was more meth based
anybody hear that yes because i opened my own stream because i wanted to see
what games i played recently i know there was a crack stream it was mario
sunshine he's a ghost it was the second one it was
the second mario sunshine stream yes so it doesn't have to be a game it doesn't
matter where the game is it depends on what the feel is
see tomorrow when i play ikaruga that's a gamer's dream that's i'm gonna play
that game i'm gonna play it well i'm gonna do very well that's what that
one's gonna be tomorrow little crack tomorrow just game gaming
but thanks for the 1500 bits thank you boneless bacon for the 10
bucks thousand bits do the thanos beatbox
i don't know what that means thanos thanos beatbox
oh what is that anybody know what that is i can't do it
i'm sorry i can't do something i don't know how to do but i really appreciate
thank you minus two on that guy what look it up
thanos beatbox was it just it's thanos beatboxing
thanos beatbox cartoon beatbox battles wait what
is
okay this is i mean that was what are you doing what that was like pretty the
actual technique there was pretty good it was very what what what's what was
wrong what's going on what are you talking about a bunch of
zoomers in the chat i don't anyways okay thanks i can't do that
one hey lm man thanks for the 250 germa who
would you romance dance with kim it'll be kim i mean
what do you want me to say here hey anarchy the op 300 bits no message
just money and i'll take it thank you lm man thanks for another 500 bits germa
the wrestling company of aew is making a wrestling game would you switch to that
when it's released if it has a better creative suite than the
wwe games and has a good amount of features and can
actually have a good rumble with more than
five or six people in the ring at the same time and the computer can all but
yes absolutely definitely a spaghetti dude thanks for
the 10 bucks thousand bits tactical reload
a bunch of ad symbols thanks for the 10 bucks
the music's not on well fuck let's show the i'm gonna bump you in the face a
little bit here sorry about that let's get the credits on
the screen all the subs from today thank you everybody for watching we'll
be back tomorrow around the same time or ikaruga thanks for the subs whether
you subbed yesterday whether you sub today or whether you
subbed two years ago and never again or if you're not even subbed it's all
good thanks for even considering thanks for
being the oil in the streamer car thank you a spelly boy thanks to the
250 is paper mario still a future option for a stream
and is tokyo now an option well it depends on how well ikaruga goes
tomorrow maybe i don't know uh paper mario
probably yeah probably maybe not immediate not for a while though
hey gold ruby production thanks for the 250 bits i enjoy tuning into the stream
on a regular basis but getting to watch on my birthday is
even more special happy birthday first and foremost
thanks germa and chat hope you hope i have some cake and ice cream is on its
way i hope it was hopefully had a lot of it lots
of ice cream two three four scoops of ice cream and two pieces of cake
for this guy thanks for the 250 appreciate it hope you had a good one
happy birthday silent serenity thanks for 250 do you
think you'll ever play house flipper again
i rewatched those streams again and realized how super chill and fun they
were love you mr germ if they add a significant
update to it probably the last time i went back to it it was
garden flipper if they add some more significant
stuff to do that would last more than five six plus hours then yeah
absolutely i love that game i think it's a ton of fun just needs to be enough
content for me to want to play it hey reaper thanks for the 250 bits
nobody actually liked bugleberry unironically not even you
you only like him because of the initial response was so negative
that it was funny you know i unironically like that character a lot
there's a lot of layers there sorry you you you you misread me here a little i
think thank you though thank you opster narwhal
for the three dollars and nine cents when bugleberry is around
you should bugleberry is a cool character bugleberry is a cool character is what
they said thank you opster narwhal appreciate that
i also think he's a cool character too both of you reaper back to back i think
he's a cool character thanks a lot titan claws again another 2500 bits
25 bucks from titan claws thanks a lot dude thanks again for the
dope streams i won't be able to watch for the next 10 months because i'm
deploying yeah same guy as before yep hope you're
not playing such shitty games when i get back such shitty games
stay safe good luck to you we will absolutely welcome you back
thank you for sticking around much love to you when you get back
i am sad to say though you're probably gonna tune in
during like blink the cat so i'm just gonna i'm just gonna give you some
fair warning there that game's good though isn't it
is that game any good during gex blinks the cat not
yeah blinks the cat i was i was hovering over like the buy
button on amazon and i was like fuck this game looks like kind of like
shit but there's like time travel i don't know i can't i can't i was thinking
about it but good luck to you titan claws i wish you
the absolute best thank you so much for a huge amount of money and then
finally we are going to end the stream here we
got one more let's do our proper the end the second blinks game is better i
didn't even know there were two i thought it was just the one uh dsgz
thanks for the 500 bits germa love you lots you've been making my day
you've been making my day for as long as i can remember and there hasn't been a
time where i show up and don't laugh my ass
off wish i could give you more but this is all i got anyway hopefully
this pandemic ends soon so you can take that chocolate factory
tour there's a little something i made in anticipation of the occasion
tirami elver it's an enderman sewage factor let's hope so too
it's not just not just for me to do a stream
like a comedy stream more so so the world can kind of get back to normal
i think that's more important but thanks to the 500 bits
i look forward to it as well finally opster narwhal thanks for the 513 bits
why did you make up something from my bit message
how did i make up something um i don't understand what you
i i i was under the assumption that pre-stream chat was
we that's we you talk about things in pre-stream chat and
don't spoil things but i was under these i thought we all had an agreement on
these things i guess not apparently not i
thought that was a agreed upon thing but zip it zip it
that's a joker voice was it no it wasn't that was a lenin and uh
that was oh fuck it is hey goobery juice welcome back you're not banned anymore
i unbanned yesterday if you didn't see maybe you didn't even see that whole
thing but thanks for the 250 congratulations on being unbanned you
and tar alecran gene wilder or johnny depp wonka
gene wilder a hundred times that johnny depp is zero times
okay like that's the easiest question i've had all day
all right i will see you guys tomorrow for icaruga
good night take care of yourselves have a good one and good night
locchio 250 just comes in or anything right at the end says germa the blinks
game killed my cat and my mom's garden do not buy it it's evil
i think are you referencing what just happened at the end of the stream
earlier is that what this is i don't understand all right good night
good night bye i think i'm still delayed yeah good night bye there you go