Hi. Hey, hi. Hey, hey, hi. What's up? Welcome back to another edition of Elden Ring.
I'm late, yes. By a lot. Uh, I just, here's the thing. I'll tell you a secret. If you want to
hear a stream, a streamer's secret, this is a secret we all have. So I'm really kind of blowing up
every streamer here when it comes to like blowing up there. Like, don't, don't say that we talk
mode. What are you talking about? So I'm kind of going to pull the rug out here. Streamers don't
shit all day. Make sure everyone knows that. Some of them do. But for the most part, streamers
pee. Oh, if you're a streamer, you got to make sure that you're empty before you turn the stream
on. I don't think it really do explain why. Now, some people have this magic power where they can
just go to the bathroom and just, just go and be done in three minutes. I don't know how that's
possible. It takes me at minimum. Okay. I get in there a couple of minutes. Sit down, relax.
What about the phone? All right. What's my entertainment going to be for the next maybe
five to 10 minutes? All right. I'm not ready yet. It's not there yet. You do it. You spit.
You sit there for a little while. You have to clean up, right? Like it takes a long time.
It takes at least 10 to 20 minutes for me to go number two. Always. I hope you have more than one
bathroom. I mean, I also have digestive problems too. And there he is. He just got you. And that's
how you know that now, now you've got to apologize to me. I'm telling you right now. All right. Those
of you that think that I want you to do me a favor the next time that you are going to go number two
and you're going to get surprised by this because people feel the same way. When you take a shower,
people think the same thing. Oh man, I take like five minute showers. What are you talking about?
No, dude, you're in there for 10 to 15 minutes. You just don't, your brain is not processing it
because you're like alone in a fucking cube and you're just like in your own head for fucking 10
minutes. When you go to the, when you take a number two next time, before you open the door
to the bathroom, start a timer and then put it, put it away. Don't even look at it. Do what you
normally would do. And then I want, when you come out, I want you to look at it.
And I wanted, I, I'm, I just, you're going to see it and you're going to go, all right, it's been,
all right, all right, all right, all right. It's been like 12 minutes. It's been like 15 minutes.
Okay. And then you're not, you got to come into the chat and you're not going to say anything.
You'd be like, Oh, hey man, what's the stream today? What do you, what do you stream today?
Elden Ring? Oh, nice man. The thing is you actually should probably, here's the thing about
showers. Timing your shower is really not a bad idea because you really can get just lost in your
head while you're sitting there, just scrubbing the same parts of your body. You've scrubbed like
10 times already. I think like having like a five to 10 minute timer in the shower is good. It's a
good kind of like, all right, get the fuck out of there. Better for like, you know, water and stuff.
You don't want to waste too much water, but also just for the, for your routine for the day too.
You'd be surprised how long you're actually in there for. Yeah. And you got to dry too.
People think that the whole routine in the bathroom is five, 10 minutes. No, you got to dry,
you've got to comb your hair. You've got to do your skincare routine,
moisturizing, tooth brushing. It's like 40 minutes to an hour to do a morning routine.
Dude, I, dude, if I was like president of the world, I would sign like a presidential world
executive order that no, nothing was allowed to begin. Nothing. Didn't matter what it was before
9 a.m. Before 10 a.m. Like everything had to start at at least 9 a.m. At least,
but that would kind of fuck up everything because there's like this stuff that like requires like
really early morning stuff. Like, okay, that would fuck up the entire world. Never mind.
You wouldn't know. No ambulances. No, no, no, no. It would be like specific industries.
All right. What I just said was really stupid. Okay. That was stupid because if you make everything
have to start at 9 a.m., then what happens if something happens at 8 a.m.? What if there's like
logistics that have to happen at like four, five, six o'clock in the morning somewhere?
Speak for yourself. I'm a morning person. You are onto something there. What about time zones?
Nothing as president of the entire universe. Nothing is allowed to begin before I get up.
9 a.m. Pacific time. When I get up, that's when the world starts and we play the world.
We play the world anthem for me. My favorite song. Learn to fly by the Foo Fighters.
Everybody has to listen to it. All right. Let's go. We're going to Elden Ring again.
9 p.m. Start. You understand my point, though. It takes a lot longer than you think it does to
do a morning routine. And yeah, it's the afternoon. I know this wasn't a morning routine. I had other
things I had to take care of in the morning. I got up at 9 a.m. Of course I did. I got up at 9 a.m.
I did my taxes. I ran two miles. I ate a full breakfast with pretty much all vitamins covered.
I consulted for a few companies. I consulted for some people. Made a few bucks, you know,
consulting. And then I got in the shower. Then I took a shit. It took 45 minutes. Okay. So it
takes me an hour to get my routine done of my cleansing routine. That's what I'm going to call
it. Hi. Dude, some people are just different. Yeah, I agree. Some people are just built differently,
aren't they? I'm going to tell you, every single one of these Elden Ring streams is going to start
weird. This is the way it is. Every single Elden Ring stream is going to be a weird stream
because it's equal parts me excited, equal parts me annoyed of me not being able to beat that last
boss, and equal parts me being happy that it's a thing that I'm happy playing. I don't think it's
ever happened before. I would like somebody to figure this out. Someone that's been in the
community for a long time. I don't think there's ever been a... I don't... I might break a personal
channel record here of games streamed in a row, time streamed in a row. I think we're about to
break a channel record here. It's on the shirt. Dr. Pepper. 40 hour in a row. It would probably
be a little bit more than that after today. Dorsary was pretty long. I don't know if it was
10 hours, 10 hours, 10 hours, 10 hours, 10 hours. Especially if I decide if I don't decide to take
tomorrow off. You're talking about probably 50 to 60 hours in a row, which I've never ever done
ever since YouTube even like 10, 12 fucking years ago. All right, so last thing we did,
I beat that boss in the academy. I got some cool stuff. We have leveled up a few times.
The Jedi game was long, but now I'm talking in a row, right? Like I'm talking in, you know, like
Monday 10 hours, Tuesday 10 hours, Wednesday 10 hours, Thursday 10 hours. Like I don't think
I've ever done it. You already decided to take tomorrow off. Yes, and what... but here's the thing.
Tomorrow is very relative. Tomorrow is incredibly relative term because it's 5 p.m. Pacific right
now, and I'm about to start playing Elden Ring. I might be streaming into tomorrow, if you know,
if you understand what I'm saying here. Like if this is another 10 to 12 hour stream or something,
I actually, I might be streaming like into tomorrow morning. So that's what I mean when I say take
tomorrow off. The ominous music in the background. It's all relative. We'll see. Look, I'm fine. I'm
fine. I've got matcha powder, which is a fucking superpower. I wish I was fucking around. I like
really do. I'm not kidding. I'm not kidding. I've been drinking like matcha just like you have like
a matcha tea. Like when we start some like vitamins and stuff, I feel like fucking fantastic.
This has been a long time since I felt like this after streaming. What about your kidneys?
It's green tea. It's green tea. Is it? There's an item here. Wait, why is there? Didn't I pick this
up? Okay. So I didn't pick this up somehow. Oh, cool. Why do I have to look? I just look like,
I look like, okay, I look like the witch from Snow White. Um, that's not going on,
although it looks kind of cool. Increases your health though. That's not bad. That's cool,
but not, not great. It's Captain Hook. We gotta, we have to stay with the Burger King because it
has the intelligence is just where it's at for me. The big bad wolf. That's what I was thinking
of not. Well, it could be go either way. I'm thinking of all the characters I've seen in
like Disney movies that like their nose goes like this and their chin goes like this almost
meeting in the middle. Okay. So let's go here. Goofy. All the witches in Disney are like,
they're like, oh, yes, my pretty. They have like, they have, they have beaks.
All right. Where are we going? Uh, this is where I was last time.
Doofenshmirtz. Doofenshmirtz. Doofenshmirtz. Yes, exactly. Oh, yes. Oh, well, there is the
platypus, my pretty. Right? Like, what was that? What is this thing? All right. Headphones going
in for this. I feel like this is going to be, what is, this is like a, oh, oh, look at the
beak on this one. You got a lot of health. Can I get behind you? Yeah. Oof. That didn't really do
much. And that was a bad time to wind up like that. Are you susceptible to magic? Oh, that's a long
call. Dude, settle down. Wrong button. 155. Oh, that's a stagger. That thing, if you hit it twice
in a row. What? Land octopus ovary. Oh, okay. So this, I hit that twice and he, boom, got staggered.
That's a really crazy enemy. This is, this reminds me of Bloodborne. This is like a Bloodborne enemy.
Okay. So the last, we can take this off because I already have the key. The dragon's still there.
Now here's the question. How come he can't do 3k damage every fight? Because that was, that enemy
was susceptible. Oh, give the key to that guy. Right. Where was that? Dummy. Over here, right?
Hopefully this isn't going to mess me up, but I'm going to give it to him. Are you still chasing me?
Didn't he say, oh, if you end up finding a second key, bring it to me. Right. What does it say?
Key to the seals, binding both gates of the Academy of Raelucaria. Glenstone Key will remember its
user, meaning once used, it can never be passed on to another. The Academy does not welcome the
indolent. Okay. I can't even give it to him. I can't, I can't give it to him. Well, I have
to find another one. Sad. Oh, so we're not going to do that. Here's, I think I want to go this way.
We've gone way, way far up here on the, uh, the Western kind of like Northwestern side
because I wanted to do the Academy to get the spells, which I did, which is cool.
But now I think I want to go over here like this way because it's time to start like trekking this
way. And I probably can't, I got here way too early, but once I go through this section, maybe
I'll be leveled enough to do this section. I think that's the play. That's where I'm going to go.
So we're going to go down here. We're going to take this road here. We're going to start
exploring this area here. And if anybody has a problem with that, then you can just leave.
Well, we'll go here. Would you say that souls games are grindy? Well, it depends on how easy
you want to make the game. Difficulty slider for souls games is how long you are willing to
grind souls to make your character stronger, to fight whatever you want.
So you, if you can really, really hunker down and really just desperately try to learn each
encounter of bosses in major places, then yeah, I mean, you could say you have to kind of grind a
little. I don't think that much though, to get to a point where you're capable of fighting something.
But I think that grinding souls is just your way to make the game a little easier for you.
And there's nothing wrong with that. There really isn't. Don't let anybody tell you that,
oh, you, you, you leveled up like three or four more times and like you went to fight the first
boss. Casual. You have to be, you have to be clear. Not everybody wants to play the naked
guy with the club with zero stats. And the fact that some people do is like, holy shit,
you're like really, really fucking incredibly talented and you have like an insane reaction time
and you're able to give yourself like an absurd challenge, right? Like a really, really big
challenge. And that that's commendable. It is, that's awesome. But like people are just going
to play the game differently, right? Like it's, I mean, okay. If I were to level up like 50 times
before going to the first boss, then it's like, uh, you're going to kill them in like 10 swings.
At that point, it's like, all right, well, I mean, you kind of might be missing out on some
of the fun of the game at that point. Like, yeah, I just went into the, uh, I went into the first
boss area, um, level 80 and, uh, I can kill, um, I can kill Margaret and force swing.
That's like, yeah, that, that kind of maybe goes against like the, oh, these guys get off
cool and calculated fall joke, man. Yeah. Stop monologuing at us. The point is don't be ashamed
if you got to level up five, six more times before going to a boss. It's not a contest.
Well, the reason why that's encouraged in this game is because unlike other souls games,
doing that is not discouraged because there's so much shit to do in the main world. That's
not just linearly go to each boss. There's so many things to see that like going and like leveling
and grinding and other places and like finding new things to play and new bosses, little mini
games and stuff. Oh, do it. No, don't how it makes me want to. So I got to, what's the deal with these
guys that just, they just light up, but these guys turn red. You get to kind of get to figure
out what that means. The music has changed though. Why is the music changed? It's like,
have I been here before? I haven't been this way. I haven't been down. I've been here, but I don't,
let me just look down here and see if there's anything there. Yeah, this stuff, I didn't go
down this little river. I also like how everywhere those things are. Why is the horse not allowed
here? Did I just get game mechanics spoiled of an encounter that's about to happen?
I got game mechanics spoiled. Bloody finger nary just what? How did that not hit him?
Dude, how can you faster than I am? Somebody bloody finger hunter is summoned. I got a buddy.
Help me kill him. Get him. Get him. Nice parry. Who is this? Oh, I got to make sure he doesn't die.
Yeah, fuck you invader. You're not even hurting him. Those dodges. Oh my God. I could feel that
guy's sweat dripping from his head from here. Oh, you're out of estus. Protect the caster,
protect the healer. Got him. So what was that all about? Reduvia with his accomplished goal,
bloody finger hunter Yura returned to his world. What was that? Is that a key item?
What was that thing called? No, where is it? What the hell was that thing just called?
Arcane. This thing scales with arcane. This dagger rips the flesh as it enters, inflicting blood loss
with it. Yeah. Reduvia blood blade, slash with the wicked dagger, transforming its never drying
blood stains into airborne blood blades. I want to see what it looks like. That's pretty sick
looking though. There's a dagger and it scales with dex and arcane. That's really cool looking.
Let me see what the combat art is. What? Okay. This is awesome. I'm assuming that's the part
that scales with arcane. This does bleed. It's got, that's a dagger with ranged. That's pretty
amazing. All right. Well, that was a cool encounter. Why am I still red? I just am. I got a lot of blood
in my face. There's blood all over my body. It's everywhere inside of me. Sometimes it goes up here.
Let's keep going. Any other weird shit that I didn't see? What was the, where was the encounter?
Where was that? Uh, that, that triggered when I went through. So here, I'll show you.
I walked through this kind of tunnel river area down here. So here from this, from the
Mirkwater Coast bonfire, I went through here to the river and that started here. And I don't know
if it's guaranteed drop from that guy. It might be, maybe it's not. A lot of stuff in these games
is not. It took a 40 minute long shit. I didn't take a 40 minute long shit. I'm just saying my
routine to get cleaned up is like an hour. This is a dungeon. Mirkwater cave. We see like, okay,
if you're getting your ass kicked by a boss and you just can't do it, it's so hard to pull it
because you want to get it done, right? It's the hardest thing to stop. Get out of there and like,
come down here. There's like so much more to the game than fighting the three phased boss
encounter with 500 million HP. I think I want to, no, this is good for now. Maybe I should put on
the starlight. What's that guy doing? What a weird patrol. I got to get my steps in. I can,
I can make sure that I could post about it. It didn't hit everybody. It should have. What the fuck
are you throwing at me? I thought this is where this thing is going to shine, man. And I have to
get it. See? All right. That was weird. What is ringing that bell? I get, I need starlight.
I can't see shit. I want starlight. I don't care if these guys respawn.
Cave moss? Mushroom. Five mushrooms. That was in the chest. Who puts five mushrooms in a treasure
chest? That seems like what a waste of a chest. It's this shit. These bells. I need starlight.
I'm running into bells, I think. Give me starlight. Um, where the fuck did I come from?
Where did I come from? Where's my bonfire? Where am I? Over here? Oh, okay. I can't see shit.
Oh, it is just a boss. All right. Well, nevermind. No object permanence. I couldn't see. Look, it's
okay. Can you see in there? Fine. All right. Here we go. Here we go. Here we go. Here we go.
What is in this room? We'll find out very shortly. Something's gonna crash through that.
Something's running around up there. It's giving me a little alien thing.
Patches? Of course Patches is in this game. Patches. Yeah! Wait, please. Really? Okay.
So, Patches is in the game. I just had to turn the volume up a little bit and I'm terrified
that I'm gonna accidentally like back into the window of the game. Yep. Okay.
I don't know. He's gonna do it again, right? He's absolutely gonna do it again.
Okay, so if some things can't be forgiven and we backstab him and kill him, we'll get something
that he has on him. Whatever it is. Or give and forget means he becomes a vendor, which he might
sell something useful and he also might show up later in the game. I'm curious.
Just what I'm tethered, like you, only free-spirited. Nothing, you might say. Only for now,
those retired soldiers turned bandits. Ah, they're paying for my gruel in exchange for my, well,
showing them the ropes. Showing them the ropes. Honestly, this looting racket is bloody terrifying.
Frankly, I'm ready to wash my hands clean. Maybe set up a legitimate shop. So don't be a stranger.
Really? Yes! Somebody did it! Don't forget to pop back for another visit, friend.
We're ready to wheel and deal. Come next time. Oh. Okay, so I gotta come back here and there'll be a,
he'll have a shop here? All right, we gotta reload the area because I got, I mean, what do you got?
You're where Patches is a reoccurring character. Oh yeah. He's always a dick. He always like,
fucks with you. Um, he's always like a weird friend slash foe that always is an asshole.
But he does, sometimes he can be kind of useful. If sometimes he can be kind of useful.
Let's come right back. Just kill him. He's going to backstab you in the next Souls game.
Okay, so can I go back down here now? Do I have to pass time or will he just be like,
can he just, can I just do it? What was with the bells? That was weird. Why, what, what,
what the bells? Why all the bells? Just, it's just like an alarm system. Okay, easy. I mean,
I want these. Okay, so is he here? There's another chest there.
Okay, purchase. What do you got here? All right. Boost rune acquisition for a time. What?
That's what that does? Market's shackle briefly binds market once imprisoned to earth.
What? Is this a way to make that fight easier? Ooh, you got a key. What? Okay.
It's like gas coins music box. Okay. Well, that's where that is. Harrying dagger. That's what that
is. Horse crest, wooden shield, sacrificial twig. Oh, this is if you die, um, you don't lose your
runes. I kind of want these. You're like, I need to go, I feel like going to that kind of farming
zone that I was in before turning that on and just, I wonder how long it lasts. I should,
he also has sells one of these too. All right. What's in the chest? Let me ask him about the
bands though. Maybe he's got something on your shopping list. No, no trouble to me. What's
going on? And it's make a clean break. Now they're all suppliers,
no good ones at that. I mean, I understand a word I'm saying, but it hardly matters.
We have a natural connection. They're all foot soldiers, survivors of the defeated army
work to the bone by their high and mighty Lord only to be thrown out with the rubbish.
Ah, it's the same old story everywhere I go to hell with it. How does patches keep getting
in every single universe? That's what I want to know that chest over there. Yep.
What's inside the treasure chest? Well, it's nothing too special. You do something to me
again. I'm going to be a trap. And besides this valuable customer could be a long time coming.
Everything is given take. Yeah. Give and take. There's going to be a, there's going to be a
bomb in there. Okay. So we might as well just open it so you guys can laugh at the
fucking explosion that happens in my face. So we're like the poison gas. Here we go.
Well, well, well, I should have known.
Okay. Could have rolled away. He's just a cat. Where the fuck did you put me?
Give me whatever that is. Well, that's got a huge arc map. Get it before I die. Stagger.
Oh, damn. I got dead. I actually got the full charge. I actually got it.
That was almost 800 damage. Damn. Okay. Cool. So where am I?
I'm great. East. This is exactly where I want it to go. You put me in the exact area I wanted to be
in. Thanks patches. You're a real friend. Let me get to a road though. There's a big, what's this
big tree? Is that the, the Elden tree? Whatever the thing's called. Oh, what are the, what are
these? Are these just refill your flasks? I think these are flask refillers. Spiked cracked tier.
Greenspill crystal tier. What's that? Temporarily boosts stamina in mixed
physics. Enhances charge attacks for a time in mixed physics. What is, what is this
physics thing? Unlock the rune you got from Godric please. What do you mean? Oh, this is a minor
elder tree. That's a refillable potion. Really? I have to go to a tower to unlock it. Oh. Well,
I don't know that yet. Spoiled me. Actually, I did know that. All right. This is kind of an ocean
here. Minor urd tree. Why is that on here? There's a reason why that's here, right? It's on the map.
What? Like a dungeon? Or is it just, hey, here's one of them. That looks like I can get in there,
doesn't it? That looks like I can get in there. Oh, what's this? An observatory. Whoa. Where am I?
What the fuck? This game is fucking insane. This is crazy. That is this much as random shit for you
just to go do. I need a, okay. Is there a fire down here? I hope so. Find out. What the fuck?
This is such a huge elevator. How long is this ride? My head would have exploded from the
underwater pressure by now. See you for a river. Well, we got one. Okay. I don't have enough to
level up. Um, I think my flasks are okay. I think five and two is fine. Let's take a look.
What's this shit? Okay. Well, there's a summoning statue thing here. Oh, okay. Rune. We're calling
finger. I might just sell a lot of the PVP stuff and all the items don't know. Stone unturned
silver firefly, which is also new. No stone unturned ruins. All right. Where's the, where's the,
where's the guy that's going to be around the corner with like a giant? Yeah. The casters,
they look like casters. Those are stale. Those are staves. Those are staves. These casters,
they casters and not, they just have shiny things. All right, let's go.
We know how to deal with groups. You're in slow motion. We know how to deal with groups. Not bad.
Immune to that. What the fuck was that hit box, hum? These guys do not get staggered really.
It's so slow. It's so weird. That takes care of that. Rune probably. Oh, nice. I need a five
somber stone, right? What is that? Oh my God. It's like a shining thing up there.
That's like a hyper item. Look up. What do you want me to look up for? Why is there a Riddler?
Why is the Riddler here? Oh no, it's a golden centipede. There's nothing. Stop. I don't know
what you're talking about. Runes. I wonder if I can just like, do these guys have any brains at all?
Probably not. They're so slow. Yeah, all right. Look up. Look up. Look up. It's structure and
bones and material and shit. What do you want? It's mountains. It's this like, it's like a sky
with rocks and wood. All right. I'm not looking up anymore. I'm not getting baited like over
and over again. Hurts a lot. Exploded. That was definitely it. No. Stop. These guys hit so hard
and they're just so slow. You're in slow motion. You make me angry. All right. What does that thing
do? I think it's just a big AOE. I can't really get behind him. So we're just going to have to.
Those go. No, I can't pull them. So it's not, I don't even need to try.
Immunizing cured meat. Oh, I want to do this. Why can I backstab him?
Rainbow stones. Those things that make it so you can don't get lost.
Which in this game, they actually might be very useful. Unlike previous games where it really
kind of didn't matter that much. Previous games, those little pebbles or pool, but
you're like in a game like this, they're way more helpful. What does it, what are the,
wow, there's so many people over here. For what? There are a shitload of you here. Is
there something here? I'm just going to, I'm not going to fight these guys.
Is there an item? I don't see an item. Mushrooms. Just chilling. Yeah. I don't see anything else.
I think that's just kind of, you don't have to go through the front door. Unless it's something
there, the glowing, I don't see it. No, I think that's just all their steps. There's nothing here.
Okay. Well, let's get going. Do I have scarlet rod? I don't believe so.
Wouldn't that be on the screen? What about over here? Yep. Item right there.
Game's too dark. Turn up the brightness. I think that's intentional.
I think I was going to see you back here. Did you? No, kill it. Please. No, kill it.
I thought it was going to be an item. Okay. Right here.
Utting horn. I have to sit down and craft. I have my, I have like five backpacks full of stuff that
I haven't even opened. So this is probably a boss door. Big waterfall. Interesting. Oh, ghost
glove wart. That's really important. I could probably go through the waterfall. It's definitely
like a secret thing to go through. Dude, I'm sorry. I'm not going to like pick up an item over here
and have 10 of you get up and kill me. Backstabbing takes too long. Just kill him. Damn it. Come here.
That thing is good, but they just have so much health. Clayman's harpoon? These people have made
it to clay? Clayman's harpoon. What else here, right? I want to see what that is.
Int scaling? Harpoon with a tip made from a sharpened meteorite shard built by the claymen
who infest dynastic remains. Blade emits a faint light and deals magic damage. That's cool. So
that's like a magic damage thrust. That's actually really good. Another ink weapon. That's awesome.
All right. I'm not going to get rid of this in case I need it for something. Okay. Let me put my
other weapon on the one I'm actually going to use. Now I'm fat rolling, so that's going to hurt.
I think stone. The phone's got to go back in. Let's go. All right. There's no way there's not
something in the waterfall, right? Impossible. When has there ever been a video game? Soap.
Is there soap in the waterfall? What the fuck? Is it a crafting material? Soap removes filth
and accumulations on the body. What? Filth covering the exterior eventually seeps into soap. If you
get dirty of this. Okay. Filth is in the game. I imagine that's poison buildup. Maybe. All right.
Well, here's the big door. It's time to find out what's going on here. Although I might want to
not do this yet because I have a lot of runes. I can probably level up before I get killed by whatever
the enemy is up here. Those guys are so slow. It'd be so easy to get back here.
I think it's time to be a coward. Yeah. Time to be a coward. Coward time. I have way. Oh yeah. I
could definitely level up in these like 11,000. One of these will do it. Actually maybe three of
them and eight, a little more. Is that was enough? It's probably 11 or 12. 13. 13. What? And then
one more of these. Look at that perfect calculation. 13, one nine six. I will have
zero souls left. Kill these guys and that's it. That's a huge knockback too.
All right. Let's go. Level up. Kill one of these guys with your eyes closed. Fine. Ready?
What do I want to put the point into? Mind probably I said, right? Mind. Yes, I do.
20. Mind gets us our friend Oleg finally. You can do wield the spheres.
Actually pretty crazy. All right. We'll be good. I got two, one. We'll see. We need to upgrade the
boys. I actually was talking to Holly last night. I was like, man, I really don't know what to do
because like if I don't get the boys to plus 10, everyone's going to be fucking pissed. And like
they're going to be mad at me for not doing that. But what if like Oleg's not that good? And what
if that is the right play? I was like, I don't know. I wonder what I should do.
Like if I don't upgrade the boys to at least like plus five and I'll never hear the end of it.
There'll be like a meme on the channel for like another three years. Can I get up here?
Just look at that. There's like a huge, there's like a giant sparkling item over there.
I can definitely get up there from here. Absolutely. No doubt in my mind.
Oh, can I, maybe I can. That was just the earth exploding sound from rapidly.
It was actually that sound. Yeah. Okay. Okay. Not bad. He's going to explode.
Do it.
Watch out for the little bubbles. All right. What happened? Okay. Throwing dagger. Now wait,
dropping down here gets me that. Oh, okay. I gotta be careful. There's a ledge here though.
Wait, I'm not done exploring because there's no air to go over here too. God. All right.
Can I make that jump? I can't make this jump. Wait, what was the point of that?
Nothing over here. Really? Why would they have a jump here?
Oh, come on. Really? No, it's gotta be something. I guess not. So let's drop here. Right there.
Okay. I gotta be careful. Oh, the bubbles. That's the bubble spell.
Bubble spell. That thing looked like it was a piece of shit though. I need arcane. There's
several small magical bubbles that drift towards foes before they naturally pop.
I'm not going to do arcane. That's cool. Um, I wonder if I should be putting any points into
arcane at all. How come this, wait, why the runes respond? The items respond down here?
Did I just not pick that one up? Will Diablo four be the Elden Ring of Diablo two? No,
not. I don't think a chance in hell. I'm sorry if I'm honest. Arcane is luck.
Look up, Jermo. Look up. Whoa, what the fuck? It's like there's an arc here. This is one of
these like arc building. Is that a map? How far am I going here? I'm going like, where am I? Okay.
There's bugs here. Just checking. You never know. Reserving ballaces. Holy fuck. Sorcery falls off
hard later on. Well, that's what I'm saying. That's why I got to make sure I'm prepared
and that I have enough like decks and other shit. And I have like an int scaling weapon
like this to make sure that I can complete the video game. And those people that were saying
that I'm a, I'm a noob. I saw a bunch of people called me noobs, I thought. And it was not making
me happy. And I'm giving you the reason why. Oh, I had a dream. This is perfect. Okay. Perfect
opportunity. I had a dream last night. Let me explain this. So in the dream, I was like walking
around, I think it was like my like apartment or my house, whatever. Like I was just in like an
apartment or something. And it was this little crab like this, tiny, tiny, tiny. And it was just,
it was as big as I would say, not as big as a tarantula, but a lot bigger than a house spider.
It was like, it was as big as a crab. So this was a crab, like a small crab. And it was just kind
of walking around little, just like walking around and it had like a, like a, what looked like a stick
in its hand. It had this long, like almost sharpened stick. And it was just kind of like
walking around holding it. And there was like a little tiny little shield that was, I would say
maybe a foot or two away from where the crab was. So it's holding like a little sharpened stick,
walking around. And there was like three or four other people in this house. And we were like,
what the fuck's going on here? Holy shit. You see what's in your house. I don't think we were in my
place. We were in somebody else's. I don't even know who these people were. So it's like, dude,
what the fuck is going on? This crazy. And this crab comes, kind of goes over it, picks up this
little tiny shield. It's like, what's going on? This is like, get a camera, somebody get a fucking
camera or something. And then like the distance was another little crab that had the same items.
And they like started to go towards each other. And it was like, what the fuck they're going to
fight. They're going to like, this is going to be like a sword fight. They get close enough
where they just barely start to like whack at each other. And I don't know if this is like the
person's dog that owned this place, but this big golden retriever just like runs over and like,
starts like fucking biting and like biting them and shit and freaking out. And the whole house was
like, whoa, whoa, whoa, no, no, no, no, no, get the dog, get the dog. Like it sprinted over and
started to like go after them. Like kind of sniff, bite, bite, sniff, sniff. Like it was like,
you know how dogs are, right? It's just something like a little bug or something sometimes. And it
was like, get the dog. What the fuck is happening? It was chaos. It was absolute chaos. Like this
golden retriever like literally was not even in my field of view. And it like slid into frame,
like it's pause. It was like, it just started freaking out. And it was like such panic and such
chaos because it was like, I don't, but they have like sharpened stuff. We don't want the dog to get
fucking hurt. Like we don't, I didn't even know you had a dog. Like it was crazy. It was, and then I
woke up. It was just absolute mayhem for like five seconds. And then I woke up. Somebody said,
dude, you have, why are you having viral video dreams? Yeah. That's just like something crazy.
That would be like on like TikTok for 10 seconds. Oh dude. There's like this weird bug here.
Dog runs in. No, no, no, no. Only in my version they had weapons. So it was scarier.
You're having Zoomer humor dreams. Yeah. Cause everybody kept was like yelling,
no, put it down, drop it, drop it. Like, don't do that. And I think, I think he like was just,
I don't know. I couldn't even tell what was happening. It was just chaos.
Oh, it was so weird. Like they were going to go fight each other. Like I think it was because
of the crabs in the game. Don't ask me why. Like I had, I mean, I, I know why I had like a dark
souls dream. This one's way more aggressive. Yeah. I know why I'm having like weird, like
sword and shield dark souls dreams. It's because of this. Don't ask me where the golden retriever
came from. And it was one of those golden retrievers that was like super big and a little
chunky tons of hair. Like that, like kind of that golden hair. It was that kind of chunky and like
big crab eggs. All right. So what is going on over here? This is, this is kind of, this is a
long little area. No map, which cause it's a dungeon. Why would there be a map? Okay. Map
right there. See ask and ye shall receive. God, what the hell is this? Wait, why? There's a map
down here. How big is this place? There's another bonfire. This is ridiculous. Okay. So where the
hell am I? How did I, I don't even know how I got here. Light the flame. Hey, that's not a map.
Maybe I have to light up a bunch of beacons or something. Okay. Well nevermind. All right. We
got this way, that way, that way. I'm going to go this way. This place is huge. Let's go left.
That's not funny what you just did. It's annoying. I know that like Elden Ring, all the From Software
games are there. They're pure comedy games. What you just did didn't make me laugh. It made me angry.
Get away from me. What the? All right. Hold on. Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait. Who is this?
This guy doesn't seem to care. I'm waiting for you to get out of the way. Is this like an NPC?
Why does this guy not care that I'm here? Barbarian? Okay. That guy was just collecting
babies. Why did you? Get away. Just leave me alone. I don't want to fight that thing.
Oh, it's a, it's a fun. Come here. Maybe it'll eat out of my hand. Long wind up. I got long winds
ups. I'm back against a tree. Get rid of it. I'm looking up his ass.
Camera's just pointed directly in his ass. Like get me the fuck away from him.
Okay. I'm glad I did that. Okay. Like how many fucking times in a row do these guys swing?
One, two, three, four, five, six, seven, eight, nine, 10. Okay. Now play the game. Now fight me.
I want to kill this thing so bad. Now fuck you. You just, you're just, you're just in the fucking
way. These crabs, seriously. It's like, why are there so many crabs in Elden Ring? There's,
there's huge crabs everywhere. They're in every area. We're down in like this downtown magical
fucking like Disney, like Hades area. And there are this seafood here. What? Okay. Get off the
horse. I'm not, I'm, let's go. Give me a break. Not playing around here. There's a guy over,
I got collapsed on. That's what happened. So let's not get collapsed on. And there he is. Okay. So
this is, this is a problem. There. Mad because crab. Mad because crab. Mad because crab.
There's crabs everywhere. They, they might just spawn. Maybe they just show up.
They do. Okay. I was wondering like, what the fuck is happening? Oh, there's a beacon here.
Get out of the way. It's whatever you are at this too. I wish you could pet the animals.
Don't you think that'd be kind of funny if you could like, who's that? Like if you could go up
and just be like, and they gave you plus one resolve. Okay. So that got that one and got this
one. I'm going to go the right side now. They're boys. You're a genuine American pleb. I was going
to say warthog, but pig was less syllables and I was angry. So that's why I said it early.
Okay. Stop picking your nose and play. We got over here. Hey, armorers cookbook.
Look at this. This is, this is ridiculous. Uh, like am I ever going to sit down and craft a single
item in elder? I have 117 of these. I have, I mean, what am I doing? Look at all these cookbooks.
I'm not even doing it. Just make soap from all of them. You're holding it just in case.
That's kind of what it feels like. I've already been, I've been, I've been down there, right?
I don't know. Have I, that's where I started, right? Yeah. So I got these fires lit that one.
I've got the one on the left. We're going to go right and see if I can't. And actually, you know,
let's rest at the balloon file because I don't care about those enemies over there responding.
Why do I care? All right, let's go like the one on the right and craft from the pause menu.
Um, blood loss. I can make, I can make 12 of these temporarily boost fire damage negation. I can make
four of these. I can make fire pots. What's even useful to make a cloud. What would even be useful?
Maybe this like, maybe this would be useful at some point. Maybe one of these fire. Yeah. Like
this is just, you cook, but can I even cope my weapon? Cause it's magic. Use the cookbooks.
I use them for my, my inventory. I can't use them from here. I have to turn them in. I think
that is there. It is auto. Okay. Well, I, I don't, I don't care. Okay. None of that stuff really is
pressing for me to do right now. Look, if I fight a boss and it's like, Oh wait, they're susceptible
to fire damage. And by the way, they do fire damage. Watch out. I can just like, I'll make like
a hundred of them. Why is there another game underneath the game? They made Elden ring. And
then they said, Oh, you know what? Um, yeah, we should make like a whole nother video game.
We're out of room on the map though. That's okay. Just put the whole thing underground.
There'd have to be two levels, like one under sea level, like whole entire video game. And then
one above sea level. How did they make this? How did they make this game? Do they have like
12,000 employees? How does this possible? They hid dark souls four in Elden ring.
Imagine like an announcement like that. Oh, by the way, I just want to let everybody know.
Uh, we actually made dark souls four and it's, we made it below sea level in Elden ring. So yeah,
there's like a whole other story down here. Uh, it's not, it's just optional. If you don't,
if you don't have to do it, who cares? Jesus. All right. I don't want to fight all these guys.
I just want the item, which there is just material leaf inverted Hawk heater shield.
That's definitely an anti-fire shield. Okay. Cool. I spent the item. There's no, uh, fire over here.
Very cool. The aggro. Okay. Um, I want to, he's not behind me, right? He is. He's coming.
He's got a bow. Will he shoot the ball or will he despawn? Leave me alone. I think I'm far enough
away. Why are you so annoying today? I'm annoying every day. Um, okay. He's gone. I've been using
this for, I don't think I need to use this one anymore. Medium sized metal shield easier to
handle than a kite shield. Inverted Hawk is an emblem of the company of slaves order to explore
the eternal city. And it's Perry. How is it different from anything else though? A hundred,
a hundred. It's a little more fire and a little more lightning, but that's big of a deal considering
that this is 58. This is not that great for fire or lightning, which I'm imagining. We're probably
not in the magic area right now, so maybe I'll just put it on. This is the best I have for fire
besides this, but I can't wear this or maybe it's lightning. We'll find out. All right, let's keep
going. Halloween grounds. Hollow horn. What is that? Is that a statue or is that, is that alive?
This thing is definitely alive and maybe it's not. I have, okay, I got a theory. My theory is
you light all the fires and then you come back up here and it stands up and then you fight it.
That's the theory I'm going with, so that's what we're doing. Yeah, yep, look at this. Yeah,
one, two, how many are there? I lit two. One, two, three, four, five, there's six more to light?
If it goes by that theory, then damn. All right, well, we got a lot to look at for that stuff to
light. Oh, goodbye. I see a fire over there. Your aim is unmatched and it annoys me. Oh,
there's a Mario thing. There's a Mario 64 thing. Let's try it. Whoa. I've never used one of these.
What? How does this work? What happened? I've never used one. What was that?
That just was fucking stupid. I didn't think it was going to go that high. That was too high.
You were facing the wrong way. I mean, I thought that those things were automatic.
I thought it was like, oh, go here, hit jump and it will put you, so I didn't think I had to like
actually steer the thing. Like I was on a wingsuit. Your urinal activated. I thought it hit me in
real life. I felt that it hit me in real life. Okay. So how does this work? Watch out. Watch out.
Watch out. Watch out. Be careful. Be careful. No, you're going too close to the edge. Be careful.
Oh my God. That was horrible. Okay. That would have been so sad, but I think everybody would have
laughed. I would have been one of them. How do I activate this? Jump. Dude, this is ridiculous.
We're, I'm in like another dimension. Glove wart. Yep. The more glove wart I get, the more that
there's a chance that the boys get to plus 10. It's just seeing if there's something down there
that might be whatever. That's for play through number two. What was the point? Nice. Actually
worth the binoculars in this game. Where are they? It's an invisible bridge. Oh, I'm sure there is.
Oh, it's an invisible bridge. Thanks guys. I appreciate the help.
Like it's an invisible bridge. You can walk over this. That's a great, really good idea. That's
very funny. Uh, even if it's true, I don't believe you. I fucking can't believe I live. Why would I
do that? I can't believe it. I figured like maybe everyone just spoiled that for me and like, okay,
whatever, we'll just go. Everybody in this chat needs to understand if I didn't do that for the
next 40 straight minutes, as long as it takes me to clean up in the morning, right? We would be
hearing back to the bridge, back to the bridge. Oh, bridge, bridge boys, uh, rise up bridge crew.
Hey, invisible bridge crew. That would have been, it would have been like an hour.
So I'm just getting in front of that. Uh, I have to go back up there. Don't kill me.
It's your voice. Oh, bridge crew shot an arrow like five minutes ago and it actually ended up
hitting me. But how do I get in the middle? Okay. I'm going to do something really weird here.
How do I get down from here? How am I supposed to get down? I want to try to go in the middle
area with as an item. I jump into this jumping into the stream of air. So, I mean, theoretically
that should work, right? But it might not try it. Wait, I can't get back over there.
How do I get home? How am I going to get back? I jump over there. Holy fuck. I almost didn't.
All right. So I want to go in the middle. This is not going to work.
Where am I going? I'm fine. What? I just want to go like this. My own head.
I was literally on purpose. It was on purpose because I purposefully thought that I could make
it down there without dying. It was on purpose. It was purpose behind it. You've got that. You've
got that first part, right? Okay. Where are they? Are they up there? Where's the fucking up there?
Why do they have to be up there? Oh my God. The game just ran forward and I just like freaking
freaked out. But I actually have to jump up there. That's annoying that it should be where
you land, not where you jump from. Okay. Let's try this now. Is that a person? It looks like a
guy with a cloak on. All right. Let me see if I can get in there from here. That's gonna kill
you, right? I want to, let's see. I have, this is going to be such a pain in the ass. Can I get in
there from here? If I just jump and then move forward at the very last second, I'm saying like,
no, wait, what if I do this? Wait, what's the jump? I couldn't jump. Why could I not double jump?
I was trying to double jump into that. I didn't get my second, I didn't get the jump.
I was going to fall, jump, like double jumping in the middle. You fell. You didn't jump. You
can do it still. You can only double jump after jumping. What? You have to jump to double jump.
Really though? Do I, I feel like I've done that before a few times. Hold on. Let me prove chat
wrong. Wrong, by the way. Wrong, by the way. Debunked. Why are you joke farming? I want to
get in there. I'm not farming jokes. I'm farming items and souls in the game. Sometimes I wish I
could just jump and like Yoshi this horse and like get further. Can I jump from the other side?
Find out. Is there a ledge like here or something that I can get on?
It kind of looks like it. What about here? All right. What happens if I do this?
Get off the horse. This is going to be a nightmare. Okay. Wait, I might have to jump. Remind me to
check that if I need to. Oh shit. I need to jump from the horse. I have to horse jump over there.
Too far? I know I got a horse jump over there. That's the only way I could have dropped. Wait,
what? No, it is the only way, isn't it? It's so funny. That would have been fucking hilarious
because I would have missed it and freaked out because it was right here. All right. There it
is. So what all this time and all this energy, what was it for? Oh, cool. Like bone arrows with
fucking goo on them. I'm glad I did all that. But there might be more. It's not. Now somebody that
is playing an archer build might go, holy shit. Nice. But that's not me. I'm going to go that way.
Can I skip that? If I just go there and jump across the whole thing, does that work?
I would imagine it does. And I'm probably going to get laughed at when it doesn't.
I mean, it might work. No, it's not going to work. And then why would I do that? I can literally go
right here. Okay. Some eagles just hanging up. I don't think so. I'm going to horse this time.
Idiot. Are there's another fire? Nice pop in. Oh, great pop in gameplay.
All right. Well, dude, all right. I'm this is ridiculous. There's so many people here.
How am I supposed to handle this? This is ridiculous. What? There's no way.
I think I just have to get off and run. It's going to be worth a lot of souls if I can kill it.
And you have magicians too. So there's magicians, axe wielders, sorcerers. Take out the archers
first. Anybody that has like magic can get rid of them too. Nice entrance. What happened to my horse?
What happened? What? They like staggered the horse. Why are there like 15 of you here?
That was going really well. It was until like somebody just and like somebody hits the
fucking horse's leg and then you get the gong sound and you fall down. Just I'm just going up
there and doing it. Is there really a need to fight like 30 people here? Okay. All right.
That's that one. I'll wrap around this edge. You piece of shit. Where are you doing that?
Okay. Give me a second. Should I pull these out? I don't know where that's coming from,
but I need to kind of know before I start moving. Okay. Yeah. It's a guy. Somebody in a tree shooting
me with these arrows. Where the fuck is this person? Like I was, I didn't even know. I couldn't
see him. Sniper on the hill. All right. Nice. Minecraft arrows run towards the arrow. That's
a good idea. I don't, I don't even know where the guy was and he could have been behind me
for all I knew. Okay. So where I died, this is the bullshit here. That's where that was. Okay.
Let's get this. Get my body. What was that? Fuck you guys. Why? Get out of the way. You stupid
animal. Get out of the way. Where are my souls? There. Hey, all right. Not stupid animal. Okay.
All right. I know. That was rude. I have to get off the horse and just like fight people,
right? Because like they're going to keep doing this shit. I mean, or like honest to God, like
what the fuck, man? Just fight them. Like they're not going to stop. They're going to keep spawning
on you until you've had it. There's another one right here. Okay. Sure. Did that come back?
Is that just like a defense mechanism for the tower? I don't, that's probably going to hurt a
lot. That one, this one, I'm going to just do a big circle because just do the perimeter.
There's probably another one or two around the perimeter. It's bonfire there, which is good.
This is so huge. All right. Bonfire. That's good. Take it. You see the clip of you twerking
during the VR stream. I lived it. I can go up there, but I'm into the, I'm trying to light
these fires here. So we're going to light the fires and blink a bunch of times because my
eyes need to be moisturized. I'm looking for fires. There's something all the way down here,
but I think this might be going too far. I think that's too far. I don't think they would put them
that far away. Although what the hell do I know? That's a backstab if I ever say that.
I'm going to assume there's probably one or two more down this way and then we can go
fight that boss in the middle. That it's probably optional, but let's do it. Why not?
I probably have enough to upgrade my weapon. We'll see. It feels like you're the baddie because
those monsters are just living peacefully with the wildlife. I love it. I live in like games
and like media play, but like your moral compass. It's kind of true though. It's a very,
it's a very pretty area. Somebody tried to hit me with a barrel. Sounded like it.
What is over there? We had some weird shit over there. Runes, waterfall. Oh,
oh, it's one of those weird beat snake animal features. Um, patches here. I just was setting
up shop. If you need anything, don't hesitate. Hell, you're a scoundrel, aren't you? I think
I'll see you later. Playing music. All right. Do, do patches right now in your room, wherever you
are and just tell me, and you're going to say, ah, that's Dewey Griffin. And that wasn't even
close to being Stuart Griffin. All right. I'm just going to, this is weird. There's a, somebody
playing music. I'm very interested. Whoa. Is that a bow and arrow that he's playing? I'm not going
to interrupt the song. Book, bunch of cookbooks. Oh man. He's got, look at all the keys he has.
I want those and I'll get this too. Really cool. Do I have anything that's expensive
that I just don't give a shit about? Not really. Maybe some of the weapons. Well, we know I'm not
using the, uh, sword sword. This is not going to happen. I'm not going to use this dagger.
No, I have the cool daggers if I ever wanted to use it for any reason. Uh, I'm not going to use,
wait, what if I dual welded it? Could be this thing. No, it's faith. I'm sorry. It's 500 souls.
Goodbye. All right. Same thing with these crossbows. No, I'm not going to use them.
I'll keep that just because it's fun to have. Uh, some of these shields might be good in certain
situations. Let's see. Yeah. They, I, you don't never throw away armor ever because it just
randomly has use that you just don't know about. In fact, I got a couple of new things I want to
look at, although I don't need to. Okay. How do you pronounce wield like that? Wield.
Okay. So I can afford, I'm just going to come back and buy the other key.
Like this is, that's, those are cheap. Those are really cheap. Um, I was seeing if anything was
behind him. I'm not fighting that. I just looking for the thing to turn on, which there was one over
here. I missed, didn't I? Oh yes. Oh, you've come to the right place. You need only unravel its
mysteries. It wasn't outside. I like yourself to begin. That's my favorite character in every
souls game. By the way, I wish they gave that guy way more screen time. I love that guy.
He needed it five times more screen time. That one right there until wait, buying those tears
will let you upgrade the blast. Really? Are you bullshitting me? Are you shitting me for content?
Should be one more. Is that actually, is that true? Cause I'll go back up there because my
flask is only at a plus one, which is sounds like it's probably terrible right now. Get out of here.
Tears are for respect. Is it, can I, let me go look at it. That's it. All signed and sealed.
I don't know. Whatever happens, you may think at all of me bad.
All right. Hey dude, I'm back and I want to ask you a quick question about the, how are the,
what are those tears do material needed by Rinala to grant rebirth? You lied to me.
Look up. It's nothing here. Different tears for flasks. Yeah. You guys, you guys had,
now we've got to run through like the weird thing over here. No, turn around. Damn it. It's too
late. It's not too late. I'm going back up there and I'll tell you why I'm going to crack a crunchy
because I want to buy that other key. I just forgot about it right there. And then please don't
fucking kill me. Like don't look up. That tear lets you rebirth and change stats with the moon
lady. Yeah. Why does he move around in the game? Like a panicked bug. Yeah. Let's see how you move
around when you're playing. Cause I'll tell you right now, if you are not sitting there like this
the whole time you play, then hypocrite Andy, when a guy appears behind you, if you, okay,
if I walk down this way and I don't know what's to my left and a guy jumps out and attacks me
and I don't know he's there and it's a surprise, I'm not going to go like this.
No, you're going to go like this. Even if you tried it, you're going to go,
yo, what the right. And then like everyone in the early friends are going to laugh
or you're at least going to go or you guys act like you have like balls of steel. Like you're just
like nothing ever makes me emote ever. I am like a stone, nothing. My courage precedes me
always, always customer. The reason why I'm buying these is because they're the cheapest I've seen
everywhere else. These are four or 5,000 gold. They're two. This guy's, this guy's very reasonable.
Next time I just say, I like this guy. I actually want to meet up with this guy again. I want to,
I want to be friends with this person. I don't want to just show up right here. That's,
that's a good price. That's a good price. I respect that guy. All right. Looking for the last,
I think there's only one more dollars gold. Yeah, but it's a spendable currency. I'm going to call
it like money, right? I'm going to call it money because it's just, it's money, whatever. It's
money that you can use to up to spend on yourself. Okay. It turns out I was right because are they
all lit? No, two more need to be lit. Got to find those last two straight up the middle.
Maybe it is for a little bit further out. Oh God. I'm not going in there yet. Not yet.
Turtles. There are two more. Oh, oh, I sensed it. It probably, you shouldn't even be shooting at me
by now. How do you still have sight? How does this person still have sight on me? They're across the
rest. They're across the whole game. You're literally, you're across the entire map. You're
across the entire zone. Stop running in a straight line. I'm running a straight line because I feel
like I'm far enough away where the guy can't shoot me with the born arrow, buddy. Wait, why is that
one of these here? Buddy. He's fuming. No, I'm fine. I'm just kidding. I think it actually is further
down. Like it's probably down here. Oh, there's two more. Let's continue. Thank you.
They glitched out. Are they stuck? Maybe stuck. That move actually is pretty good because with
more dexterity, that's going to be even faster. So I actually don't hate that move. What are they
doing? I wonder why they're doing that. Okay. Well, I got to get that. They're stomping. But why?
There's probably a reason why they're doing that. I don't want to get too overzealous and run off
the edge. Ash Fores square off. Another teleporter. Let's mark it. Those are the teleporters marked on
the map. They're not. They are not marked on the map. Okay. What's this place called? The river.
What's this place called? I got to clean this up. Uh, this guy, we already did this. I already did
this. Wrong guy. Still hates me. All right. What about C? What's the CEO? Sofra? What's this place
called? What's the place? Sofra village. Okay. Sofra has two teleporters. Okay. I'm not going
to go in them now because I'm busy. I am what you would call very busy because I only have two more
of these and then it's definitely a boss we fight. So sorry, we're not going in there and I have to
pee too. So I'm doing that before the fight as well. These guys are like, Oh, there's rats.
Why are they just hanging out with them? Stop panic dodging before I scream. All right. Here's
the, there's one more after this. I want to check this out over here though. There's a place I can
go up here. Is that it? There it is. That's the last one. I think we keep going this way though,
just for now, because there's a little ending over here. This is a little like observatory
or something. I don't know if they're going to shoot fucking arrow at me. So that's why I'm
freaking out. What the hell are those? Why are the, why were the sheeps rolling? Were they rolling
around? That was weird. Why would they go, why are they doing that? Sheep do that? It's got an item.
Golden rune and a rune arc on a rat. Holy shit. Was it worth killing then? What's up there?
Okay. We're, we're at this ending here. The fire. This is another boss right here.
It's all underground. Yeah, that's ridiculous. Okay. Well, there's definitely something right
here. Why would there not be, right? That's has to be a boss. Yeah. I can see like the lantern
whatever it is. All right. Let's go up there. We need to look down. Now we're doing look down spam.
Pretty. Really pretty. Two triangles. What's, what's the big deal? We're camp abandoned. Okay.
What is up? Yes. Let's check it out. Here we go. Clarifying horn charm. I have a third slot.
Raises focus. Wait. Oh, should I get the focus? What does that, what does that mean?
Where's this focus? Is that mana? Oh, what is focus in this game? Resistance to sleep
and bouts of madness. I already have a lot of that from intelligence, right?
That's kind of cool. All right. So what is it? What do you got? Who is it?
Can't go down here unless I spend the stone keys. Okay. I don't think I want to do that.
I don't think I want to do that. I will mark this though, because this is actually, I know
where that is. I'll just, I'll make a note of it though. It's not worth it. Well, I will see.
I'm not going to put it in because I have a few places I'd like to check out first. All right.
So there's that. That's cool. Let's actually go because that, yeah, because now I got to,
I got to light the last one. That last fire was back this way. All right. Is he aiming at
me? I think still actually turns out this thing is really good for stuff like this.
Cool. I got my flask filled up too. Thanks. All right. Final thing. Light it up. Here we go.
I want that. Whatever it is. I don't think I can get there yet. That's six. Our gather somewhere
in horned remains. Okay. How far away is that one? Like here, right? Like this thing here.
Uh, this one. After break. Yeah. I gotta go pee. I'm going to go pee. I'm going to refill my drink
and we will, I'll sit right here. We will be back and we will continue and we're going to fight
whatever that thing is up there. I'll be right back. Hey, hey, are you lean? Um,
maybe everywhere, but like the bottom of my stomach, it's kind of, I have like a big like
stomach now. See, I think it just kind of happens after you turn like 35. I think it just does.
I have like this, the dad's stomach. Okay. I am ready. Turn. Elden ring. Let's go. Oh,
here's the question. Do I have enough? I probably do. All right. Here's what we're doing. Boom.
That felt good. Boom. And boom. Anybody else's screen frozen? Shouldn't be. Now I only need
a few more things. I think your stream crash. No, I'm look, I'm here. Where's the Burger King
head from? Burger King head is from the academy. It's like, I don't know. I mean, I don't know if
you find it here every time, but it was on like a crab or something. All right. How much is it to
level up? I just gotta go kill one thing and I'm going to put it into, I'm going to put it into,
I want to get to vigor to 20. I'm falling behind on health here. I need to, I need to start putting
HP in. Let me just do that. Eight. That's it. Did you kill something? Just spawn those guys.
They spawn everywhere when I don't want them. And now I don't know where they are. Backstab.
I need, I was going to get to 14,000 or whatever. These potions are so bad. I need to find,
I'm surprised I haven't found any more of those tiers. I only have a plus one flask.
I need to drink two potions to heal bar, which is not, that's not good.
I need to find more of those damn things. The island to the south.
I might have to do that sooner rather than later because I'm going to fall behind hard here.
I'm just, I just want to get souls quickly and I'm just, I'm counteracting the whole point here.
There we go. Okay. Uh, one more should do it. In fact, I probably, I, these little like weird
weasel things. I'm sorry. I'm, I can't do it. It looked at me. It looked at me. You've waited.
I'm surprised at level three that doesn't down. Okay. That's enough.
But I get into health and let's go to that, uh, weird animal statue. Let's move. This one's
probably better classes. This, uh, I started with prisoner. She got down to say hello.
Yeah, this is better. Rest of this one. Uh, I'm going to put on the boys
as just to see how they are here. And I'm also going to probably put,
yeah, I can't imagine that I'm going to be sitting there casting very many spells.
So let's go. Here we go. All the beacons have been lit. Take a sip of my, uh,
you can drink whatever you want. I got matcha tea here. Let me go and take a sip.
Some good matcha. All right, here we go. Let's do it. I can be on the horse.
Should I be on the horse? It's not, I can do it. I do hutch. Oh, I can touch it.
Oh, I thought he was going to stand up. Okay. So we touched the remains and then
inside of his dream or something. Ancestor spirit double jump one, two, and then land.
It's a fire. No, it's okay. It's all right. So he goes down for a second.
Oh, I just got horse kicked. Two, three, four. Oh shit. Great. That's two.
Watch out. That's right on top of him. Two. No, that's just the head.
Oh, this is so pretty. Okay. That's a, that goes three, right? Oh, didn't do three.
No, I wonder if this is phase two. This feels very phase two. Stamina lying around. I like the way
that looks, the lighting. That was really cool. Ancestral follower ashes. That wasn't too bad.
That was, that was, that was like a relaxing fight. Ancestral follower ashes. Cool. And 10,000,
12,000. Cool. Lost to Jerma. Yeah, that one was good. Is there anything else I can do here?
That's, that's someone is sick too. Really?
All right. Anything else here is that, but I don't want to miss anything. Will I miss something?
Okay. So just save me like the 10 straight minutes it's going to take me to walk around
in a circle. Do you guys even know? I don't think anyone would even know the area. Would
anybody even know? That was really pretty. That was a nice like kind of change from the,
like smash my controller into a hundred pieces. It was just like nice. It was just very enjoyable.
Okay. Antlers too, like the magical dust. That was, I liked that one. Okay. So now what? I think I
can, it was one area that I couldn't, it was at the gate, right? Over here. Let me try going up
the gate. Should be going this way right here. And then through this way. Cause I can go over here.
You do the teleports. Let me check this out. I'm just going to run. I'm going to run from here.
Why was everybody telling me to look up here and look down and look up? Was it just bullshit?
I was literally just here. Um, I got to level up again because I don't want to die.
Nothing's so annoying. Bastard. Uh, what is it? 15, 16,000 to level up again.
Spend those souls on gummy bears. All right. I want to go this way. It's definitely going
to be another fire. I think I have to be up, right? Cause I'm all the way down.
I gotta be way, I'm the wrong place. I gotta go over here. I gotta go back like that way. Back
when I was on all those things. Go over to the right. Maybe I should just go back here
and run from here through, through there. I need to get to this area. It just doesn't matter. Like
right in the middle. Oh, you need a teleporter. You just, you can't just walk. Oh, I can't,
I can't just get up there. Teleportable. Oh yeah. I just can't do it. All right. Well, I'll go,
let's go to the teleporter. One of the teleporters that was here. It was one right here.
The elevator. I don't want to use them right now. There are no, I only have a certain amount.
I don't want to use them. Okay. Let's go on the teleporter. Where was it? It was like right here,
right? What was it? It was like over here. It's edge. You really should restart the game.
I wonder, you know, it's going to be really interesting eventually.
What all the speed runners do. Imagine this game speed ran. How, where do you go? Really?
This is where you took me. Is it just to go between those two? What's the point of that?
There's no point in doing that. The speed run is a boss there. Okay. Let me check that out right
there. And I get to that from here. And if not, then I'm just going to go back and we'll continue
to trek through. Don't you just love, I've been playing for almost three hours and this whole
three hours has been me stumbling upon a random ass place and fighting a boss that was at the end
of it. And it was really fun and cool. And the area is crazy. I haven't done, this was just,
oh, what's this gazebo? And then I walked in it and here we are three hours later.
Oh yeah. That's remarkable. All right. Well, I can act, I can still explore up here and I get
even further up. Is there a reason to go on that? Probably not. I love getting flasks,
but I would really like a seed to make it so I don't have a plus one flask. All right. Hold on,
settle down. Going this way. Hey, over here. You want a hint for that? Or do you want to find it
on your own? Um, I would say if it begins to start to become like a real problem where I actually
don't come across them at all over the next like couple hours, maybe because I cannot have one
flask. That's going to be horrible. That's what I mean. Still haven't used any of those. I believe
we have exhausted everything we can do in this area. For now. For now. How do I get out of here?
Do the elevator? Don't leave. Don't leave. There's a third one. Find it. Um,
can you note down the two teleporters? Yeah, I went in both of them. One of them, they just travel
between each other. They just go one to the other. I'm probably going to delete that now in my notes.
I'll come back. I've done what I've done, what I've been able to see that I can really do.
The only exception is going back here and just taking one quick look around,
like here. Oh, not here. The next one. This one here. Because there's back here.
Wait, no. Where? No, that was correct. That was correct. Yeah, that was correct. Yeah, that was
correct. This is going to kill me. So back here is this thing, right? This is the kind of in-between
area where I came from. Can I go and check really quick? Because that's the elevator.
Elevator there. What does your stream title mean? Um, I don't know. No, okay. I'll go back up.
You get your item scaling. Like I have an A scaling with matcha powder. It's just like,
it's doing so much for me and it's making my game. It's making me feel like so much better.
I think my gameplay so much better. I'm going back down. Whatever. Just get off. Get off. Get
off. I don't want to. Okay. I'm an idiot. Yeah, this just takes you back to where I was the first
time. Yeah. Uh, I'm out. It was cool. I, if I need to come back, I will. So we're going to get out
and I'm going to go back to where I was here because I don't want to, I wanted to go this way
and that's when I got, this is that area there. Okay. I want to check what this is. Let's go here.
End of the stream. What? The stream is not turning off for at least at the very least,
like five or six hours. So you've got that wrong. Oh no, no, no, no, no. And I'm going to tell you,
I am going to take a break somewhere later tonight. Like probably in like a few hours,
a couple of hours, maybe I'm going to eat. Uh, so I'm going to eat something,
wherever that is, figure that out. Maybe I eat. And after that, where am I going? This way.
So I will be able to eat something. It won't be a 30 minute break. No, this way. That will give me
the energy to be able to stream for like probably another few hours. So I'll be good to go. God
dammit. I keep going on. Wait, there's one of those things. Uh, what? That's not that, that's
literally like not that far. Why are you talking about? There was no far at all.
I've survived other falls that were far more than that. I'm terrified to do that now. What? Um,
I'm terrified to do this. That kills me. Look at how short that is. It's a bug. Uh, no, no,
it's not. I'm sorry. I'm going down here. I'm terrified to do this. I swear to God, don't fall.
Hold on. Wait, what if I pick up the souls? Oh, they're not. Okay. We're good. All right.
How did I get over there last time? Like I'm just trying to go this way.
You're going to cross the river. That just teleported you. Oh, that's okay. Right.
Does this kill me? It does. I swear I jumped down here before. I swear to God. How did I get in
there before? I was down there before. Remember? I was like, oh, if you're looking for that blood
weapon, it's down here. Well, okay. We're going to find another way across the bridge. Jump later.
I don't think the double jump stops fatal fall damage. Weird guy in a Burger King costume comes
over and wrecks your campsite and kills you. I get his weapon. Hayden sell swords. Cool. What was
that? Strength and dex or it's a great sword. That's pretty cool. What's that? What's the weapon
art? Like a cool spin. Oh, very nice. Look at how powerful I am being back in Limgrave.
You have nothing on me. Is that another armored car? Unless that's the armored car that came all
the way down foot road. No, that's another armored car. Let's go waste the tree Sentinel. I beat
him a long time ago. That was the first boss I killed. Did I already get this or is this another
just armored car? Well, let's go. How do I get them to stop? Stop. Stop the vehicle. Stop the
vehicle. Stop the vehicle. Oh, shit. Here they come. Great acts. Bye. Look at this. Oh my God.
How many people? How about you? I'm so much stronger than them now. Shut up. You fucking idiot.
What was that guy doing? I can't. Why can't I? I don't have any mana. All right. Cool. I got a great
axe. I'm so powerful for this area now though. All right. I want to go right here because like,
what is this? It's kind of cool. It's over here. Waypoint ruins. Remember there are two items.
Left stick makes it so you dismount easier. I unbound my dismount because it's crouched
too and then ruins my video game experience. All right. It's probably like a mini boss down here.
Let's get it. Low stone. There's one in the front. There's an item in the front of the cart.
You're not going to tell me twice. Thanks for making me come all the way back here.
Nothing. Okay. I need a bonfire. I mean, I have enough to level up so I can be careful.
People call me Jimmy. You guys are full of weird baits today. Okay. Jimmy. Okay. Up there.
Fortnite. Fortnite. Jimmy. All right. I got a good view. Found it. Yeah, man. I got poisoned. I was
just trying to pick up the items and leave. There's definitely a bonfire down here. That's
just a boss. Shit. I need a bonfire over here somewhere. Oh, hi there, Jimmy. Oh, hey there,
Jimmy. Oh, hey there. Oh, hey, Jimmy. There's got to be a teleporter here. Well, I'll just mark it.
I'll level up anyways because I might die to boss. Oh, I'm turning around. There's going to be one
right here somewhere down the road. Just wait. There has to be one sitting on the side like
usually, right? Come on. I'm very far away from one. There's got to be one. Not like right here.
There's a little lake right at the edge. Why am I dying? Because I am currently poisoned. It has
to be. It's definitely not. It's just so far away. Can we get a look at me, please? Look at me.
All right. I have 20, which is where I want it to be. Rebalanced. I do need more endurance and we
need two more mind and I need to get to 20. 18 endurance, 20 mind, and then the rest is going
into intelligence and dexterity for the rest of the game. I'll keep it at eight heals. That's fine.
These sacred tears. Can I get 20 likes on this? 20 likes. I'm just smoking crack. Okay, back here.
I'm going to go in those ruins and fight the boss. Ooh, pretty tree. Something definitely over here
as well. Yeah, hold on. There's a lot of random shit. Look at all these ruins. Golden rune, golden
rune. Try to get them all. Oh, very cool. Something going on up there. What's your deal? What's your
deal? Wow. Look at that tower. All right, let's go down here and do whatever is happening in this
area. Let's see what's in here. I'm her boss. Let's go. Mad pumpkin head. Oh man, I am,
I am very leveled for you. Got a thousand souls. Holy shit. Imagine if I was like level two.
Ah, you're going to sneak this back here, huh? Hello. Okay. Um, the new NPC. Oh my God, we've,
my queen, I finally found you. How long has it been? Three, four, five years. My queen.
Sorcerer. The burger queen.
I was exiled from the academy of Rhea Lucaria as a reviled apostate witch. Witch. Do you still wish
to learn from me? Witch. Well, piece of work. I could be a warlock. You are now my protege in
glintstone sorcery, but I refuse to coddle or cast kind words. Never. Anticipate grievances,
young apprentice. Did you see what level I am? A lot. Okay. Enhances left-hand shield damage
negation. I already have this. Glintstone's stars. I have glintstone arc, glintstone barrage,
or glintstone's armament. Okay. I want a compilation for the amount of times that I've gone
like over here. Just like one, two, three, four, five, six, seven, eight, nine. I feel it's been
like 30 times. Can I actually put this on my weapon? Because this is a huge fucking deal
if I can. I think so. You are a tadpole when it comes to magic. Infantile. Legs to walk.
So to become a sorcerer, first you must face your ignorance. Shall we start learning?
Yes, we shall in just a minute. Kill her. Why would I kill her when she's the only person that has
these moves? All right. The other one that I want. Crystal barrage or stars. Barrage sounds kind of
cool. Fires a volley of glintstone and crystal shards. Charging increases potency. Or fires three
magic shooting stars that pursue the target. The source can be cast while in motion and you can
charge it. Didn't the turtle sell this? I think the turtle already sells this. I don't think the
turtle has this one. He sold comets. Stars is garbage. I wonder how barrage, I wonder what that
is. I'll try barrage. I already have the other ones besides the shield. Go play with our new toys.
R1, R1, R1, R1. Goodbye. Thank you. That was cool. That was definitely worth stumbling upon.
Red glintstone, please. Okay, so here is magic weapon. So I have glintstone pebble, swift
glintstone shard, great glintstones shard, omit, which I can't use, barrage. All right, so I have
to leave this area. Okay, cool. Stars is good. Sorcery in the other From Software games is kind
of weird. It's a little it's a little odd. Some of the moves were just dog shit, just absolute
dog shit. And they scaled terribly. And it was like, why are they even in the game?
I don't know. I hope they actually are all these viable. Okay, that's kind of cool. Oh, my God,
what the fuck? This guy's dead. Sucks. Let's keep going this way. That's my destination.
But yeah, sorcery was always one of those weird things they put in all these games. Because
there's this like one move that scales and it's just unbelievable and has the right cast time
to be the best. But then they have like a dozen other of these like crystal barrage pebble stones
that they just like suck and they're just useless. PvE. Right? Because a lot of sorcery
is insane in PvP. Wrong way. Still alive. I'm going the wrong way. You're right.
Oh, Hayden armor. But yeah, sorcery. Some of those things are cool in PvP. And that's what
they're kind of maybe designed for. It does look like there's a lot more interesting spells.
At least what it looks like. At least maybe initially, I could be wrong. So we got to go
this way towards one. Hello. Oh, sapling sweet sapling of glorious gold. As your crystal teardrop
ripened. You look like an NPC from the PS2 Sopranos game. The only reason why I'm
addressing that comment is because I think I've seen that comment like 30 times in the last
four straight days. I keep seeing that comment. What do you want me to say? You want to be like,
yo, what the fuck did you say? Like, what do you want me to say? Maybe I'll run into something
else here. Don't. The Elden Ring. Yeah, the Elden Ring. The Elden Lord. Lord. Oh, nice.
I'm actually happy to find it. In the meantime, I'm going to do this.
I'm running out of mana. Let's try this. This is Crystal Barrage. It's kind of annoying. Can't do
it. Can't do it on this weapon. Oh, well. Do I have to be in combat? I don't think I do. I think
this is already a magic weapon, so they won't let me do it. Yep. Nope. It's like, sorry. Ready?
Let's see. Watch this. Sad. Sad. Because look at how it gets so blue and pretty. Sad. That's very
sad. Very, very sad. So I gotta put the other stuff back on. Greatsword is- I'm gonna keep the
Greatsword on it. It's been very useful. This has to come off in favor of Great Glenstone.
Because I want to give that a try. I haven't really played with it. That's really sad.
But this thing is really good. It's already infused. Wait, what? What happened to my- What
happened to my clothes? What happened? Korean Knight is still good. Does the armor do anything
for me? No. Aiden Armor is pretty good, too. Do any of these do anything for me? Probably not.
Red Maiden gauntlets are better. They're a lot heavier, though. They're just better.
Stupid horns off. I'm gonna have to wear this the whole game, I think.
Yeah. I'm gonna have to try that new shard. Let's go. On the horse. Going to this place over here.
Through the woods. Dude, look at the graphics on that rock. They were pretty good. All right,
new area. All right, this is like a little bear. Not as scary as the other one, but what's this?
You are quite susceptible. You're not as scary as your, uh, big brother. You're not as scary as
Mama Bear. All right, there's a huge one. Ah, Crown Slam. This is so awesome because you could
literally just come back here. You could just go this way instead of the way that I went
when you play for the first time. The new character. It doesn't matter. That's awesome
for colossal weapons. Yeah. Coming over there. Open for business. Ooh, he's open for business.
Let's check out this. See how the glint's done. It's really slow, but if it hits,
okay, it's not that big of a deal. That move is really not good at all, actually. It's not good
at all. It's actually pretty bad. All right, what is that? Because I'm about to go explore it.
Demi-humans wax Roth. Now their mother's been taken. Where are you, Lord Kenneth? The night
deviled by blood. He's in there. Let's go pay him a visit. Bring the burger queen some squirrels
to get the good stuff. I brought the scrolls to the turtle. Maybe that was a mistake. Yeah,
this thing kind of sucks. Now the sword takes the arc, takes place with the arc. Um, hole is okay.
Maybe just put starlight on just for fun. I mean, it's really pretty. I'll keep it. Whatever. I
really only use these two anyways for now, so I'll keep them on. The swift, uh, glintstone is
awesome because it just happens in one second. It's good at night too. It lights up the area.
What about the new summon? Oh, that's true. Put it on after this. Yeah, this is crazy because this
is definitely a lower, please tell me that's one of those tears. Oh, that's a golden seed.
All right, let's go be high level Andy and just fucking wipe this whole place apart.
Is he fighting? Why is he fighting them? Over level the Andy. Well, I'm, I mean, I'm coming
here for a very specific purpose. I just wanted to see what was over here. I also really needed
that. Hey, where's your leader? The only one that can give me a true challenge who runs this place
or hate. I feel like this thing's going to get up blood road for night. So this is where you watch
out for that explosion. That would actually kill me. All the things. Oh my God. Where was I?
Just stop. Yeah. You could tell how overleveled I am. I'm just seeing if they have any items in
this form. I'm just looking for like sacred tier shard things. I promise. I'm not like trying to
be like an idiot and just be like, look at, I'm just going to do the easy stuff. See, I don't even
care about that. You have to go to sacred places. Oh, this is a sacred place. You know, when swift
glint stone shard is killing things in one hit that you're going to embarrass this guy in front
of what? How many people here? 50,000 an asshole. That's actually not a joke. Imagine fighting this
guy at like level three, bloody slash and Godric night gauntlets. I'm going to say glasses. You can
probably get a sword. That sword is probably awesome. You see how cool that looks. Godric
night's glasses and just wearing them and just have disappeared glasses on. That would be so
funny. Oh my God. I LOLing so hard. There are two more Burger King masks. Maybe I'll find them
eventually. I'm looking for a very, okay. So here we go. This is like the end of the little dungeon.
Dectis medallion left. They're going to pull some resident evil shit here.
Join medallions to operate grand lift of Dectis. The right half is said to reside in Fort Faroth
in the dragon barrow far to the east. Like over here, dragon barrow far to the east is okay.
Okay, looks good. But I'm actually kind of glad I got that. Cool. So now I wonder, is it time to
start to progress through here? I mean, it's pointing me here, right? Like this is, I think
I can handle this impassable gray bridge. It wants me to go this way or it wants me to go up here,
like in this area. Or it wants me to go, is that dragon, you know what, let's go kill that dragon.
Yeah, let's go get that motherfucker right now. You should break a Sega Dreamcast over your head.
Okay, great idea. There's a ton of content in the academy that you missed. Yeah, I'm, but I mean,
I'm just kind of browsing around. I got eight flasks. I have a lot, I have more health now
and I'm going to put on the magic defense shit. I can have most of it on already. Magic defense.
Carrying gloves, cloth trousers, weirdly enough. Okay, this has got good magic defense. All right,
what about this thing? Magic brass shield, but I can't wear it this one here. Okay, I'm ready to
fight the dragon marked at number one. Where'd you find the medallion? Please, I need it.
That medallion, that east, that left part of the medallion is in Fort Haight, which is down here
all the way on like this little tail end here. Actually, literally right next to,
right, barely to the east of the lake, Fort Haight.
Sorry, I didn't, I didn't do this. Game fucking A's me. All right, let's do it. It's time. I
actually need to go upgrade this weapon too. I think I got a somber stone. Let's see. This is
a fight of just patience and just attacking only when you need to. Hope I don't get one shot by
something, but you know, I'm prepared. Got the boys if I need to call on them, which I don't
think I will. Let's go get this guy. I can probably get a few hits on him while he's lying down,
which is exactly what I'm going to try to do. I like just, I like missed like 40% of those hits.
Don't land on me. Doing, it's three hits. One, two, three, and that's it. Getting close. One, two,
one is fine. Hey, fuck out of the way. I just hit my head on the ceiling. Cookie bug ambush. Yeah,
what was that? I don't know why my brain was just like, wait, that's an item bug, but it's not.
Those guys just hang out there. It's probably a closer, uh, bonfire here somewhere too, right?
I thought this was a 1440p gamer. I am. I just don't stream in 1440p. I stream in 864p.
Not 1080. I'm not basking. All right. Well, that was dumb, but you know, we're going to go
forward again. I can use my shield as a weapon. Okay. This time don't miss every single time.
Just stand right next to his leg and do it. I didn't jump over. All right. We got to,
I was gonna say, we got to get away with this gigantic stone slab that's in the fucking way.
Hey, I got to just run away. Just after I aggro the guy, just run the fuck away.
Just get them away from all the debris and fucking rocks formation. Shit. That's a scattered run.
That's just bring them out. So we don't end up going like this.
Find a closer bonfire. Actually, that's not a bad idea. He's really strong against magic. Yeah.
He's an anti me. What the I should be killing him so much more swiftly. Okay. I'm not, let me
just see what, is there a little fire over here or something? Let's not go for him yet.
There's maybe there is like a fire. What's this? I'm going in here. What's this? Academy crystal
cave. Academy crystal cave is what it just said. And look at how much closer this is.
Okay. Summoning stone thing. I'm glad I have the starlight. It seems to be pretty helpful here.
Abe Moss, crystal cave moss. Oh, I don't like that. Give it back.
What the fuck? Why? How? I'm not sneaky. I'm a gigantic beacon of light.
There's so many people here. I'm a blip on their mini map right now. This is, oh God. Okay.
Shit. They all aggroed. Nope. Not all of them.
I look like one of you, but I'm not in the darkness. We all look alike. Don't we with our
masks? They couldn't tell the difference. The imposter. Okay. So there's something over here.
Look who glint's done. What else we got? There's definitely more. Very interested in what's at the
end of this thesis. That doesn't have to be in the head. Fireflies. Dude, I came in here with the
required item. Imagine coming down here without sorcery and without starlight. That'd be a living
hell. You just get a lantern or a torch. Don't diminish my cool character. That replaces one
of them, right? Okay. So that's that. There's that way. Can I do anything up here? Oh, skeletons.
Game is really, really loading something heavily. So I want to do a magician fight. That's fine.
Oh, maybe I'll get that one. I might get that move. Double motherfuckers. I'm out of here.
What did you bring the manna? Oh my God. He's got a magic hammer. Oh, please give me the magic
hammer. He's got this huge hammer. That's so cool. All right. Let's check and see what he was
guarding. There's a boss in there too. Oh man. It's gonna be rough. Excuse me. Where are you?
Pre-fire me. There's two chests here. Boost crystal sorcery, which I don't like. Is the sword
technically crystal? I think the sword is a crystal sorcery. Or is it glintstone? 48 intelligence to
put it on. I only have glintstones right now. Crystal ballot barrage. But the great sword thing
that I swing. Eat cereal or soup tonight? I'll probably tell you soup because soup sounds a
little more like healthy and like more nutrient based than like Captain Crunch. So I would say
that you probably have soup tonight. Okay, there's enough chests in here too. And a runic. Well,
unless there's a bonfire here, I'm gonna have to just go in here and see if I can do it.
This is about 5,000 souls though. Maybe I should just run through it. What do you think? Buy to
5,000 souls. Yeah. No, it's not worth it. Unless do I have? Hmm. I don't know. Only 5k. I can always
go get it again. All right, let's go. I'm gonna go for it. 5k is not that much right now. It's two
people. Oh, it's these two. I remember these guys. 13 fucking damage. That's it. Oh, I'm doing this
wrong. I need to hit them with something else. I wonder how I'm supposed to hurt them. Oh my god,
this guy's so annoying. Fucking R1 spamming piece of shit. Do I like end up breaking their crystals
stuff? I don't know what the fuck he's doing. Oh my god, his fucking friend is so annoying.
No, this is wrong, dude. I gotta like, I gotta attack him with something else.
I would call the boys and I don't, I can't. Do I have any? What else can I hit them with?
They made it a crystals. Maybe I should use like fire or something. Yeah, I remember these guys.
All right, we're gonna break. I got it. I got it. We're gonna get those souls back. I think you just
have to, you probably have to hit them enough times to shatter them, right? That makes sense.
Oh man, this is far. Okay. Well, just gonna run. I got the boys on standby. Fucking idiot.
Strike damage. I have slash pierce, standard pierce, pierce, pierce slash strike. I mean,
the flail is a piece of crap, but it's strike. Maybe that'll break it. I mean, this thing sucks,
but whatever. I'm not looking to do anything fancy. Will this, will like a, will it break
their armor? Maybe it will. I'll try it. I don't think I have a blunt weapon that, um,
I don't have a blunt weapon. I got rid of all of them. I have a strategy. Strategy is just kite
the guy, the guy that's like, just R1 spamming and file. I don't know what the fuck I am right
now. So we're going to have to figure that out real quick. Okay. So let's go this way.
Is that big guy? This huge guy's here. Run around. All right, let's go boys. All right.
Drag him across the whole thing because he's really slow. Okay. Now I'm stuck on a fucking
rock. I was stuck in the rock. There we go. All right. Let's job boys. They're dead. Same
strategy. Pull them all the way back. Oh, what? What's that? Oh, I think I can't even get rid of
it. Come on, hurry up. I might, I'm just kill this guy first. Just line aside him by the,
with a statue. I'm trying to time to dodge on you. Oh my goodness gracious. Get him please.
R1. You fucking annoying little shit. Get down. Oh my God. All right. It's going to work. It's
going to work. Oh, this run back is such a pain in the absolute fucking Dick. I swear to God.
That strategy worked. I have to just get in there and just wail and chant the flail.
Does it work on weapons like this? I thought it only worked on like
swords. Does it, it actually works on flail? Okay. All right. Let's sit on. Oh, where is it?
Someone's an ancestral follower. I can't summon Oleg. Do I have enough to summon him? How much
FP do I have? Okay. Yeah. Let's try this guy. All right. Let's do it. I didn't even want to press
that button twice. I just like, there's just so many buttons. Get up. He hates the boys.
You can try parrying too. That guy is really predictable. I'm always afraid to parry boss
because I feel like half the time it just doesn't do anything. But those aren't,
those are not even bosses. It's just like those crystal people that were outside.
Like I went the wrong fucking way, but it doesn't like, like running through the shit sucks.
Asshole. 5k gone, but it'll fucking just really matter. It's to the right, not to the left. How's
the pain? Uh, well the game is annoying sometimes, right? That's just the way it is. Okay.
The help of the game didn't hang for three seconds when I turned the fucking corner.
I don't have enough man to summon my friend. It's a wash. What the fuck is that move? I can't
parry with the shield. Oh, it's cause I, the weapon art with the flail. Okay. So I can't do
both because otherwise I can't summon the guy. I was trying to parry, but I have,
I have the magic defense shield on. Okay. So I can't do both. I have to, unless I want to
bring mana potions, which I'll bring one mana potion. I want to try to parry this guy. Okay.
So let's go for this fucking horse shit. The red shirts fueling his anger. This run back is awful
though, because all it takes is just one little, like dinky little bullet to hit you in the back.
And that's it. And you're going to just say exactly what I'm saying. I'm just saying,
motherfuckers. Hold on a second. The game has to like load the shaders for 15 straight seconds.
Okay. Now we can play. Let's go. Oh, he's got a bow. He's just one damage. What? He sucks.
He did one damage. Oh my God. Why did you tell me to bring this guy? Why did you tell me to bring
him? One damage. All right. It's time to parry this fuck face. You can't parry. You can, you can,
you can, you can, you can, you can, you can, you can, you can. Okay. Just keep doing that.
Keep doing it. We're good. We're good. Not good. Fucking piece of shit with your spam.
Needs to be leveled up for something, man, because that's bad.
No, you are not hitting me with all of those. What the fuck? I just want to grab these guys by
their fucking heads. It's like three stooges. I just shatter both their brains and their heads.
Like, why can't I just grab them by their heads and just three stooges crush their heads?
Oh shit, Atriarch, what's up? Welcome, raiders. Currently dealing with a, dealing with a little
bit of a problem here. Thanks for the raid, Atriarch. I've got these two crystal idiots
down here and I'm having some trouble. Chat told me to summon this guy with the horns.
The guy did literally one damage. I wish I was making that up. I summoned him, took a whole
mana bar. He did one damage, one damage point. And then they ate him alive. So we're going to change
it up. We're going to go back to the boys. No, we're not. I'll tell you what we're doing.
Bringing in the dogs. The dogs are vicious. Go. I saw you've been playing it too and hopefully
you're doing okay. You caught me right in the middle of a, I'm a little upset. Try to calm down.
I'm going to try to get this to work. So let's, let's go ahead and get started.
Okay. Everything's fine. I have to level these people up. Like I can't just have them at level
one. Although, uh, all right, I'm going to get it this time because I'm going to just,
here we go. Everything is not cool. Everything is going to be just fine. I promise.
Everything's going to be just fine. And I can tell you right now,
there's no reason everybody's freaked out. You, no, you hesitated. Can't bring it back out.
Why is he doing a different move? You've been doing the same move the whole time.
He decides to change instead of going, he goes like, what was this new move set? Try guard
parrying? No, guard parry is not going to be a good idea. Cause guard parry, the caster guy
throws his fucking goddamn fruity pebbles at me from across the room. And I'm vulnerable.
If I do a guard parry, I have to go. Okay. I'm going to kill these guys. These guys are
not even that big of a deal. They're really not. It's going to come down to parry. Get them run.
Run, parry, get them, run, airy, run, get them. And don't get hit by like the 30 people in here
that cast the same fucking spell at you like that. He's still shooting it. He's shooting it at me.
He's still shooting it. I don't know which, which direction he's shooting it, but he's doing it.
It's going to have to be, it's going to have to be, I got to bring the boys out either that,
or we're going to try the other. Cause the boys are just annoying. They just get all over the place.
I'm going to upgrade the boys. The boys are annoying, right? They're annoying.
They just walk around and bump into walls and shit.
Aurene, get it off before this idiot does anything. You fuck. All right. Get away, get away,
get away, get away, get away, get away, get away, get away. Wait till he does the
line of sight with the statues. That's the plan right now. Check this out. Strategy. Excuse me.
I tried to lock on, but I couldn't. It's broken. Okay. All right. Just have to run. Fuck that rock.
Wow. Jeez. Ow, ow, ow. Slow down. Don't let him do anything else. Oh yeah.
Crystal release. Nice. I'm telling you the strategy, the strategy was you got a line of sight
with the first guy. I lost 5,000 souls and I'm not happy about it. I'm very upset about it.
What is this? Oh, nice. Holy shit. I was on camera. You got to see what it looked like.
That's just... Where does this go? Crystal release.
Where it's a massive crystal then shadows it to scour a wide area with a violent rain.
So is that the thing where it was just around me? Just... I want to try it.
Uh, it's an exit dungeon, but hold on. Where does this go? Shinema shield.
That's actually pretty funny. That was a good call though to take that off.
Academy of... Wait, what? What the fuck? I'm back at the academy. Hold the lever.
This is a different area of the academy. Uh, I can't. Soggy or crunchy cereal, bro? Please.
Why would you ever eat cereal, soggy? You guys are eating cereal wrong by the way. Let me tell
you how to fix it. So you only eat, only eat for a little bit of cereal in and a little bit of milk.
You eat that first. Don't like dump, people dump like three or four cups of fucking cereal,
just mass cereal in their bowl. And then they just, you just dump milk in there and then it
becomes a mess. Sometimes you don't even eat all of it. You do like half a cup of cereal and then
like a little bit, like a quarter cup of milk, half a cup of milk. Eat that. It's going to be
crunchy and perfect. Then just do a little bit more. Pour a little bit more in the bowl,
a little bit more milk. I don't know how people keep getting this wrong.
What is, this is just like a secret chest. Terra Magicus. Terra Magicus. Raises the magic
strength of those within the sigil. What? I don't get it. This is just like a buff. Okay,
this is a glintstone. Draws an academy sigil upon the ground, raising the magic strength of those
within it. So I put a sigil on the ground and then I can just bam. It's an, it's a buff. Okay,
that's pretty cool. Hell yeah. Nice. Nice. All right. Awesome. You yell a little less. Uh,
I don't think that's going to happen. I'm sorry, man. Talk to the sorcerer about the gate key with
the new opening. Uh, I do have to go talk to that guy, but I can't give it to him. Maybe he'll tell
me where another one is. Fast travel from here. Uh, yeah. Let, let me go talk to him. So he says,
this, this is right. Yeah, it's right here. Where is it? Yeah. Church, the church of
fear. It's right there. All right. Oh, all right. These are great runs. I gotta go. I don't,
I don't, I don't, I don't know what those are. Is this the right place? No, it's this church,
right? You got them from the boss. Yeah, that's right. Are you going to start vaping? Uh, I,
I'm not going to start vaping. I'm the person up on the second. I can't give it to him. What if I,
am I going to screw everything up here if I give this to him? He said I can't give it to anybody.
I don't know what happens if I do it. I'm kind of scared.
So you found yourself a blintstone key, but I certainly can't take it from you.
That key belongs to you. By rights, you should use it for yourself. It's true.
I wish to return to my place of study, but that's no excuse to impose upon others.
Is this why Bluntstones always finish last? Okay. So where's another one? Head to the academy of
real. Carry on with your journey. Don't bother holding yourself up for my sake.
Dude, is there another one in the, in the second? There's a second key in the academy.
I just go get it. Academy grand library and Academy gate. I mean, there's, I don't know
where to start. Would it be somewhere in here? Eight parlors, schoolhouse. It looks like the
only place I really haven't been is here. So I'm going to go to like the church and go backwards
this way. I was going to put a marker here and just whatever. Uh, why do you hate crack?
People keep saying you need to use your great runs. I have to go to the place where I can use
them. It's like the tower, right? There's a tower that I haven't gone to yet. That I don't know.
Like, is it over here? I take it to a tower. I'm imagining this is the tower. If I were to take a
guess, I will go do that afterwards. All right. So now the play is to try to go this way. I think
I think, see if I can, can I get in there from here? I don't know if I can get over here from
there. Hmm. There's another section in this academy. Maybe from here. Okay. Let's try this.
I head over here. This is where those, um, water wheel is.
Which I need to be this way. So it looks like there's a path here somewhere. Hold on.
Out this again. No, I'm not doing the water wheel. I got to find a way over this way.
I'm here. I'm just going to run. It's like, I've already done this like five times.
I know. I'll clear this because this pot, the big pots there is this area. This is where I fought
the boss. Is there another way to keep going from the boss's chamber? But I didn't see.
If there was that way. Remember, what if you were like my dentist? Okay. So I remember this.
Was there another way to go that way? Spam age isn't fun. Maybe annoying. Yeah. Okay. Wait,
wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait,
over there. Like that way. I've been there. I don't think I've been there yet.
All right. You've kind of making this a real pain in the ass for me right now.
Can't just cheese you. Oh my God. Fuck all of you. Okay. Oh, that's right. That's right. That's
right. That's right. That's right. I didn't go. I remember I looked over here and I was like,
oh yeah, yeah, I didn't do it. Okay. Here we go. That's right. I did look over here and I said,
well, maybe later. The thing with from software games is maybe later means never again. I will
never look at this part of the game ever again. So you're right. Let's go. Ouch. Oh, it's him.
I got bad sorceries on for this. It's going to go weapons. We're just going to go with the two
handed. All right. That's that way. Cool. The POG, the POG champ, IRL pony ride stream waiting room.
It would be the most, that would be one of the most boring streams you probably would ever see
here. Just riding a pony. I imagine with a GoPro here, just looking down, just never so often just
hear like, then like the big horse sneezes, like somebody under that and check. Oh, they're
acts. Yeah, I see. Okay. Good try. Good try. I can't really cast any spells. So we're going
to have to do this. I didn't think you were going to attack. Nice try. Pull them each.
What the fuck is that move? I want it. Oh shit. This is bad. That's not what I wanted to have
happen at all. It's coming. Damn it. And cage. Oh, everything is fine. I went, I just got so slumped
down. I was like, this sucks. We're good though. And yeah, progress. Let's go. I wonder if I ring
that bell. All these rooftops. It might be another boss up here too. That'd be cool. Meteor bolt.
Oh, cool. That's cool. That's cool. What is that? Cool. It's like we're jumping. Are you mocking
yourself? Um, I don't know. I hope this doesn't hurt. Right to my marker. Perfect. Exactly where
I wanted to go. There's no way I make that jump. It's being thorough. I could go here. That guy is
scary looking. I wish I had a sorcerer to kill him with, but I don't. And he's gonna, Oh God,
this is bad. All right. Oh, it's just an archer. All right. Nevermind.
That over there. Um, I'm gonna get that. I'm gonna have to go all the way back around and back up,
but that's an item that I want. Imbued sword key. That's different. What is an imbued sword key?
I'll check it. What the fuck? Oh shit. Uh, there's a lot of places I can go. I
I'm gonna go back over here. Did you take a break? Uh, yeah, I did already. I'm gonna take a food
break here. Maybe later. You check around every single building because they put stuff everywhere.
You never know when you're going to find a something that you, uh, need. All right. Do I
go down the ladder or do I just jump over the rooftops? I'm marking it. Oh fuck. I wonder if
there's another boss. That bait was so annoying and I'm in trouble now. I can go down here,
which leads to, I've already been here, but have I been? No, I don't know. Have I been at that level
of the roof? I'm not going to go down yet because there's an area to go this way too.
What the fuck was that? I have no health. This is bad. Oh, I remember looking up here,
seeing that. Is that a lie? It might be. That was such an ugly face. I hate that one.
That was like, I, I did not like that one. I got a key after all that. I still kind of want to.
There's the main is the, where was it? Where was it? Where was it? I keep forgetting here.
Where's the court? How was the courtroom? Cause I want to go back up there.
It's a classroom and you run through and then the courtroom courthouse is like here,
courtyard. Hey, I've been up here. I haven't even been up here.
Luzuli glint stone sword. That's different. Oh shit. I gotta be careful. Get the item.
Shattering crystal. Yeah. Right. What was the last one? One, two, three, four.
I kicked the ladder down. Oh my goodness gracious. You gotta be fucking kidding me.
Hell yeah. This is definitely leads to something.
Fuck. And that's how unfair was that? He can't, I, he wasn't, we won't back up.
I try to hit him, a bump into him, slash him and he just, what? All right. Where is the,
where the fuck is that? I just knocked a ladder down. Where's that ladder? I don't,
I don't know where I am. The room where you just came from, but where first grace.
Uh, where was that? This one here, bait parlor.
I'll get your spells. Oh, you're right. Okay. Let me change my spells. That cannot stay on.
I'm going to go back to swift glint stone. We're going to change this to,
and that need more intelligence. Let's do the, the pole pole is pretty good.
All right. So I can see where I died on the map. Oh fuck. That's in the church.
I died like over here. You please read. I'm your biological son. I just found your channel.
That'd be, that'd be weird. I don't think so. I'm your biological son. I just found your channel.
That's so stupid. Yeah. Air, air to the German empire. Okay. So now that I did that, let's
browse around. You just have, you just don't give a shit at all. Do you?
You still got it off. I don't think so. Ooh, I think I already have one of those
germ of his empire. Does this do anything for me? Not really. This one just has more armor.
This one's better. Are you looking for the whopper secret formula?
That was actually a pretty good one. All right. So that what's in you.
When sage glintstone crown, what greatly increases intelligence to the detriment of HP and stamina.
Oh, I don't want to wear this. This looks awful. It's a double whopper.
28, 29, 30, 30 is three intelligence really worth losing like almost a hundred in
HP? I don't know. I don't think so. I really don't. I really don't think so. I got the new
sword. Oh yeah, that's right. Not as good. Not as good as this scales E with the decks
deals magic damage. Apparently once you use the staff sorcery, it's got glintstone pebble,
but I already have that. I already, I already own it. Fuck stats, make a cute outfit,
make a cute outfit. How many big bosses have you beat? I've done. Okay.
Uh, how many, actually I, this is a good time to think about this for a second.
How many bosses have I beaten the game so far? How many like eight, nine and two main? I know
there's definitely been three or four main. I mean, you need to see this. Uh, I, I see it right now
and I have, I do and I don't want to show that on stream. It's fucking, I hate it. It's, it's scary.
This is scary. It looks like my jaw is like unhinged and shit. I don't know. I'm not showing
that. I'm the streamer. I get to the site. No, it's fucking horrifying. I hate every,
because you took my real teeth. Are those my real teeth that you just like photoshopped in?
All right. Maybe that is worth showing on stream because I'm actually really curious.
Oh, I, this is awful. It looks like a horror game or something. I fucking hate this. This
is looks scary. It looks like a horror game. Why can't I show? Where is it? I just saved it.
It's possessed. All right. Well, that's weird. How come I can't show this?
Oh, I got an, I have an idea. My computer is fucking weird, man. I swear to God.
Where is it? I just saved it. This doesn't make any sense. It's like there's no images that I have.
Apparently zero images are on my desktop. What the fuck are you talking about?
Oh, so my real teeth, I think. Are they? Did you take? No, you didn't. Did you? What did you get
these teeth? Are they different? They are. I have a little thing here. They are different.
I hate that. You found somebody. Wait, are these my teeth from like seven or eight years ago?
It's an AI app. Oh, I thought you took a photo. That would be pretty funny.
And I don't want to give you content ideas, but like if you had taken like my teeth from
like a decade ago, like right from like a face cam video from like 10 years ago or something
and like photoshopped my teeth on it. Look at how fucking I hate it. It's just unsettling and
makes me feel like shit looking at it. Have your teeth changed? Yeah, I think a little bit. I got
like a little space here now that I didn't have like seven or eight years ago. My teeth have moved
a little bit. Okay, so let me get back to this. I don't think it's worth using, but I'll try it
for a little while. That's pretty cool. All right, so now what? Okay, go back up to the roof.
I wonder if there's another boss here. It might be. Wait, no. But yeah, so I've beaten like three
main or four main story bosses. Christ. And what, like five or six just non-story optional bosses?
You guys don't get up, right? That guy's a crossbow. That was just instant. I thought he
was going to shoot one. He might drop that. No, please no. 7000 souls. They're gone. Whatever.
They're gone. Whatever. I didn't want them anyways. Just dead weight. Who hit that guy?
What the fuck? You gonna cry, bud? What do I think of Elden Ring so far? It's very good.
About these guys exist. He just. How is he still alive? What the fuck are you talking about? How?
Oh shit, out of magical power. Right, so now this guy. Long hallway. He fires. I just dodged through
it. I imagine we're just gonna run at him and he doesn't have a chance. Jesus, man. Okay.
Damn. I was about to take off my staff and start to play.
That thing's cool, but I want health. Can't reach. All right. My God. That guy's a pain in the ass.
I gotta go in there ready. I might just try to block or I mean, he, he, he tried.
Fuck. What about all these guys? Yeah. Is there something funny?
Fucking jeez, man. What the fuck? Azure's Glintstone staff. Now this looks to be a real
staff. One that I am very much excited about. Reduces cast time of all sorceries, but consumes
more FP. Reduce cast time though. That's huge because of the dexterity I'm building.
And look at how cool it looks. What does Dex have to do with cast time? In this game,
in Elden Ring, dexterity reduces cast time. Let me just see what the difference is.
That's pretty significant. And especially doing dexterity. I think this is the one. I need 52
intelligence though. It's time to start beefing up. All right. Well, that's really, really cool.
I, I know there's another place I can go on the rooftops, but I'd like to,
I've only done one or two real encounters like bosses in the game so far.
I've spent the last like five hours kind of exploring some of this other stuff.
I want to try to do this area here. Like it's maybe up, maybe like over here or up here.
If not there, then I really want to do maybe like up here, this way. Or first of all, I want to go
here because I think I need to for like progression. I also, I'm going to take a quick break.
I want to pee. I'll be back. I'll see you guys in a minute. Pee break. And the key, right? I'll mark
it all. Let me mark it. So everything on the map has significance and something I actually really
have to do. I'm going to get rid of this because, okay. So it's glintstone key, power place, and then
up here. These are the places I want to go. And I am going to, I think that's everything I can do
here. So I'm going to pour it out. I know this probably, there's one other place I didn't go on
the roof, but you know what? I mean, I got, maybe I'll come back later. I want to progress up
north more. So we are going to pour it out. I'm going to go here through the main, no, not the
main gate, like here and go to the tower. I'll be right back. See you guys in a minute.
I cleared my throat. That's how they know I'm back. Glintstones. Meet the glintstones.
Modern Stone Age. What kind of tea do you drink? It's matcha. Matcha powder. Green tea. Yep.
Irma, you're a basic white girl. What? It's, but I like matcha. It's, hey, you know what? Okay.
Okay. Do you see how, how powerful this is making me? Do you see how powerful this is making me over
the last four days? Matcha can be enjoyed by anybody and everyone. And I'm going to enjoy
some right now. I just put a, I just drank a little too much. Matcha, matcha man.
Matcha, matcha man. I want to be a matcha man. Matcha, matcha, matcha man. That was funny.
It was for one second, but I, okay. I went a full two seconds too long. It's a type of green tea.
It had a powder form. Don't overdo it though. It's pretty good for you. Don't, it's, it's got
caffeine in it. I mean, not as much as like a bunch of like espresso or anything, but
you know what I mean? Green tea is just good for you anyways. I would recommend people
be drinking it just regularly anyways, because it's just good for you. The law, it's a different
like kind of caffeine buzz than you get when you drink coffee. Doesn't have very much. What
do you like for a brand? I'm still figuring that out. I can't, I can't give you a full
recommendation yet. I'm still figuring that out. Matcha was not allowed during prohibition.
All right. We need to go that way. So I got to get on this bridge down here somehow.
I'm going to go ahead and do the fucking famed castle skip. Nailed it perfectly here. And on
this bridge over, where's this bridge? And I'm supposed to find that way. Where is it? Where is
it? I kind of don't know. I came on the wrong side. Let's go to the front door. I don't know.
I kind of don't know how to get there. Don't aggro the entire village. Front door is probably
where I need to go. Do they follow me down here? No. Wait, what about that dog with the knife in
his mouth? You guys know what I'm talking about? Remember that crazy like it had the wolf with like
a knife in his mouth? He was rammed. Where is that? I think that's right here. Isn't that dog down
here? Okay. Hold on. Where's that dog? Right there. Right there. Yep. I remember now. Let's kill this
guy. Okay. Well, God, man. Crush me? Jesus. Imagine even trying to fight this guy like 15, 20 levels
ago. Kill him. He's in front of you. I didn't dodge. Oh, fuck off. That stupid spin. That like
little wham at the end. Fuck you. That little like, oh, oops. I'm going to turn instantly and
hit you. Oh, fuck. I don't want to be here. I want to be here. Yeah. This is stupid. It's just like
I had it too. That fucker was dead. I could have. Okay. That's why greed is good. I'm never fucking
not listening to my gut again. I had an opportunity to hit him a third time and kill him, but I was
like, no, don't do that. That's a bad idea. Don't do that. And I would have, I would have won.
First of all, I need to put both headphones in because like these fucking guys. I got to get the
boys in. Why can't I call them? Excuse me. Does it be outside? What even hit me? This fucking dumb
ass. Get the stupid bow and arrow and shove it up your ass. Fuck you. God damn it. Peace blood,
old fang. Nice job, boys. Nice work. I'm imagining like a neighbor. No, fuck you.
Fuck you. No, you can take that bow and arrow and shove it up your ass. Bow and arrow? What's
happening in there? Okay. This is the way I need to go. What's he talking to? Ooh, this is cool.
Is this the right way? This is the right way, right? Yeah, it has to be. Ooh, missed an item.
Did? Where? Missed item. Up your ass. Nice. It's the bow. Over there, dude. What sword is this?
It is the carrion night sword. Really good if you're doing, uh, if you start as prisoner and you
really want to be the sorry bastard that says, I want to do just dex and intelligence. It's the
weapon for you. I like it. I like it so far. Bolt Drake talisman. Lightning damage negation. Okay.
I wonder. I wonder. I wonder if there's going to be some lightning damage. All right. Give me one
sec. One sec. I'll be right back. Three seconds. I'll be right back. Cheeseburgers. I told you I was
going to eat. Wait, both headphones got to go in. He's really got the burger king. I have to play
the part. Hey, why don't you send somebody that could actually fucking do. Oh, there's two of them.
Nevermind. There's three of them. Oh shit. Die. Get his power core out of his chest. God, that's way
easier than I thought it was going to be. How come he doesn't have any? Why does he have more power
core? How come you get extra power? What happened? The archer with an arrow? Really? I'm going to have
a greasy cheeseburger controller. I'm not eating like a bag of potato chips. I would, I would
probably tell you that like just a cheeseburger from like Burger King, McDonald's, Wendy, doesn't
matter. It's, that's not going to, you get a bun. It's not going to get, it's not grease all over
the bun. This is bread. You're going to be fine. Burgers are greasy as fuck. Um, not this part.
This is the part I'm touching. It's dry. It's dry, dry, dry, dry. This is bread. Where are you
getting your burgers from? Show fingers or you're lying. Fine. Perfectly fine. Show the other hand.
Fine. There's nothing on there. This is going to make, this is going to power me up for at least
another two, three hours at least. I guess there's a teleporter. What about over here? Disgusting
Daniel. It's easy. It's quick, fast. All right. I'm not, I'm not going to eat steak on dinner
on stream, but you, I'm not going to eat like a piece of salmon on camera.
Where's, I've been into a gross part. I've been into a gross part. I had, I had to get out, I had
to get out of my mouth. Ooh, cotton. Asher Forest scarab. It's like, like the, all right. Increases
damage taken, but reduces the FP costs of Asher's work. You guys know how it is. Sometimes you're
just biting into like kind of a gross part and you want to get it out. Why are you eating by
taking bites out of your table? I'm like eating my desk. It shouldn't be gross parts of things I'm
eating. Sometimes you bite into a gross part and you have to go like, oh, so I know some of you get
it. It's like two gross parts. Let me explain. Let me explain for all the people here that are
yelling at me. Let me explain. When you eat something that has a consistent texture across
the board, you know what each bite feels like. You know, the texture, you know, the give when
it's something off about that. When the texture changes in one of the bites, you kind of have to
say, well, that's something that different there. That's kind of weird. You get it. Okay.
I'm ready. Oh my God. That sounded so awful. You ready? Here we go. Um, it's, it was fine.
Nothing wrong with it. He's actually attacked. What's the Eagles? If you need,
Hey, you need Eagle feathers. They're here. I was talking to me. I was making a reference to me.
Like, Hey, if you need them, they're here. Idiot. Like talking to shit, like Jeremy,
like self-referential humor, dude, they don't stop moving. I'm trying to drink out of something
that's empty. Okay. So what's at the very end? Was there no reason to come down here? Oh,
fuck. Really? There's nothing over here. You fuck. That's really pretty. Invisible bridge.
I'm not walking over an invisible bridge. I, uh, it can't get your horse here. Uh, what?
Invisible bridge crew. There they are. There they are. They've made themselves known.
There's invisible bridge crew. Stop burping. Divine tower of living grave. How do I open it?
Like that. Right in the center. Very nice. Wait, I didn't read whatever that was. I bet you can't,
I bet you can't not talk for one minute. Try me. Ready? Three, two, one, begin. I won.
I won. It's my prize. All right. For five minutes now. I've already done this. All right.
I'll do it for five minutes. I'm going to wait till the clock strikes 5 41, five hours and 41
minutes and I'll start. You already did this. Yeah, I know. That's what I'm saying. We already did
this. Be quiet for the rest of the entire stream. Well, if you would, I'll just leave. Everybody
would leave. There'd be nobody here. Oh, it's a finger. It's a dead two fingers. Restore the
power of the great rune. Rodrick's great rune. What does that do? Raises all attributes? Excuse
me. What are you talking about? Raises all attributes. How do I use this? You equip this
at the bonfire. Oh shit. Okay. Oh yeah. Is that, I think that's everything I can do here, right?
That's one thing done. Let's go do it. Is there any detriment to doing it?
Does it do anything? Is there like a, you just do it. Great runes. The great rune menu,
you can equip great runes that have had their power restored. You can use a rune arc to give
even greater benefits to your equipped great runes. Raises all attributes. By how much?
Did it do anything? I have to use a rune arc? It's, I have to use a rune arc. Um, it doesn't,
it doesn't do. Oh, I get it. So you equip it. You take a rune arc and that gives you,
okay. And then when you die, it's gone, right? That just, it's a humanity. Okay. Well,
I have no idea what the hell I'm going to use that. Anything else to do in here?
See power from remembrance. Purchase. Queen's robe. What does this do? Do I get any benefit
for wearing any of this stuff? Or is it just passion souls? There's new, uh, intelligence
stuff, right? The hat gives intelligence.
Feel her look.
I'm sorry. I mean, at some point you got to shave it all off.
It just doesn't look good. At some point you just got to get rid of it all.
Stop looking at it. So I have like eight, so I'm like,
yeah. You have anything new? No, I got everything I need from you. Thanks for the weapon, by the way.
Dumbass. All right. It's time to do step two. Step two was to go give this guy the key.
Step three, get the boys to plus 10. Did you eat without drinking? No, I got a drinker.
I really do wonder what this does, but I was going to kill me. Look what I got. I've got
something special for you. Give Adam the key. Yes, I am. Your soul.
It's kind of a Sims cry. Okay, so what? I will depart for the academy.
Decorated soul center by then. He's there now. I already bought everything he has.
Okay, so should I go back to the... Where is he? Now go find him in the academy?
Dude, this is gonna take fucking forever. Where would he be? Grand library? He's gonna die in
there. He's literally gonna die. Does he know that everyone's gone mad and he's gonna die?
Outside the classroom? This dude... Okay, this dude's definitely gonna be... Okay, here we go.
Here's my prediction. I'm gonna go to the classroom and he's gonna be lying face down
with an item on his back. Dead. That's what's gonna happen. He's just gonna be lying on the ground.
Okay, where are you at? Is he out here? I told you he was dead. I told you he was gonna be dead.
He's just sitting here. He didn't... Thop's bell bearing? An academy glintstone? Thop's barrier?
He's just dead. What killed him? This doesn't look like it was a murder. This looks like he
kind of just died in the chair. And by the way, how did you do all this out here? How did he get
in there to get all this equipment? It's like cold out here. He just got here. He just got here. We
said goodbye. He teleported here. He sat in the chair and just fucking died. All right, what was
all that stuff? Academy staff, which you already had. Thop's blessing or something. Whatever the
hell that was. What was... Oops. What was it called? Oops, bell bearing. Offered to twin maiden
husks for new item access. Okay, and then Thop's shield? Thop's barrier. A lifelong pursuit of
Thop's the blunt stone. Creates a magic force field that deflects sorceries and incantations.
Hold to continuously create barriers. Interesting. So it's an anti-magic shield. Okay, I'm willing to
try it. Well, thanks a lot, Thop. It was another place I needed to go. There it is. All right.
Ladies and gentlemen, ladies and gentlemen, we are now going to progress up through northern
Lunaria Lake up this way. We're gonna go into this abandoned room right now, but not yet. Not yet.
Some unfinished business that needs to be taken care of. Are you high? Stop fucking blowing my
spot up, dude. Come on. I wouldn't fucking do that to you. Okay, so first of all, I need to see if
I can upgrade this weapon, because it's been a while. Zomber smithing stone five. Although I can
do this. This has to replace this, right? But I need 52 intelligence. All right.
That's plus one. Okay, oleg. I can just get oleg up and get him ready. Who else should I do this to?
The dogs? The dogs have been pretty useful. Or should I save it just in case? I guess I can get
everybody, right? Most of them? Never skip oleg day. You use the dogs once. I need grave glove
for it too. Or I'll probably run into it soon. I think that's all I can do. Oh, that's right.
New items. I want to know what that person's problem is. Here, take this. Offer bell bearing.
Offer thops bell bearing. Bell bearing shop one? Wait, it just puts his items here?
I already bought his shit. What the fuck did that guy do for me? He gave me a little rinky-dink
barrier spell. What's a memory slot? A memory card? Oh, it's for spells. Watch that spell
be incredible. Uh, let's see. Okay, I haven't done this. I don't know. What do I do? Okay, I'm gonna...
Does it matter? How many of these I can make? All right, I'll make like the liver thing that's like,
oh, you boost fire damage reduction, right? Or like, uh, blood loss. I don't think I can put
these on my weapon. I can't even use these. I can't coat this weapon with anything. It's already
coated with magical power. I'll make... Okay, I'm gonna make... I'll make four of those. Yeah, I did
it. I crafted things. Because if there's a fire boss or something, I can just take it. Buy the
spell slot. Coat it with matcha powder. I sold... Okay, I'm gonna sell some stuff. See if I can get
a three thousand. Buy the memory slot. All right, what's this bullshit that I don't want?
I'm not gonna use a great axe, so I'm scared of it. Alam's Halvard. Imagine dual welding these.
That's funny, but not me. Uh, I have two of these, so why do I have two of them? Okay. I am never
going to use these. I'm just gonna get rid of them. I have no... There's no point in keeping these.
I have 99 of these? That's a thousand souls. Where did I get three brass shields from?
All right, that should get me... Okay, now I can afford... What was it? Four thousand?
Or is it three thousand? I can have another spell.
I love the blue. Yeah, it looks great. Well, not that one. This one. I want to show it off.
Well, I can't. I tried to play this game, but I burnt my PC. It exploded.
I'll get it on PlayStation 4 or Xbox. All right, here it is.
Priest memory slots. So now I have four. I'll try it. Let me try this, and let's take
gravity off, and we'll try the real... Okay, I did this guy's entire quest line, and actually,
I want to move these around. I want the two damage weapons to be here, because I want this to be
this. This to be this. Okay, I'll try it. Bedtime? It is not my bedtime. It is time to go.
Nothing else to clean up. I'm ready. I'm making noises? I can't help it. People think that I just
do this because I'm on stream. I just do this in like the bathtub. I'll be in the bathtub just
going like... I'm a bird. I'm like a weird parrot thing. I actually think I might have been a bird.
You don't ask why birds do that shit, because they just do, and it's not like, hey, birds,
shut the fuck up. Why are you making sounds? They sing their songs, and everybody loves them.
What have you ever told a bird to shut the fuck up? Just being real. King's Realm Ruins.
Cool. Not enough of that. Not about enough of that.
Ah, EZ, forgive me. These Royal Guards grounds were placed in our trust, but we stood no chance.
I just like farted in the bathtub. Can I be real with everybody for a second? Who else is afraid
to fart in the bathtub, because you're afraid you're going to shit, like you're going to shit
your pants, or shit the tub, and like shit in the tub, because I am. Like, oh, I think I'm going to
go ahead and just do this. Like, what if you just like shit? I've had plenty of accidents over the
years. Not in the tub. That's not going to happen. That's why I can't be on camera. No one asked this.
I know. I'm sorry. What the fuck? You've been streaming? No, I'm fine. Relax. What an Andy.
You didn't even say what kind of Andy. What the hell? Um, there's something under here.
It's probably a dungeon. So now my sorceries are stronger here. What's this? What's this one?
Why does this seem like a shield? It's a spell parry? Hold it. Yeah, I am. I'm holding it right
now. I wonder what that is. Does it hurt other people? I'll try it. But let me see if there's
anything under there. There's a ruin here. It takes too fucking long. How am I supposed to
parry this? All right, congratulations. Stop. Uh, you got a fucking blintstone key for literally
no reason. All right, let me find out what this is. We're looking for a way to go down in the
dungeon. I saw it right here. That guy. Where is it? Where is it? Where is it? I need to find it.
I must find it. Find I if you haven't seen any of those stuff. What the fuck is that?
They're reading a book. That's huge guys. They're just reading a book.
Is that an NPC? What's your name? We don't receive many visitors. I presume you are.
What brings you here? This guy's got an anvil. It's hardly my place to ask, is it? I am EG,
a blacksmith who once served the Carian Royals. Still quietly ply my trade on this spot.
Perhaps you'd like a display. These bones are old, but still able.
This is not the blacksmith. Oh, come on, dude. Really? I need somersmithing stone five.
You have up to four. You don't have five.
I have that sword. All right, well, you've got those, but you don't have the ones I need.
Enchanted snare, day away from that death trap.
Well, I'm not going to listen to a single word you said and I'm going to go get killed
probably two to three hundred more times. Have a good one. This is where I look over at him and
he just goes. I don't know why I'm going this way, but I decided to go this way. Oh, hell yeah.
Oh my goodness. Look at all this. Very nice. Is it maybe the back door? Maybe there is a back door.
Oh, that does not look like a back entrance. It's not a back door. Can I do anything with
this big rock formation? I don't think so. Cool looking rock. Here it comes. No,
it's not coming. I want to get off the horse because I don't think I can turn well.
Turning there, I probably would have fall down. It's so fucking pretty. It's so cool looking.
All right. All right. Let's just go on the front door. Who cares? Give me the fucking item.
There's a lake over there. All right. No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
I just checked the other side. No, we'll go front door. We made it. Lock raid. Oh,
I thought somebody actually raided Aria Manor. That's terrifying. Is that a hand?
Fucking. Oh, fucking. It is a hand.
All right. The pinky fingers of the other. They can't do anything.
Somersmithing stone too. I need a five. Please. I don't like that either. Yeah. It's disgusting.
We'll check over here first. Linstone craftsman's cookbook. Okay. Magic grease,
raw string magic grease. I just don't think I can use any of it.
That was heartless. Was it though? I have that too. I just can't use it.
Oh, they're like booby traps. Okay. Spitting stone three. No fives.
Minus two and a three. There's other little hands. Oops. Get your little friends out of here.
Very bad. God damn it. Fuck off. You can't be kidding me. Dude, I'm stuck in the fucking.
I can't get out of here. What was I stuck on? What was it? What was on me? What was in the way?
I'm just gonna fucking run out of this shit. That is way too slow. Way too slow. Shit, man.
Do I really have to fight two of these guys at the same goddamn time? Holy shit. Fuck this area.
Oh. Oh. Whoa. There he is. You fucker. I was looking around for him.
Actually, I was looking for him and I couldn't see him. Did he come out of the ground? Fucking
worst enemy in the game. It's like so hard to tell what part of his hand is attacking you. It's like
it's such a weird fucking way to attack. I can't, I like, I don't know which one of his fingers is
gonna fucking swing at me. It's like half of his hand attacks you. Oh my fucking God. I'm gonna
kill this guy because I'm fucking mad. Fuck you for being in here. Oh, I'm dead because of so much
health. What a shit enemy. I don't want to fight any more of these guys. I'm literally just walking
by him. Rimmed crystal bud. All right, that's it. I missed so much shit over there, but I don't care.
I'm in severe concentration mode. I gotta run in and pray for a bonfire. That almost just fucking
bonfire. Bonfire? It can't come in here. Oh, are you gonna do that again? No. Lady Rani,
we have long awaited you. I pray for your house's swift revival. May the full moon shine upon Karya.
You gonna do PvP? Um, I don't know. Not in the immediate future. Maybe eventually.
Maybe after a little while. I want to beat the game. Okay, examine this area. You're not fucking
hands. I don't want to fight those hands anymore. They're the worst.
As long as you guys don't have like fingers crawling out of your eyeballs and shit. I don't
care. I'll fight all of you. Will you lock on please? This is an ugly place to fight.
Don't fall off. Don't roll off. What? What? What? What? What? I didn't hit him? What? Did he? Was
his foot a centimeter away? Every time I'm a centimeter away, I get hit by that bullshit.
A lot of things went wrong there. Suck my ass. I almost jumped off the edge. I'm fucking sweating.
Okay, what about this way? Let's go this way first. Watch out for their magic.
Why are the trees moving? This tree is moving weirdly. Like it's gonna lift up and it's gonna
be a guy's face. I was waiting for the tree to do something. I thought it was gonna be,
I thought it was a guy's hair. He's gonna be like, and just fucking smash me.
Did you do the goofy goober dance? My mistake was going there in the first place.
Guess what the hell was over there? A rune arc? Who gives a shit? Yoch! Yoch! Yoch! Huh? Oh you
fucker. There's no stagger with this guy. I'm not putting up with him. Okay, so I just got punished
for going over there because everybody just collapsed on me. Am I tripping over a mine or
something? Am I summoning them? How am I, how is this happening? Am I spawning them? I feel like
I'm spawning them. I'm spawning them. They're being spawned when I cross a certain threshold,
like a certain spawn area. Or did they just, maybe they just do it randomly always? I don't know.
Interesting. Very interesting. Yeah, I'm not gonna get fooled by that. Nope, no, I'm sorry.
Not, not after like 25 minutes here. Holy shit! That sucks absolute balls. I'm gonna run.
Relax. Get that shit out of here. I'm the right firing. Really? Are you serious dude? Fuck you.
I'm sitting there paying attention to the guy back here shooting from a hundred miles away.
I have to kill him now because, yeah, I just spawned like three people probably.
Yeah, I fucking knew it. You fateful shit. How dare you. Fuck you. Oh, fuck you. I don't want
to fight him. I'm running to the door. I'm just checking for items. I just need to see if there's
items. Oh, see you later. Thank god. Oh my goodness. That was horrible. That was so scary.
It was so awful. And the hand was fucked. Fuck those hands. Oh, I can upgrade my class. I have
to go back to that area later. I don't want to go back to that fucking place. I don't like
those hands. They're too freaky. They're freaky. Like super like freaky freaky. I don't like it.
Too freaky. Way too freaky. So there's a summoning stone thing there. I wonder if there's
something here. That was a little bit different move. Really? That was kind of a different move.
God, he's just bouncing around. What is this fucking move set? He looks like he's lagging.
He has like 3000 fucking ping. He's like, God, what am I connecting to? Are the boys plus 10?
We need way more materials to get the boys to plus 10 that I just I do not have. We need like
what I got the boys to plus one. That's as far as I could get. You will regret upgrading the boys.
I probably will because like literally the first that's the first item that you get in the game.
I think that's like the first item. Oh shit. Headphones are going in for this one. I'll
leg up here. Seems safer. But again, there's always these old guys that just die in one hit.
I don't think these guys even know that they're here. They're kind of just wandering around with
a stick that they found on the ground. And when they go like this stuff comes out and they just
go, I guess I'll do that to people. All right. Yeah, I'm not fighting the giant knight.
If I can get behind him. Well, I'm killing them because they're attacking me.
They're trying to kill me. I'm just defending myself.
Geez. I don't I mean that guy has that guy is just a big version of me.
I don't have. I can't fight that guy right now. There's a fire up here. Maybe.
Oh my fucking God. It's a guy with one of those things. He's got one of these things.
Oh my God. Fireworks just went by my screen.
Duck. Okay. Um, I don't know if I want to go there.
It looks like a new area. That is a pot down there. You're right. That's a pretty, that's a
Pog pot. Oh, thank God. Oh my goodness. I'm saved. Actually saved right there.
Okay. Now I don't feel as bad as a boss without a without a doubt. I have 8,000 souls.
I'm not going for it. I'd rather fall down here, die and spawn there and run over here.
I'm going to check over here first. It seems safer to me somehow.
Oh shit. They all came over. Oh my God. They're everywhere.
They're fucking everywhere. They're everywhere.
The cracked pot. Is that it? Can I go anywhere from here though?
I think this is, can I get out of here? How do I get out of here?
Why would I go that way? Is there a door? Shit. All right. This is pot village.
I don't want to go to hand town. Everything has to be a town or a village. Oh, a hand place.
Pot town, pot village, pot world, hand world, hand city.
I'm just trying to make sure this is safe because look at my health.
Oh, that was almost not safe. What do you, what's behind you?
There's something behind.
Even think about it. All this way for something that might be good.
All this way. God damn it. What is that?
Oh shit. I'm fine. Hand, hand, hand. Oh, I need to teleport. How do I teleport? I gotta kill this.
Okay. Very important. Did I do this yet? I did already. Okay. I think I have enough to level up.
I definitely do. That was insane. That was, my heart is just like exploding.
13, 14, 15. Okay, that's enough. That was an absolute roller coaster. It really was.
Uh, mind is the easy one here because it gets us closer to Oleg.
Or I gotta start pumping intelligence. All right. So that was that.
That was that whole chain of events took us that way. So now I'm not completely uncomfortable
going, uh, this way now, which I want to see what's in that boss room.
I'm very, very, very curious. What about the new spell? Oh yeah. I'll look at it too.
It's a good call. Oh, you know what? No, let's, let's go for this. Might as well. It's right here.
He can't fit through this door. So like I can get rid of these,
I can get rid of these idiots and he can't get through here and then it'll be a one-on-one
or I'll just fucking die. That's one way that could happen.
Hey, um, so that would have been okay. Uh, I should have done the big sword move,
which I want to make sure it's there. Okay. The big sword works really well on those guys.
And I have to get rid of the, in case that happens again, just kill the dog.
The dog is gone. I can pull them back here if I need to. Okay. Now let's try this again.
In fact, here, just like, fuck you buddy. Now you come with me. Really? Get over here.
Okay. Now you. Boys, where am I? Shit. Oh boy. That's not good. Oh, he just
bumped into the wall. No, get him. Oh shit. Oh my God. I didn't dodge. Oh shit. Where are they?
Oh my God. Your moves don't, I don't know how to time them. Hey, this is a cult. Oh man. Really?
No shit. Wow. It's a magic strength. Dex scaling weapon. What does that sound like?
That sounds like somebody. I don't know who. All right. Well, that's really cool. I don't know.
How much help do I have? None. I mean, there's, there's really no point to me. I just go back
to the bonfire, right? Like, what's the point of me doing this to die? Your German, bro,
heal, bro. German, bro, heal, bro. I'm all right. Well, that was intense. Now we do the fun thing
where I go look at the boss and then figure out if I am too burnt out to continue to play.
I'm definitely feeling it. I'm definitely starting to feel the, uh, or like 42 straight hours of
playing this game. Uh, I'm starting to kind of burn out a little. Mach of burnout. Yeah. I'm
getting some mach of burnout here. 42 straight hours. I know that I'm kidding.
How long has it been? 37, 35, 38 hours straight. Essentially sleeping in between
and like morning errands and, you know, going to the bathroom.
Okay. What's going on here? What is this? Royal Knight Loretta. Do I get a horse too? Where's
my horse? Where's my horse? Oh, that was a new move. That was a one, two. Thankfully it's right
here. I wonder if you stay on his, uh, right side. Ooh, okay. That's a little, that's a little snipe.
All right. Yeah. I got to stay on his other side. Yeah. He's a pain in the ass if he can't swing
this way. Oh, you fucking idiot. Oh, I have the gravestone behind me. I really, really, really
need to go find a flask upgrade. I think, I think I might have to do some flask upgrade after this.
Okay. Dude, dude, what? Okay. Do something else. Shit. He's not that bad. I'll get him.
Unless it's like a phase two, which he knows. All right. So, okay. He spins,
he spins it around before he swings it. When he did, when he does that, you're close enough.
No, I thought he was going to do another move. Dude, like, let me just, let me get a hit it.
Like, it's not very much open. I even waited to spin. This is new. I don't know what that is.
Oh, that's new too. Okay. Uh, he forgot he has magic. Uh, casting a spell at this boss is pretty
much, I'm guaranteed to die. Takes too long. And so this, this guy's magic. He's, he's definitely,
he's going to be immune to magic. I could do the boys. Let's see.
Can't put a lock onto him. Nice job, boys. Excellent work. And add a stamina. Or I don't
know what the fuck happened. I just like got caught up with all the loud sounds and all.
I don't even know what happened. I just like all the sounds. There's so much fucking sounds.
I just heard like, I just heard it like screams and slashes and like, I just like,
I'm just going to be a part of it. I'm going to get up there. I'm going to slash him too.
Something in my eye. Come on, boys. Get him. I thought I got under the horse. I thought I
got under the horse, but I didn't. Oh, come on. All right. All right. All right. All right.
How do I get away from this? Just dodge it. What the fuck? Jump, maybe jump. I don't, I don't know.
Jump over it. I dodged that pretty, I thought that was pretty good dodge.
Maybe jump. Dodge forward. Dodge into it. I won't, it won't hit me, right?
Dodge forward might work, but it's an explosion. Isn't dodging forward the same distance as
dodging to the right or left? Wrong thing up. This is a wash. Yeah, just kill me.
I didn't have the boys ready. What about the thop shield? I feel like it's, that's so,
that's so hard to use because it's like, one, you got to time that perfectly.
I don't think I need it. I think as long as I could reliably get away from the whatever it is.
Do I have the thop step? I already found the thop step. It was just the academy step.
Uh, I forgot again. Yeah, kill me again. I keep forgetting to summon them when I get in.
I also might have to stop streaming. My eyes, I can like feel my eyes starting to like pulse.
It's probably time to stop. And I would, I, I thought I was going to be able to go longer
today. I don't, I don't think so. Did you hit, he didn't even swing at me. Billy, eat shit.
How many attacks? That's kind of bullshit. All right, here we go.
Dodge through it. Let's go on a good one. Go on a good one.
Oh man, that was hard. Magical bow? Yeah, that wasn't too bad. It was just trying to figure out
how to get away from the projectiles. Cause once, once you understand that, like, it's hard to
determine if he's going to swing more than two or three times, but just let him do it. Right?
When he, when, when you're next to him and he's like, swing, swing, don't attack. Like sometimes
he does it twice. Sometimes he does it three times. Sometimes he does it four times. You just,
just dodge it, just dodge. And then when he stops, take a swing. That was on 10,000 souls? Really?
That's it? Only 10k? That's kind of horseshit. Did he have a, let me see those spells.
Oh, these are crystals. Oh, that's probably so cool though. Let me see.
Imagine hitting somebody with this. I imagine shooting that. That's no way you're going to hit
anybody with that. Not a chance. I mean, maybe you'll hit. I mean, that's, that's awesome.
All right. I gotta call it. I, I, I can't go anymore. I thought I was going to be able to
go for like at least another hour or two. No, no way. You can probably tell my like energy,
like an hour ago. I went from like a seven, eight out of 10 energy to like a three or like a four,
like, like 45 minutes ago. I'll go back through. I'm not, we're not, I'm not going to be streaming
tomorrow. The next time I will be live. Let's do today. Okay. I will see you guys for more Elden
Ring on Wednesday. I'll take a couple of days. I'll refresh and we will go Wednesday, probably
Wednesday, Thursday, Wednesday, Thursday, Friday. Cause I'm into it. I don't want to, I don't want
to take too long of a break. Maybe like a day or two. Cause I really don't want to lose the muscle
memory. Cause if you don't play for like a week and you come back, you just, you're like a wet
sock. You're like a, you're like a dirty wet sock and it doesn't work. You'll forget how to play.
Yeah. It's true. Wednesday at, yeah. Wednesday at four. I'll see you guys on Wednesday. Thanks
for hanging out. Thanks for watching the streams. I think we're making pretty good progress.
And I talked a lot of shit about this area, but you know, I literally talk shit about the entire
game the entire time I'm playing. I'll see you Wednesday. Thanks for watching. We'll hang out
for a minute. Uh, that's saved there. Best boss in the game is coming up. Ooh, well I'm excited for
Wednesday. Thanks for staying up too. I know I, I, this launch has been kind of crazy. All these,
all these streams going into like three o'clock in the morning Eastern, four o'clock in the morning
Eastern pretty much. That will probably change a little once, uh, you know, maybe there's this
next week rolls around, but I am fucking tired. It's so funny cause like, okay, after the pot
almost killed me twice, my soul left my body even more than it already was. I don't, I'm actually,
I'm not even, I'm surprised I actually could beat this guy. People were asking me like questions
and I was like, I do what I did. I can't do that. I think I just shut my brain off and fought him.
Oh, machete immunity building up. Oh, that's just been four days. Empty head implying that you're
going to beat it. Pepe laughing. I beat Dark Souls three on stream. I beat Sekiro on stream.
If I can do Sekiro, which I think Sekiro was harder than this game so far, this is much longer than
Sekiro, but I think the difficulty in playing Sekiro is harder than this. They're harder in
different ways, but this one, this is like the harder, I don't know where I would put this in
difficulty. I really don't know. I think Sekiro is, I think is much more difficult because the
game is played a lot differently and it was a lot, it was really hard to get used to the fact that
you had to just sit there in L1 of every single enemy in the game. You couldn't like dodge around.
You couldn't, there was no sorcery. There was no dodge mechanic that was, you know, that's it. You
died. You could dodge, but it wasn't even close to, you needed to parry. You had to parry almost
every single attack. Well, I think this is probably the hardest of the Dark Souls-like games.
That's tough though, because I do remember, I remember a few encounters in Dark Souls three
being like unbearable. I'm trying to think of like comparing some hard bots. It's been so long since
I played Dark Souls three. Like Pontiff maybe. I remember struggling with Pontiff and being like,
holy shit, this guy's like not completable. I haven't really, okay, I haven't really thought
that way yet about any, Pontiff was easy. Pontiff was easy if you could parry, because you could
parry him, right? It was the, when he summoned the second clone of himself, it just was so,
my brain was so hard to dodge and get around the clone. The DLC dragon? Yeah, okay, there it is.
Yeah, some of the DLC in Dark Souls three was unbelievably difficult. I remember, I actually
had to summon people for that shit. I remember summoning people for that dragon. Yeah, Midir.
Midir, it was unbearable. Nameless King was pretty bad too, but I feel like Nameless King was not
as, just, Midir just had so much health. The fight just dragged on so long that you got kind of like
exhausted halfway through it. Oh no, I never beat Midir. I remember summoning four people and we
couldn't do it. All right, I'm taking a break from streaming for a day and a half, two days.
Thanks again everybody. I'll see you soon. I believe there's a big boss coming up here.
We'll find out. Thank you, thank you, thank you, thank you, thank you.
Take care of yourselves. I'm gonna go, I'm gonna go take a shower
and I'll see you guys Wednesday at four o'clock. Good night. Goodbye. Take care of yourselves.
Have a great night.