So let's see if they can get it situated at least somewhat playable in like an hour or two.
Let's go. I get it. Uh, well, I don't even need... I don't have to change the title.
That title is fine. So you lied to us yesterday. Wait, what did I say yesterday? What did I say
yesterday? You said jackbox. Yeah, but do you want just a random jackbox stream for like two
hours? Do you want like a five to seven hour jackbox stream on Friday? You know what I mean?
Do it both. Well, no, we're doing it on Friday. He's a liar. Right. He's like, well, wait, hold on.
Didn't I say yesterday that depending on how long we were in Red Dead 2, that we would do jackbox
maybe depending on if it was, if I only was in it for like an hour or two, right?
Didn't I say something like that along those lines? Yes. Yes. Yes, I did. Yeah. Yeah. Yes,
I did. Yeah. Yes. See, it's just like online. See? Yeah, let's give them some time to try
it again because I still haven't done all this. Where we going here? Jackbox, jackbox.
Friday will be fun. So I need to go here. So we need to take a stage coach from here
all the way across the world to here and then ride home roads. Oh, why can't today be fun?
Well, because we attempted to play a beta that wasn't ready. Am I going to make rules
for people joining the game this time? You mean jackbox? Let me actually, I might be able to
set something up where it just picks people randomly. Isn't that like an extension for you
that you can get that and then like that, that person, that person gets picked again.
I could do it like that. That'd be fun. Why do I hate Red Dead single player so much? Oh,
no, I don't. I love this game. I think this game is awesome. It's just, I mean, the
multiplayer is just the new thing and it's really, really interesting. Like, oh wow,
it's Rockstar's new online in the wild west. Cool. I think my horse's foot just explode.
I hate jackbox. Play Fistful of Frags. I don't even have it installed. Remember,
I reinstalled Windows. Remember the Windows update bullshit I was going through
where we just would not turn it. Where is this marker? Oh, right. Stagecoach.
Yeah, I had to reinstall Windows completely. So I lost all my downloads. I tried to get as
many things as I wanted before. Peggle 2 got me excited.
Full of, I'm full of letdowns, guys. I'm sorry. It's only like two gigs. Letdown stream.
No. Damn I though. I'm sorry. I'm sorry. I gotta get up before anybody witnesses it.
Quick, get me to Rhodes Ranch before somebody witnesses me. Uh, Coachman. Hello. Hello.
I'd like to take a ride. Take a ride, please. Take a ride. Coachman. L2. What the fuck?
Am I sure I'm not online? Who is shooting? Is it the guy? Is it the guy that I bumped into?
It's not a bounty. It's what? Wait, did I what? What did I just do? I just like broke into his lock.
Break. Oh, God. Did I break his wagon? This guy's gonna dump this thing off the end.
Where's my horse? Oh, for the love of God, this is gonna be bad up ahead.
Stop shooting. You have so many opportunities. Fuck off. No, now you decided to come. Now
you decided to come over here, horse, huh? It was the guy. It was the guy I bumped into.
You just couldn't let it go. Now you let it go permanently. All right. Back to the stage,
Coach. Before this guy sees me over here. Wait. What was that? Somebody in the water?
I don't see him. There's a random stranger over here somewhere. Oh, there he is.
All right. What's what? What do you need help with, sir? Mad preacher.
What?
Am I the signal?
No.
Okay. Well, that was it. He's going back up here. Is there something I can do with this guy?
Besides just push him off the cliff into the water, which is what
I'm sure everybody wants me to do. Where is he? Look out, mister.
That didn't hurt him. Okay. Got it. This is all I need.
Okay. Now why is this happening? All right. Come with me. First circle the talk while running.
No, whoops. No. All right. I need to pick him up. No, I'm not going to do anything to him.
I just wanted to see what he would do if I jumped on him. I'm putting him back in bed.
I might've hurt him a little bit, but he's back in bed. He's going to be fine. All right.
Have a nice day. He just witnessed an assault. Well, he's the guy that I
asked. Oh, now we're doing it all over again. How do I like to?
Nothing. Relax.
Just stop. Stop. Hey, stop it. Stop. What's the objective here? There really is none.
Goodbye. Have fun. Enjoy the rest of your life. That's not how you make friends. That's how I
make friends with GTA Online and Rockstar Online. Enjoy the bounty. All right. We're good.
So I need to go. It was the fucking stagecoach because the guy, look, it all started. This
15 to 20 straight minute nonsense started because I bumped. I ran into a guy in town
and it just spiraled out of control. Five dollar bounty. I can pay that. What's this?
Why is there a red circle in there? So the sheriff's office. Just pay the bounty. Take the
stagecoach. Everybody hates me here. Let's not forget. I bumped into the guy and he started
shooting wildly. Got no bounties anymore. They're all gone. Back to square one. We're good.
Stagecoach is where exactly are you right now? I already have it marked.
Why do I have so much money? Because I just did a couple missions where I made a lot of money.
I'm a good boy again. Just don't bump into somebody. Don't smash into someone.
Get to the stagecoach without any issues. Pay it. Go to Rhodes. Do the mission.
Do not break the lock. Rhodes Ranch. Take me there. I'm about 45 percent of the way
through the store. 43 maybe. I'm still playing this. We've got somewhere to be.
Yeah. Well I couldn't do online because there's all kinds of problems with it. I will give it
another solid attempt before I consider ending the stream. That is certain. So don't worry.
And then nothing tomorrow. That'll lead us into Friday for Jack Box Party Pack 5. And then
into the weekend we've got the movie night on Sunday. So should be fun this weekend. I'm
looking forward to it a lot. Let's progress. Let's progress the story of Red Dead 2.
I can't wait to get hammered and watch this weekend.
I mean Jack Box is a lot of fun. The movie night's gonna be probably a lot of fun too.
I'm also planning on doing that. I'm not sure. I don't know if that's in my plan.
We'll see. Maybe I'll have a couple of drinks during the movie night. That sounds fun.
We're gonna find my specs in my mouse. I don't even have it listed here, right?
What did I do? Is there a command still? I think there was a command at one point.
Oh there it is. Oh yeah there it is. Take a look at that. I've got 176850s.
Hey can we talk about this later? We need to learn Dutch. I have a 6850k, a
GTX 1080 hybrid. What does that mean? They were planning a visit to the Braithwaite
place but John needs to do something for Dutch now so Hosea wants you to join him.
I'll join Hosea. Seems to be a lot going on. Yeah I know I wrote that but what does it
mean? I don't know what that means. Let's get some free food. That sounds good.
The GTX 1080 hybrid has an AIO water cooler. Oh maybe that's what it is. I don't have a TI or
anything. Oh this is cool too. Rob a home. Yeah I'm doing that instead.
Is your people there? Jack of weights or english lovers? I have a death header.
It's the only mouse I've owned in probably 10 years. My dad would say that no politics was
politics. That old world bullshit it ain't got no place here. Why? Because there ain't no judgment
here. Most folks hate the negroes. They hate the redskins. I just don't have uh. When you
get used to a mouse you kind of can't ever use anything else. I gave everyone just the same.
Well in that case you're gonna want what I just found for us. What's that? I was riding around
a couple of days back. I come across this old cabin. A couple of fuckers lazing about outside
all liquored up. I didn't think nothing of it. But then I come across this hunter down by the
river. He tells me they're a stick-up crew. Says they hit a train a couple of days back
near Emerald Ranch. Nice fellow he was. Shared a bottle we did. Then I robbed the
blind. You believed him? No reason not to. If he's right it'll be a big haul for us.
Hey gamers. Maybe more but I reckon you and me we could take them real easy.
What the hell. Let's go check it out. Them sons of bitches think they're mean.
They're about to get a lesson in mean. You just keep your cool you hear me. These missions
are a lot of fun because you actually make a shitload of money doing them. Not that I need
money but it's been nice to have it and never have to worry about it. Follow behind Sean.
Oh your horse is named Sean too. That's kind of cool.
It's a bit of a ride. Oh well we got time.
That is my horse. Oh well cool. I miss Sean. Me too. I want to just go dunk on people in
multiplayer. You mean get dunked on in multiplayer? No. Should we be talking to him? Come on man.
What were you doing right looking for the take? I got a lot of nose for these things.
Duchess always honored us to get out there and bring in money ain't he?
And rightly so. I ain't like some of them others back there sitting around waiting to be
told I go after it. I see you sitting around planning. I mean I don't need no cuddling like
the rest. Have you played multiplayer yet? Yeah. We tried it for a few hours earlier.
It did not work. Well it half worked.
I'm getting rock star server problems probably every 30 minutes or so every 20 minutes and
then it upped in frequency and it started happening every like five minutes so we decided
we were going to take a break from it for like an hour to do a couple story missions
play this for a little bit and try it again see if it gets any better in a couple hours.
What's that box boy his tent for then? Camp funds supplies in fact you don't know
that suggests you clearly ain't put much in it. I always pay me way don't you worry.
How long am I gonna stream? You're sure you scope this place out right?
Yes see that's why you want the job. Probably for at least another few hours.
You're still a doubter. I ain't just some dumb kid.
Four hours or so probably. And you sure don't keep it bottled up inside.
I would assume. Made a good show in there didn't I?
You got knocked down. Ah that's what you two should remember.
Quick make a joke. We got paid. Um um um.
Got knocked down didn't you? No that was us.
Did you get split off with Mac? A guy a guy and a guy walking to a
bar. The guy behind the counter says what are you guys doing here?
Guy number one says my wife's gonna be angry. Guy number two says
so's mine. Guy number three. Jenny didn't even make it that far.
All right we're nearly there. Hard left coming up.
I was getting a text. I do have oh I know what it is. I know what it is.
I got a coffee table. My coffee table is coming in.
Yes yes. Here let's make sure we keep one of them alive. That's where they
stash the money. Hope you know what you're doing.
That was a terrible punch line. Um oh that's right I was telling a joke.
Guy number three uh something about about something about a ferris wheel
and he was eating and I think he dropped it. I forget what happened
after that though. There's one of them outside. This is
good. It is. Leave it to me. I do the talking.
You hang back. Slowly slowly. I did find the aliens. I did.
That was what? That was a long time ago.
Weirdly enough I found that I think in the first six hours of me playing the
game. I'm gonna give you and your daddy about
five seconds to get the hell out of my property boy.
Look we don't want no trouble. We just thought you might like to know
we passed a big posse alarm and headed this way.
Now it doesn't have a coming up beast. What?
Where? Right here. It's a marker. Here come the rest of them.
We've got what?
No. No.
Can I wake him up? I was stuck in the doorway and I pressed r2.
Look I I'm gonna put the fire out and then pull the lever underneath.
Don't worry I got it. Oh look a stash box. Oh well the game
found it for me. Thank you game. I really appreciate the help.
What was that? Double action revolver. That's kind of cool.
I'm not leaving yet. Hold on. Wait a minute. No that's my skull field though.
What's better when this is clean? Hold on. Is the skull field better?
Um I mean kind of. Accuracy. It's much more accurate.
Fire rate's lower but now that I think this thing sucks.
Because I have two skull fields and they are beautiful.
All right. Anything else? This guy died I guess.
Is he dead? He wasn't dead when I looked at him before.
No he's alive see. Take the meats. Not at all.
Search the cabinets. Free gin. I'll take it.
Where was the money? Where's the money? I know it's a secret little spot.
Oh there's money right here. 15 bucks. Pretty good.
Piss in the fire. You can't pee in this game so I'm sorry.
Can I not get the secret? Whoa whoa whoa.
Oh that's wrong. Maybe they have to tell you where it is.
I don't think I can get it. No prompts. No nothing.
Read chat. It's it's in the wall behind the bed.
I I just was there. The wall behind the bed. Wasn't I just over here?
I don't think I can get it without his prompt. Yeah you can't unless the
NPC tells you. See I you can call me stupid for hitting
the guy in the face of the barrel earlier.
Let's go girl. No the piss code. I can't get it without him telling you.
Yeah I wouldn't that would make sense. Otherwise you could just stay there all
day and just walk around and find it. All right Joseo what do you need?
This is not Joseo. Not at all actually.
Holy shit. Come on I gotta get the head exploding
achievement. Trophy earned. 100 heads exploded with shotgun.
So we've got uh probably some cool stuff here. These are bad
guys so it's okay. I mean yeah. Look for a lock box.
That's a lock box. If I was a lock box I'd be this one.
Medical box actually. Miracle cure. I can't take any more of it.
Opened miracle tonic. I might as well just use one right.
Where's the mirror? All right potent miracle tonic. Opened miracle tonic.
Just take it and pick up the other one.
Okay I think that's it. That's the most important thing at least. Oh no this
can I open this too? Yeah. Yeah. Hey. That's all you have in there is hey.
Uh assorted biscuits. Feeded the horse.
Corn. This is just stocking me up on food. If you piss in the fire it gives
you a code for unlimited lives. I don't want it anyways. Who wants
unlimited lives right now? Check one more time.
Ah hello there. Don't mind if I do. Who wants to live forever? No I don't
want to. Why would you want to live forever?
Okay instead of living forever could I choose a different option?
Could I just you know once I'm once I'm gone can I
like unlock an ability instead of oh I want to be alive. Live forever.
No just every like 100 years. No no probably
30 years. Every 30 years I just want to turn into like a spirit and just
kind of see what's going on. Just like walk around and look at stuff.
You know every 30 years just oh here we go. Oh okay what so what's going on now?
What's the world like now? You can do that now just be a hermit. Yeah but
you can only do that for like two times. You can go live in a cave and eat
dirt and like ping in a cup and drink it and like eat rabbits and stuff.
And then come out in 30 years and look around and be like holy shit.
But you can only do that like twice. I'm talking literally forever.
What's what if the world is destroyed and then you can just turn
it off. You can just after you wake up for that
time and it's like well this is the world is just a smoldering crater right
now. Oh okay like um I would not like to do
this again but I would want to do it at least.
No no no no no no no. No that's not a good idea. That'd be awesome
because if you kept doing that imagine like what would happen.
Like we're talking about an entirely new like
species. If you woke up every 30 years and the world was just abandoned
like in five million years this probably gonna be like a weird fucking
new creature that takes over the whole planet.
We're talking about living forever versus waking up every 50 years just to
kind of see what's going on. What are you doing?
Every hundred years yeah. Selling it back to where it came from.
I ain't got a market for it. They made it. Imagine waiting
five million years for bacteria. Stuff look kind of lonely out here.
I think we'll cut ourselves a deal. Yeah and then you could just observe
forever. You and Dutch was just doing your duty when you
requisitioned it. Waking up every hundred years.
And you get you get fast travel and you get 30 minutes.
Right like we'll see you later. Spend 10 minutes in like
Rome. What's going on here? Well that's interesting.
Spend 20 minutes in fucking Boston. What's Boston like?
So what exactly are we doing? This is the moonshine we took.
We're like an hour or something. Like two hours.
What would the point be if you can't affect anything?
Well then it's time we made a formal introduction.
Why would you want it? Don't you just want to know?
These are two big old plantation houses. All I keep hearing is they hate
each other so much they can't see past it.
I know. I've seen it. There's a gray boy
and a brave white girl carrying on a secret affair.
I've been well. What are you doing? Use the reins damn it.
The mind boggles. You think there's a street sweep to that guy?
They don't seem too involved in the rest of it but maybe.
Well I'm sure there's money in this for us somewhere if we can get in the
middle of it. There's a type of jellyfish that's
immortal. Hold on this is this is beautiful.
This is actually beautiful. Where in the map even are we? This is a sort of weird
road. Have uh. Did I get him? Why is this guy invincible?
Okay. Where's my scope? I have like a rifle don't I?
Horses got him. Hey that that horse got him without being checked.
That's not fair.
You may happily shoot me if I do. Okay okay.
Single player griefer. Oh don't sit on the back of that man.
Please don't sit on the back of that. We'll be watching you. You heard the man.
Driver proceed please. No I'm just. It is so tempting though you're right. It
really is. Just to drive him off the cliff
and just ghost ride him. Out something. Out in the hills thought.
Thought maybe you was in the market for it. For what?
Some liquor. I ain't in the market for what's already mine.
The way we see it it's ours. Well with us possessing it and I checked all over
for the life of me. I couldn't see your name on it.
Oh here comes the whole family. I know it seems that's easy enough.
Want to do a deal. Where do you sell that stuff?
Dollar a bottle. Give us 50 cents. It's already
ours. Well look on it as a reward for finding the property.
Alternative is we go sell it someplace else. The alternative is
you get shot. Now who wants to get shot over a bottle or two of liquor?
Pay the man. Really? Hosea quite the negotiator.
Pleasure doing business with you. And listen
we didn't take it. At least not without orders. Oh I know exactly who
gave you your orders. Old Sheriff Gray. You know what?
I don't want it. In fact sir now you can do me
a favor. There's an extra 10 bucks if you do.
Drop the stuff into Rhodes. Head over to the tavern run by Mr. Gray
and give the stuff out for free. Hush now.
I believe they call that a promotional expense.
They do. As you wish they do. That's true.
Come on Arthur let's take it out of here.
All right next stop the Rhodes Saloon. Here we go. Take the moonshine to Rhodes
Saloon. I finally sold those cornwall bonds.
Got close to a thousand for them. I wanted more but not bad considering how hot
they were especially after that bloodbath in
Valentine. No not bad at all. Apparently
gonna play fibbage. What is in that fifth party pack?
I don't know what's in it. I've seen a couple of random clips of what's in it
but I don't know every single game. We'll find out on Friday.
This could get ugly. You and Dutch already have that
thing going on in town with the sheriff.
Yeah Mr. Gray. That's it. Now we're uncertain ourselves in his
blood feud. We'll need something. I ain't playing
dressing. You know how I feel about that.
Of course you're not. He gave you three hundred dollars to do this. You're a
clown's idiot bro. 300 bucks is a lot of
money. I'm the clown. Back in like the 40s here.
Just and keep quiet. Even you can do that Arthur.
I have to do that.
Smoke this pipe. The 40s? Yeah. Bring your lip for it. Yeah somebody got like the 1740s.
Like the 1640s. Perfect. What about you?
What did you think I meant? You can't speak. 19?
Yowzers. You know what else people say? Yowzers.
Don't get mad. Little rocky. Why don't
they make like a gta or like a red dead type game
in caveman times?
I'll keep it and stay calm now. For mama she loved you so.
Just a shame you had to strangle her in her rage.
Grab two cases of that stuff and follow me.
Rockstar making a medieval europe game. I'm sure it would be amazing but
you know they can only do so many things. Although I can't say I'm too
sure how well they would handle melee combat.
Hey this is my brother Fenton. Don't mind him. Don't
Madden. Fenton? He's turned idiot. He killed our mother but it weren't his
fault. How'd you boys? How'd you boys like a couple of
bucks? I bet you would. I love Jose. Jose is awesome.
We're in the new trade of advertising. Which is an American art form about
ensuring people buy the correct things. I don't know.
One more dollar. Says give us half an hour. What harm can we do in half an
hour? Go along now. Enjoy the money.
Come on Fenton. Let's hand out the liquor.
Go behind the bar and let's see what. Cool.
Combat is fine in rockstar games with an S
with an S on it. That's my brother Fenton.
He's a bit funny but boy can he pour drinks fast.
For the next 30 minutes the drinks in this year bar
in this year town are entirely free.
Raise the bottle. Let's go. Pour it. All right take it.
Oh wait wait wait. Pour the bottle. How do I serve it?
Here take this one too.
You sure are playing the idiot role well.
Hey I'm gonna take one of these boys. I'm trying to put it down.
Okay so my boy Fenton can sure pour drinks fast.
Too fast one would say. I still have the same pipe in my mouth.
Are you sure this is alcohol and not like fucking like
molly? Like what the hell am I serving these people? Like ecstasy?
Good evening gentlemen. Quiet libation. You. Me. You're the bastards who stole
the liquor we was gonna buy. We're in advertising. Come on in.
It is moonshine that's right. Boys get them.
And just like that we had one more coming in.
Oh they're help. Uh oh. I don't know how to pour drinks. I don't know how to do
anything else. Jose Jose Jose Jose Jose Jose Jose.
Got him. What the fuck? I got him.
Ah there we go. Stairs. I can't move. I can't move. I can't move. That didn't
work. Please turn up your sensitivity.
Who the fuck? All right give me the repeater.
I want a better repeater than that. I don't have like a better repeater
than this shit. Is it on my horse or something?
Probably. Looks like they're about to until you
said that. More to my right.
Was that guy was that bad guy? Hey careful who you're shooting at.
That was not a bad guy. Well I mean what the hell are you doing standing
there? You need to get out of the way man.
Outlaws around. You don't want to be accidentally identified as an outlaw.
Because they're just either whoever's around I'm gonna have to beat it.
I'm being attacked from all sides. How dare he stand in town?
Well what it's just not only standing in town but standing just still
staring at me. I just yeah I got why he's got one shot.
How dare he look in my direction. Come on Arthur. We're gonna get out of
here Arthur. Doesn't look like it Arthur. Over
there to your left. Oh jeez Arthur. I'm sorry the guy
was looking at me. Well behind me is actually in front of us.
See look at these guys are just standing here. You understand that
those two guys are just standing around.
They just happen to be bad guys this time.
That was a bad idea.
Oh whoa whoa what was that? No these are not okay. That guy's
gonna be okay. Oh no he's not anymore.
Oh yeah you don't that's what I think that killed me is they hit the liquor.
Uh give me some tobacco. You see any more of them? Who thinks so?
Oh never mind never mind. Jesus all this over a few bottles of booze.
I reckon it's more they don't want another gang on their patch.
I was online. Something I'm gonna try again because it wasn't working very
well. Okay we'll give it a try soon here.
Another mission or something. We'll give it a go again.
Weird flex what? What?
What was it? Advertising. You think that woman set us up?
No I think so. Maybe. This place is odd.
I keep seeing those fellas. Some local militia.
Clearly not too happy to have some new competition. I'll go visit old mob
Braithwaite. See what's what. I gotta pee again.
The chest is filling up again slowly but surely.
Part of me thinks we just get ourselves good and lost.
But we still need a lot more money before that can happen.
So for now let me go give old Mrs. Braithwaite some of this moonshine as
well let's call it a peace offering. Sure.
This guy's old me.
I wouldn't mind. I mean he seems like he's pretty with it.
Play the entire Kingdom Hearts collection on stream.
So what do you think? I don't think so. About what?
Defying folks around these parts. Oh real nice.
Oh my god I'm gonna pull my ear off. On the one side we've got the gray family.
Scots degenerates drunkards the local law. You couldn't make this stuff up.
Rich is creasing. This thing is jammed in my ear. Wedged all the way in.
And I just yanked on it accidentally moving my butt around and I just pulled off my ear.
We believe in gold and in the middle of it all you got some
inbred retelling of Romeo and Juliet. Exactly. So what you boys thinking?
We try to rob them both.
Everybody in the camp. Why not? Because we got all men in three different states after us.
Last thing I want is to get us into trouble but we need money. Now we have
the opportunity here to put ourselves in the middle of something ain't nobody
gonna know we was here because even without us these fools
are gonna kill each other anyway. Okay well Hosea's gone back to see that
Braithwaite woman. Good Hosea should definitely take the lead on this.
I sent Sean over to Braithwaite manor too. Now you can meet up with them
or join John and Javier at the Gray's place. Something to do with the
Braithwaite's prize horses. How the hell did we get in at the
Gray's place? Sheriff Gray kindly put in a word with his father.
Can I have your ear? I'm making a voodoo doll.
We gotta convince each family that we're on their side.
Okay but can you not like do anything bad?
Can you do like good things to it?
Like can you put it in like a nice hot bath?
I mean make like a tiny little bathtub and put it with like nice
perfectly temperature perfect hot water. Just slowly just dunk me in
there let me relax in there right? Now if you will excuse me Arthur I
got to write a letter. Set it up on a little beach chair and
put me in front of the right in front of the ocean you know on the beach.
So put sunscreen on me and just let me hang out there.
What am I talking about? Did you not see the guy that just said he was
gonna make a voodoo doll of me? I'm telling him not to do bad don't
like stab me in the stomach with like knives.
I'm not paying attention to chat. Perfect I need to go hunting at
some point. I need to hunt I haven't done
any of that. I've done a couple legendary animals but not enough to do
any of this stuff. Thanks Pearson. I'm gonna stab a voodoo
version of you with a knife. Don't do that though.
Take it on vacation with you and put like sunscreen on me but from the
beach. Just great but I nearly got killed back in town.
They caught me robbing from a store and I ran for my life.
You weren't followed here. Arthur Morgan
Of course not. Who do you think you're speaking to?
Good girl. Okay I'm gonna make a terrible
kill. I'm not gonna say it. All right so who do we want to go to?
I mean I like I like Hosea. So Hosea is kind of where I want to go
because it's Hosea and why would I not do Hosea?
Let's do this mission and then I'm gonna try online again. We'll see if
we can get to work. Wouldn't that just be the size of
a regular pillow? At least give me the benefit of the
doubt of having being a king size pillow.
Please. Not now. Not now.
Can I leave please?
Get away from me. You make a twin size bed look like a
California king. You understand how thick my body is?
My ass doesn't even fit on a twin mattress guys.
All right come on horse. You sound thick.
Well thick as in like T-H-I-C-K. C-K.
What happened to online? It didn't work. It was kind of broken.
So we're gonna try again.
Like you can never say the word thick ever again.
Okay if you were at work right let's say you're at work
and you walk into your boss's office and he's like oh yeah you know can
you just give me a hand with something here?
You're like yeah yeah yeah sure. There's a stack of paper over there.
I just I need to just grab it from me. I'm currently I'm about to be on
the phone. There's like three stacks of paper.
One of them is a very large stack and one of the smaller stack
and you're like oh which one do you want? He's like oh the thick one the
thicker one. You're gonna go ha thick to your boss.
Is that what that word's gonna turn into? You're gonna get instafired in
15 seconds? Hey founders I'm with Mrs. Braithwaite.
My associates are already here. Why not?
Ego maniac thinks he's our boss? No I just said thick and you guys
damn I can't ride the motorcycle into the house. Is everything all right?
Oh yeah everything's fine. Please come in sir.
Everything's okay. This way sir. A gentleman to see you ma'am.
So your friend the other liquor vendor. Hello. Hello ma'am.
Arthur welcome. We're just playing cribbage.
Arthur Morgan. Mrs. Catherine Braithwaite. Nice to see you again.
Apparently. So this one he is big and as dumb as he looks.
Well he's surely big but his intelligence is a matter of some
conjecture. Some say he is as dumb as he looks but
I think well he's not quite that dumb.
So these other boys going to Caligahal. He's so sick of that.
We could take care of that for you but one hates to be coarse. There is
the question. Oh yes you see he is dumb. Oh we've got money Mr.
Matthews. Thick yeah he's also he's very thick and dumb.
Thick. You yanky numbskull. Hey childbirth just the most beautiful
mare on earth. Seems a lady. The young one says it.
Childbirth is gross. What? Ready let's get out of here.
Why'd you just say that? You was quiet and I took everything I had.
That son of a whore. Come on Morgan pick up the pace here.
I'll shove that silver spoon down his throat
and pull it clean out of his ass. A smoke fucker.
What she got us doing at the grand court. Oh that's gonna be a
bingo for me Arthur. She said it'd be fitting she did.
I don't think in this hell of a way quite fitting my boot up your hook.
No just snotty old bitch. Maniac driver.
Can I do one thing without destruction?
Um it's it's faster. I'm going to get there faster.
I just saved a good two minutes right there.
So far we've destroyed the break weight still. I'm gonna pay for those fences.
They're just invoice men.
They were saying oh for a second. His dialogue didn't even.
Grays English. You not worried about them grays.
And what sense? Well they know you.
Now what? I'm gonna hide in the wagon. I'll go hiding back.
If you can act now stop us from getting into a fight before we're
ready. I will try. You're going too fast.
Going too fast. I'm not going to go that far.
Change Arthur's point of view. Okay this feels so sneaky.
No I'm staying here. I want to be inside this.
We're here stay out of sight. We'll do the talking.
Okay just drink the booze. What you want boys?
I there was a ting a ting at the saloon. There was a ting at the
saloon. Well I'm delivering the supplies.
You want a bottle friend here?
I got really long arms. I mean you know I've come from Donegal
in Ireland. Yeah they said you'd understand
there's some kind of incident at the saloon in town. I was told to bring
this up here. Ask no questions I'll tell you no lies
Sort the business out. Is it just one guy?
Hey before the officials got there they said. Okay
drive this way I'll show you how to get there. Oh thank you friend.
Have a drink Sean. Do I have to hand him a drink?
All right I'm gonna with both hands as hard as I can grab his ankles
and pull him as hard as I can through here.
You've got a country you've got here. I'm not as fine as Connemara but fine
nonetheless. My people come from Scott.
Ted you and I are nearly brothers.
I'm kind of jealous. I feel like I belong up there to laugh and talk.
Just over here. Yeah straight down the path here.
It's getting so I can barely keep track of all these deliveries coming in.
Yeah and they said they was looking for more drivers in town.
I jumped at that chance. I never been there to kick a bit of honest work out
of bed. Is he floating? You folks been
having a hard time of it have you? Yeah Mr Gray's got a heap of problems
right now with another family around here.
No he's not. Much covetous lowdowns trying to sabotage his life here.
Disgusting. Oh dear oh dear I'm sorry to hear that Hamish.
Sounds like you definitely deserve that drink. No I'm not gonna
What are you talking about? Just in there.
Right you are. You can unload it here.
In here? The horse is like a swift one. Am I just gonna be in here?
Nothing. It's grand. Am I gonna have to
jump out and jump scare this guy and punch him in the face or something? How
does this not work? Quite a place you boys have got here.
Reminds me one of them big houses out in Dunnegal.
Real fancy places they was Hamish. Real fancy because if some folks got all
the money they can build quite the fanciest
places in the world. Well the average man subs on
shy yeah yeah yeah okay.
Take his hat. How you getting on? Good.
You already got these things ready. Okay.
It seemed like the quickest way. There's plenty of guards out there.
Here's how I feel. Should have shot him with a shotgun. No that's too much.
You head over to the dry barn. Sure. And you?
I'll deal with the fields themselves. We coat everything in moonshine and then we
light things up with these little fellers here.
Thankfully it ain't rain and that old barn over there should go up like a
torch. How many of these boys you think you
need? They should do it. Let's head out.
That'll do it. Look once they get wind of us
there'll be no turning back so move quickly. Of course.
I'm rebel stock boy. I was barb burning down manor houses.
Burn quietly. All right so we're gonna
torch the fields.
Sneak around. Which way are we going? Am I in his way?
I'm not fucking up his AI right?
Make him drink the moonshine.
You might as well take a sip right?
Were they? Were they? Were they alerted?
Quiet. There's someone coming on the left. Yeah and that guy's
god damn it. That noise. That was fucking loud.
This one didn't. Strange. But you got there.
Tools. Payroll. Okay. Payroll. That's the magic word there. Payroll.
Sure. See you later. You hear that? Payroll.
Yeah. Let's get this job done first okay?
I'll take care of this fella. No I'm just kidding. I'm not gonna do it again.
Joke. It's a joke. It's a joke. No I'm just kidding.
We'll be at the barn when you're done.
Going down fields will pull on it. We want chitchat.
We want shipping. Will you let me do this? He's not gonna let me do it.
When hiding among tobacco plants guards will not be able to see you as
easily. Okay how much do I have to pour?
All right that's good. Where is that guy facing?
Well he's facing this way. I'm gonna wait till he turns around.
Or will he turn around? Turn up the game volume?
Is he gonna just look over here the whole time? A lot of moonshine in here
apparently.
Okay yeah you just have to do it until he says he's satisfied.
So I'm gonna go across. Oh dear. Oh dear.
Okay this guy facing this way. Not for now.
I'm gonna wait till he crosses back again. This is the only guy that I need to
worry about. On this side at least. Okay.
Dump it. Music is dying. Angry goat music.
I gotta go across that way. I wonder if you
turn around. Probably. Not really. I could go to the left.
Or uh no I'm not gonna go now. Once he comes back this way I think he can
make it. Turn turn turn. Turn before it's too
late. Thank you. All right. Cause a problem over
here too. Turn up the mic. Who's mic? My mic?
That should do it. Long mission huh? One more on the other side.
Anybody else looking over here? Or can I just go right behind him right now?
Pretty sure I can get behind him right now. Yeah. It's gonna be a long
It's not something something Far Cry 3. Barn. I should be able to
wrap around. Should I go for it? It's uh no no. Should I go for it?
No he's gonna turn. He's gonna turn. I'm gonna get seen when he turns.
I coulda gone. No I couldn't. Do it you wuss. No I don't want to do this mission
again. I don't want to fail this. I'm gonna
have to go around him. Actually maybe not. I'm gonna just go
this way. Yeah. Just go wrap around now. Right
down there. There's no more guards around here right? Am I?
Nice. This a quick dowsing as well. Dowsing the guy? Just the guy.
Thanks you go Arthur. You too. Let's get out. Would you look at that.
Yeah well let's go loot yourselves a fat cigar.
Did we get it? Okay we got it. You almost ran into the field.
I did almost run into the field. You are correct.
We lost the horses. Uh okay apparently the horses are gone.
I'm right next to you.
Forehead yeah. Right in the forehead.
Now this is really cool though. It's uh interesting.
It is kind of hey get out and shoot the bad guys.
I was about to shoot a bad horse.
We did good. Let's go. Let's go. Looky here you get them horses free marker.
The horse is free. The horse is free. The horse is not free.
Free. Let's get the hell out of here. I'm just getting thrown off.
Right in the fire. I know I would probably absolutely do it.
Gotta leave them. Leave them. Straight out the main gate. Come on.
Oh we don't have to jump over those. Wow.
Wow.
At least the music is overpowering. Music's pretty good.
I think we lost them. Yeah we did. Quite a nice. I didn't read the whole
thing. What was the whole thing? The rest of the fight don't just put us
into the middle of here. I hope him and Jose are riding it.
There's some money at the end of it. What now?
Head on back to camp. It's loud. You coming?
Um yeah. Sure.
Turn the mic up. My my mic is currently uh actually it's funny you
say that because I am investing in a new
uh audio system. So I will be sounding much better than I could
weaker to because I'm actually going to use a
I have a XLR device but it's not necessarily like
compressor and gain and I'm trying to I want to get one.
I'm not going to do too much to it because I just want to make the audio
cleaner and be able to change on the fly easily
how loud or soft I am. So so I'm not going to really add that
much equalization or compression so I'm not going to sound
that different. I'm just going to be able to adjust it easier.
All right so what time is it? Is it time for us to try
online again? I think it might be where you can turn the volume up. The
volume is up as loud as it can go. This device that I have this plugged
into is not the greatest. I mean it's a
Scarlett Solo so it's good but it's really really hard to use.
The thing is incredibly finicky. I think I gave everything I needed.
Well I have $3,700 though. Yeah hold on.
Let me give them some money. Do this mission first? Okay
we'll do this last mission. I'm gonna give like 300 bucks
and is there anything new in the ledger? I don't think so.
I do need more provisions though. Let's buy it all.
Buy it all. Well I can't do anything. Everybody gives two bucks. Well I'm gonna
give more than that. Hey Dutch you uh you decent in there?
No that's not the front of his tent. That's the back of the tent.
Whoops. Wait what? Yeah no it doesn't matter.
Open the tent up. You don't you don't want me to come in?
Sit. Should I just wait for him? Dutch?
Uh what is wrong with his arm? What is he doing?
I can't walk in. I'm drying right now. Something's wrong with him.
Take his hand. Just grab his hand. I can't do anything. All right well I'm
just gonna. I just ate something. Whatever.
Oh candy. Are you sweating yet Dutch? Of course I'm sweating.
We're in some disease ridden swampy desy whistling shithole.
I meant about what Trelawney said about. I like it. It's got candy.
Such but maybe a little gentle perspiration.
Until we know more ain't too much harm in wasting good liquor on sweating.
So? So I think you should pay Mr Trelawney a visit and find out exactly
what he knows and who he spoke to. Take Charles with you.
You got it. Or the side of the pair of you would make a statue
sing out its secrets. Okay. Go to Charles.
Hey Charles. You and I are gonna be working together here.
Like your new home? Nope. Wrong guy. I won't miss that other place that's for sure.
Hey Charles. Keep your nose clean. I need you for some business in town.
Come on. Okay. Come with me. Why does the screen keep flashing?
I don't. I don't see anything on my end.
Hopefully that's not something wrong with your computer.
Is he coming? No. Where is he? Why do I think everybody's the same
character? What? Where am I going? What? Get on the
horse. Why is my game fucking up? What?
I can't get on the horse. Okay. That was weird.
I rode too close to the camp. Well he was on a horse. We were both.
We were hitched and I was walking right next to him.
That fool of a sheriff who runs that town. I knew Dutch was gonna play him like
a fiddle. Stop yelling at me. Working for
another. Interesting. All right. Let's do it.
I'm in plain sight. Dutch calls it.
We almost sandwiched that guy. Spirits seem good.
In the new camp I mean. We got some space between us and that mess now.
Ain't she? No more picketins for a while.
Got some corn.
Dutch don't seem too worried about it. I can't believe they're still coming
after us. We didn't even get away with the
money. Yeah but they don't know. So we'll try
online again after this mission. See if we can get another uh decent
session out of it. I've only met him a couple times but he's
he's a strange one. Feed Otto. He's just a cockroach and fancy
Otto ate earlier today. Before I started streaming he ate.
We just need to find him before we add some delicious dog food.
I think it's just up here. Easy. Recognize that one with the fire
outside. Wait didn't I? I think I jumped off this roof already.
Yeah I did. Search the caravan. Well so it seems. That's not a clue
but it's hair pomade. A clue. Spilt uh somebody spilled a plant.
You see anything there? Tactatactatacitus
Kilgore Mining Company Certificate. Interesting.
What do you think? This food's barely touched.
Looks like you have to get hurry. A little draw over here.
Nothing. Can't take the snake oil. What else we got for clues?
Nothing on the well. There is something else here.
No. Bed. Bed's not made so recently. What about the sink?
Bathtub. There's some blood here. Blood and bathtub.
But no body. Look. Okay right apple. Might as well take the apple. Never
mind. Chat demands to see Otto. He's
downstairs doing his thing. I'm not gonna go hey
come here dog and I'm gonna bring you upstairs and put you in front of a
camera. No he's having a good time being a dog
downstairs.
Let's follow the track. He's sleeping on his bed down there. He's
he's happy. He's very happy down there.
They could be 20 miles away by now. We can track them that far if we get to.
I'm alone. He was in here earlier. He still ain't sure. He has a very short
attention span. He gets bored very easily. So if
he's in here with me. Oh he's lying down on a bed or a
blanket back here. Oh okay. After two hours he's just like
get me out of here. I don't want to be here. I hate this.
And I'm like all right. I let him out and he just like has like this
zoomies for a little while. He goes downstairs and he hangs out.
Maybe he gets a little snack or something.
Where the tracks go? I think the tracks lead this way.
Well that I was going the wrong way wasn't I? Well I found him.
He's just right here. Excuse me. Yeah have you seen him? We're uh
we're looking for our friend. I don't think he's here.
Have you seen a strange sort of fella? Sort of formal?
Do Otto and Midas get along yet? They do. They're good buddies. He uses a cane.
Looks a lot like this one. That guy's getting up. He's ready to throw a
punch. I want him to throw the punch first
game. Interrogate. Where is he?
He's Trelawney. I don't know anything. No. Really. Yes. You go to hell.
Tell me now you son of a bitch. Okay. Two punches I'll take.
They took him to a cabin over by the cornfields.
Which cornfields? Left. Down the path there by Braithwaite Manor. Right
there. Okay. That it? You got any more info
from me? I should do it. Choke slam him. How do I make
the horse go? Whatever. I didn't mean- I was trying to
make him like run. That guy had 25 bucks on him. All right
looking for the the path this way. I think there's a way around so we
don't have to go through the Braithwaite's place.
Okay. I'll let you leave. I've spent enough time there
after you then. I'm good. What do you think they want with Trelawney?
Could be any one of a hundred things. Just depends if any of them involve
us. You think he'll talk? Of course. You okay over there?
I'm good. Tell his own sister to save a train fare.
He don't know how- He don't know. At least I don't think he does.
I don't know if he still deals with him. Always disappearing for weeks on end.
He's got his uses. Well loyalty matters to Dutch. Of course.
Dutch Vanderlin. Let me tell you boys something.
It's Dutch Vanderlin's voice. Nobody can do that voice.
He has the most distinct voice I've ever heard.
It's so deep. It's so distinct. I have a plan. No. I have a plan.
I have to be four or five octaves lower.
But the one thing about Dutch that's interesting is when he yells
he goes from this to- It's actually really funny. He's like now you get
those boys out of here and bring them to the other side.
I love it. It's so real. His voice just
breaks when he gets to a certain amount of power behind it.
His voice is too powerful. I love Dutch's voice so much.
If only I was that talented. When are we trying online again after this
mission? After this mission I'm gonna go take
a bathroom break and then after that
we'll try online see if we can get it to work. Another hour or two maybe and see
where we are.
This will be remembered like a good time.
Why don't I take the horse? No horse.
Should I shoot? Look and listen for disturbances in the cornfields.
Disturbances- I gotta look for a disturbance in the forest. Wait what's
this? What was that blip on the map that was
right here? What was it showing me? He's like go that- oh right here right
here. Thanks for being the- what do I do
with them? Set it? Do it. I gotta find the other
guy.
I saw the blip over here. Got him. Almost.
Close. To the birds. Birds? Down here?
That way Arthur! Idiot hat tunnel vision. Wait was it- we supposed to do this
together? No. Okay. He dumped his gear. He's
somewhere around here. He's dumped it. Where the fuck were you?
Okay. This is scripted.
Let me take him. Get out of here. He's not your friend.
I'll give you money. Be quiet. Ooh. Nice. That was a good toss.
Come on. You should have taken the money.
I'm a fool. Oh shit. Thank you. Of course. You okay? Yeah.
Fine. Charles that was pretty- that's pretty godlike.
How can they see us here? That was a warning shot.
They sense the disturbance in the corn. All right. I gotta put on the-
Let's go to the school fields. That works.
Let's go back for Trelawney. You all right?
That was easy, does it? Sure don't. Come on.
Let's go see how badly they beat up the slippery feller.
Wonder how much trouble he's brought with him.
Is that a good gun on the ground?
I'm gonna take a look at the gun on the ground.
It's good. I'm gonna take it. What is it? Rare? Whoa.
Rare. I saw rare. Lancaster Peter for rare
rolling rock- rolling block rifle. Rare. Okay. Don't I have
I'll have a bolt action. Well that's kind of cool.
Let me see it. Can we just get Trelawney and go?
It's engraved too. Weapon's clean. Well
that's pretty neat. I have to go- I gotta go put this-
upgrade this and get this all decked out, you know. Through the corn.
Do you need to get on my horse or you got a horse right?
Tactical engraving. Oh you can't with rares. Okay.
Mr Trelawney, where are you? You okay? So who was they? They were bounty
hunters. Attached to Cole Stoddermont. I remember
this guy. They weren't looking for me
per se. What'd you tell them? Not much.
I told them I was an intellectual. Come down here from Oregon.
Good job at the universe. Of course, they didn't believe me. Seems
you stirred up quite a hornet's nest in Blackwater. He made the reference?
Metal Gear stream? What do you mean Metal Gear? It might be best if I stay with you
gentlemen for a while. Can't go back to that caravan now.
All right Charles, you take Trelawney back to camp. I'll catch up with
you. Okay. Looks dumb and thick.
Bounty hunters. Inkerton's law man. Is chapter three incoming here?
More. Perhaps this is it now. We shall see I guess.
So we're still pretending to be, we are still pretending to be
law men. Okay so we are at the five hour mark of the stream. We gave
about two through about just about an hour
and a half in single player. Let's see if it was
enough. I'm gonna grab a drink. I'll be
right back. We're going to try to open up multiplayer again.
I'll see you in two minutes.