I got plenty of health. Dog food? HP up. Oh, wow. Okay. I already had pretty much full health anyways, though, didn't I?
What's down? What's this? Okay. Um... I... I'm a little concerned right now. I don't know what's going on.
Alright, left or right? Left or right? Left.
Brimstone. Whoa. Whoa, what? What the hell is this? What is going on? Whoa! Does that hurt me?
Oh, I lost a... Okay, should I... I'm just gonna go. I'm not even gonna pretend like I know what's going on.
Level 3, the caves. One. Alright. So I'm still this guy. You have to hold it down? This could be pretty deadly.
Oh. I don't know if I like this. Yeah, I don't know if I like this. You have to, like, wait before you can shoot?
Ah, it's not that bad. Let's keep going. I'd probably miss something in that room. If you, like, destroy the gar girl, you get $5,000.
Actually, this is pretty cool. I'm not gonna lie. Oh! Down or right? Let's go down. Oh, what do you know about my super stream beam?
What do you know about my super stream? I forgot those bug things are here. What do you know, Cauliflower Boy? You're done.
Let's get rid of those. Now, I'm wondering if I... I don't think I can waste this. I'm pretty sure I just have this forever until I die.
Which is... Someone just died right there, speaking of death. This is where it gets a little tricky.
I'm just gonna stand here. Oh, God. I don't want to die because I don't want to lose this. Get out of here. Get out of here!
Get out of here! Get out of here! That was the scariest thing in the world. You can't mess with my fire and brimstone, baby.
So, what I was gonna say is I'm wondering if I die... There's no checkpoints in this game, I don't think. There is not.
Can I open that? I can. Look at that health. No, I can't. I have temp... No, you know what? Now, screw the boss. I'm not going for the boss right now.
That's a bad idea. There could be some hidden secrets that I'm missing that I don't want to miss. Let's go right.
I'm gonna charge up my stuff beforehand. Ooh, I don't know how I just didn't get hit by that.
Okay, I don't have any keys. Let's just get out of here. I don't have any... I can't get any health.
Hopefully, there's something cool over here. Oh, dear God. Oh, my God. I'm gonna die. Oh, my God.
Oh, I have to hold the stupid thing down. If I didn't have to hold that down... Now I'm gonna get my ass kicked at the boss.
Shit. Die. Actually, there's health on the way. The key. I can open that item door now. That's a good thing.
How am I supposed to get that chest? I'm confused. How does one cross that and get the chest?
It's probably an item you can get that does it, to be honest. Shit. And here comes the pitch, and it's a home run.
I need to be careful here because I will die and lose everything, and then I will want to shoot myself in the face.
Pills here. So what? You just hit Q to use the pills? Yeah, come on. Get in a line like that. Just like that. Bang.
I can go in here. Okay, so here's the conundrum. Do I go in the room? Yes. Okay. Okay. Okay, we're good. We're good.
I get it. I get it. Oh, nothing. You maggot bastards. So the doors... So you get a chest, but... Whoa, whoa, whoa.
You have to do it again? Oh, God. If I knew that, I wouldn't have signed up for this deal. Geez. My God.
I bet you there's another one, too. I just really royally screwed myself right here. Oh, my God. Jesus. Oh, my God.
I don't think that was worth it, even though I didn't lose any health. That was not worth it. Gonna safely say.
But I do have a key now, and I can go into that item room. So I'm pretty stoked.
The binding of Isaac. Okay, item room. Yeah, item room. It's a guaranteed item. Why the hell wouldn't I do that?
Damage up. Blood of the Martyr. I got a lot of items on right now. I am ready to rock. So wherever you are... Oh, he's down there, I remember.
I've also got pills. So I'm ready to go to caves, too. And you can take that to the bank, wherever this boss is right here.
I got full health. Two hearts. That sucks, but you know, whatever. All right. Isaac versus Fistula. That's not disgusting at all.
Oh, don't worry. You're not disgusting. I'm not looking forward to this. Whoa. Oh, my God. Pills. Take the pills.
What? What? What is going on? No, I'm gonna die. I'm gonna die. Oh, that was so stupid. Hold on. Don't freak out.
You got this. Get the heart. Just get the heart. It's okay. It's right there. Nice. Nice. Okay, that was a minor freak out right there, but I did it.
And I got some lipstick. I don't really need range with this thing. It goes across the whole map. All right, let's move on.
Move on to the caves, too. Oh, this is gonna be nice. See ya. Can I beat this game? Please tell me I can just beat this game.
Please tell me I can just beat this game. TNT. Okay, let's go. Oh, my God. No, no, no, no. No, no, no.
God damn. So it turns out that that was not the best thing to do. I will get back up to that part.