Hey Fred. Hey Fred. What's up? How you doing? You doing good? How you been? You've been good?
Hey dude, can you play Elden Ring? I already beat Elden Ring. That was good. I know I said I was
going to do something else with Elden Ring, but I didn't do it. Me strong let's play did not happen.
Yeah, what is it? They have to, there's no way the DLC does not get announced
in the next few months, right? They definitely have DLC that's planned for next year,
right? Like 2023. It has to be. It has to be. How long did it take from Dark Souls 3,
from launch to the first DLC? A year? Year and a half? When are you going to do the axe
self-defense class? Play Lost Ark. Hey, can you start being EU friendly for streams? I don't
live in the EU, but I get up before the sun, so can you change your whole schedule to benefit me?
No, I'm sorry. I'm very sorry about that. Hey, can you do EU streams? I don't live in the EU,
but do it anyways. All right, we got some stuff to talk about. Things to go over. First of all,
let's go over what's going on this week. Okay, stop. This week, today, we got sorcery. Tomorrow,
probably sorcery. Thursday, hmm, something, something happening. Something happening on
Thursday. I won't tell you what, but I think something's going on on Thursday. You might
find very interesting. We'll see. We'll see. I'm very excited for it. We'll see. And then Saturday,
I'm going to tell you right now, Saturday is the day for Green Screen Part 2. I don't know
if I can even talk. Hold on, let me see. Yeah, okay. So it is happening on Thursday. I'll let
you know maybe in a little bit, because I don't know if it's been talked about yet.
So maybe. Maybe I'll talk about it. Is it a poetry night? No. Yeah, so let me tell you that I've been
feeling a little under the weather in a colitis flare. I'm having problems once a year or so.
This happens. It comes back maybe a couple times a year. And I don't feel fantastic. I don't feel
great. So we're going to do more streams this week, but less time. So we'll do like three or
four hours today, three or four hours tomorrow, however long the thing on Thursday is. And then
obviously the Green Screen movie night will be about four-ish, five-ish hours. So we'll do more
days, but less time this week. So we'll do about three days in a row here and then Saturday. So
should be good. Now where? Oh, where did this go? There. All right. So we left off in sorcery.
It's 11 p.m. here. I mean, hey, when you spin, the globe is big and the globe has lots of time
zones on it. 11 p.m. Where are you in? Germany? Green Screen movie night part two will be Saturday.
And we're going to do it Saturday night. Saturday night. Saturday at like 4 p.m. 5 p.m. Pacific.
Saturday night. Very cool. Very cool. Very cool. Very cool. Very cool. All right. You guys ready?
Shall we continue our story? It's been like a week, so let's refresh people what we're doing.
Where we were. Some things we did. I'll put the camera on. I hope it's not.
Hey, it's not. All right. Good. All right. So we left off. We were here at the halls of Vlada.
We still have the ape as the god. We'll give you a little look at where we were. Remember, we were
in this house here. We got chased through the alleys. We went across the document where I was
in the water. I almost drowned three times. Remember before that, we were through here
in the artist's quarter. The giant stomped on that guy's carpet stall and I burnt the whole
place down, I think. And then we rewound and I did it normally. Would you ever try psychedelics? No.
No, I'm too fucked up already. Like I've had this conversation about drugs before. I'm not. I don't
condone drugs like that. I can't do them. I would never do them. I would never try them. Ever. No
way. Too much. Way too much. And I think it is too much, right? You know, if you smoke marijuana,
you know, you have a few beers, right? Cool. But like, it's too much after that. Anything
after that's too much. At least that's my opinion on the whole thing. Remember, nobody believes you.
That's fine. I don't need to prove to anybody that I don't do crack. All I can tell you is,
guys, I don't do crack. I don't believe you. I don't care. That's fine. I don't care. I don't
give a shit if you don't believe me that I don't do crack. I don't have to like get on stage in
front of 20, 30,000 people and sit there and go, guys, I don't do crack. I promise. They're just
booing. Boo, you fucking liar. I just have to sit there and go, that's fine. You are free to believe
whatever you want. That's the whole show and then the curtain comes down. All right. So here we are
now. This is what it looks like. We're going down here. We're trying to get the poem for the door.
I'll show you the clues, which by the way, you can't even hear anything, but now you can.
Let's open up the, let's take a look what we got. Let's get that music going. All right. So we have
a lot of beeswax, a skull cap, two doses of blimberry juice, a bamboo flute, eight goblin
teeth, a giant's tooth, green haired wig, bracelet, a bone and a sun jewel. We've got a lot of items.
I still have my standard sword and here are the clues. North spell gate. Remember the North gate
requires a spell made of four lines. Without the lines, you will not be able to leave the city port.
The fifth noble, Shinva. Lord Shinva is the fifth noble. Korga. Remember this?
The ritual of Korga involves his three eyes, the left eye, right eye and the third eye.
I don't get a puke. If you don't, okay. I got it. Let me give a refresher on sorcery. Sorcery is a
choose your own adventure game. It's back in like the 1960s, 1970s by Steve Jackson. It is a fantastic
experience. One of the greatest, one of my favorite games of all time. We're doing it again because I
passed a million followers. So where are we going? Are we going to go through the arch? Are we going
to go to the halls of Vlada or are we going to go to the left port? It's up to you. Remember the game
is from 2013. Yes, and it's the first game that I streamed on Twitch. I passed a million followers,
so we're doing it again. This I believe is the gambling hall. The last thing we did was the
statue. I think I can show you. You go over to the statue, look at the pot, it seems to contain 20
gold pieces. We didn't take any money from this. People wanted me to, but I said no. I said no.
Keep rubbing it in my face that you had a million followers. Well, what do you mean?
That's what I'm doing. All right, let's get a poll. Any mods around or should I hop in the
chat and do it? I can hop in the chat and do it if I need to. Would you ever do an IRL gambling
stream while I'm doing a poll? All right, so we're going to go. This is one, two and three.
Keep that in mind. One, two and three. Here we go. Oh, a poll is already active. Oh, shit.
You didn't say no. I, whatever. I didn't say anything. You said that. I didn't say shit.
Remember one, two and three. Through the arch. One. The halls of Vlada. Two. The left fork.
And we are going to two. Here we go. Oh, do I still have my voices? Let's see. Does this work?
Work. Work. Work. Work. Work. Work. Work. Work. Work. Work. Work. Work. Work. Work. Work. Work. Work. Work. Work. Work. Work. Work. Work. Work. Work. Work. Work. Work. Work. Work. Work. Work. Work. Work. Work. Work. Work. Work. Work. Work. Work. Work. Work. Work. Work. Work. Work. Work. Work. Work. Work. Work. Work. Work. Work. Work. Work. Work. Work. Work. Work. Work. Work. Work. Work. Work. Work. Work. Work. Work. Work. Work. Work. Work. Work. Work. Work. Work. Work. Work. Work. Work. Work. Work. Work. Work. Work. Work. Work. Work. Work. Work. Work. Work. Work. Work. Work. Work. Work. Work. Work. Work. Work. Work. Work. Work. Work. Work. Work. Work. Work
Work. Work. Work. Work. Work.
And a bristly innkeeper are waiting to play.
We went all in. Oops.
Alright, so let's look at the tables.
First of all, oh how? What's going on here.
Crazy
The tables are arranged in different sections by the size of the bet and the number of dice to be played
Sad looking creatures move down from high stakes tables to lower ones
Brassy and bold creatures move up
At the two chip tables are the old man in the sailor
At the table with the ten chip bet, the innkeeper is waiting to play
The old man in the sailor have just finished a game
The old man must have won
because he stands, cracks his knuckles, and moves to the five-piece table.
The sailor ships down to the table with the five-chip wager.
It's the same innkeeper? Um, I don't know, it might be.
Cash out.
All right, that was fun.
I've, I've moved him around in my hands for a few minutes.
I'm out of here.
Uh, let's just, hold on, let's wait and watch.
You sit back and watch for a while.
The players on the tables form themselves into pairs,
and settle down to play in deathly silence.
The rattle of dice fills the hall like a clash of swords in a barrack room.
Nearby, on the five-stake table, the old man and the sailor finish a tens game.
Sailor must have won because he stands up, barks a laugh,
and moves to the table with the ten-chip stake.
The old man shifts down to the cheap table.
How many chips does the old man have?
I feel like this is a fucking math question in a math book.
How many chips did the old man come in with?
Okay, uh, the spin lady leaves the booth at the front of the hall
and makes a circuit of the room,
offering refreshments at the cost of four gambling chips.
The burly innkeeper buys two rolled-up flatbreads and devours them without looking.
That's four gold.
All right, I'll do it.
You buy a hill fox thigh and eat it quickly.
Someone curses from the back of the hall, but no one seems to notice.
All right, let's, should I pick a table?
Are we going to the big bet?
Or what, what are we doing for bets?
Should I just keep waiting?
Maybe, maybe a fight will break out.
Should I just cash out after watching the fight?
It's gonna be a fight, right?
It has to be.
You stand back and watch the players.
Over on the tables with the 10 chip bet,
the sailor and the innkeeper have played each other.
The sailor shifts down to the medium table.
All right, all right, pick a table.
At one end, games are being played for stakes as low as two.
Uh, at the other end, players are betting 20 on each game.
Most tables also offer long games with four or five dice each,
alongside shorter two or three dice games.
But not all the tables have players ready to play.
You look across the tables.
At the table with the two chip wagers, the old man.
At the five piece table, the sailor.
And at the other side is the 10 chip with the innkeeper.
I, all right, are we doing long 10 short two or short five?
I mean, I took 28 chips, 27 chips.
We gotta go 10.
It's the same guy.
You take a seat across from the innkeeper,
who you do not recognize from your travels through the city.
Okay, different person.
Let's make this quick, he says,
his nervous eyes giving the lie to his weary smile.
The innkeeper counts up five dice each and waves you to bed.
Here we go, swindle stones.
How about we lead at one, two ones.
Let's just fuck with them.
Three threes.
So I got one, four threes.
Call, oh, oh, did I get swindled?
What?
All right, I got swindled.
It's okay, it's all right.
It's all right, it's all right, it's all right.
All right, this guy's a good player.
This guy's a good player.
I got it, I got it.
Are you staying in Kare for long?
Two fours.
Shit, he started, okay, what about twos?
I have one two, he might have a two.
This is a bad start because I have one.
I'm going to say three threes.
Call it, that's fine.
There's no way you don't have one three out of you.
You got five there, right?
Holy shit, what?
There's nothing I could do there.
I'm actually in trouble now.
Two threes.
Say three threes and let me win this.
There we go, there we go.
All right, let's go for it.
There's no way, call that.
There it is.
We're coming back, we're coming back.
Oh, this is huge, this is a huge deal.
Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh.
Oh, that you think they're.
Oh yeah, you're already saying there's one.
Why don't I just go this fucking four, right?
Do you think he'll call this?
If I say there are three or should I go there?
Should I say there are four?
You think he probably has one, right?
He's going to call this and he's going to lose.
Call it, call it.
What?
No way.
So one, two, three, four, he must have at least two.
Shit, you have to call it.
I can't do it for you.
Call him on it, but he's probably going to have two.
Oh my God, I could have said six.
I should I was gonna say six. I could have done six. I was gonna do six. You saw me do it. Come on
There are two twos. Okay, call that shit. That means you have to have three. Fuck you. You don't have three
What the fuck this guy's getting insane hands. It's stupid. It's actually not fair. I have one of those two
Oh fuck off again. Do it again. Do it again. Do it again. Do it again. Do it again. Do it again
He got three insane hands in a row. I got so screwed. I really did. All right, let's start with one two two fours
Okay, let's do three fours. Call it four fours. Okay, five fours. Do you think he has two?
He's gonna call it and I'm gonna lose because that said we both have two then let's do it
Don't call it and actually might have got him. That means he has to have three. Let's call it. Just zap him
No, I can't just kill everybody. I have to be I have to win
Diplomatically, whatever this is. Listen, you couldn't let me win. Could you? Why we start at three?
Why are we starting at three? Oh, he started at two. What are you doing? Three ones?
He definitely has at least one one call it brief. Okay, so that means I have one don't call it shit
Okay, but does he have a do you have four fours? No, you don't. All right, we're getting that money back
Okay, so we're gonna do open with what do I not have right? Okay, so let's do one
I'll start with one the two two
Two threes two fours, okay three ones. He's definitely has him on
I wonder what he has I'm gonna say four cuz he might he probably has two
Well, okay, that's that would be an insane hand if he had if he had three fours, which would be ridiculous
And he does nope. Oh, thank God. Okay, I got it. So you've been to Vlada before no, you're a regular
I guess he only has two dice. So that's one three. Okay, so let's say
There are two threes which makes it physically impossible you have lost the game is over well one more round
But it's it's almost it's almost a 98% chance that he loses. Okay, so I got a one
one
one five two threes three threes
I have one he probably had no I have two four. Yeah. Sorry buddy. That's not possible you lose
All right with a hearty laugh the innkeeper hands over ten chips you now have 24
All right, I'm back to where I was I have I'm back to my where I started with change table in the hall
More food and snacks the sailor buys a snack pick an opponent. I play the sailor. I'm gonna play the sailor
This is for five. I think right. Oh, this is a this is a short game tips use hat puffs his pipe. Yoy
Ain't good
What you join the swarthy sailor at the table? He tipped his hat to you and puffs his pipe. You ain't good
He asks you merely nod and reply. Okay. What did he say? Let's start. Alright, so I got two
Two twos. Okay, really that means you might you must be well, let's say three then call it
Okay, do we both have to that's the call. Yeah, you're full of shit. God damn it. We both had to that's unlucky
Yo, ain't lot the car. Oh suck. You're in like car. Oh suck. I don't know one three
I mean, this would be accurate. So let's see if he does three. Okay, there's no do you do you seriously have to again?
Bullshit. Yeah, okay back to even start with
One one three two threes. Okay, that's your full shit. You had to have had him both cuz I'm a liar
I'm a liar. What are you gonna go with one five two fives? Oh, sorry for that's impossible
I take your money
Continue you take his last die away winning the game with a frown the sailor hands over five chips
You now have 29 he gets up and swearing colorfully
He marched out of the hall to find something to drink now
Let's go play the old man
Pious looking monk steps into the hall looks about and then sits down at the ten chip table a creature with only one eye gets
Sobbing and runs out of the hall. It seems it has lost the other eye in a bet
Let's watch once again you spectate in the corner of the room
You notice a gnome who rushes in through a crack in the wall
Steals something from one player's pocket that is gone again
Nearby on the tables with a ten chip bet the innkeeper and the monk have just finished a game
The innkeeper shifts down to the five-stake table follow the gnome
Should we go after the gnome? I think we run after the gnome. Why not? What are these?
We don't know what he stole you dash after the gnome curious to see what he has stolen
The crack in the ball leads to a path that heads out through a wasted area of fallen down buildings
You lose sight of the gnome amongst the rubble what? Oh, I'm fucking dead
This is a narrow dirt track that dodges around piles of rubble on either side of the street
Looks as though a gigantic boulder has rolled down the path crushing everything in its wake
Even the pebbles underfoot have been ground to a fine dust. There's no sign of the gnome at all
A few blueberries grow by the side of the track look at the berry plant kneeling down by the plant
You look more closely at the blueberries. They seem perfectly ripe and glisten with juiciness
But you do not recognize them smell it you lean in close and take a deep breath from the plant
They smell sweet and rich and quite enticing pick a handful
You gather a handful of berries a few are squashed in your palm as you pick them coating your hand with a dark blue juice
Taste them you shove a handful of berries into your mouth
The taste is sweet almost sickly a moment later
That is exactly how you feel and you look down to see your hands are turning blue
Your breath is short in your lungs. You are suffocating from the inside out
Thinking quickly you stick your fingers down your throat causing yourself to be violently ill you make a terrible blue mess all over the ground
But at least you can breathe again you gather your strength then get back to your feet
You leave the deadly berries and move along. How do I I got a cat? How do I cash out?
I have chips. Do I how many chips do I have? I don't have any money. I have 29 gambling chips
Maybe I could maybe I can cash them in go back and rewind. How many do I have left? 29
Cryptocurrencies the gnome berry wasn't worth it rewind. How many do I have to?
I don't know. Okay, I'll rewind so it was not here. It was here not the track
It was right after this right here, right? All right, I'll use it
I'll use it cuz I have to catch I can't just drive 30 gold. All right, I'm gonna I'm gonna cash out
I've got 29 chips or should I just play against the old play the monk pick an opponent
The monk seems to be on a winning streak. All right, we're gonna play the monk
The monk hands you your dice and waves you to bid. Oh, it's a two game. That's it. Oh, oh
I think we just start right off with two right cuz then he'll be like, oh shit
Do I just start right off with two ones?
I should just do one one if I do one one then he says two ones then he's gonna be like hey
I got a one or do one like one five or someone three. I'll do one one two
Call that that means no wait. That's a lie. It wasn't a lie one one two ones. I got a one two, buddy
Oh, that's the game you lose
Furious you gift you remain at the table. No five. All right, this is dead. This was better
This is easier win. Look at this. I got three here. Let's just start with it. Let's start with like two
Something I don't have let's go fucking three three twos
You know what I mean? Three three twos four twos like you have three of them idiot
You have to have you have to have like there's no way right? There's no way that you have three again
No, there's no way. Yeah, that's not gonna say it. I get twice in a row get out of here
My ten gold maybe
All right, good start. Let's go with like one five one four
I always can't see that as five because of regular dice two fives. Okay, well three ones call it
There's no way what an idiot what a bad play that was. Okay, four ones
You might have five ones. You definitely have two ones. You would not have bet that if you didn't yeah
I've always wanted to come here. This is where the best players in Kari come to play. That's right
You're looking at one right now. Okay, I've got let's go with let's do something
Wacky here. Yeah, two ones two threes three threes call it call it four. Oh
Really? No, you don't. Mmm
two fours
Three four. All right, so you probably you have three fours. Wait, don't call that
You're gonna have two aren't you? Yes, I win. So what do you she got two to one dice left, right?
How many does she have left that two? Okay, so one two two twos three twos. It's got played actually a good
I almost got in trouble there. Uh, there is one
There with his one
One one two ones done. All right, we're back to even with a frown the beggar girl hands over ten chips enough
Twenty nine. All right. All right, let's get out of here cash out
You had enough of your turn to cash your chips at the booth. Yeah cash out. I'm done
I made five dollars twenty nine gold pieces. I see you've come out a winner reply with a smile
You had one coin profit. No, I bought food in there. Okay, here we go
So plenty of ground to cover. All right, we're gonna go up or down. Well, by the way, this is up. This is oh so daisy
Where am I? I didn't mean it up. Okay
Up or down down takes us through here. This this is down down here up heads through this square
We were here before we were here before
We were this is where we were and then we could have gone up through this square
But we were up here before although we might be able to go through a different alley here
Then we're gonna go up or down. That is what the pole is up or down. I'll give you a big view
this is what you can look forward to going this way or
potentially this way few places to go looks we can go like this or
like this or
This if I go follow that gnome again or this
But that's not part of your choice
It's close, but it's not too close. So
Okay
All right, that's pretty that's pretty much it 70% say go down. So we're gonna go down. Thank you for voting
Okay, you fall. Whoa, that's a lot you follow the road
Around the side of the gambling hall to a wide open space laid out for a market
There are several stalls all selling the same goods. They're traders arguing loudly over who has the cheapest or best quality
provisions weapons
useful gear magic items the well
Okay. Well, I got I got money so we need to buy food. It's important
Browsing the stalls you find that food is reasonably expensive with the cheapest provisions being sold at three gold pieces each
One trader is also selling a wrap package of six meals for 15 gold. What's that come out to be? That's a great deal
That's a really good deal save like three gold, right?
But I don't but what if I run out of money don't buy food you turn the trader
Down the trader and move through the market. I think I can come back. Let me see what else is here
Let's browse the weapons take a turn about the armorer stalls
Mostly what is on sale is of poor quality or weaker than the blade you carry already
but two things catch your eye a hefty broadsword with a good solid grip and a bow with a quiver of
Silver tipped arrows a bow you lift the bow and test the string
It seems firm and responsive and although you have little use for ranged weapons
This one seems hardy enough the quiver is interesting it contains ten arrows
But each has a tip made not of steel but pure silver the armorer nods at you significantly as you discover this
Well, you know what?
No, the dead
Only silver can pierce the hearts of the dead and he adds in a whisper
six gold pieces I mean
Silver arrows, I'm buying it. I'd like the bow you tell the armorer
He makes a great fuss of packaging it up, but eventually hands over the bow in the quiver you pay him six gold pieces
Okay, what about the broadsword?
You look the broadsword and move your microphone up a little closer to your face
So you get that more podcast style storytelling voice perfectly balanced
Who's the sword maker not an antique either but made of brand new?
Eight gold pieces. Yeah, okay. I don't need it eight gold. No, thanks. That's too much
I'm moving on you found a clue. Oh cuz the silver shit do I lose my opportunity to buy food
It's okay. I've already eaten. All right
We're gonna browse magic items you scour the market for items that might be useful to you in magic
But find nothing except for one jeweler's stand which in amongst a lot of very expensive and overpriced jewelry is offering a sun jewel
For sale the exorbitant price of 15 gold. I already have a sun jewel
I already got it the trader's sun jewel is as beautiful as your own perhaps even slightly more polished
I don't need it now
Fuck off you point out the jewel a nice piece
But a fake in lower car a these cost ten I'll give you ten a nice piece
But a fake wait cuz I have one that's a fake the jeweler laughs softly and pointedly removes the jewel from your hands
It most certainly is not fake
But if you cannot see that then I do not think you are the correct buyer for this exquisite piece
You take one last look at the Sun Jewel sigh and leave it walking back into the market
Mine is fake is mine the fake you browse around stall selling useful gear and items for travelers and crump across tooth ring
You know, they look useful
The first thing is a tinder box for lighting fires
Though it will not work without tinder and the second is a bottle of snake bite antidote the tinder box costs two and the antidote
Three I'll take them both you pay five gold pieces take both items you thank the trader and move off into the market
All right. I got a ton of stuff. You're definitely gonna get bitten by a snake at some point. Yeah, I got a snake antidote. Okay
So we can go down or it's giving us the opportunity to go up again
But you guys did not choose up you chose down so we're going to continue to go down that that is what that was decided
You guys did not say down then up you said down
By the well beyond the market is a street of tall iron fenced houses
You're entering a rich district built in relative safety close to the wall on the highest point of land in the city
Few creatures live here and it would seem that beggars are not tolerated
The streets are empty and for the first time clean you pass a well with a pulley attachment built above it
But no rope you flick a coin into the well and wait for several seconds before you hear the plop as it hits the water
The well is clearly very deep suddenly from below you hear a woman's voice singing throw down one more coin for me
Two wishes will I grant for thee throw a fucking fireball in the well? Oh, wait a minute. Okay read minds
God this dump dump
That would be insane. Imagine that like I'll throw another coin down for me. Hey, hey, you can take the whole crate
That's funny. All right, you can do that
Mud create quit when I'm gonna fill the well with quicksand and like drown the lady
protect from magic
Throw down another coin for me one more for a wish for thee
Yeah, back it up right here back. Yeah now pour the cement in there
mmm
That's fucked up. Um, I don't know what to do. These are all kind of funny. I mean sauce makes sense
Dodd is funny too. Let's do dud
Cast the spell creating a mountain of gold and treasure would you tip into the well piece by piece?
The voice inside begins to sing
Deliriously giddy with excitement at so much wealth after a few minutes of this a hatch opens in the side of the well house
Which you had not noticed before a tiny gnome clamors out
he reaches down into the well unclips a rope from one side and attaches it to the pulley and then begins to haul up the
bucket, uh
What are you doing you demand but the gnome appears not to notice you it seems he is blind and maybe deaf as well
He continues to wind the pulley until the bucket reaches the surface of the well
All the water inside has drained away through holes in the base
There's a gold piece the gnome tips these out the gnome tips these out into a pouch
What's in the pouch though, right?
This is the same gnome that was stealing shit from the casino has to be it's gonna be probably ten twenty gold in there
Or do I wait and see what happens watch with a workman like air
The gnome lowers the bucket clips the rope away once more inside the well and strolls away up the road
The well begins to sing again now. I'm ready to work again one gold piece and I'm your friend
Shit, I wanna rewind. Okay, ask him what he's doing
Okay, the gnome tips these out into a pouch
The gnome has a pouch of money grab the pouch
you reach down and snatch the pouch from the gnome who jumps almost out of his skin and then
Scarper's for cover in the well house once more in the pouch you find your gold piece
Along with a giant's tooth that someone must have thrown in by mistake. We've got two giant's teeth now. Yes
All right. That was worth a rewind. I have two now, right? Yep. Okay. Thank God. That was definitely worth a rewind
I'm out of rewinds by the way
Whatever you've reached a wide desolate area fenced off by an overgrown iron railing
Inside tall you trees reach up to twice the height of the city wall beyond
This is the necropolis the city of the dead for those who pass away and care with enough money to ensure their bodies are not
Simply tossed into the water the road to the north gate passes straight through and offers you no way around
The main path is wide enough for
processions and carts
But leading off it are several smaller paths that wind between the trees and headstones to all different suburbs of the graveyard
There are plenty of places for things to hide here enter the necropolis
After the hubbub of upper caray the necropolis has a silence which is almost deafening
Either side listing gravestones crawl with small creatures
No flowers grow here. It is like the bodies give off poison as they rot
Everything here is dead. And yet this place is neither empty nor still the graveyard
The wind whistles between the tall trees the Sun is setting behind the wall
Look around you step nervously off the path and walk between the nearest tomes
Some are ancient headstones
Ty
Tilted to crazy angles and some of them fallen face down as though the citizens of this graveyard have been drinking since they died
Others are fresh neatly carved and clean of all moss and weeds
They sparkle in the moonlight as though cleaned by maids and waiting for their occupants to arrive. Okay
explore the newer tombs explore the older tombs or
leave the graveyard
one
two three I
Will run a full one two three again one two three
One two three, what do you want to do? This is a one is newer tombs
Two is older tombs and three is to leave the graveyard
Hmm, where do they want to go? Seems to be pretty
Unanimous don't say that we're gonna be going to the older tombs. Thank you for voting explore the older tombs
You leave the path for the oldest area of the graveyard in the corner nearest to the city wall
Most of the stones here are now mere rubble a few statues lie facedown in the mud
A tree has split through a carved stone coffin search for grave goods
Find the oldest grave or search for grave goods
All right
We're gonna find we look for grave goods you search between the ancient headstones for any offerings of grave goods left behind
These tombs are hundreds of years old. No one visits them anymore and offerings that were left have long since sunk into the clay
Find the oldest grave you soon find what looks to be the oldest tomb
It is a small mausoleum with a low roof supported by ornately carved pillars an inscription reads here lies
Lorag founder of Kare
Lorag the tome is a simple stone cabinet carved with the likeness of a man from centuries of rain and wind
You can make out nothing of it, but a long grizzled beard below the inscription is a longer tablet
But it is half weathered and covered in moss
open the tomb
Mini F, you know, I actually this weirdly enough. So I figured out what was going on
I didn't really figure it out. It's something to do with the game
Because have you noticed that when I streamed multiverses that not there was no problems at all
I actually did a test with the game open
I streamed this with just the game open and going it through OBS to the test servers and I dropped like
10,000 frames and I looked over at my like my internet and there was no drop frames through OBS. It was weird
So something about how this game is captured and I've I tried to make change a few settings
but yeah, I I was literally streaming this game to the test servers and dropped 10,000 frames and
The internet was up the whole time
It was just up the entire time and it was like I was streaming the game to the server, right?
So I it was like you're dropping a ton of ton of frames 10,000 drop frames, but the twitch
Application I use is like no there's no drop frames. What are you talking about? So it's something to do with the game
So I apologize for that or maybe it's a little bit of both
I don't know but let's go we even need frames
Antivirus software hates this game for some reason. I don't think that's you
I don't think that should be the problem, but it's not a big deal
We you might see it happen once or twice a few times, but it's a text game. So we should be fine
Yeah, let's go. Okay, so I'm going to I'm gonna examine the man. I did put a frame limiter on this game
I put to make it so it doesn't have just like that like the 5,000 frames being rendered
So I put a hard frame limiter on the actual application itself, but it seems like doesn't really help that much
I don't know. Okay, you look closer at the car of man, but notice nothing more
It is just an engraving of an old man in a serene death pose
If this really is the grave of the founder of Carr
The chances are he did not die quite so peacefully the eyes of the carved statue appear to be watching you
You clear away the dirt from the carved inscription
But you still cannot make out the words only trace their outlines with your finger make a rubbing
For a rubbing of the inscription you would need some kind of charcoal to rub with and you have nothing to do that
We can't do it. All right, are we go are we opening this and getting like?
Possessed by the the demon that's in here, whatever
I mean we're going in right you look for a crack to lever open the lid of the tomb but find nothing
Presumably if there was anything here to steal it would have been long gone already you head away from the tomb fuck
We didn't have the right item for it. I couldn't do magic
Shit. All right, whatever. I we're gonna go to the newer tombs. There are several tombs here
There must have been a recent plague on the rich in the city. They're scattered around in roughly alphabetical groups
explore the tombs of
anagile to ferret
Explore tombs of Goyle to nephrit Oxl to Tamarin Oaks
Oaks or two years
Let's start down here. You browse around the tombs looking for a name you recognize
But none of them catch your eye something flitters past your face a bat
This is a bat who cares
Alright, how about but wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, right?
Malus should we be looking for these names?
Corgo
Nick you're gonna be looking for these names. Let's do oxl to tamarin
You look from one headstone to the other a few catch your eye, though. You cannot immediately say why ah
Shinvas mausoleum you approach Shinvas mausoleum carved above its door is here of rest Lord Shinva
If noble of Kari here we go
The door to Shinvas mausoleum seems to be unlocked and as a crack ajar as though
Someone regularly came and went just in front of it is a ring of little mushrooms
Growing up against the front step of the mausoleum
Hell somebody here
How safe passage
Protect from magic sense danger big
grow in size
You just walk around huge
Just do big
Big or sauce. What would be okay? Why would I want to be huge here? I'm gonna do sauce
Cast the spell and your mind is filled with a clear sense of danger
Rising from the circle of mushrooms in front of you
Presumably they are poisonous, but you would surely not have been tempted to eat them anyway
So isn't the spell being overly cautious? I definitely would have eaten them. Look at the ring
You cross down and look at the mushrooms
They look highly poisonous not least because you cannot see a single insect crawling around or under any of them
Unusually the ring itself is also perfectly circular in shape in its center something silver glints a steak pushed into the soft soil
I take the steak you reach over to pull out the silver steak
But you cannot reach it without stepping inside the mushroom ring and your spell warned you against that but it's a shiny
Steak it's shiny metal do it. Anyway, I'm not taking it
It is too cold to stand still in the shadow of the wall. No jump over the ring
I'm so paranoid without this ring
I'm jumping over the ring you take a run-up and jump clear over the circle of mushrooms landing on the step of the mausoleum
I'm not walking through that nice magpie brain
Okay, shouldn't was tomb the air inside is freezing dust coats the floor urns line the walls
But there is no coffin the floor space is empty except for in the far corner where a narrow stone staircase leads down into darkness
fog
summon darkness
Dopp open doors
sap cause depression
Sun create light. Well, this is not dark. What else can I do all float in the air?
Okay, well will I use the Sun jewel?
Does it consume it or do I get to keep it? I don't know
That's why I don't want to use it
You cast the spell in the Sun jewel in your pack begins to throw and ebb growing brighter and brighter until it fills the room
With a pale but brilliant light that reveals the mausoleum for what it is old stone and dust and nothing worse for that
Your spirits soar. Let's go make a move skulls peer at you from the walls turn and flee go downstairs
Unafraid of what you might find below you make your way towards the stairs
But you must have stepped on some kind of switch as behind you you hear a noise and you turn to see the door
It's swinging shut try to block it run for it
Fuck it. You stay back not wanting to be crushed by the heavy stone door
It seals with a bang in the dark the echo of the slamming door circles the room your light forms a pool around your feet
Wait, this door did that or this way what door did that?
I don't need the coat the ape feel the door or catches. It was the entrance door
Yeah, make a move. We're going down the stairs. Maybe there's a way out below you head for the stairs once more holding your light
Out in front of you. I'm not leaving
Downwards you make your way cautiously down the ancient stairs into the dead earth
The walls are damp and there's a foul smell of decay
The only sound is a dripping coming from somewhere in the depths into the crypt you emerge into a large dark chamber
Lit only by the light from your Sun jewel a coffin occupies the center of the room
Covered over by dust and spider webs. It's a wait and watch you hang back taking a few breaths to ensure the room is silent
That's when you hear the sound a moan and a rattle of chains coming from inside the coffin
The lid is moving back
Push it closed
It's not like a boiling over a pot of like spaghetti. What do you mean? What do you mean put the lid on it?
What are you talking about? This is like a 5,000 year old demon person. I'm gonna stay back
You hang back watching and that's when you see the ghostly figure emerging from one of the owl cloves in the room
It is a death Wraith
wielding a cruel hooked dagger and
sliding
Mercilessly towards you death Wraiths like all ghosts can only be harmed by weapons of silver
But it is quite capable of causing you harm. Thank God. I brought the fucking arrows attack
What can I do on hot fireball?
God
Illusion of worship. Oh, I couldn't pretend to be a god
yak fear
Hell should I read his mind? I wonder what it's gonna say
Kill kill kill kill. Like why would I do that?
in summon a replica creature
Kid create an illusion
Wall invisible wall walk his shield
Just use the arrows
Hell does not cost stamina
You put on the skull cap and cast a spell reaching out to find the thoughts of the creature and perhaps learn something to your advantage
But you find nothing there is nothing and no one alive down here only specters shadows and death you hold on
Attack you stagger back to clear enough space to ready your weapon fire an arrow
Working quickly you unsling the bow from your back and notch an arrow the death Wraith grins with abhorrent glee
Until you let fly and the arrow strikes it in the arm it howls with pain
Shocked and angered at being hurt again. What follows is a terrible fight with every arrow you fire the death Wraith
Stagger is back
But as you reload the bow it creeps near again slashing at you with its knife as the quiver starts to run low
You know each arrow counts and should and should even one miss then Shinva's tomb will become your own as you reach for your last
Arrow the death Wraith beams with glee it is weakened
But still not defeated fire the last arrow you fire the last arrow aiming directly for the death Wraith's heart
The boat flies true in the silver arrowhead buries itself deeply into the specters being it begins to flicker and fade and then with a last
Tortured gasp it slumps to the floor and threw it melting away into the cold stone
The crypt becomes peaceful as the battle ends
But then there is a creaking sound that makes you look back at the coffin it has opened and a figure is rising up
You watch as the figure takes shape a very old man and no monster
Stranger I am in a great debt to you now at last I can die in peace
Tell me quickly before I am lost how may I repay you you stare in amazement
This must be the fifth noble Lord Shinva himself you step forward to greet the apparition
Oh, this is important. You are Lord Shinva. I have come to find out about the North Gate
I'm looking for the first noble. I required nothing of yours
I've come to find out about the North Gate you come looking in a strange place
Then the only gate down here leads to the underworld and I have been denied it for a very long time
Time
What do you know
Are you Lord shit fuck what a terrible thing would be nothing you are Lord Shinva
I'm looking for the first note. Wait, hold on. Don't move. Let me look at my notebook. He's just like
You he's just disintegrating and I'm like flipping through my notes. Wait, wait, wait, wait, hold on a second. Um
the first noble is
Sansa's and um
Lord shit fuck
What do you mean Lord shit fuck?
Okay, only Lord Sansa's knows the whole thing
Yes, it's me Lord shit fuck
Okay. Okay. Okay. Okay. I'm looking for the first noble of the city
I'm looking for the first noble of the city that I hope your mission is to kill him
The first noble will bring this city to wreck and ruin if that has not happened already while I have been down here
Tell me
This car I still stand nah, dude
It's fuck shit got fucked up like 20 years ago. Does it still stand? Should I say for now?
I feel like that's like hey, give me some info or should I be like, it's fucked up. It's over
I don't know what to say. Yeah, honey to pull
I actually don't know which one of the what does what so one two or three one two or three one two three
Cuz he's crumbling right now. I don't know give him peace
Yeah, what I have to say is no and it's all your fault he's like no
Okay, one two or three this would be quick that would be wicked fucked up
Yeah, it would be all this dude's just turn around just open the window behind him and look out and be like it's fine
How dare you? All right for now everyone's saying for now for now for now for all right. All right
All right, all right for now for now. He nods you shall see what follows perhaps
I will not I met a fortune teller once
a woman named
Cirici and she showed me how Sansa's would bring the city of fire and destruction
It was this knowledge that led to my fate of course such as the way of fortunes
Trickles of dust rained down from the roof of the crypt, but you are Lord Shinva
I am oh, I was once the fifth noble of the city. Would you believe?
And you who are you? I'm a stranger
I'm from Anna land Shinra raises a dusty eyebrow. I know what interest does Anna land have in the ways of Kari
Hmm. I traveled to the backlands
I see so you need to pass through the North Gate and for that you must know the spell
Perhaps you know it already. No. No, I do you know it. I tell me it. Do you know what it is?
No, I don't know it. What should I say? Do you know it? Do you know it?
I know one line one lock made of golems hide
I wish you luck finding the others but tell me what lies in the backlands that Anna land could want I explore for myself
Mampang and the crown of Kings. I mean this guy's about to disappear. Thanks for the line. I got what I wanted
I'm here for the crown of Kings a crown. What of the crown? It has been stolen. Oh
Then today is a good day to die
Crown of Kings is an ancient object you understand from a time when the world was young and great forces
Stuck the land force is too great
But such as we are today powers that could shape beings and minds with the slightest whim and mold the land and see to their will
Do you understand what the crown does it provides influence? It allows control. It is nothing just a symbol
It provides I think it provides influence provides control dead guy voice
Influencer crown it provides influence. It provides influence much more than that
Only once was I in the power of the crown as it passed from lend the land to Bryce
I was an envoy at the court when it arrived and as the power to turn your will to
Another's without you knowing what is happening. You see the power of that
No one under the influence of the crown can ever revolt as they do not understand that they are in servitude
What can you tell me of the backlands very little? Oh, but I remember one told to me in my crib
Will you hear it? Yes, please tell me for sleeping of the sleepless ram seek out the one they call the sham
Shinva shakes his ancient head
I could not tell you what the sleepless ram is perhaps device and not mere nonsense
Your light flickers for a moment ready to plunge you into darkness. Farewell old man. Farewell stranger
May your life and fate be better than mine the spell lines you have found are listed in the key section of your inventory
Finally with a withered finger
He directs your attention to a gnarled rope that hangs down in one corner of the room that controls the trap on the door
And he's gone
RIP shit fuck that's just bugleberry
No, it's they're different you slash the rope with your sword a heavy counterweight falls and shatters to the floor
Lord Shinva nods wait. He's not he's still here. Well, she even nods and drifts towards his coffin
I give the last of my life to you
You feel a cold strength flood your veins and turn quickly and make your way upstairs
Nice the door at the far end of the mausoleum is open step outside
You return through the open door to the path still shivering from your meeting with a ghost. So hold on. Okay, where's my?
Victorious noble Northgate spell. Do I have this like the spell anywhere? It was just the clues the keys
Okay, that's Shinva's line one lock made of golems hide. I have a bunch of other clues too. I need three more
We have enough. We have a lot of clues for the other ones. I think
You avoid the ring of mushrooms as you leave
Outside night is falling and things are stirring between the moaning trees
You would do well not to linger here so scurries across your foot and is gone. All right, we're up this way
Leaving the graveyard you return to the path gratefully and make your way to the far side of the graveyard
Beside the gate is a disused well
Perhaps once used to draw water to wash the bodies before in turn mint look down
You lean over the side of the well house to peer down
It's pitch black of course and seems to go down forever and for a moment
It looks as though there is something in the shaft but a moment later it is gone a trick of the moonlight
Perhaps pull the bucket up you turn the winch on the side of the well drawing up the bucket from beneath
It comes to the top filled with clear water
Is this as fresh as the water from the other fountain you tried?
Frank you scoop a handful of water and taste it despite your surroundings. It is fresh and quite clear
You like a 20 health throw a coin in you toss a gold piece in it falls for a long while and then you hear a
Distant tiny splash the rear gate of the graveyard hangs from its hinges, but not from age
It seems it has been taken apart
Maybe widened even to let something through beyond as a deep forest when's green screen movie night part two Saturday
Saturday this weekend. We're gonna do it again this Saturday. Yep. Yep. Yep. Yep. Yep green screen part two
All right, let's keep moving. It'd be another
one to
130 150 videos you walk for half an hour through thick trees along a narrowing track
Until you reach a fork in the road to the left the track gets narrower still to the right a massive shadow looms
so large it seems as though a colossus has seated itself on the wall and thought a
Chill wind blows through you as though ghosts walked back and forth this way the shadowy
Thing to the right has a jagged silhouette
It's a ziggurat with perhaps a hundred steps leading to its apex the trees whisper and move
Looking left you see distant flicker torchlight through the trees the north gate
Perhaps night is drawing in you should get moving things whisper between the tweeze
The ziggurat or the road to the gate one or two
Let's get a pole going for one or two one
two
One leads up to the gate two goes into the ziggurat one two two for the tiger mount
I don't know that's a reference to is that a wild reference all right. We're going to
Thanks for voting the ziggurat
you stand at the base of a towering ziggurat built from carved stone blocks each the size of a hay bale the temple rises higher than the
City wall and position to catch the first star of evening at its uppermost point a moment
Which is just passed for an opening you tilt your head back looking for an opening and finally make one out a
Small black dot about a third of the way up
But even that is quite some climb for the less devoted worshippers a small gargoyle by the steps has an open mouth
Ready to accept offerings climb up a look at the gargoyle the gargoyle is carved in the shape of a small but spiky dog
With long claws sharp horns and a pointy beard its mouth is wide open and its tongue
Lawls out with a coin-shaped slot at the back of its throat
You need to take attack the tail
Okay, so drop in a gold piece you slide a gold piece in the gargoyle's mouth for a moment
Nothing happens then it appears to swallow and next it opens its stone eyelids to reveal two crisp and beautiful eyes
Look into the eyes
Looking into the gargoyle's eyes fills you with a sense of calm and peace
The eyes closed after a moment, but the sense of well-being remains, or did you just imagine that the gargoyle moved?
Oh, what should I do climb make a move make a move you have a healthy fear of Kari's weirder gods
You return to the fork. Oh, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, that's not what I wanted
That is not what I wanted. Let's do everything the same way did it
Okay, climb up you begin the climb hauling yourself up the first step either this ziggurat was built for giants or
Ascending as an act of devotion the next few steps are equally exhausting you have to throw your pack up first and follow
I think I remember doing this last time
Zen hover. Yeah, I think I remember doing this
Sun create light. Yeah, we can do big and just yeah, we can do big. Oh
Sauce is good is there too. What else?
How is interesting safe passage?
Float in the air is a good one. Are they both one? Yeah, I remember doing big before
Let's do it. You cast a spell swelling to three times your size. You are now able to run up the stairs
But the scale quickly changes
It seems the builders of the pyramid created an optical illusion and the later steps are not as high as the lower ones
The change is so gradual that you hardly notice as the spell fades
You reach a halfway point almost as high as the city wall beyond and pause to rest halfway up
You're halfway up
breezies of gargoyles and polished metals ring the temple on this level view you pause to take the in the view
from this side of the ziggurat you can see nothing but the top of the wall and
Beyond the gleaming darkness of the marshes of the backlands walk around to the north walk around to the north
You move around to the north face. You can see the path ahead running straight between wild and overgrown trees
It seems very few people come this way anymore. The north gate itself is now visible
However, and appears deserted then you notice a point of light torches been lit between the trees
Watch the torches you watch as the torches move through the trees towards the path. They're making slow progress
But they are moving towards the graveyard and presumably from there on into town
The wind claws at you trying to pull you to earth. I haven't eaten. I only have one revision
I'll eat it at least away from the rats and night foxes that live on the ground
You're free to eat you take out the last of your cheese and I still have cheese
You still I still have cheese from like three months ago. However long it's been. Okay
Let's go higher you continue the weary climb to the first level of the ziggurat by the opening
You climb for another 20 minutes up the steep stone steps until you are gasping and panting for breath once more
But finally you reach the dark opening that you saw from the base of the temple
The steps themselves continue up a little further still to the very peak of the temple
The opening is guarded by rock sculpted images of unimaginable creatures
Beyond you see a long dark hallway with something large and gleaming at the far end
Treasure I mean
You step into the temple the hollow space
Amplifies your footsteps and they echo eerily for several moments on the floor in
Guilt inlay is written the name of the god who inhabits this space
It seems that the ziggurat is of corga the gracious don't wait. I have something on corga
Corgas three eyes the ritual of corga involves his three eyes the left eye right eye and the third eye in his forehead
That it I think I remember this
Yeah, I remember this I forget I forget everything. Okay, let's wait
You wait for a few heartbeats to see if you have disturbed anything
Nothing happens and you catch the tail of a gigantic snake
Slithering across the floor and disappearing into a crack in one wall for the markings along its back. It's highly poisonous
Drink my snake antidote. I didn't get bit yet. Why would I drink the antidote? I didn't get bit drink the antidote
Why would I drink it now? I haven't gotten bit yet
Free antidote. Let's go. Oh shit. You went to the temple, but the snake still manages to catch you by surprise
Launching itself from a crack in the ceiling behind you
All right, we're going like eight. Oh
Come on
Temple snake snaps and hisses in the air between you you swing out
Wildly hoping to chop it in two as it slivers away and do around a pillar out of reach
It lifts up bearing its mighty fangs dripping with poison. Oh fuck you you drop into a crouch the temple snake strikes
You desperately defend yourself against its poison soaked fangs. You fall badly as you stagger back. It hisses from the darkness
All right, so they just went full blast. We're gonna go like two like two point. Yeah
Good
Now we go full blast. It spits in the gloom. Is it can I get it and get it?
Yep, dead
Temple snake is retreating but you give chase you cleave the air with your sword with a weird scream that echoes around the cold stone
The snake dies its head crashing to the floor
You wipe your sword clean and wait for the violent echoes of the fight to fade away
Then you go further in the side of the shrine takes your breath away
The walls are decorated with brightly colored murals depicting scenes from the religious mythology of Kare fine ornaments and precious metals
Are set into owl cloves around the pews and rich woven tapestries cover every surface a cunning trick of architecture
catches the wind past the doorway and
Creates a constant ethereal humming as though a crowd of monks sat in permanent meditation inside
Leave further in at the far end of the hallway for large stone gargoyles of winged demons watch over the shrine
from mounts high up in the eaves
Guarding the altar on which a gigantic idol squats
Corga himself. It is a life-size version of the model of Corga you saw in the abandoned house yesterday
Steal something approach the altar. I'm not gonna steal anything. This is the dumb thing to do
This is how you get the wrath of the gods
I'm approaching the altar you walk up towards the altar across a richly patterned carpet something about it gives you pause
Its surface is decorated with wide symbols that seem to deliberate
Too deliberate to be accidental walk across avoid the star shapes avoid the circles avoid the spirals cast a spell
Can't we know
Zen is float
How would be good right what but that's too literal isn't it?
Wouldn't it just say turn around and leave yeah, it's gonna say turn around and walk out the door remember
How is completely literal it's just how to find a safe passage is out
It's not gonna be like oh the carpet do this that no it's gonna go leave turn around
mmm, I
Could float I'm just gonna float over it
Cast the spell reducing your weight to that of a feather you should now be safe from any pressure traps and just go across
Relying on your spell to keep you safe you step forward across the carpet towards the idol
But it seems whatever trap is here does not require much weight to be triggered
Something happens although you cannot be sure what one moment you're in the temple of corga and the next you are falling what
What are you talking about?
You're floating slowly down through the air turning and over you're in pitch blackness. You cannot see a thing no
I'm in the sewer again. No no no no no no no no no I can't rewind let me rewind
Can I let me rewind please I don't have any more rewinds left, but can I just go back?
I want to do that I used them all can I go I want to go do that can I go do it you made your choice up
Okay, all right run a poll can we get can we get a chat's choice rewind it has to get at least if it has
To get at least 50% to be yes has to be at least 50%
That's so easy to get to all right. I'll make it harder at least 70% save scum
I know, but I want to I want to go do that. Okay. I just got like thrown across the whole game
I just went into the air and floated and the God was just like no dude. That's not happening all right
That's at 76% just walk back there, bro. That's so far away sure
Can I can I actually get back up there? I don't think I can I don't I actually don't think I can get back up there
And I think it's gonna be great out. I can just keep going
Yeah, do can I actually get back up there when I get out?
Okay, okay, you cast the spell and a clear calm voice enters your mind and informs you
There is indeed a trap in the rug in front of you before it can tell you where a second presence enters your mind
Booming it declares make your choice worshiper
Corga himself perhaps avoid the stars the circles of the spirals
The circles avoid the circles all right
I'm gonna go avoid the circles you walk up to the altar stepping carefully around the circle in the carpet and re yeah
All right. Yes, we made it you stand before the idol a fat statue set with gems and curious pock marked features
Above his head is a plaque that bears an inscription read it
Reads on corgas face you kiss across and finish with the lips
For answers to your questions you must err not else he spits
You step nervously up the steps until you are below the great statue you consider the idol
It is the same as the statuette in the abandoned house
Except that had blue dots painted on its two eyes its third eye in the forehead and on its lips
Okay on corgas face you kiss across and finish with the lips for answers to your questions
You must err not else he spits okay, so don't ask a question because he's gonna literally spit in your face
So we need to on corgas face you kiss across
Finish so you do the you kiss the lips last you stand on tiptoes and lean in preparing to kiss the statue
But where does the humming in the temple seem to be getting louder I can pray to the ape
Imagine going into another God's temple and putting your hands together and praying to your God and my God is an ape
This is like an all-powerful
Like super demon God I have this I have like a monkey. That's just to hang it out looking over a cloud
But what is the ape gonna do here? That's blasphemous should I pray to the ape?
I'm gonna do it for fun
You try a prayer to the ape for guidance, but it seems in the temple of another God the ape cannot hear you
You're on you're on oh
Okay, all right
It was it was a cross right and then lips last
Ritual of corga involves his three eyes left eye right eye in the third eye in the forehead
So what we go left right forehead left right forehead left right forehead lips or left forehead, right?
Let's go for it left eye. It's the left eye first
You place a kiss on the idols left eye you hear something flittering in the upper levels of the temple kiss the idols right eye
Next you kiss the right eye kiss the idols forehead. It's the idols lips
Finally you lean low and kiss the idols lips as you straighten once more you see the idols eyes flick open a soft voice
issues from its mouth
Stranger you are not of my faith and yet you have completed my ritual. How can that be?
I merely read your instructions. I'm lucky. I've merely read your instructions the gods laughs softly
Graciously very well. I see you are modest if impolite
My reward is to answer one question
But I am the god of grace and I require my followers to show grace and you have not I can see all
Remember, I am a god and I see that you have committed murder a red-eye guard
So I deny you my aid as you denied others their lives
His voice rises from a gentle whisper to a rolling thunder that echoes around the walls now leave
Or I will repay you in kind
What get the ape down here? Oh, yeah. Oh fuck you. I got the ape. What are you gonna say that?
Yeah, fuck you Corga argue you deny me my right you declare I
deny you
Everything
And then the idol moves standing gracefully onto its two bow legs and leans forward tag the monkey in do I run no
Let's fight this motherfucker. I look I've got beeswax. I have a helmet
Drive run what you can't kill somebody if you kill people you can't do this
I don't remember this breeze before you can react the statue of Corga plants a mechanical kiss on your forehead
You hear the click, but you do not feel the sting of the poison dart as it enters your skin and burrows into your brain
Okay, whatever
So I just have to leave I can't what am I supposed to do?
I have to leave I literally might as well just rewind back to when I was in the sewer
I should have stayed in the sewer then is there anything else I can do here. Okay, I am I've read
I've read your instructions. Oh, you killed people. Oh, I
I'm gonna repay you in kind fine. Fuck off leave
You don't need a second warning you turn and hurry out of the temple for the god can get revenge
What a fucking crock of shit you're back by the opening in the temple what I killed a person
So I'm not allowed to have a god
Help me go back up. Oh
Wait, yeah, I can go to the top right right right. Let's go up top
All right climb for the top you turn back to the steps and climb higher
All the way to the top of the ziggurat night has fallen star spread across the sky in a peaceful repose
That bellies their true nature
Warring spirits tussling for control of the world below. Look at the stars
With your head tilted back. You can see more stars than you ever have seen in this city
Perhaps you are above the level of the lights and the smog and the dust or perhaps more stars choose to cluster here
around this sacred site if
You were a true mage and not a mere sorcerer who knows what spells one could weave at a spot like this
You lean back and look up trying to recognize the stars from your studies puke
Tar have I learned anything
Have I do I any info?
Did I get any info? I might have I don't know zip are
res
Zed I would have had to have known it the page at the beginning had CA
That's right that the lady took it didn't she is there a CA here?
Let's try there's no see
Pu per I know that there's a few combinations you can actually do here and I am not I don't
Her is good. There's I know there's at least three or four you can get from this
Should I do per puke? Should I try per?
What does purr do?
Her all right. I'm gonna try it fashion stars into alignment and an enchantment is created
For a moment nothing seems to happen and then a screeching noise reaches you
From the distance and across the city. It is the sound of a thousand mewling stray cats
It lasts a few minutes and then fades away you found one of the secret spells of the temple of corga
What I can summon a thousand cats
You look out across the city in the far distance you see torches in the woods towards the north gate
Looking back you see the lights of caray coming on and the shouts of revelers drunks and nighttime thieves
The view is quite run. It's wonderful, but your journey beckons you start the long climb back down the ziggurat once more
Hmm, let's go the climb back down is going easier halfway down you pause to rest
You look out to the north the thick trees are still lit by torchlight and you hear the distant bang of wolves
Half an hour passes nothing changes except the sky grows colder and the wind picks up cutting through your cloak wait
You settle down to wait on one of the stone steps watching as the line of torches fans out through the trees and
Marches slowly forward as some disappear new ones are lit
But eventually after the Sun is finally gone and the stars come up above you the trees around the north gate are inky blank
And there is no light except for a single flame on the gate itself
The way through the forest should now be clear. Oh, that was this that was going this way. Okay, so now that I was looking at this
There's a bunch of torches, right? Okay. Okay, work the mud under for to stamp with footprints and in between them the Prince of
many paws
The road to the gate you walk between clawing trees and thick bushes
The north gate is finally in sight
You can see it's imposing or nately carved wooden doors
Over the top of the guard huts and low buildings that lie at the end of the road you pause to watch the guard huts
They seem quite still one has a hole in its roof weed grows through the chimney of another are they abandoned?
But before here in there is a long road
Lined by thick and gloomy trees a patch of wild forest like you haven't seen since the hills go cautiously
You make your way slowly forward trying to ensure your feet do not crunch too loudly on the gravel
Something is keeping pace with you just behind the tree line stalking you stop and look you stop and turn to look into the trees
There's the faintest flicker of a gleam
And that's all the warning you get a wild bristlebeast leaps up from the trees and knocks you down you scramble for the sword
Set right here. Nice
start
Do it again
Got it again clean
We're gonna go again
2.1. Oops. Oops rewind rewind
I think I have enough
Okay, that's fine. I have to defend now
Drops its jaw. All right, it's coming in. Oh fuck off. It's coming in now. I have to defend again
That's fine. Now I go full blast the bristlebeast hunkers down
Got it leveling your blade you strike backed up against a tree
You can barely swing your sword, but you muster all of your strength with a final swing
You bury your blade deep into the bristle beast it twists on the metal then curls up like an overheated beetle and dies
The night air falls silent once more you continue on quickly through the trees. You're at the north gate
You've reached the north gate the ground before it is wide and clear and lit by blazing torches set into brackets
Either side of the enormous sealed doors should there be archers hiding in the shadows
They would have a clear sight of you off to one side as a well, but there's no other cover
You don't know all the spell lines, of course, but perhaps the gate will open to adopt spell after all don't have all the spell line
I will tell you guys
I know what happens when you get to the door and
It is not up. It does not work. I have one spell line
It'll work clueless. It'll work huff blow it down
This how
No, no, I okay. I think I'm trying to remember how this plays out
I know how it plays out, but I don't know how you get there
I'm gonna wait or I'm gonna stride right over to it. Can I do per?
No, but yeah, I can't do per I'm gonna just I'm gonna walk over to it
Throwing caution to the wind you step out of the shadows and approach the gate time to see if you have learned enough of
Your travels to go through the city and unlock the gate you reach the other side of the clearing unscathed and stand below the enormous door
recite the spell
Something something something something something something and the golem has armor you knock firmly on the door
When there is no response you call out I am here to open this gate
There is no response you begin to wonder if you have been tricked if there is no gate here at all
And it's simply an illusion painted across a solid stone wall
Suddenly you are not alone a phantom voice issues from the wood itself
Oh stranger, do you know the spell which controls the gate?
Uh, no, I do not
Then the gate denies you from across the clearing you hear a scrabbling sound of metal moving over stone
You look around but see nothing. Look at the shadows. Look along the track. Look at the well
You look over at the well and catch a flash of moonlight on a metal blade
It is the hooked claw of a grappling hook
Attached to the edge of the well shaft as you watch a face emerges
It bears the leering hook tooth smile of a goblin
The creature is climbing a rope with a grappling hook attached which is hooked over the lip of the well
Attack hide you turn to run aiming to find somewhere you can hide and watch what unfolds
But then you realize that you are running for your life as goblin after goblin
Clammers from the well and begins to race across the clearing towards you
There's no way you can fight a hundred goblins
So you dash aside into the shadows the goblins pour up to the gate are they going to try to ram it?
But then they stop and in their midst a small figure is being propelled forward
You cannot clearly see him
But he is wearing a dull metal circlet on his brow which he clutches as though it was keeping him safe
They're king perhaps but since when have goblins had a king
He is surrounded by a guard of nearby nearly 20 goblins as though he was indeed precious kill the figure
All right, let's go wherever this goblin king is he needs to be stopped. Oh
I had a grenade. There's a lava grenade over there. Uh
Yo
What happens here you cast the spell?
Throwing down a Giants tooth which erupts into smoke a moment later
A giant is standing in the middle of the clearing it grabs a fistful of goblins and tosses them away over the wall
Then grabs the goblin king in its fist and raises him up into the air
He looks to you for instructions toss him away crush him
Crush him crush him. Um, should I crush him? No, I can't I need to know who I need to get info
He I love that. He looks to you for instruction like um
Well, what do you want me to do with this guy put him down put him down you need to
You should put him down do a 1v1 PvP. Yeah, I can 1v1 PvP this guy think about that
I've got this giant here all the goblins are gonna fuck with me now
I'm gonna put him down put him down you call them the giant lowers the king back to the ground
It is enough for his goblin guards to react and they quickly surround him once more and push you back
More goblins charge the giant clamoring up him and working in a large group to cut his head from his shoulders
The kick shit we're gonna kill him
The king smiles holding the circle on his head as if it was a source of some kind of power and then he hurries to
The gate leaning down to the lock he whispers something but you cannot hear what he says a moment later
The gate begins to move it is opening run for the open gate
This is your chance to leave the city you rush forward chanting fearsome sounding
Liturgy at the top of your lungs to scare the goblins and clear them aside
You're nearly through when suddenly a great cry goes up from outside the walls
Something is moving out there run you keep pelting madly forward for once
Simply running madly and not waiting to look around you are almost through the gates when you see what is out there an
army of marsh goblins
thousands of them fully armed and
Stampeding into Carr keep going you try to fight your way forward
But the invading army pushes you back with a force like an oncoming tide
That sweeps you off your feet and dumps you on the other side of the clearing the incoming
Goblins spill through the gate filling the clearing and meeting their hill cousins in a loud and violent
Celebration the man with the circlet at the gate cries with glee a new day for Carr begins
He cries clamoring onto the shoulders of a nearby goblin as though about to make a speech
Quite suddenly the goblins that are carrying him let go he cries out as he falls to the ground a sword goes up
Slashing down there is a scream. They have murdered their own king
What is going on here the circlet from his head rolls to your feet the goblins clashing sword on shield look towards the city with
Violent eyes take the circlet from the way the king was clutching the circlet
You might have thought it was a thing of power perhaps akin to the crown of king itself
But it is nothing cheap hammered iron it still bears the groove
From when it was once a goblin sword you toss it into the dust go for the gate their attack on Carr is not your concern
Darting forward through the crowd of creatures you hurt you head for the open gate and the backlands you run for the gate
But your progress is slow goblins are surging in and they are starting to organize
One a leader of some kind is hoisted up by the others so he can address the crowd
Suddenly the goblins eyes are turning on you as if they had not seen you before one springs forward
But there are a hundred more behind
You ready your sword the creature rushes towards you you try to gauge his size and make a play for the creature's chest the
Goblin drops back quivering with fear shows his teeth and spits
Put him down. I haven't gotten over the fact that they cut the Giants head off. That was horrible. That was a lot going on there
um
Crushed him even they were gonna kill him anyways. They would have been happy
They definitely it doesn't matter all right all right all right you had a full blast. We're gonna go for
shit
He's not gonna go full blast
We do it again
Fuck sorry do it again. Oh my god one point eight one point nine get out of here with this bullshit die
shameful oh
God damn it. Okay. All right all right all right. Oh come on the other one attacked immediately
No, oh my fucking god. I why did I hate the deep and deep and deep and deep and deep and deep and
Start over again. I don't care
Tell me
He's he's he's going to go full the Goblin hefts its sword, but it looks a little tired
six
Yeah, all right. That's good. We're good. We're good good now. We go full blast
Come on like you gotta be shitting me
Really?
My god you beat me by point one what the fuck
That's such dog shit. That's dog shit
Okay, it stares at your stance
six oh
Fuck off
All right, we're doing low three. How did you get four? He just did his whole bar excuse me. You did your entire bar
What's that? What are you talking about? How did he get the four Santa points? He did his whole bar
Yeah, it is sit the fuck down
More goblins are appearing I can run you cannot keep this up
Wave after wave of goblin is filling the yard you cannot hope to kill them all with just your sword
You turn and race away into the shadows then a voice rings out
Stop there is a better way you look around but can see no one but all around you something is happening
It is as though the goblins have slowed down their warmongering becoming an absurd stately dance
The noise in the clearing dulls to a low rumble
I command you to stop from the smoke of the torches by the gate a figure emerges
It is an old man with a long beard and deep black iris eyes
He paces through the churning goblin army to stand in the open his legs disappear into a spectral trail
He is at least part Wraith step forward he commands and you find yourself
Bidden the goblins seem to part around you like smoke as you approach the figure. I have aligned three stars
Vic rises tonight the goblins show their hand tonight, but also you you are here tonight
My name is Lorag I was once a scholar and a noble of the city later
I founded it you founded it later. Who is this crazed shade? I saw Kari was falling
Sansus had lost his mind and sided with the goblins council was in ruins my life
My own life was threatened. I saw that Kari needed to be saved
So I went back to remake it in a way that could be saved and here we are now
You've been here two days. I've been here hundreds of years
Waiting for you to bring me the spell for the gate
The gate is already open the goblins opened it their leader did
The spell does not open the gate his tone is heavy and dark like tarred timber
The spell controls it and there are deep matrix burned into the wood itself
Drupi dog
Drupi the dog
Burned you know god damn it fuck. I don't care burned into the wood itself
Magics that have poisoned the city and burnt
Into the eyeballs of those who live nearby he stares at you his cold black eyes expressing no emotion
The magics I placed there to be used by you
Tonight I am dead. You must act for me. How can I find the spell lines?
I tried to find them. They were well
They were too hidden the lines are known to four nobles or theta is blind and living in the wastelands of upper Kari
But malice was a follower of the gods slang and in his shrine near the docks of lower Kari
You may learn his line as for my line. I give it to you freely
Tumblers to seals deep inside, but there's no more time. It's too late
There is a magic that will give you the time you need
I cast it on myself once and went far back to before this city was built
I found it Kari now you will save it
He waits to let his words sink in if you will allow me
I will blend time itself so that you may return to the city and find the spell for the gate
So shall you take the adventure or will you leave Kari to burn?
Understand I will curse you and the journey to follow if you do not assist me you hesitate
Kari is a city of traps, but also of secrets. There's still more that you might find
Can you afford to let the city burn so this is what happens if I say?
Yes, continue the search we go boom and the whole map is reset
We go back to the very beginning we can then go and pass we did not go and get the actual lines
To open the door we can do that we can do the whole thing again, and we can go find the lines or
We can just leave Kari
We don't you don't need the lines you don't have to get the spell lines
But if you do leave Kari, and you say I don't care let the place burn let the goblins kill it Lorag
Becomes your god, and you can never replace him, and he's a piece of shit
That's what we're dealing with here should we try to save the city or do we just keep going say fuck it move on?
That's spoilers
I mean it's a pretty important spoiler that if we just leave we leave and if we and that
That's a very important spoiler, but doing going rewinding and going back to the beginning
Yeah, it means there's more content here
But we do have to play through and find them and if we don't find them through the second time if we don't get the other
two lines
Then we get back here, and he's just like yeah, fuck you you can't do it, and we just leave and it's over anyways
I'm gonna leave it up to you guys. Let's put a poll in the chat
By the way abandoned car we go on to the third episode we go on to the third game
So this is either stay in episode 2 or move on to episode 3 with some repercussions
What do you think go back save the city get that go get the spell lines because we have some clues now
Or just let's go and move on to the next game. We can do it. We can do it
Okay back to the future. We need to get that legendary sword. Did you would you last time I?
Abandoned car a last time that's what I did last time
I just walked through and I said fuck it whatever
And live with the repercussions for the rest of the game
We did not go back and get the lines last time yes
You keep everything you keep all of your items you keep all your money literally nothing changes besides you go back to the very beginning
Here or actually maybe here
I forget where they put you but then we can use the clues to go and find
The two places where we need to find the lines because Lorag just gave us his all right. Yeah, we're going back all right
Let us go back continue the search. I will help you. I thank you ready yourself
He raises his arm and begins the spell the raging goblins stand like statues
You feel yourself lifting up from your body as though you've been snatched away by birdmen as you lift into the air you hear
Lorag cry out one last piece of advice
Find the lines and find the order of the lines
Karate dwindles beneath you and you feel your body growing weaker oh
You get to decide where to go all right all right. What are the clues? What are the clues?
You were given a clue about the backlands for sleeping okay now. That's the backlands of the next episode
Lord malice Lord malice is one of the nobles of Kari, but where is he okay?
Lord theta is in the ruins
What theta can be found blind and begging in the ruins of the fallen quarter of the city?
Was the fallen quarter of the city
Fallen quarter
What was the other one priest at the shrine of slang might be able to help you find the spell lines the gate the shrine is
Located between the well and the docks in lower Kari so the well and the docks of lower Kari which is
Here or here it literally says the well was is between the well yeah lower Kari though where we drop in
Yeah, but where do you want to go first should we go to the well? Yeah?
It's right here. There were yes. We get to go back in time all right
You get what I guess it really doesn't matter because that way we can go back twice all right, so we're gonna
Go here you ready
We got to go find who we're looking for shrine of slang located between the well
We don't look at the shrine of slang or go to the festival
I guess we could go here and go up through the festival if you wanted to see the festival
I have literally one health. Oh, hey, maybe that's something you do in your game. Maybe you do your game
Maybe you go to them. Maybe you go do all this we didn't do any of this fallen quarters down here
So we've we would need to start how would we get over here all right whole time are we gonna do be like?
festivals festival into the fall and quarter or
Well to go to the shrine because I'm imagining it's probably an opportunity for us to go like this
Right or even go like this
That's possible, too
This just kind of skips us over here and goes a wham and we might be able to go wham wham
Ready when I start the fields of the well we might we probably can get both if we go from yeah
We can probably go
Or if we start here we can go
Now let me get a poll in chat. I'm gonna say well or fields where we gone. Oh, it's already with okay
It's already there fields well this does not count as a rewind it does not okay, okay?
It's still not it's pretty close. I'm
Going in five seconds. I don't think it's still it's only it's like 200 votes. That's not that much okay? That's it
We're going to the fields three two one
Like penis music you are being wretched in directions
You did not know existed the pain is unbearable
And just when you think you will go mad from it the forces tear you apart
You struggle to grab onto your belongings in your very self as you tumble down from the clouds
And then you are awake your eyes open once more your surroundings have changed you wake click you wake quickly from sleep
Your journey must continue
There's no time to lose following the track for a few minutes you reach a junction where three roads begin
These are the outskirts of caray
That's huddled like beggars on either side of the tracks leading uphill into the city port time to choose your road
Somewhere in the city must be the information you need to find the spell lines for the north gate that the innkeeper told you
About just at that moment a cart rolls down the road from the right and careens around a corner to take the main track ahead
This time however the crates on it wobble, but do not fall and it disappears up the road leaving nothing behind
Interesting it seems not everything is fixed after all remember when we got the blimberry juice. It's different. It's different
Speaking of that I need to drink something. I am I look at my health. I mean I'm just gonna take them both I
Need them both
All right, so you guys wanted to go towards the festival right? Oh?
Shit, I didn't want to do I didn't want to drink them both
Yeah, I should I should that was my mistake. That's a mistake rewind. That's a mistake rewind cuz I can do the doc's bill, okay?
Let's head towards the festival we need to end up in the fallen quarter or up at uh up at the well here
So we've got to find our way up
We're gonna go to the festival you head right along a wide track until you reach a large hut
It is the only building on this path that is still standing either side are empty plots
Once the houses of the farmers who planted the fields to the north and now collapsed and thick with grip weed
It seems that here in the shadow of the city wall
It's not a place people choose to live by the side of the door by the side of the door to the hut is a sign
Delicately painted chainmaker the door is just a crack a jar and from within you hear a gentle tinkling sound
Metal on metal as though a creature in a chainmail dress was endlessly pacing the floor listen at the door
You pause a moment longer and listen closely to the door
But there are no voices or footsteps from within just the sound of the chains
From somewhere further on comes the falling and rising sound of a crowd some kind of event is taking place
There are several places you could go next so we could uh, we're not going this way
So it's either go into the chainmaker hut cut through the fields or walk on the path
Let's go in here. Let's go. Let's go. Let's go to the chainmaker you push open the hut door and enter
It is dark inside the floor is sawdust and the air smells of oil
Oil polish and burnt metal from the ceiling hanging like ivy are metal chains of all lengths and thickness
Some suitable for machinery some for oxygen and others for arms and feet the chains shift and whisper to themselves
There seems to be no one here. There's another room beyond its door is hanging open
Call out a greeting search the room. Try the far door
Hello, I'm here
BDSM house try the far door
Let's get some loot. No shop owner and car
I should leave their wares unattended
Steal from him would be to teach him a lesson you begin to carefully search the room trying not to set the chains to
Rattling now a god left wall under the table far door
Near the door to the shop
I'm gonna say near the door to the shop searching around near the door to the shop
You find a copper key. It is carefully stashed into a crack in the wall as though secret and valuable
It is far too small to be the key to the shop door you take it and put it in your pack nice nice
um
Under the table or just stop I'm gonna get caught. Why am I doing the same thing? I did earlier
I never went I didn't go down here
You mean the place right that from like five years ago did I do the same thing?
We haven't been here in this playthrough search along the wall as you move across the room
You stumble clumsily into a chain and it begins to swing hitting other chains on either side
The far door opens in a spin a man orc from Torrapani appears and it looks like he is angry
The chain maker growls fiercely and snatches up a particularly heavy length of metal holding it like it was a thread
Talk my way out of this
What can we do?
sharpen blade
I mean I could throw a fireball at the guy
fix
Cause fixness. Oh
mud
quicksand
I'm gonna I'm gonna talk my way out of it
I'm gonna talk my way out of it. I don't I don't have enough. Look at my stamina. I'm not stealing from you
You reply calmly I called out, but you didn't hear me. I heard nothing
Exactly the chain maker stops and thinks about this. I understand. All right, you want chains
It worked look for a chain to buy he's worthless
All right
What do you got?
You look around the shop a chain after unremarkable chain then one stands out a short length of silver
Which seems to move more energetically than the one swaying on either side the chain maker nods good chain
Magic chain, what does it do magic?
How much does it cost he sizes you up thinking you must be wealthy. It's five gold pieces. I'll take it
I'll buy it you hand over the five gold pieces. He wants happy that three of those five pieces are his anyway
Oh, yeah, that's right. You shake the chain maker's hand and take the chain
It is clearly enchanted the ends seem to snap and bite at one another like a snake
Good for taking out their knees
Okay, is this a weapon it is a weapon really that's all right. That's cool
We have a
Chain as a weapon though. Okay
Uh, should I cut through the field or should I just walk on the road? I'm gonna walk on the road, right?
I don't have enough health to like step on a beehive or land in a trap or something
I'm gonna take the road you continue along the road land rises gently
Thin meager scrub broken by rocky outcrops like teeth through an infant's gum
Goats roam the slopes paranoid shifty creatures who flee at the sound of your footsteps
Suddenly you could be back in the fields outside kristin tonti. This part of the city port is barely habited
So you're unlikely to find clues to the north gate spell here
There will be more people to talk to near the docks
You continue walking along the track and begin to hear the sound of a large crowd up ahead
There's some kind of market or fair happening further on near the river
You pass a dirt track on the left that leads away across the field
Yeah, we'll head right you guys wanted to we wanted to the festival we're gonna do the festival
You continue along the road towards the noise after a few minutes. You are walking between tall poles and rippling colored flags
people and creatures
Sprawl across the path and several tents have been erected the poles joined together by more flags
You ease your way into the edge of the gathered crowd. It looks
All good spirited and fun and with so many people here. Perhaps you will pick up useful information about the spell lines
Listen you mill through the crowd keeping your ears open for anything interesting
But most people in the center of the field are arguing over where to go next
Or lamenting how many gold pieces they have spent you might do better to have a closer look at something
Okay, this is through the end of the midway
You walk to the south end of the fairground midway a boy with a barrel stands off to one side
There are more exciting stalls further north
barrel boy
Or in the middle of the midway
I mean barrel boy, right?
You approach a boy standing by a barrel and looking sheepish
What are you selling the boy points into his barrel but doesn't answer
Look in the barrel
You peer into the barrel. It is full of small hard apples
Most are blackened by disease
Or else are shot through with maggot holes
Your apples are all rotten
The boy shakes his head
Then picks one up from the barrel he squeezes it hard in his fist, but nothing happens
And he drops it sharply back into the bucket
uh
Um, why don't you speak?
The boy shrugs but doesn't seem to want to answer properly
How much is an apple?
You ask despite the fact that it's hard to imagine anyone paying for one
The boy holds up a single finger with one hand and all five fingers of the other
One gold for five apples
The boy nods
Five
I'll take it
You hand over a gold piece and the boy supplies you with five apples
In your hands you feel that they are indeed not rotten
In fact, they are rock solid hardened by some disease into stones
The boy bows his head in thanks
And then gestures behind him
A girl possibly his sister pops up from behind another barrel and pulls a face at you
Throw an apple at her
Like I just full baseball pitcher throw this into this girl's face
Why would I do that? That's horrible
I'm gonna cause mayhem if I do that, you know that right?
Stick my tongue out. Yeah, i'm gonna go
Guys i'm not baseball throwing a rock at a little girl's head
I'm, sorry you you have a playthrough you can do that in your playthrough. That's not happening here
I am not going to full baseball pitcher from the mound
Throw one foot away from me a rock into at some at some girl. I'm not doing that
I'm, sorry
You did it last time
You stick your tongue out the girl giggles and then dodges behind the barrel
The boy looks at you expectantly the girl peeks up again
I'm waiting for her head to pick up
Is that your sister?
You ask pointing the girl's direction
Boy nods and then takes an apple from his barrel and throws it across the field
His sister dodges quickly out of the way
You lob one of your apples at the girl, but she dives to one side and it misses the boy claps his hands
The girl sticks her arms out at either side then quickly ducks
You ready your second apple and wait for the girl to show herself
As soon as she pops up you throw but your aim is off and you miss by a finger's breath
The girl giggles and ducks away out of sight
I I've I didn't mean to do that. I was trying to throw it again. I've can I rewind I fucked up
It's waste i'm wasting apples. I'm I want all five apples
Wait, I toss them all into the mud
You walk away as you go you try biting into an apple and almost crack one of your teeth
They're completely inedible. You toss all of them into the mud
What no go back
Go back go back go back
Six gold pieces one piece for five apples. Okay. All right. Let's go. Let's go. Let's go
Stick my tongue out
Okay. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah
All right. Here we go, bro
Throw another
Okay, throw another you try another throw, but your aim is really terrible
Perhaps if you spent more time practicing your sword fighting and physical skills and less learning book magic your arm would be better
Your hand you hand back your remaining blackened apples to the boy
He grabs the apples and throws them at his sister and you walk back into the midway
what
The fair spreads out all around you a collection of booths and what I is that a like a strength check
I don't get it. I just wasted a dollar
There's just a hint of violence and an atmosphere of cheerfulness
what
All those fancy books
All right into the midway
You push your way through the crowds to the very heart of the fair and look around at the attractions to offer
A beer tent the dancing bear
Let's go to the beer tent
Just by the river is a low tent surrounded by several stumbling figures
It could almost be a tent for dancing except for the strong smell of brewed grain that drifts over the air
In the stall a group of three half goblin women are pouring mugs of beer and talking to the locals
The sign reads one mug one gold four mugs six gold
That's doesn't make any sense
Smell the air you pause to inhale the rich smell of brewed grains that hangs around the tent
It is quite nourishing
One of the bar women catches your smile
Nice. Yes
Even nicer in a glass
Tall spiny creature raises his voice to announce. He is buying four mugs
A huge cheer goes up
But mostly from the women behind the bar
Um, I don't know. I'm gonna run out of money
You elbow your way to the bar and wave to attract the attention of one of the women
Gradients, what can I do for you?
Uh, what's on sale? I'll buy some beer. Why are four mugs so expensive?
You ask isn't it cheaper to buy four separately?
Oh, no, no, no, it's a special offer you say four mugs for six gold pieces
That's but that's more than buying separately
Oh
I see your mistake. It's a common one. We should fix the sign
But she doesn't explain she quickly disappears to serve another customer
Just then two creatures walk past
So you say he wasn't dead when they buried him?
This is the first
Not quite dead enough undead. You could talk to him
You move away from the tent to listen to the creatures
nobles
Why can't they just stay dead when they get dead?
Couldn't agree more
But at least they bury him anyway one less noble for the boss to worry about
They disappear into the crowd a stocky dwarf knocks into you briefly
Begging your pardon. He murmurs before slipping away into the crowd
He just took like I stole me. I got robbed
I don't want I don't remember what this does. I'm fine
You head back over to the tent and wait for a goblin s
I'll buy four you say
The half goblin woman returns with a grin and raises a cry as you pay six gold pieces and she pulls the drinks
He's buying four
Another lucky customer taking advantage of our offer
nearby drunks turn their heads
um
So just share it with everybody. I'll share them you tell the surrounding crowd
The woman behind the bar nods and murmurs
Good idea. This stuff's a bit too strong to drink a lot of
She sets down four mugs in front of you. Should I just drink them all? They're all laughing at you
I don't did I do this last time? I don't drink i'm gonna drink them all
Selfishly you knock back the first mug then the second then the third and fourth without sharing the mugs around
Despite buying them on offer
Beer is watery and somewhat unpleasant, but you don't really notice the ill effects until a few minutes have passed
Suddenly your head is swimming and your stomach is turning over
I had two more chat view. Well, why don't you settle your stomach with another?
I feel terrible. You've poisoned me sure
Too far under the influence to not to agree you buy another mug of beer and drain it
Now you feel really bad
And your head and stomach are swirling like you've been faced down in a cesspool
As you staggered away from the hut stumbling over your feet you look back and see a wide pipe
Running from the back of the tent and directly into the jibaji river
The last thing you realize is that the beer isn't beer at all, but river water
You've been poisoned with river water. I'm dead
I'll drink them all i'll drink them all and they're all mine. They're all my beers. Nobody can have them
And they're all like dude. All right, go for it. Oh my god. He actually bought four
Yeah, fuck you. I'm drinking them all
Yeah, but what smelling the air is delicious, but apparently so what what am I smelling that heals me for one health?
I'm gonna buy one mug
Paying a gold piece you buy a frothing mug of beer. The air looks muddy and somewhat disgusting
It doesn't taste like beer at all
This isn't beer
Excuse me. Uh, what is this?
Finest beer from her expression. She isn't telling the whole truth
You drink some
Oh, I wish I could but I can't drink while working
Yes, then another customer rolls up his nose bright red and his eyes soggy
I'll
Buy it for you
He puts 10 gold pieces down on the counter
enough for all six of you behind the bar
To you he remarks
cannily
Three sets of twins remarkable, isn't it?
Steal the money and run out of the league
Make her drink some
No, no, no, no, excuse me. Excuse me miss to have some of that have some
Have some
Please please have some
It's your beer. It's delicious. I by the way when I took that sip, I was just kidding
It's the it's delicious. You should you should have you take a sip have some take a sip of your own beer
Take half the money and stay quiet
It's 10 gold. What if I take half of it?
Take the money and run
Enough of this you snatch the money from the counter
Thief shouts the woman behind the bar the drunk man and quite a few others turn on you furiously
don't
You mess about with our beer
They cry and jump on you fist pounding fight back
You try to fight back, but the energy of the drunks is furious and they are fearless to boot
You eventually escape with several cuts bruises and scratches look back
Looking back you notice a pipe running from the tent directly into the jabaji river. It seems a beer isn't beer after all
Hey, we're good
murmur of excitement then quite suddenly a small what
From across the field comes a murmur of excitement then quite suddenly a small tornado lifts a tent sharply into the air in a way
I got 10 gold for that
You can enjoy your your your shit wine. That's fine your poop wine
I got 10 gold
You cross the fair to join a crowd gathered at a safe distance around a dancing bear
A dwarf stands in front of the bear holding a lead that is fastened to a ring in the creature's nose
See my beauty dance he growls jerking the cord the bear stumbles around in obvious pain
As he tugs the cable he plays a pipe with great gusto
The crowd are in stitches of laughter at the poor bear's performance
Really bear I might die doing this
Hold on you hang around for a moment and watch no fuck you
Most curious see if the bear will strike down its miserable little owner suddenly a cry goes up from somewhere in the audience
My gold my gold my pick pocket beware. That's a pick pocket at work pick pocket
You and the rest of the crowd spin around towards the voice and see a small creature darting off away from the crowd and into one
of the tents
No, fuck you
With everyone looking in one direction you turn to look in the other and see the dwarf release the cord holding the bear in place
But the creature does not go wild or attempt to run. In fact, both the dwarf and the bear seem to shrink down to the ground
What's going on?
Is this part of the show?
Okay
Just illusions perhaps
The crowd are out for blood now. It seems several of them have been robbed
Turning on one another accusations of theft begin to fly this way and that
Things are turning ugly and you are caught in the middle of it. See what I can get
in the tumult
You wait for an opportunity in every fight. There will always be some gold pouches swinging low for the plucking
You are knocked about a fair bit as you wait, but finally you see a bulging wallet just inches from your grasp
Look at the owner
Glancing up at the owner of the wallet. You find yourself staring into the huge face of a mountain man
You're a thief are you?
No, i'm no thief you tell him
Look at the size of his gold pouch
Remarks another voice nearby in the crowd
It's a trigger that sends the mountain man who had just been robbed himself into a fearsome rage. Oh god
I have to win. I gotta win every single one of these. Let's go
seven
Oh fuck
An instant later the man is thundering down on you arm swinging and he charges with every ounce of his strength knocking you back
The mountain man swings a final punch that knocks you into the mud
Then for good measure he stamps on your head and walks away
He probably doesn't realize that he has broken your skull wide open. Whatever
defend
All right, he's gonna come in full blast
Let's go like eight
How are you? No, no
Okay, wait, wait, wait
You put up your own and circle the mountain man steps back. He's gonna block again. All right
You stay low the crowd around jostle and struggle fighting amongst themselves. He circles
Through the fighting crowd. He's coming in
He's coming in full blast
Oh my fucking god, dude. What are you talking about?
i'm dead
That was three defends in a row. He steps back
Okay
He paces left
He circles right
He edges back you piece of shit
Fine take that
Okay, he sneers at me
Does that mean he's coming in or?
Does that he's nears at me? Does that mean he's gonna swing?
Got him
That was too much though. That was way too much. I'm dead
Yeah, i'm dead. I literally no
I'm not dead
pray to the ape
We're good five health
Nice, hell, yeah
Thank god for the ape
I wouldn't be able to beat that
Now he dodges back now we go little tiny little bit 2.0
And that should do it now. We go full blast. He goads you. All right, can I do it?
Yeah
You launch at him again. You grab a nearby bottle and break it against his head
The final punch makes the mountain man's head spin
Oh, never mind
He curses throwing up his hands
Keep your gold thief
But that he stomps away punching a few other people as he goes
You slither your way back out of the crowd to the main part of the fair
From somewhere nearby you catch a glimpse of a shadowy figure disappearing behind a tent
Something about the way it moves is familiar
I didn't get his gold
Follow the figure
Follow the figure you push through the crowd following the dark figure into a narrow gap
cautiously you enter the narrow space
And suddenly there is a hand at your throat
I will kill you
Reads a voice you recognize
You laugh with delight
It's flanker
The assassin whose life you spared before you reached torapani
Greetings you declare enthusiastically
Flanker nods he does not smile, but he seems pleased to see you
Aha my friend and enemy
I see like myself
You also enjoy the fun of the festival of thieves
But you look in poor shape
Have others been treating you more roughly than I was able to myself?
And how have you fared in Kari city is full of devils
flanker laughs
It is indeed
But at least you have not had to face the portal traps
They'll take your smile and move it to your throat as we assassins say
portal traps
I want your help
flanker nods
Ask of it and I shall do what I can
Oh, we send him on like an errand
I've been told to find a priest. I need to find a beggar who is a noble
Tell me about those portal. I need to know the order of the spell lines
um
Probably this one right because that's
check
uh
Lord theta is in the ruins
So this is the beggar
So I probably want to know this right?
Or the order I need to find a beggar who was a noble. I need to find the order of the spell lines
order
Okay, I need to do the order
flanker nods
I am told that Sansus did not entrust any of his nobles with the knowledge of their correct order
It was his final failsafe
But that does not mean it is not known
You might appeal to one of the gods to learn
Which god?
Slang is not strong enough for such knowledge. I think
Though you could try his shrine
between the well and the docks
otherwise
Corga would know but his temple is by the north gate
He nods finally, but I must be away. Perhaps I will see you again
I'll be drinking at the wayfarer's rest tonight in the docks join me if you will i'm getting fucking weirder
You nod to flanker in return. All right, the wayfarer's rest
um
Slang, okay, we need to we're gonna go find slang
Flang is up here, right?
Yeah
At the where is it tonight?
The wayfarer's rest. Where was that?
Go do corga. I can't do corga. I killed someone corga won't talk to me
You walk to the north end of the fairground midway
The fair continues from here and a road leads uphill
Fair knuckle fighting musicians
Um, let's do the musician
You head over to where a crowd are watching a troop of dancers who spin and swirl in time to a lively tune
There's something quite hypnotic about the performance
Wait, I can do it too
Let's do it i'll play with them
Cause a stench somebody farted at the concert
uh the sus
There's goes slow
I mean i'm gonna play with them. Yeah, that sounds like the fun thing to do. Let's do it
You cast the spell and begin to play your pipe
With the other dancers already setting a wonderful mood the spell's effects are magnified
And soon the entire crowd is dancing and jigging with each other
It is quite a sight a hundred of kare strange and wonderful creatures all waving their arms and stamping their feet
after about half an hour
The crowd grows tired and wanders off arm in arm and claw in claw
To see the other attractions of the fair
One of the musicians approaches you
nice work
Not often we get a talented amateur for the thieves dance
The crowd will think you were a stooge
Oh the thieves dance
The musician shrugs
It's just a name
He looks you over with a cany eye
Pack sword battle scars. You're not from kare. Are you?
Not just here to enjoy the fair
I'm visiting my father
Just visiting my dad
Maybe you can help me
Maybe you can help
Yeah, maybe I can
The musician drops down to the dirt and puts his hand out. My name is jira and it's good to meet you
You shake his hand
So you helped us get enough coins to pay for our night. How can I help you?
I need to open the north gate or I need somewhere to stay
I'm probably gonna say that
Because we we know what we need to go for the spell lines
But I've really my health is terrible
I need somewhere to stay
Well, you have to be careful in ins of kare some of them work in commission for the slavers if you know what I mean
He smiles sadly and for some reason taps his forearm as he speaks
We're staying at the meat and cleaver by the docks and I wouldn't recommend anywhere else
If you value your freedom, I'll see you there
He winks and heads off into the crowd
interesting
Bare-knuckle fighting you cross the fairground to a wrestling ring of ruffian inside is announcing the current challenge
People of kai
Are you ready for a fight?
In the white corner, we have our challenger
anva the barbarian
Crowd cheers and whoops
Look over anvar anvar is about half as tall as you again with sheets of muscle on his arms and legs
But he's probably lighter than the ogre
Which will mean he has less momentum
And in the black corner the brawling champion of kare the one they call skull splitter
the ogre kaga of tadu lei
The ogre looks as thick as any ogre you might meet but he is made of solid muscle
His arms and legs like the twisted bark of trees
Challenger, are you ready demands the ruffian anvar nods and beats his chest
Place a bet you find a wager man by looking for his enormous hat to which odds and returns are pinned on bits of cloth
Feeling lucky, are you?
Place your money on me
His palms are sweating and you notice he carries flick blades inside his sleeves
Give me all your money
What are the odds three to one on the challenger one to three on the champion?
What does that mean?
For every coin you bet on the barbarian you get three extra back if he wins
But for every three coins you put on the ogre you will only get one extra back if he wins
All right place a bet you take your money bet on the barbarian. I bet on the barbarian
Maximum bet is three pieces good odds though
You hand over three gold pieces and the bookkeeper makes a mark on his hat with a bet
Meanwhile in the ring the fight has begun the barbarian in the white corner growls and beats his chest
The ogre raises his fist into the air and shakes them quite a lot of posturing so far, but not much actual wrestling
Read minds
Stop lock doors
cause slowness
sap
Cause oh, yeah, I can cheat. I can cheat. I can cheat
I can sap the ogre and win. Yep
What is k?
create illusions
This might be fun. Wait, that would be cheating though. It'd be like why the fuck this guy come from
Let's do slowness
You ready the enchantment preparing to slow down one of the two combatants cast it on the ogre
You cast a spell over the ogre and the balance of the fight begins to change
Suddenly the ogre looks dizzy and slow and cannot seem to grip his opponent properly
The barbarian beats his chest and pounds the ogre heavily about the head
Anvar is looking good
Shout for the barbarian
Finish him
To the barbarian who bellows with anger
The slow-moving ogre roars with rage and struggles forward against the barbarian landing a mighty blow
Anvar's agility is helping him take the fight
Then the ogre puts in a devastating side swipe
The barbarian staggers suddenly the crowd gasps, but he picks himself up once more
Come on just
Cast depression on the ogre
You cast the enchantment over the ogre who begins to look thoroughly miserable
You have given anvar a much-needed boost
The ogre's lip has split and is bleeding
Anvar roars and thumps his opponent in the back
Anvar is winning
Should I wait cheer for the ogre?
Cheer for the barbarian
Should I cheer for the ogre now?
Uh, let's read the ogre's mind you read the ogre's mind, but find no particular thoughts except one
a sound
Playing over and over
It is the sound of an arm bone snapping in two
Growling and muttering the ogre works into the barbarian cracking his skull
Anvar is looking stronger than ever what?
God damn it kill him already
Okay illusions you ready the spell but what illusion will you cast make the ogre see the barbarian as plague-ridden
Make the barbarian see the ogre grow taller
Make the ogre see the barbarian as plague-ridden
You cast your spell over the ogre making the barbarian appear plague-ridden and infectious
Begins to hang back not wanting to engage
And every time anvar grabs him he begins to whimper with fear
The fight is going really badly for skull splitter now
Finally it is all over with a single throw anvar the barbarian powers forward and hurls skull splitter to the mat the crowd goes wild
You find the bookkeeper to collect your winnings
You got lucky
Sulk the bookkeeper he hands over 12 gold pieces. Oh, yeah
Inside the ring the master of the fight raises the barbarian's fist in the air
Who challenges our champion the prize is 10 gold pieces
I'll do it
I challenge him
You cry
All eyes turn to look at you the fight master beams
We have a stranger taking the challenger
Let him through
You got any food?
Yeah, all right. I can drink this. I don't care about healing somebody else. It's for me
Okay, the crowd parts and you are helped up into the ring under his breath the fight master outlines the rules
A fair fight no magic and pound your opponent until they can't stand
Ready?
You look over your opponent. He is almost half as tall as you again with muscles on his chest and arm
It's like sculpted to wax
In the back corner, then the ruffian announces is anvar in the white corner
ruffian turns to you and hisses
What should I call you?
The anilander the stranger. I don't care. Just get on with it the anilander. Oh boy. I get out. Okay
The anilander are you to cry?
Shouting it out to the crowd so they can hear they catch the name and throw it up to the sky
the anilander
They cheer the crowd begin to furiously place bets. You can hear them discussing your relative merits. He looks feeble. He looks like a maniac
You ready your fists
ball blast
Got him
Got him. Mm-hmm
He steps backwards across the ring putting space between you
That's gonna be a defense. He's gonna defend but we're gonna go like 2.5
Fuck you
All right
He grabs you and knees you in the midriff knocking the wind from your chest. Okay, I gotta defend here
Oh, come on. It's all right. I got enough power
I'm gonna go in full blast
Mmm
Reading a forceful blow the barbarian blocks
drop back defensively
Knocking you back. Okay, so he used his whole bar. We're gonna go like four. I could actually he might be able to do more
Yep, thank god
We're good
A gasp goes up from the crowd. We're going full blast again 6.4. Get him
It's all right. It's okay. It's okay. All right. All right, I'll win
The barbarian drops into a defensive crouch
The barbarian is holding back someone in the crowd is shouting advice body blow time
There it is. Got him. What?
How is that only one?
Shaking his stupid head. He picks himself through his feet once more. He moves away towards the other corner
Can I get him here? Can I catch him?
I caught him you lunge forward again writing a forceful swing you hurdle forward
Anvar staggers back gasping his face a mess of blood and bruises
Summoning the last ounce of strength in your arms
You ready a final knock back knockout punch that sends him back across the mat and out of the ring
Look at this fucking cash. I'm building up here
You stagger from the ring the crowd cheering for you and collect your winnings
I got 33 gold now
All right, the end of the fair
You push your way through the crowd following the road uphill
The party is getting wilder and you would do well to be away from here before things get out of hand
At the far edge of the fair the litter has left a tide mark on the grass
There's one last small tent here probably a ticket booth that has simply been ignored by the crowds of kare
Looking back you see what looks like one of the tents going up in flames
It must be part of the entertainment as no one seems too concerned
In fact a great cheer goes up as one of the strings of flags collapses into the bonfire
Ahead the road continues through empty fields and patches of rubble strewn wasteland
But it climbs so it must be heading for the center of kare
Steam rises from a large building beside a fork in the road you pause to walk around the small tent
To discover it is in fact a small attraction of its own a sign above the door reads cabinet of fortune
Try your luck a prize for all
You have time to test your luck
No doubt if you wanted
Uh, we're gonna go in here
You go over to the tent and push back the flap inside
A grubby bearded man leaps up from where he was sitting cross-legged on the floor and comes over to pump your hand
Welcome welcome my friend
And let's see what prize you can win today
You must know this there are no losers at honest hannah's cabinet of fortune
He gestures with one hand towards a large glass cabinet in the center of the tent interesting
Uh, what do I do? How much does it cost look inside the cabinet?
You step forward and peer in through the glass
Inside there are piles of jewelry books gold and other things as well as a small wiry creature
Curled up fast asleep. What is that creature?
My little pet
He's perfectly harmless. Oh, well, he bites but only when you open the cabinet to feed him
Uh, what do I do?
It's a most simple game
You give me two gold pieces and then my little pet will fetch something for you. Fuck up
The fuck up the fuck up
resurrect the dead
rap talk all languages
Talk all languages
tell
Read minds
Uh sus, obviously
uh magic protection
I'm gonna i'm gonna talk
I'm gonna do a rap you put on the wig and cast your spell not on hannah. Of course, you can understand everything he says
What about the creature in the glass cabinet?
Sadly though it is not speaking it sits in glum
thoughtful silence
shit
Here you pay two gold pieces
And hannah goes over to the cabinet and presses a small button on the side. It seems to operate a hold on
It's sneezed. I have to sneeze again
seems to operate a
canted levered spike
Which pokes the creature who squeals jumps from its perch and begins fluttering around inside the cave
What now?
You can try to influence its choice by shouting at it the angrier you can make it the better for the prize
Usually i'm not sure why
As if to make the point the creature picks up a ruby ring and smiles and drops it and flies up to the top
of the tank
Shout something
Although it does not seem very fair
You determine to infuriate you you determine to infuriate the creature as much as possible
Stupid creature freedom lorag
Kari lorag freedom freedom the creature in the tank flaps around gently. What else could you try?
I mean hannah obviously like right
hannah
The strange might is still flying around with glowing eyes
There must be something that will get this creature to see truly you see red
Lorag the flying thing circles around furiously
Eventually the creature selects something from the prize pool which it drops into a chute at the far end of the cabinet
I take what if I just leave it will that do something?
What is it?
a giant's tooth
a good prize
You nod to hannah who grimaces as you head back out of the tent
All right, we got us we got another tooth. I wonder how that could probably go a few different ways cool
Okay. All right, so we can all we can either go
Yeah, we can go out now
So we're trying to get
here
This area here get that in mind
You're back by the bath house on the edge of the fair. All right, so we can go in the bath house
Well, we can go uphill. We need to eventually go uphill. So we're going to bath house
Let's do the bath house. You step in the cool of the bath house
It is a wide building of marbled tiles and a sweet smell of pine and fresh wood
Gentle noises echo and murmur around the walls a creature by the front desk greets you with a smile. Good afternoon
The water is cool and fresh today
My swim costs four gold pieces. I need it. Is it worth it? Oh very the creature replies
The waters of cara are known for their healing and refreshing qualities
We have a steam room in a lagoon pool. You'll be well catered for sure
You enter before gold pieces and the concierge gestures you through into the center of the bath house
Where a wide pool awaits with trees and shrubs on either side the pool
From across the room steam curls from the doorway of a glass doored room
You strip off and pile your clothes and belongings in the corner of the room
I'm going to the steam room
You enter the steam room and take a seat on one of the benches. The temperature is almost unbearable through the curling smoke
You see another figure in the shadows. You are not alone
Hey, what's up? Hey, how you doing? What's up, dude?
I would that would never happen. I would never do this. Hey, what's up? Hey, you need a spotter
It's a steam room, dude
Greetings
You call through the smoke
The other figure does not reply but stands and moves away through the steam
You feel the blast of cold air as the door opens and then closes
I'm sorry if i'm in the steam room and I hear somebody from across
I'm sitting on the other side of the bench say greetings and be like, yeah, i'm getting the fuck out of here
I'm gonna go somewhere else you sit in the smoke enjoying the relaxing steam until you cannot take the heat anymore
Wait a little longer
You wait a little longer as the steam sinks deep into your bones and makes your muscles relax
You feel quite wonderful for it a second figure who you would not notice before stands and leaves the steam room
You head back out of the steam room. You feel your shoulders unknotting and your body relaxing
You dive into the pool and swim a few enjoyable lengths. You feel better for the exercise
You feel a great calm and relaxedness flooding through your veins feeling much better. You turn and collect your belongings
Yeah, check them over not trusting the city to pass up the chance to rob you you check through your belongings
But everything seems to still be in in place
Pleased you head for the exit the creature at the front desk beams cheerfully at you you step outside onto the street
We just that's there it is good rest
All right
We're gonna go up uphill the road twists and turns up the rise until you emerge into a wider road on the edge
Of the dense slum from inside down a street to the left
You can hear the very faint sound of singing a smell of rotting fish begins to fill the air
You must be close to the docks
All right
So where is this place between the well and the docks is it this way or is it this way?
Is it the docks or is it near the well?
I'm gonna imagine we can we can go this way and hopefully we can go from here to there
Let's go to the well winding between tall
crazily built slum dwellings the road you are now on leads through the dense lower city
The street is narrow and you keep your head held high in case someone should try their luck with a blade
After a few minutes of edging floors you emerge into a wider space a flag-stoned plaza at the center of it is a circular well mouth
alleyways lead off in four directions
You pause to look around the edge of the square
The alleyways all look the same except that to the left the lane heads downwards turning away from the center of kare
The only thing the alleys have in common is that they converge here once presumably this well served all the people in the district
But perhaps there were too many people because now the well seems dusty and dry
Look down the well
Leaning over the edge you peer down into the depths of the well strange
This well seems to have handholds cut into its stones. They appear good enough to climb down
Uh, we're not going down here. We're gonna choose the road. Here we go. All right, so we need to this is where we need to go
This is where we need to be
This direction between the well and the docks
This street is a little wider and more well paved than some of the others. You can see tracks where carts have come this way
You hear the sound of voices around a corner
Walk on
You walk around the corner intrigued by the sound
There is a small crowd of people talking and singing inside a low stone shrine
Beyond you can see the sparkle of the river and the smell of rotting fish. You're nearly at the docks
There's the shrine. All right, let's go. Let's get that out of the line
You step into the doorway of the shrine at the same time as a woman and her child are leaving
He really is a holy man mother the little one is saying
Lassen's lame brother answered his question and he ran off the stage the mother nods and the pair leave interesting step inside
The shrine is an old stone building
garishly decorated with hanging cloths and thick candles
That fill the air with the smell of grease and tar at the far end on a low platform stands a hooded figure in a white robe
Who was talking to the assembled crowd? Oh, this is the cerise. This is okay. Yep. I remember this remember this
We saw maybe we've read our own fortune. This is we did this already remember it was a guy in the white robe
Does anyone else wish to test?
Let me do that again. Does anyone else wish to take the test of slang god of malice?
Reese calls out a murmur goes around the crowd people are nervous but excited examine the crowd crowd is a mixture of young and
old women and men some cheer and joke and murmur while other
Have their legs and arms folded in a devout pose and pray through silent lips
How many are spectators and how many are followers of slang you cannot tell anyone who can answer the question will be granted their wish
The priest continues wait and watch you wait and watch suddenly a man leaps to his feet
I'll do it. He declares the rest of the group cheers and the man a geriatric
Is helped up onto the platform. Are you a follower of slang?
The man spits very well in one corner of the room a gong is sounded and the crowd falls silent
Which do you choose the priest demands of the man?
Will you take the impossible challenge or pay the price of the easy challenge?
The man looks uncertain and turns to the audience people begin to shout suggestions
Choose the impossible choose the easy one choose the impossible you cry out adding your voice to those around you
Bellowing loud and confidently after a few minutes the priest quiets the room and turns back to the man
So what do you choose i'll take the impossible challenge the man grins very well very well
There is no price for the impossible challenge. Are you ready?
Wait and listen then tell me what is the answer to the question that is never asked
The man falls silent for a moment chewing his lower lip and musing over his answer
Um
Silence the priest smiles sadly and shakes his head a clever answer but not correct. Oh
The crowd sigh in disappointment a man at your elbow remarks
People always try the impossible challenge
You'd think they'd get the hint the man leaves the platform and the priest turns back to the crowd
Who will be next as he waits for an answer the priest plucks a knife from his belt and casually stabs it into his own hand
I'll take the challenge because we know the answer. I will take your challenge a stranger
Welcome him, please. Welcome. Welcome him. The crowd whisper and murmur as you make your way to the platform
Welcome stranger. Are you ready to take the challenge knowing folwell that very few succeed
I am
the crowd cheer
Your response
Then know this flying is not a punishing god, but he is malicious
He does not wish for you to fail
But should you fail?
He wishes you to know that it was all your own fault
Mm-hmm
The priest continues
Our practice is that you may choose which question to answer but know this one is impossible and the other is easy
And to answer the easy question you must give up something you hold most dear
The crowd are watching in it and expect in silence. It's time for you to choose
Make sure I get this right
What was it?
The answer to the question in the vision you saw the answer to the question that has never been asked sirisi
Okay, that's making sure I get it, right
I choose the impossible question
The crowd wait expectantly and the priest closes his eyes and intones
What is the answer to the question that has never been asked?
Your heart leaps your vision is coming to pass. I don't know
sirisi
There is a moment
pause
As the priest screws up his eyes
The priest nods once slowly that is correct. The question has never been answered
In the three thousand years since this site was first made wholly to slang
The answer has been passed on from one priest to the next I never thought I would be the one to hear it spoken
Because I do not understand it
And I do not know the question he turns to you and bows his head once you are truly blessed
Please what is your wish?
I wish to be rich beyond my imagination. Tell me the spell for the north gate
Tell me the order of the spell can kare be saved. I wish to be stronger than anyone ever
That's like a toddler the thing to say
I wish to be stronger than anyone ever even superman even god stronger than god answer man
um
It's the spell right because this is where one of the lines is from tell me the spell for the north gate
Tell me the spell for the north gate
The priest closes his eyes and summons his god
I cannot tell you the spell in its entirety
But mulaz the second noble was a follower of slang
And the line he knew was I bid you portals
wide
open
Got it. You thank him the crowd reach out to touch your tunic as you make your way to the door
Clearly not many survived the challenge of slang back on the street at his night time to find somewhere to rest
I said I said I said it wrong
This priest has the only opportunity in his entire lifetime to hear this it's been thousands of years
And he screws up the sentence. He must be like fuck
Oh, how could I do that? I gotta be so stupid
You needed the order. Well, I didn't have I I didn't have the line
This is where I could get the line
Yeah, the order is I don't I need the the the lines first. Yeah, I can still get it
I think I don't I already have the order. Wasn't it scratched on something? Hold on
Remember wasn't I like I I swear see here it is right there
No
Something corgis grace one lock. Wait, is this it?
That's that's it. Isn't it?
Tumblers to yep, that's that's it. We got the we already have the order
One lock made of golems hide
Tumblers to seal deep inside
I bid you portals open wide
For my legs to walk in here and fucking stride
We just need the last line
Which is down here
Okay, let's uh head to the docks. What's the the clue for this one?
Okay, seventh noble theta is a beggar
blind beggar
Can be found blind and begging in the ruins of the fallen quarter of the city
so
He's down here
So we're gonna figure out a way to get down there
Okay
Uh, let's have it the docks
The smell of rotting fish and mucky water fills your nostrils. You know this area well
You've reached the docks once more the beating heart of care
There are two or three ships moored for the night
And the space between them and the road is filled with a large huge number of stalls and little shops
Selling everything from fishing tackle to sailing blocks to barrels of woodlouse rum
This must be a thriving marketplace during the day with night approaching. It is a maze of booths and cloth
A single bridge crosses the river here operated with ropes. He'll let the tall ships through
Right now the bridge is up to allow ships to sail through undisturbed
There are two inns visible from here the wayfarer's rest
And the meat and cleaver the second is the one jira the musician recommended
Well, wait a minute
um
musician friend or flanker
We had a new musician friend
Do we give a shit about flank? All right. This is that you guys have to
Put a poll up here
Meet the one is going to be here two is here
One is flanker at the wayfarer's rest two is jira the musician and a band of merry musicians
Uh while you do that, i'm just gonna go piss. I'll be right back. I am back. I'll just be quick. Uh, so how how
Uh, how crazy is this 69 want to go to flanker?
Okay, but what about our band of merry men?
What if they have a bunch of cool stuff or they have items and what if it's like what if it's like five people?
They all hang out with us
All right wayfarer's rest. Let's go
You make your way inside the wayfarer's rest. It's a lively and bustling place
Jesus
The innkeeper behind the bar is trying to serve numerous creatures all demanding ale at the same time while around the tables
Salty types and buxom wenches are laughing together and singing shanties
the table with the bar
Um flanker flanker flanker. I don't i gotta meet flanker here. I'm meeting flanker here
Let's go to the bar. I got money
You fight your way through the creatures to the bar with a thump on the bar top you catch the innkeeper's attention
greetings
Nice place you have here
The innkeeper nods at you. He's clearly impressed by your dress and well-educated tone
And what would be your purpose in these air parts? I do need food. Uh, I need food
Can you feed me in this hell hole?
The innkeeper nods. Hi
Uh the gills or six gold pieces hearty as you like
The other creatures at the bar jostle and push each other for space
um
That's that's expensive. I need it though
You hand over six gold pieces the innkeeper nods
Get yourself a table and we'll bring it out when it's ready
Okay, what about your ale the innkeeper holds up one finger
A ruffian knocks over a dwarf's mug of ale the fight that breaks out is short sharp and ends with the heel of an axe
Breaking the ruffian's nose a great cheer goes up and the innkeeper replaces the ale
free of charge
Uh, i'll take some ale i'll have a mug then you declare you lay down a coin and the innkeeper passes you a flagon
What about a room? How much is a room?
The innkeeper holds up four fingers rather than shouting across the bar
Uh, i'm gonna drink my ale
You knock tankers with the creatures on either side of you then drain the beer in one swoop
It is a nutty pleasant beer fills your stomach with a pleasing warm glow
Anytime I read about
You guys get like this too
when I read
about people drinking beer
In fantasy novels, I want a beer right now
right
I don't really like beer. I'm not a big beer guy, but I just think of this frothy freezing cold mug
That's got this stout in it. I just want one
They describe beer so insanely and so deliciously in all these fantasy novels. Oh a flagon of ale
I don't know
They describe it like a nice root beer. Yeah replace that with a with a soda right or a root beer
A nice frothy foamy root beer. Oh, it's so good
Okay
Uh, let's take let's take another one. Come on. I got money
Oh, I didn't read this
But you knock tankers the creature on either side of you then drain the beer in one swoop is a nutty and pleasant
It fills your stomach with a pleasing warm glow
finest and curry
The innkeeper remarks seeing your satisfied smile
Ain't nothing that beats a good glass of wayfarers ripe. You should have another two seconds always better
Yeah, i'm taking another one. Let's go
You knock back your second mug of fine ale and feel yourself ruddy with good health
This inn is a charming place really and the people here are very friendly
The innkeeper nods with approval
All the best can put it away he remarks
Another one you buy some more beer you sweep back a third mug of ale. The effect is immediate
First your eyes start to fizz then your head starts to ache
You half get to your feet, but you can barely work out which way is up
Three blurry men approach you and take you by the arm
You're all right. Let me help you with that
Something moves and you feel a hard blow on your head about three seconds later
You realize you've been knocked unconscious as everything goes black
What?
What about flick flanker your eyes open your head is thundering and it feels ready to split
Where's flanker?
We drank two beers. What was what's going on?
Do we get to rewind?
This is a chat decision not mine. It's got to be at least 75 percent by the way
One rewind yes or no
It's got to be 75 percent. Yes, or it's not happening. This is the only that's it
It's got to get to
75 percent
Are we rewinding? Yes or no?
It says a pole is already active, but I can't see it. You guys see a pole. It says one's already there
Where is it? Yeah, it says a pole is active. Oh
Uh, let me see if I can I think it's stuck. Yeah, it says a pole is already active. It's stuck
You had to refresh for the pole. I'll try refreshing it. I have to refresh chat. All right. Hold on. Let me refresh chat real quick
Uh-huh refresh did that work? I can't see it. Wait. Oh you guys are lying. Um, I can see it now
All right. So what was that? It was 80 percent 79 percent. All right
79 percent we're going to the bar. All right greetings this time. We're gonna well this time. We're gonna just we're gonna buy food
This place is great pay for a meal. I'm gonna do everything at the same, but i'm only gonna drink two beers
Oh, whoops. All right price of your ale. All right. Yes, it's the best. Yes. I'll buy some
All right delicious. It's good. It's so good
All right, buy another one. This one's delicious, too
All right. Goodbye
You push your way back out of the crowd at the bar your eyes roam around the busy room
And the light on a shadowy figure in the corner. It's flanker
Blankers table. Okay, let's go
You go over and sit by the assassin. There you are. He declares with pleasure. He seems more relaxed than earlier
Perhaps he has completed whatever mission he was here to perform
But tell me friend
Do you play dice?
swindle stones
Ah, I see, you know it from a hidden pouch in his tunic
He pulls a set of dice out and pushes half of them across the table to you
Sure
You take them
Uh, what's the steak?
Let me propose a modest wager
If you win
I will help you with your quest
But if I win
My obligation to you is at an end and should we meet again?
I will have the freedom to cleave your neck from your shoulders
Do you agree?
Uh, I prefer to keep you in my debt if I lose you'll kill me
Very well
well
I just have to win. Let's go
Like your hands are your dice and takes the first bid just don't lose. So what are you doing? Car it my friend
Three ones
Let's go fucking hard
Whoa
You don't have he has to have four of those
I will not allow your inane words to turn me from my game. So do not attempt such a strategy
There's no way
There are five threes. You gotta be shitting me dude. Really? That's so that's actually bullshit truly
Two ones
Three threes
Oh, no
What is this hand
This guy's got a full house. What is this twos and ones?
What is this? His both of his hands have been?
Outrageous they've been outrageous
I'm so screwed
Yeah, I mean I have one of them call it. Uh
So he has to have three of them. Does he is he gonna have three of these? No, there's no way you don't have three
It's your whole hand call. There we are. All right, that's better one three
Two fours
Don't call it you piece of shit. You definitely have it
Okay, so i'm gonna say four. I have two that means he okay. Yeah, we're doing four
Call it. Yes
All right. This is not a bad hand. I'm gonna say two ones two
fours
Oh, you're in trouble. You're actually in trouble three fours call it four fours
Mmm
But should I say five fours? No, that's that has to mean that
One of us has to have a full set
But what if he has two we have the same amount of uh dice
liar
one two
Uh, two twos three twos
You are stupid you are stupid what a comeback this is big
Uh, let's start with
One two one five, okay two ones call it. Okay, so he has a five fuck
He has a five so I have uh, I have a five too though
Three
No, I I keep saying five because I just see it as a regular dice. Don't call it
It's fine, whatever he's gonna win a round he picked the two worst possible things. It's all right
one three
Um one four two threes. Oh you lose
Ha you are in my debt now
Blanker
You flick flanker's final die off the table with a grin
I win
Blanker nods deeply
Sinler preserve me
I have lost to you again
Come with me. I will take you to the council. I want the spell lines
Council the leaders of kare are mad men and pirates, but not fools
They might be persuaded to see the sense of your mission
Especially if we have the gold to cover their pockets
Shall we go?
Where is the council?
It is hard to find
It is the tallest building in kare, but most of its height is built or underground
But from the street, it looks like just another dwelling place
But I know where it is
Um, I kind of want to do my own path
but
Should we just go with them? What about your food? All right, let's go
Excellent flanker beams finishes his beer and then gestures to the door follow me
Follow flanker
You follow flanker across the top of the dock. He moves fast like a fleeting shadow
But somehow contrives to never disappear from your sight
He does not speak and your attempts at conversation are met with immediate silence at the council
Finally you arrive outside an ordinary looking building. This is it wait here and I will go inside
He disappears through the door the house into which flanker has gone is just that surely
The windows are thick bottle glass
And the door is tarred wood studded with rivets and painted black the roof only a single story up is overgrown with weeds
Other identical dwellings stand either side still nothing the building in front of you does not seem like any council chamber
Perhaps this is a trap
Um look in the windows you peer in through one of the windows
But the glass is so thick and heavily streaked on the inside with candle grease that you cannot make out anything
I'm gonna wait you wait flanker does not reappear. I will wait minutes pass
Wait time passes in the distance
You hear the sound of cartwheels rattling down the cobbles from the dock
They're quickly lost in the bustle of loakare. Wait, you hear the footsteps of the guard marching past
Perhaps they will come here, but then they turn away this place
It seems is not even important enough to warrant a visit long minutes pass
Time passes more time passes minutes pass. All right
All right. It's time to go because what if something happened to him one more one more more time one more one more
Try the door ignoring flankers instructions. You try the door. It is unlocked
I'm sorry, but like that was that was like 40 fucking minutes. That was 40 minutes something could have gone wrong
You were in a wide room chairs line the walls, but there is no other furniture
If this is someone's house, then it has become meticulously robbed
But if not, you cannot see what function it does serve
But it cannot be abandoned a fire in the hearth blazes out heat. There's no sign of flanker anywhere
But there are also no other doors god. It's too sus cast the spell and wait as a calm voice enters your mind
It speaks in reassuring tones telling that you are quite safe and everything in this room can be trusted
Although that not not everything is quite as it appears
Look at the fire you go over to the fire to warm your hands
It seems normal enough and it's hot enough to roast a pig a voice booms out from nowhere. Please be seated
Uh, okay
You choose a seat close to the fire and sit down
Something strange happens the moment you take your weight off your feet
It is as though the far wall no longer exists in its place is a long hallway
Lying with cloth banners and torches on brass poles two guards stand half way down the hallway
And between them you see a flanker deep in conversation. Yeah. Well, what the fuck? Why am I sitting out there?
Let me in you hang back and watch the scene. I'm sorry
The council is in session. You cannot be disturbing them. Blanker is shaking his head
That is incorrect as you well know the guard smiles tightly in reply blanker turns around and waves to you
Please join me. Yeah, what the fuck man you stand astride. You leave me outside for like an hour
I'm sorry, but there's always okay if i'm gonna if we're adventuring together you and I you and me us
And I say don't come in yet. Let me go in there you wait outside
But if more than 30 minutes pass
Come in with your swords run and be ready to fucking kill. You know what I mean?
Like you give a time limit if 35 minutes pass come get me because something horrible happened to be ready with a fucking magical fireball
Okay, always give a hard time limit the council. I'm afraid the council is in session. The guard repeats louder now
Wait, I need to see what are you talking about? We need to see them and I need to see them
No one sees the council when they are in session. Um, what does flanker do?
You hang back to see what flanker will do the assassin bows his cowled head. I am sorry for your family
He says quietly then a moment later his long steel blade is in his hands and at the neck of one of the guards
I didn't do it. I didn't do anything. Um, should I just let him do it? Should I go for the other guard?
All right, we're gonna go attack the other guard. I gotta follow flanker's lead here
The two guards leap into defensive positions
Wielding their halberds weapons with reach hard to defend against and capable of doing unusual amounts of damage
All in the three fucking damage move the guard raises halberd
He is clearly shaking with fear hardly surprising since flanker is already besting his comrade
You feel the weight of your sword and bring it round to slice deeply across his chest
The council guard responds with a tough blow balancing strength and impact
But he has misjudged your strength and you knock him back you catch him deep in the side
His tunic reddens well played friend flanker murmurs from the other side of the hall
You see his arm grow tense. He is readying for a strong attack. Be aware. He's gonna attack you with a strong attack
All right, ow
Okay, so that he used a lot. So we're gonna go with like a small one like two like three three point. Oh three point one
That's okay
Three point one time to attack you swing your sword fast
Pants heavily he's toying with you. All right, should I defend i'm going all in he's coming in hard
Fuck it hurts so bad
flanker is back seating you
You whip up your defenses as he attempts a strong stroke flanker turns from his own fight to laugh deeply
I see you've lost none of your powers of foresight
Uh, let's go like 1.8
All right. Now we go
Things are getting serious. The guard is now fighting for his life. You see his biceps tense. He's preparing to strike hard
more than six
Yes
What was that?
That was flanker and the other guy he was looking over laughing while clang clang clang clang clang clang with fighting the other guy
What do you mean? What was that? You know exactly what the hell that was. He's like
They're sword fighting next to me
All right
Uh, it is enough time to finish him the guard collapses backwards against the stone floor of the chamber
At the same time you hear a second scream. The other fight has ended as well
Flanker has cut his man down you and your comrade clean your blades
Flanker says a short prayer and then tastes a fingertip of blood from his victim opening the door
He gestures for you to go first council. This is the main council chamber
Rewind stop. Okay sip. Okay. Let's do that again
This is the main council chamber of caray
That's a hard sentence a wide room with a domed roof supported by tall pillars ornately carved with monsters
serpents and instruments of torture in the center
12 throne-like seats are arranged in a circle with one on a raised dais
Presumably the seat of the first noble all are empty a chalk circle has been drawn just inside the ring of thrones
Flanker frowns. This is not right walk around the chairs. You make a slow circle of the chairs
Flanker doing likewise in the other direction. No one here. No secret doors. No hidden passages
You notice the chairs all have names on their backs
The throne of the first noble has the name sansis embossed in gold leaf on its back
The names of the others are smaller and fashioned from plain iron mulas tiffin lorag shinva
Ziren and theta it would seem that none of the chairs have been satin for a very long time
Sitting the throne over the circle you approach the chalk circle. It appears to be just what it seems
A circle inscribed on the stone floor of the room. The only remarkable thing about it is how perfect it is
It is a flawless curve
Rather too well drawn that makes me suspicious
Don't fucking walk into the circle. Don't you dare i'm gonna sit in the throne
You walk back to the first noble's chair and lower yourself down
Crossing your legs and surveying the room. Flanker looks up from his forensic investigations of the chalk circle with amusement
Should I go in let's just should I go into it? I don't remember
I don't remember what happens does something bad happen? What happens? I don't remember
Leave leave leave is it I I think something bad happens. There is nothing here. This has been a waste of time
You remarked to flanker the assassin shakes his head. Perhaps i've learned something
He points to the circle on the floor. Do you see that? I think that is a portal trap. No, it's not
What's a portal trap?
The portal traps of kare will build to protect citizens in one area of kare from the citizens in other areas
Each region dwarf towns finnville the rest were given one trap to place as they saw fit and to move whenever they chose
Then if anyone from a neighboring town attacked they could not tell what was a trap and what wasn't so what is this doing here?
Now that is a very good question by all logic. It should not be here. They are quite invisible
They can appear as anything but should you stand in one you will be transported. But where are the nobles?
Blanker looks as puzzled as you I cannot believe they fell for their own trap
They are fools, but not such fools as that but here is a portal and they say sansis entered yet never left
Transported where you ask looking at the chalk circle of curiosity wherever the center chooses
Inside solid rock high in midair the tradition in kare has been to dump
Unfortunates into the sewers most do not come back
Blanker moves suddenly towards the door then turns to you
But the important thing about traps is that they are no longer under the control of the people of kare who controls them now
Your naivety is most pleasing. What do you think when a people is given something of power who takes that thing away?
The nobles of course for many years now every trap in kare has been moved and placed
By sansis himself and where is sansis now? He's not here indeed indeed not
Blanker turns about once more. I have seen enough. I must think on what we've seen
So why are the guards here? Are the guards just sitting here? The guards were just outside the door?
No, you can't you can't go there. Sorry. They're it's in session right now. How long were they there for?
We just killed two random guards for absolutely. No reason. They were just npc guards
They were just hanging out. I could step into it. Should I step i'm going in i'll remind if it sucks
With his attention turned you take a deep breath you step towards the chalk circle
You feel nothing as you cross the boundary
But one moment you are in the council chamber and your foot touches nothing inside and you are falling back in the sewer
Shit, all right back it up. No, no, no, no, no, don't do it twice. No back up. Okay. There we go
Oh, we have to do this again. It's fine. And that's probably i'm gonna call it here
I mentioned that I wanted to do more streams this week
But less time because i'm still not feeling great and i've got to go do something. I got something I have to do
Uh that might take a while. So sorry
Sorry
So if you weren't here at the beginning of the stream
I said that I was only going to go for like three or four hours and we were going to stream tomorrow and thursday and then saturday
I'm going to get to this point here. So tomorrow we're going to just pick up right where we left off here
We are absolutely going to get through part two tomorrow and likely start at least the beginning of part three thursday something else is happening
Which I don't I can't really talk about right now because I don't know
Exactly, what is going to happen?
So I don't want to like talk about something that either does or doesn't happen, but should be fun and then saturday
Is green screen movie night part two? Is it a sponsored stream? No, it's not something else. But yeah, we're um,
We'll be back. We'll be back tomorrow and I say we and I mean me maybe you if you come back and watch
Okay, cool. That makes me suspicious. Let's leave. There's nothing here portal traps. Yes. What does that do add clues?
What does it look like interesting? Oh, okay transported where can you avoid them? How where the nobles I don't know
Where does a trap go? I don't know who controls them. Why is there a trap here? Who is I gotta get all this info?
Okay, let's get out of here. All right, so blanker and I are leaving the council chamber
And we are gonna call it right here when I get out
The road climbs further looping back on itself as it climbs several little alleys disappear off between homes and buildings on either side
This area of town is a spider's web that would be easy to lose oneself in you pass a shop with a brass sign above its door
Metal workers guild. However, it seems to be closed for the night. Oh, it's closed. Okay
Uh, I sneezed and i'm gonna sneeze again. So we'll call it here
We need to go remind me tomorrow that we need to go down here. This is the next
destination
So this is where we're gonna go. It's a bit
I mean, I really am sneezing but i'm pressing the view button a little like a half second too late, right?
We need to go to the falling quarter get the last line
And then I will tell you if we get the last line down here for the first time in me ever playing sorcery
Will I leave kare?
Without just saying fuck it. I don't care lorag come with me. This would be this would be the first time
So that's cool. I usually just go through it and go. Ah, whatever. I don't care and then just keep going
Okay, that's it. We'll see you guys tomorrow. We're gonna complete part two
We'll do a little bit part three and then some other stuff
We'll take a break from sorcery. Uh this coming week and we'll see if you guys really like it
I mean this seems like a lot of people are just having fun hanging out. It's a chill thing to do
it's really just
Nice, it feels nice to play so we'll see you tomorrow. Thanks for watching everybody tomorrow
Uh, probably around the same time somewhere between like two two to three ish green screen movie night is this saturday part two is this saturday at
4pm pacific. We'll see if you're gonna show up. We got we'll be streaming pretty much all week. See you tomorrow
Good night and goodbye and then baseball right that baseball is um, not long after that baseball's the 19th
I wonder what what could we do next week if we could if we finish part two of sorcery tomorrow start part three
Do this thing on thursday potentially green screen on saturday
um
Because i'm not yeah next week is going to be the last week of like regular streams because obviously
Um leading up to baseball i'm gonna have to spend a lot of time on it
We'll figure we'll do something fun. What time is baseball? I think it's gonna be
At like three or four o'clock in the afternoon. I'll get you guys a hard date
Like i'm in a hard time. Uh, i'll confirm it maybe earlier
It's either gonna be i'm trying to think of when it would be okay
It's either gonna be like three or like two
PM you're gonna give us a hard time play stray
I keep seeing people talk about how that's like the greatest video game ever made. Is it really that good?
Is stray that unbelievable? I keep people keep talking about how unbelievable amazing of a game it is. I don't know. Maybe we'll see
Thanks for watching everybody. We'll see you soon. See you tomorrow or if you're not going to be with us tomorrow
Maybe we'll see you on um saturday or something. Good night guys. Take care of yourselves call your mother