What's happening? How are you doing? You said no delays? It's 402. It's 402.
I actually turned the stream on at 401. No, there were no delays. 120 seconds late. Yeah.
Whatever. How you guys doing? It's Cuphead time. Yep. Funny story about Cuphead.
So I obviously reinstalled it. I got into the game. Just to get a feel again to how
the game works and everything, right? And I beat, because my save file didn't carry over for some
reason. I don't know why. It's been a long time. So I beat the first five or six bosses and kind
of painfully went through some of the running gun levels just to get some money to be able to get
some of the upgrades. And I was like, I fucking hate this game. It's like, I hate this. And the
DLC fights are apparently like a way harder, right? So I figured that would be a funny title. Now,
I'm kidding. It's going to be fun, but I don't have my save file. So I don't have all the
unlockables, but I don't need the unlockables. This is all I need. I need the spreader,
the invincibility power up. And that's it. That's it. That's it. Don't, I don't care about anything
else. Just give me the spreader attack and the invincibility. And I got it already. I'm ready to
go. You want the homing one? Well, if I have problems, I can, I have smoke dash too. Yeah.
I got, I got enough to make it so I was gonna get destroyed, right? I also, okay. I got to remember
how I did the controls last time. Did I make B dodge or circle dodge on PS4? Cause it triangle
or what triangle or Y is dodge by default. I'm trying to remember what I did. Does anyone
remember? Did I do R? I did R2. R2 is probably not a bad idea. R2 for dodge. Shit. That's actually
really good idea. I might do that. I did change it. I remember I did. Cause I was, I got really
mad. But before we do anything, I have to have a few announcements. Announcement number one
is very, it's about the green screen. I told you I'd have some things ready for you.
So everybody tap, tap, tap, tap, tap, tap, tap. Hello. Hello. You have, and should I wait? Well,
I wait till a lot of people get here. Is this your face on the moon and the planets?
What kind of ego megalomaniac would do something like that? He's a NASA imagery. Okay. Well,
let's wait. Just wait a minute. Just hang on a minute. The best part about this is I,
I could have had this changed a bunch of times by now. Since this thing was created, there's what?
Three or four other planets. Only two planets exist in this. So it's Earth, Jupiter, the moon
and the sun. That's it. There's no other planets. And we have every planet at this point.
I like to think that at some points, I don't know. It's funny to me.
You put the emotes in chat right now that are not in the solar system in the intro.
Jeremiah, I haven't watched in a year. Let's go. Hold on. I have a couple of announcements.
I have a couple of things to talk about. And I'm just hanging out. We're just sitting around.
I haven't watched you in 10 years. You know, it's kind of funny. Somebody could actually have said
that. Hey, dude, I watched your grandpa insane aquarium video. And then I didn't come back for
10 years. You could actually say that. That's that that much time has gone by. All right,
are you ready? Here we go. All right, let's talk about green screens. First of all,
green screen you have until 1201 on Monday the 18th to submit a green screen video.
That is precisely two weeks from this moment right now. Pacific. So essentially Sunday the 17th at
night. If he's not if it's not ready, it's not right. You have two weeks. There are rules you
need to follow. They are in the discord right now. They're posted there for you to read.
Read the entire set of rules before you do anything. That's too long. I'm gonna forget.
He's giving us homework. What do you mean rules? There are there are rules. Tell us the rules.
I mean, I could tell you the rules or you could just go read the rules right now.
Right this very second. You could want to read you the rules.
Do you have to hear it from me? Is that what it is? Would you like me to read you the rules?
All right, let me read that. They will be posted in the look. There's going to be a form.
It's going to don't worry. Just just keep an eye on the discord. There'll be announcements.
There'll be things just go look in the green screen submissions form. I can read you the
rules that you want. Let's do that. Fine. Okay. Ladies and gentlemen, rule number one. Listen to
me. Let me find them because I I've wrote them and I need to find where where they are.
Here they are. Ladies and gentlemen, your submission submissions must be between
10 seconds and three minutes. And they have to be uploaded to YouTube between 10 seconds
and three minutes. Just like in previous years. Also, if your video is of me just dancing
or of a song or something, it cannot be longer than 30 seconds. 30 seconds for kind of a dancing
loop. That's what it is. 11 seconds. Got it. Yeah, that's fine. There is a max of stop
residents sleep. Bring me this is important green screen information. There's a max of two
submissions. I really have just going over the syllabus. Can I just play Cuphead now?
I feel like a teacher. There's a max of two submissions per user. This actually is really
important. I need to make this really clear. This rule is important. Listen to me. You can only
submit two times. If you have previously submitted a video for an old community content night,
and you want to resubmit it. That submission had to have come in after the last time we did the
broadcast. May 22 2020. So do not submit something before 2020. That is a green screen edit that you
still have. They're not going to be accepted. But on top of that, if you do fall in that category,
if you do fall in that category, it is incredibly highly encouraged that you reevaluate the video
and add some potential new content. Think about how much time has passed since we last did this.
A lot of the jokes in some of these videos from two years ago, probably not relevant anymore.
So I'd rather have stuff from recent time than from two or three years ago.
But you guys told me to read this. You guys, you told me to read this. You said I want to know.
Read it to me. Okay, here's the next rule. This is lame. I'm explaining the rules. All right,
you know what? You can read it. If you don't, by the way, no, you know what? Fuck that. I'm
not going to read you the rules anymore. If you want to know the rules, go read it. If you don't
read the rules and you submit something and you didn't follow the rules, you're going to get
snapped out. Okay. The amount of submissions will likely be five to 10 times larger than any previous
time we've ever done this. So any submission that comes in will potentially not be shown or
seen regardless of its quality. There are 10 rules. You're going to be here for a while. You
little shit. Whatever. You can read them if you want. Somebody tell me my porn setting was on.
Oh, this is okay. This is pinned. These are pinned messages. Oops. All right, let's play Cuphead.
Fine. I don't want to read anything. Well, that would have been fun to hear that delicious last
course. It's a delicious last class. It's kind of loud. How loud is that? Okay. All right,
you guys ready? What's up? You guys good? Good. What's a good place for a webcam for this game?
Those roles aren't put up yet, so nobody can read them. Oops. They'll be there, but you got two
weeks to make the video. You can just read the rules. They'll be there in like an hour.
Why does it look off center? Is that off center? Whatever. All right, Cuphead DLC. Let's go.
Yeah, 48% already in the main game. What? I played for like two hours last night. What? All right,
so I wanted to get some money. Center right. What do you mean? Like over here? Like here? I feel
like that's going to block a bunch of shit though, isn't it? Was it down here? Should I even just
turn the webcam off? Bottom right's better. Doesn't that show lives though? I don't know.
Yeah, I know this film grain in this game. You can't turn it off unless you go into like the
system files, but whatever. I would probably, I would turn it off and somebody would say I was
cheating. You know what I mean? Somebody be like, oh, he turned off the vignette. Now, of course,
the game's easier for him. All right, so let me, let me, let me go see, I want to see the DLC.
Yes, I've beaten this game before, but I, I came in here. Here we go. So I talked to, let's, I want
to see, I want to see the DLC. I didn't, I didn't do this. Oh, shut up. How come you're so orange?
This is a new webcam. What can Legendary Chalice be looking for all the way out here?
Oh gosh, Capetta, I don't know. I hope she's okay. We sure are far from home.
Jumping jelly beans. You boys made it. I have the most amazing news.
And it all has to do with these here cookies. Take a bite and see for yourselves.
Wow, that was probably really loud. I'm sorry. Is that that loud? I fucking hate microphones.
Of course, I don't hate microphones. You know, I like microphones if they're a road wireless go-to.
The best microphones. Is that worse noise? It might be. Whatever. All right, so for ages,
I've been trying to find a way to escape the astral plane, but nothing worked. Until now,
boys, let me introduce you to Chef Salt Baker, the greatest chef in all the land.
Welcome, friends. Welcome to my bakery. Oh, Miss Chalice, I see my cookie has worked wonders on
you. Oh, my stars. I'm a ghost again. Oh, my, a finicky thing, that cookie. The taste is sweet,
but the effect is brief. Fret not though, my concerned little cups. I've come up with an
amazing new recipe. One bite of this wonder tart and you'll have complete control over the astral
plane. This wonder tart could bring Chalice back to life for good. No swapping places or nothing.
Indeed, just one problem. The recipe requires exceptional ingredients held by the most fearsome
of foes. Well, if the wonder tart is what takes to bring Chalice back to life, then by golly,
we'll find those ingredients. This game sucks. I'm sorry. All right, fetching those ingredients.
Remember, like any good bake, heart and soul is a secret ingredient. Look, I'm just getting it out
of the way. I'm getting out of the way before I rant about game development. Okay, mad because
bad. Yeah, that's fine. All right, so we're just going to bring the ingredients back. All right,
should I, I got to change some stuff here. Hold on. Should I try R2 for dash? I feel like that's a
good idea. R2 dash, R1 lock, switch weapon L1. Wait, switch weapon, maybe Y, the film grain,
turn off the film grain. The film, it's on every single person's stream. Nobody turned it off to
film grain. Don't make me turn off the film grain. You're going to be the only person to turn this
off. I turned off the film grain. Okay, uh, switch weapon. I'm going to say triangle. That makes more
sense than the L1, right? And then dash R2, switch weapon, triangle, EX shoot. That's fine. All
right. Let me try that and see if that's better. This is going to take a little bit of getting
used to, I think. Whatever. I'll die a few times. Turn off the screen shake. There is no screen
shake. One more thing, chaps. Remember to equip that nifty cookie charm in the menu if you want
to battle as Ms. Chalice. Oh, okay. Play as Ms. Chalice. Gain access to her double jump dash
parry an invincible roll. Um, what? Let's see how that works. I don't have any, I don't, I don't,
whatever. What's this one? Recipe for Ms. Chalice. Why are you orange? I don't know. It's his new
camera. Oh, all right. Seems like a kind of a short jump. Oh, but it's double jump parry dash.
Wait, you can jump, you can dash twice. Okay, this character is broken. This character is fucking
broken. Broken character. Broken. Okay. Dodge roll? Dude, broken character. Okay. All right,
let's go. The fuck? What does it want me to do here? Dodge roll? Oh, it's okay. Whatever. All
right, I get it. It's pretty cool. He's a journalist. All right, what's this? X-ray,
X-ray. Chef Salt Baker awarded best baker in all the lands. Boy, if you're heading down for
trouble, this aisle has got a load of it. But you sturdy pips look like you've seen the upside of
a low down brawl. But hey, here's a little tin to help you on your way anyways. Oh, all right.
Okay, use that to buy homing missiles. Let me explore. What's that? What's that? What's that?
What's that? What's that? What's that? What's that? What's that? What's that? What's that? All right.
It's a really unoriginal joke and chat's going to make it worse. I don't know what I did. What
did I do wrong? An audience at last. The climbing contest medal ceremony is about to begin.
I can't believe I've won. Things are looking up. Okay. How much money do I have? Minus 200
orange. Hold on a second. I got all these like people that are screaming you dudes,
you're orange. I've just got even, I just got more orange. This doesn't feel right though.
Is that right? I feel like that's also not right. Why am I only orange and red? I look like all the
whatever. It's going to stay like this. This is fine. This is fine. This is fine. It's going to
stay like this. This is fine. All right. All the start banning complainers. You have a twilight
filter on? I don't. This is just how the camera came out of the box. Twilight filter? It is. It
is like a soft filter. What the fuck is going on? Why is it doing this? This is just how I took it
out of the box and I turned it on. I swear to you. There's nothing. I didn't turn anything on. This
is just how it came out of the box. Snapchat filter. It's new. I don't know. Whatever. All
right. What should I buy? Broken relic. A simple bobble of unknown orange. I only have five coins.
Heart ring? Gain one HP on your first, third, and sixth parry. That's actually kind of good.
Crack shot and this. All right. I don't have any money. What team? Are you team Edward?
No, I'm not team Edward and I'm not team Lucas, whatever it is. I'm team merchandise.
I'm the guy that I see what's going on here and I start designing t-shirts for the two teams
and make a trillion dollars. All right. Let's go. Gnome way out. Let's just give it a try.
Who is Lucas? I don't know. What's the other character's name? Hey, spikes. How do I get away
from that? Ow. Geese Xing. Oh, what's the special for this? The lob. I didn't even fucking come
close. All right. So this guy sucks. I haven't played cup it in six years. Okay. Relax. I haven't
played cup it in since 2016. Okay. Give her relax. I'm kind of getting used to the new controls.
What the fuck? Where do I go? Oh my God. I thought I thought it was invincible dash.
I thought it was an invincible dash. Didn't say that her dash is an invulnerable.
Oh, the role is invincible. Whatever. Start over. The role is invincible. Whatever. I
where are they going? Shut the fuck up. I'm fucking I'm so mad. I got complacent.
I can't even see. R2 is dash. R2 is dash. R2 is dash. I don't have all the items. Okay.
Like, oh, we just go suck. I don't have all the items. What? And by the way, steam cloud.
Does steam cloud only last for a year? Why is my steam cloud saved? How come my steam cloud doesn't
exist? Where is it? What the fuck just hit me? Nothing even touched me. Okay, go, go, go, go.
We're good. We're good. Phase two. Stupid. I don't think I like. I want to try. I don't
want to try this character. Different character. So much shit all over the screen. God damn it.
All right. What do I have for a move right now? I don't actually don't even know.
What's that? What does that do? What does that do? What the fuck are you talking about? What
even hit me? Oh shit. And it fucked me up. I should have invincibility frames when you do a dodge.
Perry. This is giving me an extra life. There's too much fucking shit to look at.
All right. Get out of here. Come on. Come on. Oh my God. Where am I? What the fucking ceiling hurts?
The ceiling hurts. The fucking ceiling hurts. How am I supposed to go? Excuse me. Where's the
other shit? Where are they? Oh my God. I tried to jump. This one's going to be wary of where
they're jumping out from. Come on. All right. Come on. I got three health. Let's go. And I have a
punch. All right. Quiet. I got it. What the fuck? What the heck just hit me? Bro, don't even. Let's
go. Did I get the old parries? I got how did I not get three parries? I paired three of the
what are you talking about? That's stupid. Three parries. Does that not count as a parry?
Oh, I got the gnome berries. What does that do? It doesn't count. How loud can I scream? I don't
want to do it because I have bad microphone settings. All right. That's fun. No way. Is
there anything else I can do? Can I go down? Not yet. All right. Let's do this one. Equip the
crack shot weapon. Is it better? Crack shot. Straight shot with good damage breaks into weaker
aimed projectiles. Okay, wait, super art shield pal. Someone familiar from the will take one hit
for you. I'll try. I'll do this one. Should I stay as I don't know what that does. I'll still
I'll try this for a little while. Snow cult shuffle. Let's try it. And begin. Fuck off.
I know how to switch weapons. Stop telling me. What the fuck? Okay. Um, what the hell is this
thing doing? What is the power? Excuse me. I'm going fucking what I usually do. That was should
have been dead. How? What? How did I not hurt anything? I didn't even hurt it. I don't I don't
know what this thing is doing, but it's kind of cool, I guess. All right. What the fuck is that
thing? You piece of shit. This thing does a lot of damage. So that doesn't count as a parry.
Fuck out again. That was such horse shit. And you all know it. Oh, invincibility. Yeah.
What does this do? Okay. What? I don't get it. What does that do?
Is it just vertical damage? Why would you use these? What the fuck? That stupid ass popsicle
dog shit. Like, I'm gonna come from all stage right and hit you. I want to I press B to dodge
like an idiot. What was it? It takes 10,000 hours to master something. I don't have that much time
to play cuphead. Okay. Those popsicles are dog shit. I hate them. Especially during this fight
like this. Like they just cut you can't fucking dodge them. They just What the hell?
You should be you should be invincible after you parry something for like a 10th of a second.
Shitty RNG throw fucking coins in the air and see what it lands on heads or tails.
Fucking throw coins in there. They land on tails. Oh god. What does this mean?
What the fuck? I can't hit. I can't do what the fuck was happening. I was trying to dash into
the thing and it wouldn't hit it. I put the ball out. I'm trying to dash into the ball to shoot it.
I touched it like three times. What the fuck? Why? Why? I've like, look, let me show you what
I'm trying to do. What the fuck was that? I was doing this shit. Oh, it works this time.
Piece of fucking junk. Piece of junk. Where's the second jump? Why would you launch me that high?
I'm like a ping pong. Oh my god. Shit. I hate this thing. Get this thing off. I don't want to
use this thing anymore. It like didn't shoot the little snow guy. I can't get tilted on boss two.
He's getting tilted at a children's game. All right. I'm telling you right now,
all kids would cry if they played this. You give this to a kid that under 10 years old,
they're going to cry after five to 10 minutes. They're going to cry. You want to make a kid cry?
What's wrong with you? Fucked up? What's wrong with you? What are you fucked up?
All right. Just don't get hit again. That was such a bad roll right there. There's no where I could
have gone. Heads, heads, heads, heads, heads, tails, tails, tails, tails. Oh, shit. I lose.
I lost. Oh, come on. Wait a minute. Fuck you game. That's not a damaging move. That white snow that
goes across the screen does not hurt you. Really? It's to show you that here come the spikes.
I'm trying. I've been trying to dodge that the whole time. Let's freaking go. Fuck you. So those
don't count as parries. Can you not parry actually as chalice? I do look red when I look so I go. I
look red or orange on this camera. This dude's drinking fossil fuels. I'm just drinking like
fucking oil. Let me. This doesn't look right. This looks so fucking wrong. It's only red or
orange. I'm doing every single other setting. Is that better? Maybe a little. I look really
washed out. You look really dehydrated. I don't I don't know. I think that whatever. That's fine.
I don't care. Washed up. All right. That was that was fun. What's this? Say young fry. I'm
haunt on the trail of a mystery but I'm that contest of skill that broken artifact this eerie
graveyard. I've discovered part of astral energy in all of these places. There must be an order
and method to it. Okay. One two three. One two. Nope. Nope. One two. Uh here. No. One two. Really?
I don't get it. What's the. Yeah wait. Well let me read this again. I'm hot on the trail of a mystery
but I'm stumped. That contest of skill that broken artifact this eerie graveyard. Okay. Contest of
skill. The broken artifact. One in the middle and the eerie graveyard is this whole thing.
Doesn't matter. It must be an order. How am I supposed to know this order? Yeah I don't know.
I'm just considering a guess. There's no way I could know. I'll get it. Maybe I'll do it later.
All right. This looks like a plain one. Dog on dog fight. Oh god. This already sucks.
Oh shit. Let's load up some cup head.
That's good. Just duck. That's just I don't even know that I just looked over on my right side of
the screen. That thing hurts me. How's the audio? I gotta get the super built up. All right. Phase
two. What do you got? Let's go. What the fuck? Do it. Did it hurt? What just happened? Am I hurting
him? What the fuck? Dude how am I supposed to play like this? Oh my god. Okay. That makes the first
phase nothing. All right. Come on. This one's not bad. Just get a jump. If you guys want some
some actual tips on how to play games like these. I know that I are. You suck. You should be looking
in a two to three foot radius around your character. I'm not even looking at the enemy
right now. I'm just looking at like a circle around my character. Always. Fuck. Here we go.
Ready? God damn it. God damn it. Where am I going? Oh my god. That sucks.
I'm going back. Okay. On that phase, we're going shotgun blast. Yeah. Without a doubt.
Brawl is surely brewing. Come on. Come on. Let's go. Not a big deal.
Fuck. Yeah. Oh my god. I just went the fucking my fingers. I just I hit the wrong button to
switch weapon. I've I've changed. I haven't pressed that button like an hour and 10 minutes.
I want to change this shotgun. All right. This is it. This is it. This is the one. This is the one.
Let's go. Stop being angry and play. It hurts my fucking brain. Yes. Yes. Yes. Yes.
We're good. No parries. I would be getting such great scores if these parries counted.
All right. Somebody help me here. Somebody help me. Can I not parry as Miss Chalice? Am I? You
can't. I can. Dash. But yeah. But when I dash parry, it doesn't count. Jump dash. You can't
just dash. You have to. I've done it a bunch of times. It hasn't counted. Only optional parries
count. You didn't parry. Yeah. But I mean, like the whole time I've been playing the last three
bosses, I've parried a shitload of stuff and it didn't count. I'm dashing into them and it counts
as a parry. So why is it? I don't get it. I'll prove it. They weren't optional parries. Boo.
Did I scare you? Nothing I love more than a good ghost story around the campfire.
Yeah, I had heard a word of a ghostly gal roughing up no good varmints around here.
You know what? That's been in my body for four days. I've been that I feel great right now.
You know, how many times I've gone like this, looking at like up to a light and towards like
the bright sun and stuff. We're not looking at the sun, but you know what I mean? I can't. I
haven't got that on four days. Stop talking about me. That's what that means. All right.
I'd sure love to tell the tale of the villainous veggies vanquished.
High noon hoopla. You should make chat slower.
There were 500,000 people here. How is that going to make any sense?
Okay. Listen, you know, in your school cafeteria, you know how loud it is in there? Just those
voices that are just imagine that like times 500. Of course we can't see. Of course we can't hear
anything. This is this is like 5000 school cafeterias in here. Can I shrink? No, not with
this. I thought I could. Oh, I can shrink and hit the wrong button. What the fuck is going on? Dude,
what the hell? Oh, what? Oh, the gold's coming out. What the heck? Oh, damn. This is weird.
Yeah. Oh my God. What the freak are you talking about? You have to go through the,
this one's long and this one sucks. This part is horrible.
Get out of here. I wouldn't even that fucking hard. So Perry's. All right. There we go. What
the heck? There we go. Time to pay out. Oh, you guys have been betting. Wow. Some of you
guys made out pretty good here. Desert rhymes. All right. But what about this puzzle thing?
How come I'm so white? Because I turned my white balance down because it makes me orange. Puzzle
is after the game. Oh, okay. Hey, Fusty. Thanks for the raid. Welcome, Fusty. All the raiders.
Oh, wait. No, no. Back up. Bootlegger Boogie. Why do you continue to annoy us?
Get out of here. Oh my God. I'm going to be so bad at this one. I'm so bad at
going down. It's ever since Super Mario. It doesn't matter. This is going to be horrible for me.
These explode or something. What do they do? Oh, they do explode into bugs. Whoa. You can't kill
that. What the heck? Whoa. Hello. Is that hurt? Which hurt? Which one? Which one of these hurts?
One of these hurts. Which one? Which one hurts? Bro, get out of the fucking way. Where are you
going? Where are you going? And be good. I double jumped, you dumb game. I hit X twice.
All right. This actually... Okay. Excuse me. Dude, I don't know when the fucking thing starts.
I... It's like the go up, up, up, down, down, down, down, down, down, down, down, down, down,
down, down, down, down, down, down, down, down, down, down, down, down, down. I hate falling
through floors in games. I hate it. It's so annoying. I hate the fall through the floor mechanic.
I am so bad at it. Oh, shut up. I hate it. No. Yes. Uh-oh. Oh, come on. Mid animation.
What is he doing? Oh, God. What do I have to hit? Hey. Got it.
Fuck that. Now, I don't stop playing this game until I get to this screen a lot of times, guys.
In no way. I don't. Nope. Not going to fucking do that. We did it. That was the last ingredient
we needed for the wonder tart. Let's get back to... Did I beat it? Did I beat the DLC? Did I do it?
Oh, no, no, no, no, no. I don't want to do this. Ladder and... Oh, yeah, yeah, yeah. Okay.
So I should do that first? If I go in there, am I going to end it? Ladder. Oh, okay. The king's leap.
What? Hail ye cups, I bid thee welcome to my floating palace. I am the one true king,
the king of games. From afar, I've seen you battle with zeal and aplomb, and though I grant
thee a place in my royal tourney, and these bouts, your weapons and charms shan't be of use,
you'll have to find different means to best my champions. From victories, riches,
now into the frie... So I can't use any of my items? How did I get all that on my finger?
How did I get all that on my finger? I didn't even do anything. What just happened?
I don't know how I did that. Okay, so... Oh, I can't, I can't shoot anything?
Okay, so just dot parry. Well, never mind. All right, I get it.
Okay, so that was like a little tutorial. Wealth untold. One, two, two coins. All right.
The next match. Whoa, all right, let's go. What's this one?
I can't shoot. I got the stupid grease all over my hands and it's everywhere. It's all over the
controller. Okay, I get it, I get it, I get it, I get it. Oh, I'm gonna get so greedy here.
Oh, God. Shut up. I'm so impatient. Oh, shut up.
That hitbox makes a lot of sense. Fix it.
That's when he goes, when he goes like, look, he does that.
That was almost perfect. I'm just getting so lazy and greedy. Stop being greedy and stop being lazy.
I have the same problem with Dark Souls bosses, man. I just want to get in there and just start
punching and slashing. I don't want to wait for you to go here. No, just, I want to just punch,
punch, punch, punch, punch. That's an opportunity. Oh, greed. Come on, dude. Stop. Okay. All right.
That's not so bad. Once you get a hold of it. Okay, more coins. I actually really need these.
Did I do it? Is that it? Is there more? Oh, there are more ladders. Okay. New challenger lies beyond
the door. Still dodges. Yep. Do I have to put these out or I'm gonna put them out. Oh, God.
All right. I get it. I get it. I get it. You just spawned on top of me. All right. But if I was
doing fine, I was doing fine. Followed me all the way back over here. What the fuck? Oh, stop. What
was that? Dude, what the hell was that? Do you eat peanut butter out of the jar with your fingers?
No. Do you? I was, I was drooling. It was, it just wasn't moving.
Oh, stop doing the fucking daffy duck. Get out of here. All right. Yes. Yes. Yes. Yes. Yep. Hold on.
All right. More money. Cool. How many of these are there? I haven't blinked in, I think,
over an hour and a half. Launch them back. Yeah. Okay. All right. I get it. Come on.
Oh, this shit's coming out of the bottom. Dude, stop shooting that. I was trying to be fucking
cheeky. What? No, go this way, bro. There it is. All right. More money.
That's a different door. Stop being good at this game. Again, I need to make sure everyone's very
aware of this because it's very important that I continue to prove this. If the game has two to
three moves, I will fucking dominate it. Jump, dash, shoot. That's it. I will absolutely destroy
that game if there's two moves. If the move is jump and shoot, I'm going to do very well. I'm
very simple, right? I'm very simple. But with the simple shit, I can do it pretty well. Just like
dodging an axe. Not that hard. It's just move out of the way of the axe. I think I would be very
good at it. You know what? Honestly, you know those rooms with the lasers that all the spy movies
where they go in? Watch out for the lasers. I would be that person in the heist. The person that you
send in to make sure they don't touch the lasers. That's it. My only job is to don't get touched by
this thing. It won't touch me. It just will not. Oh, this is cool. Oh, I ran out of juice.
You ran into a stationary microphone. I wasn't trying to dodge the microphone. See, that's where
your logic is flawed here. If somebody picked up the microphone stand with the microphone and
threw it as a javelin at me, it would be yank. It would not touch me. I wasn't dodging it. I was
unaware of its existence. Three coins. Tournament has concluded. Henceforth, my castle shall remain
a training ground for thee. Fare thee well, champions. That's cool. And there are more little
kind of hidden secret little things like that. So how can I do that? Can I turn the fire on?
Do the puzzle. How? Should I know it at this point? I can't believe I've won. Things are looking up.
Second place just ain't right. Down one place from last year. It ain't right. I trained too hard only
to come in third. Wait, things are looking up. So what middle first row middle just ain't right.
Down one place. So down right. So middle, top right most. It ain't right. And then right.
So it's middle, right, right, or middle, right, left. No, what the fuck was it? Not right. Yeah.
Okay, so hold on. Hold on. I can't believe I've won. Things are looking up. Second place
just ain't right. Down one from last year. How do I look at it? Up, down, left, left.
No help. No help. How come I can't touch the middle one? Why can I touch the middle one?
Give me the answer. I don't know. I don't care. I just want the answer. That's not right.
Use the relic? How do I use the relic? It's equipped. It's not right. Top, middle, middle,
left, middle, right. That's what I just did. Wait, top, left, middle. What did you say?
Wait, they can be on the same row? That's right. Oh shit. Hold on. Oh, they can be on the same.
All right. Hold on a minute. Upper, bottom, middle, left. Thanks. Appreciate it. Think of it as a
numpad. Someone just give me the answer right now. Give me the answer. Give me the answer.
Give me the answer. Give me the answer. Up your ass. Give me the answer. Top, middle, down, right,
right. Thank you. I didn't know. I did. Whatever. I thought you were smart. Well,
before I do this, let me just say one thing. Yeah, I played Diablo Immortal. I don't recommend it.
Don't play it. It's really not good. Don't play it. There's no reason to download it.
But I got to the section where there's nine torches, and you have to light all the nine
torches. I couldn't do it. It was a simple puzzle. When you turn this torch off, the ones next to
it will turn on. I sat there for probably one full hour trying to do it. I couldn't do it.
I can't do that kind of shit. We've got a raid from Joel. What's up, Joel? I hope you're doing
well. Welcome, everybody. Welcome to the stream. Currently at the, I think, one of the last things
in the Cuphead DLC, and I've only been streaming for an hour and 45 minutes. I thought this was
going to take me all day. I thought this was going to take all day, but thanks for the raid, man.
Hope you're doing good. Okay, well, that hurts. All right. You have the capacity of somebody with
a squashed head. How did I get hit by something already before the fucking cut scene? All right,
this one doesn't fuck around. All right. That's the lightning from under the cloud. Of course.
I can refund it. No, why would I? It's fun. What's happening? Am I winning?
Am I beating them? I don't know. Did I win? Holy shit. Could it be the fabled cursed relic long
thought lost of time awoken at last? I've seen writing that say despises bravery. For the greater
foe more evil shall go. What could it mean? What does that mean? Jinxed curio that inflicts various
status ailments. Does it make it hard mode? I don't get it. It just went random. How did I
brute force that? Don't equip that. Yeah, I'll keep it un-equipped. It makes the game really hard.
I have money. Hold on. What should I get? Full screen piercing three-way shot. Whoa.
Foe interest. Fake phony interest. Foe interest for the YouTube video. Foe interest.
Ooh, I like, let me try this. Roundabout. Should I try it? I don't want that. I mean, just buy them.
Why not? I'll try it. I'll have to do the recipe, right? Well, let me do that first. I'll keep what
I have. Uh-oh. Here it comes. Welcome back, you meddlesome brats. I didn't think you'd be back so
soon. No matter. It's too late to stop me now. The wonder tart will be my finest work yet.
Ah, shame I never told you about the most important secret ingredient. Coffee. Oh,
I thought we were coffee cups. Whatever. A living soul. While you suckers were out
doing my bidding, I nabbed your little friend here. When his soul is baked into the wonder tart,
the cosmic powers of the astral plane will be mine. Mugman, Ms. Chalice, it gotta help me.
But first, I'll take those ingredients and then I'll use your heads as serving dishes.
Oh, my God. That's fucking scary. All right. That hurt. What? Run that all the way back. I dodged it.
Oh, my God. My eyes. Oh, my God. This is so brutal. All right. What's phase two?
God, here he goes. Oh, shit. What do I have to hit? Oh, my God. All right. All right. All right.
Okay, I got it. I got it. This is really cool. Use the new gun. Oh, yeah. I kind of like this one.
There are bugs in my hair for all so long. No, I didn't want to do that. I didn't want to
do that. Bad RNG. Dirty streaming. No, I'm not. I'm very clean. I'm incredibly clean.
I'm very clean. Don't ever say that again or you're going to get timed up for a fucking whole day.
Let's go. All right. Now I know what to do. Oh, my God.
Whoa. Where to? What's going on? What the fuck?
And bugs in my hair. God damn it. I'm so actually mad. This one's the best one so far.
I like the first boss and this boss the best. If this is the end of the DLC, which we'll find out
very shortly. Let's go. All right. Don't get hit here. All right. Let's go. Let's go. Let's go.
Let's go. When do I use it? God, how are you supposed to not get hit by that? I pressed
it twice. Should I not even fight? Or is this him? I'm so confused. Oh, my goodness. Don't die.
There it is. All right. Hell yeah. Let's take an A. You didn't do every parry. No, I didn't. Cuphead.
Thank goodness you're okay. That dastardly salt baker. He had us hoodwinked the whole time.
Yeah, Zoogs, this place is coming down. Let's get out of here.
I didn't press A. No, my bakery serves him right for duping us. But with the bakery destroyed,
you're never going to get that wonder tart, Chalice. That's okay. If some poor soul has to
be sacrificed for me to live again, it just ain't worth it. But mark my words, boys. I'm never going
to stop searching. And in the meantime, if you ever find yourselves in a scrap, just one cookie
bite away. Besides, who needs a wonder tart when they can have a two new best pals instead?
Oh, hold on. Well, I didn't beat the game.
Did I? I'm not done streaming. We're still going. I kind of maybe I'll just keep playing this for a
little bit because I want to try the other items. Is there any more? That's in? Okay. Try them on
expert mode. Yeah, I'll try a few. Yeah, I really completely underestimated how hard that was going
to be for me. I was thinking, man, this is probably going to be at least an eight hour
experience of me playing this. You mean overestimated? You know, the right one,
whatever the one that's the right one. The one where I think I'm going to be worse than I am.
Our sincere appreciation to the members of our team whose loyalty and creative endeavor
made possible this production. So do you want me to keep playing? I'm still here. I want to just
play. Maybe try the expert stuff. And then maybe I want to try the other items. Dude, if I'm never
going to play this game ever again, then I might as well do a little bit right now. What I think I
really. All right. So here's the here's the plan for the rest of the day. I think as long as we do
that, there'll be enough time later in the stream to be able to add some more stuff at the end,
maybe do a little bit of just chill, chill. And then we can maybe do some tomorrow.
Wicked funny. Can you slow it down? I don't think so. That was a pretty cool ending.
Forty four percent of the DLC. How's it make any sense? All right. I want to let me see
because I want to try the new weapons. I'm not just going to converge and twist up and then
what's this one? Oh, Perry for HP. Let me try these new moves. OK, this is no way out. Expert
mode. It's right. It's got the expert. Oh, it's like kind of a spreader. This one's weird.
How do you how do you make how do you utilize this one? Honest to God, how do you utilize that?
This one's not bad to point it to point it down. Oh, I get it. Does this do enough damage to
justify using it, though? It's kind of weird. It's weird to use. Does it do a lot of damage?
It sucks. It kind of does. All right, let me try that one. Do the secret phase and the dog boss.
This one's not bad. I'll do spread for that. Actually, maybe I should try that. Yeah,
let's try that crack shots. Best weapon in the game. Oh, it went up. What the heck?
Oh, I like that. Good weapon for this one. Hey, oh, let's try it again.
Actually, I didn't like this boss. It was too kind of too random, too random shit going on.
Come on. This thing doesn't hurt him. Where's the damage? Oh, it does that too. All right,
come on, let's go. What's this last phase? I forget. All right, this shit. All right. Oh,
I didn't want to press that. That's fucking I hate this boss. This boss is just like this random
shit flying in every direction. All right, what about another one? What's the secret phase?
How do I do the secret phase? Change weapons in the death screen. How does that work?
Don't kill any ads on the second phase. Okay, don't kill. Okay, cool. That's right. That was
such shit RNG. This weapon's kind of annoying. All right, don't kill the dogs. What? Okay,
don't kill the dogs. You idiot. Did you? I'm just getting lazy. I already beat this dumb,
stupid boss. Shoot. What do you mean shoot? Shoot them. I thought you said don't attack. Don't
hurt them. Don't kill them or something. How much do I have to hurt them? What's going on? How do
I do this? What's happening? You have to do it until they have gray smoke. All right,
afterwards I want to do something stupid. Let's fuck with new people that come in.
I'm going to put a death counter on the screen. It's going to be like 600 something
on a boss and I'm going to be sitting there like crying. Can one of the mods set up like a command
and add like 630 deaths already so then when I die you can do like exclamation point death and
it adds 631. All right, all right, all right. Smoking. That one's smoking. They're all smoking.
They're already smoking. All of them are smoking already. Okay, that one's smoking, smoking,
smoking, smoking. Now what? Great. Nice work. Shut up. I got out of the way. Please.
Whatever. 631. Hold on. Wait, wait, wait, wait. I got to get like into character here.
And the thing is like, let's make it so what a dummy, right? I'm going to use shit that I
shouldn't even be using. What's something that somebody would be like? Wow, this guy's a fucking
noob. Like the extra hit point, right? But I'm a new and I don't understand that what parries are.
Okay. All right. So wait, let me, let me go down here. Use the charm. No, no, I want it to be.
All right, here we go. Ready? And I'm going to individually press the button to shoot.
Fuck. How do you stand still? All right. This is hold the button down. This is games. It's not for
me. I just really, I don't think the game's for me, but I'm going to try and I'll do some
mods. Keep track of it. Whatever. Fucking hate. It's so stupid. Fuck. I don't fucking, I don't
understand why people fucking play this game. I don't, I don't, I just don't get it. I don't
fucking get it. I don't fucking get it. I don't give a people play this. Why would you play this
game? Take a break. I'm not taking a fucking break. Stop saying it. Stop telling me that I've been
streaming for like two or three hours. You can hold to fire. I, I like to shoot losing viewers.
I don't fucking care. Why do, and again, why did people say play this and play the DLC?
That's what I don't fucking understand that this community sometimes I don't play hard. You guys
told me this wasn't a hard, this is not supposed to be a hard game. Why tell me to do this?
Why tell me to play this game? It's, I thought it was like a fun cartoon game.
You're just bad. So actually mods actually start fucking banning people. It's really actually
really fucking annoying. Is it four more? Get the auto-aim weapon. Crying Andy, crying Andy.
Where, where is it? Take a break. It sucks so fucking bad when I look over here and I see
that I've died 600 fucking times. Somebody said to die 600 times in two hours. It's not even
possible. It takes, all right, hold on. How long does it take to die? Let's see. How long does it
take to die? Count. Ready? This is not even possible. Ready? One, two, three, four, five,
six, seven, eight, nine, 10, 11, 12. All right. Let's just benefit the doubt. It takes 10 seconds
to die, right? 10 seconds to die. How many? 10 seconds times 636 divided by 60. All right. So if
I die every 10 seconds, that means I have to die every 20 seconds for this to make any sense.
At that point, man, you don't even play. Why are you here? If you're dying every 20 seconds,
it's possible to do that. That would be so painful. That would actually be painful. 20
seconds every time. That means the stream turns on. There's no intro. I just start walking into
depth, walking into traps and walking into people's... There's no intro. All right. So what
should I do now? Any of the games I should play today? 600. I don't think I died even half that
amount of times in the base game. Let me take it to the other side. Hold on. Let me go off the DLC
island. Play Tarkov. Dude, I'm not playing Tarkov. Okay. Wait a minute. What's this? I didn't do this
one. Did I? Oh, wait. Oh, dude. Tarkov. Is it weird that I think Tarkov is a game that I want to
read the manual for? Like the shit that comes in the disk box. Play Morrowind? I'm not gonna play
Tarkov. That's 30% of games. Go back to Miku? I uninstalled Miku because I never thought I was
gonna play it ever again. You hear what I'm saying? I uninstalled it. I didn't think I was gonna ever
play it. Chills. Well, reinstall it. Is that what you guys want? All right. This has to be unanimous.
This has to be completely unanimous. Do you want me to play that Miku rhythm game? This has to be
80%. Yes. 80%. Oh, no. I've been exposed. You died 79 times. Hey, like five of those would just be
fucking around. So it's like 70. I want to let me do some running gun. All right. What do we got?
Play Miku. Let's get on. I'm hating these levels with a passion. I'm so you know what? I'm actually
kind of glad none of these were in the DLC. I genuinely hated these. Oh, yeah. What is it at?
Is it even remotely close? I wanted to dash through it, not into it. I'm screwed here.
This weapon is so good. Oh, what? What do we got? That's not even. That's not close, guys. That's
not close. 58%. Way too many of you don't want that. I'm not playing Tarkov, but why? I need a
guide to play Tarkov. There's only one way I'll ever play Tarkov. It's like if a Tarkov streamer
or somebody that knows Tarkov is like, Hey, dude, I can teach you Tarkov. You can walk behind me.
And it'd be like, you'd literally just walk behind me and I'll do everything.
But it's not gonna happen. I'm not playing Tarkov. Democracy is dead. No, what? This wasn't a
democracy. This was a goal you had to reach. That didn't say this was a democracy. I said,
get it to 80% or it's not happening. If I can hit one more time by one of these star guys,
I'm gonna punch him in the fucking mouth. Play Isaac? I got a list of stuff I'm gonna jump into.
I figured out. Wobble dogs? No, I'm good. No. Stop it. Noita? That's a- I've not heard that in a
while. What are you doing? I hate this level. Let's go. What about more demos? Do some more
YouTube zoomer humor videos. Morrowind? You don't want me to play Morrowind. It's gonna take us like
three hours to get to the first island. All right, get Morrowind to 80% and I'll download it right
now. No, I'll make it easier. Get Morrowind to 70%. Jumbo rebound. Everyone's gonna leave when I
play Morrowind. We're gonna sit there and just listen to dialogue and opening cutscenes and I'm
gonna kill the first NPC I see and have to restart the game save file. That's- that- there you go.
I just streamed it. I just did it. I don't even need to do it. I just streamed it. What is this
one? Oh, this was in the base game. Oh, I remember this one. This is the dragon one.
This match will get red. Can I charge even more than that? No. What was that?
It's just like a- a pup. Uh-oh. Don't these guys jump? Yeah, they do. Well, you don't think I
fucking knew that? I'm getting real sick of the back seating. You didn't get it to 70%.
You didn't make it. You didn't make- you didn't make it to 70%. What do you mean riot? Recount.
What do you mean riot? No, you- I said 70%. I made it easy. Stop. Stop. Stop. Stop. That tail
should be removed from the game. Where the fuck am I? Play Peglin? No! We want RollerCoaster
Tycoon 3. You're the only one that's written that in the last hour. Oh, by the way, if you have a
green screen submission- oh, something else I wanted to bring up too. So a lot of people that
might be new viewers might not know that- that tail. A lot of new viewers might not know the- the
green screen stream from a couple days ago. We've done that two other times. So there are three
full green screen streams. So don't- you can use them all. Don't be afraid to use them all.
I think a lot of people might think that that was- oh, wow, that was- you just did that for
the first time. Nope, that's the third time we've done that in the last three, four years.
So use all the footage you have until the 18th at 12.01 midnight. 12.01 midnight on the 18th.
That's July 17th, very late at night, to submit your video. There are rules. Please read the rules
that are in the Discord, the channel. There will be a form for you to fill out.
Please do all the rules, otherwise you're going to be in big trouble.
That- this- that sucks. That just sucks. This is base game. We're just like kind of playing for
that. That sucks. That's a dumb mechanic.
Play Cruelty Squad? I don't think I can play Cruelty Squad, guys. I looked at the trailer
and I wanted to puke. I'm sure the game is fucking phenomenal, but it kind of hurts my head.
Play Breath of the Wild? I would rather play Morrowind- Mora- I can't talk. I would rather
play Morrowind than Breath of the Wild. Is that bad? Is that going to make anybody angry?
Just right now, I want to play Morrowind, not Breath of the Wild, but I don't want to play Morrowind.
I hope that makes sense. I hate this boss. This boss is stupid.
I beat this four years ago and I think I said that. The phase three when the little
thing comes out and you- I don't know if I'm going to hit it or not.
You know, I'm not- I'm not paying attention. That's the problem. I beat the DLC in like 60
deaths. Don't ever forget that. I'm just like shit. I'm just shitting here. I'm just talking.
I'm not even playing. Play Morrowind? All right, we have to get you guys to like 70%.
Do something else? I'll do something else after this. I have to beat this guy just because I'm
going to be so pissed off for the rest of the day if I don't kill this thing.
Like, this is going to ruin my day if I don't kill this guy. It's going to ruin my whole day.
More attempts on a boss that I beat fucking five years ago than the entirety of the DLC.
How are you supposed- What are you supposed- How am I supposed to fucking fight this with-
I gotta change weapons. Like, Jesus. That fucking tail. This is not even hard. I just don't care.
Oh my god. I'm so- I don't even care. Like, why do I have to- I don't have to beat this.
This guy's not even hard. I just don't even care. I have to kill this thing.
This dumbass shit boss from 2016. I hate this fucking boss. He's so slow and this- the stupid
moving platforms. I don't even need to beat this. Why am I even here? I beat this guy on expert
already in front of you all. Why the fuck do I care? He has to die. These weapons suck.
I don't care. Why am I doing this? I don't have to do this. I just beat the fucking DLC.
What am I doing here? I can't take it anymore. This weapon sucks. I'm gonna freak out.
Does anyone think it's funny that I'm getting more annoyed and upset at the fucking base game
which I've already beaten after dominating the DLC? Does anyone else think that's funny?
Does anyone else think that's humorous? Because I do. I'm getting more annoyed at a boss from
the base game. It's so easy to fucking fall down when you do that shit. This is my last
try and I'm gonna fucking smash my monitor with a hammer. Doesn't own a hammer? Yes I do. I own
a mini hammer. That's all you need. You don't need these huge hammers. Stop talking. You're
gonna make me mad. These weapons are so bad for this. Oh my god. I don't- I forgot- I forgot
I did that. Why do I care? I can't fucking stop guys. I don't know why I need to beat this stupid
boss. I've beaten this so many times. Why do I care? By the way I have a mini hammer. It's like
this big. That's all. You don't need anything bigger than that. Well you're not strong enough
to swing a hammer a little extra. It fits in way more places. You don't need a huge ass hammer.
You just need one of the little ones. Dude I actually have spent more time on this than any
of the DLC bosses. Put up that 600 deaths thing again. It's just the last phase is just unbearable.
It's so easy but it's- that makes it so hard because he just shoots this- shut up.
You can't even attack him with that- I can't attack him. Oh my god it just auto attacks the
fucking stupid flaming orbs. I beat the fucking secret boss first try in the DLC.
Look at mod chat. Don't distract me right now. I'm trying to get over this dumb thing I'm doing.
I'm just trying to get over playing this stupid game. I have to get over it. Should we post the
rules? Yeah. What if I died? All right fuck this game. Stupid ass game. I don't give a shit.
All right why is this breaking apart in my mouth? Okay I'm fine. I don't even know why I did that.
There was no reason to do that. I beat that boss like five different times over the last five years.
All right so what are we doing? Morrowind? What's happening? Yeah the rule- you can post the rules.
Dick fart. That was a mod that said that by the way just so you know. Morrowind? Copium? Should I
just play Morrowind? Should I just go for it? I don't even think I own Morrowind. Do I own Morrowind?
Does Morrowind even run on Windows 10? Whatever the hell I have.