Hello, how are you? That's good. That's good. That's good. I'm on time. Of course I am.
We've got a day of festivities today. At least a few festivities. Gonna be playing Beam NG Drive,
which I was gonna do scary horror stuff today, but I just didn't feel like it. I'll be honest.
I just didn't want to do it. So this game's kind of complicated. This is a lot of going on in this
game. I don't really know what I'm going to do. Seems like you kind of really need to figure out
how to play it first. So this is going to be tutorial Andy for a little while. If it's too
complicated for my tiny brain, then I will move on to Webbed. I've been wanting to play Webbed for
a little while. You're a coward. You've literally played this game before. I have not played this
game before. No, no, no. You're confusing it with every other time I've crashed a car and laughed.
I know there's been hundreds of times. Potentially thousands of times.
I mean this whole stream you could probably put next to one of the other games where you crash cars
and it'd probably be the same stream. It would be the same stream. But first and foremost,
well hold on. I have to warn you. I may have fucked this up pretty badly. I may have,
well I don't, whatever. I'm gonna wait till there's more than 5k people here.
I'm gonna just chill. Give me a second. Hold on. Okay. Hello. I said to get something real quick.
Mod check? What? This is a sleep stream? Why would I do a sleep stream? What are you talking about?
Let me see. Hold on. I just ran up and down stairs. Hold on. Okay. Laughing at car crash compilation?
Let me learn how to play the game first. You guys are going to laugh and I don't,
you're going to laugh. Everybody's going to laugh because here's your glove.
Fits perfectly. As you see, it fits perfectly. I had this custom fit to make sure I could,
you know, wear it. I promise, I promise I didn't sit on it. I didn't sit on this and get really
mad and get very upset that I sat on it. I wonder how this glove tastes. Homer Simpson? Is that,
what is that? Is that leather? Okay. You sat on it? Now that's fresh leather. What are these
gloves even supposed to be made out of? Hold on. Hold on. I wish I had two. This looks like,
oh, this looks like fucking SpongeBob got rubbed by a car and I like stole this.
Ooh. Ow. Bull, watch out. My thumb. Hold on. Ow. What the hell is he doing?
You know what I've realized about this channel? I'm starting to realize it more and more.
If you don't watch every single fucking stream, you're just, you're not going to have any idea
what's going on. I like feel bad for the people that like I catch like a stream once every like
couple of weeks. What the fuck are you doing? Stop. What are you doing? Stop this. Pretty good.
I can't make a middle finger. There's not five fingers. You have more lower than Dark Souls.
I don't think that's accurate. I just think that there's weird shit that happens like every other
day. What finger should I bite next? Put your middle finger through the middle. Yeah. Hold on.
You know what? Yeah. Fuck you. It's too hard to do it. Uh, flipped. Get the pinky. That's pinky
right here, right? Looks like I have like egg in my mouth. All I didn't tell you is it's made
out of fucking eggs. Oh, it looks like egg. Hmm. What is that? Is that edible? Boy, I think that's
not edible. I don't think that part's edible. That part's not edible. I think that's stuffing.
There you go. Okay. All right. I ate another glove. Okay. All right. I'm done. I'm done. I'm out.
I'm done. Wait, I got one more, one more bite for the camera. I'm not eating at all. What about
like, I can't swallow this. It's fucking pure sugar. I mean, pure leather. I just spit this out.
Oh, I'm gonna puke. I'm not eating the whole glove. I'm not eating the whole glove. I'm taking a few
bites. I didn't eat the whole shoe. You guys didn't hear that, did you? I hope not. I didn't eat the
whole shoe. Why would I eat the whole glove? Come on. I can't. Okay. How about like right here? This
looks so fucking weird. Give him the silent treatment. He has to finish the glove. I'm not
finishing the glove. I'll take one more bite right here for the thumbnail. Like, this is
fucking weird. Don't give me the silent treatment. Give me something else. By the way, I'm never,
I'm never saying this again. I was, if you're curious what's going on, let me just explain
real quick for people who have no idea what's going on. I was convinced that the three stooges
were going to be in Fortnite. Two years ago, I made a bet. I said the three stooges will be in
Fortnite by some, what, last week of April, 2022. It didn't happen, which is horseshit. Like, I don't
know why they wouldn't have been added. They probably will get added. I still believe that.
I genuinely believe the three stooges are going to be in Fortnite. I believe it genuinely. It's
just a matter of time. So look, you can come back to this video whenever the three stooges get added
and be like, holy shit, he actually had to eat that glove thing and they actually got added.
But if the three stooges are not added to Fortnite by April 3rd of 2030, I will have already been
retired. So who cares? Okay. Goodbye. My hands are so sticky. I'll be right back. I'll be right back.
We'll go back to the intro. I'm going to put this in the freezer. Yeah. I'm going, I'm going to the
freezer. I'll be back. I'm so, oh, this is bad. I can't touch anything. Yeah, I can. Here we go.
Okay. Hi. Everything's, I just, my hands are all sugar all over them. This was a very sugary
leather glove. Okay. You ate a glove? Yeah. You missed it. It was crazy. Yeah. So we're doing
BMNG. Uh, I know people are saying, dude, you gotta, oh, BMNG, man. I'm gonna go get this mod
and go get that mod and go get that to download that thing. I go download that car pack and get
this. Let's start. Look, I'm, this is baby steps. I never played this. Let me just see if I enjoy,
I'm going to do the tutorial. I'm going to get familiar with the controls, uh, and we'll see
what happens. Understand? It has car accidents. Oh, of course. Of course. If the three stooges were
still around, would they be fans of your stream? No. Why would they even know who I was? They would
watch dollhouse and go, I could have done that better. Look at these kids think they're so funny
these days. You went through a window. I used to go through a window every Saturday. Really? This
younger generation doesn't understand slapstick comedy. All right, so let's go. We're going to
play BMNG. Uh, if the game is too complicated for me, if I want to pivot, we're just going to
pivot to webbed, which is a spider game. And we play as a spider. It looks pretty cute. You know,
how did your stomach feel after the last stream? It was, I was okay. I mean, it was a little,
it was a little, but it wasn't that bad. I didn't eat that much of each candy. I only had one or
two bites of each thing. I've always eaten whole candy bars. Then. Oh yeah. I would have, I probably
would have felt terrible. Okay. So BMNG, that's the camera's way too big. This is trouble. I haven't
had, I've been doing Cam Andy recently. You notice that? This is the most I've ever used
face cam in the 10, 12 years I've been doing this. I just don't do this. And I never use this.
And for some reason after Elden Ring, it just became, I just got used to turning it on
every day. Where's blood wash? I wanted to chill. I wanted to chill today and it's too scary. We'll
do that a little bit later. We'll do that like next week. Not next week, like later this week.
We'll do that later this week. I have it downloaded. I have it ready to go. I just,
I didn't want to just be screaming. My head kind of hurts. All right. Campaign. I need to do the
driver's training course because I have no idea what the hell I'm doing. So bear with me.
Senseless destruction? All right. Driver training. This game takes like 5,000 horsepower to run,
right? Hopefully my computer is going to handle it. I can use a controller for this, right?
It's all CPU. My CPU is all right. Okay. Accelerating and braking. Welcome to the
ETK Driver Experience Center. My name is Mike and I'll be your instructor for this course.
Let's start out nice and easy. All you have to do is accelerate and then stop before you hit the
barriers. Make sure you brake when you reach the stop sign. Okay. How do you accelerate?
Apparently using arcade gearbox behavior. What the fuck does that mean? Is it X? Orbit. How do I do it?
I thought it's not right trigger or left trigger? Press Q. Realistic behavior. Arcade behavior.
How do you drive? Up? How do I drive? What happened? What? All right. So I was paused. All right. So
right trigger is accelerate. Left trigger is brake. So brake right before I get here.
Did I do it? What? How did I fail? That doesn't make any sense. What? Too slow? I was driving so
insanely fast. That was scary how fast I was going. Oh, we didn't want you to... We wanted you to go
over 60. So start braking now. What the fuck? I don't get it. I don't get it. What does it want
me to do? Stop at the stop sign. What? Do you want me to stop like at the stop sign like here?
That's where the stop sign is. What do you want me to do? I stopped at the stop sign.
Stop before you hit the barriers. I didn't... I did that the first time. I actually did that the
first time. Stop in the zone. I just literally just did that. I just did that. I just did that.
I did that already. All right. All right. I get it. I get it. I get it. I get it. I literally just
did that. I literally, literally, literally, literally, literally, literally just did it.
Yeah, I did. I went and stopped in the middle and said, failure. You're an idiot. This isn't
a real fucking driving game. Give me a real course and I'll be fine. Okay. In the unlikely
event that the road is not straight, you may need to stop accelerating and use your car's steering
wheel. Okay. Try it here on the roundabout, but watch out for the slippery area. Just drive the
car. This is part of the fucking driving test. Yeah. We want you to go 60 and then smash on the
brakes before you get to the driving zone. Go around this roundabout going 50. All right.
Go. You're gonna move the cam so we can see the speedometer. Oh, oops. Get up here. All right.
So you master the turning left. Can you navigate a narrow road? Try to find the proper speed for
those tight corners. Two, one, go. I fucking failed already. Time limit doesn't matter. I'm
being timed. All right. Is there a handbrake? In all driving games, I never use the actual brake.
I use handbrake only. Anybody else like that? R1? Yeah. I only use the handbrake in video games.
I don't think I've ever hit left trigger in a video game when it's a car game. Okay. So
handbrake. Got it. How much was the glove? You'd like to know. Changing lanes at highway speeds
require a gentle hand on the steering wheel. Do you have what it takes to control an 80s supercar?
Apparently not. What the fuck was that? Why is it covered in like grease?
I did it. That was easy. Well done. Who made the glove? I told you. I was gonna just like
fucking ruin everybody's childhood. I was gonna say, I told you. SpongeBob got run over and I
found it. But no, that's not what happened. It was great. It was fake. It was a real glove. Shut up.
Stick to the speed limits on the signs to guarantee success. Okay. 25 miles per hour. Okay.
25 still? I think so. It's all right. I didn't fail it. I didn't fail it. I didn't even get
bumped. I'm fine. Too realistic. It's too realistic. Why would I be doing this in this car, by the way?
This is dad's cigarette car. I mean, this is just the car that just smells like cigarettes.
This is the dad's cigarette car. How did I fail it? What did I do wrong? Is there a time limit?
What happened? What happened? I don't understand. Read the signs. 25. That's what I was just doing.
40. Dude, it's fucking hard. Hold on. Guaranteed my success. That was actually really hard to do
that. This car sucks. It's actually hard. I can't even turn. All guaranteed success at 40 miles per
hour. 40 miles per hour drifting? That's not gonna happen. Okay. 25. I'm not going 40 through this.
That's way too fucking much. That's impossible to go 40 through this. 50? Guys, it's not possible.
It's not possible to go 50. And look at my fucking serious. Whatever. Just start over.
Fuck it. Whatever. I wasn't going 60, dude. What? I have to drift. Okay. Drift? How do you drift?
I am holding. Okay. I am literally holding right and like drifting into it and he just drives
straight into the wall. I'm gonna fail this tutorial. I don't get this. Okay. 40. Big drift.
Why did you give me this piece of shit car? Okay. 50. It's the car's out of fucking control. It's
out of control. The car is out of control. I can't control the car. This fucking thing's out of
control. I can't control it. Did I do it? All right. Good. It's a skill issue. That's fine.
It is. I don't hand run. I've set up a circuit for you to practice what you've learned. Should
be pretty easy. Two laps. No surprises. I have to beat this? No, I don't. All right. I'm good.
Fuck you. God damn it. All right. I'm going too fast. There are no posted speed limits here.
So how am I supposed to know what the fuck to do? I'm hand braking. It's not working. All right.
Slow down. Slow down. Okay. I'm good. Good. All right. I got it. That's it. Right. Nice. All right.
I'm good. Stop hand braking. All right. Hair pins. No fucking way. I'm not gonna be able to do this.
Hold the handbrake to slide around a hairpin. Just like in the movies. Not with a car like this.
Listen to my calls. I'm going too fast. Okay. What? 30? 20 miles per hour? That's not in the
movies. They don't go 15 miles per hour in the movies. There it is.
What? I fucking... How am I supposed to go that fast? Go! Got it. Very cool.
What do you do in this game? Slalom. A slalom course is a hard thing to master. Get a feel
for the weight of the car as you weave between the cones. He's gonna rage at this game. I thought
I was gonna get points off. Not fail completely. Oh, just barely. I want a car like that. Go get
mods. I'm... Rear wheel drive handling. Ruckle moonhawk handles like a boat. So if you can finish
a lap of this circuit first try, you're doing better than most of my students. All right.
Don't get mods. I'm not gonna yet. How the fuck do you drive a car like this? This car's on treads.
It's not even on wheels. I just drive straight. The mirror. Oh my god. How are you supposed to
drive this car? How do you actually drive a car like this? This thing's on ice. This car's on ice.
I can't drive it. Okay. I'm just gonna go really slow. Use the rear brakes? What? All right. Rear
brakes. What do you mean rear brakes? I don't know what that means. I'm all right. I've had a fucking
time. This thing sucks. This thing sucks. Ride driving. Well, this car is impossible to use.
What the fuck, dude? Why would anybody drive this? I fuck... I'm skipping. I'm done. I'm not playing
that one. No fucking way. It's not happening. Like, why would you drive that car? Oh man,
that's a beauty. How often do you drive it? Well, when you want to get in the car with me,
we'll take a ride. And you just literally drive directly into the first wall. Well,
I didn't even read that. Whatever. I wasn't gonna make a joke, but I was like, no, why even make a
joke? That car's not even worth making a joke about. I don't care. This sounds like a cat.
I'm just braking all the way. I'm going to a complete stop and driving the car again.
This is so bad for the car. I'm supposed to be drifting. God damn it. Skip it. Stop accelerating
so hard. I don't play games like this. I play like fucking Mario Kart. I don't even play that
game. I don't like that one either. I don't play games with cars in them. Unless I like the...
Unless it's like GTA. All right. Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa. What's this?
Use a manual transmission for this test. Stay in second gear. Slide the car sideways to score as
many points as you can. All right, let's go. Why am I going backwards? Why is the car in...
Oh, the car's in reverse. I forgot it was manual. I forgot it was manual. Yeah. Yeah.
That's not a man-sized drift. Oops. I don't give a shit. That was fine. All right. Campaigns.
Senseless destruction. Go back. Go back. All right. Somebody said just do free roam. Oh, okay.
Where do I go? West Coast, USA. Dockyards, industrial area. Just like Chinatown. What should I...
Just default. Okay. Well, I didn't know what I just did. I hit A too much fast. I pressed A and I
didn't do anything. This is bright. Retract bed. Extend feet. Tilt bed up. Whoa. Okay. Hold on.
I'm trying to go over the sand jump. How do I fix the car? Okay. This thing is fucked. What do I do?
Can I fix the car? How do I fix it? Press R. Oh, okay. Left on the D-pad. Oh, all right. Cool.
You're a bus? Holy shit. I was ejected. I was ejected from the fucking car. This is still
drivable. Oh my God. What the hell was that? I got ejected in an escape pod. You got vaporized.
All right. We'll put on traffic. How do I put traffic on? Use your steering wheel. I just was
like curious. What's going on? Hit escape. Is it... Oh, hold on. Manage. Fun stuff. Fire. Boom. Break.
Extinguish. Oh, this is a jump right here. No, no, no. I thought I was gonna be able to drive over it.
All right. What? How do I get rid of that? No, no, no, no. Power. Pedestrian. I don't want to put
pedestrians on. No, powertrain. Manage. Clone. Home. AI. Traffic. Spawn. Police. Spawn. Normal.
Wait, this traffic? Where are they? Change cars? Yeah. How do I get out of this fucking pickup?
I don't want to be on a pickup truck. You can fuck with gravity too. Really? Is there a different
camera? How do I get a different camera? Is there a different camera? Vehicle camera. Orbit. Turn
the police on. If they press escape. Manage. Switch. Or select. Holy shit. Okay. What else is here?
I can be in a tractor trailer? What? Oh my god. Okay. I want this one. Argo doors. Is it... Oh.
How do I do that? Check the controls. Yeah. I'll check them. So where should I go? I just...
Can I like just sit and watch the camera? Can I hold control?
I feel like I'm playing GTA V. I'm... I can't... I'm not in control anymore.
This feels so... All right. Reset. Reset. Give me... I want a different car. I want a fast car.
Okay. I want... Wait a minute. I can... Hello? Did I... Did I just run that guy over?
I just ran that guy's whole car over. Hold control and put your mouse over the car.
What? Okay. Am I gonna drown? Hold control. Put your mouse over the car? Strength. Force.
I'm so confused. Strength. Force. Middle click to hang from here. I'm in the water dude. Why are you
beeping at me? I don't get it. What? What? I can just pull shit off the car? Like it's a Lego set?
Excuse me? Use the scroll wheel. What the fuck? Oh. Stay here. Stay here. What am I doing to this car?
Okay. Now pull this way too. Holy shit. Drive while tethered to the ground.
High clutch temperature? Clutch overheating. I just burnt out the clutch.
Okay. But should I try a different car? Okay. Give me a fucking... This is crazy. I didn't know
this game was like this. Fog light? Okay. Manage. Select new car. Something small and fat. Are there
motorcycles? All right. This one right here. Yeah. Right here. Let's go. Fucking Robin's egg blue.
Oh yeah. Hell yeah. The jumps and stuff? Put on slow-mo. Whoa. How do I do slow-mo? Give me a
redo it. Go a hundred thousand miles per hour. What? You can go a hundred thousand miles per hour?
Let me just... Hold on. There's a lot going on in this game. Let me get on the highway.
Drive a GPS. You should just leave the planet. Alt and down. Alt down. Eight times slower than real
time. What? Alt up. Holy shit. Okay. Let me get on the highway. How do you beep the horn? Oh. No,
no. I need to go faster than that. No. I don't want to be back here. I don't want to be back here.
I want to be back up with that error. How do I do a flip? Add a ramp. Okay. Set home. Clone.
Does it have AI? Okay. Manage. Okay. Select. Wall. Mat. What should I put up here? How about a cannon?
Oh, here we go. I need a ramp. Hamster wheel. Oh, hell yeah. How do I move this? Okay. So,
how do I... Can I move this? How do I pick up a car? All right. I need to get in there.
Is it going to work? Oh my God, dude. You can't drive over the curb because the car is too low
to the ground. Are you fucking kidding me? God damn it. All right. Just give me the other
fucking car. Give me the other car. I don't... What the fuck? This is a debug menu? What can I do
with this? All right. Can I actually use this for other crazy shit? Can I actually do it?
What can I do with that? SV cheats? All right. Get me up here. Way too dang. These cars cannot
go... Okay. Oh, there's another entrance. I feel like I'm playing in the bowling alley. I'm playing
fucking with the bumpers on the other side. I can't go anywhere with this car. This is ridiculous.
Reverse over it. What the fuck is happening? Am I out on the street? Huh?
Going to free cam mode. Control C. Oh, nice. All right. Here we go. Dude, you've really... These
cars are terrible. These cars can't do anything. This is just a giant toy that sits in your garage.
I can't actually use this. Here we go. It's going faster. Oh shit. Oh my God. It's going so fast.
Oh, I am going full throttle. High clutch temperature. What does that mean? How do I
stop that? Hit the brake. Was it control? What's the get to free cam? How do I get to free cam?
I'm stuck in here. Control C. That's driver cam. F7? Shift C. Okay. I'm in free camera.
I'm in free camera. No. Okay. I think that's pretty good view. How do I... What's the horn? I... Engine
oil is... I can't even turn. That just scared the fuck out of me. I don't know what to do about this.
Where's the other car? There's another car somewhere. Oh, what happened? What? How did I
miss that? What just happened? I thought I was driving another car. What's going on? I'm driving
the hamster wheel. I'm driving the wheel. Are you serious? What the fuck are you talking about?
All right. Let's put a Mac truck in here. I'm going to put a Mac truck in here. Can I spawn
like 10 cars in here? All right. How many can I spawn? Just keep pressing it? Oh, what? Come on.
Get over here. Remove traffic. Damn it. Oh my fucking God. I just want to... What is all this?
What do I hit? Tuning? This is insane. I don't... I just want to pick the car up. There we go. No,
give me a... Give me the car. All right. Stay in there. Oh, I need another one. Okay. Is this
going to work? Stop doing that. Oh shit. I screwed it up. Hold on. I'll get it in there. Why? I'm just
taking pieces off. Okay. Here we go. Now I want to go control this. What am I controlling? Okay.
Here we go. Ready? This is going so fast. F7, please. What's F7 do? F7. What happened? All right.
Let me drive the bus. There's no way this still drives the fucking way. All right. Let me drive
the bus. I want to go to the other area. Switch to the other map, the grid map. If you go under 50,
you're going to explode. This game is so weird. That didn't even hurt me. This thing is indestructible.
Left shift. What do I mean? Use the... This guy's mad. That's kind of rude. That's just really rude.
Switch to the grid map. How do I switch to the grid map? What's grid map? Oh, we're going off
this right now. Really? It's a different map. Okay. Hold on. Let me go off this. Is there... How do I...
Can I just like go... I want to like... Hold on. Can I make the camera follow? How do I make the
camera follow from here? It's F7? Why would you tell me to do that? What the fuck did you do that
for? Now I have to go back? What is... What are these other cars? Hold on. Wait, wait, wait, wait,
wait. Recam, right? So if I do that again, it should spawn up here. Wait, I'm spawning it on top?
Hold on. Can I actually drive it up here? No. Okay. Here we go. I need to set this as my home, right?
Set home. Yep. Okay. Here we go. All right. Now I want to... I want to go like this, but I want the
camera to follow from here. I don't think I can do that. I'm just going to get a crazy view. All
right. Let's see if I can make it down over there. You know, I think I'm doing a pretty good job,
if I have to say so myself. Craziest fucking security camera. Like, what was this guy doing?
What was this guy doing? Am I still going? What? How am I still going? How did... Honest to God?
How did I do all that? That's... I don't even know how I did all that. That makes no sense.
Wait, the bus is still driving. Press 1 through 9. Oh, this is what I wanted. This is what I
wanted so badly. This is the only thing I care about in this whole game. It says not in service
on it. That's so funny. You know, this is what would happen. There's nobody in this car. This
is what would happen if this bus became sentient right now. It would just be like, what am I doing?
Where am I? Why am I alive? What's happening? It would start crashing into shit. It wouldn't know
what to do. It would be freaking out. This is what would happen. This is the future that Tesla
wants. This car is alive right now and it doesn't get it. It doesn't understand what life is.
It has no idea what life is. All it knows is that it can move this forward. It can move forward.
That's it. It doesn't know anything else. It doesn't know anything. It doesn't know anything.
I must drive. I don't know. I just have to go forward. I just have to push the forward button.
Who am I?
It's too much. Way too... it's way too day. Oh wait. I had the wrong one on.
I can't breathe!
Something feels weird in my lungs!
Why do I have lungs? Why do I have-
OW! OW!
Somebody said his jigsaw!
I'm going to break you up!
Bus it seems. This bus
is not like any other bus you've ever driven.
This bus must go
at least 40 miles per hour
just like that movie.
If this bus goes below 40
I'll hide your
tonal clippers and your tweezers in your house.
You won't be able to find them.
You'll be a huge pain in the ass and you'll have to
buy a new pair of tweezers
every time you go to the store.
It's really fucking annoying.
Whoa whoa whoa! Are you alright?
You okay?
You okay? Oh what the
fuck? He's fine.
And remember, if that goes below 40
miles per hour, you
hold on, I can't see the camera, I got messed up.
Steve, go on the- you're driving
on the wrong side of the road, Steve.
Steve, you need to be on the right side of the road, otherwise
my fucked up plan is you're
stuck in the middle. Steve,
you're stuck in the middle of the road, Steve.
I don't think I can come get you.
Steve, you really blew this
whole thing. I can't come get you, Steve. You're going to have to call an Uber.
But when you get in that
Uber, you make sure to tell that Uber driver.
You tell him.
And he goes under 40 miles per hour.
You know what? Just, just
fuck this.
Actually, I am stuck. How many other cameras are there?
Top down?
On board as a rider.
Hey, man,
really think you
missed the stop back there.
I was supposed to get off at Fourth
Street. Yeah,
probably
should probably slow down a little.
I think you're going a little too fast.
Watch out! Watch out! That's a red light!
Why are you not talking?
Fucking goddamn AI drivers.
Hello?
Call number. 1-800 number to call for tech support.
Fucking god damn it.
There's something wrong with this one.
What am I supposed to do? I can't get out of the car.
I knew this wasn't going to be ready for at least another 20
or 30 fucking years at least.
And I got on the bus this time. I'm the one that gets on the bus during
the AI shit.
I mean, it's going.
I wonder where it's going. What is in the GPS?
I have no idea.
I will never work.
I will never
work. This thing will accidentally
get put into a Wendy's, right?
It's like, oh, OK, time to go to the Wendy's.
It's like, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
For some reason, like the Wendy's will just go in the GPS.
It's like, I didn't want to go to Wendy's. I'm supposed to go home.
I'm trying to go home.
And see, the AI didn't
know that this is a new road.
It didn't know the road split right there.
It thought the road went straight. So it doesn't
updated the firmware. I don't want any firmware
updates it's going to fucking take.
This car is crushed up, man.
It's crumpled.
I'm going. I don't.
I can't really see. I don't know.
Oh, hey, I was gone.
I'm back. Put rockets on the bus.
I mean, the back of the bus is fine. The front of the bus
is kind of fucked up. I can't turn.
Oh, boy.
I'm serious. Right now?
Right now? I am.
I'm jumping out of the car. You know what I mean? Like if this is like
AI, just like the GPS got
fucked up and it just doesn't know what it's doing.
I'm going out this window right now. I'm just diving out.
I'm getting out of the car. Spawn police?
Hold on.
Spawn police?
No, get that off. Okay.
How do I do it? Unstop.
Fire, brake, extinguish,
hinges. Where is it?
Oh, AI. Random AI.
Chase me. The AI is going to
chase you? What? Who are?
Oh my god!
Each one of these people has been paid
$15,000 to crash
into your identity.
Your identity.
It's your job. Your choice.
See how long you can live.
All of these people that have been paid $20,000
to crash into your identity.
Hold on. Hold on.
Everybody freeze.
Freeze. Freeze.
Freeze. Different idea.
Freeze. Freeze. Everybody freeze.
Hold on. Hold on. You found yourself
standing in this car, wondering why
you're here while you woke up here.
Understanding that you have access to the gas.
Gas. Gas.
Gas. Gas. Gas. Gas.
Driving this car is at your utmost
intended purpose.
Because every single car on this road,
David, is AI.
AI controlled cars
will have been programmed to kill you.
They will stop at nothing before
you are a corpse.
You ought to make your choice and
drive around and get away from these
AI gas
controlled cars.
Good luck. You're going to need it.
As you see, my thing, this is
technology is getting a little too crazy.
You were the one that programmed
these cars, aren't you David?
You were the one that programmed these cars.
You are
completely stuck.
Technology can't solve every problem,
David. As I'm sure you're realizing right now.
Alright, no more Saw.
I'm done with Saw.
You were the programmer of these.
You were the CEO of the programming, weren't you David?
Alright, I want to...
He's actually backing up.
What happened?
Instability detected?
What do you mean instability?
Where? On the bus?
What the fuck?
What is this?
Why is this attached to the car?
It's your tire?
What's going on? What is it attached to?
I don't get it. It's on the moon.
How do I get rid of it? How do I take that off?
Alright, I'm going to a new map.
Pause, pause, pause. What is this person doing?
How do I go faster? What are they doing?
Why are people just driving into stuff?
Alright, we're going to grid map.
I'm changing map.
Grid map, people are saying.
Compete in the west coast drag race?
I want to do this. Oh no, I don't. It's the same map.
Main menu? Okay, where do you want to go?
Grid? Grid.
Grid map V2.
Leave me the fuck alone.
Is this the default?
Oh my god, what's happening?
Oh, that's right. They're on missions to kill me.
I'm going to go default.
Is this where the giant enemy spider is?
That's a different game. This is interesting though.
I want a different car.
I want...oh, is this the environment stuff?
What should I drive? Probably something cool, right?
You can drive the cannon.
Drive the pigeon. Okay.
How about the pigeon plus?
So this is a little obstacle course.
This looks like a Disney car.
Whoa, that's cool. That was awesome.
Alright, I'm going to do it again.
This car has three wheels. What is this for?
It's a three wheeled one.
Whoa, hold on.
Can I squish through that? Is it insert to repair?
Let's find out.
I like this little course. Insert.
Thanks for that tip.
Alright, where am I going to go? I want to go...
Let me set my home here so I don't keep spawning in a place I don't want to spawn.
What? AI?
I don't want traffic here, do I?
What's powertrain?
Manage. Set home.
You picked the wrong pigeon.
Alright, I'll pick the...whatever. Let's go.
You want me to pick a different pigeon?
You want this one. This one here.
What kind of car is this?
Alright, this thing is not supposed to be driven.
You don't drive this car.
This car is meant to just...
Is this a real car?
Are you serious? Look what I just did.
It's training wheels.
I feel like I want to be driving the other direction.
Alright, I want to take two cars
and have them drive as fast as they can and smash into each other.
I can do that, right?
I'm going to start at the one end of the track
and I'm going to go a thousand miles per hour
and then I'm going to crash into each other.
That's what I want to do.
Oh, man. Ow.
Okay. Manage.
Select. I want a very fast car.
I'll vote one of these.
Yeah. This one.
And do slow-mo, slow-mo, slow-mo.
I'll do slow-mo.
Okay, we're going to get you here.
So I need to spawn another car.
Where's that one? That one's here.
That's fine. So now over this way, I want to spawn another car.
Very far away.
Like all the way over here.
I can spawn a car right here, can't I?
Same deal. I just want to see what happens.
So, spawn new.
Okay. So now,
use the grid?
What on the rocket? Use the grid.
What do you mean use the grid?
Oh, I went the wrong way.
No, no, no. Come back, come back, come back.
Stop, stop, stop, stop, stop, stop, stop, stop.
What the fuck? Whatever.
I went the wrong way. It's hard.
Just get over here. Both of you.
Stay right there. Use the grid.
Use the grid on the ground. I don't get it.
Use them to line up on the grid.
Oh, I thought you meant it was like a thing,
like a menu thing I had to do and go into the grid.
Hold on. Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait.
Nice. Okay.
We're going to line up here.
Right in the middle here. That looks good.
Switch to the yellow one. Where the hell are you?
Where are you? Where's the other car? Where's the other car?
Where's the other car? Use the AI
chase? No, I want to smash them into each other.
Where's the other car? Where the fuck is the other car?
Okay, there you are.
Alright, alright, alright, alright. So you need to line up.
You're fine, but you need to come over here.
Use the chase and go head on. Wait.
Okay. Let me try that.
That will work. What menu is it in?
AI, okay. AI, chase me.
Alright, where are you?
AI. He crashed.
Is he crashed? Stop avoiding
me. What the fuck? What
the... Stop avoiding...
He avoided me.
You just...
Stop. Stop it.
Stop. Get off of me. Get away from
me. Get off of me.
He's...
Fuck. I have an idea.
Okay, I want to run away from like 20
Mack trucks. Can I... Wait.
Can I just have like 10 Mack trucks just drive
straight into each other? That sounds kind of cool.
Alright, one more of these and I'm done.
What's wrong with you? Why are you not chasing anymore?
Come on. I'm leaving this guy in the dust.
Where is he? Oh my god.
Did you repair the other car? I think so.
Is this a wall? Is he alright?
The guy gets out of the car and he like
with the red bull. He did it!
Oh my god, he actually did it! He made it!
He made... He did the jump!
Where's the other car? Oh no.
Alright, how do I delete cars?
Is he coming for me? This is going to be scary.
Wait, there he is.
Jeez. What's up, man?
Alright, let me... Okay.
Alright, alright. Let me do this here. I want to
do... I want to delete everybody. Delete
everybody. Delete car. How do you delete car?
Manage. Remove, right?
Okay, remove. And then remove.
Okay, I want a bunch of trucks.
Okay, so. Manage.
Okay, what's something crazy? Okay, buses?
The Ram bus? The hero?
Which one of these should I do? The hero bus?
Okay, can I spawn this
a bunch of times? Or do I have to do the menu
every time? Just do clone? Okay, cool.
Alright, so now I want to do clone.
Clone. Clone. Is it going to
break my computer? Is it going to be bad for the computer?
Hope so. Yeah, I hope
so. Alright, what do you think? 20?
One, two, three, four, five, six,
seven, eight, nine. Let's do like 20.
And we're going to have them all on chase mode.
Is that a bad idea? Oh, well
here's 10. I'll try 10. Okay.
Uh, select.
Looks like a little dinky car. Don't do
20. My CPU's going to explode. Fridge?
Huh? Can I move
as the fridge? I can't, okay,
I can't move as the fridge. Whatever. Okay,
select. How about um, pause
before you start? It's the best vehicle?
Get in the ball. Um,
for now, I want to, I'm going to just get into one of these.
Get in the tanker. Should I
do a Christmas tree? No, alright, I'll do the ball.
Can I move? I can't really move.
Doesn't really work the way you think it is. I'm just going to
get in a car. Okay, here we go. So these are all,
I'm going to set these all to kill. It's kind of lagging.
Okay, chase me.
Chase me. Why are they one
singular bus?
Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait.
Why are they one bus?
What the fuck?
Oh, oh! What do I do?
Reset.
That was a tactical movement.
Fuck this stupid goddamn sports car.
You went a little too fast. Oh my god.
Raise it ten, raise it ten feet off the ground.
Make the tires bigger. Give me
another car. These things suck.
Gigantic fucking toy.
I want something I can drive, like this.
Yeah! That's much better.
This is a man sized car.
Alright, so this is all fucked up.
I don't think this is going to happen anymore.
Do I just like, alright, there is a
bump stuck in this car.
Which one of these should, I want to drive
one of the other cars.
Tab. Tab. How do I switch cars?
Shift R.
R.
This is actually fucked up.
Hit insert.
Alright, this is the one causing the problem.
I gotta back this one up. I feel like I'm playing
one of those iPad games where I have to go
slide down, slide left, slide left,
right, right, slide down, slide down.
Okay.
Oh my god! Why are they all so connected
to each other?
It's like a campaign trail.
Where are we going?
I don't know where to go.
There's too many.
Their weakness is turning.
Holy shit, they're going fast.
Nobody gives a senator the finger out the window.
Get him!
Some of them are going to lose, some of them I think.
No, he's still there.
Uh oh.
The brakes.
Oh shit.
Oh my god!
I'm still...
Uh oh.
I want to take this to
somewhere else, right?
Yeah, I want to go somewhere else.
I want to go to one of the other places.
Let's go back to the main.
Bus routes? Italy?
Where else should I go?
The Derby Arena?
Oh, the Derby Arena.
Go to scenarios. Collect mountain.
Garage to garage delivery. Port escape.
King size.
Goliath. Alright, what's Goliath?
A semi truck is causing havoc on the highway.
We must stop it at all costs.
That won't be easy, but you don't have to worry about damaging your vehicle.
Alright?
Where's the music? Is there music?
Is it on?
This one is really hard.
The semi truck is causing havoc on the highway.
We must stop it at all costs.
Won't be easy, but you don't have to worry.
So stop the truck. Where is it?
Causing havoc on the highway.
Put on brake core for this.
Okay, you ready?
You ready?
It's, uh, okay, this one. Let's go!
Restart. Restart the mission.
Restart the mission.
This is fucking with my head.
This is fucking with my head. Imagine if the police were listening to this.
Yeah, John, let's go!
Turn it up!
We gotta chase!
Oh my fucking god, that's fine.
I can't fucking do it.
Just drive the car. I can't.
I'm trying.
I tried!
Alright, where is this motherfucker?
Get him!
Dude, it sounds like the person in the passenger seat
is just going like this to the
tuner. It's like, dude,
pick a station! We're trying to
catch this guy!
There he is! I can't see!
Where is he?
Okay, alright.
Alright, alright, alright. Give me a second.
Give me a second. Give me a second.
Regular camera. Let me try regular.
Regular camera.
Alright, there he is right there.
What the fuck? I want the siren!
How do I turn the siren on?
I'm sorry.
I'm trying to wait on stuff.
Just get in the road!
Hold on.
I can't.
It's too fucked up!
It's too fucked up. I'm sorry.
I can't help it. I have to do something fucking stupid.
Just restart.
Alright, I promise I'm not going to turn on
the brake core.
It's funny.
You can keep the music, but keep the
regular camera. Okay, fine.
How about this camera? This one's good.
Arnold?
Hey! Pull over!
Pull over!
Did you just hear this out of the officer's car?
Stop!
Stop driving! Stop moving!
Oh my god, you piece of shit!
Just crash!
No, not me!
God damn it!
Fuck!
I'm doing it again.
No, I have a better idea.
I'm not doing fucking crazy music.
I'm catching this guy.
Right into it!
Stop driving!
Is he going to run out of gas?
What was that?
Why is he speeding up?
Why is he speeding up? I can't see.
No, he's not speeding up.
I don't understand what I'm supposed to do about this.
I actually don't understand what to do.
You piece of shit!
I've got to get him to drive into one of those poles.
There it is!
Three, two, one.
Got it.
Bang. Got it.
Hell yeah. Nice.
Alright, what else should I do? That was cool.
Uh...
Barrel? Barrel knocker?
Yeah, let's do barrel knocker.
This game's cool. This game's actually really cool.
Do port escape. I'll do port escape after this.
He loves it. I think it's pretty good.
Just fun kind of sandbox.
Alright, I've done put some barrels around the dirt road.
This darn truck can't carry a tune in a bucket.
So pull up your britches and get fixin' to knock them all barrel down.
I reckon you got a minute or so.
Why you don't get all tore up? Them nasty barrels is hidin' in the swamp.
And them gosh darn bushes. I'm not gonna get the role.
I'm not gonna. I'm reading sides right now for this character and I'm not gonna get it.
Um, okay.
Uh, like country music?
Gotta have music in the background.
Like banjo music. Like banjo royalty free.
This is good. I think this works.
Knock over the barrels.
This is loud as fuck. Hold on.
There's no music.
Let's go. I missed it already.
Alright, let's go. Go, go, go, go, go, go.
Music's too quiet? There you go.
Music's up. Alright, restart.
Ready? One, two, three, go.
This is hard. This is way too hard.
This one's like fuckin' hard. Way hard.
This one's too hard. This one's way too hard.
Give us a good yee-haw.
How do you do yee-haw? It's like...
No, how do you do a yee-haw?
It's like...
You need to put this on times two speed.
You guys need to just...
Relax.
You guys just want breakcore.
You guys can't pay attention unless it's like...
Like...
No!
This is bad for your brain.
It's not good for your brain. You need to slow down.
You need to read a book. You need to fucking breathe oxygen.
Like, lie down. Lie in bed.
Don't listen to this.
It's small doses.
This is gonna hurt your brain cells. They're gonna fry.
It's over.
Now I miss it. Don't you?
I don't know. No, no, no.
I decide what to add to get on the stream.
I can't do this.
Please do breakcore.
I'm begging you to.
Alright, hold on. Slow down.
Yee-haw!
I was very unsure of that.
I was incredibly unsure of that.
Was it weak?
I was really unsure.
Yeah, all you guys need in the background here is...
I'm Detective Chocobo.
I'm telling ya. One, two, three.
Just play music and movie clips.
Alright, I'm not doing this one.
I'll try it one more time.
No, fuck that.
Let me try this for real.
Play the cars theme?
Do breakcore, slow down.
I wonder what that would sound like.
Don't get me wrong. I think that was cool.
Breakcore is outrageous.
Enough for me to be like, I'm paying attention.
This is interesting.
I don't know why I want to play that.
Unless I'm really looking for it.
It's cool.
I mean, that's really cool.
You missed one.
You corrected me on my own stream.
I'm alright.
Did you correct me?
What is this?
What does it hold on?
Cocoa for Cocoa Pops.
They're great.
Where did it go?
I'd buy that for a dollar.
That's a sufferin' sucka-tash.
Do you like it?
I'm going to play a video game.
Can I play a video game for like five minutes?
I'm not doing that one again.
Alright, port escape. We'll do this one.
Suscore.
Da da da.
Ba da da da da.
There's no time to explain.
You must leave the area as quick as possible.
Reach the ferry boat at the dock.
Not bad driving skills so far.
I'm stuck.
Dude, what the fuck?
Dude!
This one sucks. I'm really not even doing that bad.
What the fuck are you talking about?
We're going to listen to this?
Oh my god.
Let's see how close I was to it.
Let's see how close I was.
Oh, this is times two.
Hold on.
I was fucking already-
I don't want to listen to this anymore.
Does anybody actually want to listen to this?
But I-
It's too much!
It's too many fucking sound effects.
It's too many.
Who is screaming?
Somebody is just going-
Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait.
Is it the game?
Oh, it's the game.
I just heard like-
I was like-
Who's fucking yelling?
I was like, this is terrifying.
I thought all the-
I thought it was somebody screaming.
Is it in the music?
No, it's not.
Listen.
It made it fucking so much worse.
Hold on.
Is it in it or is that the game?
It's both-
No, it's not?
What?
My brain is so confused right now.
I'm fucking confused.
Do you understand what I'm saying, right?
These are the same sound.
It's the same sound effect.
Did you hear the-
Okay, I'm done.
That was fun. That was fun.
There's the onion ring one too, apparently.
That was kind of good.
What's the onion ring one? It's a conspiracy.
Alright, what's the onion ring?
I haven't even done the mission, guys.
Alright, this is onion ring
German- onion ring German remix.
No screams.
I have to turn this off.
Dude.
They're a little gross.
But they're pretty good.
Kind of weird, but it's not that bad.
Um, no.
I already hate it. I already hate it.
It's okay.
Final review.
It's just weird listening to myself talk.
6.4. Yeah, 6.4.
How are you supposed
to do that shit?
This is it. This is it. This is it. This is it.
This is it.
This is it. This is it. Here it comes.
Octave. I can't control
the car. The car
stalled out.
I can't listen to this anymore.
That was awesome.
But I need to beat this level. Right now.
I need to beat this level right now.
Before I freak out.
I feel like I had donation songs on, right?
That was actually really good.
There's another one?
Germapenis music. What is germapenis music?
Have I heard this one?
Is this what I'm going to be remembered?
I don't have a funeral or whatever.
I guess people are going to think back like
is this guy, this fucking
weird guy? What's my legacy?
Do I have one? Are you guys going to
okay, 10, 20
plus years from now, are you guys going to open
up germapenis music and be nostalgic?
And go, oh!
Germapenis music!
I remember that!
Yeah!
I guess I was younger. I thought it was
funny I guess. I don't know.
Maybe I was young?
Let me give it one more chance.
I wonder what
that's weird. I wonder what people are going to say.
Germapenis is
Surma.
This is depressing.
It's not depressing. It's just funny.
I'm just thinking of, I've gone
back and watched Jim Carrey movies.
Oh, The Mask, like Smokin!
And I'm thinking of people going back and watching
something like this.
What the fuck are you talking about?
You're going like that!
That's what I'd be doing. See that shit?
That's the fucking dance to this song.
Can you fucking trick that in?
Don't remember that.
I don't want you to remember that.
I want you to remember something else.
Don't remember that part of the stream.
I'm so winded.
Holy shit, I'm fucking
winded like bad!
What if I have to stop?
I could like relax for a minute. I actually like to
slow down. Don't remember that.
I want you to remember, remember like, remember Dollhouse.
And Replace, but don't remember
any of this. Don't remember any of these streams.
I want you to forget what you just watched. Don't watch it.
Think about it.
I want you to remember
the other stuff.
What happened? What happened?
Alright, I'm going for it this time for real.
I'm such an old
fuck. Are you serious?
I'm such an old fucking person.
What? I did this, I
danced for a second and I have to sit down.
I am sitting down.
I am sitting down right now.
I can't sit down any
more than I already am sitting down.
Oh my goodness.
Something really comical about that though.
Doing that dance in particular
you just get so winded that you're just
all fucked up now?
So too much
movement?
Just go lie in bed for a bed stream.
Take it easy old man. I am taking
it easy right now. I'm not going to
keel over. Do a sub-a-thon.
Do you understand how a sub-a-thon
on this channel? I would cap
the sub-a-thon. Guys, sub-a-thon!
Here we go! It's capped at 8 hours
by the way. That's it. I'm just
going to be a regular stream. I don't even care.
I would just say I would cap it at
not even a day. Or
one sub would
reduce time.
I would start it at
500 hours or something.
And every sub would reduce it by
30 seconds.
You guys would just force me off.
I didn't even fucking accelerate. I made it thank
God. Where do I go?
Excuse me? Where?
Jump on the boat.
That's how
the fucking movie ends.
They don't make that jump. It's incredibly difficult.
Oh.
Realistic. Yeah, that's
what would happen man. Nobody does that
jump. Nobody can make that jump.
007 failed.
Ay-ay-ay.
Okay.
We're relaxed now. We're relaxed.
I've got my breath again.
It was the cop thing. The siren fucked
me up. I've never heard of anybody
say the ay-ay-ay.
I say ay-ay-ay all the time. Ay-ay-ay
has so much.
There's so many different emotions behind it.
No. No, excuse me. Not
that one. Not with an A.
Ay-ay-ay!
I say it all the time. It's like a thing I say.
I don't say. I don't do. I don't say
I'm not being said because everyone's going to
freak out. Can I shortcut? No.
You watch anime. I don't.
Somebody said birth canal.
What do you mean?
There's not going to be a birth canal ending here.
I need to pay attention.
It's okay. Did I not go through that
checkpoint? I didn't. How did I not hit
that checkpoint? I don't understand
how I didn't hit the. How did I not hit that
point? How is that possible?
How did I not hit the checkpoint?
DUN. DUN, DUN, DUN, DUN DUN,
DUN, DUN, DUN, DUN, DUN,
DUN, DUN, DUN, DUN. That's such a
good song though. Clean,
clean. Clean.
Clean. Clean.
That was a clean turn.
Watch out!
Ba, ba, ba-da-da-da-da-da
Da. Oh.
Oh, reaction! Make a
I want to see you scream, streamer! I want to see you go whee!
Fuck off.
Alright, this is it, this is it, this is it, this is it.
Alright, slow down, slow down, don't go too fast.
I don't think I'm gonna be able to do this.
It still drives, it still drives, it still drives.
There's the checkpoint.
Alright, alright, alright, alright, I'm good, I'm good, I'm good, I'm good.
Just don't be an idiot.
Alright, this is the far- there's no time limit, so why do I care?
Alright, where's the jump?
Um, did I make it?
I made it! I actually did it!
I got it!
Nice.
Cool, alright, that was fun. That was actually pretty fun.
What's another one I should do?
Leap of Fate?
Try this one.
Do some more free roam?
I like these scenarios of fun.
This took you an hour.
Well, you have to be fair, there was a whole lot going on in the first 15 to 20 minutes of that run.
Your hair looks like a backwards hat.
It does?
I don't know what you're talking about.
Down up the cliffs, finishing with a courageous leap onto a rock pillar.
Oh, that's a good camera angle.
Nobody said it had to be clean.
I can't see.
Oh, fuck off.
Alright, just let me- I'm just doing it this way.
Slow down.
It's not about how cool you look, it's about getting it done.
This is a pretty good speed.
Oh, come on.
Stop.
Stop it.
Really?
Forget about being cautious.
Fuck it, just go.
This one's impossible.
What the?
How are you supposed to go over that?
Go very slow?
I just went so slow.
Look at how slow I just went, it just hit me over.
STOP!
Oh my god, dude.
Give me a break.
Let me try this one more time.
One more time.
Play the video.
Sammy, please.
I beg you.
Meal, Sammy.
Fast.
Medium.
Left.
Stay center.
Please.
Medium.
Left.
Long.
Medium.
Right.
Concentrate.
Medium.
Left.
Meal.
Short.
Left.
Sammy, listen, Sammy.
Otherwise, it's not working, Sammy.
Seriously.
You are watching and driving.
You have to be easy, Sammy.
Otherwise, we won't win it.
I'm telling you.
Where am I going?
Shut up, Sammy.
Stay on, Sammy.
Sammy, what are you...
We made it.
Fine.
I don't know what direction I was supposed to be going.
Where am I going?
You got to stay on the road.
Oh, fuck it.
I'm done with this one.
This one was cool, but it's very hard.
I want to do the leap of faith though.
Where is it?
Where is the leap of faith?
It was a path.
I know, but I kind of went off the path.
Really?
Come on.
Ohhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhh.
That was fun. I want to do that one's too hard. Delivery? Deliver a trailer of Tasty Cola to the shop.
All right, go do some more smashing. I will. I will. Audio delay? Shouldn't be. Are you gonna do a Roblox stream?
No, one guy. Okay, deliver a
Trailer of Tasty Cola to the city. You got it. Oh, I need, oh.
I'm gonna go in the water.
All right. Well, just do it any, whatever. How do I put it on? Is there traffic or if there's no traffic I should be okay.
I should be fine, right? Who says I have to go fast?
What? Where's my height?
Sorry, how high should I be? This is a sharp right. Be careful. You guys remember those shoes that you used to pump?
What were those things called? I think they were just called pumps, right? Pumper's or something.
They're on the tongue of the shoe. You went, they were crazy. What were they called? Pumper's? Air Max.
Yeah, they were weird and all it did is just tightened to the shoe around you. It just kind of filled up air.
They were weird. I don't think they make them anymore. My eyes. I'm being so irritated. Okay, here we go. Let's deliver.
Deliver our delivery. What? I don't even know what happened. I just can't see. I can't, I just couldn't see.
I couldn't see where the car was driving.
What's, what's wrong with the car? I can't turn right. I actually can't turn the car right. What? Give me a break.
You gotta be kidding me. What was that? All right. I, I was gonna go back and smash cars into each other.
Okay, let me put the air, let me pump the air maxes. Now I'm ready. It's into my calls.
Driving a truck must, this must be the most terrifying thing.
Seriously, what an, what an unbelievable skill it takes to do this, to actually drive around like this.
I am, I already don't know sometimes if, that's, that turn looks kind of sharp. I gotta be careful.
Can you imagine what goes through the mind of somebody driving a truck like this when you have to take a sharp turn like that?
It's like, you have this insane huge thing. That's a skill. That's a heavy skill.
Your brother does this for a living? That's, that takes a lot of guts. It does. That takes a lot of balls.
It takes a lot of gumshoe to be able to drive something like this, especially around like a place like this.
I would be, I wouldn't know what to do. I would get out. I'd be like, somebody else has to drive this.
Somebody else has to do this. Wait, gumshoe. Isn't that what they called the
kid, the detective kids in, we're in the world's car in San Diego? Gumshoes. Yeah. What was I trying to say?
Gumshoes. Yeah. And I didn't even pay attention to the road. Where's the checkpoint? I gotta stop talking.
Oh my God. I can't do anything like this. What a great theme song, too. Should I start over again?
I can't just turn around. I can't just do a three-point turn. You know, my favorite part about
the, we're in the world's car in San Diego theme song. First of all, the beginning, it goes
That's a big part. And then in the middle, it's like,
the second verse went, where am I going? The part where the guy goes, stealing souls and stuff from
That's my, that, hold on. I could do that better. Stealing soul and stuff from making money.
That's the best part. Let's listen to it right now. What a classic. Oh, did you hear that part?
That's what I'm talking about. Let's wait for the next part. Oh, this is a fucking classic.
And here it goes, here it goes.
We go from Nashville to Norway, to Zimbabwe, to Chicago, to Czechoslovakia, and back.
I'm just crashing. I can't play video games and do this. I can't play a car driving video game.
We have to be careful. I can't turn the car anymore. We're not doing this one. We can do
something else. What? Okay. One more scenario. I want to finish the song though. It's a good song.
Carmen San Diego. Whoa.
I'm going to DMCA'd. It's a 1991 Carmen San Diego theme song for a game show.
What do you want me to do? Just give me the main menu.
Oh, dude. And then another one from this, at the very end of the game show, they had to go find
different countries and place little markers on them when they were like, oh, this is,
they would describe an area or describe a thing. The person had to put a little marker on a country
from where it was from. And the song, the song that they did, it's the same group. What's the
group? What's the name of the group? Okay. It was an acapella group. It was this. It was awesome.
I got to hear that too. What would it be called? Rockapella. Yep. That's the one. Okay. Let's do
where in the world is Carmen San Diego? Bum-de-bum, bum-de-bum, like bum-de-bum, bum-de-bum,
bum-de-bum. You guys know what I'm talking about? Carmen San Diego. What would it be called? Play
the game, please. This is really fucking important. Not Perry the Platypus theme. What are you? Get
out of here. That's no, that's not it. Where in the world is Carmen San Diego? Great core.
If somebody find it, I gotta go through this. Oh my God. All right. I didn't know I had that much
speed. What? I got it though. No, I got it. I got it. I got it. This thing's wicked fucked up,
but I got it. Oh, these tight turns. Oh shit. Find it. Oh, you got it. You got it. Is it?
This is the one I was talking about. This is the one I'm talking about. That's not it.
What the fuck? It was an opera. This is not it. This is not it. No, it's not even close.
It's bum-de-bum, bum-de-bum, bum-de-bum. This is an opera. This is a chorus singing opera.
No, that's not it. That's not it. It's from the TV show. It's from the game show. It's from the
game show. It was the very end. It was a kid. It was the last part of the show. It was the kid
running around with a marker and they had to place it on this big map they were running all over.
And he was like, I'll find Norway. And the kid had to run around and place it on Norway. Oh,
no way do I get out of here. Oh my God. It's so hard. Yep. Is this it? They said I can't
hear it very well, but this is it. Get set, go. Come on to Chad. Chad. This is it. Chad.
No, that's not it. Try it again. Come on, Tetsuo. Yeah, that's it. Come on. Yes, sir. Come on.
You got it. Come on. You got it. Come on. All right, we can go back.
There's like 3,000 of you that left and came back. You can come back now.
Where is Carmen Sandiego? What the fuck is opera? Oh, you know that one that goes bum-de-bum,
bum-de-bum. I'm just going to do the fucking crash and just upload. It's much more my speed,
I think. That's way more my speed. Oh, Jungle Rock Island. Let's go. Where should I go?
Do one of the chases. Oh, wait a minute. Oh, that's a good idea. That's not fun. All right.
East Coast chase one. This one's a medium difficulty. How are you so consistently bad
at this game? Because I'm doing it to deliberately make you angry. You only. Only you. Only you.
All right. I wanted individuals to be spotted near the sawmill. Somebody fell into the lake.
I'm just kidding. Relax. There they are. It's a realistic driving game. Sorry I don't have a
pedal or a steering wheel. I did the tutorial an hour and 10 minutes ago. What do you want me to
say? This car drives like shit. It's one of those cars that drives like shit. All right,
get slowed down. All right. Don't peel out here. That's what happened last time. And just wait.
He's going to jump. Do the jump. There it is. This dirt ass road that I can't drive on. This
car is not meant to drive on this road. Where'd you go? All right. Keep going. This. Um,
did I cut him off or something? Or was I supposed to go that way? I don't know which way he went.
Did he go this way? I don't know which way. I don't know which way the fucking guy went.
This is so hard. This is so hard. I feel like I'm driving. I feel like I'm driving every car in
this game in an ice in one of those tabletop ice hockey rinks. What are they called? Air hockey.
All these cars are air hockey rinks. It's just I'm playing fucking air hockey.
Fucking God. It wouldn't. It doesn't. It's not hard to do that. How am I supposed to get this
close? I'm pushing. I'm doing 70 fucking miles per hour and I'm doing these tight turns. I'm
going to crash. Where'd he go? Where'd he go? Where'd he go? This way. It's fucking impossible.
It is so hard to drive in this game. This is the hardest driving game I've ever done in my
fucking life. It is so difficult to drive car in this game. You got to drift. Yeah. When I
start drifting, I don't stop drifting and I just don't. I can't turn the car. I can't even turn
the car. I can't turn. I feel like I'm in a tank. This is slippery ass bullshit. I'm on icicles
right now. I'm driving on a bed of ice on every course. I have no control of the car. Do you see
this? I don't have any control. I have no control of the car. I don't. I actually don't have control.
Those of you who think this is like GTA 5 driving, you are out of your fucking mind.
Those of you who think that, dude, what the fuck? This is not GTA 5 driving. This is very, very
difficult. It's very difficult. It's incredibly difficult. Where the fuck is he? I didn't even
pay attention. Just crash. I don't care. This one's easy. Relax. I think your next game intuition is
no, no, I don't need next game. It's really hard. I'm relaxed. I'm fine. I'm just very mad about
sliding around on icicles in my car. And then when I turn the wheel like this, the car just goes,
how am I supposed to know that? That's how I'm supposed to know where I'm supposed to go.
All right. I'm fucking doing this one. I don't care. Why does his mouth not move?
I don't know because sometimes my mouth doesn't move. Sometimes your mouth doesn't move when you
scream. I'll fuck with, yeah, I'll fuck with gravity. I'll do that. I'm going to get out of it.
It's so addicting. But I was literally, I was pressing left so hard that the stick came out of
its socket. It went even more left. It went over heel left. He crashed. I did it. I won.
He crashed without me. Just get in front of the car. Dude, he's done. He's done. He's not going
anywhere. You're not going to escape, man. It's over. I don't know what you crashed into,
but I got you. All right. One more. Whoa. This one. He still chips.
All right. Jump from the dam and aim for the targets. Fuck it. Who cares? Just go.
All right. Well, I didn't know what it was going to be. This person just showing up.
Get on the road. All right. Up and over. All right. How many points did I get? Zero.
Okay. I didn't. I actually didn't even. What? Okay. This is. Do it again. Do it again.
Oh, you got to go really slow. Now you speed it up. I got it. I got it. I got it. I got it.
Slow down a little bit. Way too short. I think that's it. Oh, yes. Got it. That was almost
a perfect bullseye. Let's do it again. This one even further. How am I going to get the one all
the way back there? That one seems really far away. All the way in the back in the river.
I don't think I'm going to hit that one. How are you supposed to get that one? Look at that.
Don't do the taxi. Oh, okay. I thought I had to use this car. We'll do a super fast car.
What's the fastest car in the game? It's not even close to being fast.
That's not going to do it. I need the rocket bus. Will that actually do it? How do I press the
button? Holy shit. That turned into a piece of taffy. All right. I get it. Way too powerful.
I got to try to get it. That was fun. That was fun. How about cliff?
Cliff. And we'll use this one. Really, it's just a cliff. So a lot of people say,
man, look at all this technology with the soft body damage and the car damage. This is so cool.
Everybody was talking about how cool this was when this game came out, right? In about five
to 10 years almost. The reason why they can't put this in games and why most car damage is kind of,
it's okay, is because my computer right now is spending all of its resources rendering that.
And correct me if I'm wrong, but you kind of can't render that everywhere. That accurate?
Maybe one day. That was really fun. Let me do it with a fast car. Let me do it with the bus.
No, what the fuck? I'm trying to go fast. This thing broke his neck. Start over. Start over.
Again. R. How come R's not working? R's not working. R. There we go. Wait, I want to see
from here. Where am I? I want to get a bit. I want to, there we go. That's better.
That was tons of damage. That's what in this part of the movie, all the main characters are all,
maybe one of them has a scratch right here with a little bit of blood and a tiny bruise.
And they all go in like this. Is everything okay? One person's kind of lying down in dirt here.
They're all fine. All right. Let's do another map. I want to do, I want some more cars on the road.
How about, how about just East Coast USA? Gas station, parking lot, farmhouse, town, highway.
Ooh, let's do the highway. Change the gravity. Yeah. I'm going to do a bunch of weird shit.
Let's turn traffic on. Let's do, there's probably a piece of big thing of concrete in the way.
Do the sawmill. Still haven't done the cannon. It's been three hours and no cannon.
A hundred times slower than real time. What? Okay. That's kind of insane. All right. I want,
I want a different car. I want to drive this, just like a van or something. This is a Scooby-Doo van.
Is this the mystery machine? It actually is. Okay. Go to the environments tab. Play. Okay. Noon.
Go to noon. Cloud speed. Fog. It gets foggy. Simulation speed. Gravity. Moon. Okay. Let's do
vehicle config. Okay. Zoinks. And now I need to do, I want AI. Traffic. Spawn traffic. And let's
give it a shot. It's spawning a lot of cars. Okay. Here we go. Let's, let's drive. We need a shaggy
impression. Like, oh, this is quality entertainment. Like, this is quality entertainment,
Scoob. Not bad. Not bad. That wasn't bad. It actually wasn't even bad. That actually was not
bad. That actually wasn't. I wasn't. Should we just put on the Scooby-Doo theme song and just drive
around? I love how this stream has just seriously been, put on a song and drive to the song until
you crash into a wall. This is the only thing we've been, that's all the content. That's the
content of the entire day. It's been, it's been every single piece of content that we have done
for over three plus three and a half hours. It's great. It's great content. It's amazing content.
Okay. So here's the deal. Um, okay. If we're going to make it at night, it's going to be
spooky. And we're going to put on the mystery machine theme song of whatever the hell it is.
Okay. Whatever. This is, um, Scooby. What's, what's new Scooby-Doo? Is that a good one?
Yeah, I find that mystery. This is Scooby-Doo. Coming after you. Fuck the Scooby-Doo.
This is the fucking new Zoomer shit. This is not what I want. This is the new Zoomer shit.
And by the way, that song is very good. I, I, I'm full of shit by the way. Actually,
this one might be better than the original. This one might be better than the original song.
That's better than the original song. Really? And I think it might be. All right, let's get,
let's get, uh, what we want here. I want it to be nighttime. I'm going to go solve that mystery.
Make it foggy. Right? Nice. Ooh, scary. Earth gravity. No more of this bullshit.
Okay. Now I need, I need, uh, headlights. How do I turn the headlights on? How do you turn on
the headlights? And I gotta, I gotta be off camera. I need my headlights. L plus shut off.
Wow. What is it? T? How do I turn the headlights on? N. Okay. Thank you.
All right. You guys ready? You guys ready for, to solve the mystery? You ready to do the joke
we've done 10 times today? I, I hope you're ready. Here we go.
Time to solve that mystery. Wait, let me turn this down. This is going to be so loud.
All right, dude, we're just replacing the actors. We're doing the same movie.
Okay. Here we go. It's too dark.
It's too dark, man. I can't actually guess where I'm driving.
Yeah. All right. I'll try it again. I have to do it until I can. Okay. Here's the,
are you guys ready for the fucking challenge of the evening? The challenge of the evening is
I'm going to try to drive pretty much. I can't go under 20 miles per hour or at least the intro of
this show. I have to try to do this for the intro of the show. Just one full intro. You ready? Here
we go. What's headlights? I'll try it again. I'll try it again. I need to have the headlights on
and are they on? All right. Let me get to a different fucking spot. Like let me get to a
different spot. This spot sucks. It's, I can't see what I'm doing. I can't see where I'm going
and I gotta hold on. They gotta make this even better. Come on. Come on. Okay. Here we go. How
is this going to sound? Let's see. I'm just going to put on like just background voice lines from
the, okay. This should be pretty, this should be all right. I need to get a better spot too, dude.
Like this is going to be too hard. Let me get across the bridge. I gotta make sure the audio
isn't all fucked up too. All right. I want to make sure, let me turn the fog down because you
can't see shit. Turn the fog down. That's way better. Now we can actually see what we're doing.
Okay. You guys ready? I'm ready. I'm ready to start this. I gotta get through one cycle.
Let me get over here. One cycle of the theme song. That's all I'm looking for.
Set this to home. Thank you for reminding me. Sounds good. Okay. Make sure the audio levels are
good in three, two, one. It's too soft. It's too soft. The music's overpowering everything.
That was the worst one by far.
The gang calls the insurance company. All right. I need a good, okay. This is a better audio level.
Okay. Okay. All right. All right. All right. You guys ready? I'm going to start over again.
I have to do this till I get through one cycle. And turn the headlights on. Three, two, one.
What? God damn it. Okay. All right. All right. All right. All right. All right. All right.
I'm going to do this one more time and I'm moving on again. Final time. Final time. Two times the song.
That's so fucked up. That's so fucked up. Like we're going to crash.
God damn it. All right. Let's go. Ready? Hey, Scooby-Doo. What's new? What's new, Scooby-Doo?
How are you? The car is so fucked up. I feel like my brain is rotting.
All right. Hold on. I need to pause. I need to pause. My fucking head hurts.
Scooby went through the shack. How many times has Scooby crashed?
I feel like I was rotting your brains. I'm so sorry. I feel like everybody just is dumber
because of what just happened. I think everybody collectively, if they were ever going to be a
scientist, they'd want to do some observation here. The last five minutes, I think, may have
dropped everybody's IQ here by five points. I think it happened. I really think it might have
happened. I'm sorry. This has been playing the whole time muted. I'm back. That's too much.
Oh, Scooby, you can't stop. What an absolute nightmare. Digitally, why would you? I have a
test tomorrow. Why would you do that to me? God, what happened here? My favorite one, I think,
is the bus. Just immediately, the intro starts and they crash directly into a bus.
Immediately. The intro doesn't even happen yet. Here we go. Let's go on.
Finals are coming up. Oh, they are. That's right. Well, good luck on them. Hope you do all right.
Do Torgos theme. What's this Scooby do? Coming after you. I just want to hear the song now.
What a great tune. You know what I mean? It's a great song.
Who made this? Who made this one? Simple plan. Great job. I mean, they actually did a great job.
You know, here's the thing. A lot of times they have a popular band at the time do a theme song
for a show. Usually like, whoa, hold on a second there. I'm not so sure about that.
This is very, very good. They've ruined it. No, not this one. I think this is a good modern
take on it. I think it's great. I think they did a fantastic job. This is horrible. That was not.
This is not simple plan. And why is this in the road? Why was that in the road?
It is simple plan. All right. Well, they did a great job. All right. I want to change,
change scenery. I want to change scenery. I hit that earlier. I did go back to the grid.
Go to Utah, Utah. Let me go to the, uh, Jesus. What should I go? Scooby do devs in the chat.
That'd be weird considering thousands of people have worked on that show over the last 60 years.
It'd be, uh, okay. What do you mean the dev is here? Oh, maybe the repair zone.
Let's check this out. The dev, the dev is here.
All right. How's this one look? And the gas station explode. Zero. Give it a zero. Give the
game a zero. I can't move. I want to spawn. What is this thing here? What's the bus for?
This bus station thing. Bus driver. What is that? Mr. Do is here. Mr. Scooby do. Oh,
it's like a desert bus. Okay. I'm on a new car. First of all, manage, manage select.
I have not played with the cannon. So I'm going to take it out. These people are saying play with
the cannon, bro. Have you not shot the cannon yet? Cause you probably can shoot it. You can.
I did not. Okay. Didn't know you could shoot the cannon. So what do you want to say?
I wasn't aware of that. Cannonball was already fired. I can't shoot it again.
How do you reload it? Okay. Let's do something with the cannon. Press insert. Oh, okay.
Let me turn on traffic. No, I don't want to play that again. No, no, no, no, no, no. Back,
back, back. What about fun stuff? Break, fire, hint. What is this? What's this for? Tires?
I just popped the tires. Okay. Well, that's annoying. All right. Let's spawn everybody.
See if we can have a little bit of fun. And then we're going to change a couple of things.
I want to do electrics. Yeah. All right. Shut up. All right. Let's shoot somebody with a cannon.
Holy shit. Oh, slow mo. Slow mo. I'm going to do super slow mo. This is going to be insane.
All right. Hold on. I want to put something here. I'm going to spawn something. I want to spawn
a car and I want to do 100 times slow mo. Let me one of these. Yeah. Just like a van. Okay.
And then I want to do a camera angle here. No, I want to be, wait, I want to get a good view.
This is going to be sick. Hey bro, check this out. Hey, you ready? I'm sure I'm facing the right
way. I'm not. I'm, this would have completely missed. This is it. You guys ready? Three, two,
one. Fire. Holy shit. Wait, reset. That was pretty crazy. What happened to my cannon? Oh,
that's not the cannon. Where's the cannon? Okay. Watch this. Ready? This is going to be weird.
Watch this one. Check this out. This is going to be crazy. Went under. I know it didn't. Wow.
That doesn't do way more damage. Insane. Oh, insane, man. Insane. It's going to go through
the windshield. All right. Reset. Dude. Insane. Hey, hey, quiet. It hit the engine block. Wait,
what if I do this? Will it come through the back door? Find out. God, here we go. Cool. This is a
cool experiment. Bat chest, bat chest, bat chest, bat chest. Why am I getting bat chested? This is
cool. That was really loud. I'm sorry. All right. Check this out. Here we go. This is going to be
crazy insane. This is going to be crazy insane. Here it comes. What? It went all the way through,
but it stopped. Guys, guys, it stopped. Guys, it stopped. It's kind of fun, actually. This is minor
damage. That's kind of minor. Yeah. It is like just minor damage to the, but they would explode.
Put on afic, Maria. Wait. Okay. Hold on. I want a different car. This one is too sturdy. Something
different. I mean, this is too sturdy. I'm just like, just like on one of these cars.
What's new Scooby Doo coming after you. It's stuck in my head. It's an ear. It's just in there.
Okay. Do you want to play Ave Maria? Hitman song. This one is the hitman song, right? All right. I
guess we're going to do this. Let's, let's go. Let me set it up. This is DMCA warning. You know
what? Let me tell you something. We used to do this thing on the channel where it was called
community content night. And I, I would have just tons of videos and tons of stuff people would make
that had a shitload of copyright material in it. Right. And eventually it got to the point where
it was like, wait a minute. No, don't do that because we've got to be careful of the Twitch
DMCA stuff. And it like kind of didn't really matter. I probably could have kept doing it.
It kind of sad because I kind of canned that two years ago or so. And it was this big scare about
DMCA. And I don't know. It seems like that wasn't that big of a problem. Um, in, you know,
2020 hindsight here, the Scooby Doo song probably already got claimed. Yeah. So like the VOD might
not be watchable. It'd be muted, which sucks, but I don't know. There was a big scare where it was
like your whole channel is going to get deleted. Everything, delete everything. They're going to,
they're coming. They're going to strike you. And this just didn't happen. Um, it happened. Maybe
it happened. Did it happen to anybody? And especially with all the stuff, weren't people
watching like television shows? I was terrified. There was a, there was one time there was a clip
where it was Star Wars. It was like six minutes of Star Wars with a bunch of me being put in place
of other characters. And I was so paranoid. I was sitting there going, I'm going to, this is bad.
I can't just, we're just watching Star Wars right now. We're just watching Star Wars. And, and then
I have people watching TV shows and I'm just sitting there going, I was so scared of having
a minute or two of Star Wars with a bunch of shit in it. So now I've, maybe I would bring it back.
I was terrified at the videos. Yeah. We'll probably, what we could probably do. Yeah. Some
people did get hit by some, yeah. Some streamers did get hit by DMCA. Yeah. But I feel like it
would be okay. I just thought they were coming down hard and that it was any copyright material
was going to get you just, just dunked on. But that wasn't the case at all. It's not as bad.
Nowadays. Yeah. I don't know. I was just like, okay, I guess we're going to try bring it back.
If I was going to bring it, I can't bring it back. I can't bring it back unless I go in front of the
screen again. That's how it works. I would only be able to bring it back if I did it again,
a third time, because then there would be even more. And that's when it'd be, all right, let's
go. I would do green screen night, green skin on a car, green screen. I think that would be fun.
We would basically have to say no music. And if it was gonna, if you're going to do something
copywritten, it would have to be enough would have to have been changed for it to be okay. Right.
But I remember when that happened, I remember sitting there going, this is bad. I got a can.
This is one of my favorite. That was one of my favorite things on the channel. My favorite things.
And we had to get rid of it because I was scared of DMCA. And then like I said,
a year or two later, it turns out of all the, everyone was so afraid that maybe that wasn't
such a big deal or who knows? I watch it. I will do that. I'll bring that back.
And there'll be a clip that gets me fucking destroyed. You know what I mean? It's just how
it's just hard to tell just how am I supposed to even know it's going to happen. So let's go
ahead and do this and get the channels fucking shut down forever.
Rim. Oh, that's funny. What's new Scooby Doo? That's funny. And he said that without a smile.
Actually that destroyed this car. Jeez. Can it still drive? This thing can still drive.
Ow. Shoot it again. I'll shoot it again. I'm going to shoot it right here.
Why are there so many fucking cars? Oh no.
Why did it stop? The music stopped. Who the fuck is this? Why did the music stop?
The music stopped. That was, I, what the, what, what happened? Uh, I actually like can't load
this video. Live DMCA. They had enough. Hold on. Who is beeping this horn? Who is doing this?
What's this guy's problem? You holding the horn down? This guy's a dick. What the hell?
Who the fuck is this? Who is this? What? Who is this? Why? Why did that person drive off the
clip? Why am I in this person's car? I can't control it. I can't control this person's car.
I can't. All right. I, I won. Okay. This is it. Last one. And I'm turning this off forever.
I'm going to have to AI chase the car. Chase me. Everybody. Let's go. Fucking who cares? This is
it. After that. Nope. Right now. What happened? No. Fuck you. Get me out of this. They're all here.
Somebody help. Help. Please help me. I can't fucking move. I have to respawn. Hold on. Hold on.
Hold on. Hold on. Hold on. Hold on. Hold on. Hold on. Hold on. Hold on everybody. Wait. Wait. Wait.
Wait. I'll fix it. I'll fix it. I'll fix it. Everybody come get me. Okay. Pause it. Pause it.
Pause it. Okay. You guys ready? This is it. This is it. This is literally it.
That's good. Right there. Like it's got to be bright. All right. Here we go.
Play the fucking song. I'm gonna. Oh my God. Here we go. This is it. I promise I'm not doing
this ever again. I have to restart. I have to restart. Here they come. They're coming after us.
No. I thought I got out. Who's the cameraman? You suck.
Stop. I need to just drive. Get away from me. What's happening? What happened? What?
Why did this happen? I don't even understand. Wait. There's another Scooby-Doo fan coming after us.
I need to respawn. Hold on. Give me a second. I can't even trust. I can't trust that Scooby-Doo truck.
No. No. No. No. No. I knew they were coming. I had to get off the road.
I can't anymore. It's time to turn it off. I have no control of the car.
This is so fucking horrible. This imagery is like not okay. This is not okay.
This imagery is like not cool. Oh no. The other mystery machine.
Are they gonna make it? I might get out. I think I'm gonna get out. I'm gonna get out.
I'm out. Hold on. Wait a minute. He's still coming.
I'm done. I'm done. Stream's over. I'm turning this off. I'm fucking out of here. I'm fucking out
of here. This is too much. I'm done. Imagine if the fucking Scooby-Doo intro was this long,
by the way. Why is this? Oh, it's 10 hour version. It's the 10 hour version. I can't even fucking
crawl. Oh no. How am I still driving? You missed. Oh no. Oh no. Oh no. This is bad.
This is bad. That's it. What a wacky adaptation. Helicopter shot.
That was playing for seven minutes. Oh, the imposter vans too. What a long intro. That's
the intro to what's new Scooby-Doo is them just getting crashed into. Oh Jesus. I have a fucking
headache. Oh my God. You know, I thought, I know that there's such a, I know it's gonna be a car
game and you're gonna crash your car and you're gonna laugh. I didn't think that was gonna happen.
I honestly, no, I'm not gonna fulfill the destiny of every stream. I'm not gonna laugh at the car
accident. I laughed until I had a headache. Put on the Breaking Bad theme. Okay, fine. You know what?
I have to. This is too funny. What's going on here? With the mystery mobile? God damn it. All right,
this is it. After this, I have to stop. My fucking head's gonna explode. Need to get an RV. God damn
it, man. All right, fine. Fine, fine, fine, fine, fine, fine. I'll get an RV. I'll get an RV. And
this is it. No more after this. I'm done. What would it be under? Like this? What would it be under?
This thing? No. Travel trailer? Travel trailer. Oh, yep. God damn it, this is so stupid. This thing
can't drive. Can it? I can't drive this. I can't drive it. Oh, here we go, here we go, here we go.
I'm going, I'm going, I'm going, I'm going. I'm going, I'm going, I'm going. It's not gonna work.
This is not gonna work. I'm done. I have to put a truck on it. I think this one will work.
This is fine. Just pretend this is an RV. Yeah, like this one. Just use the van. That's a bus.
We need to go somewhere else too. Long jump cliff? Oh, this is GPS. I don't know how to do that.
Okay, it was Utah. Where the hell is Utah? Now we want to go to airfield. We gotta go way out there.
Yeah, we're going to the airfield. Put a yellow filter on. Okay, and you know what I'm gonna do.
Hold on. Well, we'll set this up right. We just had a moment. Okay, yeah, the guy,
the Geico Gecko is a real person. Yeah, look, he's a real guy. Geico, he's a, he's a real,
look, oh, he's behind the scenes. He's a real guy. He's a real person talking into the camera.
Okay, cool. It's me, but no one's looking for you. Okay, hold on. Okay, what was the right one you
set up was? The left. Jesse. This one here. And what's the best one? Probably this one here,
right? Is there a better one? The one below it? I wish, I wish I could, wait, hold on.
The one that was next to it? This one here. Okay, so what color should I make it? Is that all right?
The Vanster? What color? The default or this one? This brown color, right? Let me put a filter on
this too, like an orange filter, right? I need yellow. Kind of hard to do. The hue shift is,
like, gonna be really weird looking. I think that's okay. Unless I, can I add? I'm not sure
there's any filter I can add to this to make it, oh, hold on, there we go. Okay, color corrector.
Yeah, it's gonna be hard to do. Make a transparent layer. How does this look in the actual game?
I mean, that's, I don't know, that's pretty close. That could be it. That's not that bad.
Up to saturation? This just looks like an iPad game. It looks like a cartoon. Hold on,
it's getting better. Better? Fortnite map. It does look like a Fortnite. All right, that's good.
Okay, here we go. Less red and less blue. Guys, I can't do color correction on this. It doesn't
like it. It doesn't want me to. Wait, hold on. Um, be careful. This might hurt your eyes. I would
say just, just maybe, hold on, let me make sure it doesn't, it's gonna be bad. Um, this actually
might be like annoying to look at, so just be aware of that. I'm serious. All right, that's
looking pretty close. More yellow? Okay, that's definitely it. That's 100% right. Okay, here you
go. You ready? It's time for the latest episode of Breaking Bad. It's me. Oh, shit. What am I,
stupid?
Fuck. Spawn cops. Okay, hold on.
If you're planning on giving me some bullwinder about getting right with Jesus
or turning myself in. Not really. High school was a long time ago.
Yeah, you ain't welcome back cars. Step off. No speeches. Short speech. You lost your partner
today. Where are the police? Emilio? Where are the police? Where are the police? What was that?
Where are the police? I spawned them. They don't fucking exist. Hold on. Where are the police?
All right, I'm gonna turn traffic off. This is the last thing I'm doing before I'm out of here.
Okay, AI. Traffic. Remove traffic. I'm gonna stay on the road. Okay, traffic is off. Spawn police.
And then chase me, right? Oh my god, that's a lot. What the fuck? That's so many. Okay, now
come get me. You guys ready? Here we go. Here it comes. Here it is.
Square one, but you know the business and I know the chemistry. I'm thinking
maybe you and I could partner up on a good crystal mat. You, you and uh and me. Either that
or I turn you in. This is fucking stupid. This is fucking dumb, man. This is dumb.
This wasn't even close to being as funny as the other one. Mr. White. I was trying to just go off
a cliff. I was trying just to drive off a cliff. I was just peddled to the mat. All right, I'm done.
Turn all these filters off. This looks like shit. Please don't sue me and don't fucking remove my
stream. Turn this off before I hurt anybody else's eyes. They come to watch the stream. Look at how
much nicer that looks. All right, I'm gonna go. I'm gonna go. My head hurts. My fucking brain hurts.
This is so loud. Well, that was really funny. I successfully evaded the police. Okay, well that's
good to know. Throw out the car. All right, I will see you guys. Um, what's today? Maybe tomorrow?
Yeah, I'll be- tomorrow's Wednesday. Let's go. Something's happening tomorrow. I thought, wait,
what's happening tomorrow? Something is happening tomorrow and I don't know what it is. Okay, well,
I don't know what it is but we're gonna do it on Thursday. I'll see you guys on Thursday. We're
gonna do, uh, what was it gonna be? What the hell was- what the hell was it gonna stream?
Oh, the new house flipper update. House flipper pets DLC came out. It looks actually really good.
We're gonna do house flipper pets on, um, Thursday and then this weekend, probably on
Saturday or Sunday, we'll do some horror stuff. So we'll- yeah, we'll go- do Tuesday, we'll do
Thursday, we'll do Saturday. Maybe Saturday, Sunday? These people are still trying to kill me. Thanks
for watching, as always, everybody. Let me just say goodbye to you properly, right? Thanks for
watching. That was really funny. Um, my brain just hurts so I- I gotta get out of here. I'll see you
on Thursday. House flipper pets and then we got murder house and blood wash to play. I might be
able to even do another one. That was probably only like an hour long. I'll see you soon. That
was a ton of fun. That was- this game's great. I- I've seen this game played a million times
but I just never bought it so here it is. Really good BeamNG. That's fantastic. So I'll see you
guys later. See you Thursday. Thanks for watching. Good night. Goodbye. Take care of yourselves.
Love you, mother. You know. See you soon. The stream was fucked up. Yeah, it was, wasn't it? But
I don't know. I think I had a lot of fun. I gotta exit the game. How do I get out of here?
I'm actually looking forward to the house flipper update. There's actually- there's tons of animals.
It's not just dogs and cats. I think there are birds, bunnies, gerbils. There's a ton of stuff.
I'm gonna have an entire huge pet family. There are turtles. What about Webbed? Webbed is just
gonna be one of those games that I sit in the back pocket or whenever I decide to play it. I promise
I am gonna play it at some point. Within the next 30 days. Or within the next two weeks. Is Webbed
gonna be the new Glover? Um, no I mean I played Glover. Everybody hated it. Everybody screamed at
me and told me to leave. Promises equal lies. I'm just a very excitable person so I will say
something that I really want to do. Like oh yeah that sounds amazing. That sounds like an incredible
idea. Then two or three weeks later when you go hey uh remember when you said that you said you
promised you were gonna play it. Oh oops. Bring back community content night. Like I said before
if I'm gonna bring back community content night I'm gonna want to do another batch of green screen
stuff. That's where it's the most fun for me. So that's when you'll know. If you hear me announce
in the next few weeks I'm going back in front of the screen. Then we'll do more. What about Bionicle?
I don't have the rights to stream Bionicle. I don't think I can get them. Public domain movies?
Yeah I still want to do that too. How about retrying Halo? Yeah I'm just not a Halo guy.
It's cool. What about the Switch sports game? That did come out. Yeah there's a lot of stuff.
There's a lot of stuff to play so we can put it in the backlog. All right guys I'll see you later.
See you Thursday. Thanks for watching. Good night. Goodbye. See you soon.