God damn it, I didn't write a title. Fuck. Oops.
I was so busy getting here and turning the stream on that the title is just Amusements.
It's a- that's the worst title.
It's gotta be something better than that.
Quick, quick, before the Vaude can- can make the- seal it and keep it there.
What's a great- what's a good- uh, it's Thrillville off the rails.
Is Amusements fine?
I mean, it's really boring, but does it get the point across? Maybe.
On at the park. I think that's even worse.
Hold on, hold on, beer back.
Somebody else had this problem, where you have a normal night's sleep.
There's nothing weird about your sleep, it's just a kind of a normal night.
But for some reason you wake up, and it- it's like you're- you're living in another dimension.
Just everything's so groggy, the world is in slow motion.
Like your head, like my eyes feel like they're in somebody else's head.
Why does this happen?
What happened today?
That's every single morning.
Any doctors in here dehydrated?
No, I drink a lot of water.
I always, before bed, and it kind of depends on the night.
But I will always, before going to sleep, drink at least an eight ounce glass of water.
Just like, just drink it, and put it down.
Usually over the course of a few minutes.
Your breathing is being obstructed?
Drink water.
What about- yeah, I always have to get up and pee after like four hours.
I have pee a lot anyways though.
It's caffeine?
But I never drink coffee after four or five o'clock in the afternoon.
I have a hard, strict cutoff of coffee.
Coffee and me?
We don't hang out after five o'clock.
Six o'clock, maximum, ever.
It's all the cigarettes you smoke.
I don't smoke cigarettes.
My voice just sounds like shit.
My voice just sounds like this because I- I don't know.
I've had a junky ass voice the last two years.
I don't know why.
I've been to an ENT.
They've looked down there.
They go, it looks fine.
Everything looks great.
Why is my voice such junk sometimes?
What's going on here?
It's in your head.
Your voice is fine?
Well, no, no, no.
I'm just- it usually is.
But sometimes, man, I just- I got these like cysts in my sinuses
and I swear to God, even if every doctor has told me like,
oh, they're fine.
There's nothing wrong with it.
Last year or so, man, I get like a blockage in my nose.
My voice gets all junky.
I've got to get him removed.
I got to get him out.
I don't even- even if it's elective, just get rid of him.
He's called me a bestie?
Oh, thanks.
What the- what WTF?
Why is he alive?
I mean, I told you guys are going to be live on Wednesday.
Why are you getting your nose removed?
No, I'm not getting my- I'm getting- whatever.
Today, we're going to play- sorry I was at about five minutes late.
Happens.
Today, we're going to play Thrillville Off the Rails.
Very highly requested game.
I remember a long time ago, probably like four- at least three
or four years ago, more than that, when I was still making YouTube
videos a few times a week.
I played this game for, I think, 10 minutes and I was going to
make a video on it, but some- I don't know why I didn't.
Something in the first 15 minutes of the game made me stop
playing and I just never came back.
I don't know why.
2013 was nine years ago.
I know.
This game fucks.
This game sucks.
Fuck, I just got- why did that hurt?
Oh God, why am I so old?
You can- all right.
Let me tell you how you can tell when you're old, or when
you're getting older.
I just realized something right now.
The more that you hear me talk about me going to the doctor
and medical issues that I may or may not have, I feel like a
lot of our conversations are about me going to the doctor
this one time.
I remember having conversations with like grandparents.
You know, I was at the doctor last night and I'll tell you,
I don't think- I'm not entirely sure he understands that
my foot hurts.
I- I'm doing that to you.
And I'm only 36.
Yeah.
All right.
So this is a- this old game.
This game came out in like 2006?
2007?
Classic.
There are apparently a lot of mini games that people really
want me to play.
And I'm gonna play them.
I'm gonna go for it.
I'm gonna give you guys a little bit of a content plan
here now that we're in the new year.
By the way, if you've missed the New Year's Eve stream,
and I haven't had an opportunity to tell you,
Happy New Year, first of all.
Last time I streamed was on the 31st into the 1st of the
new year.
Hey, let's make- let's make this- let's make this a good one.
Scrumptious cake.
This is the first real stream of 2022.
What's my New Year's resolution?
I got too many.
There are way too many.
I have too many New Year's resolutions.
It's not even worth telling people what they are.
It's not even a New Year's resolution.
It's a New Year's grocery list.
You don't tell anybody what a grocery list you have is.
If you need like three or four items, like I need eggs,
I need milk, and I need Doritos.
You can tell people that.
You can say that to somebody.
I don't tell you the entire cart that I have to fill
on a weekly or bi-weekly basis.
It's way too many.
Top three
are all top three.
All- all 40 of them are in the top three.
They're just shoving each other around trying to get into
the first spot.
Top two?
I'll give you- well, no, this is not even a resolution.
I want to do- okay.
2022.
What- who cares?
I'm gonna- I can help- I hope to do a little bit more laundry
this year.
That's a real one, and that might even be number two.
Okay, let's go.
I need to start doing more laundry.
Like I've got to- I've got to do some more laundry this year.
I can't just like wait around and like, oh, is this clean?
Is it clean?
No, I can't do that.
It's stupid.
It's selfish.
It's annoying to like be like, oh, I don't care.
And number one is to clean my laundry machine, my washing
machine.
People forget to do that.
Every- every like six months, you should really use one of
those machine washing packets.
Oh, and I also want this to be the biggest content year
I've ever had.
Somewhere up there in the top five or whatever.
I don't know.
Somewhere up there.
This game has a theme song.
I need to listen to this.
Let's hear it.
Is this a real song or is this- did they make it for this game?
This is a real song?
I don't think this is DMCA.
I think they made this for Thrillville.
This is an original song?
It's a perfect day in my amusement park.
Be careful, dude.
This game is a DMCA landmine.
Oh, whatever.
This isn't a real song.
I got my ticket to ride on my rides in my amusement park.
Nobody made this song like on a- on an album somewhere for
like just a regular releasing it.
This is for this game.
All right, I have a- this is very important question for
everybody here.
First of all, I got a 1440p monitor now.
Isn't that cool?
All right, shut up for a second.
Not you guys.
No, I actually like that song.
All right.
So here's- this is really important.
This game has two different graphics settings.
One of them is the original, the original PS2 graphics and
the other one is the new updated Xbox 360 graphics or
something, right?
Everybody that I've seen talk about this game talks about-
Is this a real song?
No, you just spelled Thrillville.
This is not a- of course it's an original song.
They're saying Thrillville.
I'm fine.
I'm DMCA fine.
All right, so do you want- let's see what it looks like
with the- with the new graphics, okay?
There's two different graphics.
This is the new, updated.
You pick a character.
That's what they look like.
A lot of people said that the old PS2 original models look
way better, but we're going to be the judge of that.
Okay.
So what does it look like with the original models?
We might have to do a trade-off here though, because I think
it makes all the other stuff worse looking too.
The actual park and the environments and the lighting
and everything.
Let's see.
I mean, this is definitely a little more charming, I think.
But should we play with the original graphics?
Original, original.
Do vote.
All right.
We get a poll up here.
Original graphics or updated graphics?
Scene two.
This is an- how- do they have an entire original album?
How come nobody's- has ever said to play this OST?
This is the whole album.
Whiplash baby on that roller coaster.
I- why have I not heard this?
This is actually ACDC.
This is not ACDC.
All right.
Well in the meantime, I can just pick a character.
Who do I want to play with?
This whole game is played in a third-person perspective
and you can ride all the rides you make and the rides
are not normal.
They're like shooting people out of cannonballs and stuff.
I don't know.
Who do I want to play as?
Harry?
Thomas?
Jasmine?
Greg?
I kind of- I kind of like Eden.
Wait, hold on.
Oliver?
Bethany?
Lane?
Jim?
Joseph?
I kind of like Jessica too.
Hmm.
I think it's gonna have to be Eden.
Eden.
Is this just- is this just Ness?
All right, appearance.
Head style.
It's Aaron.
Not- I can't do that in 2022.
I like this hair.
Hair color.
No, it's just Lucas.
Should we make Lucas?
That's fine.
All right, what about clothing?
I don't think I want to change any of the clothes.
I like it like this.
It's Bart Simpson.
Well, it's whoever.
I like this.
I don't want to change anything.
Edit name.
It's not- it's definitely not gonna be Eden anymore.
It's definitely gonna have to be Lucas.
Lucas.
Oh, I'm ready.
I'm ready.
I could do it.
I could do it and I could make a lot of you real mad.
I could go for it.
Thinking about doing it.
Thinking about making everybody very furious the first stream of 2022.
No, it's too early.
Too early for that.
I'll probably do it at some point this stream.
I won't be able to contain myself.
All right, you ready?
We'd have to- does this soundtrack just play the whole game?
Original graphics.
That's what we're gonna stay with.
Sounds good to me.
Start the game.
Here we go.
Three, two, one.
Are we little?
Are we tiny?
Are we like a- I feel like we're as big as mice.
Is that what this whole thing is?
Yeah, we're like mice.
We're as big as little mice.
Is this PS2?
This looks really good for PS2 FMV.
This looks great.
This reminds me of that guy.
The guy that was in every Disney movie.
And he was like this.
Oh, let me tell you something.
No, you have to be careful out there.
He was like the Mad Hatter.
What was that guy's name?
He was the Mad Hatter.
Not Goofy.
No.
Not Rick Sanchez.
If you know, you know.
Okay, this is my park.
I was like, that's dangerous.
Maybe it's because of the no safety equipment on any of the rides.
I have a feeling that's why.
Okay, everything I do is thrills.
And I can do missions to do more.
Okay, but wait a minute.
I own this park and I like ate.
My stomach is what?
Oh my God, that's fast.
Okay, there's a sprint.
Is there a jump?
Oh wait, hold on.
All right, build.
Now that you're in charge, one of your most important jobs is to build rides and stalls in the park.
I can build these rides.
That will make your guests happy and make you the most money.
Ed Wynn was the laughing guy in Mary Poppins.
Is that who it is?
He was always a guy that made toys and shit, right?
He was always a toys guy.
Like I'm the toy maker.
I'm the toy maker.
Right?
Now that you're in charge, one of your most important jobs is to build rides and stalls.
All right.
These build zones are for cargo rides, games, and stalls.
Anytime you want to build something, simply walk into one of these zones and press the A button.
Oh shit, okay.
How much customization do I have?
Every attraction requires power in order to run.
Power?
This meter shows you how much power each section of your park has left.
Pay attention to it.
What if I run out of power?
Okay, I looked down at the lower left and I thought that was a cryptocurrency.
I was like, what is that?
Oh, and then I'm...
Okay, that's like a...
That's a euro.
I was like, what is that?
The crypto euro.
All right.
I get it.
Can I do USD?
All right.
Tank frenzy.
The first build mission.
All right.
We need to build tank...
Wait, can I build whatever I want?
Sideshow.
Test your strength.
Fucking bowl.
Wild frontier.
Oh my god, mini golf.
Prospector stakeout.
What do I do?
I kind of want to do...
How about Luftwaffe 2?
What is this one?
Bandito chinchilla.
I feel like I heard that name before and I don't know anything about it.
Stunt...
All right.
How about this?
Test your strength.
Oh wait, I have to build...
Okay, for the tutorial I have to do...
Where is it?
What happened to it?
What happened?
Where is it?
There it is.
What happened?
I can't select any of these.
Should I just back out?
He's a loser.
Bandito...
I can't select any of these.
Oh, wait, what?
Oh, I have to build tank frenzy.
I have to.
I thought it was just saying that you could build tank frenzy
if you wanted to.
Okay, so spin it around.
Does it matter where it is?
I guess I'll put it right here.
Oh shit.
All right.
It's ready.
Let's talk about roller coasters.
To build one, select coaster from the build menu or walk up to...
Can I actually build coaster?
And take it from there.
Oh, nice.
I'll be there to help.
Oh, hell yeah.
Hell yeah.
And you'll just love some of the crazy new wall coaster pieces I'm designing.
These coasters do things that people never thought possible.
Amazing, huh?
Are people going to die on this stream?
I hope not.
After you've placed down attractions, don't forget to paint and style them to look just the way you want them to.
Oh, I can customize even more.
Okay, cool.
So I can build.
Build tutorial complete.
Now then, make your way over to another column of light.
I'll catch up with you there.
Okay.
All right.
Manage.
Your park is in good shape when two things are healthy.
Guest happiness and profit.
You can use your cash to build new rides, hire staff, and run promotions.
When you charge the right prices, your park value will soar.
The park menu helps you manage the big picture by giving you lots of useful information about your park.
Your name is Jeremy, laugh out loud.
What the hell's your name?
Like, Greg?
Who cares?
Why is that such a funny thing?
Is this just a name?
It's just a name.
The overview screen shows a summary of the guests in your park.
It can help you see what your guests want.
And the happier they are, the more money you'll earn.
Make people happy.
Use the park upgrade screen to research new rides, or start a marketing campaign to attract more guests, or even take out a loan.
In park information, you'll find all kinds of useful charts that can help you see how your park changes over time.
And finally, in Thrillville stats, you can see your greatest products from all your parks.
Let's start the first manage mission.
Manage.
It's time to think big.
Let's create a great advertising campaign that will have people flocking to Thrillville.
Don't forget to put the ads where everyone can see them.
Alright, so we go to Teen Monthly, Daily Gossip, Parenting for Success, The National Newspaper, Witch Mansion, The Kiddy's Channel, Toon's TV, The Know-It Channel, or T-
Alright, what's cheap?
I'm not blowing-
Let's just Teen-
Teen Monthly.
That's fine.
Well done.
I don't want to spend a bunch of money.
Remember, the park menu helps you decide how you want to manage the place.
Cool.
It shows you what you've done, and what you can do.
Alright, we're almost through the tutorial.
Halfway.
Okay.
Now, head over to any other-
I'm so ready to play.
I can't wait.
We need to-
I need to know these things.
I know, tutorial, resident sleeper.
Just relax.
Don't worry.
You can talk to anyone.
What?
I can talk to anybody in the park.
I can just chat with people?
Alright, that's cool.
I can put them on the spot for trivia?
What?
Wait, hold on.
What do you mean, matchmaking?
I can put people in the park on dates?
It's a dating sim?
No.
Alright, here we go.
How do we do this?
Go talk to somebody.
Go talk to Sammy Dowie.
Hey, Sammy!
Hi.
So, I thought that car was just gonna run him over.
I thought the back truck back there was just gonna kill us.
Okay.
Okay, no.
What do you mean, no?
That's not a place for children to be.
Alright, what do you-
What do you needs?
Alright, they like gentle and mild rides.
They have to go to the bathroom.
Very badly.
They're pretty happy.
Alright, so you hung-
I need to build some stuff.
What should you-
Can I give him a gift?
Trivia.
Okay.
What is it, breathing in gas fumes?
What- who cares?
The grosser the better.
We're- we're-
I'm making a good friend right now.
The United Kingdom got its first female Prime Minister in 1979.
She must have been really excited to get the job.
Oh, wow, we're friends.
Okay, what's the-
What- what-
Do you know the home run record?
Wait, what about just chatting?
We saw Piranha at the zoo.
They were awesome.
Awesome.
Those things scare me.
Okay, a lot of you guys are like question marking and going-
If you've ever heard two kids talk to each other,
this is exactly what they do.
They're just little weird factoid machines
of things that they know.
This is exactly how it goes.
They just say a sentence of something that they know or found out today
to each other.
I don't think they're even listening to each other.
Didn't like that.
Lemonade.
I heard the guy who did Whiplash is playing Lemonade this summer.
You have a lot of skills for such a little kid.
So what-
How long do I-
Squadron Ace?
Have you played Squadron Ace?
The end boss is huge.
I haven't tried it yet, but maybe I will soon.
This is-
That's disgusting to me.
That's an M rated game.
Who bought you that?
Who bought you that game?
You shouldn't be playing that.
Hey, spring training starts soon.
Baseball season is almost here.
Baseball is my favorite sport.
Okay, liked that a lot.
What just-
What happens when we get all the way up?
Oh, have you played Tank Frenzy?
I just made it.
For all-out action, you should check out the Tank Frenzy arcade game.
That car back there is freaking me out.
I feel like this is gonna land on everybody.
I haven't tried it yet, but maybe I will soon.
Doesn't this kid have to go to the bathroom?
It went from 62 to 67.
What's with all those talk radio stations?
Play some music already.
I know.
More music, less talk.
It's important to eat a healthy diet.
Now, kids don't want to-
No.
We have an old cat that loves to sleep in my bed.
We have an old cat that loves to sleep on my bed.
Okay, that's enough!
That's enough little Lucas!
Now come over here and let me show you the candy machine!
Like, how long is it gonna go on for?
Cats are so annoying.
Why would you let a kid run this place?
You don't like cats? Why?
What?
Our school has a really great marching band.
I can't wait to join my school's marching band.
I just want to see what happens when you get to the last-
the second bar there.
You all want to know.
We need to know.
You should try Stunt Rider.
It's a great new arcade game.
I chatted at another park.
It was pretty good.
Alright, can we please be best friends?
Seafood is really great.
I love to eat fish.
I love to eat all kinds of fish.
My dad catches fish.
My mom cooks it, and I eat it.
It's a great system.
Okay, we're almost there.
Haven't even asked, how are you yet?
How are you?
I have to go wheelie real bad.
Shit!
Why are all the rides always broken?
Who's fixing them?
Isn't that me talking shit about my own place?
If you had to go on our mini cold dogs,
I hate cold hot dogs.
Cold hot dogs are the worst.
Yep, we agree with that.
Alright.
Whiplash.
Have you heard the latest smash hit, Whiplash?
Have you heard the latest smash hit?
Whiplash is-
I'm a huge fan of that.
Alright, now we're best friends.
I even have the ringtone.
Good friends.
Alright.
Now go- go on, get out of here.
Bows can throw up.
They expel their stomachs,
use their forearms to dig out the stomach's contents,
and then swallow the stomach again.
Ew!
She hates me now.
I'm sorry.
See?
That was fun, wasn't it?
Talking to people is going to tell you a whole lot about how well your park is doing.
Okay.
Tutorial complete.
Just two more columns of light now.
Pick either one.
Alright, upkeep and then- wait, there's games too.
Alright, upkeep.
Upkeep, upkeep, staff.
Your staff will keep things running while you're busy with other projects.
They keep Thrillville in tip-top shape.
Okay.
Mechanics fix and maintain riots.
Groundskeepers keep the garbage under control.
Yep.
And entertainers cheer up the crowds.
Entertainers.
Staff will start working as soon as you hire them.
Do much better with training.
Okay.
Please find the gambling minigame.
And training is a hands-on situation.
You'll help your staff get more efficient by pitching in and showing them how it's done.
Okay.
To hire, train, and fire staff, go to your park menu and select staff.
Let's start the first upkeep mission.
Crowd pleaser.
Shake your groove thing by performing Thrillville's Stuntz new theme song with the park's cheerleaders.
It's good exercise and an even greater way to promote the song.
Watch the success gauge.
It indicates how satisfied the crowd is with your performance.
If it drops to zero, it's game over.
Hey, oh God crap.
It's, it's an Xbox controller and you know, I'm going to mess it up because X is Y and Y is, you know what I mean?
All right, let's go.
Wait, what?
Oh shit.
Okay.
This is a real song.
Do they make this for Thrillville?
I feel like this is a real song.
I can't, I don't know.
We just wait, do they say Thrillville in the song?
Listen up.
Thrillville, right?
This is a real song.
Is it a, it's a real, this is a real song.
Oh, whatever.
Goodbye.
This is the last scream.
I don't think this is, I don't think so.
Okay.
I don't think so.
This is Miley Cyrus.
Why do I look so sad?
All right, I get it.
So we're not going to ever do the cheerleading missions.
All right, cool.
Now you're starting to get it.
Even the work at Thrillville is a game.
And now you also see how we.
All right, final one.
We're almost ready to begin our play through of Thrillville.
Welcome to the game.
Many of your jobs will involve playing games and riding the rides.
Yes, I know.
It's tough being a park manager.
You can play every game and ride every ride yourself by walking up to it and pressing the A button.
Every single ride.
And then selecting play from the context menu.
Can I ride my own rides?
Let's try the first games mission.
All right, we'll play stunt rider.
You can perform spectacular stunts in the air, but try to land on your back wheel.
Celebrate, lean, reverse, horn.
Previous music track.
God, lean.
All right, whatever.
Why did this just turn into like a Newgrounds game?
Big air.
Slow down, slow down.
All right, I get it.
I get it.
This is cool.
Don't land on your head.
Oh, I missed the star.
It's all right.
Level two.
All right, let's go.
Oh!
This is fun.
All right.
I got to be careful.
Don't go too fast.
Oof.
That was bad.
Slow down.
Yeah, there's a game like the trials, right?
I was always so bad at these.
I was awful at these games.
Always.
The trials games was such a huge thing on YouTube.
Back in the YouTube days.
I never played them.
I never made a video on them.
I don't think because I just couldn't do it.
I was embarrassing.
I think I maybe there was one.
I think there's one.
Give me a break.
No!
Get up there.
Is this happy wheels?
No, this is not happy wheels.
I never played that either.
Oh, I didn't play that for another reason though.
I just don't know.
I didn't want to play it.
And not because I didn't think I was good at it.
Did I do it?
Is it?
I feel like this is made in a little big planet.
All right.
I'm so bad.
Cry.
It was made in flash.
I'm sure a lot of these probably were.
Are these mini games?
Are there a lot of them like this?
How many games are in the game?
Dude, your little big planet screen sucked.
I didn't, I never streamed little big planet.
What are you talking about?
I've never streamed a little big planet.
Slow down.
There it is.
All right.
Nice.
You did.
You literally did.
When did I stream little big planet?
Did four years ago?
No, I didn't.
You forgot.
I have never played little big planet on stream.
Not a chance.
It was in 2015.
I did not.
Here we go.
It's time.
If Rick talked like this, would half of you guys like the show now?
All right.
I said, why is there an event horizon happening?
I now am the park manager.
I want to talk to, let's talk to Olivia Edwards.
How you doing?
How's it?
How's your day in the park going?
You do?
Well, I'm the owner.
Mr.
Obvious attitude stinks.
You know that?
I just got money for that.
I thought the person just fell down.
It's too many sounds.
I don't like how loud it is.
All right.
I'm gonna ride the roller coaster.
Ride.
What?
What happened?
What's going on?
What is this?
What happened to me?
Why did I get ejected?
What happened?
Oh my God.
This is terrifying.
It's not finished.
What do you mean it's not finished?
What?
Why?
Why are we doing this to everybody?
That's not just happening to me.
Oh my goodness.
All right.
Well, whatever.
That was kind of cool.
Kind of want to play a tank game.
Tank Frenzy.
Trick out.
Western theme.
With axes.
Badge.
With a dollar.
Arrows.
Cute.
Definitely F present.
Play.
I can sell it too?
How do you play Tank Frenzy?
Keep moving or you'll be a sitting duck
for the enemy fire.
Okay.
Left trigger, right trigger.
Left up, right down.
Whoa.
Oh, I hate these controls.
What kind of a ride is this?
Was it shooting people in like a military scenario?
What's going on?
This is a fucked up ride.
It's a very fun ride.
Oh wait, no.
It's an arcade game, right?
This is not, we're not, I'm not in this tank.
You are, I am not.
Wait, I got bomblets?
What does that do?
Real tragedy.
This is not a war crime.
I'm, this is an arcade game.
I'm not going to get upset.
The building's just huge.
All right, let's go.
Can I do anything?
What else can I do?
Oh wait, the repair pod.
All right.
I'll get it.
I got it.
Missed health?
Is it this thing right here?
Yeah.
Ooh.
This is scary music.
Cheating.
That's not cheating.
It's a health pack.
What are you, I can't even look over there.
What are you saying?
I had a dream that you were like staffed somewhere.
Let me, hold on.
I'll read it.
I'll read it if you stop saying it.
My bed was filled with piss.
Thanks for the dream.
This is really loud.
I got to turn this down.
Wait, what do you think I was playing?
All right.
I want to get off the fucking war ride.
I don't want to ride this anymore.
I want to take the VR helmet off and get out of the war simulator.
Die.
Rapid fire?
Oh, I'm alive.
All right.
That's better.
That was horrible.
Why am I playing flash games?
Well, we're inside of a machine right now.
Wait, we're playing a game inside of the game in the machine.
Get it?
Now I have to pee because you told me that dream.
Area neutralized.
55 people defeated?
Is this a boss fight?
Where?
He has to go real bad.
And I'd say it's probably at like 65 right now.
Not that high.
65 maybe.
Do it.
Imagine you go to an amusement park and you spend the whole day
playing the like tank kill everybody simulator.
All of my friends right now are outside riding the rides.
And I'm just in here trying to get a high score on this machine.
They all have cotton candy in their hands funnel cake.
What happened to Jeremy?
Oh, he's he's playing.
He's playing the war simulator still in that like weird dark room.
Does he want anything?
I don't know.
It doesn't get I don't think he gets reception in there.
My texts aren't going through.
Where's fart simulator?
No.
Hey, thank you.
Dan P for the 10 community subs and thank you to Swift Sean for
the five community subs.
Appreciate it.
I'm gonna die.
What are your opinions on funnel cake?
I think it's great.
You can only you can only eat it like once a year though,
or twice a year.
It's amazing.
It's really great.
Hey minimum and thank you minimum entropy for the 25 community
subs.
Appreciate it.
And then we invested motherfucker.
Thanks for five community subs.
I don't want to play that one again.
I gotta find my friends.
I can't see over all this what I mean all this trash where staff
get Courtney is the entertainer $35 a month.
That's not very much Charlie's $20 a month.
All right.
Well, where's Charlie mechanic ground with the groundskeeper?
I got a train.
I got a train this person.
Hey, what what I have a horn Heidi some items are worth more
points than others.
So select what you collect carefully.
What?
Wash and vacuum.
What am I trying to vacuum puke off the ground?
Oh, this would be so screwed up.
Why can I get it?
Get it.
Is that it?
No, there's more puke.
Wait, come here.
Get out of the way.
This place is disgusting.
Wait, there's no barrels.
You reverse suction pick it up.
What the hell are you doing?
Oh my god, pick it up.
Get out of the way.
What's wrong?
Oh, you need to level up.
I have to do that again, right?
Training 90 foot.
Why am I even as why am I this character?
I talk to people not one food stand.
What's that?
Oh, I got whatever that was.
All right.
I think that's okay.
Should I train do it one more time?
Yeah, I got to level them up.
You've arrived that drops you from 300 feet.
Why are you surprised people are puking?
I do.
I didn't know that only clean the puke that is worth more.
You're right.
Okay.
Yep.
Good idea.
It's that parachute ride.
I'm gonna I want to make a ride the other way.
It only gives 7500.
You're gonna do an amusement park IRL stream.
No, no, I know the puke in here.
It's very cute everywhere.
You must not leave this area.
It's good.
Battle fielded.
Get it.
Oh my god, pick it up for the love of God.
It doesn't matter.
I just need level up once.
Nice.
So what does that mean?
All right, you're at a hundred training.
You're good to go.
So you got money.
All right, all of you, all of you freeze.
Sam, I need to talk to you, Sam.
Hello.
Your park is absolutely amazing.
Thanks a lot.
Appreciate that.
Okay.
Huh?
Matchmaking girl who would be perfect for you.
You should ask her out.
Who?
I don't think so.
I don't think I've met anybody.
I really hate whining customers.
Yeah, don't you?
I don't like people whining.
I just heard an explosion.
What's happening?
Why?
What's going on?
What was your worst?
I think I made bandito chinchilla cry.
Oh, okay.
People are talking about that one.
It's really funny.
Don't you think so?
Advertise the game.
It is an awesome game.
Bandito is my hero.
All right.
We're almost friends.
I challenge you.
And I'm here to prove it to you.
Challenge you to what?
You have no idea what you're in for.
Let's play.
What did I just challenge him to?
Okay.
I thought that said Thrillville fumes.
What do you mean?
Like we get what we're going to breathe out of a paint can together.
What are you talking about?
I thought it said fumes.
Okay.
Prospector putt.
Which one should I challenge him to?
The flumes?
I don't know how to play bandito.
Prospector putt.
All right.
Judge the power of your shot carefully.
Sometimes a soft shot is better than a hard one.
Shoot flyby scores blimp.
Blimp.
All right.
Sam got four on this one.
Okay.
Let's go.
How hard do I have to hit it?
I don't even that's 50% power.
Holy shit, Sam.
You got five on this?
What?
You are awful.
Well, an eight-year-old is going to show you how to play this game.
Okay.
This is greased up.
Somebody greased it up before I got here.
I still beat him.
You got four on the next one too.
Wow, pathetic.
So what if I win?
Do one full power swing.
I want to beat this guy.
I don't know.
I don't know what it does.
Okay.
Four.
I think this kid only gets four.
Oh my God.
Come on.
That would have been awesome.
Get in there.
Straight ahead.
All right.
This should be a hole-in-one.
Hole-in-one.
Oh.
All right.
I'm currently winning by a lot.
What does this one look like?
All right.
We're going off this wall hard.
Whatever.
Let's get it up there.
It doesn't matter.
You guys understand that I can literally just swing and miss five times.
I'm still in first place.
It doesn't matter.
You got four again.
It's this one.
All right.
Through the tunnel.
Into the saloon.
I'm just going to go hard.
I don't think you can't get a hole-in-one on this one.
Do it with your eyes closed.
No.
I bet you can't get a birdie.
All right.
If I get a birdie on this one.
What are you going to do for me?
What do I get?
Figure it out because it's about to happen right now.
You don't think I still have confidence that I can do it?
Okay.
Actually, I got to be careful because I can't screw this up because now I'm in trouble.
Oh, no.
Uh-oh.
How many?
What am I?
How ahead am I?
Okay.
I can't screw this up.
It's going to be close after this.
Sink that.
All right.
I'm still fine.
I got five.
I'm five strokes ahead of him at this point.
I would have to literally just throw for fun.
What do I get for that one, huh?
What do I get for that one?
You going to give me some of that?
Now it's just BM time.
I can't even BM.
I just win.
Is that too hard?
Yep.
So what do I get for BM?
Okay.
What do you actually get for doing this?
You get its pride?
Battle results.
He's not going to be mad at me, right?
Thanks for a great contest.
You're welcome.
Wow.
All right.
Friends has a new puppy so cute.
Oh, I know what happened.
He just let me win because I'm seven years old.
Right.
I hate dogs because they're too noisy.
Okay.
I get it now.
Your posse seems so cool and close-knit.
These explosions, man.
I don't like these.
Wow.
Thank you.
Oh my God.
Somebody's dead.
What happened?
What happened over there?
I think my cell phone just started ringing.
It's like,
like text, text.
My phone's blowing up right now.
I got to get over there.
I have to go.
Holy, what happened?
Did you do anything fun last weekend?
Last weekend, my family and I went to my cousin's wedding.
Okay.
What about, um, let's go.
I'm friends.
We can gossip.
How about Teen Monthly?
HG Crop really has it out for drill though.
You read her a review of the park in Teen Monthly?
Another explosion.
That review deserved a Pulitzer Prize.
What do you, wait, what do you mean?
My God.
I don't know what's happening on that ride.
But I think a mechanic needs to go check it out because
that's not, I don't think that's, that's not good.
Oh, yeah.
Actually, the countless people that are exploding in your car ride.
It's way too fast.
It goes 140 miles per hour in a track that's designed
for about 30.
It's a little weird, I think, man.
Will you just be friends with me?
What do you mean?
Oh, he's starving.
I think I got to open up a hunger stall.
Wait, let's ask him about mini-golf.
I need help being a mini-golf pro.
No, trivia.
Good friends.
You know how an albatross sleeps?
They'll soar through the air at 25 miles per hour.
I'm not a big fan of birds.
Oh my God.
April 15 is National Glaze Spiral Ham Day in the United States.
Okay.
Ham is great.
If only because it inspired the hamburger.
Okay.
Well, you're not, you're not very bright.
All right, we're good friends.
That's all that needs to be said.
And I just want to let you know that I appreciate our friendship.
Can I ask you,
now that we're friends,
what do you think is a good idea?
How do you think the park could be improved?
Where's the food stands, dude?
Right.
I got you.
I hear that.
I hear that feedback.
I understand.
And I understand I say, I thank you for your feedback and criticism.
I need a food stall immediately.
Where can I put it?
I need a food stall right here.
Carnival ride, game, stall.
All right.
Balloon stall, coffee stall, fizzy, hat, ice cream, pizza, pizza stall.
Get it right here.
Fizzy entrance.
Right there.
Everybody get out of the way.
All right.
Pizza stall.
Play?
All right.
How much is pizza?
Pizza's dollar?
No, don't think so.
It's like four bucks.
Three dollars for pizza.
How do you play?
Do I actually make the pizza?
You want to play vendor tender?
Rebound your shots off the walls if you haven't got a straight shot.
All right.
What?
Oh, it's just bust a groove.
Whatever, bust a move.
I gotta chain it together, right?
Eight times multiplier.
I'm like, what?
No.
Big chain.
This is a Rugrats voice actor.
Is it?
It actually might be.
I think you got it.
All right, chain it.
There it is.
Thank you.
Do you get anything for doing this?
Or is it just the thing that you can do for fun in the park?
Oh, come on.
Put your cam on.
I don't know.
I don't think not today.
Maybe in like a half hour.
Maybe in a minute.
I will put my webcam on and maybe a half hour.
That is that's um, that's Phil and Lil, right?
Phil and Lil, right?
You're already here on bottom left.
I want to, I want to do it.
I want to do the, I can't though.
That's a 2021 thing.
What?
Okay.
Why is that such a, what's with like the like manager trope of
like, why all, why do managers have to be like this?
Are you lucky you haven't been fired yet?
Like why, why are they all such, why are they all such shitty people?
I think management, you got to make sure that your employees are fucking happy.
Right?
Why is it like this?
I think there are some managers that do, do it right.
Yes, some do.
I don't know.
I just don't, you got to like, you can't just be a fucking dick.
Like God, please.
Managers can be, unfortunately, easy on Jerma.
He's never had a real job.
What do you mean be easy on me?
What do you mean I've had a real job?
What are you talking about?
Assistant managers.
What did you say?
I'm going to read that.
Assistant managers tend to be the good ones.
I can't fire anymore.
What happened?
Here we go.
I forgot I was watching this live and I tried to skip this boring part.
I'm just doing a mini game.
I'm gaming right now.
All right.
I don't want to do this anymore.
I have like two hours remaining.
That's I have the entire runtime of the lower the rings in the top, right?
I don't want to do this anymore.
Skip it.
I'm doing well though.
Look at how much I'm making a lot of money.
I think I don't know what this is for.
I'm just going to lose.
No, I'm not.
This is I can change together now.
Check this out.
All right.
I lost.
So I got that I'm ready.
I want to make a ride.
I want to build a ride.
This is the space over here.
What should I do?
What's that?
I got 15 grand.
How much money do I have?
All right, let's go.
Carnival ride.
Build.
Oh, whoa.
Light Fiesta.
Head metal.
Head over heels.
Rotorvation.
Supercell.
Turbo prop.
I build a roller coaster.
Maybe not yet.
I think I probably have to unlock it.
This one's really high nausea.
I thought that was 48 minute duration.
You can move to the next vill.
Again, how do I move to the next vill?
Go finish your existing coaster.
Oh, is that the one that's hurting people?
All right.
What do I do?
Crick out.
Ride.
Manage.
Real day edit.
Edit track.
Okay.
Oh, it does just go into the air.
It doesn't end.
What is whoa?
What is this?
This fire?
A stunt jump.
How do I stop it?
How do I?
I don't understand.
How do I like?
Hit B.
Is that actually?
Wait, did I actually edit it?
I think I edited this track.
Where's my?
Where is it?
Holy shit.
That was cool.
Double jump.
Okay.
All right.
I have to get in there.
So sorry.
Anybody rides this.
Nobody ride this.
Nobody ride it.
I made it go right into the wall.
All right.
Delete this.
Zoom this out.
All right.
Maybe I should just do track assist and just have it help.
If you'd like to track assist to help you at this point.
Yeah.
I didn't even start this.
Oh, what?
Yes.
I'd like to use that.
You've succeeded.
Completed track 72 thrill.
I didn't even start this one.
So I, of course, I'm just gonna let it get finished.
All right.
So now people can actually ride this and not die.
Very cool.
All right.
Saddlesville.
I got to build my own.
Yeah.
I need to, I need to plot a land where I can build my own.
Who are these people?
Hello.
Hi there.
Crashes in thrillville are like candy.
Only sweeter.
Samuel Jackson.
They're having a steel cage match when wrestling comes to the local coliseum.
Wait, there's wrestling?
I like to go to the matches and yell arm bar.
Put him in an arm bar.
Happiness loneliness.
This is very odd.
So he's incredibly happy, but he is peak loneliness.
Isn't he here with like an entire family?
What?
But he's really happy.
I can't stand it when the park is messy.
No one likes a messy park.
I once had an African great parrot named salty Joe.
I found him while walking down the street.
What?
Great parrots have a lot of special needs in their heart.
Just want to insult this person.
I need to find a plot of land that I got $14,000.
I'm going to a different Ville.
Go to HQ.
Oh, I can't you said I could.
Would you lie to me?
Wait, the lower the lonely bar, the more lonely they are.
Oh, that's kind of confusing.
Keep walking.
Well, I have to walk to the other parks.
Why can't I just ride the train?
Wait, I it's I'm just here.
Why would I need to drive the train five feet?
Poster.
I get to build it.
Oh hell.
Yeah, let's go coaster.
Where's the coaster?
Prospector stakeout.
Oh, that's one of those shooting games.
That's cool.
I have to build it.
All right.
Carnival ride.
Use the carnival ride.
I don't think I've unlocked roller coaster yet guys.
My rides.
I have to level up.
Yeah.
All right.
Let me let me I gotta level up.
I'm very invested.
Let's go.
You have to place them at the coaster bits.
Here.
You have to do it on the platform.
Coaster.
Which met build your own?
Would you like to begin with a tutorial?
Advanced coaster.
Let's cover some advanced techniques.
I'll show you how to build a coaster by following a design
that I made myself.
As we go.
I'll point out some of the tricks I use when designing coasters.
I've made a lot of these.
Your job will be to match your track with the gray one.
Remember your preview may show many different possibilities.
Sure.
I built the starting lift hill for you.
The most important part of a lift hill is the drop.
We got a big drop.
The drop gives your coaster the speed it needs to reach the
end of the track.
The longer or steeper the drop.
I know what I know with thermodynamics is whatever it is.
I understand aerodynamics green and then place the track.
All right, so we got to go like this and another piece and
now create some airtime airtime is when you're lifted from
your seat.
It's one surefire way to gain airtime.
The drop you've just built gives us the smooth the pre
airtime until good now at the top of the bump.
We want a level.
Excellent.
Now make a steep slope.
Okay, now flatten the track.
Another good way of increasing your coasters thrill rating
is to add whoa coaster pieces.
Whoa coaster.
Yep, left bumper.
Add intensity and fun to your parts like the pendulizer.
So let's now scroll over to the pendulizer piece and build
it.
What would you ever get on this ride for the thrills?
But when building a coaster, okay, should also try to keep
a low nausea rating a high nausea rating means some who
cares refused to get on a ride.
The secret of low nausea is to keep your coaster turn
smooth by banking.
Yeah, banking you bank it to the right a little bit a banked
turn twists on its side to ease the strain to bank a track
piece.
There it is.
Then use the controls to bank in the opposite direction.
Try it now.
Now try making a tight right bank turn when your preview
turns green place the track.
Yeah, I know.
I bank it.
All right, bank it.
We're really getting it.
Now it's time to straighten out the track first nice job.
Now make a short slope now at a small bump at another short
set and a final track piece.
All right, easy.
Incredibly easy.
Let's go.
Coaster remember the secret to it, but after all this is
let's go.
I don't want this piece of shit.
I want to make my own coaster.
No, I want to build.
Okay.
Thank you.
Pendulizer wagon trail.
Whoa is high.
Let's we got hot rod stunt log movie a log flume.
Pendulizer which I start with wagon trail.
Wild mine wagon trail.
Let's go.
All right.
How do we start this?
I'm going to say how much room do I have to work with?
I think it can either go this way.
Let's have a go this way.
All right.
Let's start it.
I can do the whole map.
Well, I have 14,000 pounds.
I need one of those.
Go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go things.
You know what I mean?
How do I put that on?
How do I put on like the thing TNT alley where I just people
get on the ride and I just blow them up.
Okay.
I need I need the chain lift.
Yeah.
How do I get the chain lift?
Is it part of the whoa?
It's just automatic.
Is it?
Pull it back.
No, stop it.
It looks it's automatic.
All right.
Okay, that's too much.
I want to have a go.
That's what I want.
This way.
I'd straighten it out.
Add a couple explosions and then we're going straight down.
Oh, wait, wait.
I can't they smash into a wall.
Have a go into the church goes right into the graveyard.
I'm not done yet.
Now back it up.
It's going to be a little higher.
What is this safety alert near too many guests?
How much is this going to cost?
I don't have a price for this.
I've got even afford this.
Oh, I can.
Okay.
I see you on the left.
I can do that.
I want to just test it.
All right.
Now help me finish it.
Thrill 92 nausea is not even that high.
I swear.
I wanted I'm just the first coaster ever.
I want to see how it works.
All right.
Let's write it.
Here we go.
It's time.
Oh my God.
We're going up on our first coaster in Thrillville.
That would be scary.
I like that.
It pretends like it's going to dump you.
Not bad.
I like that first loop.
Nice.
All right.
It's pretty good.
That's a 92 Thrill.
I like it.
All right.
It works.
Oh, I think I leveled up the G's.
I'm going to try to make a nausea coaster.
That's full 100.
I just was 10.
That's my first roller coaster ever.
New park available.
New technology available.
Coaster Tron.
Thrillville other worlds.
Ah, select a park to open.
Thrillville giant.
Incredible new ants eye perspective on life.
Dodge rampaging pets in Lawnville.
And Marvel at Candyville.
All right.
Explorer.
Or holiday.
Which one should I do?
Giant?
Other worlds.
Other worlds is, or coward.
All right.
Let's go to other worlds.
Whoa.
This is a, oh, there's robots.
Anyway, find out what they're doing in Thrillville and stop them.
Do they talk?
Unit 11648.
Uh, should I make friends?
I'm a big fan of fast food.
Unit is only programmed to discuss numerical algorithms in eight hour intervals.
All right.
Really cool.
What are your needs?
How would you possibly?
Yeah, I was going to say, hey, you don't have a bladder.
There's no nausea either.
We can put these guys upside down a thousand times.
All right, let's do it.
Let's put, let's, let's put this shit at its absolute limits.
I'm going to have the coaster spin in a circle a hundred times.
What is this?
Sparkle Island 2.
Of course I want to play Sparkle Island 2.
Yeah, do you mind?
There's a huge line for this ride.
What is this?
This is running at a weird frame rate.
This brings me back.
Yeah, this is, this is just complete nostalgia bait for all of you guys.
The reason why I'm playing this is because I know a lot of you grew up with this game and I knew a lot of you were going to be like,
Oh my God, he's playing Thrillville.
What is that?
Is this Super Frog?
There's a million games that will like this.
It's not just this one.
I kind of like this game though.
This is fun.
I imagine if he touches you, it's over.
Make it so people have negative g-force and make them.
Yeah, I mean, I'm going to try to do something crazy.
That's my first coaster.
I got to at least get a minute.
I'm having fun with this game.
The diamond jump.
The character is so floaty.
Hey, just go play Bubble Bobble.
I just saved you 40 minutes waiting in line.
All right, here comes the coaster.
How much money do I have?
I only have $2,000, but I only have two grand.
What?
Two grand, that's it?
What happened?
We're going to jack the prices up.
Oh, no, I'm kidding.
I'm kidding.
It was a joke.
It's $6.
See, it's $6 again.
Oh, I'm sorry.
It was a joke.
I was making a thing.
It's not expensive anymore.
I can put a coaster here.
All right, that's cool.
Oceanville is that way.
Let's put some food stalls.
Balloon stalls.
All right, coffee.
Definitely need that.
Coffee shop right in the corner.
Prices for the coffee.
Let's make it $2.50.
Get some more food here.
Don't coffee and donuts.
I think that makes sense, right?
Coffee and donuts right next to each other.
$1.50 for a donut.
All right, coffee, donuts.
And then maybe like a game or something.
Yeah, like a little game.
Robo-K.O.
Shoot Zone.
Coconut.
Space Trampolines.
That sounds awesome, actually.
How much does this cost?
I think I can afford it.
Space Trampolines.
And then let's trick it out.
Space-themed.
Spaceman.
Oh, I like that.
No.
No, Spaceman.
How much does it cost?
$10.
A space-themed ride in space.
Yeah.
Well, this is a space-themed theme park.
What's that big Pikmin monster?
What is this thing?
All right.
Donuts.
Coffee.
Let's go this way.
Make it $30.
No one's going to buy it if it's $30.
That's a bad idea.
All right.
Let's put something right here.
How about a...
Oh, there's already a couple games.
Let's do stalls.
At-stall, pizza, restrooms.
Here we go.
Right on the side.
I think that's a good idea.
Does it cost money?
Oh, you can't.
All right.
Edit.
No.
All right.
Bathroom.
I'm just generating income from the other place, right?
I need merch.
Pizza, mineral water, balloons.
I think balloons is cool.
Put that right here.
Yeah, I do.
Oh my God.
They're all flocking over here to get balloons.
$50.
They're all freaking out to come over here.
Are they?
What are they doing?
Oh, they're all getting in line.
Okay.
That'll generate some money.
There's a merch link in bio.
Astroville.
All right.
I'm going to pee my pants.
I'll be right back.
See you in two minutes.
I get to use this one more time.
This is the last time you're going to see this BRB screen probably.
Until next Christmas.
Get a good look at it.
It's awesome.
I told you I was going to be quick.
I am back.
We're using the fall theme and not the winter theme.
I like this one a lot.
I like them all.
I just kind of picked one.
Well, you'll hear this again next fall.
There's going to be more music from Blurred Owl, by the way.
At least in the probably four or five tracks.
Coming.
All right.
Let's get back to what we were doing.
What were we doing?
I have no idea.
All right.
Too loud?
Eh, whatever.
All right.
Let me get, let me, let me get nice and comfy here.
I think, do I, I have to fake like friends with somebody.
Hey!
Family!
I require your attention.
Mr.
Brooks.
Oh.
What a little shit.
I challenge you.
Jim Brooks.
I challenge you to a game of Warp Speed.
Good luck.
Wait, why am I riding on his back?
What?
This is weird.
Oh, no, I'm not.
Okay.
What?
This is weird.
How do we play?
What's going on?
This is weird.
I don't even know what we're doing.
I'm just going to copy him.
I think he knows what he's doing.
This is up, hold up.
Okay.
What the fuck is all this?
Good.
All right.
I just took him over.
Geez.
My woe level is pretty high.
All right.
I want to get off.
I want to get off right now.
There's 25 more seconds left.
I don't want to play this anymore.
Where did he go?
Where is he?
Oh, spinning.
I don't like it.
Okay.
I think I just lapped him.
That guy was Toad in Super Mario Kart Bowser level 1.
You pass that motherfucker every time.
And so I'm sorry.
I have to give you a gamer opinion here.
If you are not lapping Toad in the Super Nintendo Bowser's Castle level,
just return the game.
At that point, right?
All right.
Add it to my crowd.
I give Jim a VIP pass.
What does this do?
Whoa.
All right.
So now what?
What do you think about the park?
All right.
How'd you hear about us?
You should try-
No, I want to-
I'm gonna make a coaster that's guaranteed to kill somebody
and I'm gonna tell him he should ride one.
I'm gonna stay.
All right.
I gotta remember what it says.
Jim.
My crowd.
Molly Noodles.
Jim Brooks and Sam Lee.
Sam Lee still has not gone to the bathroom since the very beginning of the game.
Remember this kid?
He was looking for a bathroom and he said he was starving.
That was an hour ago.
Just fucking unfriend this kid.
All right.
Do you even have toilets?
Yeah, in another park.
I think this is the only bathroom.
New mission.
Robo-
Oh wait, I have to do missions.
I completely forgot about missions.
Oh my God.
I- This is why I don't have any money.
All right.
Guest.
Robo Love.
Robots don't understand flirting.
It messes with their logic circuits.
Use matchmaking or matchmake mode on a teen you are friends with
and put some smooth flirtation moves on some of those tinheads.
Wait, what is- what do you want me to do?
Do I even have any friends?
So wait, I'm supposed to introduce two people.
I don't understand.
Become good friends with a teenager and then use matchmake mode to flirt with robots.
I-
That's a very weird sentence to say out loud.
Right?
Okay.
I can't do that one.
Robo Losers.
Nothing fries a robot's circuits faster than losing.
Challenge every robot you see to play a game and then show them the agony of defeat.
All right.
I got to challenge a robot to a game and just- and just- and just- absolutely just wipe the rest.
How about-
Nineteen ninety-six eight.
Okay.
All right.
Warp speed.
I'm not playing that one again.
Robo KO.
We're going to beat you at your own game.
Repeatedly hitting the same part of an opponent's body will cause their armor to fall off.
So it's up, down, left, right.
Punches, hooks, block.
Block is left trigger.
Uppercuts, right trigger.
All right.
Just punch him in the face as hard as I can.
Choose your boxer.
Uh, clink, clunk, or clunk?
Clunk.
I'm definitely a clunk.
Oh shit.
Clunk mirror mash.
This is bad.
What's going on?
I can't even hurt each other.
I got to get an uppercut.
No mercy.
Get that armor off.
What the hell?
He's blocking?
Oh, what?
You're going to play the game?
He's going to block in the corner.
Did I win?
Yeah, that's an exposed.
He's exposed.
Bottom left?
That's what- that's my moves I'm doing.
Whoa, wait.
What?
I have combos.
Will you do something besides just sitting in the corner?
Nice.
Good work.
Throw in the towel?
You talking about- that's what- that's what he should do.
All right.
Well, whatever.
I win.
I'm going to get that- I'm going to get the fame for it.
You're killing this guy.
It's third round.
It doesn't matter.
He's done.
All right.
I- I'm going to knock him out.
Just do- I'm going to do that combo over and over again.
He just never blocks the uppercut, ever.
He just never blocks it once.
You're going to stop.
You've already wiped their ass.
You've already wiped their- whatever.
You already-
I need to get a knockout, right?
I'm just going to tell you guys right now, if I was ever a boxer, every single competition is going to end in a knockout, even if it's me.
I'm never going to block a punch.
I'm just going to go in and just be like-
I'm just going to swing wildly to windmills and shit.
I'm just going to try to hit them in the head as hard as I can.
And even if I get knocked out, I guarantee it'll be a show worth watching.
Like, I'm just going in there with the hands up and I'm just- I'm just swinging at their face as hard as I can.
Over and over again.
And they'll catch me in like a- like a quick little jab to the chin and I'm going down immediately.
But guess what?
If I knock them out- oh, I'll knock them out every time.
And I'll do a bunch of like weird movements and shit, too.
I would be the worst person to box against.
You would never be able to do- know what I was going to do next.
I would do like weird, like, jerk, dancing moves and stuff in the corner.
I'd get booed.
People would throw shit at me in the ring.
I don't- I don't care.
If I knock them out, I'll knock them out every time.
Yeah, that's what I mean.
Like, I'm only going to end fights and knockouts.
There will never be a scenario where it goes to decision.
I'm going to be like 4 and 60.
You know what I mean?
Like, it's- you'll know what's going to happen when I get on stage.
Imagine knowing that.
Imagine knowing that the guy that's in the card next will always end in a knockout.
You just don't know how.
That would probably be bad.
It's always- I wonder how he's going to get knocked out this time.
You'd be the first mini boss of boxing games?
Gabby J.
Yay, yay.
I'm the guy that everybody just starts cheering.
And when you're on your second or third beer to rile the crowd up,
I'm just the clown that comes out and does a bunch of goofy shit and then gets knocked out.
How barbaric.
That's not- that's not fun.
That's barbaric.
Yeah, like kill him.
Kill his ass.
And I like run around the ring.
I'm like, oh, whoopsie.
And then the guy just fucking rocks me and I go down for 10 seconds.
And everyone's just screaming, like spilling their beers all over him and shit.
That- I don't think that's a bad idea for boxing.
I would just be- I would just be like a clown.
Court jester.
I disagree.
I'd watch it if it were like old wrestling.
Don't like pizza?
Come on, man.
What do you mean?
All right, well I won.
I get my trophy, right?
That was a thousand bucks.
Robo losers, awarded.
I gotta do more of the missions.
Too expensive.
What do you- what?
It's- how much is this?
All right, fine.
We'll go on the other strategy and that's make sure it's so cheap that every single person can afford it.
Everybody can buy it.
So eventually I'll make a profit.
You're gonna die in the ring.
That's not how it works.
Okay, if a hundred thousand people buy a balloon for 25 cents,
or if 50,000 people buy a balloon for 50 cents,
what are you talking about?
It's the same.
Put it back to 175, fine.
It's the same amount of money gained.
King of math.
If you sell a hundred thou- okay.
If you sell a hundred thousand balloons for one cent,
or you sell 50,000 balloons for two cents,
you've made the same amount of money.
It's the same amount.
I get a dollar.
What do you have cost per pollu- balloon?
Wait, wait, wait, what's this?
Why do you have a trophy?
Oh, it's molly noodles.
Oh, do you have any hints?
I gotta go.
All right.
Park Island Plus?
We're already doing plus?
I don't want to do that.
I don't want to do this.
Why would I sign myself up for this?
What's the- what do I have?
All right.
What do I have to beat?
Five?
No, no, no, no, no, no.
Just go, go, go, go, go, go, go.
It's got candy.
What?
Hurry up.
Hurry up before the thing comes.
How many- how many Fios do I have to rescue?
Do I just farm the fruits?
I think that's probably- that's probably a good idea.
I think.
Monkey Island.
Oh, yeah.
This game was published by LucasArts, right?
What happens if I win this?
If you sell one balloon, that's one dollar, and you sell it for one dollar, you get zero dollars.
But if it's two, you get one dollar, so that's profit.
But you don't know how much the balloon takes to make.
Why are you assuming that it takes a dollar in cost to make the balloon?
You're assuming that.
We don't have that information.
It could be one cent.
Neither do you.
Will you play Hitman PC for VR?
Whoa, wait, hold on.
Everybody stop moving.
Everybody hold on.
Will you play Hitman VR on PC when it comes out on the 20th?
Is that going to line up perfectly for all the VR shit that I want to do?
Are they actually coming out with that?
I remember it was just a PSVR thing they did.
Remember how angry I was that it was PSVR only?
I'm absolutely going to do that.
Yeah, I mean, you can 100 million percent expect that.
Yeah, so the plan's over the next couple weeks.
I'm going to set up the VR.
I don't know if I'm going to do it immediately.
We'll probably do one more stream where I'm not in VR this weekend.
And then, oh shit.
Oh, I got the...
I was waiting for the fire because I thought I was going to...
Look at how long that takes.
Whatever.
All right.
So what was I saying?
Okay, right.
So I just shit out a bird.
It's so floaty.
You have to give me some slack.
All right.
So we'll probably do something this weekend.
And then after this weekend, I'm going to set the VR, the big giant VR room
again. We'll do VR for a couple weeks.
Then there's going to be something that you probably don't want to miss.
That last week of January, maybe the first week of February, I'll give you a hard
date, but I'll make sure to let you know.
You probably don't want to miss it.
I would probably make sure I was there when I give you that hard date.
It's not baseball.
Baseball is going to be in the spring.
Something else.
But it's going to be very fun.
I think.
I hope.
I think it's going to be very exciting.
But that'll be the last week of January or the please don't drop.
There we go.
It'll be within that few weeks.
January into February.
Don't let this one just sit up here.
And nothing even touched me.
By the time I get this all done.
This girl's not even going to be in the park anymore.
Why am I even doing this?
Oh my goodness.
Fire.
That's a lot.
Doing it for Molly.
I think there's only one more.
Is it like a, no, it's not.
It's not a cat boy stream.
Is it is a large event.
That's all I will tell you.
That's it.
You're not getting anything else out of me.
This is not Thrillville.
Yes, it is.
When do I get to stop?
I don't want to play this anymore.
Molly, please.
I have no more lives left.
Did I win?
Oh, I did it.
It was fun rescuing.
I'm laughing because your challenge was a joke.
No, I want to be friends.
Sparkling plus.
I got it.
All right.
Do anything else you want me to do?
You got a gold thing on you.
What's that?
Wait a second.
Why don't you like me?
Wait.
Hey, I was, I want to talk.
I wasn't, why does she hate me?
All right.
What are the missions we got?
Upkeep.
Mechanical marvels.
Balloon tender.
Italic balloons and interview the robots.
I don't care about robots circuitry.
Build.
Busted.
Build a coaster the longer the better and then break it.
Wait, what?
Globo joy robots are so stupid.
They'll go on any ride they see and I'm trying to hurt them.
I'm trying to kill them.
Make a coaster crash.
I think I have enough money to do it.
Let's do it.
Where's there a coaster one?
Right here.
Park upgrades.
Do more research.
Marketing.
Research.
Earnly a hundred dollars spending.
I could do 300 bucks.
You have to kill them.
I mean, I'm about to.
All right.
Where's this coaster?
I can build a racetrack too.
No coaster coaster.
Let's go build my own.
Ooh, a dinghy.
Yep.
We're doing a dinghy.
All right.
The direction is going to go this way.
What do we got for whoa?
Ooh, wait, this is just supposed to crash.
Why would I waste any money?
Just dump them right here.
Just dump them into right.
Why not just dump them?
Let's go up first.
I need length first.
Oh, okay.
How about we get them out of the game map?
So they actually can never come back.
Right.
Out of bounds.
Oh, that's fine.
Yeah, I want to make sure that they actually can never come back.
This would be out of bounds, right?
That'll throw them far enough where they get out of bounds.
Read the mission.
Wait, wasn't it?
Jack them into the parking lot.
It needs to be hot.
They need to have more fun.
All right.
Let me actually make something.
That's not a straight line up in a straight line down.
That'd be nice.
You need to build a ride with 1400 feet of track that kills them.
Oh, okay.
All right, then let's start here.
Let's have it go back down through it like thread and needle.
That'd be kind of cool.
Okay, now let's add a whoa factor.
I don't want it to be that far.
There we go.
Add the pretzel.
You're gonna get decapitated.
You're gonna be all right.
And then I'm gonna shake the fuck out of them.
And it's supposed to crash, right?
Crash directly into this tree.
How far is it?
Do I have any indicator how far?
Back speed 86 miles per hour.
Length 1500.
All right, this should work.
I think that's good to go.
Let's go.
Stop building.
If you stop building now, your coaster will crash.
Yeah, but that's what I'm supposed to do.
All right.
I try it.
Let's try it.
Actually, this kind of looks like a water slide.
That's at a water park.
Where am I?
Oh, there I am.
Water does not go up like that.
Why am I saying?
I thought it was the same clip again.
Go first person.
All right.
Oh, here we go.
That was kind of cool.
Did we do it again?
Oh, all right.
It's perfect.
I wouldn't ride this though.
I don't, people are riding this?
I thought I made this to kill robots, not kill people.
Before you go on there.
Oh shit.
Can they even make it back over here?
I don't think they can make it back.
Why is this crashing every five seconds?
There's too many people on this.
Okay, but what is, what happens if I hurt too many people?
You're nothing.
All right.
So am I, is this, am I doing this right?
Build.
Busted.
Oh, I got it.
Okay.
What's this one?
Stick it to those rascally robots by building an incredible mini golf course that will foil the robots and logic circuits.
Wait a minute.
What?
I can build my own mini golf course?
Excuse me.
Uh, excuse me.
Really?
Let's put it right here.
I'm gonna put a hamburger stall right next to it.
What?
I can do my own mini golf course?
Oh my goodness.
Okay.
No way.
All right, that's hole one.
This is hole two.
Okay.
All right, now hole three.
Can you get a hole in one in this?
I don't think so.
Stop, stop, stop.
What?
I'm, come on.
I'm having fun.
People are gonna get stuck on this forever.
No way.
It's gonna take three hours to do this.
I don't want to play this.
Should I try it?
Wait, I gotta do a paint, paint job on it.
Oh, I kind of like blue.
No, it's ugly.
Um, I don't want the red though.
I want, I don't like it.
Oh, here we go.
They're actually gonna play.
I'm very curious.
Get out of the way camera.
Stop it.
I want to see.
Let's see how they do.
Hole in one.
Nice.
On to the second hole.
This one's a little trickier.
Cause you have to go forward with it.
Yeah, nice work.
Pretty good form.
On to the next hole.
What about, uh, what about Ted here?
Ooh, did you get it?
Nice.
Very nice.
Good luck.
Realizing what you've done.
Realizing you may, maybe shouldn't have played.
Good.
Where'd you get it to?
Right there.
That's one shot.
Nice.
This is gonna be quite a bottleneck.
This queue.
One person an hour can play this.
It's gonna be like a 20 stroke course.
All right, everybody out of the way.
It's my place.
I want to play.
All right.
I got a bet for you.
Can I complete my own mini golf course in less than 20 strokes?
20 strokes or less.
Here we go.
You want to bet?
Like, no, no, no, no.
Way more than that.
30 strokes or less.
I'll do the whole thing.
Predictions.
Let's do it.
I think I can do it.
I don't think you guys understand my strategy that I'm going to employ here.
You don't know the strategy.
Go ahead.
Bet against me.
Do it.
Can I do this whole course in 30 strokes or less?
You said 20.
Yeah.
Then I corrected it before the poll went up.
30 or less.
Good luck.
I hope you vote correctly because I am going to show you something very special.
Another few seconds.
Or you'll give 5,000 subs.
That's not going to happen.
So no.
Let them all vote.
30 strokes or less.
Here we go.
That's one.
Really?
Two.
That's so easy.
Oh my God.
Don't.
All right.
Two.
Three.
All right.
We're good.
Here we go.
Just a straight shot.
Oh, please.
Was that three?
Four.
Five.
Six.
And seven.
Here comes seven.
Motherfuckers.
You didn't think I was going to skip the whole goddamn course?
Yes.
You all lose.
Never bet against me again.
Okay, do it.
All right.
I got 11 under par.
That's game over.
Congratulations to those who would actually understood what I was doing there.
I did that in less shots that I took to the first hole.
I didn't.
All I told you was I was going to complete this in under 30 strokes.
I didn't tell you how I was going to do that.
I just got 85,000 points.
Oh goodness.
All right.
So now what do I want to do?
How much money do I have?
Only 3,200 bucks.
How?
My wife is going to kill me.
Escape drop coaster?
All right.
We have to have a really crazy escape drop.
So let me understand what's going on here.
We're trying to get rid of the robots and to get rid of the robots.
We have to make rides that are incredibly dangerous.
So they leave.
But in the process we're going to kill thousands of actual just park goers.
Okay.
Do you like hockey?
Do that again or scared?
No, I don't have to do it again.
I already did what I was going to do.
A crush lizard and ratchet bandicoot.
Thanks for the 20 community subs each.
Thanks a lot.
Appreciate it.
That's a lot of money.
Thank you.
All right.
I can't be friends with these people.
I don't think they like me.
These robots don't.
I can't make my friend me to go up.
Wait, I want to jump on the trampoline.
Oh wait backwards left right jump trick one two.
Ooh.
All right.
This is kind of scary.
Does anybody else feel like the trampoline is like kind of just bad for your organs or something?
I feel like your stomach is going down to where your groin is.
Oh, that was on the head.
He's all right.
Is that eight?
Wait, did you say 18th century way of thinking or something?
What do you mean?
Like because I don't know how organs work.
Do that again.
I want to do it again.
Oh, you're gonna put olives on all your fingers for 10 million off the debt.
That's the weirdest comment I've read all day.
I don't have olives.
Why are you assuming that I have a jar of olives in my house?
Olives?
That was fine.
I don't have olives in.
I don't have olives in my fridge.
All right, last try.
Oh, go buy olives.
Okay, the next stream you see.
I will put olives on my fingers and go into the camera and go like
with all my fingers with olives on them.
Okay, is that what you want to see is I'll do it.
He landed on his feet.
I landed on my feet.
It was always if you ever were on a trampoline.
It was always really embarrassing because I was always the guy.
I could do the backflip on a trampoline, right?
It was like no way man.
You could do backflip.
Whoa, no, it's awesome.
If you ever screwed it up, if you ever like landed like on your
butt, it was like a huge embarrassment.
It's like you're supposed to be the guy that can do that.
You're supposed to be the person that can do that and you didn't.
Everyone just kind of like, oh, nice try.
I guess like no, no, I promise I can do it.
I promise.
What a dangerous thing to have.
The trampoline is incredibly dangerous.
I need to clean this place up.
I almost have a level up though.
This is cool.
All right.
Guest robo losers.
Frederick Moe Potts is saying he's going to write another bad review
of Thrillville now that robots are running amok in the park.
Why don't you see about giving him a gift preferably something
he likes that will keep his mind off of writing.
All right.
What do you look?
What do you like?
It's review time, you know, huh?
How's it your fair and honest, you know, I'd be even more fair
if you help me out with present.
You want a present?
Okay.
A bribe it is Moe.
Bribe is such an ugly, unsophisticated word.
Is this Bart Simpson?
As if you're doing me a favor and then I return said favor.
You know, Knowledge TV has a lot of beauties.
How many?
Pop a walk creep.
You get bup kiss or maybe there is something I can do for you.
I'm glad we can agree to agree.
So what present do you want?
A nice sideshow prize would be great.
Sideshow prize.
I can get home and show it to the family.
Wouldn't pretend like you got it.
You want you want you want to have the prize where you can prove
to people that you got at least 60 or 70 on the test of strength
because you can't do it on your own.
You can tell people that you did because they know that's where
the prize came from.
I understand.
I get it.
Get it.
Okay.
You want a prize?
This place is awesome.
Well, I want to play the basketball game.
Oh, that's Robo K.
Oh, I want to play the basketball.
Then no basketball.
How do I play that?
That looks like fun.
How come I can't do that?
It's just a decoration.
Oh, what was I doing?
There's money just over here.
What is this?
This is another decoration.
This place is crazy.
Oh, I need to build.
I okay.
I have to build the drop coaster.
Yeah.
Okay.
I got to find a place to build a coaster and it has to be horrible.
Like terrifying scary and hurt people.
Is there a place for a coaster here?
Now we're going to go back keep haven't done any of these.
If you got about the bribe.
Oh, right, right, right, right.
How do I get a prize?
How do I even get a prize?
All the games I played haven't had any prizes.
Am I left?
Oh, right here.
All right.
Here we go.
So it needs to be one of these drop rides.
Line coaster.
What was it called?
I'm going to sneeze.
I can't hear.
I couldn't mute fast enough.
I'm sorry.
I really did try.
Another 25 subs from Addie.
Thank you Addie.
Actually more than that like 35.
You guys are giving a lot of money today.
Unnecessary.
Don't do this.
You don't have to give me any money.
Thank you.
We're racetracks.
Isn't this thing a dropper?
Oh, here is escape drop.
All right.
Let's go.
This is just one of those like tower terrors.
I'm going to have it go this way because there's more room over here.
All right.
So this is it's it goes up.
And then I'm going to put at the very beginning.
I let's go another let's do loop, loop, loop, loop, loop.
I think loop at the beginning.
Then go through the fire.
I need five drops.
I don't have enough real estate to do that.
I barely have enough room for one.
So I have to do just do this five times.
I don't want to spin it.
It counts as a drop, right?
I come back this way.
This variety is being named big Chungus.
I don't think it has to be named that but I'll consider that name.
Hey, there's one two.
This is this is crazy.
This is not a bad one.
This is pretty cool.
The stats on it 82 thrill.
I got to make it really really horrible, right?
Let's get it back up then.
Oh my goodness.
What am I thinking?
Hold on.
Wait, can I I can just go straight down?
That that would be awful.
Too much too much.
Too close.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no.
Oh, it's a corkscrew.
Oh, that would be cool.
And come on really.
All right, just help me finish it real 100 nausea 79.
This thing is awful.
Check it out.
This is going slow.
I'm just hanging people upside down.
This is not going fast.
Is it okay?
Was that just to get you ready?
Why is it going so slow?
This sucks.
It just puts a bunch of a blood to your brain.
Why is this a hundred thrill?
Is it going to actually move now?
Guys, this is going straight down.
It's not on slow mode.
There's no such thing as slow mode.
The whole thing is just a powered track.
The whole thing is it is chain.
Where's the drop?
Okay.
So this ride we just hang people up.
All right, whatever.
They're not going to want to ride it.
Okay.
End the ride, please.
They're lining up ready to go.
They want to ride it.
All right.
Well, oh, what did I do wrong there?
I did everything wrong.
Somebody has a big plan to stop Thrillville.
New minigame in party play.
Sparkle Island Classic.
Do you wish to view your new trophy?
No.
Good luck everybody on this ride.
I hope you like it.
I think all the robots are coming here.
All right.
I definitely got that mission for sure.
That skill rating is not high enough.
All right.
There we go.
I ain't got a games.
Some coaster types are slower than others.
Yeah, not that's going as fast as traffic goes on a highway.
It's like five miles per hour.
All right.
I need to I got to get this guy present.
So I bribe him.
I got a hundred dollars for doing that.
It's not worth doing that.
All right.
I got to find a prize.
Do I have anything in my inventory?
Aranoid Android.
Manage.
Teen dream.
All right.
I've got 75 teenagers here.
I need to get rid of robots still.
All right.
Buy up.
I got to get a balloon or something.
Is there a balloon stall somewhere?
Okay.
I got to go this way.
Let's go to Oceanville.
Where are my friends?
VIP pass.
Tim Twinklefingers.
I don't even know who this is.
Remember Molly noodles?
Mo Pots.
All right.
Should I give him a pass or something?
Let's teleport to to Mo Pots.
All right.
Can I give him something?
You get prizes from minigames not vendors.
Yeah.
All right.
I got to go get a prize then.
Go watch Bionicle with him.
This is cool.
I need two more Lindsay's notes.
What is that?
What do I get with that?
I got to get some more attractions and some more money.
I need to get a I need to get some something here.
Pizza.
I need to make money.
Ooh, let's go.
Pizza and hats.
I need a sideshow game.
Put one right here.
One more Lindsay's notes and I'll get Lindsay's notebook.
All right.
Where's test of strength?
Is it a stall?
Is it a game?
Okay.
Running cost.
Ticket price.
Mini golf.
I don't see any of those Midway games anywhere.
Oh sideshow.
Okay, alley ball.
Coconut shy.
All right.
Let's do alley ball.
It's not a bad spot for it.
If anyone price judge the strength of your throw carefully.
All right.
Oh, it's ski ball.
What?
What the fuck?
Why are I at full power?
Take it down.
How do I take off full power?
How do I take power down?
Buttons?
I'm at I'm at max power.
I don't know how to put it down.
That one doesn't work.
A B what nothing works.
I don't want to be on max power.
The trigger buttons.
It's not the trigger button.
Nothing works.
Full power.
I don't get it.
Right click.
Why did that go down?
I don't understand this at all.
I don't get it.
We just have to work with it.
You're flicking too hard.
It's a okay.
It's about the speed of going forward.
Good luck trying to get that to work right.
I have to flick softer.
There is only one speed on flick.
It's flick.
There is not slow flick.
It's just flick.
It's forward.
How much do I need for the prize?
Oh, come on.
Do it again.
Pull back then push forward to throw.
Come on.
Oh my god.
It's impossible to do this.
Because you have to go you have to aim in different other directions.
I can't even throw it another direction.
I'm trying to go to the right.
This is impossible, man.
I'm leaning so far in.
Get in there!
Get in!
Full clear.
There it is.
I'm starting to understand this stupid minigame.
It's still dumb.
Please.
You can't go to the right or left.
You can't do it.
This is not possible.
I'm trying to do it so slowly.
I just did that so slow.
There's not much slower I can go.
This is all based on the dead zone of the controller you're using.
All right.
I got the prize.
Let's go.
High score.
Did I get a prize?
Nice.
Table tennis bat.
Where is he?
Where are you?
Oh, my crowd.
All right, dude.
Let's go.
Give me a good review.
It's review time.
All right.
I'm positive you're going to give a good review.
You know, I'd be even more fair if you helped me out.
You got it.
I'll be like table tennis.
Or give you a VIP pass.
Here, has a bat.
Is this a good enough?
That's excellent.
I think Thrillville just got the hottest park rating on my show.
Hell yeah.
They're still playing this.
All these, this is really scary looking.
All these robots are waiting for this kid to be done.
Is that the couple that first was here at the very beginning?
They're all waiting for these little kids.
Absolute hell.
You guys enjoying the park?
I own this place.
I'm the park manager.
Oh, the tone really changed quickly now, didn't it?
All right.
Here, you want a VIP pass?
Now we're best friends.
So now, I am going to ask you a bunch of questions.
I want them answered immediately.
It's stupid that they call the playoffs the World Series.
All the teams are in the United States and Canada.
It's true.
All right.
How about trivia?
Wait.
How do you think the park could be improved?
All right as is, I guess.
No, that's not good enough.
That's not good enough.
What do you think about the park?
You can't just say, oh, it's all right.
You got to tell me what you think.
I really like it here.
All right.
These are, what about your kids?
How are your kids doing?
Bradley Adams, Sarah Adams, Emily Adams, all the, the Adams family.
All right.
How's Sarah Adams?
Good.
I challenge you to a duel.
All right.
Mini golf on my course.
Can I do it on my course?
Or is it going to be, I don't know.
Is it my course?
I don't think it's my course.
It is.
Good luck.
I want to see how many strokes she has.
All right.
Hole in one.
Okay.
She got four strokes on hole two.
Not bad so far.
I'm going to probably laugh pretty hard if it's over a hundred.
It's going to be probably like 60.
Dude, please.
I'm of the opinion that all right, this should be a, this should be a circle.
Two or three inches around this hole.
That if you just get it in that circle around the hole, then it counts.
Does it matter?
It should be, this should be a small like target around the circle.
And if it leans onto the lip, it should count.
I don't care.
Call it like, it's like golf with the bumpers, like bowling.
I would rather play it like that.
All right.
She had 19 strokes.
It's a par 19.
She had, she got 19 strokes.
I'll get it.
Uh-oh.
I got to find the right spot.
That's good enough.
Too hard.
Stroke 11.
I'm okay.
I win.
You see what I'm saying?
It's just, just have a thing here with a bumpers on it.
I win.
You're welcome.
One more game.
We're going to do escape drop.
No, I don't want to do it.
I hate this one.
Back out.
I, I quite a forfeit.
She's happy.
She's having a good time.
She's very hungry though.
Warp speed.
No, what?
I don't want to do this one either.
Forfeit.
What do you think?
What do you think about the park?
A kid will give you a real opinion.
Okay.
Good.
Have a nice day.
All right.
I need to figure this out too.
So I need to like do matchmaking.
That's like part of the game.
Hello.
Good to see you again.
Why does she hate me?
Hello.
Hey, this park is even better than the last one.
Why won't she?
Wait, I can't, I can't talk to her.
I need to do, it said matchmake with a robot, right?
Okay.
So how do I do that?
It was just to complete a challenge.
How are you guys doing?
All right.
Jake Lopez.
How's it going?
What's up?
How are you doing, Jake?
I can't tell you how cool, oh wait, I just did.
All right.
Thanks.
That's good to know.
Matchmake.
How about, what do you think about the alley ball?
You can get some cool prizes.
The classic sideshow game brought the-
I already played it at a different park.
I'll try it again if I have time.
What park?
Who stole my idea?
Somebody took it?
Well, you must have very strong thumbs from dominated arcade games.
Yeah, I try, you know.
All right.
I don't think this, I don't think this kid's going to be into
a fishing tournament.
How about Trivia?
It's easier to make new ones.
In fact, a recycled can takes 90% less energy to make than a new one.
Wow.
Hot body?
This is young Sheldon.
I need to eat more spinach.
Okay.
I really like drinks in glass containers.
A human body gives off a hundred calories of heat each hour.
That's the same as a hundred-
Running that park was very difficult for me.
My friends would always come to the park and give me criticism.
I did know plenty of information.
We're best friends now.
All right.
What?
It's me.
I don't know who that is.
Hey, did you-
Hockey man, did you do-
Did you know this?
Did you know this man?
Hey, did you know all this info?
Oh, how am I supposed to do this?
What would a robot like?
You're like cotton candy, so sweet.
Friends first?
I can't make any-
How does this even work?
Oh, this is a person.
Space wave trip video is so freaky.
I love it.
It's one of my favorite bands and definitely one of my favorite-
Favorite band?
I'm gonna run in a marathon.
Good luck.
That's one of the toughest athletic events ever.
Okay.
How about that football game last night?
It was an awesome display of skill.
It was a great game.
And I was cheering all the way through.
All right.
How about piranhas?
Should I give facts?
How about a new puppy?
This is an AI-generated conversation.
Yeah, it is.
Because it's two AIs talking to each other.
Created in a video game with pre-scripted dialogue.
So you're absolutely correct.
They're all robots.
Okay.
What about penguins?
I didn't like that.
What about hamsters?
I got two hamsters as a birthday present and now there are 27 of them.
What?
A hamster once peed on my head.
How?
Monkeys have to be one of the smartest animals on the planet.
Put a hat on you and you'd be a dead ringer for a monkey.
Oh, okay.
Ow.
Ouch.
Have a great day at the park.
Ooh.
That was pain-
I felt that one.
That was painful.
Hello.
Is this person here with a family?
It's gonna be rage inside the steel cage when wrestling comes to the local coliseum.
I like to see the women wrestlers.
They're really something.
I guess it's looking over here.
All right.
Do you like penguins?
I'd love to see penguins at the zoo.
I wish I could pet a penguin.
All right.
Okay.
You like penguins.
Very cool.
What about piranhas?
Nah, too, too much.
Barbecue.
Everybody loves a good barbecue.
I went to one last week.
There's something so great about eating something hot and fresh off the grill.
Okay.
What about spicy food?
You can't go wrong with spicy foods.
Spicy food, chicken wings, jambalaya.
What is he saying?
He's just trying to talk to me.
Did you get the game last night?
Okay.
I got an old cat.
You like rhinos?
This is going to go to animals.
All right.
What about seafood?
Okay.
All right, all right, all right, all right.
We like food.
We get it.
So how do we...
How do I...
I just made friends.
I did...
Okay.
I did that wrong.
That was...
I...
It's got to...
All right.
It's...
How about...
Um...
I need...
That was an adult.
Oh.
Are you going to call me a monkey?
Okay.
What about pets?
You like hamburgers?
Nope.
Wait, it's a robot.
I could do...
Oh.
I just want this stupid trophy.
Oh, I remember you.
Addy just gave 50 community subs.
Oh my God.
That's too much.
That's insane.
Thank you.
Too much.
Way too much.
Okay.
Well, do you like hamsters?
Oh, did one pee on your head one time?
This is my favorite subject, and I really like going to English class.
I hate doing lessons on grammar and punctuation.
Okay.
What about...
I got tickets.
I'm taking my friend to the Hickchick's concert next week.
I saw them live last week.
All right.
Do you know any languages?
I don't think I can learn a foreign language in school.
My Spanish is terrible.
I don't think of a language.
Okay.
Do you like spicy food?
I don't think I can get along with spicy foods.
I have to drink a ton of water to put out the...
Well, that's your problem.
What you should be doing is have a glass of milk and don't swallow the milk.
You swish it around your mouth and spit it out.
Milk will...
With the enzymes in milk will help break down
the spiciness of the food.
But if you swallow it, then you don't want to swallow it because it goes down.
Milk ruins the fun.
Are you...
I'm telling you that...
I think I learned that from Alton Brown.
Who is way smarter than you when it comes to food.
Everyone likes Alton Brown?
Yeah.
I've seen all of his shows.
I can...
How am I gonna...
All right.
We're almost friends.
I guess.
Who doesn't like Alton Brown?
I know.
Oh my goodness.
I'm about to leave.
It's just random.
We'll get it eventually.
I know.
Okay.
Hey, we go to the same school.
We should hang out.
You don't even have a fishing pole and I'm hooked.
Oh my god, fucking delete that from your vocabulary.
Forever.
Whenever somebody yells,
Freebird, our band, plays that song.
Okay.
Normally, I wouldn't go out with someone cuter than myself.
Fucking get rid of that.
Delete that from your vocabulary.
I'm in a band.
We're called the Bloody Snowmen.
Delete that.
It's all bad.
I love to dunk the basketball when I'm playing for my school team.
That's a stupid annoying flex.
We go to the same school.
We should hang out.
I mean, we go to the same school.
These are all terrible.
Hey, we go to the same school.
We should hang out sometime.
You know my boyfriend is just over there, right?
What?
I know I have a talking parakeet.
Why would I pivot to prison food?
Well, I just want the trophy to the mission.
All right, Mark.
I don't know who to say.
I just want to complete the mission, which is have a teenager.
Go have a romance with a teenager or something, right?
I just looking for the mission completion.
Mark.
Okay.
Hi, Anna.
How are you?
It's really good to see you.
Not going well.
She hates everything.
I'm saying everything.
Oh God.
Great.
Animals.
Okay.
Cats.
They did.
Elephants.
Wow.
Don't talk about.
Okay.
Now what?
Yeah.
Good.
Okay.
What about rhinos?
I don't.
We I don't know.
I feel like it's kind of a weird pivot to go from like, oh, I love animals.
I love animals.
Grill up those fucking turkeys and smother them in oil.
I feel like this is kind of weird.
It's a weird conversation.
We that's all we've talked about.
All right.
Do you like lemonade?
Oh, okay.
That's lame.
What's your favorite subject in school?
Oh my God.
Where are the animals?
All you want to talk about is barbecuing and then cute animals.
Oh my God.
Just fine.
Oh dear.
Yes, I know.
Absolutely.
We got a crazy teacher.
What?
What the fuck?
Where are the animals?
God.
These people want probably want to leave so bad.
We are ruining this hangout session that they're having.
I don't think any she doesn't want to talk about sports.
She doesn't want to talk about school.
So how am I what am I supposed to do about this?
Oh, okay.
No, I'm running out of options.
I'm running out of things to talk about.
What the fuck?
I have no other conversation pieces.
We've done every single option.
No.
Isabella?
How are you?
Do you like dessert?
All right.
You like dessert.
You like foods.
Yeah.
All right.
What's your favorite pizza?
I actually love thin crust pizza.
I mean, come on.
It's the best.
It's best way to eat pizza.
I don't like the doughy thick doughy shit.
Get it out of here.
I don't like that.
No.
I don't want a lasagna.
I want a piece of pizza.
I like fast food too.
No healthy diet.
All right.
What do you like?
You like movies.
I hate them too.
What's your favorite steak?
I thought I saw salty parrot and I was like, we're not talking about eating parrots, right?
Why does it say that?
I don't want to talk about that.
I was like, why does it say salty?
Okay, we're out.
Come on.
Barbecue.
Okay.
I find that pizza.
We know that she likes pizza.
She likes food.
We're both in.
We both like food.
I think that we should have some pizza.
I think pizza is perfect.
Okay.
They're having a big chili festival next week.
Would you like to go?
Okay.
I am also pretty good.
I mean, I like, I like bread.
Who doesn't like bread?
Okay.
Really concerned about the plight of the greater prairie chicken.
You have a really great sense of humor.
You know that?
Bonzo-palooza?
You got a great, I think you got a pretty good sense of humor.
All right.
Yeah.
What about, you should see me run the mile.
No.
We should go see a movie.
I don't know.
I don't think I know yet.
I love to read.
We just, I mean, this is seriously,
we seem to agree on everything.
I need CPR.
No.
None of these dumb one-liners.
Stupid.
I write my own songs and I was thinking I should write one about you.
Don't do that.
No.
No, thank you.
Don't do that.
Do you think we'll ever see the return of polka music?
That's fun.
Lert mini game.
Huh?
What am I trying to do?
Money?
I have to hit the bag of money?
Oh, that's very long travel time.
All right.
I got the bag of money.
I need a heart.
Another one of those.
A lip.
All right.
I need another right here.
Shit.
Money, money, money, money, money, money, money.
No.
Money.
This is so hard.
It's going so fast.
I can't even see what I'm shooting at.
Don't move.
Dude, what?
Headphones.
How'd it go?
I think it went pretty well.
All right.
Money.
No, not telephone.
Another bag of money.
Another lip.
And headphones.
They change on you.
It's horse shit.
Money again.
All right.
We're sweethearts.
We're at max attraction.
All right.
It sounds like we're raisins.
I am involved in a lot of after-school activities.
What does a raisin mean?
All right.
Wait, what?
Did I complete the game yet?
Did I complete the minigame?
She's really thirsty and really hungry.
Does this win?
I think our lips were made to be together.
Okay.
Let me cook dinner for you.
The great pasta dish.
I am telling you right now.
I don't know.
They're like, I don't know, 14 or 15 or 16 or something.
I don't know, but you don't make great pasta.
No, like 16 year old makes great pasta.
No, like 17 or 18 year old.
Nobody makes great pasta when they're like fucking 15.
Okay.
So am I done?
Yeah, like what I was, what I should have said is
and my mom makes a really good pasta.
It has to be a robot.
It does have to be a robot.
Oh my God.
I don't think I can, how do you even do that?
How do I flirt with a robot?
This is weird by itself, by the way.
What about your world famous pasta though, man?
Oh yeah, world famous pasta.
I don't, I can't do any of this.
They don't care about anything.
Is there one that is supposed, is the one that just works?
Great humor, brum.
I would think the alien invasion one would be, right?
Prison food.
It has to be an adult woman.
No, it's not.
What are you talking about, man?
What are you talking about?
I was gonna, I don't, I need to look at this.
I need to look this up.
Robo losers.
Robo love.
Oh, I just have to do it three times.
I thought I had to have a robot like,
girlfriend or boyfriend or something.
I thought I had to actually like go out with a robot.
Okay.
Well, I got 7,900 bucks.
It's time to make some coasters.
I got some new rides to do.
Let's put one right here.
A lot of people are hungry.
So it's time to get more pizza.
How many people at the park are hungry?
Pizza, donuts.
Okay.
And maybe some water.
Oh, yeah, people are thirsty too.
Okay.
Those, they can stay at the default prices.
It's fine.
Alright, mission.
So we got games, questing 101.
I don't want to do that.
Do some crazy stunts.
Tim Twinklefingers claims he's the best alleyball bowler in Thrillville.
Oh, let's go show him up right now.
Going on Twinklefingers.
It's the weirdest way to introduce yourself, but that's fine.
Ooh, good one.
Embarrassed.
All right.
Let's kick his ass.
It's this thing.
I'm going to lose.
You should go smoke a bowl.
God, it's so hard.
I feel like the mouse is probably better, but I can't, by the way,
if you're going to buy this game and you have more than one monitor,
don't buy it.
Unless you have a controller, you cannot play this game with your
mouse, if you have two monitors, your mouse is still being captured
by your desktop, no matter what you do.
So when you, it'll, if you, you'll move the mouse around in the game
and you'll see it on your other monitors.
And if you click, it'll exit the window.
There are fixes for that.
How did that miss?
Just turn the other monitors off.
Yeah, but that's a pain in the ass.
This game was on PS2.
I'm going to play it the way it was meant to be played.
Get in there.
All right.
That's a full clear.
Again.
Come on.
Get up there.
Full clear.
Come on.
Nice.
Sorry.
It's always those ones are so hard.
I'm not going to be able to hit any either one of these.
Come on.
Get in there.
Did I win?
I beat him.
It was so easy.
Oh, your time will come.
You can be sure of that.
Oh, I got a rubber chicken.
Nice.
Oh, it's Moe.
Okay.
Thanks for the review.
Were you waving me down?
What's up?
Why would you wave me down?
I got $8,000.
Crash.
Oh, okay.
Hold on.
Up.
Oh, I haven't done any upkeep.
Lindsay's notes.
Lindsay knows has left her valuable notes on hotdog physics all around Thrillville.
Find those notes and Lindsay will be so grateful.
She'll gladly help you with your robot problem.
All right.
I need one more.
Just get those robots to buy lots and lots of balloons.
Oh, I don't want to do that.
Build the robot.
Okay.
Train a mechanic.
All right.
Mechanic train.
I don't even have a mechanic.
I don't have a mechanic.
There's only one person.
All right.
Train.
Build its reliability.
Maintain the ride.
The circuit pieces are not already placed in the order in which they have to be positioned.
I don't have any staff.
Oh my God.
This is going to be horrible.
What?
Okay.
Who's did it?
Holy shit.
Oh, it gets weirder.
It gets weird.
No, no, no.
Go back.
How do I delete?
Oh, I can't.
Is this, am I doing that?
I don't get it.
Wait, what?
I go back.
Hey!
All right.
They trained.
79 training.
That's good.
I need some more staff, right?
Okay.
I have a mechanic.
I need a groundskeeper.
Wait.
You're already a mechanic.
All right.
Train.
What are they wearing?
They're wearing, what are those things they're wearing on their heads?
What is that?
I feel like that's kind of, they're wearing like, like plastic bags on their heads.
Where's the oxygen?
What are those things?
What, there's like no oxygen in there.
Let me complete this.
Good, good, good, good, good.
It's from the underwater section.
Oh, okay.
That makes sense.
Trained up.
Very good.
All right.
Now we need an entertainer.
You're good.
Staff.
Entertainer.
Ethan.
These are Abigail.
I have to do this.
I know that we're going to get DMCA song, but whatever.
Oh my goodness.
This reminds me of every single live-action Disney Joe's intro.
Somebody always gets like a pie in the face.
There's always like a pie that goes in somebody's face.
Even if it's not in any episode.
Hair tied up and braids.
That was one of the worst things I've ever done.
I don't care if I'm doing bad.
It's fine.
Don't worry.
It's okay.
Hold it.
Release.
All right.
That's definitely going to be some good training.
I actually have staff members now.
That's fine.
All right.
So now we can get out of this.
I got 10 grand.
There it is.
Danger.
So how do we take care of the robots?
That just burped really loud.
Speed pool.
Okay.
I'm thinking giant.
I want to build another coaster.
What do you guys think?
I think I want to do giant.
Thrill build giant.
Is the game too quiet?
I turned it up.
The music was too loud.
I turned, I went in the game engine and turned it down.
So we're good.
Is this an actual person or is that an animatronic?
That would be a really scary animatronic.
It would be so horrifying and unsettling.
I would hate that.
All right.
Let's get a coaster built here.
Only 2000 bucks.
Give me a break.
I can afford it.
Andy drop.
Wagon.
Wild mouse coaster.
Oh, we have to make this crazy.
Yep.
I'm going to make this all over the place.
Let's take it this way first.
Oh my God.
I want it to go up.
At what miles per hour do the insides of a human liquidate?
It's got to be more than like five, six, seven hundred, right?
Still too high.
An airplane goes, it's a pressurized cabin, but that goes like four, three hundred miles per hour, four hundred miles per hour.
Oh, I'm out of bounds.
Okay.
Depends on acceleration.
Now let's have them go through like ten of those walls.
Right here.
Vertical overhang.
Whoa.
Oh, I need my, okay, increase my loan.
Okay.
I'll take a loan.
What do I want this to end?
This thing's crazy.
I'm going to make this crazy.
Maybe this would be a little tighter.
You think people are going to fly off this?
Okay, that should be fine.
Slicer, dicer.
Too many pieces?
What do you mean, I have too many pieces?
Oh, shit.
Where's the end over here?
I'm running out of money.
What are you talking about?
It's right there.
100 nausea.
All right, let's take a look.
Let's get on it.
Wait, it's backwards?
Why is it backwards?
Oh, wait a minute.
It's one of these.
Oh, I thought, okay.
So this thing can spin freely.
This is going to be awful.
Oh, my God.
That's too much.
First person?
All right, first person.
Launch the carts into the guy's mouth.
The fact that you're going like more than 150 miles per hour
and the thing is turning.
No wonder it's nausea 100.
This is awful.
What does Max spin?
Oh, see you later.
Oh, the poor kids.
Don't you have to be tall enough to ride this shit?
They were not tall enough.
Oh, I don't think I'm tall enough to ride that ride.
Oh, they want a bathroom.
I got it.
I got you right here.
Cheeseburger stall.
Oh, I want a cheeseburger so bad.
Build an arcade.
Auto sprint.
Bumper cars.
Ghoul gunner.
Ghoul.
RC wars.
Hauntings.
Splatamo.
Stunt rider.
Tank frenzy.
Trampolines.
Auto sprint?
This costs $1.
Oh, it's already built.
Okay.
I need money.
I think that just exploded.
What's Lawnville?
The ghoul game is fun.
All right.
Let me get a bathroom.
Too many people complaining about no bathroom.
That's very much high priority.
All right.
Now I need a game.
What did you say you said?
Haunting is fun?
Shoot zone.
Haunting.
Let's sit back a little bit.
It's all right.
How does this work?
Shoot zone.
Use the correct weapon for the situation you're in.
Jump, reload, duck, shoot.
Is this an FPS?
This is an FPS.
Oh, this is fun.
Got it.
Reload, reload, reload, reload, reload, reload, reload, reload.
This kind of reminds me of one of those games you would download
and have a virus baked into it.
I mean, the game still existed, but it was a virus.
Reload.
Oh, he's shocking.
His name is shocking.
I gotta get skulls.
Is there a sprint? That's crouch. Where are they? There they are. All right, get in. This one is pretty fun
I actually like this one. This would be awesome. This is the kind of game that somebody plays in the background of a movie. It is
Yeah, this is the game that's on the TV in the TV show
That's good. I like to do a weld
Let's go up here. There has to be right? No skull? Get out of here. What are you talking about?
Um
What this one there?
One more it's gonna kind of sucks die already. What is what is going on here?
Where's the skull? It's only one more. This looks like a VR
Anybody see there it is. All right, go go go go go
Finally, he's playing destiny to this thing to PvP. Yeah, I didn't even jump he floated that was dumb
What I gotta go higher, right? Yeah, of course get me out. Oh
My god thing. No, don't fall. We're fine. All right, I did it. That's not it
Do I have to I gotta kill all the ghouls? Yeah, that's what it is
All right. I got two minutes to do this. I got it. I got it. I got it. I got it
I got it. This is the best gun running out of time
I'm gonna get a huge big double cheeseburger or something. Oh, yeah, not right now. It wings instead. Um, I don't know
I'm not like I'm into wings right now
Like one more spawn and that's it make sure you get olives I will I guarantee I promise that I will do the olives on
my fingers thing
That's fun. I'll do that this weekend in Dito chinchilla best minigame. I'll get it right now
I think they have to that's in the other park though. All right, I'm going back. Let me check on the other part
All right, people are starving and thirsty and need to go to the bathroom
I thought there were nine people in the whole park. I want to go to
What's Lonville what's wrong with this lady? What's wrong? What's this lady doing? Hi, what's wrong? Hi there
I don't like the scary ride so much. Are there any less intense rides here? Yeah, may I suggest the
mouse
The mouse ride. Oh, sorry. I'll handle it. I dig that fun here. I want you to have this. Oh, thank you
What happened to this kid do stunt rider? Whoa
We are little
Where we are little I told you we were little I told you we were small. I didn't think it was real
I didn't think we really were tiny one-inch tall people. I thought that was just a little thing in the beginning. Oh
I told you we were little
Pardon. All right, you want you want little boring rides. I'll give you a little boring ride here
Something where is it? Here you go a little fucking teacup ride there
No, this is not this sucks. I don't want to ride this one
However long this ride is it's two minutes too much longer than it should be. Oh
It's awful. I thought this is a gentle ride. I don't think I even have gentle rides
Was that nausea 30 I would puke immediately are getting off that ride. Look, here you go this thing here
No space for it. Oh, well, I need to go back to the other park
Cassaville we'll go this way press a to scream next time, please. I keep telling you about it. There's a scream
I don't like this. Wait press a to scream. I don't want to play pool, baby
Now we got to go back to the original place with this candy bill. It's a lot of parks
This is the one that I have that's most developed. All right, everyone was gentle gentle job. I want to be gentle
You want gentle fine here. Here's a gentle ride. There you go. There it is. Nice and gentle
Mom that one was so fun. That was so crazy free money. It's still too loud. I
Got some more. Hey, I got some gentle rides. All right. What's that game that you guys all want me to play?
What is it called?
Game where is it? I don't see it the bandito. It was it was there before
People doing this because they have to go to the bathroom
Oh, she's dying of thirst. All right. All right. All right. All right. All right right right here. This is all right
I've have not placed one of these yet. I'll do two one here and one here
Where's the bandito game different park the first park is there a way?
Can I fast travel their way can just like fast travel to something the train really map?
I don't I think it's just this is the map of this park over from the train. Yeah, I couldn't use the train yet, though
Oh, it's cuz I didn't have another park unlocked. All right. Let me do that. All right
We're gonna go to thrillville stunts a lot of people here watch it. People are really thirsty. I got it. I'm on it
Okay, I gotta find a good place to put the bandit game probably over here. All right, bandito chinchilla
It's already built where you can juggle enemies in the air
All right jump weak attack pick up item use attack and strong attack
Who's your fighter and Dito chinchilla?
Nito lightning fists
Alito the mosquito
Salma the little mama light as a feather
Quick is something very quick this one here. This is the best mini game. All right, let's see. How does it work?
Okay, that's a strong attack this is a beat-em-up
Okay, I get it let's go points combo it's like castle crashers
What a great game that is by the way. I wish they made a castle crashes, too
I know you can't really make that game any better than you but still I would love to have seen another one
You're hiding behind the cactus. Oh
El lizard is boss. No, not really a guitar el tortoise
All right, it's ass el lizard plus fell off plus ratio. I want some more weapons
I have a power move, but I'm sure I don't think I'm sure I'm not even use it. Oh
I okay, I get it. I
Got a juggle
In this an amusement park game, this is one of the arcade games in the amusement park game
What does plus two mean? Oh
We're gonna explain that a lot of new people on this stream
plus two and minus two are
a way to gauge how much the chat room has
has agreed or disagreed with how comedic or funny the last thing that I said was or
Sometimes they they abuse it and they do minus two
Based on something that somebody in the game says like I don't even say it but apparently it's my fault for showing it
I don't understand
Where's face cam? Fuck you. You want a face cam? You want to turn the face cam on you really want that?
It's very very soon. I'll turn it on you're about to see me on camera. Alright, hold on. This is important our move
I don't just do it. Ooh
This is a big punch. Okay, cool. Oh
Oh
You know, it's fine, you know like Golden Axe
Have you guys ever played Golden Axe for real and not just for five seconds on?
Like an emulator that you have or something. Have you ever played through that game?
I don't think that game is actually possible to beat. I don't think it's possible that probably would have been
fifty to a hundred dollars in the machine
The final boss in that game is not possible to not die at least five to ten times at least
How come chat wants me to show my face because I've never done it before and I've been waiting for a face reveal
I've been trying I've been hyping it up ever since I had like only a few hundred viewers
I've been hyping up a face reveal and people like show it already do it already and I'm like
It's like alright eventually I will and maybe I'll just do it. Maybe I'll just do it today
You could please do it today. You know what?
I'll do it today. It's gonna be really kind of nervous about it though
I don't know you never know what somebody's gonna say about you right like oh, that's not how I thought you're gonna look
That's not what I thought you look like and I get it right you have like an image of what you think I look like
2022 is the year. Yeah, what about your face emotes? What is this? Um, well, I
Mean that's not my face though. I
Mean I've uploaded and I've shown I've uploaded like really heavily Photoshopped doctored images of my face
All those that you're seeing a really heavily edited
exaggerated features and
Eltoad I always imagined you being over six feet tall. That's what I mean. This game's fun
Job
Make the Eltoad noise. I'll try what do they do? I can't I can't do that one
That one's way too much
These are just all like inside of the toilet bowl sound I can't do these
face reveal
Stop stop it. No
Okay
You see me. You see me Wow. Do you look completely different? You're not what I thought you looked like at all Wow, dude, really?
That's what I mean. This is why I didn't want to fucking do it because
Now like now everybody knows and whatever it's just fucking annoying
I'm like mom like I'm like really no one's ever seen that before
Like the lizards
That was the worst joke it's not even my joke you can't count that as my joke, this is your joke
I'm just enabling you. That's the difference
Is that I do this is not my joke. I'm enabling your joke. What though? When does Elden ring come out?
That's such a you just said tomorrow, and I don't know why I thought that was funny February 1
I'm gonna play the hell out of that when that comes out. You better believe it
Comes out in 45 minutes hell. I'm how much further in the game do I have to go? This is like an entire game
Okay, I can't hit this
Elden rings gonna be awesome. It got delayed again. No, it didn't it actually I don't remember hearing that
February 24th. Yeah
The stunt rider minigame after this
We don't
Take I can go fast
Do blood-borne stream I would if it was 60 FPS. I don't think the game can even be 60 FPS, right?
I would do a blood-borne playthrough for you guys. And those of you don't know that's one of my favorite games ever made
I've beaten that game probably ten times
At least it's one of my favorite single-player games ever. It probably is my favorite single-player game ever made. I
Cannot play it again. I don't want to if it does a 60 FPS update
And I will have it's a reason for you to do it again now get up eat frozen fruits. Oh
It like a smoothie. I don't just eat them out of the bag or something. I put them in a smoothie
Remember this game doesn't end it has to
frozen food is
frozen food is delicious
Why are you eating frozen? Why are you eating frozen food?
Frozen if you just eat it you can bite into it. All right, let's do it ice cream. That's not the same thing
Ice cream is not even frozen solid. It's at the certain temperature. It's still you can still mush it around
It's not frozen
It's very very cold, but it's not it's not a frozen solid piece that's not frozen
I can hurt each other. Okay. This is getting actually pretty tricky. You're gonna move popsicle popsicle is frozen
At what temperature does ice cream freeze solid somebody look it up at what temperature is ice cream?
Does does milk freeze like that zero Celsius? It's the cream. Yeah. Yeah. Oh
She's the boomerang
It is a solid. No, it is a no. It is a non-Newtonian fluid. I'm it is a non-Newtonian fluid
It's not solid nor is it liquid I like frozen pizza. Yeah, but you're not eating it frozen
Frozen is solid defrosted equals liquid is ice cream frozen ice cream is a sweetened
Non-Newtonian liquid typically eaten as a snack or dessert
It may be made from milk or cream and it's flavored with sweetener
Either sugar or an alternative and a spice such as cocoa or vanilla or with fruit such as strawberries or peaches
We're just playing semantics though. It's just a it's a game of semantics. It's a liquids
You know, I think is a weird and look I know people are gonna call me like
Two head Andy, okay
But just think about the world right it's about how interesting this is
So ice is frozen water ice
It's fra water that's been frozen. It is at a certain temperature to be solid frozen water
When you put ice cubes into water the water does not become frozen
Even if there's a hundred thousand ice cubes in the water, that's so weird doesn't it's so weird. It's interesting to me
If you have a bunch of ice cubes in water, the ice does not freeze. It's just cold water
It's so weird
It's thermodynamics. That's what I'm saying. They're gonna dynamics is weird. You know what else is weird?
an
oscilloscope
Well, we have this tube that can make lights up to blow up on to make a tube on your television to have an image
On your screen what?
You know, you guys don't know this people think that well, oh my god, imagine if we lived in a world with magic. Oh
Man, imagine that we had like lived in the Harry Potter universe. There was magic
We have magic our ability to do like electronics is just fucking magic fire is magic
Can you think about it the fact that we have steel?
We can create steel. That's literally magic. That's magic
If an alien were to come down here, imagine if they didn't even know what like a metal processing was
Or what fire was we would just we would have magical fire powers
The fact that I have the fact I'm going full cam for this one the fact I'm at like 10 FPS doesn't matter
the fact that we can
Relive our memories right now right this very moment
You see me right now on the screen I am sitting here
I'm sitting in this in this spot you can relive this exact moment right now
You can read you can see memories how crazy is that that alone should be that's magic. That's literally magic
We can take photos of stuff and just like just it's there it is
You have a you you have a physical memory that you can see it's crazy
Your urinals rotating yeah, that's to make it extra interesting when I go it's a game for me. I'm serious think about that
Imagine if aliens could didn't have like like video or photo evidence of anything. They would be so freaked out
I can you tell an alien you stand right there alien
I'd like you to I'd like you to sing the alien national anthem and they're like
And you and then you show them you videotape them and you show them doing that they're gonna go
The
Heads gonna fucking explode you're literally
Showing them a memory that they had you have burnt that into a physical medium
I'm gonna CBD gummies did you have zero the fact that we can actually capture memories is crazy
You can open this video in three months and relive this exact second of your life and my life, too
We think the aliens the aliens what if the aliens don't know shit, okay?
What if the aliens don't know shit, we think the aliens are gonna come land and they're gonna be like here's our alien technology
It's just like ultra hyper electric beam and it's time travel
What if they don't know anything and we're the ones that have all this crazy technology
Yeah, the fact that they're gonna want to take shit from us. They're gonna want to take all of our technology
We are the aliens be speaking in chapstick. I'm just saying it's crazy that we have all this like magical stuff in the world
Electricity is just magical light beams like you got like
Palpatine the fact that your refrigerator could just be powered. What if aliens don't have anything aliens could just be like
Oh, wow, you have this this thing over here that keeps your food from spoiling
Well on our planet
fructose
we have
We got stuff what's that over there wait? Oh, it's a calendar. What's that? You keep track of days and
You have this
Device in your hand tells you when your next appointment is gone
I would love to know in my next appointment with what fruit lawn was they don't know shit
Aliens don't know anything. We are alright. I'm freaking out. I'm losing my mind
But yeah, you get what I'm saying that I'm going a little too hard here, but you know what I mean
It's crazy. We have bees on this planet
There are bees think about what a bee does think about what a bee does all of you what think about what a bee does
Oh, no, that's not like we could fucked up an alien. Oh, no, this is little thing that that that pollinates plants
It it goes and collects
Dust that comes out of this weird thing that grows out of the ground by the way
this thing grows out of the ground plants are weird and then it travels and
Puts that dust on other stuff and pollinates things. There's the simple act of pollination to an alien
It would be probably absurd to them
Who knows guys the fact that you can have sounds come out of your mouth might be the most absurd thing that they've ever heard
Imagine an alien that's just sitting there watching back those. Yeah, I get it. We like what is that coming out of his mouth?
Shoot it
Like we they would like they would level us they would level us when they heard the sounds you don't know what they have and
Neither do we what's this tangent is tangent is the world we have a magical fucking world and people don't think we do
Stay right there. What what is this?
What is this? Why does this exist? This is magic powers do explain this to me
Why does this exist?
Okay, every planet has that you don't know anything about planets
All we know is we can see like Mars has a bunch of red gas all over it
You know, we don't know anything what our magnets. It's a big red planet. It's just my hands are like all dusty
Hold on. This is a big red planet with red gas all over. There's no people on Mars
There's no aliens on Mars, you know, how many planets exist it
It's probably crazy that we exist in the first place the fur the top when an alien lands on this planet and they go Roger that
Yeah, this is not another planet, but just like red gas everywhere and a bunch of like red red. Everything's red
Oh, see this life there. Hi, mr. Alien. How are you?
The heads are gonna explode
Exactly what I told you was gonna happen. I'm telling you that's what's gonna happen
But with them that means they would have to be able to talk to no, but maybe they'd have like telepathy
What is it? What are you doing?
someone someone stop him
Why can I do this do you see this non-Newtonian fluid do you see what this is capable of I would they would get off the
Ship and I'd go. Oh, hold on. Mr. Alien. Oh, what's that device? He's putting in his mouth
We're gonna go
We're gonna go. We're gonna go. We're gonna go. We're gonna go eat it eat it
Well, they would think it was food. Well, did they even know what food is?
Huffing chapstick. Don't you get it?
Like they put it what if they don't even know what food is
The fact that they could just be this weird sentient thing of light that doesn't even know
Imagine if you the fact of the eat a cheeseburger in front of alien and then seven to twelve hours lady
You go into a room and that food comes out of your body
What a bizarre fucking planet we're on just the act of shitting could be so
world
changing and world ending
Pregnancy the fact that a person lives inside of somebody else's stomach. It's like no way, man
They would show up and they would leave we would scare the living hell out of everybody that came to this planet
L torches you would well, I'm not the ambassador of Earth. How do we even decide who that is?
I'm serious like it would have been macho man rainy savage
What the world is so fucked up with such a crazy world with all these magical powers like that would be the person they would
Probably expect
Just fire man fires just magical powers
We have furries. I don't but that's not a
So what do you mean by that?
Wait, you saying that are the ambassador of the planet should be like somebody in like a fursuit
Yes
That I'm into that I'm actually into that that would be fun
Mushrooms are weird
Classical music is weird. You have music
we have no idea we could be the ones that have all this art and entertainment and and
electricity and power
the sight of
running water
Could turn an alien inside out. And by the way, we've made up all these chemicals names
War would not start with the aliens over all power. It's about power
No, we call water water and that's not what it is
It's something else completely different and we've been completely wrong about it and they're like, it's actually not water
It's something else entirely you have the wrong chemical makeup. It's not okay. What's a chemical chemical chemical. What's that?
No, this is a bit we could be wrong about that and what if they tell us that somebody just fucking drops a nuke on planet fructose
This is the boss this dude is beyond zonk. Oh, we have a crazy world and
We make up all this stuff that we already do that the aliens are apparently gonna do better than us, right?
And we have virtual reality. So, I mean the aliens probably have like a real holographic virtual reality world
We're projecting what we think we're gonna be able to do in the future and that's just gonna be us
We're gonna scare the living shit and anybody that comes over here
even alien dark souls
You would have to explain to the alien the concept of controlling something that isn't alive
With your hands and your mind
Huh?
Well, you see here. Mr. Alien the thing on the screen right now is not alive
I'm controlling it with my brain and using my brain to put inputs into a device which controls the non-living being on the camera
On the screen right now. Don't worry when you see it get its head exploded by the sledgehammer. It's not real
It's just I'm making that happen because I feel like it has that fun
Hey, so where's your teleportation device? That's what we're really looking for. Mr. Alien. Hey, you guys can teleport, right?
Are you gonna teach us?
So offensive to an alien viewer
Explain horror movies to an alien
So what's happening right now, you know, we're watching somebody get killed
He just put a knife on that hurt the knife is though as a weapon in your people's culture that hurts
Yes, it is
That that man just put that thing that hurts people on their neck and slash their neck and their life fluid came out
No, no, no alien this stupid alien. Are you dumb? We just pretend to kill each other
Gruesomely horrifically and scarily it's for fun war and death is not fun, huh?
Why are you doing this human? Oh what you see
We all get together and you're gonna love it
We all get together and we sit in a big room with potential hundreds of us
We go into a big room and we eat get a bunch of snacks and we watch that exact person
Slash the throats of tons of innocent scared people when we all clap in and it's a really great time
And it's real though
And by the way, it's being projected into your brain through your eyeballs and it's a fake thing on screen
Let's be the game explaining a horror movie. Why do they do this? What's wrong with them?
We must do a re origination of the plow. That's right. Sorry. You have no technology
We're projecting that image of an alien. That's gonna wipe us out
We're the scary ones. We must do every origination of the plan. That's gonna be us
We're not gonna be happy with like the like a season of like some alien TV show
We're just gonna get rid of it magic being a new viewer. Are you done?
Yeah, this guy's an alien
No, I'm not going off again. I don't need to explain what a dinosaur is to an alien again
No, cuz we don't even know what a dinosaur looks like
We pretend to know what a dinosaur looks like reserved bones. It's Steven Spielberg. I had a t-rex go
And we all go yeah, yeah, that's right. That's exactly what happens. All right, I'm done. I'm done. Get me out of this
Get me out of this moving on. I'm gonna continue my playthrough of
Whatever this thrills real seeker. I'm a little hungry. Let's do ice cream and pizza. It's a good combo
Relax some ice cream
Everybody loves ice cream. How did frozen fruit get to that? I'm so sorry everyone
You're trying to explain language so much but not writing
Guys, we're gonna meet aliens one day and it's gonna be such a disappointment
there's gonna be a puddle on the ground with a face that just goes like
Yeah
And that's gonna be the extent of our alien contact. This is gonna be so disappointing
Oh, where's the time travel? Where's the holograms? No, this is a puddle that has a face
It like burps every four to five minutes. I want to build something else. Oh wait
I want to play this the aliens probably just gonna be a bat of bacteria
Yeah, it's gonna be small bugs
All right. I told you get me off this not give me on again. I'm doing with a controller by the way. Oh
Alright, that's cool. What's this do you welding? Oh, what is this?
What's going on the vacuum?
Okay, again, it points my need by the way, if I'm wrong about all the alien stuff
They take it be hostage first. I mean like oh you talked all this shit. Yeah, I'm gonna be the first like
execution from the aliens
explain porn to an alien
I think that's so hard. Oh, you see mr. Alien
We've got these two people and they they have an intercourse with each other on
This device that you've been shown before and it's it's and it means to excite the watcher. Oh
Okay, that makes perfect sense to me. I guess oh
good
That's not all you see
Also, there's a ton of other things that people find to be in that same realm of
Like a procreatable intimacy
It's not just that there's a lot of stuff
What could you possibly be?
procreation is procreation
You not entirely, you know, I'm sorry mr. Alien see some people
I
Am done. I'm done. I'm done. I'm done. I don't understand you but what's the point of 30 people being in this room?
well, I mean, I
Feel like we would be
held at arm's length
Ultimately, I think we would probably be
diplomatically
We would get like texted every now and then just to see how we're doing and I don't have to come over
I just want to know how things are things are going. Well good
Please leave us alone. Oh god. I don't want to do this cat. This man is almost 40 by the way
I mean not almost
Flows but not really it's plain toothpaste aliens. I want to ride this thing. You see how cool this thing is
I'm not 40. I want to ride this was that
Auntie thrillville ad oh shit
Try the go-karts. I want to ride the this monster truck thing. It looks crazy. I thought that was a nose
Pizza slice. I was like, what is the giant nose stall? What is that? How do I ride this? I want to ride that
I will put this one here big enough space for it, right? Yeah, it's cuz it's not a ride
But there sure is a lot of people dying on it
What how is that on a ride? I have to leave this stream is too much. All right. Well, just know that
Oh wait, this is Sammy from the original first five minutes of the game
Are you it was weird?
Like small like eight-year-olds don't do they don't shake hands. It was weird. They don't shake hands
He still hasn't gone to the bathroom
All right, you got to go to the bathroom we're gonna do a running competition. I actually don't play this is gonna be sick
What's your worst moment
You sure it's not not being able to go to the bathroom
What's your favorite hobby I've done it for years it was the best steak
Little kids eat steak. I love my dad. I don't remember eating steaks when I was like seven or eight
Steak I don't I didn't eat steak. It's love steak. I don't remember eating a steak
I didn't eat steak till I was like, yeah, at least like probably 14 15 or 16
Maybe that now probably like for 13 or 14 not this young
Well, that's the best game you're right
Alright, get out of here. He's why is this sad? I got 16 gram. We're gonna make an insane roller coaster
Is there another slot for a roller coaster? I don't think there's an oh, yeah, there is okay. Let's make a coaster here
All right, this one's gonna be nuts wagon trail
Pendulizer log. All right. How about the pendulizer?
But like what I got for whoa nothing so far
What's the maximum way to like liquefy somebody's insides right it's like to do this and then this immediately, right
Oh, that's yeah, that's pretty cool and your Lizer
Come on let me do it
Liquify their spines
Man you're just pressing buttons. I'm so bad at this kind of stuff. I know that there's a ton of you guys watching
That you likely spend a lot of time meticulously making a track and everything. I just
Not enough power. I need more power. Oh
All right, let's try it everyone, how can you not get a full solution from them we're talking about
Why I
Can't go this far. I don't have power
I
Added more electricity. I guess I can't build a roller coaster
Unless I end it here
This coaster sucks just build in another park. I want I had a lot of money here. Yeah
Alright, you're really excited to ride this one on and tell me how you like it. Where is she?
Hello, it's fun. All right. I'm gonna go with the other park. I gotta catch up on the missions here
I
Know what I'm doing here. I've got okay games. No guest
Watch out three critics just enter thrillville as park manager. You can talk with people and win them over
Let's see what the notoriously grumpy HG crop has to say
Okay
I
Can't believe how rude you are
Anybody gives a shit about your opinion about my park
See how many people are here. You see how many customers are here right now. Go look on Yelp
I got a 3.4 right now. I got a 3.4 on Yelp you what you're gonna say is meaningless
It's a fair price
Fair price lots of attractions
Nobody cares what you have to say
That's Sammy
All right, but there are no jokes aside golden ticket
You have a VIP pass from your inventory to a critic mo po. I already had didn't already give him one
I already gave him something didn't I saw review? No, not the movie
What I
Bribed this guy an hour ago, and he said he was gonna scratch my back if I scratched his you dick
What I can't believe I'm giving him another one
Okay
I
Need to make dune buggies, let's go in buggies. Where is it? I don't have it yet. Where's that test of strength?
I want to do it. It's a coaster
I don't have racetracks unlocked. Okay, power up and action
Are you swing up?
What's happening
You have to do I thought it was all in one go. All right power up
Okay, then
Select the angle and then right in the middle one. I can do I can get it
Damn it one more time. I just want to get it right in the middle
Fuck you. Whatever one more time
I'll get it
Bingo that was
Relax, seriously relax. That's not that big of a deal. I just did the thing with that guy with the guitar
They're like do do do do do do do like relax. That was so uncalled for I
Already won who cares I got a bear cool. How much of the drinks? That's fine. There's only been four customers
It's too expensive. Okay, what did I want to do? Oh that I want to unlock racing
Where's research park upgrades research increasing was okay compact coaster
When do I unlock the thing to beat them the movie critic?
Thousand dollars a month. I'm gonna do a marketing campaign in the national newspaper
Alright we're gonna have to I got 11 friends out of 26 some of these up we're gonna have to cut some of these
molly noodles
Get unfriended and I unfriend you no pots. I don't want to be friends with any of these people last activity restroom
So why is the bladder so high? I just built a bathroom. Wait, he's going to this bathroom. No, there he is
Timmy, how are you? Good to see you again Sam. You like the new bathroom. Oh the facility. Oh
He's probably so happy right now. You have a beer or bear
What we'll give it back give me that back I have that back
No, I don't want to do this I
Have to beat this kid's ass in something right like I got to destroy you in something
wagon trail
What's one that I can just just absolutely wipe the floor at this kid?
Which one I mean a bandito possible prospector putt wagon trail
Why are they all these weird floating VR games? I don't want to do that
They're all just like these odd VR games. Oh shit. This went the wrong way you putt-putt
But I can't just do I'm gonna beat everybody in putt-putt. We just got a raid to this Coney
Welcome everybody from Coney. Thanks Coney for the raid playing thrillville
Outrageous, hope you had a good stream and welcome everybody. What's going on? How are you? Thanks for the raid
He's gone to the bathroom. So we're fine. No, you know what?
Welcome everybody. It's time. Let's just beat it. Let's just beat him in the putt game. Oh
I don't actually want to I want to play on my broken course where I can cheat. I don't want to do this
Actually have to play nine holes against this kid. I want to play him against the one where I can beat him in one hit
All right, this is it really actually pretty important. He's pretty good. He got that hole in one. So did I all right par three
Let's go right there. I think you make up I can make ground up here. Just don't screw this up. Oh
How much softer was I?
Supposed to do that
Alright, he got four here. I'm gonna use that old strategy. You might as well just leave now kid. Good luck. It's over
What I get two for that one got to hit this one a little bit harder
This does have to go uphill. It's back-to-back only one and I make it three in a row
Let's make it a hat trick. He went over. Oh, you know, you went under that's fine. We get a good look. I hugged this wall. Oh
Yuck
Nobody knows how to do these doesn't matter. I made up a lot of ground good. All right it
He could still come back. This is par four. I wonder if I just avoid. Yeah
I'm thinking just avoid the middle
Or just to hit it hard enough. I'm gonna try to hit it hard enough. Let's see
Perfect. Perfect. All right. He got
He went under on this one. It's a little weird up there
Not bad sink it very hard for me to lose this now. I'm thinking full power right here or at least like 80% power
Oh
Almost get silly with this one. All right. Okay. All right, don't screw this up. I won
I was pretty good and I kind of blew it at the end there, but I think that was fine was
We're literally best friends so now what can I what's the point of this what can I do? Oh, no, it doesn't
Lightning strikes the earth 17 million times a day. That's a lie
200 times a second lightning is striking the earth. Wow, how
All right, good conversation. Goodbye earth is big. Yeah, but 200 times a second though. That's a lot
I got 20 grand. Let me go to the other section over here
Let's go to Saddleville. Oh, that's right. The ocean. I don't know why I keep thinking like
New York City getting hit by lightning 200 times a second or like LA. Oh, yeah, this is just 200
It's literally that these oceans
Forgot about the ocean 200 times a second
It's a bad ending
Okay, the ocean sucks. Anyways
Why you say that?
That's kind of a weird opinion. The ocean sucks. Like fuck the ocean. Why that's a weird opinion
Why you hate the ocean? The ocean is actually kind of
Unbelievable
Imagine explaining an ocean to an alien. Oh, I played that already. Is there even room for more rides here? I don't think there is
All right
Battleville, I don't have a battleville. Whoa. It's that ride. Who is this?
I love money. There are just tanks running over stuff. All right, I'm gonna build something over here coffee and
Bathroom, all right. Can I do a race car now racetrack build your own Oh dune buggies
I can I can go against the critic. Okay, I don't want this to be too boring, but I don't want to be too
Well, there's planes of fire
Like my pretend enthusiasm what is it okay to sell the following rides that are in the way what ride whoops
Well, I sold that ride that was in the way
Alright, I just want to beat that guy
What?
Just finish the track
I blocked it did I though hold on
I
Go down
Oh
Boy that's a big one. All right. I gotta practice first
Break is X accelerate is a power slide is right trigger. Okay, let's do it. He's practicing too. I
Was just trying to kill everybody. All right, let's go
No
No, how many laps three? Thank God there are bumpers. Yeah, I would have fell off five minutes ago
The track minimap on the left looks like you got shitfaced and tried to make a pretzel. It's a great drunk idea
let's make pretzels tonight or
the
You know like when they have the skeleton in the classroom and it has the organs
It's just the intestines that weird that kind of cut in half person
Alright now I got a challenge that guy. All right, leave in the dust five stars. Hell. Yeah. All right, where is he?
Hey mo pots. Hey you piece of shit
You're about to lose to a child
Oh really
You like a drum
Okay, it's time. I'm gonna get a prediction gone. Will I beat this guy?
I think I will yo the map track looks like Squidward. I have to see it. I don't know. How's it?
mo Biden
What's good for acid reflux?
Don't eat before bed
If you're gonna eat make sure you have like at least an hour or two to digest before you let on
Don't eat anything too crazy before it's usually a lot before bed void stuff that really kind of makes it
I mean, I was told one time and I made like a little joke to the doctor and he like didn't think it was funny
He just kind of moved on I probably was like the 30th person that day that made the joke when I was first talking about
Oh, man, I've got acid. What should I do to stop the acid, right? I've got put on
A day anti acid protein pump inhibitor right before and he gave me a list of all the things that you should avoid
Completely if you're trying to reduce acid and see how it goes it was coffee
Alcohol spicy food chocolate. It was a list of just all this stuff and I looked at him and I was like
Oh, man, all the good stuff, huh?
You got can't eat all the good stuff and he did he with a straight face. He just walked out of the room
He didn't even listen. It was like he did not even care that I spoke. It was like garlic onions coffee alcohol
Cheese literally everything that you like on earth. He walked out of the room. It was as if I didn't say it
He probably hears that every day. Here we go
Hey y'all fuck now. Neither one of us can win. You're trapped here forever. You're my prisoner
What if he goes but above beyond the finish line?
Hi motherfucker, it's not Squidward. What are you talking about?
Doesn't look like anything at all like Squidward
This guy's bad too, by the way, the the guy that I was racing in the generic race was better than the guy
That's the best racer in the game. Let's see if I can lap him
I'm gonna tow this motherfucker never in the beginning the stream. I talked about lapping toad. Oh
Shit, I'm gonna try to turn him the other way. I want to spin him backwards
Oh, I can't accelerate up the hill. Where is he? Wait, where'd he go? Where is he? Oh shit. He's always screwed
I'm trying to get him stuck so I can lap him. I've won. Oh, I beat him. Oh, okay. Okay. All right
Now get out of here scram
I don't get at least a 3.5 on Yelp
I'm taking the VIP back and I want my bear back and I want that rubber chicken
I gave you to a lot of people in the park though. I'm getting hungry
I want to eat times that's been five and a half hours. I don't feel like it's been like three now
The real question is what are we gonna play this weekend?
It's completely up in the air because after this weekend stream whether it's probably Saturday or Sunday
It's Saturday after this weekend stream every Sunday every Saturday
I'm doing about like a week or two of VR straight. I'm setting that room up again. We're gonna go for it again
Hey, I want to see how this one works. No, I hate these why would I I don't understand why people ride these
You know, don't even explain this to aliens explain this to me why people get on this because I don't get it
This makes you feel awful
That's wrong. What needs repair
Ten million versus one. Wow. Yeah, I don't I don't get it not into it at all
It makes you feel awful
Even if it doesn't make you feel like sick or anything. It makes you feel bad
Do a coaster. All right, what about some of the pre-built ones? I'm very curious about these
Ye olde wagon. I'm looking one of some of the pre-builds. I'll build my own
You
All right, let's go oh I just got this compact coaster
minimum power
What area power limit? Oh, I can't just play inscription
I keep people keep saying to play that but I don't know a more ever hood
That's not a bad idea either. You're too dumb for inscription. That's what I'm afraid of. I'll be honest
You gotta do monster rancher. That's right. We'll figure it out
That all right, I'm gonna play one more game and then I'm gonna get some food. We'll end it in like another 20 minutes
So what turbo Ville? She's putting in double time there like NBA 2k
Alright, do you guys think if I played NBA 2k 20? This is not gonna happen. Just I want to be I gotta get this out there
Would more than 5,000 people be at that stream?
Would that stream get more than three or four thousand viewers if I played NBA 2k 22?
What's wrong things broken sell it what I sell the guy
This thing too. Yeah, this thing was always at the fair. Oh
I can't even look at it anymore. I don't even look at it. Yeah, I don't think that more than 5,000 people are on that stream
All right. What's the last thing I'm gonna do? I need one more thing to do
Viewers choice, what should I do one more game? I'm pretty sure there are 15,000 people that don't give a shit about this game
Yeah, but there's a difference between a game there's a playing NBA 2k and just playing NBA. I
Think there's a difference
None of you guys would want to watch me play Madden either
All right one guy in the chat want to be placed on writer really bad again
So I'll do it. I'll do it for the guy in the chat
Play Dota. I don't know what's worse
playing Dota for five hours on
stream or playing
Like Madden NFL 2k 19. I'm not sure what you guys what you guys would like less
2k would be way worse. I don't know. I feel like I could it
It might be fun just to even play maddening like lose by a hundred points
but playing like poorly in Dota or League would just be
Kind of embarrassing and there's no fun funny any it's just like wow this guy just sucks at League
Like if I if I run the ball back for a touchdown, that's that's excitement if I run into the tower
I'm an asshole and nobody likes me. I was doing all right right there
Bobas are really boring to watch the only mobile
I've ever really played with smite and if I even understand that people don't really want to watch that
unless
Unless that you're good enough because those games are really competitive and if I was
Unbelievable at Dota or something right laughs. I was like
Super rank or whatever they whatever it is. I mean yeah
I mean you're what if you're if you're not super diamond rank, and I am diamond rank then it's like okay
But if I have no idea what I'm doing. I don't know what the characters names are I feel like people would just be like
Jeremy what are you doing? I don't know what items I'm buying
Okay, that could be fun a little while, but not for more than a couple of streams. I don't know I don't think
late Tekken 7 oh
You mean this cuz that's all you that that would be
It's a real song
Here we go here. We go here. We go now now
Here we go, right?
You hit next track. Oh, I'd love to I don't care about DMC. I turn this up
Oh boy what what what was that I want to hear that I wish I kind of interested
What was that I'm so confused is that like a remix or like a
Like three songs
What is this and why is this in this game
Very interesting soundtrack is this one
P h r i
b i l l e
What are they spelling? Oh?
Yes, all right this one safe
No, I want that song
It's from Red Dead
But he can't apprehend
When the other kids are lost
Space plastic rocket ships
Chips well he's meeting bad guys face to face with a big iron on his head. Yep
There's a word he's heard but it don't place when the ghost does it it goes like
Where is it?
No
It does doesn't it?
Oh is this one's he was a little no we they have like 10 songs in the whole soundtrack
All right, i'm out of here i'll see you guys later i'll see you out what's today wednesday see sunday
I I kind of want to hear this. I like I like this. I turned it on. All right. I'll see you guys later
I'm i'm kind of at my end of this game
That's really cool. I hope your nostalgia brain was uh, that's you have to
Scratch it for a little bit. I'm gonna get some food. I'll see you guys on saturday saturday
Probably still gonna be four o'clock my sleep schedule is awful right now so saturday at 4 pm pacific
It's gonna be a mystery game, and we'll probably pick it in pre-stream
So if you want to have a say in what is gonna happen on saturday afternoon
Uh, we will do a poll in pre-stream i'll come up with a few things and then after saturday
We're gonna do probably two weeks of vr at least a few times and then after that
It's gonna be a big stream and then after that we'll see in the nelden ring, right?
I'm ready. It's gonna be an exciting few weeks. We have a lot of community subs a lot of subs in general, too
I didn't catch them all but thanks
Here is everybody
That was subscribed tonight
Thanks. Why was it? I had a great time. Sometimes it's fun. Just to have like a little game in the background
What we just chill
It's a lot of fun. I'll be back on saturday. Do you pee in bottles? No, I pee into a toilet
We'll figure out what we're gonna do explain aliens again. Yeah, that was I don't know
I can't the the goblins just kind of took over there. I don't know. I don't remember that whole conversation
All I know it was about 30 straight minutes. I don't remember anything about it
It was the chap. Ah, ah peter. It was the chapstick peter. Don't forget the olive fingers
I will not forget the olive fingers. I promise
I will do on that stream on saturday the stupid thing that that person wants me to do and I don't know why they
Want me to do it
I'll see you saturday. Have a great night. See you this weekend. Thanks for sticking around. Thanks for hanging out
Have a great one. See you guys soon