So those of you that know me know that it's very difficult for me to play a
game and talk at the same time so we're just gonna let the it's gonna let the
game speak for itself and I'm gonna burn to death all right guys turn on your
favorite rock song because this is where we get nuts this is where we track
somebody where is he where is he across the way we're gonna protect this hammer
that's what it's all about you alright no you're not I'm having a lot of fun
with this game though guys it is free to play on Steam and you just kind of run
around shoot people right that's fun you know what else is fun like dropping
down on somebody that has no idea and then having him get the health pack and
heal to completely full health it doesn't matter though I'm gonna get the
hammer yeah I'll get the hammer who wants to mess with me I got the fucking
hammer you want to get railroaded I'm gonna crush this guy up here oh he's
key I'm gonna come I'm gonna beat this guy down here he has no idea all right
so for those of you that have no idea what just happened right there would
this is capture the flag when you capture the flag you can kill people with
the flag it's an instant kill so what happened is I need to pay attention here
we both kill each other at the same time come on through daddy daddy no daddy
why am I saying daddy the fuck does that mean you know what buddy it's I've
had enough out of you I've had enough why was I saying daddy that was very
strange daddy help me I'm being chased by a mean man oh you got a shield screw
holy shit look at my character are you serious dude I look like I look like the
cookie monster oh yeah that's two cookies that's so awesome I don't ever
want to get my head back I want to be the cookie monster forever can that be a
thing well I guess I could but I'm gonna die no don't take my cookie monster
avatar oh shit oh shit look out boys oh one shot and I'm dead better to make
this count I see health over there though gonna make the run around this is
not safe not safe not safe dude this title this video is just gonna be like
the noise video right just make like a shitload of noises it's intense though
man it is I should not have jumped all right now we're safe now I don't have to
make as much like weird noises fuck you sorry that was a little loud and mean
good job you can dance around all you want it's fine let's string it together
here huh
oh that's two there he is he just killed one of my boys come up this way yeah you
ain't getting away with that yeah geez this guy's got like a cluster bomb I
ain't going that way I'm gonna wrap around dude holy hell and a hand basket
I got two grenades grenades are important that's for sure you're about
to see why could he walk into it no he's not he's smarter than that but is he
smart enough got the assist wish I could have saved him in time but that just
wasn't gonna happen well don't do don't rain fire on me I have too many holes in
my body where's their health back I'm on a five kill streak right here
this guy's still on my ass look at my health help me nice okay here's our flag
we're gonna cap it nice job team I want to get like a ten kill streak is that
gonna happen right now it could it could come on whatever somebody will kill him
somebody will kill that guy I'm gonna get the hammer maybe actually I think I
could get this there's probably two or three people in here protecting it which
means you throw a grenade in and just insta kill someone no I could pick it up
though let's pick it up go for another hammer kill he's gonna wrap around this
corner damn it screw you give me the health cookie monster man I am the
globally known cookie monster I think somebody has our flag though I don't
think we can cap this oh now I can he doesn't know him behind him he has no
idea you know what we're gonna drop this I'm sorry I'm sorry I would have killed
him I will kill him oh I will kill him this so many people no I had a fucking
streak going I like this gun it could be a little better though this loadout
could be a little better in here oh boy got it bang we won we are the winners
quick everybody do the dance you get for free for downloading the game well we
won that's loadout guys it's on Steam it's free to play if you want to check
it out go check it out take care everybody see you all soon take care
everybody and new good night