Hey, what is going on everybody? Jerma here with Facecam Fortress 2, playing as the Scout on CTF Doublecross.
And before we get into the video, playing Scout and talking, my brain will not be able to handle this. See you later.
Today's my birthday. I am 27 years old, September 22nd, 2012. Jerma is 27.
So, what does this mean? This means I'm getting old. I'm on the later part of my 20s.
Because I used to be able to say I was in my mid-20s, and I can't really say that anymore because 7, 8, 9 is a lot closer to 30 than something like 24, 25, or 26.
So now, I am a full-fleshed adult. A real adult.
Is that a spy? Oh my god. What is this guy doing, man? This guy is acting like a spy.
There's nothing I can do besides try and get away from this guy. Oh my god. I actually got away.
Oh, he got me with a needle right in my back. Oh dear god. Good shot, Medic. Coffee.
Actually, this is blueberry iced coffee. Please, I'm going to just beg you guys.
If you drink coffee, if you like the taste of coffee, and you have one maybe once in the morning or something, or maybe once every couple days you'll have one, please try blueberry coffee.
Blueberry coffee is phenomenal. You will not regret it. It is one of my favorite things in the entire world.
So please go try some blueberry iced coffee if you like coffee.
This heavy Medic parry. This is bad news. Oh, not anymore. This guy. Come on. Get out of here.
Nope. I gotta get the intelligence. That's the number one thing here. Oh hey, so that's a spy. For sure.
Bumped right into his butt. Oh, scout on scout. Scout on scout. More scout on scout. Who wants it? More! Who wants some of this?
I'm dead. Oh, I'm so dead. Oh my god. How do I keep escaping from these things? I'm insane right now.
Something's going on. The gods of Team Fortress 2 are being insane. They are letting me do this.
Because normally I would get myself killed in all these situations. So, let me get that intelligence.
Oh, I just heard a sentry. There's no way. Oh, it's not up yet. No, I didn't want to go this way. Oh, damn it. Oh, damn it.
Oh, no. I did not want to do this. I'm dead. I can't even hit this guy. Oh my god. That was so lucky.
I can't walk by here. I cannot. There's nowhere I can go. I might as well just sit here with my fingers in my face.
Hold on. I can get up there. Come on. Come on. This is embarrassing.
Well, so I'll tell you a story while I sit here and can't jump over this thing. Oh, it's not up. It's not up. It's not up.
Oh, wow. That was got to use that. My noggin wasn't being functioning right there. Unfortunately.
Are we going to cap it? What's going on here? Let's cap that thing.
Yay. I have a new rank on my strange scatter gun. This guy is going to run into that.
I just got so confused right there. Oh, I'll take this guy out right in his back. Come on.
Spy up top. Oh, baby. Give me those crits. Get crit. Get crit. Where is he?
Damn. Whoa. Whoa. Did I get him? At least I got him. Didn't get the heavy though. Oh, yeah. Blueberry iced coffee, baby.
But the beginning of this video, before all this weird stuff started happening, I'm getting old, guys.
I'm starting to feel kind of like grandpa. My joints hurt. My neck hurts. My face hurts.
I wake up in the morning sometimes and I'm just like, my god, what did I eat for lunch last night? I have diarrhea.
Oh my god. But that is starting to happen now. I'm an actual real, real, real adult. And it's kind of scary.
I'll get that guy up there. I will get that guy right now. Get me up here. Get me up the stairs.
Around the corner. Around the bend.
Take it out. Come on. Come on here. Come on. Come on. I can get that sentry. I can get it.
I'm going to get this sentry down. Come on. Yes. Wow. Get it. Get that. Oh, good job, demo man.
Damn it. I should have went for him first because he was eating a sandwich. I should have killed him.
And I should have killed the sandwich eating heavy, but I didn't do that. I didn't get the heavy.
This respawn time is really, really long. We'll get it and we're going to get it. We're going to win for sure.
Come on, guys. Come on, guys. Come on, guys. Somebody pick it up. The ambassador. Here we are. Here we are.
You are a spy. That. Take that. They got our intelligence. That's not cool.
Not going in that front door. No bags. Go around the sewer. We'll go into the sewer and like stink like a sewer rat.
You know, where am I going? Excuse me. I'm going to get this. I'm going to cap this. God damn. Why? What?
What the hell is going on? Oh, he's putting stickies down. Oh, he doesn't even know I'm there. Watch this.
Oh, my God. Come on. Come on. Let's go. Come on. At least I'm going to get it.
I'll get it far enough so that somebody can get it on the other team. On my team. Come on. Somebody pick that up.
Pick that up. Somebody. Come on. Somebody get that. It's right there. Come on. Somebody get that.
Come on, spy. Just touch it. Just touch it, spy. No, no. I'm going to get that. I'm going to cap it right now.
Whoa. No, I'm not. What is this guy doing here? How do we get two people spawn camping? Spawn camping.
Dude, let's go. I'm doing this thing. I need some backup. Come on. Oh, need to get that. Need to touch it.
Need to touch it. I touched it. Yes. Yes. All right. Now somebody go over there and grab it.
We can win this right now. We can win this right freaking now. Touch it. Come on, man. Good. Good. Good.
Oh, come on. We got to get this. Come on. I'm going to get this. It's going to happen.
Oh, now they got a soldier here. No, I got it. I got it. No, I'm getting stuck on stuff. Oh, this is it.
That's not a spy. Where am I going? What am I doing that for? Oh, my God. My brain just fried, but this is going to be it.
And boom. Thank you guys so much for watching Face Camp Fortress 2.
Germa the old man. I'm old now, so 27 years old. I'm so sad.
But anyways, thank you so much for watching, guys. I really do appreciate it.
And I'll catch you guys all next time. And of course, take care, everybody.