How's everybody doing? Yes, I'm very early. There's a reason for that though. You shouldn't go live if you are sick. I'm all right
Just feel kind of terrible
Why are you live? Get out of here. Yeah, right leave
What if I just left? I was like, all right fine. I'll go to bed
You sound awful
I just wanted to hang out for a few hours. Yeah, I you haven't seen me in like five days
Well, I mean well, hold on. When was Halloween?
And those of you that didn't watch the Halloween stream on Charlie's stream haven't seen me in even longer
Uh, the reason why I'm early
For those of you that don't know
yesterday
Um, I was in the pre-stream chat
I typically am
And I talked about how I didn't feel very well. I was like oh shit
Had all this fun stuff to do
And it turned out I didn't feel very good
So, uh, I was like I got up today. I took a covid test by the way. It's not covid
Or if it is it's not detectable in a test yet
But I've been testing every I want to say 12 hours
It's not that apparently
But it's something
And it's annoying
You have a weak immune system
I actually have a pretty strong immune system
Go to bed
Well, okay, so I got up and I was contemplating if I was gonna stream today
But I mean I pushed the stream yesterday to today
And I didn't want to do it again because I want to stream i'm here. I want to stream
So we were gonna play neon white and frog detective, but I definitely can't do the frog detective voices
So we're gonna play a cute dog game where you take pictures of dogs
This I've actually had this in my steam list for
months
It's called paparazzi
nice cheese voice
Wait, do you mean that's the milk voice? I know what you mean
This is what you sound like when you eat like a block of cheddar
That's so gross
Uh, yeah, i'll take the whole milk, please
Oh, yeah. Yeah. I love whole milk. It's so good
Who's you don't who does anybody drink whole milk in here?
Be honest with me. Do you drink whole milk?
To me whole milk is something you put you mix with eggs
And you make food with it or like desserts doesn't nobody drinks whole milk, right?
Only two week olds drink whole milk. Um
It's better for you. It's better for you
I actually don't really like a dairy milk at all anymore
It's crazy because after a while of drinking
I'm an oat milk chad, by the way, but wait, are there any other oat milk chads in here?
I would hope so
Yeah, so oat milk
When you drink or you I put it in my coffee usually or whatever. I put it in cereal
Going back to real dairy milk
tastes
Like it, I don't know tastes like blood
It's weird. It tastes like meat
Does anyone know what i'm talking about?
Those of you that uh did a milk substitute for a long time went back to real milk. It tastes like you're drinking meat
It's very weird
milk substitutes
I honestly I I used to like almond milk
but then I kind of
Read some articles of how like almonds are destroying california
and was like, uh
I think I thought that maybe i'll switch to something else
So I was like, oh, maybe i'll do oat milk
And then I tried soy milk and that's soy milk sucks
Can I let's be very honest here soy milk is like
I hate it
It's like rice milk, which is okay. That's fine. It's a little thin for me
And then I found oat milk
And it's it's got full of flavor. It's a little sweet
It's it's delicious
It's great stuff
If you wanted me to do a milk tier list, I would and oat milk would be number one s plus
Are you for real? No, you actually you said are you real?
But yes
Are you for real?
What do you say most people what?
Oat milk is the reason why you're fucked up. That's not accurate. I started drinking oat milk like two years ago
But fucked up for a long time
How come there's no milk mode enabled in obs? I don't know
Almond milk is really good
No, I I like almond milk
Just almonds take so much to grow and they take so much to harvest and stuff
I don't know. I've read some articles
But anyways, i'm not feeling great
But I didn't want to not scream because I wanted to hang out
It's been a while
Um, so we're gonna play paparazzi. Let's do it. Why not?
He's educated andy
I've been listening to this music the whole time
I'm gonna be muting to clear my fucking cheese voice. I'm sorry guys for those who that are just joining
I have a whole charcuterie board here and i'm not going to put it away
I've got cheddar. I have swiss
I have uh
Fig paste and i'm gonna enjoy my cheese plate and i'm really sorry if you can't fucking take it
Yeah, i've put the cheese plate away. Put the cheese plate away. No, i'm gonna finish it
All right, so did I try to do face cam today? Whatever. I will fine
I'm fine. All right. This is paparazzi
Let's go
I'm actually kind of excited for this. It's gonna be a chill day
Uh, uh
Yarr, are you the new
razz-o
About time we see dogs had someone to photograph our adorable wee faces
Will you take a photo of me?
I feel like I shouldn't be playing this game
I don't know. It just hit me like i just like a brick
I don't know. It's freaking me out for some reason. Why I don't know why this is freaking me out
This game's like cute. What's it? I have to like settle down. All right, hold on use the mouse to look around
Aim your camera with the right mouse button. Okay, take a photo with the left mouse button
There it is. Open your journal to view objectives
This is dogs running around
um
Post to dog net
This is the kind of photo that gets like two thumbs up on dog net
I'm gonna do it. Anyway, i'm gonna do it. This photo is blowing my mind. I told you it was one person
It's literally one person
Raise this photo to recycle one film if you have saved it in your favorites you can view it later
Well, it's our it's our first. Um, okay. It's our first one so we have to save it
Okay, get five followers to oh, you actually have to get people that you have to it's like instagram
All right. All right. I'm ready. Can you take a photo of me?
I'm the wee gray one in in front of me shop. Be sure to crouch to catch me best angles
Okay, where are you? I'm the wee gray one
in front of me shop
Oh, there you are. What's that gonna get on dog net?
Hold shift. Okay, so I got I did that
Take a photo of c dog. I always knew I was handsome
You can now pet dogs walk up to them and hold interact
Shit you really well, that was a very long arm
Who is this? Is this my arm? It doesn't feel right. You can pet the dog. Okay, so now what?
I only have 10 pictures I can take. Oh cool
Oh, okay
That one's going on dog net
That one's pretty good too. Wait, wait, stop stop stop stop stop right there good
over here
Where are all these dogs? Where are the owners?
Why there's hundreds of dogs. This is like a dog town. Wait, that's not safe
They live here. Am I a dog?
Click that one's going
Cringe compilation
Okay
You know like a selfie
All right. I need five followers
You got two new followers take a photo of a friendly dog. What's going on here?
Okay
Perfect promo material for the shop
Oh, I can rotate the camera now. You have to lala. I will dude
You kind of look like a bull terrier the bull terriers the ones with the
That was an ugly sound that I just made bull terriers are the big chunky snouts, right?
I look like a bull terrier. Do I the target dog? Oh
All right. I need five followers. They only have two followers right now
Can you send me a photo of a dog playing with a stick? Okay
I love to see my friends play around I can do that easy when there's a stick right here
All right, who should play with it? That's a good one. That one's even better
Yep. Oh your eyes are closed. Hold on. Look at that one. That one's perfect
Okay
Yep. Oh my god, so cute
You got three bunks use cash to buy items in the shop. All right
All right, which one should go on dog net this one for sure
Now this is a good dog spam am I spamming people I have six followers. Oh, you can't see that. Hold on
Where should I put the camera?
No, I don't I hate doing this because I have to flip it. This is a cute game. This game's cute
Oh my god, he loves you. Yes. Okay. I don't I've spam if I do too much
All right, that's good. So now what do you need now?
Five followers I get access to the shop find a vending machine to use it
All objectives here complete you can leave the area check back later. All right sick
This here is a dog feed dog world
It'll be fame and fortune aplenty if ye
But stay true to your course photograph dog save the pics you like it soon
You'll be setting your sails and distant seas in other words gain followers complete objectives and unlock new locations. Sounds good
golden dog bone
Don't go to the water. What are they looking at? I love this dog. Look at him. Good shot. Yo
All right, watch out watch out
Unflip it i'm not why no, I have to be looking to where the gameplay is that's streamer 101
Okay, so now um camera. Ooh, I can get a zoom lens. Okay. I have to go to a vending machine see dogs
There's okay. Here's one here
Uh, this this is what would be
Inside of a dog vending machine, right? Like this. Oh, okay film pack black and white film pack
Stylish film pack or fisheye lens
Stylish film pack. I don't have enough of the fisheye lens
I'll get the black and white now because I think I have to do it for the like tutorial
basic
Color basic black and white black and white filtered. Look at this looks cool. Hold on
Now that that's like actually kind of an artsy photo
Look at that one
Yep
Dog net take a closer. Look zoom. Give me some of that food
This one's i'm going in favorites. All right, just get rid of these i'm not gonna like lose followers, right? Can you lose followers?
Okay, so now, uh
Leave the area and check back later. All right, so i'm gonna leave
How do I get out of here?
You're gonna lose them
They're all sitting completely still that was almost a perfect photo turn around. How do I turn around?
No
Sorry. All right. How do I get out of here this way?
golden dog bone sick
How do you fix the stream he looks weird eat a dog treat now eat a dog treat now
People don't like it
It's a dog plus one
I'm telling i'm spamming dog net. Oh leave area. Okay
scorn
What is going on here? Wait, what? Home?
Oh, it shows the different dogs in the photos. Oh, that's cool. Okay lighthouse co
Go, are you the pupper rotzer on behalf of the doggo documentation project?
We need your help someone in our record-keeping department got distracted by a tennis ball and accidentally deleted everything
Now we need someone to photograph all the different kinds of dogs for science
These photos will be added to our state-of-the-art puppypedia system anytime you find something new
You can view the puppypedia from the home button. All right
How do I get out of here though?
Find this request hidden somewhere in the area
How do I get out of here this is an envelope in the shop
You can't go back
I can't go back go to the sea dogs
Oh
shit
Okay, I got it
I need swashbuckling spirit. Give me a photo of a dog on a boat
Take it from below
Yeah, that counts, right?
What? Oh, we need it. You can submit a photo to the exhibition. Okay, a dog on a sailboat taken from below
Didn't I just do that?
That's it, right?
Too close
Okay, there's that
Thank you. The boardwalk is now open. All right, cool. Let's go
You know, you can save photos that you really like
Some of the best photo that you've taken so far
Uh probably this one let's go to the boardwalk
These pictures suck
I just started
What what where's frog detector three frog detector three got bumped?
because i'm
Kind of sick
Uh, and I wouldn't be able to do all the voices and when I talk loud my head hurts
Stop having me act stop asking questions. It makes me talk and it makes my head hurt
Okay. Um
Where's this boardwalk?
Down here, right?
He's dying
puppy boardwalk
Let's go
Okay
I'm the king of all dogs your paparazzi programming appears to present potential you can gain more followers
You may yet impress me. What even was that? Is that a dog?
But there are people here
eggnog voice
By the way eggnog is fucking disgusting
I can't think of a more
Disgusting beverage than eggnog. Oh shit. All right, i'm fine
You know eggnog takes like raw cookie batter
It says something about it tastes raw
Like I shouldn't be drinking it. It's like oh, yeah, and this is a bunch of raw eggs and a bunch of like, uh raw
It just tastes raw
That's a good one. I kind of want to
Oh, you're here. You're surfing. Well, that was a good one
That's a good one, too
Oh, you built a sand castle
These are all good
Dog lifeguard. Yep. Yeah, get the fuck out of here human
No, I don't want humans in my photo. Is that a cat? It's a cat
Is it a cat?
No, it's not. Never mind. Okay. So what what do I need to do? This looks like auto now
Oh
That was absolutely adorable. I i'm glad I got it. Okay, so I need to what do I got?
I'm definitely posting this one a dog net with the shovel in his mouth. Oh, yeah
100 percent
Sam post has been a dog net
Definitely this one going on dog net. This one's absolutely going on dog net
This one has to go on. No, don't i'm gonna spam if I do it again. All right, I got I got a uh
You probably noticed those tall things waddling around. Those are the human orbs
They take care of the boring stuff for us
You know things like cleaning up paying taxes doing math or robots. They love stuff like that. Show me one
I take a picture of a person
All right, I got one
Okay
They're good followers for that mix it up
Automatically randomizes your film after each photo. That's cool
That photo you posted is so cute. I think the only thing cute would be a dog wearing a hat
All right
All right. I gotta get a dog with a hat on
Got it done give me the fucking money. Whatever it is
18 followers
All right. Look, I know it doesn't sound very safe, but the scooters the dogs ride have ton of safety features
Those poor arcade games are trapped in the closed arcade sneak in there. Take a photo of an arcade machine
All right, let's go. All right, and a dog with a scooter
That's just now. This is just ab I just this is just abnormal a dog
Selling yogurt out of a food truck now. That's not that doesn't happen that way
That doesn't happen that way. I'm not a film saving that one. Yeah
Yeah, yeah
Yeah
Yeah. All right. I want to let's do this in a different style
Film shuffler. Should I just do the shuffler?
Yeah, and then i'm gonna post this on facebook. It's gonna be like
New ceo with like like two crying laughing faces
That's my truck by the way, like that's my business
Like the I own me I own the frog yogurt business and like I take I take this photo and I say new ceo
Well, wait, you're on a scooter
Be careful
This is stupid. I want to get you riding
Nope, not good enough
close maybe
Fucking influencer dog. All right. Here we go. I wanted you to be crossing the plane of the camera
Fuck turn around and go this way
That's the one
There it is got it. Yep. Perfect one 20 that was a lot of followers and I got three bucks
I can take a selfie with the dogs
You love you love thirds lower thirds. You love thirds
rule of thirds
I do i'm such a sucker for the rule of thirds. I swear to god. I am i'm such a sucker
All right, so the people that don't know what the fuck anyone's talking about here the rule of thirds rule of thirds, andy
That's fine. It's fucking looks great
rule of thirds means
Paint a grid in this square, right?
It's two lines down two lines horizontal and what you're doing is you're you're essentially matching
The where the cross points are
So for instance, you don't you know, oh that looks like shit. You know what I mean? But this
That looks fucking great
That looks cool
I love rule of thirds
Straight on camera pictures. What are you a fucking amateur?
I wouldn't want to do this, right?
I want to get you in the bottom left third and you in the top left third. Thank you very much
That is a great photo. This photo looks like absolute dog shit
This photo is a fucking award winner
This photo again terrible
This photo award-winning
I sorry I swore in front of you
I'm sorry you two
You should let your followers decide what's better
And rule of thirds works for other stuff too for instance, right?
You might think
What an amateur you might think that i'm trying to take a picture of these dogs and I am
And I am but you notice what's in the what's what is in the what is in the rule of thirds right now?
What is it?
What am I taking a photo of to make sure that this comes together? Well?
If you said the light posts you would be correct
And i'm talking both light posts
i'm talking about the one on the right as well
and
The pier goes out on the bottom
Lines it up in the top left
So I've got pictures of dogs in this photo, but I also have a really well juxtaposed photo
See this photo like this
Oh my god, delete it
That one you can put his profile picture
You explained that better than my photography class did
Well, all I said was like that's dog shit
I don't think like a professional
Like photo class is going to be like take your photo like this is dog shit like this is good
I feel like that would you probably wouldn't do that. Let's get a good landscape. That sounds good to me
Let's go ahead and take a look and I want you guys to tell me
Is this a dog shit photo or is this a beautiful photo and I want you i'm not going to tell you which one it is
I am going to take a picture
Of the of the boardwalk and the buildings and the buildings right? That's what i'm trying to get that was dog shit
You're right. How about now?
Oh, okay. All right, you guys are good
better
Still dog shit
How about this picture? I just missed a huge opportunity to take a cool photo
dog shit
How about now? Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait. I have to delete some stuff. How was that photo?
How was this picture?
Actually not great
It was it was okay, but this is the subject here. I'm gonna show you something else, too
So remember the subject is this is the subject here on the right. Look at that. Look at these
Look at that. Look at these. I spammed
I just need to stop moving
He's he's
That's not my fault
No, that's just cute
So also remember
What's going on with this bench?
Can anybody tell me what's going on with the bench?
Can somebody tell me why i'm filming it like this?
Somebody tell me why i'm doing it like that because the bench is the subject
The bench the corners are lining up with the thirds
Like this. Oh
No, that looks terrible
I don't why are you following my account if you don't want pictures dogs?
Oh, you're spamming me you you signed up to my dog. You're on dog net right now. You're on dog net
Who goes to dog net and gets annoyed at too many dog photos?
I'll see look at this one
This one has just speaks so many things
I don't fucking care from spamming you
Your mahali took all the sunflower photos for you. Don't act like you know anything about photography
I was there like directing
I was there directing
I was directing dude your dog net and your twitter are complete opposites
Why because
Don't wake the dog
Oh my god, you're so cool
Hold on. Do I have any do I have any new bangers for you guys?
Let's see. Let me find out if I have any new bangers for you guys that i've saved
Oh, I gotta talk. Okay. I gotta talk about this
But first of all
I don't know why I wrote this. Okay. This is a draft. This is the latest draft
Hey, I want to try something can everyone at exactly 3 pm pacific time monday
All collectively pray for me and send positive thoughts to me
I want to see if I feel good or something when it happens
You know what I mean? Like like everybody at like exactly 3 pm
It's just like everyone just like praises like says like oh my god like germa like we all like love you
And like I want to see if I like feel all right
You know what I mean? Like i'm just gonna sit there and be like like do I feel any different?
I wonder if like I feel like cool
I imagine like a cool feeling
I don't know
It's not an ego thing. I swear to god
I was just curious if like we got like 50 000 people all to like just in their rooms
Just sit there and like just think like a positive thing to me
Like would I feel what would happen?
No, not a cult leader. I stop it
No
I'm just saying like if everybody all collectively did it would I feel any different for like a minute?
What a narcissist no, I that you're missing the point
The point is I don't care if you actually believe this stuff. I just want to see
like
If like, I don't know what I see like a dove
With like a like a bird fly by
I don't know
everyone pray to me
Like not pray pray is the wrong word
the word i'm looking for is like
Like send like positive like messages in your head
Like towards me the spirit bomb
Um
Good manifest good vibes. Yes, that's what I mean not pray to me like i'm a fucking idol
I gotta talk I gotta tell you this story because it's fucking crazy
So at the airport
I came when I was if you didn't know I was I was I was on charlie's stream
Uh, I was out on the east coast
Hanging out with charlie. It was fun. It was awesome
Those guys are all incredible definitely gonna be doing some more shit with with that group because they're so fun
They're so funny and they're they're awesome to be around but so
I on the I got home, right? So
As I get home and i'm you know, i'm at the airport and I have to get into an elevator
I oh, yeah, i've got my land i'm in vegas. I gotta get in the elevator, right?
so
This elevator
Is a lot of people use this elevator in the vegas airport and it goes up and down it only goes one floor
and
I'm I have my bag
And i'm dragging my well, no, but not that's wrong with I had a backpack
So I had a backpack on didn't have very much luggage. So I was just walking around. No, this is not a bit
So I have to get in this elevator and I see there are people already in the elevator
And it's like okay. I'm i'm walking
I'm far enough away where I could probably make it the doors are open
There's only a few people in there and they start to close
And you know when somebody's coming, right?
Usually you like oh you put your arm out or something. Oh that person's there, but they couldn't see me
These people could not see me
so
Usually you've got to hold it for the person that you see coming because they're going to get into
So i'm walking nobody's doing that because nobody can see me
And I just i'm like, I think I can make this the doors are closing
And as I walk
I perfectly I have no fucking idea how this happened. I have never done this before
As i'm walking I get to I get in right when the doors are in the exact
Micro meter
Of space for me to get in and get crushed by the doors. I got fucking smushed
I've I just walked in and I was like I can I can make it I can make it
Yeah, and I went out and the both the doors went like like on my shoulders and it was like
and then
Honestly, I would have laughed right? Nobody's laughing. So they're just kind of looking at me like
Oh shit, I was like, oh
I said something I was I don't know. What the fuck did I say? I said like
Gotta be careful these don't I don't I said something like fucking stupid because it was embarrassing
and then
So the doors start to close and that's done with and then I hear oh you have room for one more and i'm like
Yeah, and the dude the door is closing again. And again, I I get my hand in there
Right when it is in the worst possible time the doors are closed
And it was like like closing on my hand
And it was like oh shit
The doors will open again
And like I should just let it close but like I don't know. I like I wanted to let this guy in
And this guy had a bunch of stuff
and I think the people that were in the elevator with me were just like
Like this motherfucker. I swear to god dude, just like there's the it goes one floor. It'll be back
so the guy rolls in all of his stuff and
I think I don't know. I was trying to be like, oh i'm like a weirdo. We're like, oh hey like
And I think I said like be careful those doors again, and then I kind of was like
I was like, huh?
And I'll tell you right now. I was the first person out of that fucking elevator
I was the first person out the elevator opened and I was just gone like just like have a good night
Yeah, the guy had like they got like at least four or five bags that he kept bringing in
But I just imagine man you sit there in an elevator
And you're just you've been traveling and just somebody just as the elevator is closing walks in and gets perfectly
To the to like the millimeter directly walking into the doorway right when it crushes both of his shoulders
And he goes like oh
That would live in my head forever. I would think I would laugh at that every day
I would laugh at that every single day. I think I would in the shower. It would just pop in
But anyways any more tweets?
I actually wrote it. I said walking into an this is a tweet walking into elevator. I got crushed like a cartoon sideways
Period audible. Ow
Okay
I don't know why I wrote this watching tv in my hotel room
I just saw two different lactative commercials for two completely different products in a row
Followed by a fried chicken commercial. What the fuck?
That's true. That was fucking weird
It was I was like what the fuck is going on?
Yeah
Release your tweets. No, these tweets are for me
This is a fucking really good one here
And I mean it is like one of the best and i'm going to post it
I am i'm not going to read that one. That one's too good to read
That one's going up eventually. It's too. It's like the best tweet i've ever written and you're not going to hear it until it's there
I use it like a diary. Yeah
No, i'm not going to tell you i'm not posting it now either. It's very specific. No, i'm not releasing them
All right. What was I doing?
I just gave myself like a bad headache. Fuck
I was supposed to chill today, but it was so I had to hear about it. It was so funny
I can't I can't post it. All right, I gotta let's slow down
I have to help clean up the skate park. See what you knew about the trash
There should be dumpsters around then send me a photo
I want to take a picture of this
Take it easy, man
Oh, I like that one
Oh my god
Oh, that's sad. All right
Hey germo
Oh, it's dev dev dev and chat. We put a lot of love into this game
Where i'm a huge germania fan and i'm thrilled to see you playing
Oh shit, really? That's cool
Try to get some food
Try and get some food from the vendors
Oh shit, really?
Hold on that would have been perfect. But the uh on the right
So can I buy stuff?
How do I buy the uh the frobert? How come you look like this? I don't know because i'm sick
Oh, wait, can I buy uh, can I buy from you?
Oh my god, I'm gonna like puke
What's going on here?
Actually, not a bad photo considering
Look at you're on a bike
Not bad
Okay. What was I doing?
Oh, I want to get the fisheye lens
Yep
Let's go
Stylish pack
All right fisheye lens
velvet
mocha
Let's do regular
Is this fisheye on? Well, this is not extreme fisheye
Okay, I need to clean up the skate park. I need third. I only need one more follower and i'm a fucking millionaire
Whatever it is
Look on the truck
Oh my god. All right
What?
You want this?
Oh, it has a face
Look over here
Look this way
How to survive a falling elevator
Here's the only way to survive a falling elevator
Most people think you should jump right before you hit the ground
However, it'll be difficult to jump while you're falling
That's me
Secondly, if you're falling at a speed 45 you should just lie. Just remember
You know what's so funny about the green screen stuff and i'm actually very happy about this
Like when you're looking for just like just royalty free shit
It actually can be kind of hard
It can be kind of annoying
so i'm actually kind of happy that like people can use it whether it's like a corporate video or any like
Project whatever like those those green screen
pieces of footage
That you could just use them, right? I i'm not gonna sue you. I'm just telling you right?
Uh, that's actually I like seeing that that's funny. That's really funny though
Show it
Okay. Well, hold on
It's like me jumping
Uh, hold on. Let me put this in here
He's against question three. So is she?
and labor unions too
Crime is skyrocketing
Okay, let me put this on
Here's the only way to survive a falling elevator
Most people think you should jump right that's what I thought you hit the ground
However, it'll be difficult to jump while you're falling and secondly if you're falling at a speed of 50 miles per hour
And you jump five miles per hour into the air
You're still gonna hit the ground at 45 miles per hour
Now instead of jumping you should just lie flat on your back
This way the impact is spread equally throughout your whole body
But just remember with today's modern safety features your chances of dying are about one in 10 million
I love that jump too. It's like that's that's a very extreme jump
People wouldn't jump like this
Jump while however, it'll be difficult. However, it'll be difficult
Uh, I love it. No, but that's what I mean though. I it's that's I like that
Getting like royalty free shit
Is like it's just so it's a it's a pain in the ass
There's apparently more in that video
Okay, that's cool
Hey educational too. Is it just yeah, would you can I just spam this?
Oh
Yeah smart
All right. I'm gonna bring uh, this one. This is probably pineapple. Oh my god
I want to dole whip so bad
Oh my god
When we were at disney
Probably eight fucking seven of these
I want it so bad. All right. Wait, I want the yogurt
Wait tennis ball
Go get it. Oh you you're into it. All right
Go catch
Nice catch
You don't know what dole whip is it's pineapple ice cream. It's pineapple soft serve
It just nobody does it
It's pineapple ice cream pineapple soft serve
Why do why is it only at fucking disney?
Yuck ban that person. I'm not even kidding. I want you to ban them for at least a minute
Make your own. Yeah, but it's pain in the ass
Make my own ice cream
All right. What do I got here? I need 30 followers. I'm just gonna post some photos
I love your photos, but wait until tomorrow. All right, fine. Uh, i'm gonna leave the area
Wait, I need to save the photos
Some of these are really good. I don't want to get rid of. Oh, yeah
Some of these are gonna be huge on dognet
Okay, mango dole. Yeah, that one's good, too
All right. Some of these would be big. What about what's the shop? All right, what's the best disney ride?
I'm gonna tell you right now
I actually don't even care about the rides
I'm gonna give you a tip a disney and any theme park tip really especially like a disney place
I I just kind of like looking at stuff
I like going to the shops and eating the food and walking around and looking at all the statues and stuff
The rides they're good. I mean prior to the caribbean ride is pretty pretty pog right at least at disney land
But I don't know. I don't sitting in
The line and usually waiting sometimes like an hour to get on the ride
I i've just i'm so
I just hate it
Yeah, I would rather just be an npc
No, that's that's fair. It is
No, you're that's right. I'd rather just be an npc
disney loves
germa customers
Wait, this is weird. Hold on
Jesus
That was a good one. I actually think this one's gonna be this one's gonna go really hard on dognet
Of course it is got it 30 followers. Wait, what I heard there's some killer waves
Oh, it's a new day. So it's okay
Let's go to the boardwalk
Uh, no, I okay. So here here's here's my reasoning
When you walk when you walk around and you look at how long some of these rides take to get on
Oh, yeah, the the haunted mansion
80 minutes
Prior to the caribbean 40 to 50 minutes
Oh, this ride's about 40 minutes to wait and and the rides are two to four minutes long
You are deleting
Sometimes four plus to five plus hours per day
waiting in line
I would rather
Pick what are you doing?
I can't read this
What's your favorite topping for mac and cheese ass because i'm preparing my 40th birthday party and it's gonna be germa themed
Then I want to serve mac and cheese. I want to make sure it's it's germtastic enough for my guests to enjoy
I already have all the decorations ready. They're all your face and this this this is like a blocked word
This literally is like a a deleted word. I can't I don't even I don't know what it says
I'm also giving out little uh plush dachshunds. They're auto. We're going to watch every germa rumble in the dollhouse dream
That's my favorite, uh breadcrumbs
Bread crumbs, it's easy. Anything else is weird
bread crumbs
boring
Oh, it said butthole
Anyways, um, so here's my here's my reasoning for this
I would rather pick one or two things that I want to do
And go do it they introduced this new thing and I am sorry, but it sucks
It's like the genie plus
It's the new fast pass, but it's just like a confusing fucking mess
I just
Just like what the fuck is this?
So, I don't know. I don't think we even used it
It was just like oh you have to decide what ride you want to go on
When you get there and you have to be in the park and then plan your day
You're like you like plan your day
around the genie plus and I don't
What the fuck are you talking about?
but
Uh, so waiting in in line for rides you pick the one or two per day that you want to do
And you eat six doll whips and puke when you get back to the fucking hotel room
And walk around and look at all the stuff
Don't actually eat six doll whips. Oh, okay. I'm I gotta tell you I
Paul are you in the chat holly?
Was it three?
How many when we were there that night that we were there did I have two or three?
Was it three doll whips over the course of like four or five hours?
How many did I eat?
Oh, you also helped eat mine too
Like three and a half four
Yeah, and guess what? It was great walked around ate doll whip
and
looked at all like the
shops and was it npc for a little while
rode pirates of the caribbean
and
You know, all right something about disneyland that you guys this is fucking hilarious
So, uh the winnie the pooh ride at disneyland
Is always a zero minute wait always zero
Zero
It's you could just go on it whenever you want
It is the shittiest ride at the park, but it's who cares
I rode that
It's not even that bad either
Okay, we got
Got the surfing dog
How do I sneak into the arcade?
Also like in line
for the winnie the pooh ride
I remember just being like just being holly. I'm just being like, oh, hey ma'am. So yeah, i'm glad we got into this line
Yeah, it's good that we use the genie plus on this like i've this is always swarmed. Just like talk is saying it
You just I can feel the eye rolls
All right. Let me play the game
All right old arcade
Oh my god, disneyland also has these cream cheese filled pretzels. Holy shit. I don't want to tell anybody about this
I don't want to tell anybody because then because then you'll all go get it and I won't be able to get it anymore
Yeah, there's like one place
Okay, there's one place in disneyland that you can they move it around. It's a secret. Fuck. I just told you the secret i'm an idiot
This is actually like a disneyland secret and I just fucking told you and I feel like an idiot now
It's like now the line is going to be long
They have a cream cheese filled pretzel and it's literally one of the best things i've ever eaten in my entire life
And I don't even know where it is because they change where it is every single day
The cream cheese mickey mouse pretzel is the best thing in the world. Yeah
and great
Now we're gonna go back to disneyland and that line's gonna be an hour fucking long
And they're all gonna be sitting there talking about each other talking to each other. Oh, man, you know, this is a secret
Don't tell anybody this it's like I
I fucking told you
how
How do I get into the arcade?
Around the back sneak into the arcade
How do I get in here? Yeah, I go to disney for the food
That's so funny. I'm really the guy in roller coaster tycoon that walks in pays the the and you make the fee to get in
Expensive i'm the one that walks in has a bunch of money in my pocket. I walk around buy a pretzel and leave
How'd you get up here?
Oh
This is the
What the fuck how do I get into the arcade?
Yeah, cream cheese pretzel is one of the best things at disney
Without a doubt
How do I get in here?
No, help. I figured it would've been on the roof
Uh, I do have to get that so i'm gonna go back
Double jump in this game. That's kind of insane
All right arcade. So well, come on. There's got to be a way to get in here
Right like back here
If I saw somebody do that on the boardwalk, I would fucking freak out
Okay
Sports and dogs what's not to love. I have a photo request. Give me a pic of two dogs playing with a disc
I've heard it. This is a common activity. Okay
The disc right there
You're gonna go get it
Ready somebody get it
There it is
There it is 100 percent
Why is your face in italics today?
Because I have a crooked face
Get over it
All right, submit a photo
The dog has to be centered in the photograph and facing the camera for a photo to be considered professional quality
That's not the one I wanted to give this photo is bad
What about the rule of thirds?
I didn't want to submit this one
Oh, I got the selfie device
Selfie mode
Wait, what i'm the camera
Okay, that just I was so confused
I thought the camera was floating in front of my face, but that this is weird. All right
This thing is scary
All right, 40 followers
Finally some good non-dog content. I really like that
Okay, help clean up the skate park
Cool. Let's turn that selfie off
This game's cute. I like it
Okay, so now
Clean up the skate park
skate park
Where's that?
Why does he always address holly like a spirit in his house?
holly
You can hear me
Hello, germ. My wife's been preparing a birthday. All right, just delete that
Okay. Now that I think about like pretzels and shit
I if it was like a
I found out I got it
I'm trying to think of like a food item that I would present to the aliens
When they landed like we had to come together and be like this is the thing that is the best thing in all of humanity
This is the greatest food
This is the greatest thing that we could possibly do to eat
Because they're going to judge us on it
It would be a hot pretzel
And I think that we would the planet would be spared
It would be a hot
crispy
Soft on the inside a hot huge pretzel salt
a hot thing of like beer cheese
And honey mustard and it would and they would they would be
It would be fine. I think it's a single greatest food invention of all humanity
I think uh, that's like the the greatest thing i've ever had in my life
fuck beer cheese
Or you know, we could just like cheddar or something just cheese like hot cheese
Okay
Arcade's open now. Wait, what can I play a game?
If I were the alien i'd leave if the people that are writing gross we're talking about like a hot pretzel
You you you're doing like a troll face in real life
I don't think there's a human on earth
I don't think there's a person that's alive on earth right now
that
Doesn't but does not like
Like I would turn down a hot pretzel
I don't I can't imagine anybody would ever do that
If you're hungry and you know, I've got snacks and I go. Hey, I got hot pretzels. You'd be like what? Oh, okay. Nice
Really nice. Yes
Like if I said, oh, yeah, i've got yogurt
I mean some of you might be like, oh nice, but a lot of you might be like, yeah
Not really into that
If a hot pretzel everybody would I don't think anybody doesn't like that pretzels taste like ass. I just they just they don't
put frog in here
I'm posting this one pretzels demonstrate our advance in agriculture and cultivation. That's true
That actually is true. I mean it would be but okay. So I think when he said pizza
I don't know. I've had some really bad pizza before
And it's definitely I don't think I would want to give the aliens something that's gonna give them diarrhea
Right. So anything else that you could think of?
Pretzels not going to give you diarrhea
But like a really bad pizza might because of grease and stuff
Or like burger like we wouldn't want to give the aliens burger king because what if they have diarrhea feel like why do they eat this?
That was a cool photo where's the skate park?
Uh-huh
Oh here it is. Okay, clean up the trash dumpster over here somewhere
You wouldn't want to feed the alien something that was going to give it a gastric upset
Pretzels are plain enough
And but they wouldn't upset your stomach or anything
No, I would not give the aliens water burger. It's too much
Think about it an alien has not had like fucking pizza grease before
It's gonna taste it and it's probably gonna shit its pants
Taco Bell
But you would give them beer cheese. No, I didn't say I was gonna give the aliens beer cheese
I said I would that I would prefer beer cheese with that
What if the aliens can't process the um, I think I cleaned it up, right? This is good
Oh, is it more trash?
Oh, hello
um
Yeah, you'd have to be what's plain enough
That but is no because i'm telling you what if aliens probably eat
We don't know what their digestive tract is like
They might not be able to handle like a cheeseburger
Banana, oh, that's boring though
a baked potato
That's like kind of plain
Crisp apple actually, you know what? That might be the that might be the one
I don't think you can get yeah, like just like a fresh apple
You don't start the aliens with the cheesy goatee to crunch
The alien would be like take a bite out of it
Cheesy goatee to crunch. Okay. Let's see. This is what you are here giving us for food
And it's you said the best that you okay
Yeah
They're gonna like shit and then they're gonna take their laser gun out and point it at you and like
Liquidate you and then that starts the fucking war because they're gonna think you poisoned them
Way too much fat too much grease, right and I trust me. I love these things
Spicy ranch would take them out
Apple would be probably fine. Whoa
Give him a ghost pepper. They would think they would see that as an act of war is what you don't understand
They would think that this was poison and you were trying to like kill one of their alien ambassadors
It's an act of war
Give them one single talkie
Oh, you need a photo. Okay
Skate park is now open
Of course
Oh
That looks like it hurt
Holy shit. Hold on
I mean I got it and what about fluids too? All right
So we figured out like an apple would probably the best thing for the to give them first
Would it be just water?
I feel like water is not impressive though
Give him a mountain dew. No, that's all that would also be like it like an act of war. I think it'd be like
some kind of tea
milk
Maybe like a lemonade actually that might be look strawberry. What'd you say?
Strawberry banana smoothie actually that might be a good one
You put a red bull
They're not used to caffeine
They don't know what caffeine is and it's like they take one sip of the red bull. They got oh sort of tart
What do you call this again?
Their fucking heads explode
It has to we have to be careful. I gotta go rest right
sour warheads
No as an act of war
I actually like this one a lot. What do you think the aliens would give us?
I don't know
See, I there's no way to know because I don't know. I don't have any of their experiences. Okay gain 150 followers
The dogs drive cars
Is there a dog driving this car?
Holy shit. Oh my god
Oh
Most it's a dog
dog net
Right before I got run over
I'm the bowling seller. I need a good photo of our new location. Okay
and
This unit loves dogs, but wonders if it could love ducks
a photo of a duck
Safety records are lacking. We need a photo of a dog with a fire hydrant. I already have one. Oh, I don't
Okay, so I need a photo of a duck a photo of the shop
Down here, what if we give the aliens edibles? No, that's an act of war
That's cute. Okay, is this the store?
Nice
And 150 followers
Can I buy a bone?
Do you want one? Who wants a bone? Here. I'm trying to put i'm trying to get a funny photo where the oh
Well, that's funny. We could make that no
Anything where the alien would feel different?
Would be
A why did you what did you what did you what do you what why do I feel like this?
And then that's when they would start shooting us with lasers
Yeah, i'm posting this one just give him gas station sushi just give him one single olive
I'm telling you a hot pretzel is the way to go
All right photo of a duck
I'm sitting by the water maybe
dog with a fire hydrant
Oh, i'm gonna take a picture of a stocks chart or something noodles actually might be a big deal
just noodles
right feels like like a
Like a cup noodle like instant ramen. Yeah, I think instant ramen might be a good one to put in there
one apple
instant ramen
Because because like cup noodle and the instant ramen stuff
Is very very palatable. It's not
It just tastes nice
It just tastes nice. It's like a broth right with the noodles
We don't want to freak them out
I mean that was cool
That was fun
good job
spaghetti
I don't know. I think the tomato sauce would be a little would be like an active war
Grilled chicken
Yeah
just grilled seared
Chicken breast sliced a grilled cheese grilled cheese might be pretty good. Yeah
You got to think of stuff that is very very
Palatable chicken nuggets, maybe
honestly
It's what it's like the little kid diet is what we're gonna give to aliens
mac and cheese
apples
chicken nuggets
Like noodles
But it's but that's why though, right?
Like little kids can sometimes be really picky eaters
And those are all very very plain very palatable
I can dress up the dogs
Cheese strings. Yep
Literally anything from this planet would be poison to aliens. I don't think so
takes a lens
Can I buy another lens?
I need uh, this is if there's other lenses
Okay, let's get the uh, where's this weird thing?
Here
The charts with the up and down lines i've lost them this should be on an easel near a picnic bench
That doesn't give me very much
Watch out. Why am I moving in real life? It's like a cute dog game
This is the inception music
You did such a good job painting that painting. Here's a delicious shit for you. That's a good one
This one's going on dognet
Is this like me branching out to other animals
Like oh, I know stog net but like
Maybe taking pictures of birds now as well
That one was popular. I like this one. All right, so now
Find the business cat's chart
There's a niche
duck community
What about music?
Would you introduce breakcore to aliens? No, I think I would start with a snare drum
I would just get this into a room
Like okay here like everyone relax. We're all relaxing. I'm just hanging out
There's a there's a drum in here one snare drum
And there's two of us in the room two of the aliens and I want to show you what let's show you this
just watch ready like
And they'll they're gonna put the back against the wall and they're gonna be fucking terrified and
I mean just very slow
and i'll be like you you do too, right like
See kinetic energy
I don't think you go full on a band
No
And not electric guitar either
It's one snare drum
And then maybe a flute
just like
That's it and then just let's just relax because it's gonna be a lot for them
And then I say you
pop hop hop
You that and they go oh
Oh
And then I go
And then it's that's music that's what we call music
And then you can give them a cd of fucking your favorite atlantis more set songs. You know what I mean?
Then you give them a cd of all the blink 182 albums you have
And then they'll figure it out, right?
Then you give them the slipknot album
Okay, so where I gotta find a park bench
Picnic bench now, that's one big hydrant
Now all you guys that want to have
big band
No, there's too many instruments. It's like
Like there's too many sounds that they've never heard before
You guys want to have a full drum set a saxophone a flute a cello player
Two electric guitars a piano they would you they wouldn't be able to handle it
You got to start very slow
At this that is a cool picture
Maybe some lounge jazz. Uh, yeah, that's what I would go to next
It's very very light smooth jazz
I'm talking like the the hey Arnold background music. That's the kind of stuff that I would level them up to
Just that kind of like
I can't find this
A picnic bench would be like in the park. I guess that's what I think
I mean, this is a picnic bench and there is a cheeseburger here
They mastered space travel, but they can't handle a drum set
cheeseburg people happy
You want a cheeseburger?
No
Oh a cheeseburger
What that's a huge stick wow, no watch out watch out that is the biggest stick i've ever seen nice job
Heisenberg
Dog is this
Oh is a puppy. Okay
Wow, hold on that's a big stick i'm saving this one
All right. Now it's spam
I this is my favorite one. I think so far
You look really angular. I know
It's because I flipped the my face is going like like this because I flipped the camera horizontally
Uh, I want to go
Wait, this is kind of cool
Oh, they're watching perfect opportunity to get an awesome cool photo here ready
I need to go lower
I need a wider lens. I love wide angle lenses
How do we feel about this one? Now? That is what I would call
an unbelievably good photo
This is your last photo for today spam, but unfollow me then fuck off
Wait, stay right there. Stay right there. Stay right there. Stay right there
Stay right there. Don't move
Don't move stay right there. Stay right there. Stay right there
Stay right there. Stay right there
Stay right there. Stay right there. Stay right there. Stay right there. Got it
Pick this one apart
This is not dog shit. Uh, I have to like go home
But let me I gotta find this
Painting whatever it is
How do I get the new camera parts?
Have you ever played the new spider-man games? Um, I streamed the
The new spider-man game that came out. It was ps4 exclusive
Like the spider-man game. I didn't play the the new ps5 one though that I have ps5
Yeah, five years ago
Miles morales one is really good. It looks it it looks good, but I have to get a ps5
I have to be i'm gonna tell you something right now
Like every time I want like is every time I want to get a ps5. I just can't
It's on pc
Oh, i'll be really really honest. I know if some of you I don't want to be like, oh, it's the console war. Here we go
What's even on ps5?
Besides demon souls, which is the reason to buy the console, right?
What's on ps5? That's like an exclusive that's worth getting the console for
Because i'll be very very completely upfront. I have to be incredibly honest with you
the xbox game pass
Is actually kind of fucking unbeatable. It's actually amazing
Like I have found so many games through game pass just because they're ready to play they're right there
and
80 of them, you don't even have to install them. You just play them in the cloud
i'm being dead serious about that
and
Games like service type shit like that. I'm not bullshit. Yeah, I wouldn't bullshit
The games as a service type stuff
think about like the switch like the oh we're gonna release games, uh, like the
The snes and n64 type shit. Yeah, maybe once every two fucking months. You'll see something
X there are at least three to five new games on game pass. It feels like every couple fucking weeks
I'm dead serious
They load that shit up all the time. It's actually awesome
He's bullshitting us. No, i'm tell I just told you I wasn't
Can you play dark messiah might magic? I already screamed it. The game is amazing. All right. Where is this stupid thing?
I have to find this this picnic bench
This person has like stocks all over it
I shouldn't have done that into the street
They remove them too, don't they?
So games will cycle through it
um
They have I think like a hundred something games that are always getting kind of cycled through
But they're there for long enough where you can just play them. I actually think you I think you can install some of them, too
There are a few constraints. Yeah
Yeah, the okay playstation now
was
garbage
It was garbage. I remember trying to use it
It didn't fucking work
I got disconnected like 70 percent of the time when I used it. It was trash
It was absolute trash and i'm I really hate to say that because I like sony's games and I like I like playstation
this xbox, um cloud service
Is like everything that stadia wanted to be and it just works and it's better in every conceivable way every conceivable way
Is it better now?
When I tried to use it a few years ago, it was like this is like why i'm even trying
All right. I'm just gonna reset
It's better now copium. It might be it was bad before i'm trying to play red dead redemption
I think oh my god. I'm getting a flashback
You guys remember when I told you about that time when I was like screaming in the car
And I like forgot my credit card
Like I went to like walmart or something and I forgot my credit card
I I couldn't get the game to run on the xbox or something
And I was like screaming going back and forth in the car, right?
And then I tried to just I tried just to play it on ps now and it just disconnected every 15 seconds
Then I just turned the stream off
That might have been the worst stream like ever. That's probably the worst stream i've ever done
Yeah, 100
It was so awful. It was just so painful. Everything was awful. Everything sucked that day
It was just so bad
Oh, I know what that is
It was your first collab with vinny too. That's right
different artists today
Uh, two dogs with bones
dog playing in the playground
And find the business cat. All right, the playgrounds over here
Actually, I can buy the bones
playtime activities
This is a playtime activity two dogs with bones
Okay, so I need to get some bones
Come over here thought that was a chicken. All right, let's get the bones over here
Okay, there's one and you want one too look over here snowflake snowflake snowflake look over here snowflake
85 followers picnic bench. Okay. Is this a picnic bench?
Or is a picnic bench a picnic table?
This is like a picnic
Bench a picnic table is a picnic table, right?
All right, I just need followers now, what's this?
Oh doll web
Should I post the stocks?
How long did it take me to line this up? Not long at all
All right 85
All right, there's a hidden envelope. I love the flip
Do you guys remember those little dog toys?
They were kind of scary
Where it was a little dog was it was it looked like a stuffed animal, but it was hard
And it was like
And then this thing
Went snap and did a full backflip. It was kind of terrifying
I'm just i'm bringing myself back to an era with a bunch of weird
animal like mechanical toys like that
Do you remember there was like the little gopher or the like a ferret?
There was a ball and it just kind of rolled around with the ball
Yeah, and they would always be in this little playpen at the mall
There was a store
And in the front of the store was like a little it probably was about chest high
And it was a circle area that they put all this shit in
They put two flipping dogs three ferret balls two like cat things
And they would always fall out. They would always flip out of the thing and always fall out of the thing
I wonder how hard it would be to track one of those down
They were violent
Hamsters
Yeah
They still sell those at flea markets and you could hear it across the mall. Yes, you really could
You could you would be
60 meters you'd be a hundred meters away
and all you would hear would be like
Oh
That's all you could hear I completely forgot that you could actually hear it
How much is a meter?
a meter is
A yard is three feet
a meter
One yard is three feet
So that means a meter
is two
Point two pounds. That's a kilo
Um
a meter is
Two is I don't know one yard is three feet
2.2 pounds is one kilogram
Um, and a meter is exactly
I don't know three and a half feet three point two feet. I need 150 followers, right? I'm spamming but I don't care
3.2 feet. So what's why do we use yard then? Oh wait yard is yard. Um
Dumb dope american stuff his yard
Oh, no, he's american
He's american stupid idiot, right?
What the hell?
Hold on. He's pissed
Get out of the way
You're spilling it everywhere
They are driving the cars. That's so weird
What is freezing in celsius zero
Ask me more of these. Um, that's fine
How many meters in a kilometer?
I don't what you don't even know that
Yeah, okay. I don't know meters to kilometers. I could dodge a fucking battle axe
Who gives a shit?
I don't think you guys understand like who cares
You don't know what a meter to kilometers to then to uh, micro meters
Uh, then uh do that deduce that to yards. No, but I could dodge a battle axe and uh, you can't
And i'll prove it to you
It's in the name
kilobyte
What is what is kilo what is kilo what is that some what is what is that some what is that?
What is kilo? What is kilo? What is it?
A thousand. Yeah, what is it though?
What is it latin?
Yeah, it was latin. I don't know some greek god's fucking name. So what?
Yes, the greek god kilometer the prefix kilo is derived from the greek word
Helio meaning a thousand. Yeah, uh, uh-huh
Oh, no, I didn't know that's what it was
I if I took more than one second, i'm playing a video game and i'm talking about aliens eating pretzels. Okay?
i'm
I'm busy. I don't have time to think about how what a kilometer is what a what a fucked up question
Like imagine you sitting there
Okay, imagine you're sitting there and somebody just kind of walks up to you busy. I'm just like hey
What's kilometer?
It's like I don't know frank fucking leave me alone. Like i'm busy
I'd be like, what are you asking of how what how much is it?
What is kilo greek? Is that what you're asking?
What do you what question why you want? How much is a kilometer frank? It's a distance of some kind
You're a himbo
Fine. I need I want to buy this new stuff. You are a substitute teacher. You don't guys I don't need to have
I don't substitute teaching was
Essentially me like just keeping the classroom
In order it wasn't like oh by the way students a kilometer is a thousand kilometers
And a millimeter is a million. No, it was just a I honestly was
It was just just to make sure like the students behaved
millicenti
One one thousand one one hundred. Yeah, I know
Do you think I need to know that for this?
Do I need to know what a millimeter?
To ounces is
And fuck everybody
Fuck everybody
You definitely still type into google. Um
Ounces to uh to liters everybody does don't even don't even pretend don't pretend
You still type google ounces to liters, um conversion
And you type it in and because you don't know
Don't even tell me
Don't even tell me you don't do that. I don't believe it
What's an ounce
He looks so cute
All right. I gotta uh leave the i'm gonna go to this other there's other quests in the other area
The different measurement units, dude
Cognitive dissonance danny
All metric is easy. It's just times 10. Yo heard tony bark is in town. I'm really busy trying to stop a different
Uh skate park from getting demolished
Can you give me a shot of him shredding the pipe?
Okay, the old arcade is open again haven't heard if it's getting used though. Can you find out for me?
It's definitely getting used. Take a look
Place is bumping
Oh close up of a dog at the arcade looks pretty good. That's a good photo. What's your favorite photo?
Um
That one's better
Hey kid, you got some real talent. I can see that but your photos they're severely lacking in the fear department
Unleash me from the vending machine. I can show you a new world of expression. All I have to do is watch
Okay, what oh there's tony bark, all right, I gotta get him
Doing the thing half of photography is just waiting
Got it
Uh, okay, there's new stuff in the
Wait, what's wrong? What's wrong?
Didn't I get it? Oh, that's I don't like that's sad
Oh, no
um
Tony said you're gonna play frog detective not today
I'm very sick
Well, not very sick
It's okay
Wait, where'd you go?
I want to make sure you know that it's okay. Where are you? Oh, it's okay. Don't worry
Um, i'm like, oh i'm very sick. No i'm
I'm sick
I have like a sinus cold. I don't know what's going on. I don't know what's happening
I have a bunch of pressure here
My throat's all fucked up
And my ears are popped
so
Um, I wanted to stream though. I didn't want to just not stream
Because I feel like i've been away from the computer for a while wanted to at least hang out for a bit
I tested for covid already a few times. So
It is not covid
But I don't know maybe who knows i'll test again tomorrow or tonight
Uh, if I get worse then I i'm just gonna stream tomorrow, but we'll see
I need more. I need 150 followers
It could be a different virus
Sync up
I'm all right. I'm good
I just took I feel actually okay right now because i've been taking this um
Um
This like
Tylenol cold and flu thing
Essentially, it just kind of pumping myself up
It's like the cold medicine
Um, i'll be fine though. Don't worry
It's it's just literally just thick probably a cold
But if I change this by tomorrow, I'll let you know
all right, I need
100 I just need 150 followers
I'm 35. They like that one plus three
Oh
There it is to the moon
We love the moon
I unlocked the moon
One inch is about two and a half centimeters. So it's not a huge difference
You know, it's kind of funny. I've talked so much shit about how how there should be a standard
buttons on all controllers
Because remember I said oh pressing a
Is annoying because if I press a on an xbox i'm actually pressing b
on a nintendo
or
you know, um like x on a
playstation
Make them all the same right and then we don't have to worry about it
Oh, yeah, I did say get congress involved
I distinctly remember what you're talking about
I like screamed that too
That was was that during what what stream was that?
Yeah, I was I was like fucking pissed
I was really pissed off
It was super monkey ball. Oh, yeah
Whatever. Oh, there's new items
You know, just somebody on like, um
What is it like c what's that that government political kind of like congress channel
Somebody's up there with like a bunch of papers. I got this is I want to show you
We need to standardize
C-span. Yeah, we need to stay. I have this is me. I'm putting for the bill
uh
standardized game controller
I'm getting real sick and tired of pressing b when I want to press a
My fellow friends on the other side of the aisle seem to not care about that
They want to keep it. So when you press x
Might accidentally be pressing b
They always do that and it's so fucking annoying
I hate when they do that that okay
So if it's a democrat talking about a republican or republican talking about a democrat, they always go
See my friends on the other side of the aisle
Stop stop that
Uh, my friends over there. Oh, you see my friends over there
like all right, like
friend like come on
politics, baby
I can't laugh right now
My evil foes
I don't even think that would be like kind of funny though
I feel like I would be more I feel okay if all of a sudden if like one of the democrats was just like
now
my
Evil foes on the other side of the aisle there. I feel he'd be like that's funny
He kind of got me there like I've
That's funny
my arch nemesis
my worst enemies
I feel like that would make one of those like old motherfuckers laugh and then they'd sign your bill
You see senator senator davidson over there senator stevenson
You know one of my true enemies and then they they cut to him and he's like
I'll sign it now. I'll sign it
Those fuckers over there
All right. I'm i'm doing the build the minecraft house and take it down over and over again
Um, I just need to go to the machine
vending machine
There's one over here nice gameplay
Whoa
earthy pack
extra film
artsy pack
Tricky camera part focus lens. Ooh, okay
zoom lens
flash bulb film
Okay
Arcade
Whoa?
alien
cmyk
Predator vision don't you just wish that like on halloween?
No, one of those like senators is in like a banana costume
You know what I mean? This gets up there and just like let me tell you you think might think I look ridiculous
But my friends on the other side of the aisle
They're the ridiculous ones
I you know, I feel like I feel like I would be pretty good in like congress. I feel like I would I could do it
I think I would be able to do it
Where's the pixel one?
No, you couldn't
ooh
What is this face? Oh, what did I just do? I just flash banged him. What i'm so sorry. I didn't mean to do that
Oh my god, i'm so sorry
My friends on the other side of the aisle over there
All right. Let me leave here
You would never get elected. I don't think I would can I keep going this way new requests?
You know that tire swinging is considered an extreme sport. I think I know where that is
I need a pixel lens
I don't think I have that I have arcade
No, I don't think I have it
focus lens
Oh depth of field
That was pretty that's actually good
I like that one
longest bit
Taking more than five minutes
She's running for president
Talking to tire swing you are where were you? There you are. No rule of thirds, andy
Hey, this one's just for fun
Oh, I think that's a good photo
There are new rare items in the shop
Rare yeah, it's funny. I love depth of field, but I hate depth of field in video games
The first thing that I do I always just turn off every single
thing in the video settings
Motion blur depth of field dramatic abrasion. They all go off
Oh, okay, that's cool
There's the pixel lens, okay pixel lens
on a chroma film
Candy shop
Blair lens. All right. These are I need this one. How do I get more dog bucks?
Okay, I need to scare four dogs or more with the vacuum cleaner
No, they're playing I don't want to do that
somewhere else
You got you you're operating heavy machinery. I don't want to do that here
It's only two
Why are you playing with a landmine?
um
Has to be four dogs get scared by it. You just don't even care
Oh now you don't
Okay
I need another one. Oh, hold on shit. It's only three
Like I know I have the solution right here. Here we go. Ready?
Oh, they're not okay. Wait shit. That's four, right?
There it is two followers
Stop
I'm good. All right turn this up
And then it's okay, don't worry
It's okay
There we go. Oh my god
So cute
Is that a greyhound?
Greyhounds are so cute. Oh, is it a corgi? How much is this?
All right. I need two more dog bucks
Can we have the auto voice, please?
um
I need to see auto. I can't just do it. None of these are auto
It kind of looks it. No, it doesn't. I almost did it. You heard it. It was coming out
That was not auto
Uh, I need one more. All right, let's get the other lens
Auto
Okay, I can buy the uh
Are you all right? She's gonna buy a car
Send you the picture
No, I already told you why I don't do that
Get a picture of a dog from the rooftop. Okay
They're just kind of hanging out over there
Expensive dinner
I need the zoom lens
The mountainous nature park is open now. Ooh
cool
Uh, I do want to buy the pixel lens
Prima, you really tried to look pretty today, didn't you?
um
I woke up
maybe
Like maybe 40 minutes before the stream started
I didn't even know if I was gonna stream because I was like I feel like so terrible
And then I took some talent on I was like, all right, let's go I was not trying to look good
Why you think I look good today?
He's trying to make it seem like it's effortless
Stop doing that
Pixel lens this looks like shit
Pixel lens or is this a um
Like a 160p stream photo of a biking. Oh a dog on a bike. It's kind of cool looking
All right dog on a bike
Found one. All right. Where's my money? Here it is
All right. Let's try the other area
Rocket ship. How do I go to that one? Oh, it's the moon the actual moon
Oh, I beat the game
We went to the moon
Well, I I this other stuff to do
I played dark souls. No
Today had to be a chill day
I'm not done. I want to fly. I want to do the other thing. Wait, it's not over
I think they were just saying like thanks for playing
Oh, all right
It's like an alien
Three moon dogs in the earth. Can you show me what a real flying saucer looks like? I want every dog on earth
Okay, I wanted to take a picture of earth. Where's earth? Is that earth?
The actual gravity that's funny a tiny flying saucer. You can take photos with mini ufo. Wait, what?
Oh, it's like a drone
That's cool
Picture of the dino
I feel like if you posted this to dognet, you should get way more than four likes on this
Like i'm on the moon, man. I'm on the moon
Like bro, i'm on the moon
I think this deserves at least a thousand likes
This is actually a cool dogless pic. I'm more interested in close-up shots of dog outfits
Didn't like it
Okay
Yes the sun
Hey, you gave me a like that's all I care about even if you're wrong
You can be completely wrong. That's fine
All right. What do they have to say about this?
It's refreshing to see a no a no dog photo. I'm more interested in close-up of dogs outfits
I can't believe you aren't more famous
zoom
Though these are all my fans
It's mostly art kids
We made extraterrestrial contact and they come in peace
And an astronaut and an alien dog just hanging out. Okay, that's the flying saucer, right?
Oh pixel lens shit
What that's a flying saucer, isn't it?
Can you show me what a real flying saucer looks like be sure to use the pixel lens
That's a good photo of a flying saucer. Oh, wait turn around. That's like a satellite. What's that like a sled?
All right, what's the flying saucer?
All right. I need an alien and astronaut. This song is really good and they have to be happy
I mean, this is one right here
It's an alien dog, right?
That counts, right?
Do you hear that?
Did I have a gatorade sitting on my desk here and it just popped it went boom
I don't know. I have no idea why it was weird 200 followers. Nice
A challenge take a really good photo using film from the stylish pack. Okay, stylish pack was like
Arcade, right? Why not use the alien one bar out film pack. No stylist. There we go. How about mocha?
We'll do
focus lens
Wait, actually
That kind of cool, right? That's pretty cool
How to focus on purpose
alien interesting staring
creepy
funky
Three moon dogs in the earth. All right
They're gonna line this up
That's kind of cool looking
You're doing something cool right now
Ah, it's like a shitty photo, but it's all right
Three dogs in the frame and the earth
That's actually not bad could have moved it a little bit to the left. I'm going to nice lock screen
Actually pretty good lock screen
Okay, why is there a gas station on the moon? See you later. That was radical. Nice job. That was a good trick
All right. Let me check out the other area
Oh you unlock it daytime and nighttime and stuff. This is a cool area
It's beautiful scenery
I like that
Let's get a good one of these. You know what I mean? What do you think about this photo?
How do you feel about this one?
Dog shit or good?
Probably could have zoomed in a little more
All right. What do you want? What do you got objectives here?
Any dog and bird will do but the dog needs to look like it really loves being there
Oh, there's birds. Okay a picture of bird
I feel like this is the right lens to use
Like the tf2 bird
I gotta go up there. I need a dog and a bird. Can you pet the birds?
Would you take the rule of thirds way too far? Okay. There's a bird. There's one over here
I think that works. Oh a friendly dog with a bird. Hold on over here
Over here over here. I think that's perfect
Actually, perfect. Yep
Okay, wouldn't it be cool to have a game of minecraft what pixelated dog in minecraft
bird photographer simulator
What i'll play that soon
All right pixelated dog in a minecart
And then a fun challenge photo using film from the far out pack
And then a dog in a minecart
What is this cookie?
Oh, here's the mine. Oh, it's not pixelized shit
dog shit
No, it's not
This photo is not dog shit
Look at these you think these are bad. Look at these photos
Okay photo from the fire watch tower
And then safety alert when you do something about them throw the scoot vac in the trash and send me proof
Okay, uh far out pack. Whoa. Okay. This one's cool. I like it
All right. I gotta get a scoot vac put in the trash and then I have to take a picture of the fire watch tower
That one was actually bad. Yeah, it was
I told you I wanted to do the bird watching stream
Where I actually just go and get a bunch of equipment
And go to a place where we can really see some actual real birds
And set you guys up with a lens so you can see
Venega, let's do the bird watching stream
Go get lenses that like pro lenses
That stream is either going to be really awful
What if we don't see any birds?
What is all this?
Oh, so this is i'm opening
It up at night
What is this?
stripe lens
I kind of want to try the candy one. You should get an actor to show up in a bird costume. I think
That's probably that's probably what would happen
It's like somebody would just paint a huge bird outfit
Oh, no, fuck that. I got but don't tell anybody this because this is like gonna be funny
Uh, I shouldn't say this
Because I feel like it'd be really funny
I'm not gonna say it because it's like the whole stream
I'm not gonna say it. Nope, just i'm gonna keep it in the back pocket, but I want to do something on that stream
That's gonna be really fucking stupid
Yeah, now I know why I can this is how I can do this stream
And i'm i'm putting it down now. I'm going for it
We have made jokes about this stream for a long time
I'm gonna go for it now. I'm actually gonna go for it. It's not gonna happen for a while. I'm just telling you
It's already like shit being planned the next like couple months
This is something that is gonna this is gonna have to be later like probably next year
But I think that's fun to do
All right, I gotta go to the fire watch tower
Spring yeah spring would be perfect
What are these what are these little weirdos? What are these what are these little weirdos? What are these dogs like the big goofy dogs?
They're so cute. Where are they?
Pomeranians. Yeah
they're always they're always doing like
they're always like
You know what i'm saying? You know what I mean?
Good one. You now go to the cove at sunset for some dramatic magic hour lighting. Okay, I need to do the
Pomeranians are very sassy
How do you feel? Um, I'm not good, but not bad either. I'm fine
I don't think I'm gonna want to go for much longer though
hot dog
A hot dog
Hot dog dog with a hot dog in his mouth
Yeah, this is actually really bad
Oh my god, I want that hat
There's no hat
This is a bot
I paid for bots on my account. I'm gonna get fucking thrown off this platform
Are you in a hot dog costume too?
Wow, I need one more, uh dog buck because I want to get the
Candy pack and see what it looks like
So what does it look like?
Bubble gum wait, I want a better view bubble gum. Oh, that's cool
candy coated
winter
two strip
velvet
Let's do the bubble gum filter
That does feel like bubble gum
Now a lot is so what do you guys think about this photo? It's good. It is good. It's not dog shit
You might be at this see this was bait here
This is trying to get you guys to be like wow dude like not that's bad right in the center and like right down here
Not even in the thirds. What are you crazy?
bang bang
Done
That was bait. Yeah, if you said it was dog shit, you had it wrong
Uh, I need a vacuum throw a vacuum in the trash and take a picture of it
Carry on my skyward sun
I got that's okay six seven eight. That's almost 10 likes
10 new followers for it's not even a dog
That's the most I think i've ever had
Okay, where's the uh
All right, I need a trash what are you all doing up here? Oh you're watching the geysers that's funny
Is there even a trash can here?
Where's the trash? I have the same hat. Why do you look so sad?
Um, I don't know where a trash is you think there'd be one right here
Bottom left. What do you that's not a direction. It's right here. Go left
This is just so cute. I need a picture of this. I don't want to disturb them
I'm out of focus. How do I focus it? I can't see any dog outfits. I'm your biggest fan
Uh, hello there my little feathered friend
This photo is blowing my mind
Why?
You already posted this today. What there's one person that wants the dog outfits
Hey, when are you gonna do a dog outfit? When are you gonna show the dog outfit? I want close-ups of dog outfits
Like the person that comes in here every day and says, uh, dude, when are you gonna when are you gonna play? Um,
When when are you gonna play fucking scorn again?
I'm just not gonna
When are you gonna play skyrim? I'm waiting for skyrim. Is he playing skyrim today?
That's actually cool. All right
There's no trash. I can't do it
I want to go back here to the to the sunset, right?
Oh
Let's do it then after this i'm probably gonna take it off
I'm starting to
This side of my face is starting to hurt
But I had fun i'm glad I could at least straighten a little bit hang out drink some tea
Yeah, I will i'm gonna chill
And i'll just keep an eye on the sus
If for some reason I get worse, I I just will skip tomorrow
But I might be fine. I don't know. We'll see
Let me close up of her way
There's a spotted dog who hangs out at lighthouse cove after hours
You get a close-up photo of her face
Look at that
Can't you just see text right here?
Being like sunset at the beach or something or whatever like town this is or whatever city this is
A bad composition. No, it is not
Like drifting away with the waves right there
They could sell these for six dollars each
All right. This is somebody have to take a photo of
Find the shy dalmatian
Over here, maybe I keep forgetting that i'm this weird
mascot character
I'm probably horrifying dalmatian. This is dalmatian
This looks so strange
Oh, I got it. Ow, my head got it dude. Look at this one
Don't tell me this is not a good picture. Oh shit
Challenge no dogs
Easy challenge complete. There's a dog that sleeps under a boat somewhere in the cove
Can you give me a picture of her? You have to go there at sunset. Okay
He's under a boat
Maybe right. Oh right here
Got it. There's one more here. There's uh, one of those hidden envelopes
On the roof maybe oh right here
Oh, we didn't have a chance to talk about it
But I was laughing so hard looking at the comments from uh, the tummy time stream
People were like that deadpool was fucking one of the worst things i've ever seen
I was laughing my ass off man. Somebody was like dude. He just is he's
Confusing michael angelo from the ninja turtles in deadpool
I was like, oh actually kind of makes sense. I had a lot of fun
I thought it was like a fun. I'll do it again and i'll fucking do it again
I'll do it again. I'll put that costume on and i'll do it again
It's I like couldn't it's funny because like I couldn't see the chat really at all because i'm in like this costume
And i'm not like looking over there
And I was just having a time. I was just having fun pretending to be deadpool
I didn't care what anybody was even saying
People were begging you to stop
That's so funny though
The fact that people felt like begging
Please stop
And I can't see them
I have no idea
Somebody said, uh, what was it? One of them was making me just roll
they were like charlie's expressions and charlie's demeanor was like
Talking to a kid that's dressed up for halloween. Just like oh, yeah. Nice job, sweetheart
Okay, cool. Show him your high kick
Like yeah, show me my high kick like a parent
It's like a parent that has this like kid that just just acting up and just like, okay
Nice job son
That was a lot of fun
I said it before in the beginning of the stream, but those guys are all awesome
That whole group it was just like a joy to be around
Okay, honey
He was really calm compared to you
Well, he had he had that unit on his arms
That thing was electrocuting him
Please do la la I already did
Oh wait, everybody has wait you need something
You need a toy? Oh
What is that what happened?
That was crazy
Wow
Now best photo of the whole night
All right. What's this the last objective?
Take an old timey photo. Okay, so I get a black and white photo
Show him your high kick
I just did it. Oh
That's so much fun though. I'm glad people thought it was fun
All right, black and white the boardwalk is now open late. All right, cool. What is this new emo change scorn?
What is that?
scorn
Terma scorn one
Terma scorn two
What is that?
skern
Whoa
That looks cool. That actually looks really cool
Looks like an old video game
Like mist or something
All right
I think i'm gonna wrap it up here guys
um
Starting to to feel it and I want to make sure I don't stay here too long
Hold on
Uh, so tomorrow keep an eye on the sus. I know the whole schedule got thrown off because of this
Um, i'm gonna go chill. I'm gonna go take some more of this take it every four hours
Although I really don't like doing that. Anybody else get like that
Like a cedaminophen especially be careful with it. This is not a joke
Um, if you take too much of cedaminophen and in one day it can actually fuck up your liver
So every time it's like oh take this every four hours. It's like, hmm, maybe i'll do it every six
But yeah, I think that's what's making me feel better. So we'll see
tomorrow
Uh keep an eye on the sus
I would say tba for now
But if I felt okay, then I was gonna just go today and I did
So the plan tomorrow
Is I want to play breath of the wild again
But I also want to do frog detective and um neon white
Then we got a lot of vr going on that next week
pretty much the entire next week
from
Like wednesday forward is all vr
and of course
culminating with the among us
sus rebranding of the entire channel
And I hope you understand i'm i'm selling the fuck out on that stream
It's I it's gonna be a joke
But yeah, uh, we'll do a lot of vr
Hopefully this hopefully this is just something very small like a head cold or something. It just goes away
Obviously, i'll probably test tomorrow for covet again. And if it's negative then whatever I just have a cold or whatever
but
I'll see you guys
probably tomorrow
short stream, I know but
I'll see you
Let's see what happens tomorrow. Keep an eye on sus
Do I have a sore throat? Yes, I do
It's not that bad though. I can I can like i'm talking for three hours today
See you soon regardless
Thanks for watching. Thanks for hanging out
That was paparazzi
That was like the perfect game to play too
Just hang out for a few hours
Have a great night guys. See you soon
Bye mother. Take care of yourselves
We'll be praying for you. I forgot about that
Give all energy that's
Give us one more lala
You don't even want me to do this
Send positive vibes pray for me
Uh, all right. See you guys later. Take care