Alright, unfortunately we're gonna have to pivot, because, uh, Beautiful Jo's not gonna work either, because this memory card is, is, is not, it's just like, toast.
Uh, alright, good, cool. So, I'm gonna have a new memory card, it'll work tomorrow.
Alright, so we're gonna pivot, we're gonna pivot.
I'm gonna use the same fucking console.
We're gonna pivot to the Wii.
It's time to pivot.
Oh, we're, we're pivoting.
To Rage Cooking Mama Cook-Off.
That's a, that's a hard fucking rage pivot if I've ever seen one.
It's in a fucking disk.
Unbelievable.
Ah.
I'm gonna be on cam for this one.
Me.
Imagine wanting Rain World over Cooking Mama?
I mean, they're both, they're both pretty interesting.
Uh, so tomorrow, we're gonna, we're gonna do this again tomorrow.
I, I know, I know, I, I see that it takes 10 minutes for the SD card, but I don't know, I, I don't even know where an SD card is.
I have to go, like, look for where my SD cards, I, like, that, that's like a 30 to 40 minute experience.
It's not just, download two items, download, and it's done, done.
We're in the middle of a broadcast, I'm not gonna be like, ah, see you guys in like 30 minutes.
Or, like, I'll look for an SD card.
There's one somewhere in this house, and I don't know where it is.
Now, we're just gonna do it tomorrow.
In your Wii, I don't have an SD card in the Wii.
Alright, let's go.
Here, you know what, let's just do this.
Welcome to the stream.
Because we're starting over.
See you in a second.
We're also gonna go on cam for this one.
Because, you know, I have the Wiimotes and shit in my hand.
Hey, what's going on, how are you guys?
Just joining, we're, we're welcome, everybody, to the stream.
Hope you guys had a good, uh, couple of days here.
I've been alright, I've been okay.
I'm pretty good.
I had a run in with, um, some flash memory over the last couple of days.
I want to take, um, I'm thinking about taking a hammer to something.
You know, just nothing too major.
Yeah, we'll get started.
We're gonna do Cooking Mama Cook Off.
Cooking Mama Cook Off.
That's what I've heard we're gonna do today.
Sounds good.
Alright, let me just make a tweet.
Delete the old tweet that I had.
I had something wrong with my iPhone like an hour and a half ago.
It said, it said, the chibi robo.
I didn't, I didn't write that.
I had something happen.
I got like a fucking virus or something.
Alright.
I'm so sad.
I like it, it worked too.
I'm hounded by a fucking ghost.
There's a ghost that follows me everywhere.
Like a technology ghost.
Alright, let's go.
Cooking Mama.
I'm ready.
I actually am excited for this one too.
I also have to change the title.
Because this doesn't make any sense.
The ultimate household, the ultimate household chef.
How does that sound?
The ultimate household chef?
I just have to change one word.
Cooking Mama.
How many Cooking Mamas are there?
There's like 30 of these games?
Alright, let's go.
That looked weird.
Alright, let's get a good view of me and my Wii.
I've got my Wiimote.
I've got my Nunchuck.
Let me make this look better.
Okay.
I'm ready.
Time to chop and cut and eat.
Why do I look so mad?
Well, an hour and 25 minutes went by of a game I wanted to play and my fucking GameCube memory card was corrupted.
I don't think it's sunshine and rainbows right now for me.
Yes, I do.
I would love to create a save file.
Watch this not work either.
Hey, by the way, no hand strap physically even on this Wiimote.
It's got a corrupted Wii.
I'm ready.
Should I go?
I should go like...
Can you guys see my hands?
Don't matter.
New game.
File 1.
New file.
Friends is...
Let's cook.
Alright, I don't know how to play.
I need to learn how to play.
You sweaty?
I'm not sweaty.
Let's cook.
Select recipe.
Okay, there's...
What is it?
Minestrone soup?
Is this game hard?
Beef and wine sauce.
Custard.
We're doing custard.
Okay, start.
I'm just...
I'm going off the grid.
I'm fucking deleting myself right now.
You can reach me through fucking carrier mail.
Alright, practice.
Swing the Wii remote in order to tap the eggs on the bowl.
When it cracks, press the A button to put the egg in the bowl.
Okay.
Add and use the clues to add the correct items to the bowl.
Point at the item and pick it up with the B button.
Follow the on-screen instructions to add items.
Okay.
Point the Wii remote down and turn it to stir.
Don't do too hard, it'll spill.
Twist the Wii remote right, left, to pour.
Okay.
Twist the Wii remote.
We're using a microwave, mama?
Game's too quiet?
What?
Game's too loud.
Don't think mama's using a microwave?
Alright, I got it.
Let's try it.
Got it!
I thought I was putting...
I thought I was cracking...
Ew!
I thought I was cracking eggs.
I thought I was supposed to be cracking eggs.
Oh, this is practice.
Okay.
It's each step.
I get it.
Alright, we'll do eggs.
Nah, I don't...
I'll practice, I'm good.
Let's go.
Swing the Wii remote in order to tap the egg on the bowl.
When it cracks, press A to put it...
Okay, here we go.
Ready?
What's wrong with that?
Oh, it's gonna be little.
It's gonna be small tap.
I got it.
Alright.
Done.
Better than mama.
Mama, you're doing not very good.
Alright, now it's gonna add ingredients.
Use the clues to add the correct items to the bowl.
Point at the item and pick it up with the B button.
Okay, follow the instructions.
Oh, shit.
Okay, I gotta pick up the...
Egg.
I don't know which one of these is egg.
What?
It's not egg?
Oh.
Okay, we're good.
I was asking for egg.
I gotta leave him for the coffee.
Alright, stir.
Point the Wii remote down and move it around quickly.
If you don't stir too hard, it'll spill.
That's going too fast.
Faster?
No, I don't want it to spill.
Okay, now put it into the mold.
Push the Wii remote...
Okay.
...right to four.
Put carefully to make sure it doesn't overflow.
Okay.
Careful.
Is that good?
No!
It's okay.
We turned it into a muffin, mama.
Ooh.
How many do I have to do?
I want us a hundred points.
That's pretty good.
Not bad.
Good.
Alright, I'm almost done with it, right?
Alright, this is just twist the Wii remote while holding the A button to adjust the oven.
Watch the meter carefully.
When it reaches the red part, switch it off.
What?
I have to hold my finger on the oven?
Ten?
Fifteen?
Twenty?
How hot does this have to be?
That's good.
I didn't even cook them.
Alright.
Now this is just throw it out of the mold.
I remember.
Don't shake it too hard.
Okay.
Good job.
That was close.
That's good.
Did I get good on the whole thing?
Now do I have to eat it with my hands?
Eat it.
Alright.
Results.
Very good.
Good.
Try harder.
Did I lose?
I got a new recipe.
Oh, a fucking grilled cheese sliders!
Alright.
I want like a...
I don't want just like a piece of custard.
Let's do soup.
Finish from.
Hold the Wii remote upright.
Yeah, alright.
Upright and moving forward and backward.
This is to open the can.
Press A button when the meter gets to the yellow portion to open the lid.
That's good.
Why is it coming out of a...
Mama, you're using a toaster oven.
You're getting soup out of a can.
Alright.
Move it so we can peel the potatoes.
Move it from the top to the bottom to peel the skin.
Okay.
Not efficient.
Very inefficient.
Alright, it's done.
It's done.
This is where Mom doesn't ask you to do this again.
This is where you peel the carrot to a point where there's like a toothpick worth of carrot.
It just turns into this like skinny little shitty thing.
Because you peeled off the skin and you peeled off all the actual vegetable.
Oh, you did it better than Mama!
See that?
Alright, finely chop.
First, trace the arrow with the...
I spit all over my mouth.
Trace the arrow with the Wiimote to cut the ingredients when they are cut.
Shake the Wiimote up and down to finely chop them.
So I go...
Boink!
And then...
Onion!
Green bean!
Very good.
Move the Wiimote forward and backward to cut the...
More cutting.
Okay, I can do this.
I'm pretty good at the cutting.
Bacon.
This is a lot of bacon.
This is like a whole loaf of ham.
Stir fry.
This is...
Alright.
To add to the pan, select the icons with the A button.
Move the Wiimote toward and away from you to prevent burning.
When the...
When two circles appear, press finished.
We're just like...
We just...
This is how you pretend to be a chef.
Do you ever want someone to think that you're interesting?
Let's say you have a date and somebody's like,
Oh, but you can cook!
You're like, I can cook.
I can cook.
Just period.
Listen to me.
Put spinach.
A little bit of spinach in a pan.
A little bit of like olive oil.
And just like...
While they're in the room with you.
It'll work every time.
Put like some green beans, some bell peppers, some onions.
And like a little bit of other water-based vegetables.
And just shake it like, yeah, I know what I'm doing.
This is the I pretend to know how to fucking cook stream.
I don't know why I'm streaming this, but you know.
And then make something up while they have to leave.
Alright, let's put the bacon in.
Onions.
Green beans.
Carrots.
Potatoes.
Doesn't even matter.
Let's just do this.
Looks pretty good.
Just put it all in the pan.
Carrots.
Okay, take it out.
What was wrong with that?
Underdone?
I didn't finish it?
What was undercooked?
What?
Stew.
Stir.
Rotate the Wii mode.
You put everything in at the same time?
Yeah, that's what I'm saying.
That's how you impress your date.
Everything just goes into this and it makes like a...
And then they just think that you know what you're doing.
Rotate the Wii remote.
Add.
Point to the icon and press the A button to add.
Adjust the heat.
Twist the remote.
We're just stewing it now.
Add what?
Add?
Add salt.
Medium.
Stir it.
A little bit of salt in there.
I don't know.
Pepper.
Heat on high.
What do I put in the corn?
Put in a can of tomatoes?
Add wheat.
All right.
Green beans are in.
Stir it up.
Looks good.
Not bad.
I did it.
And then your date, you present this to them.
And they go...
And by the way, use a shitload of time.
But like, it doesn't even matter if the recipe calls for it.
Put like...
Half the bottle of the spice.
Half the spice bottle of time.
Half the bottle of time.
Like into the soup.
It just will smell like, oh, what an aroma.
And when you bring it, it'll fill the house with this thyme smell.
And it's like, holy shit, this person, look at this.
It smells delicious in here.
Just make sure they don't eat it.
Like...
Make a phone call.
Oh, what's the...
Oh, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
What, you want to meet us at...
Fucking...
21 Beef?
Or whatever the restaurant is?
Oh, yeah, sure.
And then you fucking hang up.
Hey, don't...
Don't...
We got a big dinner with some friends.
And then you go in there and you just pretend that you got fucking blown off by your friends.
And enjoy a nice dinner with your date.
Yeah, they have like 21 different steaks.
I don't know.
Web of life.
Wait, I didn't do the...
The flan?
Oh, I gotta...
Okay, I gotta try harder on this one.
Oh, honey, that looks...
Why would your first date be calling you honey?
Shit.
There we go.
Little life.
Fuck.
Egg sucker.
You want to know something funny about me and my life?
I...
I can't eat.
I don't...
I don't do egg.
I don't know how to do them.
I don't know how to open them.
Every time I try it, it just goes like...
It gets all over my hands and shit.
I don't...
I don't do...
I don't crack eggs.
I don't do it.
Alright, same deal.
Add the ingredients.
Egg.
Going in.
What's that?
Liquor.
Milk.
Instantly done.
Good.
That's easy.
Even better than mama.
I'm gonna do this wicked fast, but not that fast.
Ready?
Oh, nobody does this better than me.
Can I take...
Can I have it come up faster?
No bonus?
That's bullshit.
Bake it in the oven.
Now this...
Okay, twist the remote while holding A to adjust the oven.
Watch the meter carefully.
Turn off the oven when it...
Okay, so turn...
I gotta turn it on.
I got it.
I had to have made up for it, right?
That was when I just make them come out carefully.
That was gentle.
Fuck you!
Why?
I got it, right?
Try harder?
No, I got it.
This is...
I got a bronze medal.
I got it.
No, I got it.
Okay.
This is...
Mochi.
Let's do it.
Okay, add water.
Turn the water...
Turn on the water and fill the pot.
Tilt the remote upward to stop the water before it overflows.
Oh, I only get one shot.
I only get one shot.
Why am I apologizing?
What did I do?
Point the remote down and hold it upright.
This...
How long did it take this time?
An hour?
Forty minutes?
Swearing.
Okay.
Point the remote down and hold it upright.
Move it around quickly to wash.
When done, tilt the remote to drain the water.
So you go...
And then like this.
Say sorry to Mama.
Mama's not a real person.
What? Did I just knock it over?
I just...
I just washed everything.
And just dumped it onto the counter.
Go back, go back.
No, no.
I want to make Mochi.
Okay.
I hate Mama.
No.
I just said fuck.
I said like fuck you game.
This is not...
I don't have to apologize to somebody that...
No, I'm not apologizing to anything on the Wii right now.
I'm very upset with the Wii right now.
And the GameCube memory card in particular.
Go around quickly to wash.
Then tilt the Wii remote to drain the water.
Isn't that what I did?
Okay, A.
Now tilt.
What the fuck is going on there?
I'm just going a little...
Hold A.
Watch the meter carefully.
When the barbeque gets to red, switch it off.
Fucking simple.
Floor Mochi.
Alright, pound the Mochi.
Move the Wii remote up and down to pound the rice.
Take care not to accidentally...
Hit your hand.
There's no hand.
Mama, I'm sorry.
Mama's going to have fucking bruises all over her.
I've tried to do twice before.
You gotta go to the darkness office like this.
I'm covered in fucking wilt and fucking bruises and shit.
Oh, this is so bad.
I'll get this one next time.
I need to practice.
Hold the Wii remote upright and move it left and right.
If it gets hard to grate, move the Wii remote up and down to shake the loose ingredients.
I gotta grate the cheese?
This cheese?
Get off!
This is shitload of cheese, Mama!
Mama, what are you doing?
Why is there so much cheese on this?
You know what I do whenever I'm cooking with a great bunch of cheese like that?
I get a little overwhelmed.
And I just grab the whole mound, the soft, mushy, stick-together mound of Parmesan cheese, and I just eat the whole fucking thing.
And then I have to do it again.
Follow the on-screen...
Okay, make some Mochi.
So just follow the on-screen action.
So it's like left and right, tilt, turn.
Okay.
Put it into the flour.
Roll it back and forth a couple times.
Get it dusted.
Into the chocolate.
Soak it up.
Good.
Wrap it up.
One more.
Come on, hurry up.
Done.
Chocolate and cheese.
Well, it has to look like whatever.
Well, I don't even know what it was.
Complete.
All right.
Mochi.
I'm probably going to have to do this again.
Bronze.
Sorry.
I still completed it.
Three cookies.
You have a new recipe.
I don't know what that is.
I'm looking forward to it though.
Should I do the scrambled eggs?
I knew it.
See?
Oh, I thought it was scrambled eggs.
It's scrambled eggs.
I make a brutally good scrambled egg.
What I do is I panic.
When I get the eggs into the pan,
and I freak out because I don't want to undo them,
and I end up overdoing them by about five straight minutes.
But they're like brown all over.
So, I make a pretty mean scrambled egg.
Okay.
Swing the Wiimote in order to tap the egg on the bowl.
Is it good?
All right.
Open the can.
I need to do a test here.
Hold on.
It's a way off.
All right.
Hold on.
Ready?
Oh!
Hold on.
Wait, wait, wait.
I got it.
Right eye, left eye, right eye, left eye, right eye, left eye, right eye, left eye, right eye, left eye, right eye, left eye, right eye, left eye.
Good, right?
Better?
It's better.
It might take a little bit more moving around.
You need a psychiatrist.
You're trying to sync my gameplay to my webcam?
All right.
Scramble the eggs.
What the hell is that?
Egg?
Why is it doing like this weird mystery thing?
Cream cheese.
I don't know what the fuck cream cheese looks like in this game.
Milk.
How's that not milk?
All right.
Now in goes the prosciutto.
Grab.
All right, guys.
Do the wing.
Down.
I think we're good.
Spread the butter.
Build the Wii mode carefully to coat the frying pan with butter.
It's gonna stick right there.
Gotta get it all before the time runs out.
Got it.
Let's go read a bunch of books.
Good idea.
Increase your smarts.
All right.
Cook eggs.
Shake.
Shake the Wii mode.
Ack and forth.
Hold Wii mode upright.
And turn it around while holding B button.
Season.
Shake Wii mode while holding A button.
Okay.
Let's cook these eggs.
Not too much.
All right.
They're done.
Mama, too much salt.
Looks like vomit.
Mama.
Sodium.
Mama, too much sodium.
I don't like salty eggs.
I'd rather take...
Instead of putting a bunch of salt on eggs,
I'd like to do...
Just a little dollop of tabasco...
I was gonna say tabascio.
Like pistachio.
Tabasco sauce.
Just like...
And then you just like...
Let it get in there.
Tabasco.
It's a...
New?
What's this?
Beef and wine sauce.
Ooh.
I like it.
Okay.
Trace the arrow with the Wii mode to cut the ingredients.
This one...
This is elaborate.
This one's a lot.
All right.
I gotta get a good score here.
Beef rib.
Geo physics?
I love a good wine.
All right.
We gotta peel.
I was bad at this before.
One fluid motion.
It hurts my ADHD so bad.
You know what I mean?
It's hard.
I fuck.
This hurts my ADHD.
Like it hurts my whole body.
Yeah.
Some of you guys know what I'm talking about.
All right.
Mince the beef.
Shake the Wii mode.
Up and down.
Chop the ingredients.
That's it.
So just chop.
The shallots.
That looks like a banana.
Get the mushrooms in there.
Come.
Okay.
Use the clues to add the correct items to the bowl.
This one.
You have to guess.
Point at the item.
Pick it up with the B button.
Okay.
Pepper.
Then...
What's that?
Gravy.
And then...
The vegetables.
And then a little bit of this.
There it is.
Garnish.
Is that thyme?
Is it a coincidence that the Blade and Sorcerer video went up on YouTube the day you played Cooking Mama and you made a Cooking Mama joke in this video?
Yeah.
I think so.
Sprinkle.
Poke the ingredients.
Press A and the B button at the same time to sprinkle.
But I didn't...
Is that too much?
I don't know what I'm seasoning it with.
I'm just dumping shit on it.
I think that's alright.
Why is she so...
Wait, she...
She's so great.
Why...
What's going on?
Alright.
Spread the butter.
Coat the butter in the pan.
I know this one.
Around the edges first.
Dun dun dun dun dun dun dun!
Okay.
Stir fry.
Let's go.
Get it all in there.
Alright.
What cooks the longest?
Put the beef in first.
And then the mushrooms.
And then put the rest in.
It's charred.
It's charred, mate.
That's what I'm saying.
Alright.
Rotate the Wii mode.
Add.
Okay.
This is the stew part.
Put it all in the stew.
Add.
Salt.
Medium heat.
On medium.
Stir it up.
Add a little bit of whatever the fuck this is.
Put it on high.
Put a little bit of whatever this is with it.
A tied up thing.
Stir it up.
Put it on low.
Perfectly done.
How's it look?
Pretty good.
I don't like a chunky potato stew, though.
I like my potatoes to be...
Cubed.
If I do not have cubed potatoes,
I don't like it.
And they have to be...
Less than a half inch thick and a half inch wide.
You know what I'm saying?
I want cubed potatoes.
Big chunky potatoes don't do it for me.
The beef has to be also...
A cube-like shape.
I don't like big stringy long...
Pull.
I gotta pull it.
No, no, no.
No.
It's gotta be cubed.
Small cubed up meat.
All carrots...
Must be a perfect small circle in diameter like this.
Like very small.
And they have to be less than a half inch thick.
Alright, we can move on to this.
Next one.
Ooh, shrimp and chili sauce.
Kurogi.
Popcorn of the United States.
Ooh, what do we have?
Oh, we have lots of great Italian and French cuisine.
Minestrone.
Oh, this is Japanese.
Mochi.
Oh, France.
Scrambled eggs.
What do I have from America?
Popcorn.
This is one step.
I love making popcorn on the stove though.
It is actually really good.
You gotta be careful though because you might put too much in
and that's when the lid starts to go up
and you start to make too much.
You start to freak out.
Look at this American cuisine.
Gotta keep it in the yellow.
That's it.
It's not burning.
It's fine.
Ah, classic American cuisine.
Add seasoning.
Why is it an open, like, salami sandwich?
When the bottle blinks, shake the Wiimote.
Shake with good timing.
When the bottle blinks?
What?
What's going on?
When the bottle blinks?
No bottle is blinking.
What do you mean the bottle blinks?
Who's putting the salt on?
That's not blink.
That's not blinking, by the way.
That is just growth.
That's growing and shrinking.
That's not a blink.
Just like a typical American dish.
It's loaded with as much salt as you can physically fucking tolerate.
There's no wink, liars.
You're a great chef.
Hey, thanks.
Oh, another classic American dish.
The hot dog.
Why is classic American food food for toddlers?
The classic American.
Hot dog.
Chopped up a bunch.
Popcorn.
Macaroni and cheese.
Look, we're going to get another thing with an American flag that's like Cheerios.
And you just have to pick them up like a baby.
Just eat them one by one on one of those toddler dishes.
What's a classic American food?
What's a classic American dish?
American.
Apple pie.
Pies, yeah.
Desserts.
Burger.
I don't know about a burger.
Isn't burger German?
Hamburger.
That's like, that's German, right?
What's an American cuisine?
Barbecue, yep.
Barbecue is, yeah, absolutely.
Turkey.
Turkey, barbecue.
Diner food.
But that's not like, that's not like...
Diner food is just a place, that's like a genre of restaurant style.
That's not like classic American recipe.
Diner.
KFC.
Yeah, I guess so.
Beer.
Anything fried?
Like fried chicken.
Yeah, but hopefully we get some, hopefully we get like a...
Beer is German.
Germany didn't invent beer.
Who invented beer?
The Mesopotamians.
The Mesopotamians invented beer.
Sorry.
Vegan?
Alright, what's this?
Spaghetti and squid ink.
Eggs.
I fucking can't do the eggs.
Even in fucking fake life.
Light, light, light, light.
At the same speed, man.
Eggcellent, I get it.
NA doesn't have much distinct because it's all brought from other countries.
Yeah.
But, I mean like barbecue, like a smoked barbecue brisket.
That's pretty American.
No it isn't.
What are you talking about?
If you get smoked barbecue brisket from America, it's going to be better than anywhere else on Earth.
That's a fact.
Literally any chef on Earth will tell you that.
Some of the best chefs in the world will tell you that the best barbecue is in America.
Of course it is.
What country does barbecue better than America?
I'm sorry.
Like we're like, oh America is popcorn!
But I'm going to defend America when I need to.
Like fucking barbecue, American barbecue is better than anywhere else on the planet.
Like what are you talking about?
Come on.
He's a patriot.
I like eating smoked meat.
I need the dough.
We have the best burgers?
America's got some really good food.
I mean, yes, you could eat like chicken tenders and like pizza hut every day.
But like, I mean that's like the joke, right?
Like Americans, they eat fucking the pizza hut hot dogs and mac and cheese.
I mean they do.
We do.
I do.
How long does this need to be?
Is it too long?
What was I making?
What was that?
I don't even know what that was.
Oh, it's supposed to be spaghetti.
That would be one giant tube of spaghetti.
Okay.
Make some pasta.
When the pasta is flowing from the pasta machine, it reaches the length of the line.
Shake the Wiimote to cut the pasta.
Alright, so cut it when it gets...
This looks like fun.
Is this hard to do?
Alright, you know why I want to make my own pasta?
Because you guys remember the Play-Doh play set?
Where you did the same exact thing except it wasn't pasta.
It was Play-Doh.
But it wasn't supposed to be pasta.
You just smooshed Play-Doh through a machine that turned it into this for no reason.
That's why I want to make this.
Childhood.
Inspiration.
You grew up at Toys R Us.
A lot of people did.
Alright, rotate the Wiimote so we're going to stew this again.
I've had some experience stewing.
A little bit of salt.
Get that heat up.
More stirring.
This is just really easy Guitar Hero.
Stir the pasta.
Damn it, I did.
Wonderful.
Better than mama.
It had really good...
Wait, what?
What was mushy and gross?
Alright, drain the pasta.
The whole like this.
Tilt the pot to drain.
If you tilt too much, it'll spill and you'll like burn mama's hands again.
Good job.
That was it?
That's all the pasta that was in the fucking bowl?
What?
Get your hand in there and like get it out.
Prepare.
Move the Wiimote in the direction of the arrow.
Prepare the ingredients.
Ugh!
It just ripped his head off.
Wonderful.
I'm sorry.
Anything that has a slimy outside...
I would not ever eat.
I know, I'm sorry.
Octopus get disgusting.
Squid disgusting.
They're like slimy, tendril aliens?
No.
Never.
I'm sorry.
I...
Why would we eat that?
It's squid.
It's octopus.
No.
And their legs...
They have...
You eat like octopus legs, they have like the suction cups and they're long and they like...
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, never.
Ugh!
I just like imagine it like...
Like sucking in my lip and maybe like...
It's on my lip!
It's on my fucking lip!
And like Cam has to reach over and like...
Pull it off!
I can't get it off!
Ugh, no.
I don't want it.
Why is the squid turned into onion rings when you cut it up?
No, that's gross.
Weird.
Squid when you...
It's just like little weird slimy wristbands.
That tape that you chew through like rubber.
No, you don't...
Garlic, you're speaking like...
That's it?
Alright, yeah, sure, okay.
I will eat a piece of calamari and be like...
Oh!
That's...
Mmm!
That was good.
That was kind of good.
It was a little salty.
But when people pick up...
When people pick up the fucking piece of calamari...
That's...
Like when you launch a grenade launcher at an alien in a fucking video game.
And it's like spread out and all fucking...
Like it looks like this!
It looks like that and it's fried up.
Mmm.
Nope.
And it's like the legs are...
Can't handle squid.
No, why?
I just don't eat it.
I don't want it.
How long does this take to cook?
Alright, alright, alright, alright, alright, alright!
Stop, stop, stop!
That was the squid ink!
The taste buds of a child.
A lot of people don't like fucking squid or octopus.
Why would you want to eat squid ink?
That's just something that humans decided they were going to eat because they decided
that they thought it would be cool to eat it one day.
Like, what's the point of this?
It tastes.
It's tasty.
I don't...
I don't agree.
I've never had it though.
I'm gonna...
I'll be back in an hour with the squid.
No, you know what it is for me?
Here's what it is.
It's welcome to our restaurant.
We put squid ink on this to make it so we can charge that plate of food like 30 more
dollars.
That's what it is.
I'm being scammed.
You hate to see people get scammed!
Let's make some pierogies.
More egg cracking.
I'll get it.
Perfect.
Just like that.
Again.
It was identical.
Roll that clip back and watch it.
Where did I go?
I went to the bathroom.
Did I tell you I was going to the bathroom?
Wait, it didn't say where I was going?
Wait, what are you talking about?
Oh, it's...
My voice is delayed by a thousand milliseconds.
So, when I say something right here, you hear it a full second later.
So, I said, hey, I'm going to the bathroom.
Be right back.
And I muted.
So, you didn't hear that.
Oh.
I muted too quickly for you to get the...
Okay.
What do you think about these?
These are getting long, huh?
They look nice though.
Like, they actually are like very healthy nails.
They're very healthy.
Too healthy.
They grow like a wheat.
I club them once a fucking week and they just keep going.
What's next?
All right.
No, no, no, no, no, no.
Put it down.
Sell the clippings.
I can't think of anything more disgusting than what you just said.
Except for maybe eat squid ink pasta.
No, no, no.
Put it down.
Leave this dough.
Are we making squid ink pasta again?
I want his points back.
Where's the boomer brace?
I haven't been wearing it lately.
It's been constricting me and giving me a little sore.
Oh, let's shape the pierogies.
Okay.
They have to shape them.
Get it?
When am I done shaping it?
No, no.
Other way.
Stop going the other way.
You can't go faster than this, guys.
The snow go faster.
Why does he look so upset?
I think that's just my face.
Rest in boomer face.
All right.
Stretch the dough.
Move it forward and backward to stretch the dough.
Rotate dough with one and two.
Okay.
We're going to spread it out.
One and two.
Careful.
Mm.
Pierogies are awesome.
I love pierogies.
My mother used to make pierogies.
It looks like too much onion.
The wiki.
Why?
All right.
Hold it horizontal and move it as though you are turning the handle.
We're going to do the jack in the box.
Do, do, do, do, do, do, do, do, do, do, do, do, do, do, do, do.
Did you wash your hands before prepping this meal?
Of course I did.
Stir fry.
Add the buttons.
Get a little salt in there.
The meat and the pierogies.
Going to make sure it gets cooked.
Come on, meat.
A little bit more.
A little bit more onion.
Pierogies.
We're done.
Should have left it in there a little longer.
Now wrap them up.
Okay.
So we just have to go.
Excuse me.
Where are the gloves?
Now, I don't eat food prepared by anybody unless they're using rubber cleaning gloves.
That wasn't a lot of meat.
This one's, all right.
This one's a little light.
All right.
I know.
I didn't do enough meat.
Let's do.
Okay.
What are we going to do?
All right.
I know.
I didn't do enough meat.
Let's do.
Okay.
We'll compensate more meat.
Yeah.
That's a big.
That's a hearty one.
We're just out of the side a little bit.
It's all right.
You just tip it upside down.
You go.
That's all you need to do.
Deep fry.
Grab the ingredients on the tray with the V button and add them to the oil.
When they're fully cooked, grab with the V button and put them on the bottom tray.
Do not mind.
Wait.
Did I pick these up?
All right.
Turn the heat down.
That's good.
Oh, it wasn't.
They weren't done.
Do not mind.
One pierogi.
They all wasted.
It seems like you have only one pierogi on your plate, judges.
Yeah.
Germa, you just wasted like $40 worth of food.
Have you ever used a stove before?
I don't know.
I've never actually used a stove before.
Uh, this looks...
I don't want this.
It's like tapeworm stew.
I don't want it.
Uh, what is that?
No.
What is that?
Lasagna?
No, no.
Get rid of it.
That's not appetizing to me.
I don't like this.
It looks like fruit roll-ups.
Don't want it.
Hand-fried lobster.
Parimpuffs.
Those are awesome.
What is this?
Actually, mussels are pretty good.
I ate mussels once.
Oh, fuck.
I didn't look at the instructions.
They're open.
They're done.
I thought when the shell opens, it means it's cooked, right?
That's what it means?
Yes.
Yeah, that's what I'm saying.
So what was wrong with that?
The shell opened.
When they open up, pick them up with B and move them to the tray.
So what the fuck?
What are you going to overcook this shit?
When they open, how is that wrong?
Food poisoning.
It said when they pop open, move them to the tray.
Awesome.
They're open.
I did wait.
It said, take it, please.
Look.
Just literally wait for the arrow.
I did.
Okay, this one's done.
This one's done.
Now this one's done.
Mine were done, too.
That's horseshit.
Mine were done.
I didn't have an arrow on it.
Wonderful.
Better than mama.
Yeah, my last dish was better than yours, too.
Yes, they were.
Don't criticize the streamer.
Let's mince.
I love that.
Play this for me.
I have a shitload of Wii games back here.
So I'm enjoying myself.
I think it's fun.
Dedicated cooking mama stream.
I don't like squid.
Squids are like, I don't like squid beater.
Oh.
I think you're ripping off the thing's fucking legs.
I don't like it.
I'm never eating meat ever again.
I don't know.
It freaks me out sometimes.
Wonderful.
Better than mama.
He's going to puke.
That's bullshit.
All right.
Oh, wait.
Okay.
Let's go.
All done.
Let's get a couple of good ones.
All right.
Come on.
Squid.
Not in a different...
What was that?
Why is it doing this?
What?
Oh, shit.
Okay.
I got it.
Is it sake?
I love sake.
Sake is great.
All right.
Let's make paeyas.
I'm going to be the paeya, not the paeyas.
You don't like wrap them up.
Arrange them as you'd like.
All right.
Let's arrange them as we'd like.
So let's...
Oh.
Better than mama.
What?
It was fine.
I did that because you want to get some broth first, and then you pick the stuff off the
top that you want.
I make my paeya buffet style.
Oh, it's delicious when I make it.
If you ever come over, I'll make it for you.
It'll be like...
Oh, yeah.
And then we'll go have a steak.
New recipe.
All right.
Shrimp and chili sauce.
That sounds pretty good.
All right.
Should I make the cream puffs?
Wait.
What else is there?
How about a good old-fashioned American hot dog?
Yeah, we got to make some American food.
I know that there's like a shitload of Europeans in here that are like, ugh.
Let's watch.
The sophistication of American cuisine.
Watch as I use the knife to slice the bread down the middle.
And watch as I put hot dog into a bun.
Outside, apparently.
What the fuck is this?
How much of this do I have to put on?
This much cheese on my hot dog.
Decorate it.
This is American cuisine.
Make a hot dog and then be at the fucking Fridays with a placemat as a four-year-old
and draw with a crayon all over the placemat.
Oh, this is ketchup and mustard.
Okay, that's a mustard sandwich?
With a handle, that's a hot dog.
You pick that up by the hot dog and eat that.
That's a reverse corn dog.
Double cheeseburger, American.
We're doing all the American stuff first, because I'm American.
And I'm going to tell you how correct it is.
This is a double cheeseburger.
Why does it have to be a double?
I don't get it.
Why can it just be one single cheeseburger?
What are you saying?
All Americans eat McDouble cheeseburgers?
McDoubles every time they go to the restaurant?
You all do.
When was the last time anyone ordered a single hamburger from McDonald's?
I mean, like a regular cheeseburger.
I'm not even sure they make those anymore, because people don't order them.
That's a special order now to get a single cheeseburger.
You have to pull around and park in one of the parking spaces,
because they're not fucking ready for that.
All right, let's see what we've got.
What kind of veggies have we got in here?
I'll tell you how accurate this is.
Buns.
Okay.
Slice the tomato.
No tomato on mine, please.
Yes, please give me something that makes everything wet and acidic while I bite into it.
Disgusting.
Get it off my hamburger.
Tear the lettuce.
Oh, what?
Did I break my finger?
Why do we have to do this?
Why don't we use the pieces?
Is it like something in the center?
Can we take all that lettuce off to get to the center of the lettuce?
Eat the center of the lettuce.
Make the meat.
All right, I'm very, very American, because I looked at this and went,
what the fuck are they talking about?
Just go to the grocery store, get patty, and put patty in the pan.
Oh, this is going to make quite a few hamburgers.
Looks like the whole baseball team is coming over, mama.
Because this is like 15 hamburgers.
Eggs.
Oh, right.
It's a binder.
More than two or three eggs to make.
That seems like a lot.
One hit.
I messed up one this time.
Perfect record there.
Perfect record.
The burger is not a meatball.
You sap it.
Is that the grate the cheese?
Okay, grate the cheese.
Like this?
How does one do it like this?
Seems weird.
All right, grate the cheese.
Do it again.
Do it every time, and I love it.
Because the cheese is so soft when you do that.
If you grate a fresh block of Parmesan, the cheese is so soft
and almost moist.
And when you pick it up, it just bunches together.
And it's so...
I love Parmesan cheese.
It's my favorite.
I love hard cheese.
I'm a hard cheese guy.
Not a soft cheese guy.
Marie sucks.
Okay?
Hard cheese, yes.
Soft cheese, get it out of here.
I'm a hard cheese guy.
I'm just telling you how I feel.
Why is this so dirty?
Why are there like bugs at the restaurant?
What's up, Megan?
What's up, girl?
Mama, why are you making me guess?
Mama, I appreciate the fact that you're using one of those old toys
from the fucking early 90s
that you take the magnet and give the guy a beard,
but get it off my screen, please!
Knead the dough.
The hamburger dough.
Knead the hamburger dough.
All right, make a hamburger.
Hold the B button to take a piece of hamburger,
then hold the Limo up right
and move left and right to shape the meat.
All right, this is a long one.
So grab some meat.
Up right.
That's not how I've ever done that.
It seems...
I'm making a pizza?
That's not how you do this.
If my mother ever saw me doing this in the kitchen,
she would come and grab my arm and be like,
hey, hey, hey, hey!
Big patty.
Why am I playing this?
Because it's a fun game.
Because my chibi-robo got fucked up
because I don't have a...
I have a corrupted...
You know what?
Let's just say I started with this.
All right, butter time.
Come on, get it.
Just forget the first hour of your life here.
All right, time to pan fry.
Turn over, move forward and back.
Shake just a heap.
Oh, fuck, I have to make the patty.
Why does it look like this?
Why is it in half?
Forward and back to move to flip it.
Shake it and then adjust the heat while holding A.
Okay, turn it over.
Put it on medium.
Down to low.
Put the patty over again.
Put it back on medium heat.
Flip it over again.
This is huge!
Who is this hamburger for?
This hamburger is a pancake!
I know who is going to eat this.
This is a challenge burger.
This is not a hamburger that you eat in a restaurant.
Choose freely.
All right, let's make my ultimate hamburger.
Are you ready?
Okay, we're doing cheese down first.
Then patty.
Then two slices of cheese.
Then lettuce.
Then the pickles.
Get them off.
No, no, no, no.
I don't like pickles.
That's it.
And then where's mayonnaise?
There's mayo.
A little bit of mayo and then a little bit of...
That's done.
I'm done.
There were no onions.
No, I would do some fresh chopped raw onions too.
Or maybe some cooked caramelized onions if they were available.
But they were not.
That's...
Okay, if there was a little bit of mayonnaise on that
and there was some caramelized onions,
I want to eat that right now.
Wait, I told you if it was caramelized or not caramelized,
I'd like it either way.
Or you know what?
Get...
Listen to this.
It was unavailable.
Get rid of the lettuce.
Hear me?
Mushrooms.
Sauteed mushrooms on top of that.
A little bit of fucking...
A little bit of A1 steak sauce on top of the bun.
Or...
Nothing.
Bad sauce.
Ew.
Wait, I just made the...
I made the...
I just made that.
Reversed.
Washed.
Oh, this is the blood soup, right?
I know how to make this.
Good to you.
Okay.
That Hachini.
I love that Hachini.
Salisbury steak.
Can I make the blood soup?
All right.
I'm going to make blood soup.
A1 steak sauce.
Oh, sorry.
Or barbecue sauce.
Or something very, very dense.
Or just some Swiss cheese.
A little bit of mayo.
Mushroom.
A mushroom in Swiss hamburger, guys, is incredibly common and very popular.
I don't know what you guys are talking about.
A Swiss cheese in mushroom hamburger is on every menu at every restaurant you've ever
been to that serves more than three different kinds of hamburgers.
What...
Where are you guys from?
Fucking Maz?
Dude, I'll go even a step further.
I'll go a step further.
You want me to go a step further?
I will.
I'm one of those guys that I would be totally happy if you gave me just sauteed mushrooms
with butter.
I would just eat the fuck out of them.
Sauteed mushrooms and onions with butter.
I would just eat that and I would be happy.
They're so unbelievably delicious.
Sauteed mushrooms in butter is un-fucking-bearably delicious.
I can't even imagine somebody that would disagree with that.
Those of you that get it, imagine like right when you're done sauteing and they're in the
butter, the mushrooms, and you take that forkful and you just taste it to make sure
you got it right.
Imagine not liking that and not thinking that was at the top of the list.
Can you imagine being that person?
I'm that guy that sounds awful.
It's so good.
Hold on, there's a cattle.
Mushroom crew.
He's preaching.
Beets are okay.
I don't like to eat beets.
I like to drink beets.
They kind of taste like dirt.
A nice beet salad though, it's okay.
But beets blended in with another juice or something as a base.
I like beet juice.
I think it's okay.
I'm not a big fan of people that drive by 100 miles per hour by next to the house.
I'm really not a fan of that.
How do I feel about borscht?
I've never had it actually.
I've never eaten this.
It looks like it'll be alright.
Beet salad?
Yeah, beet salad's good.
Alright, I'll get this one right now.
White powder?
What is white powder?
What is that?
What's going on?
Hello?
Why is nothing blinking?
I have to shake?
What happened?
Mama, tell me!
Mama, tell me what you want!
Mama!
You can't just stare at me, Mama!
It didn't crash?
The timer's still going.
This is where Mama goes.
Oh, sorry.
She puts her phone down on the fucking table and it's like, Mom!
Remove the foam.
Hold the V button while pulling upward and lift the foam?
What is this, bacteria?
No, borscht is awesome, Jeremy.
You just have to remove the mold that cooks off.
That's fat from the meat?
I know what it is.
Thank you for taking the bait.
Thank you.
Alright, let's do it.
He doesn't know.
I was merely pretending the whole time.
Can I put this in?
How about a little bit of this?
Yeah, some laurel.
Next goes in the blood.
Didn't have a blood soup without blood.
And then the cabbage.
Where are the beans?
I said I didn't forget it.
There's blood in the borscht?
I'd probably try it.
It looks like it would be alright.
This is not even how you make borscht.
I mean, it's close enough.
What are those?
Potato tots?
Tater tots.
Tater...
Chicken kieb.
Uh, yeah.
Wait, is this like chicken cordon bleu?
Is this like a frost filled with ham and chicken and cheese and stuff?
That was pretty good.
I like chicken cordon bleu.
Alright, mince meat.
I love chicken cordon bleu.
It's so good.
This is human skin.
Why did you say that and why did I read that?
Butter, salt.
That was easy.
It's basically chicken nuggets.
Aw, damn you, I'm fasting.
It's supposed to be cheapy, Robo.
I know, I'm sorry.
I know.
It will be tomorrow.
I will buy like ten different memory cards.
And an SD card.
I'll have them all connected at the same time to make sure it works.
Alright, let's shape it up.
These are hefty chicken nuggets.
He's getting disgusting hands all over our chicken nuggets.
I already winked.
I just did.
Oh, that was a big one.
Wink again.
These are huge.
Use your feet to make the nuggets instead of your hands.
Oh my god.
This is like a whole breast.
This is like mom or dad doesn't care anymore.
Can you make me chicken nuggets?
Yeah, sure.
Here.
Just bite it.
Just eat it slow.
Just one super nugget.
Alright, grate the cheese.
I'm pretty good at grating cheese at this point.
Not cheese, by the way.
Alright, eggs.
Can't make a chicken kebab without eggs.
What is she saying?
Do not what?
Do not nine?
What is she saying?
Do not mind?
Alright, stir it up.
Don't go too fast.
Put that over a hot stove.
Steam it a little bit.
Rizzle that on some eggs with some toast.
You guys sell fucking fake eggs Benedict.
Try the chicken.
Alright, this is kind of ridiculous.
Okay, got it.
Not done.
Stop rubbing mold on the chicken nuggets.
I got a super scroller on that.
Heat fry.
When they're fully cooked, grab them with the B button.
Alright, we're going to do one at a time.
Three at a time is fine.
Okay, so let's increase the heat a little bit.
Over the heat a little.
Are they done?
Are these done?
Oh my god, they're black!
Turn the heat down.
I got to get at least one.
Otherwise the judges are going to fucking kill me.
Mine didn't look like that.
These look kind of good.
I would eat these.
These actually look pretty good.
I feel like this would be like cutting into these.
You get the moist chicken with the crunchy outside.
What is this over here though?
What's this moss? What is that?
I didn't make that.
New recipe.
Beef stroganoff.
Alright, what did we miss?
We didn't do shrimp and chili sauce.
Let's do shrimp and chili sauce.
Lettuce.
Can't we just cut it up?
Prepare. Rip the head off the squid.
And then dump all of its ink into a bowl.
Head of the mama, that's good.
Alright, chop. Chop time.
He's going to puke again.
That's a lucky one.
Right down the middle like that.
You know one of my favorite snacks was growing up?
Take a celery stalk.
Like the boat inside the boat of the celery.
Cut off the ends right.
Smear peanut butter down the middle.
Inside the little crevice inside the boat section.
I loved it.
Celery peanut butter into the celery boat.
That's pretty good. Yeah, no, it is good.
It's a good snack.
That's a boomer snack.
It's peanut butter and celery.
What, you guys don't like peanut butter?
I don't even know what to do.
What is this?
Ginger?
The zoomers only exist on a diet of uber eats.
Okay, drop in the oil.
Alright, when the oil reaches the
correct temperature, add ingredients.
Pilt them to coat them in the oil.
Quickly coat twice
then finish.
What? Quickly coat them twice
and then pull them out.
Quickly coat twice and then finish.
I'm just, okay,
look, it may have been raw, but I'm following the direction.
If that was on the back
of like the blue apron
card, quickly coat
twice and then take them out.
I'd be like, okay, idiot, I just follow
the instructions. I don't know what the fuck I'm doing.
Alright, sorry, I can cook them right here.
They're gonna cook right here
anyway. We'll put them in for a little bit longer.
There we go, and that chili sauce.
Alright.
Come on, shrimp. They cooked in here.
That's fine. Why'd I have to cook them twice?
I'm gonna mix squid ink in with your peanut butter.
Did he ever apologize to
Mama? Yeah, like two hours ago.
Where have you been?
Was that crab?
Ooh, I like crab.
What is this?
Stir-fried crab.
Oh, stir-fried crab.
Let me try this.
Stir-fried crab.
I love crab.
This went from
it's a chibi-robo stream to everybody
get hungry watching me play
a 20-year-old cooking game.
Stir-fried crab.
I don't want that.
What is such a fun system? What a fun system
this was. I wish the memory card worked.
Sorry, we're past it.
Alright, shake the Wii mode up and down
to chop the ingredients.
Damn, that's it.
This is chunky.
The SD card will work.
I'll make sure this is ready to go.
I'll make sure of it by tomorrow.
Alright, cut the pieces.
A lot of ginger.
It is kind of a lot of ginger.
Whoa, alright.
Turn all the legs off.
Alright, come on. Now what? That's it?
This kills the crab.
No. No.
I don't think so.
What are you talking? Alright.
Same thing. Oil.
Coat them in the oil. Quickly coat them
twice and then finish.
Ow! What?
You can't cook a fucking crab like
that. You don't just put it
in hot oil and take it
out.
That's not how you make food.
You just wasted an entire crab. That crab
was probably like $140.
It's not that expensive.
Crab meat's cheap. Well, it depends on what kind of
crab this is.
What is this? Is this crab? Blue crab?
Snow crab? King crab?
It depends on what kind of crab
this is. You can get all kinds of expensive
crabs. It's the pay attention
crab. Ah.
Soy sauce. We're going next.
Oyster sauce.
And potato
starch. This looks really good.
Serve as much
as you'd like. Oh, alright. Let's serve
it. I mean serve as much as you
like. Wait, no. How do I
let's put them back together?
Where are the vegetables?
No shit! I was trying to serve it. I was
gonna make my own crab with the
I was gonna make a fake crab with the tomato
as a head. Crab
and two cherry tomatoes.
That's a lot of crab though. You wouldn't be
complaining.
Alright, let's go back here.
Mapo tofu.
Beef stroganoff.
Let's get it.
Go back to American food. There's only been two.
There's only been two American foods.
Just wait till we get the accurate
like 3 a.m. Captain Crunch.
Popcorn, hot dog, and hamburger.
Alright, mama, don't fuck this up.
Popcorn, hot dog, hamburger.
Yeah, why is the American food the stuff
that you could order at a baseball game?
That's where it ends.
Alright, let's mince.
Good.
They should have you make apple pie.
How many recipes are even in this game?
Are there a lot of recipes in the game?
How many recipes are in the game?
You making a PC?
No, there's no RAM here.
There's no RAM here, man.
There's every single dish ever made.
Nice.
So unhealthy.
Cooking with a bunch of butter in the pan.
Use avocado oil, idiot.
Wink.
Get a little salt on there. Get some wine.
Get some pepper on there.
Quickly, quickly, quickly.
Stew.
A lot of stews in this game.
Where's the fucking, where's the pizza?
Alright, add salt.
Add milk for a baby.
Bondu.
It's a little heavy on the onion, but
karma looks like a basement dweller.
Well, I'm not in a basement dweller.
I'm in an office.
Come on.
Beef stroganoff.
That looks pretty good.
Now, have I done them all?
Wait, I didn't do Salisbury Steak.
You know, of all the
foods in the world, I've
never eaten Salisbury Steak.
But every time I see it, I want it.
It looks so
delicious and yummy and
full of flavor. I want it so bad, but I've never
had it before. I see it all the time
and I want it.
I feel like I would really like it. Let's see what's
in it. It's a burger with sauce?
I would probably like it.
It's like a weird read between
hamburger and meatloaf.
I would probably really like it.
Let's see.
I'll tell you at the end if I eat it.
It's high in sodium, but it's really good.
Mushroom gravy.
Wait, there's mushrooms on here.
Are there sauteed mushrooms on a Salisbury
Steak? Yes.
Why have I not eaten my favorite food yet?
This is probably my favorite food.
Sauteed mushrooms. It's like a hamburger
with gravy and sauce on it.
Try it.
I'll get it next time I haven't.
Wait, you can't order this.
Where do you get Salisbury Steak?
You can't order it at a restaurant.
I have to make it
myself? I'm not very good at that.
No, I'm not going to get the one that's in the frozen
food section. No. I want a real one.
At a diner. What
is this?
Egg, okay.
Breadcrumbs.
Pepper.
Nutmeg.
At a diner?
It's at Southern Shit Diners.
Hey, where do I get Salisbury
Steak? Oh, at a Southern Shit
Diner.
Let me look that up on Yelp
and see what it's got for reviews.
God damn it.
Salisbury Steak.
I want this though. What is this part?
What's this right here?
What is that? Is that supposed to be like a
cheese or is that another meat?
Is that the cheese with the wax on it?
That's salmon?
Oh, why would that be in Salisbury Steak?
You told me it was sauteed mushrooms and meatloaf.
You didn't say there was a crab shell on here.
Alright, make the
hamburger. Dragon fruit.
Are you talking? Why would they be dragon fruit
in this?
I just saw myself in the fucking webcam.
I didn't like that. That's fucking
weird. Okay, spread the
butter. Alright, we're getting to
that next step coming up here.
Like the salmon.
See, this doesn't go in the oven.
I always thought that Salisbury Steak
was the thing you made in the oven.
No.
He doesn't know?
Fucking egg.
What?
Is eggs on here?
Shake to shake it and then
yeah, mix it. Hold the Wii mode upright and turn it around
while holding B and then A is salt.
You cook eggs?
Those look good.
Those look
good.
Let's make the big pie.
Turn it. Medium heat.
Sear it on one side.
Look at the loaf. Spin it.
I know what this smells like too.
Like if I lean
in and just put my face over the screen, like I
could smell that.
Oh, that smells so good.
Especially the mushrooms
scent in there.
Oh, it smells so good.
Smell-O-Vision. Alright, make some
decorative cuts.
Where's the mushrooms?
Why is there a fucking
decorative hot dog?
I would pick that off
the plate and like set
it slowly aside next
to me. Off the plate.
I wouldn't, I don't, I wouldn't want to eat that.
Alright, serve as much as you'd like.
Okay, what is this?
Happy birthday.
You can just put as many
as you want. Why?
What is this? What is this?
Dessert? Hold on, wait,
wait. Yes, I ordered the sauce
for a steak. Oh, okay, sure.
Oh yeah, this is a dozen
eggs. And
this really flogs that we've been in the fridge
since last Wednesday. Wait,
where are the mushrooms? What is that?
Sausages?
What is that? Sausages.
Yup, let's go.
Grate the cheese. Do we make
the links? Do we actually make them?
Not everything needs to have mushrooms
you spore snorter.
The thing is, I don't, I only
like the, okay, I don't know much
about mushrooms. I just know the one that I like.
I like the
the ones you just buy
at the grocery store that are just sitting there
that are in the package.
What are they? Portobello?
I don't like it. That's the only one I like.
The grocery
store ones.
The ones that are already chopped up
that are in the little package with the plastic on
top. And there's like 700 of them lined up.
The grocery store mushroom.
Colorado? They look
like a white, like they're white.
They're white.
They're white button mushrooms.
They're not portobello. They're called button mushrooms.
3D printed
mushrooms.
Why does this stream have 6,000
viewers?
I don't know.
Why does this stream
have 10 viewers? What are you doing
here? What are you doing
here? Is this seaweed?
Parsley.
Because your face came to the zone.
Why do I believe that?
Not bad, not bad.
Alright, need the sausages.
I want to put them in the casing.
Is it natural casing?
Okay, a lot of times
you go to the store or you find sausages
Oh, natural casing.
All natural casing.
Right? What is
unnatural casing? What is that?
Plastic.
Natural casing
is like intestines
or something. What is unnatural casing?
It's an edible plastic?
Why would anybody eat edible plastic?
Why would you ever buy that?
Why would you even make it like that?
Plastic? It's cheaper.
Okay, hold the B button to add minced
meat. Careful not to tear the skin
then tilt the Wii mode to twist the sausage
into links. Is this natural
casing, mama? I'm trying
to- I'm tilting the Wii mode.
How do I cut it?
How do I tear it?
Okay, got it. Just one
huge sausage.
Okay, I messed up one casing.
All right, throw it in a stew. That's how you make everything
in this game. You just boil it.
Eat on high.
Boil. Wink. I just did.
It's just sausages. There's nothing
else there. This is a house of
dish.
There's no seasoning.
Just sausages? That's it?
It's like some kind of ground up
stone mustard and lettuce.
There's nothing else in here. There was no seasoning or anything.
It's just boiled
hot dogs. New recipe.
This one's from England.
What's it? English food. Okay.
Fish and chips! Yep.
What's it gonna be?
Toast sandwich?
What does toast sandwich mean?
UK food is toast.
Toast? That's it?
That's all they eat in
England is toast.
Toast and beans.
Toast and beans. I actually like
that. I like
those. I like English beans.
Slow down! Slow!
Toast.
Eat in England.
He toasts sandwich.
They just eat toast.
That was pretty funny.
That was funny.
Toast.
He needs to do
manscaping?
Relax! Where?
Do I have chest hairs?
Alright, let's make the fish.
What the fuck? This is not...
I killed him! I killed him!
Your counter's too small for this,
mama. I'm not gonna filet
an entire swordfish
in my home kitchen.
Oh my goodness.
I thought it was a cob.
Isn't it like haddock or cod
for fish and chips?
This is an expensive fish and chips.
Swordfish.
Why would you fry
swordfish? Hold on.
Why would you fry swordfish?
That's not gonna cook.
That's gonna be fucked.
You don't put swordfish
in a fryer later.
It's too thin. You can't do that.
You don't cook
swordfish like this?
Hey, what are you doing? I'm waiting for the blink.
I didn't even move, mama.
Mama, I didn't even fucking move.
Fish and chips with swordfish.
This would be kinda gross.
I don't know if this would work.
Have you had swordfish before?
Yeah.
I like swordfish.
It's really easy to mess it up though.
Swordfish is like hard to cook.
Deep fry it.
This is wrong.
Take it easy.
You're not mine.
That was like $40 gone.
Take it out!
Watch that heat.
I'm trying to take it out of the
bow.
What is this, potatoes?
You're gonna get punched.
Good job.
I was hitting the fucking side.
Shadow streamer.
Yeah, I know, I'm in the truck and
dark.
We lost to fish and chips.
Oh, mega lulz.
America! The United
States of America!
What's on tap from our favorite dish?
I think it's a little further
south. I mean, I love
tacos. Tacos, burritos,
some of my favorite foods in the
world. But,
um, like, George Washington
didn't make it up.
I need it.
Yes, he did. Oh, yeah.
One of my favorite things George Washington, Ben
Franklin, one of my favorite things he invented
was the burrito.
Are you cooking, are you playing this on 3DS?
Yes.
Yes. You don't want to be that big,
right? That's good, that's good, that's good too much.
And then you sprinkle all the fucking ingredients
in there, get them all in there,
like, what's that thing?
Is this guy okay?
Let's make some pan. Ooh!
Ah, I love this.
It's so delicious.
A nice hot tortilla.
Whoa!
I want to eat this. I want
a nice, like, traditional
taco right now. You know what I mean?
With, like, that soft
like, that soft corn
tortilla.
I'll see you guys tomorrow.
See you guys tomorrow.
I'll be back, I'll see you guys in a little bit.
Don't you like when I do this?
Mince. Onion.
Let's get a little bit of
cilantro. Maybe some
carne asada. Oh!
And a corn tortilla.
A little bit of green chili sauce.
Oh my God!
I'm gonna see, I'm leaving.
The onions are browning?
Ah, it's alright.
Dude, why is it a hot dog?
I don't know what this is. My back of my
mouth right now. Right here.
Like, right here.
It's just, it's activating.
It's activating right now.
It's like that, Matt, you know
like that smell, that taco
meat smell? It's activating.
It's like in here, like back here.
What, are you a toot?
Am I a toot or
am I a teeth fucking hurt right now?
I gotta go to the dentist.
Is it a lizard? No.
I sound like glands. Yes, my glands
have been activated.
I just smelled that and it was like
into my nose, into the sinuses.
Activate glands. Glands are now producing
endorphins and serotonin
into my brain. My brain's saying
go get this right now. Put your
head over the pan to smell. Then that's
going all the way down to my stomach and my stomach goes
bleh. I can't wait.
I'm getting tacos tonight.
It's not a joke.
You have
salivary glands.
We can't talk science
in this chat room? Why not?
You're a dog.
I'm being real.
Why do I have such trouble with the lettuce?
I'm just trying to pull. Pull the
fucking thing.
I believe science.
I believe in the science of God.
Alright, I gotta make this.
I gotta make my taco.
Look at that JPEG.
Ugh.
Okay.
We're not at
Subway. Okay?
I don't know how many cheese triangles I would
put in. Okay. Where's the meat?
Where's the meat?
Where's the onions?
Why can't I just put it in?
That's a joke.
That's a
I have a friend that works at Subway.
And
I'll give you like six more triangles.
What am I even
looking at right here?
I can't even tell what that is.
Alright, what do we now do?
Alright, we gotta do this tofu dish.
No meat.
Oh my god.
It's a lot of
chopping.
How close am I to the Wii sensor bar?
Umm.
It is right here.
Right there.
Is that bad? Should I pull back a little?
Tofu.
The flavored soap
of the culinary world.
It has radiation.
Everything. What is all this?
Wasn't I doing tofu?
This is
tofu.
Wait, why
Wait, this is more
It's like three times more meat than tofu.
That's not a cube
meat. So what, we're doing tofu
and meat? What kind of meat was that?
It was minced
pork. Alright, take that up.
Alright, come on meat.
Come on, cup, cup, cup, cup, cup, cup, cup, cup, cup, cup, cup.
Alright, take it up.
Cutting the meat with the tofu.
Alright, now stew the
Mapo tofu.
In goes the spicy miso bean
sauce. More red chili
paste. Really crank it.
Soy sauce.
Let it simmer a little bit.
And we have white salt. Or is this garlic
powder? Onion powder? Potato starch.
I need it.
What does tofu taste like?
Whatever you decided to put
on it. You can make it taste like pretty much
anything. That's why I said it's
the flavored soap of the culinary
world.
New recipe. Ooh, what are those dumplings?
I love
dumplings. I love
dumplings.
Oh, they're pork buns. Okay. Oh, but still.
Pork dumplings seriously are
like, there's this place in
Paris. I forget the name of the restaurant
but there's a place in Paris that does, they have
a park that moves by in Paris.
No, no, no.
Paris Casino in Vegas.
Not like I went to
Paris and had steamed pork
buns.
There's a place in Paris that does
really, really good
steamed dumplings.
Yeah, I got the best
dumplings ever in Paris, France.
Dude, I can't.
Rich streamer goes to France.
No, I went to Pretend France
in Las Vegas.
Paris Resort and Casino. They have a
dumpling place. It's pretty good.
At the dumplings. You have the pork dumplings, the spicy
pork dumplings. They're fucking phenomenal.
What's the name of this place?
I say Hash House or Gogo every day.
Like, I might as well say another one.
Rich streamer eats out regularly on
the Las Vegas strip.
I've been to this place twice in two years.
It's not expensive.
He's blowing all the bits on dumplings.
What if I was? What if I was blowing
all the bits on delicious dumplings?
What if I was?
Would you rather
use it on drugs?
Didn't think so.
Let's make, we're gonna mince this.
Do a drug test.
I know a lot of
people will be like, whoa
Pog, let's make him do a drug
test.
I mean, my
fucking sodium level might be a little high.
Nothing on there.
Gonna be a lot of X's.
My cholesterol might be like slightly
elevated. I don't know.
Slightly. I eat pretty healthy guys.
I don't eat like crap every day.
I just told you guys
about one of my favorite snacks.
It was peanut butter and celery. And everyone was like
UGH!
That's like a healthy thing to eat.
That's not healthy.
But wait, what year
is it where peanut butter is not
seen as a healthy food right now?
What planet
are we on? Peanut butter is
you could fucking literally live on peanut butter.
You could eat peanut butter
and live off of it. It's got everything.
Peanut butter is very
It's not a saturated
fat. You guys, fat is not
bad. There are good fats.
All fat is not bad.
Who told you this?
Who told you that fat was bad?
Yeah,
don't drink the fucking grease
out of the pan when you're done cooking your hamburger.
But all the unsaturated
monounsaturated fats are
are good.
What doctor are you going to?
Everybody knows this.
I'm going to fuck
people fucking with you.
So many hydrogenated oils. Get the real stuff.
Imagine being a doctor.
I'm not a fucking doctor.
Real peanut butter is good for you.
What?
This is not like wow.
Hold on, I'm going to steam these.
Turn it off!
Magic cooking was just fucking hard.
All right, you put it in there for one second
and turn it off at the exact moment or you're going to burn it.
Idiot doctor.
Mmm, those look good.
So you want to see how
you want to see just how
ridiculous Earth is right now.
I hurt my hand, accidentally hit it
on my desk. You didn't see it. I just typed
in peanut butter of radiation.
Let me just shut it off here.
Are peanuts radioactive and do they cause
cancer? I had an x-ray
recently.
All right.
I ate like 50,000 bananas.
For like 200 million bananas.
I'll never eat
that many bananas in my life.
This is huge.
Wait, is this tofu? Is this a bath towel?
What's my favorite fruit? Kiwis.
Whoa, I put it on the wiki.
I didn't know that.
Wait, I gotta pay for this.
That's actually kiwis. Kiwis are fucking unbelievable.
You can't eat a kiwi
and not like it. It's so sweet.
When you bite down
on the seeds, they're a little bit
chewy. You get that little snap
on the seeds. Nothing is better
than that. Yeah, if you know, you
know. How many do you eat?
No, I don't eat the skin.
I don't eat the skin. It's like fuzzy and weird.
Watermelon? Do we...
Watermelons are pretty good.
Watermelon is almost like a dessert
fruit, though, because it's just
water. There's nothing really
in it. It's just water.
It's the first word of the fruit.
I love it. I like watermelon,
but you're essentially
breathing air when you eat a watermelon.
Xiaomian? Oh, I love
Xiaomian. BRB? I'm gonna
stick my head in a watermelon. Why?
Pineapple sucks.
Pineapple's my second favorite fruit.
Pineapple has bromelain
in it. Like, oh my god,
holy shit, I can't believe this guy knows what that is.
I thought he was just an idiot.
I didn't know how to knead dough in Cooking Mama.
Let's get bromelain in it. It's good for you.
I don't eat too much pineapple, though,
because the same thing that's good for you
actually is like a flesh-eating enzyme.
I don't eat too much, just enough.
Ooh. Oh!
Do it! Dude,
this is sick!
Why is it all going onto the floor?
Granny Smith apples to guard here. Green
apples. Green apples are better than red
apples. Pax! Just hit
right here. Yep. Xiaomian?
Macintosh apples are better
than both of them combined.
No, no, no, no, no.
I'll throw the axe.
Like, that was wrong.
Macintosh apples are better than
Granny Smith apples, but
green apples are
better than Macintosh apples.
Okay, that's better.
I love the little soft
Macintosh apples. You can just eat them.
They're so...
The flesh is so mushy and so
easy to bite through. I don't like eating
apples because I have to cut them up and
carve them up and shit.
I want to eat it with my hand. And a lot of times
when I eat an apple, it's like...
Ow, ow, ow, ow, ow, ow!
This hurts. This hurts.
And I use my
bottom fucking teeth to go in harder.
It hurts. I don't want to do that.
Curry. Ooh, nice.
I see a dentist. My teeth are in fucking
perfect condition.
You want my teeth? You want my x-rays from my dentist?
It's like releasing your
tax returns. Let's see the x-rays of your
teeth. Let's see your teeth
returns.
Alright, let's grate that cheese.
Ginger or
ginseng or whatever it is.
If Kim was in the room right now,
she would be doing the thing
I was doing when I was making
the tacos onto the spring.
She'd be going, oh my god,
yes! Oh, look at that!
Kim loves curry.
Does she like curry?
Yeah, I guess.
Alright, let's put it together.
Fruit tier list? I already did it.
I did a fruit tier list.
Human.
Remake it?
I'm not going to remake
the list. Oh shit, I can do this!
I'll put the cinnamon in it.
I didn't know I could do that. Get it in the stew.
Are you depressed?
No, I just, okay.
I have deep set eyes.
Okay, sorry.
Dude, are you angry? Is something
wrong? Why do you look like you're going
to swing at me? I have deep
set eyes. I can't, what?
That's what it is.
There's a shadow cast over my eyes forever.
And it just makes me
look villainous because there's a shadow here
because of the lighting. If you see me out
in person, I look happy.
I have deep set eyes.
Why do you stream in the dark?
Do we have to talk about this
every stream?
I start the stream during the day
and during the night time,
if I have my webcams
gain up, I'll get blown out.
Why do we have to keep
explaining this? And I don't use auto.
This looks much better?
I disagree. Nice chest tier.
I was going to give the finger to the camera,
but I decided not to.
Because it would be used against me.
Alright, I fuck
this up every time.
Slowly pour it, right?
Slowly pour it out, right?
Okay, slowly pour it.
We have to
bake it? Steam the rice.
Let's go.
What do I think of Cadbury Eggs?
I'll tell you.
You've never seen the commercial?
Oh, right. Because
you have not seen that.
Right. Cadbury Eggs had a commercial
with a bunny rabbit that did a chicken sound
like that. Exactly like that?
Um, okay.
I forget that I'm probably 20 years older than half
the people in this chat room.
Sometimes I forget.
I'm 25. I never saw that.
I'm still 10 years older than you.
I'm a decade older than you. Think about that.
I'm 10 years older than you.
Look at the wisdom
that I have that you don't.
Wait, didn't I just make this?
Am I making this?
Am I remaking this?
I'm doing it. I'm doing it again.
This is a different one. Okay.
Okay, the lamb curry.
Let's cut it up into pieces.
I love that sound. That like
shwoop, shwoop.
What happened to Chibi-Robo?
I got pushed to tomorrow.
The disc was broken.
I had to return it.
Like, I got a fucking broken disc.
I don't know what happened inside the way it broke.
Actually, I'll be honest with you.
I've got to make sure I prepare that.
I've got to get that ready to go.
There cannot be any fucking
mistakes there.
I will make sure that that's what we're doing
tomorrow. No matter what.
The SD card is a couple of options.
I just didn't want to do it like in the middle of the stream.
Like, I would have fucked something up and it would have been bad.
Give me another one. Another bullseye.
Rage, quit Chibi-Robo.
Cook, not gonna lie. You'll be
vibing. So I'm just gonna give 20
subs. Knock, turn.
Knock, turn.
Thanks for the 20 community subs.
Tak-ta-turn.
Knock, turn. Act-ta-turn.
Thank you. That's a fucking...
No problem.
That's a lot of subs. Thank you.
Congratulations to those that got the community
subs. Knock, turn.
Tax return?
What a god. People drop huge
sub-gifts in here.
This is kind of crazy.
Laurel? What is Laurel?
What is Laurel?
Yanny? What is a Yanny?
What are you guys all saying?
What are you guys doing? What is this?
What is a Yanny?
He's pretending. I don't know what
that is. I don't know what
Yanny is.
It's a joke.
It's how I'm pretending.
I don't know what...
I'm not pretending. I don't know what that is.
Do you
live under a rock?
I live technically under wood.
Hot ass.
I don't know what that is.
Oh, he's a wise guy.
He knows it sucks.
I...
Yeah, it sucks. Whatever.
I remember watching it when I was younger.
How am I going to make
this little doll up into something huge?
This is my favorite
game. I did not know he was playing it.
How did I not know I was... Well, because we had to pivot.
We had to do a hard pivot
in this game. This is not something
I planned on doing today.
But you're probably really happy to see that it's here.
Cilantro,
carne asada, green chili sauce.
Oh, yep.
We're good.
Cilantro tastes like soap.
If you use
too much of it, I agree with you. I don't like a lot
of cilantro. I like just enough to get a little bit
of that flavor.
Too much
cilantro just doesn't taste
great. My father hates
cilantro. If my father's even in
the same room as cilantro, he will
throw up. Did I do them all?
What's left?
Holy shit, there's a whole page I didn't do. The cream puffs!
What am I thinking? I didn't do the cream puff.
Cream puffs with ice cream
are better than cream puffs with the cream.
Is that, um, accurate for a lot of you guys?
That's wrong?
That's okay. Is it soggy?
Well, you have to eat it right away. You gotta eat it right away.
Stew?
Oh, we're making sugar?
Oh my god, vomit
father. I thought we were over
that. Vomit father.
That's a lot of butter. I don't
even know what to say.
It makes me cry! Just eat
butter. Vomit father.
Why is there an egg going in
here?
What is this?
Local streamers afraid of butter?
It's custard, dummy.
Well, get away from me, because I go violent!
Oh, I can't, okay.
I finished, I fucking, I can't.
I have ADHD.
Let's use that as an excuse for literally everything
I've ever done in my whole, my entire life.
Okay, good.
Now do it like this.
Jeremy!
Blah blah!
He's snapping all the time.
I don't give a shit.
Alright.
Turn off!
Do it that quick.
Oh, he will. He will.
Anything can be...
We've seen like five to ten different deepfakes
at this point. Do you think I really care?
Do you think I'm at the point right now
where I'm like, man, I really hope they don't like
put me in something that I'm not
in? Not right now!
What's Jello made of?
I don't know.
Bones.
Jelly, on the other hand. Why would you
do it like this?
What the fuck?
Only one egg? I can't try again?
It's wasting.
It was implied that she's just doing it for me.
What's the difference between jam and jelly?
Tons of differences.
A fucking huge amount of differences.
But we're not going to get into them today.
Jelly is based...
It's just based Jello.
What are you talking about?
Vanilla extract.
Can't that stuff kill you?
If you have too much vanilla extract,
can it kill you?
Anything can kill you. Yeah.
Probably. If you chug it...
No, it's like straight alcohol, right?
It's very bad.
Hold the B button to squeeze the cream
onto the pastry. Be careful!
Alright, let's do it.
I don't know what you're talking about,
Mama.
This is how me and my family
like it.
That one in the top row, I would grab it immediately.
Too much cream?
I don't think this is actually a sentence
that makes sense when you say that.
Too much cream in your cream-filled
pastry. I don't know about that.
Ooh! What's that one?
Ooh, lasagna. My least favorite
Italian delight.
Dessert. Whatever.
My least favorite Italian
fantastic food.
Lasagna.
Actually, I don't like it.
Those of you that might be new
viewers,
I'll eat lasagna, but I don't really...
I would choose not to eat lasagna.
To me, it's kind of...
I don't know. It's kind of boring.
It kind of bores me.
Do you like spaghetti and meatballs?
Yeah, I do, but
lasagna is...
It's always like
mushes together.
It's usually like a meat sauce
and just layers of this
pasta sheets, and you take your fork
and just mush through it.
I don't know. I'm not...
I'll eat it. I don't hate it.
But I wouldn't order it.
It just doesn't do it for me.
It's like a spaghetti cake.
That's a good way to put it.
Do you like balsamic vinegar?
No.
I don't.
I actually don't.
I love olive oil, though.
It's like one of my favorite things on Earth.
That I can't stand by.
Why not?
A really good EVOO just dumped on top
of hummus. I could eat that every day
and be happy. You could just put me into a room
and have a fridge
in there, and in that fridge was just a ton of
just garlic hummuses,
some pita bread to the right, just like
hundreds of bags of it, and then
like 30 bottles of EVOO.
And you'd think like you were
torturing me, and I would be like, no, this is perfect.
Thanks. See you in a
fucking couple months when I want more of this.
Mr. Virgin olive oil.
Yeah, what's wrong with that?
Do I have an irritation under here or something? What's going on?
I'm a little irritated under here.
Why?
A mold rash.
EVOO.
Extra virgin olive oil.
Oh, I can taste it already.
So many foods.
I love food.
I'm a really
food motivated person.
You're a dog.
Says the man that doesn't eat lasagna.
Yeah, I have my different preferences,
but I love food.
You don't look like it.
I
really love food.
I never said I like to eat
too much of it every day.
When did I say I love food?
And I love eating way more than I'm
supposed to. Every day.
Well, I didn't say that.
Get that butter in there.
Hold on, guys.
Not ideal.
They're struck a nerve
there.
McDonald's?
I like McDonald's.
Onions.
All right.
Perfect timing.
Onions.
McDonald's is good.
If you say that McDonald's sucks,
you're probably smart.
You probably have a lot of intelligence
and your brain is huge.
I mean, come on.
For the rest of us, dumb fucking idiots.
You only eat McDonald's if you're
a fucking moron. For all of us other idiots.
I think it's
good. I like it.
I don't eat it all the time.
Here we go.
Idiot crew.
The idiot move is not going to Wendy's.
They're all good.
You just feel like them sometimes.
You go on a stint where you want one
of a month's rate.
And you don't want the other one.
Tomatoes, though.
Wendy's is dog shit.
No, I
ate it too much. So I'm just sick of
eating it. All right. Time to make
some lasagna. Memorize the example.
First,
a point of degree. First, a point to add the ingredients in the same
order. Make it in the same
order. All right.
Mushrooms, meat,
sheet.
Meat, sheet, mushrooms.
What is all that on top?
All right.
Meat, mushroom, sheet,
sheet.
That lasagna is terrible.
That's a true mess up.
Sheet, meat, mushroom,
sheet, sheet.
Sheet, meat, mushroom, sheet,
meat, mushroom, sheet, sheet.
Holy shit.
All right.
Put it in the oven.
We're going to cook this slow.
Slow.
Five degrees.
Looks like banana bread.
A lot of very good. Got something new.
This is a new dish.
Ooh.
Pumpkin.
Grilled bonito.
Hand fried lobster.
Let's do the bonito.
Gotta dice up the fish. What kind of fish is it?
It's a bonito.
Filet-o.
Head. Oh, sad face. His head.
He's slaughtering a fish.
Why are there four different salts?
I don't know.
It's like
sea salt and Himalayan
pink salt.
Deep salt. I don't know.
There's a lot of different salts.
Grill.
We didn't have the grill yet.
Hold the fan with the B button and wave it to increase
the heat.
How do I flip it?
Turn it over.
That looks pretty good.
Fish to me.
I love video game fish.
Hey.
You didn't tell me to take it off.
Video game fish looks so appetizing.
I like fish too in real life.
It's something about in a video game.
Just a fish on like a stick.
You know what I'm saying?
SpongeBob?
How many of these do I have?
Ah, that was raw.
It's the newest fish from SpongeBob.
All right.
Move the Weemo.
We're going to cut it up.
It's cooked, right?
It would.
I feel like it was tough to cut through that.
Shouldn't it have been moist and tender?
There's some grating.
Orito's the hardest food in the world.
The hardest to make
or it's physically hard
to chew through.
It's hard.
Physically hard.
You could kill someone with it.
Really? So that's accurate.
So it's like a big block.
How are you supposed to eat it?
How do you eat this?
Fine dining.
Plate was $180.
You shave it into strips, you idiot.
Why didn't Mama not do that?
That was an inch and a half thick cut.
I'm the idiot.
I'm sure it's not Mama's instructions
and Mama's bad recipe.
You consume it as an enema.
I should go to a restaurant.
Yeah, I'll take the bonito.
How's your bonito?
Is it any good?
Well, it's one of our more famous dishes.
You're like, I'm not sure.
Let me just get an opinion here.
You look over, there's a guy like two tables over
who's like,
Hey, how's the bonito?
Fantastic.
Okay.
Too salty?
It's just perfectly, perfectly seasoned.
I'll try the bonito.
Oh, bruschette.
What is bruschette?
Oh, dude, bruschette's the hottest
fucking food in the world. You could kill somebody
with this loaf of red meat.
Thinly sliced.
This conversation wouldn't have happened in Chibi
Robo. Yes, it would have.
Why are you giving...
You're giving a lot of credit
to the fact that we would have this same conversation
in Chibi... There's a cooking mission
in Chibi Robo. Isn't there?
Cooking Chibi Robo? Don't you
make food for the family and stuff? I can't wait
to play it. God damn it, Jeremy.
Get it right.
It's I hope we never part.
Get it right or pay the price.
Up in two pieces.
Ooh, I love asparagus.
This is... That's a huge
asparagus. Shiitake.
Onya. Worst joke
in the night. By far.
Like, by far.
That was so bad. I'll
take that one.
That was really bad.
Wait, you roll the onion into the meat?
You roll the mushrooms into the meat?
Hold on a second.
It's a thinly sliced piece of
meat, like beef or steak.
And you put a big chunk of onion in
and you roll it up.
Why have I not eaten this yet?
I think I would really like this.
And you place it on a stick
in the same order.
So it's almost like a kebab?
Okay, so...
What the hell are you talking about?
Wait, I'm supposed to guess?
No, take that off.
Why are you making me guess, Mom?
I really thought I was going to get a first try here.
Wait, it's the same every time, isn't it?
Oh, okay. Right. I thought they switched
it up on you.
One more. Thoughts on the democratic debate.
Ah! Eh! Eh! Eh!
Turn it! God, it's like
sucks being the grill guy, you know what I mean?
Like, I don't want to fuck up everybody's food at the party.
But I'm not qualified to be over here.
I'm the only one that said I just raised my hand
when somebody said, hey, who can get on the fucking grill?
Oh, there's like
a hundred people here that I could fucking poison.
It's great. Put me on.
Don't eat that one. No, no, no, no.
Don't eat that one. Throw it in the trash.
Throw it in the trash.
This hurts the old arm here.
By the way, why are we in like
14th century England?
Where's like the
propane or the fucking charcoal?
I didn't even cook this one.
It just started rotting.
Did you use your other hand? No, I'm a brighty.
Propane and propane accessories.
Actually, I wonder
how dividing this
will be.
I like a grilled food,
right? I'm a big fan
more than propane. I like charcoal
more than propane.
I think charcoal tastes better.
Alright, is that
weird?
Alright, that's it.
Let's eat pan-fried lobster.
Everybody agrees with that. Alright.
Some people are like, no, man.
Jesus.
Why did I cut his arms off first?
There's a lot of things here.
White powder, white powder.
Uh,
Pokmon 1, Pokmon
2, and then
Pokmon 3.
Now, that's the worst joke.
You're getting it. You understand.
That's the cover up of the last one.
You'll remember that one. You won't remember the other one.
Just fucking complete and total
tactics.
Everyone's going to be like,
dude, remember the Pokmon
green joke thing?
It was so bad.
Alright, dude, that was not funny.
Yeah, and then you're not going to talk about the other one.
But I win.
I win.
The house always wins.
I really eat
grilled lobster or like
pan-fried lobster.
I'm actually not a huge fan of
lobster, but usually
I don't eat it like that.
I know
it's a really popular way to eat it, but
I don't eat like grilled or pan-fried lobster.
Alright, let's serve it.
Why is dessert
on the same plate? I don't get it.
He doesn't know?
I mean, why would you... Dessert on the same plate
just seems... You get like lobster juice
in your flan. Aren't you going to be a little upset?
You don't like lobster?
Where are you actually from?
I don't hate it.
I would prefer crab.
I like crab more than lobster.
Lobster.
Wherever it is.
Alright, we're moving on.
How much do we have left?
Pettuccini.
Tortilla.
We've done a shitload of these.
Whitefish manure.
Meatloaf with sausage?
I thought this was like a raspberry pound cake.
Let's do the whitefish manure.
Menure.
Menure? Menoir? How do you say it?
How do you phonetically pronounce it?
Manoir?
Mou-nier?
Mou-nier. Mou-nier.
Whitefish manure.
It's garlic in everything.
Imagine if you were like allergic to fucking garlic.
You would never be able to eat food.
It's put in everything.
Oh, salt.
Nearly finished.
Flatfish.
Go for it.
Ooh.
Filling up the skin.
That easy, apparently.
Better than mama.
Whitefish manure.
Add to the milk?
Soak
fish in milk.
I won't be eating this anytime soon.
I will not be ordering
whitefish manure.
I don't think I will.
What does this taste like?
Shake the milk and then
flour the flour? Is it fried?
Somebody just fucked with me.
Somebody fucked with me.
That's like I took the salt
shaker. I'm going to put some salt on
and the whole thing comes out like the
shitty prank.
Somebody pranked me.
So bad.
Alright, now we pan fry
our milk fish.
Milk and flour.
I mean, I guess that's not super
weird. I guess it's not weird or anything.
It's just kind of different.
Although you
soak it in the milk. You don't just like
lay it in there for a second. You soak it.
It's two different fishes.
What about the bones?
There's a void there.
There it is.
It's how you make fried chicken.
I think chicken is a little different than fish. I don't know if I'd want
milk on fish.
I don't know about this.
Something about this is weird.
No new American dishes
by the way.
Oh!
Bulabase.
French bulabase.
Scallops.
Scallop, huh?
It's like the only little thing you know.
You're using a chisel to get a scallop?
What fish is that?
It's like Stardew Valley fish. What was that?
What animal is this?
It's weird meat.
Round like red animal.
Why are you farming?
I don't know because it's fun.
Why am I cooking a tail?
You don't eat the tail?
Why do you need three salt shakers? I don't know.
Ask mama. It's her house.
I use the spices to
flavor the spices.
How do I pronounce this?
How do you actually pronounce it?
Bulabase.
Come on!
The bulabase is
silent.
I think I've had this before.
Yeah, I've eaten this before.
This is delicious.
There's like a bunch of seafood, like that tomato base.
It's fantastic. I've had this before.
It's alive? No, it's not.
Kim ordered it and I tried it.
I had like three or four sips of the broth and I tried like one of those scallops and shit.
Kim, you're so worldly
and cultured.
I thought that was American.
I thought it was going to be like a Cobb salad.
Crudite?
It is a Cobb salad.
What is this?
Remove the yolk. Alright.
I caught it! You're kind of losing me here.
Eggs and vinegar?
That's a lot of vinegar.
You know like the way that raw eggs smell?
Now imagine
raw eggs and vinegar
in the same...
That's mayo? That's not mayo.
Mayo's oil. I mean, no.
Old men like peppers.
It's a stable
emulsion of oil, egg yolk, and an acidity of vinegar
or lemon juice.
Give it like a tiny bit.
Like only a little bit of lemon juice.
You don't like dump half the bottle in like she was.
Cutting is satisfying.
It really is.
Red pepper, yellow pepper,
and onion.
Maybe it's a lot of mayo.
Making an egg salad.
I love egg salad.
Oh, this is the last pieces for some reason.
I do.
I acknowledge it looks gross.
If you make egg salad
chunky enough, it looks a lot more
appetizing than if you make it paste.
Put a little bit of dill in there too.
You make it look not just like a paste.
You can go south real easily.
Well, you gotta eat it within a couple of days.
You can really get into trouble
with egg salad if you make it and you make a bunch of it
and then a week and a half goes by.
And you go,
oh man, I really want some of that egg salad.
And you open the fridge
and now your whole house smells like rotten egg.
Okay, here we go.
I don't know what this is.
It's like a salad
of some sort.
I've never had this.
Like, I wanna, fuck it, I don't even care.
You're really gonna have to
fucking find it, you know what I mean?
You really gotta search for it in there.
It's a nest
for an egg.
It's an egg nest.
That's a stand up and leave
the restaurant kind of presentation.
That's a like,
excuse me,
what is this?
Is this gonna get fixed or
I don't want to check or anything
after this.
Let's make the raspberry pound cake.
Crack the egg.
Where's the American food?
Oh, I'm with you. I really am.
I've been playing it for this long because I want to see
what the American food is.
Bonus.
Fried butter.
Meatloaf with sausage.
Alright, let's go. Onion.
Chop it up.
What are we gonna make? Burgers?
We made burger before, but it was a long time ago.
I don't know that American cuisine
is not just hamburgers.
It's the rest of the menu
at that restaurant, which is 12 different burgers.
We've got a cheese burger.
A barbecue sauce
and onion rings burger.
A macaroni
and cheese burger.
It's not just hamburger.
And they all have really cool names.
Like we name it like, you know,
like the super juicer.
And it's like a fucking lettuce with like two
eggs on it.
Oh, the lazy sundae.
It's like two patties with
two pieces of bacon and like
a couple of hash browns on it.
Wait, that's American.
Where are all those?
I want that garlic in here.
Come on, onions.
Alright, whatever.
Make the webcam wider.
You wish you could see what was going on over here, don't you?
How's that?
Alright, meatloaf with sausage.
There's a whole wall of streaming trophies.
I would kill
the smell of some onions in a pan right now.
I mean, you probably have
onions in your house.
You could make that happen right now
if you really wanted to.
Onions are in every house.
You can just go do that.
Just go do it.
Chop up some onions.
Sizzle them up in a pan with a little oil.
Put it on like a bologna cheese sandwich.
Who cares?
Just eat it.
Where's the American food?
How would you ruin a perfectly good sandwich like that?
What's wrong with that?
Onions are good.
What the hell was that?
What am I doing?
Hot dogs?
What are those?
This would be a really heavy lunch.
Oh, sausages.
They don't look like sausages.
They look weird.
You're hiding turds.
What do you say it looks like?
Kitty litter.
Cut it?
I don't know if I like this.
This is weird cartoon food.
Serve as much as you like. Isn't it just the brick?
I would eat two of these.
Two would make sense.
I'm trying to make it actually presenting.
Yeah, it does look like Fancy Feast.
Somebody said cat food.
It looks like
when you turn the can, it just
Fancy Feast?
And they have that big, huge, white, fuzzy-ass cat?
What they don't show in that commercial
is Fancy Feast.
Oh, cat's going to love you.
And the goblet and the cat's like...
What they don't show is the mom
going...
Oh, more hair in my mouth.
There's hair all over my mouth.
They don't show that part.
That's real life for the cat like that.
Yeah, they don't show the mom
walking over with a tray of Fancy Feast.
Okay, here you go, honey.
He's not licking the cat.
It's just in the air.
Just because an animal licks you
doesn't mean you should look at that.
No, that's not a joke. He's correct.
I know.
But people are saying that I'm licking a cat.
That's not what it is.
What am I saying?
I'm saying that there's hair everywhere.
But it's just real life.
That's just what you have to do.
Yeah.
Brush your cat, even if you brush.
I'm normal.
That's a lot of vegetables.
Spread them out. We need the olive oil.
Yeah, get it in there.
Come on, eggplant. Fuck you.
Let Bugleberry play.
No. Absolutely not.
Wink.
You're going to lose 500 viewers
just mentioning Bugleberry.
It's bound to happen, actually.
You're right.
I thought winking was over. No, in three days it's over.
Alright, American.
American cuisine.
Mac and cheese.
Do you want to do them all?
Fettuccine. Ooh, I love fettuccine.
Fettuccine is amazing.
The best part about fettuccine is when
you're done.
Oh, now I want fettuccine.
We're going to have to do a poll after this.
So when you have
fettuccine alfredo
and when it's all gone, the
pasta's gone, and you just have that...
You know when you eat cereal and there's
that delicious milk at the bottom of the sugary
milk? This is the... it's the same
thing, except you dip
bread in it. It's like the milk after you eat the cereal.
It's fucking incredible.
You just use it to put bread in
and... Oh wait, but you have some other...
You're going to eat that? Let me like dip that and use
that in my fucking cereal milk. You know what I mean?
It's so amazing. I want it so
bad now.
We're going to have to do a poll.
We're going to have to do a poll tonight.
Is this a salmonella?
I defended your
cat fur a bit. I can't defend
that one. Well, you can't defend...
Eating the rest of the alfredo
at the bottom of the bowl?
Alright.
I said, why are you so out there
tonight? I'm just like having fun.
I'm just like hungry and having fun.
Oh, I think you're talking about cereal.
Look at how much... how many steps there are in this.
Don't touch my food.
Don't worry, I won't.
Oh no.
When are we going to get a real life cooking stream?
I don't know.
I don't know. We never will.
Alright, here we go.
Pasta time. The best part.
Yeah, we're going to do a food poll after this.
This is the most important
thing the entire day, by the way.
Is what
food am I going to go eat?
It's the most important thing the whole day.
What are the choices?
You'll see. You'll see.
Calamari will not be on the list.
Vote for squid. You're not going to vote for something
that's not on the part of the ballot.
Has reservations about cooking stream
but will get slimed in a diaper
for two and a half hours. So?
Vote for durian fruit.
I can't wait for some nice American cuisine.
Watch the next one just be
Oh, a new American cuisine unlocked.
Bag of Cheetos.
And it's just
pull with Wiimote to the left
and you open them.
And then you just dump them on a plate.
Alright, that's great. Now this is going to be cheese.
See? I told you.
Party clogs? Fuck you.
He hates foreign food.
I just told you.
There's a pizza crust.
Mmm. Pizza's pretty good too.
But I gotta start. Yeah, I guess he likes the pizza.
Trying to cut back
on just all
the bread and cheese and stuff.
Although that's pasta.
Whatever.
Pizza's kind of dull.
It's not that it's dull or anything. It's just
you know exactly
what it's going to be when you get it.
There's no surprise anymore.
This is pizza and I know exactly what it is
and it's just I'm doing it because I'm doing it.
How is this overcooked?
It needs some adventure.
Just order a different kind of pizza.
But why would you
ever order anything besides a pepperoni
thin crust pizza? There's no other pizzas. I'm sorry.
They don't exist.
That heat up.
I would send you a can of Sir Stromming, but it might be
a
I wouldn't eat Sir Stromming.
Powered.
That shit would get in the walls. Thick crust.
No, not thick crust. I don't like thick crust.
No! Where's the American
macaroni and cheese?
I know you have it in here.
Truffles!
Sushi! I love sushi.
Sushi. Sushi.
Sushi. Sushi. Sushi. Sushi.
Sushi.
What kind of fish is it though? Tuna.
That's a spicy tuna roll. Yep.
Yep. Yep. Yep. Yep. Yep. Yep.
Spicy tuna roll.
I hope it's spicy tuna roll.
JPG.
Scallops.
Why are there scallops in my sushi?
I don't want this.
I wanted a tuna roll. I wanted a spicy tuna roll.
I don't want scallops.
Is this a durian?
That is a durian.
Let's get going. Cut!
This is a sea urchin.
I don't like that either.
I like salmon sashimi.
Maki rolls.
I don't really like...I like
Maki rolls. I'm not a big fan of...
Tuna sashimi.
Salmon sashimi.
Just over the rice. I'm okay with that.
But I don't...I like
rolls. I like Maki rolls.
You're a normie.
Uhhh.
Um.
No.
I'm just a normal person.
Um.
Um. Am I?
Because I know a lot of people that
don't eat sushi.
That just physically will
refuse to eat it.
That's a lot of wasabi.
That is.
Alright, add water.
hours i love sushi you eat exclusively california rolls i just told you i eat fucking salmon raw
salmon that's not a california roll that's not special i just what do i have to be special i like
what i like tuna i like um i like tuna rolls i like salmon rolls i like um on occasion i like
snapper i believe like snapper on occasion a lot all the time very good sushi like actual actually
raw snapper am i taking an x-ray oh you like sushi name it with three albums
now let's make sushi here we go what the hell am i doing i'm spreading out the rice that sounds
fake all right here we go make hand rolls make fatty tuna sushi on rice no wasabi
tuna that is tuna what the fuck are you talking about game what's happening make sea urchin sushi
with wasabi yeah let me put it on make scallop sushi what what wait once i pick the fish i can't
put the wasabi on what does it say what does it say i don't know what was it what did it say
what did it say what did it say what did it say what did it say make salmon roe hand roll sushi
no wasabi no where's the salmon oh the salmon roe salmon roe salmon roe i thought it was salmon
and roe oh okay yeah so fucking huge all right there's there's the canned cranberry sauce sushi
here's the potato chip sushi beautiful glazed potato chip sea urchin this bowl is not big enough
all right we're gonna take give me this shit nice plating it's a blue game dude like this
i'm not serving this to a fucking guy that paid me a shit lot of money to make it
of this is i'm not like serving these at a restaurant where's the ketchup
i don't know where is the ketchup come on dude baked beans oh it's japanese
you know what i think that we could get for an american cuisine is new england clam chowder
i'm just a home chef that would make sense oh dude dude listen to me
can be out on this banana cream pie after eating today i'll throw that pie in your face too much
sugar it's so good banana cream pie is fucking it's legendary it's the only dessert worth eating
it's somebody said worse pie you're just doing that to make me angry
it's like cooking mama i'm just i just gave me indigestion i'm saying that squeeze okay
it is the best pie i know it is what is what's wrong with these they need to be bigger shape the
truffles oh this is gonna be fun are these creamy are these chewy are these okay are these creamy
and chewy that's what i look for on a dessert sometimes i can't even respond because then i i'm
part of it you look over it well i mean one could argue that i would i would be considering
all chat was saying right there was that i was molding shit shit all over my hands poo hands
shit in your hands is what's what's the proper reaction oh i can choose my topping cool chocolate
oreo oh that's like cookies and cream what's this one it's like sand i don't want that one
chocolate and cookies and cream spider eggs spider eggs spider eggs he's so over it
the mick rib is made of spider meat wow why does that make sense all right we're gonna oh
gnocchi gnocchi it's delicious it's so succulent thick this is how you say gnocchi
now we chop up the tomatoes you're not you're a fake italian
that's interesting because i'm not italian why would i
like
i have to go off game somebody's people write this stuff this is making me nervous then
hiding because i have sometimes i have to hide
i'm gonna stop watching the stream then what who mashed the potatoes aren't there better ways to
do this don't make a machine don't just put it in the machine don't break
like grapes stopping just chew them chew them up
i gotta go off camp yes i can hide yes i can chewing up potatoes and spinning them into a ball
and you do that for like eight different potatoes holy shit oh my god that's disgusting
okay i'm coming back nervous signature recipe mouth potatoes that is fucking heinous this is how
look how much goes into gnocchi small world you know what i mean i just open up the bag from the
grocery store and put it into the boiling water this is a lot of work whoa world is literally
the world's actually very small geometric galactic space based on the fact that we are one of
six to seven trillion different galaxies within one or two star fleets of us so sorry sir that's
incorrect oh let's cut it you're so talented and liked by many who said that all right what
we're gonna add all the women from the pole we're gonna put tacos on the pole and that heat up sir
tacos are going to the pole let it change going on the pole barbecue barbecue is going on the pole
yep okay McDonald's is going on the pole no it's not
oh we got most of them can of sir strumming and everybody pew and put it on youtube
here we go mints banana and sprite challenge that's wicked fucked up what like why does it
happen that's like it's really screwed up why does that happen it's is it potassium
why do you puke if you drink sprite and eat a banana is it just one banana how many bananas you
have to eat i tried to add it what the fuck what the fuck am i talking about um this is one of
those dumb oh man it's if you mix coke and mentos diet coke and mentos the thing explodes
and it shoots out because of a chemical reaction apparently like sprite and bananas if you eat a
bunch of bananas and drink sprite like it you get sick i don't it's weird i don't understand
all right that's a stupid thing people are doing
um
america no just pancakes tomato sauce all right let's make the pancakes why sprite specifically
that's weird too i don't know i'm not a i'm not a like youtube challenge historian i have no idea
oh
i can do it this uh
me
the me the milk the me like the me life you either the meal i fly it or the meal the meal
uh
good job american yeah last time i checked i lived in the united states of america
it's pronounced mealy mealy fuel fuel fuel mealy feeling like you learned fake french in fake
nope i went to a tourist attraction in las vegas sorry it's a big sheet paris nevada
all right bake in the oven let's see if i can get it
if this doesn't go on the screen it's it's fucked up let me tap the thing that this thing is sitting
on so i mean it's it's fucking close why the fucking do it look it's right see see where my
eyes are right there right there if i lean in for right here what i'm saying am i right yeah i'm
all right you good yeah i'm good it should be three feet away from the sensor no did i i said
six inches away from the screen i need to be able to see yeah i could i'm not even paying
attention to the fucking game i'm at a safe distance don't worry guys nerd hair am i wearing
the wizard whoa why is it going that fast guys what in the name of all that is going on here
oh scrumptious that was an e3 reaction
what is it what's the american recipe short shortcake strawberry shortcake
oh that is american isn't it that is american there was playing a rerun right now
that should be kind of funny if i was
okay hey jerma it's a shortcake just for you all right i've seen it like 100 times already
what was wrong with that was that fucked up i was trying to do like a pitch higher
it's a funny joke 100 percent of the time you say so jesus christ why
your lips don't move what are you talking about wait what am i doing
i'm trying not to yawn your lips sinking
bored no i'm not bored i'm hungry all right let's see what the cake looks like all right
bake the cake in the oven here we go make it good make it right perfect shortcake is english not
american but we put a strawberry on it and now it's ours we don't have anything
yes we do spread the cream oh we could actually do the cream spread nice
people in the uk still mad about the revolution
pepe laugh take as much as you like all right here we go let's do what's our welcome mat
extra frosting get this out of here why the fuck would i ever put that on here
no get this out of here too i don't want like a birthday cake welcome mat is this how big she is
jerma the cake decorator whoa jerma must be
mama what a fucking awful cake cake sucks why was that wrong why is it shitty you just like
three strawberries and dollops that's it's a shortcake that's what this is it's ugly it's
not even ugly it's a cake it's a cake oh another america what is this one chiffon cake what the
hell is this what is a chiffon cake what does what does that even mean he's got a big raid come
in josh josh thanks for the raid josh what's going on everybody like cooking mama thanks a lot for
the raid thanks welcome hope you guys have a fun night cool name yeah blueberry cake is that what
this is hello writers i don't think i even can talk because we have follower only mode on
because i'm a fucking terrible i'm an awful tyrant of a streamer
but i don't go too fast i was like it's everywhere the terrible host hold on let me just mix up my
like acorn i'm running out of time dude this is too hard to do it's too hard to do that
you're a sack of shit easy we've got this 500 new people that just came in right now
i'm trying to scare them away this looks good i don't want to cook this i just want to eat this
i want to eat this with a spoon with ice cream in fact i want to turn this in i just want to eat
the ice cream version of whatever this is that's a strawberry milkshake yep that's what i put that
on the pole make sure remind me put strawberry milkshake on the pole how many am i making a lot
only strawberry milkshake for dinner oh they'll do a dessert i put it in the uh let's bake it
let's see what it turns into looks all right how far can you throw a weed boat
uh let's find out oh probably like at least six or seven hundred feet something like that
uh i'm not outside though what's that pineapple upside down cake
tart we're into desserts time is it all right i gotta go in like 30 minutes yeah i gotta get out
here i gotta go in like 30 minutes i gotta i have to like i need food i we talked this is a food
stream i need to eat it by the way speaking of my favorite fruit it's this one right here
josh said that he respects you highly well thank you josh that means a lot thanks a lot
is this how you do it this is how you do it you got it correct
what idiot likes kiwi this idiot it's delicious
is it kiwi ice cream there's an ice cream for every fruit but i feel like there's not an ice
cream for kiwi isn't that weird kiwi doesn't really it has a weird flavor hard to pinpoint
it's sort of just sweet and tart you're allergic to kiwi
josh viewers are doing exactly what josh said not to do the fuck are they doing
oh we we bring the the ban hammer down hard here what's going on here what's going on they
said don't embarrass him i really blew up the handle on that one um we're a community we're
very welcoming to everybody here come on in what's up have fun here that's what we do
do
no not embarrassing the streamers i embarrass myself every time the broadcast turns on at least
once the first hour of this stream guys was me fighting with the fact that i had a broken
corrupted fucking game cube memory card i'm gonna sit in the bath tonight and just be going like
this i didn't i did my research
he's getting upset already whoa i'm gonna sit myself in the face i wish i set myself right in
the tooth clean the wee in the bathtub just like done
every card in the bathtub whoa i jumped up all right now we decorated here we go
they're gonna fall off are they oh shit here asymmetric asymmetric
yeah i'm not a machine okay i'm a person i'm a human and i i have human eyes what is that
this is random fruit pie thing mixed fruit and that's a uk thing apparently the english
decided to eat fruits ever it's just fruits pretty good start though with pineapple
dig it pineapple too i don't eat the skin dude cut the skin off you did this so badly
what the fuck are you doing what the hell no one's gonna eat that that was lazy
awesome it's uk style the sticker is still on don't eat the sticker orange kiwi gotta go
quicker than this you're doing this wrong just do what i do put the put the ring in your mouth
with the skin on mush it up and chew it up and separate it in your mouth like a hamster
you're doing this wrong you're not doing it right all right serve it up it's just root
but i put this on here oh fucking who cares rabbit food that's just the trash that's all
the stuff you're not supposed to eat it's just the the compost carrot food carrot food oh
all right let's make a steamed egg let me get this right
two wings drop the weed mode on the floor sure you're gonna drop the weed mode on the floor
sure that's brown upside down he hates screaming i mean i i heard somebody told me that we modes
bounce is that like that's kind of well that's i didn't know that that's insane my god that's
fuck that's fucking crazy i didn't know they made it a rubber that's fucked up
that's a that's a classic clown joke by eating steamed egg custard oh here's the stirring part i
fuck this up every time not now not this time ready ask him if she's expecting because you make a lot
of dad jokes this spring all right put it in the mold i didn't do that holy shit i've overfilled it
is in this
nice steam them here comes a scream ready i didn't skip two wings i did them i did them in this proof
on file this proof on video that i did them the new recipe what is that one what remains
i think we only have a couple of bucks to do tomato sauce farfaro tomato sauce farfaro
just don't know pizza is weird i said it right it's farfaro right type of pasta
egg joke again try to call me
oh
my mother would love this game hey mother's in the chat
the baby game we get to see all kinds of foods
we get to see so many foods that we didn't know existed like farfalla
like mixed fruits baby drinks go-go squeezers and plays baby games
get your comedy up
yes put in the middle i fucked it up not really cooking mama recipe tier list
i don't feel like that actually exists it's going to be every cooking mama not just this one
so there'll be six or seven hundred recipes there mixed fruit s
yes all right here comes the tomato sauce
get in get in here comes more cheese trumpet mushroom what the hell is this
a trumpet mushroom i've never heard of that before
oh
japan loves mushrooms yeah i love mushrooms but i like the ones the grocery store in the package
sealed up um ones that are at the grocery store
so
cooking mama speed runs i never heard of it
you scare me when you do this my eyes crossed for a second on that first one i tried to hide it
come on mushrooms hurry the fuck up hurry the fuck up whatever extreme nerd neck
oh i want this too i want every food oh i don't even need to do a pole no i don't guys where can
you get every food not the cheesecake factory where can you get as much of any food of every
food in the world that you want i don't even need to have a bowl gonna go to a buffet he's
going to the strip again pizza let's go i'm fucking pumped
that's it that's how you make a pizza you just chop mushrooms with it
we saved the best for last bacon on a mushroom bacon pizza she's gonna be a meat lover's pizza
okay open the can of tomatoes canned tomatoes corn why is it a can why are we putting canned
corn on our pizza mashed the tomatoes
add the ingredients
why is it cake flour in here oh evio well
mama's on drugs
crack recipe well hold on let's let's wait to hold our reservations till we get to the end
scratch the pizza dough why do i stop i mean it's not a basketball then crust i'll put it
into the here we go all right no i wanted to take it off
they fixed they fixed it for me it's not the fucking pizza i made it's not the pizza i put in
the oven you're microwaving the pizza okay what would happen what would actually happen
if you made pizza a pizza dough and you put it in the microwave for 10 minutes
what would it do if you microwaved it for like three four minutes what would happen
would it just be fucked up would it burn i don't think it would burn all right hold on this tofu
here it would be fucking horrible it would be so rancid yeah it would be so bad
all right let's dump it it would melt and bubble the soybeans it's the fastest i can go i can't go any faster than that stop looking down when do you have to leave king
yeah right now i think this is the last one
i'm milking the tofu
it's tofu is tofu can you have tofu milk soy milk right is that how you make soy milk
that how that makes milk soy milk is that how to make it kind of interesting
all right put it into the mold how you're gonna get how you're gonna get big and strong without milk
just a couple more and then i got it milk is just sugar
milk is just it's just sugar it's not even actual milk what are you talking about
oh no this is atoms all right remove the tofu carefully from its cup
beat cooking mama cook off on stream
assorted vegetables let's see with this we did a sorted fruit so vegetables were invented in japan
what's the problem with eating the carrot like what are you doing oh we're making a design
making a flower what else we got taro it's like a coconut bamboo shoot whoa make it like a wing that's cool
okay now we stew them all it's baby food
where's my shroomers
all right let's put them out the way we want uh all the vegetables on this list i'll tell you
i probably really would only eat the carrot and maybe potato i don't know it doesn't matter
he's tired because he just started reading chat potato is not a vegetable what is it then
what's it what's a potato it's a root vegetable how's another you're a great chef oh i got a
another was another pizza pan fried batter cake
i'm up i'm gonna get food it never ends i'll see you guys tomorrow go to bed king i'm hungry
this game just made me want to eat uh so we're doing four days in a row this week so we're doing
today tomorrow and thursday friday so didn't beat the final boss we can come back and play
this after won't we look it's kind of plugged in so if i want to make more recipes i can
uh i'll see you guys tomorrow nearly beat it no wait good to be pulled no we don't i'm going to
buffet yeah that's it is this the guy that ate dinner on stream one of them that off all right
i will see you guys tomorrow for what should absolutely be chibi robo i'm going to do
everything necessary to make it so the game is savable i'm so annoyed by that you have no idea
like the one fucking thing but i'll see you tomorrow let's put on some music let's do the
bits go back to six and a half hours ago we had 500 bits from clink thank you clink chibi robo
is legitimately my all-time favorite game makes me so happy to see my favorite streamer play my
favorite game i'm excited to see you experience this little bumper boop boop of a game i can't
wait i'll be playing it tomorrow feels bad feels bad sir can i thanks for the 250 local streamer
gets scammed out of a hundred dollars for robot made game only to have also been scammed out of
a functioning memory card one of those statements is true thank you though clink again 500 bits
thank you clink it actually makes me really sad that the memory card is giving you such a hard
time right off the bat i hope it doesn't affect your feelings of the game no it does not that is
not a chibi robo problem that is a memory card game cube we problem and we'll get it solved don't
worry and i'll be playing it tomorrow thank you clink don't worry hey it's boo thanks for the 250
germo sunday was my 20th birthday and a few friends and i went to hash house so go go for dinner
it was as good as the first time and the server gave our table a free caramel waffle with vanilla
bean ice cream since he overheard it was my birthday thought it was nice hope you enjoy the
game yeah what a what a fantastic restaurant what a place that i would go and eat at at every single
scenario that i was around for it sounds like a pretty great place to go look at how well they
treat their customers it's unbelievable spooky biscuits thanks for 10 community subs biscuits
missed that earlier but thank you mecha murph thanks for the thousand bits no message just a
bunch of money thank you wembley ttv thanks for the 250 germa i got into a debate in sub chat
about a certain sound you made to me it sounds like you are spitting hocking some saliva and
spitting now this is saying you are drinking iced tea but anyway it sure does not sound normal
why would you have an argument about this what are you talking about right here what are you
talking about let's see i'm gonna make sure i can hear okay turn this off all right let's see if we
can hear it you know i do whenever i'm cooking okay um you're talking about like the and i'm
drinking that i had a cup with ice what you're hearing is there was a cup that i had that i was
drinking out of through a straw and there was ice at the bottom of the cup and that's me shifting
the straw around and making ice straw shifting movement sound that's what that was appreciate
the concern though thank you i wonder who won the argument hopefully it was you why no there's
somebody else in this chat i have no opinion jaded thank you for the five dollars 500 bits
don't have the money currently to do this every month but wanted to support been around since the
star days your development to streaming is some of the best stuff i've seen on twitch
big love for you germ thanks jaded appreciate it everyone's saying raid raid we'll get there in a
sec we'll find somebody thank you jaded i really appreciate that i'm happy you still think this is
interesting like seven to eight plus years later it's a long time thanks a lot s kilo thanks to
the 250 germa love your streams please keep going and you need to put some more exposition
on your camera settings because you always look so blue also i didn't know you played
sasuke on naruto shippuden that's fucking awesome oh my god what is this this is just saved here
instead of the thing that i was trying to do oh my god what is this thing called i don't get this
maybe somebody can fill me in i don't understand thank you though i don't get it
but thanks a lot thank you is kilo peaceful hailey thanks for the 250 germy don't know if
you heard of the kfc donut chicken sandwich but i got it tonight i gotta say it's actually good
chat don't dan's game it's good this will probably give me 20 kidney stones i don't care anymore
donut chicken sandwich okay it's probably okay it probably it probably is good but i think that's a
once a year sandwich i wouldn't order that more than once every six months
i wouldn't make that a habit once in a lifetime why am i wearing the same shirt from the 500 sub
video yep yep that is the same shirt i have it's the same exact tank top i have not gotten rid of
it it's the same one really really good eyes you've got there that's correct this is actually the
exact same shirt i was wearing 10 years ago yep disgusting disgusting well yeah i don't wash the
shirt apparently this has just been sitting on the ground for 10 years but thanks a lot hailey the
sandwich was good gnarly thanks for 250 i bet you're just streaming cooking mama and the easy
bake oven stuff to get out of doing an actual cooking stream i want to see you actually cook
your secret pancake recipe have a good night oh thanks for spoiling it that was supposed to be
a pre-stream chat only thing and you what what what uh what are you doing
are you leaking pre-stream chat spoilers uh oh i read it yeah i i got to that sentence i didn't
i read it banned for life banned for life banned for life now they're post chat secrets that yeah
that's true this is not currently a stream you're right the stream is over yeah you're off the hook
don't worry thanks with 250 uh it's kilo thanks again for the 250 hey jerkma985 no i don't think
you're a jerk it's a meme we please do a cooking stream someday i'd love to see you stop shit
talking and cook for us also i took this picture of your college graduation party please explain
i'm not i don't i'm not showing that on stream that's fucked up it's like a guy shitting into
a cooler with his pants off yeah i'm not showing thanks thanks the 250
the cooking stream i'd want to do it somewhere i'd no trust me there's i've been i've thought about
it before there are ideas don't worry it's not that bad they're linking illegal images they're
linking illegal images illegal images uh one hey zeus thanks for the 20 dollars 20 bucks from one
hey zeus thanks a lot hey zeus remember love you streams almost at a two year sub pog what
three controversial food opinions do you have i think i made a few of them tonight
um i made them tonight what were they it was at least three or four of them it was a few i know
i know i made them what were they squid ink pasta yeah i don't like that i don't like the lasagna
yeah i'm not liking lasagna is sort of is pretty controversial yeah he's defending
america defending american cuisine it's like barbecue it's an american to have the best
barbecue and that's you won't look at every contest that's ever happened
it's always this huge fat guy with a smoker in his backyard he wins every contest that's
exactly no no no no uh barbecue is that's a that's an american thing you i that i we don't get to
have very much but true barbecue that's here that's here that's here korean barbecue is better they're
both good but that's american american barbecue come on pulled pork smoked brisket fat guy in his
backyard goes to shake your hand it's really dirty and there's tons of dirt under his fingernails
you shake it anyways and that's the best food you're ever gonna eat your whole life
anyways moving on sir canine thanks for the 250 why does cooking mama turn into pinwheel when you
get a grate she's trying to remind germa that pinwheel kicked his ass omega low oh i don't even
i have no idea what that even means uh yakutare thanks for the thousand bits thanks a lot
ten bucks i want to stop by and give thanks and shout out to the second germa editors
for the people like me that don't get to catch every stream or streams often
but also isn't too much trouble could i get something along the lines of that's a good item
yeah to finish off my item filter item filter what was an item filter can i get something along
lines of that's a good item yeah to finish off my item filter is that like a sound pack thing and
you can put in oh that's a good item yeah i've been talking for a while oh that's a good item
yeah got it that'll be ten dollars oh you're you pre-paid you already paid me thank you
thanks a lot snoozing copter thanks for the 250 i have deep set eyes as well and very big
eyebrows on top of that so when i was in high school i was waiting in a line for the cafeteria
to find a few kids behind a few kids a couple grades below me they're talking to goofing about
not noticing their surroundings then i stepped forward because the line was moving and one of
the kids jumped back and looked at me terrified i was dumbfounded then he said whoa i thought you
were gonna punch me he said because i looked angry that's that's deep set eyes big high
brow bone i'm we i get it oh i get it did you punch him afterwards
innovators thanks for the 250 jur American psycho let's change the scene why was that instant
that just freaks me out a little okay why was that instant did i mess up my transition somehow
let's run the credits the flash punch yeah thanks everybody for stopping as always i really
appreciate it a lot of you tonight a lot of re-subscriptions you guys rock much love to you
thanks a lot everybody there are a lot of you thanks again finishing up the bits we have
uh sir canine for 250 easy bake ovens are like actual sized ovens the germa so
haha
it'd be one hell of a cooking stream is that how i think that that was word for word what you said
thanks to the 250 though smelly boy thanks to 250 what is the best noodle to eat with fettuccine
alfredo also with or without the chicken well uh you answered the question already it would be
that would be fettuccine uh and with chicken with chicken you gotta have something else besides
cheese sauce and bread red walrus thanks for the 500 bits why is this not germa sour
that's not right um because we already have one we already have one oh but joe here's josh josh
uh gave it came in with a raid of 500 people thanks josh they also get five dollars they said
i've been watching your stuff religiously since 2013 love your stuff man well thanks for the huge
raid and thanks for watching and thanks for the five dolls i'm not sure what you guys are doing
or what you were playing but hopefully it was fun thanks a lot josh big money big money from
you guessed it i like your lich 5000 bits 50 dollars big money you should do a nostalgia
stream and turn the bia sub sounds and orson wells back on maybe for like a fuckface stream one day
they'll just turn it on for when winks go on fucking like 50 off sale i might just do like
the cleanup stream where i play like two dlcs i said i was gonna stream and like wink every five
seconds and put on that would be like a total fuckface stream this is a lot of shit you know
that thanks for the 50 dollars though dude appreciate it uh anyways bulbous swag desu gave
a thousand bits you read my mean comment about the cake and i felt a sudden tinge of guilt
because i like to bacon stuff you're doing great don't worry and strawberry milkshake is top tier
of shakes we got a wink do you guess tomorrow don't worry about it we just walk around people
you talk shit that's all in good fun don't worry bulbous work it's all in good fun i know you're
not i know you just mess around don't worry uh go ike go ike go ike thanks for the 500 bits you have
to stop making crews soon there's going to be a gang wars in the chat stay safe turbo shroom crew
and shroomers assemble there are a lot of cooking mama games which is why this scares me and made
me laugh gnarly thanks for the 250 memory card issues remind me of when i had a game cube as a
kid and didn't own a memory card i didn't know that what i didn't know they were a thing i thought
you just had to restart the whole game every time i have the opening cutscenes memorized from mario
sunshine shadow the hedgehog thousand-year door and battle for bikini bottom but i have no clue
how those games end i love the game cube so much i'm happy to see you play it that's sad
but so cute at the same time now we'll we'll get it right don't worry but yeah i'm looking
forward to it i have a stack of game cube games over here to play we're gonna do them slowly
enjoy them all these are classics over here it's one of the reasons why i just was like no fuck it
i'll just do it tomorrow i didn't want to sour my experience with chibi robo being annoyed that my
game cube memory card that i bought corrupted itself for no reason
so not gonna let the sour me oh the music sorry but we uh also had 500 bits from ff12
uh pen yellow thanks for the 500 bucks
500 bits i do that a lot hi germa didn't get to see most of the stream but the ending was a really
soothing way to end the night off topic question i've wanted to ask but do you plan on playing the
resident evil 3 remake absolutely curious because your resident evil 2 remake streams maybe get into
the series finally be a treat to see you play it i cannot wait for that game i'm sure it's
gonna be fantastic you will definitely be seeing me play that game on launch
uh mecha murph gave thirty dollars three thousand bits thirty bucks a few minutes ago
mecha murph says not gonna let him beat me i'll be germa not gonna let him beat what would you do
and you're doing donation wars is that what this is mecha murph is now we don't have to have donation
wars you're all in the same team thanks with 30 bucks though that's a lot of money and finally
before we leave future gamer gave 250 good all's and 50 cents i also had no game cube memory card
really this is the thing i played the first few levels of rogue squadron and simpsons hit and run
so many times and my house got broken into and they stole my game cube well that ended really
fucking horribly jesus i'm sorry to hear that thanks for the 250 and i'm gonna make sure i
okay this is freaking me out because i'm gonna make sure i get i'm gonna get like three memory
cards uh phylactery just came in and said sit down with 50 dollars that's no that's not a
there's not a war when you're both playing on the same team thanks for the 100 bucks phylactery
10 000 bits in the last 10 minutes a lot of money wink wink wink by the way i know i know
wait wait wait wait wait grave embrace five dollars from grave embrace your name can be shortened to
jellaberson yeah be pleased to call me we got a wink i don't worry let's wink thanks a lot
i'm not we had another uh message come in right now from uh shrew heffner thank you shrew
hey germa i've been watching you since early high school it's four dollars by the way
and recently graduated and got a job after college thanks for the screams through the years
by the way what place should i eat in vegas i've had hash house already they have it in san diego
blue cheeseburger isn't even the best thing there what is the hell what the heck what
it's not even what happened sorry i blacked out um other places to eat in vegas uh gordon ramsey's
steak is ridiculous it's insane if you want to drop a bunch of money on a special occasion
it's expensive but holy shit it is ridiculous could have been one of those single best pieces
of meat i've ever eaten in my life was from gordon ramsey's steak only been i've only been
there twice and both were very special occasions sponsored that's not sponsored that's reality
that's the only good restaurant that gordon ramsey has i i don't know how accurate that is
but gordon ramsey steak is phenomenal like 10 out of 10 um mecha murph just gave another 50
i will not sit down with 5000 bits that puts you at 110 and it's a fight no not before i'm
going to end the stream so they can't be a fight thank you mecha murph for the ridiculous amount
of money appreciate it that's so much money one hey zeus thanks for the 250 if we keep donating
he will never eat well that's accurate but grave embrace thanks for five dollars just joined game
sucks there is no game thank you grave embrace with the five dollars pigeon thanks for the 250
germ it's been a while but i heard you saying gordon ramsey steak was good but i had a beef
wellington there and it was ass sorry the mushroom risotto was godly though
you gotta you gotta get the steak don't get the meme menu item from gordon ramsey's restaurants
i know like the beef wellington that's like the gordon ramsey loves beef wellington beef wellington
no no get a steak from gordon ramsey steak the meme that you're ordering the beef wellington is
ordering the meme that's like the gordon ramsey meme menu item meme restaurant no no all right
all right i gotta go i gotta eat i'm sorry you had a bad experience with the uh meme wellington
the mushroom risotto is fucking incredible though it's always their sticky toffee pudding
it's their dessert it's the best restaurant ever i hope you got it c4g thanks the 250 it's like an
event thing like this oh what brave embrace thanks for the three dollars and there's a twitch
clip why don't we click it and stay here forever how would you know that if you just got here
hey just opened up the browser hey this game sucks oh really how would you know that yeah
i agree with past jeremy uh yeah i agree finally c4g 250 also hey jeremy why did you pronounce my
girlfriend's name as pen yellow i don't know because my brain is fucking scrambled eggs
all right who's streaming right now we stream let let's do let me guys miss my twitch dashboard
let's see who's even live right now it's an eternity all the time yeah okay we got
i barely follow like anybody we got vinnie we got kraken we got novus playing gta 5
don't follow anybody who else is streaming craig yeah we haven't said hello let's go say hi to
kraken what's he doing he's ratting his title automatically like we did we show up
raid doctor disrespect hey hey dude here comes a raid it's doctor disrespect
raid my friend no no i'm not raiding anybody's friends today that got messy real quick
all right let's just let's let's raid kraken raid stir wait star's not streaming what he's not
i would be shocked is he streaming right now this is late for him no he's not
oh i got lied to i would have go say hi to oh yeah it's been a while since we've said hello to kraken
planning he's got rat in the title like i said you'll love it he's stat boosting his friends
all right i'll see you guys tomorrow goodbye goodbye see you tomorrow