And I haven't done the tutorial and I'm on the tree he's gonna well the tutorial the tutorial is
I mean there is no tutorial it's just click on ball in the right spot in ember oh you didn't do
the tutorial in the other game no I have I gotta I gotta uh well wait you've just been addicted to
the pitching game for the last like 30 minutes I time zoned wrong and I started my stream an
hour early oh I gotta do something I might as well you know super psycho oh it's literally
five minutes it doesn't it takes less than 10 minutes have you started your stream are
you like ready are you waiting just turned it on oh god I was under the I didn't look
2023 stir I'm trying to be more on time and I appreciate that but I didn't expect that I was
waiting for you to be angry at me that I wasn't quite immediately ready at 1 pm because like I'm
you know I'm here but I'm not quite ready and I was like I thought I was going to get the
spiel with oh I'm like oh here he is late late guy 2023 I'm trying to be less on time
because I keep showing up on time and no one's there and I feel like an idiot
like I went out to go uh like meet up at a restaurant with someone and showed up like
exact I'm so good at getting an uber and getting there at the exact moment like hey like let's do
6 pm I'm there 6 pm and me and Ashley walked around for 30 minutes to wait for them I'm done
well anyway this is gonna be fun um I just turned on my stream let me say hello hello everybody
welcome to another stream today we have a special guest uh no never mind
I mean isn't that imply that's implying that like oh it's it's oh Bob Hope is here
you know what I mean I'm not a special guest I mean you're yeah I mean you're you are but
you're always a special guest right like you I'm not Bob Hope uh stir is here we're gonna play
ember the firefighter game in about 15 minutes because he's not ready so we're just gonna hang
up we'll just chill I heard from a little bird yeah that you were interested in playing some
like ps1 games I am yeah um driver one is the first one I have got a hard hitting recommendation
do you have I played it I don't know not a lot of people have played it uh you know I'm into like
the hipster games that no one enjoys and no one likes but I think you might like this okay uh
shout out to jade cocoon any jade cocooners I actually I think I own that I just never played
it it's the it's the dark souls of pokemon is what they would be saying in the modern era
oh no I don't know it's not that I have something else um you need to you need to get in on some
jade cocoon is it a ps1 I believe so okay it's actually an amazing game and it's like you like
breed your pokemon and like based on what two types you choose they like gain traits of each
other and they like visually look that way I'll try also everyone in the world dies oh well it's
dark souls of pokemon don't spoil it we haven't even played it well I'm just I like I don't want
to see you cry on stream it's a real tearjerker yeah but every time we've ever seen a movie
together it doesn't matter what it is I cry at like every other scene sir say it's like monster
rancher with better combat is that a selling point have you played monster rancher I used to
play a ton of it okay I was gonna I was gonna reverse recommend you monster rancher if you
never played it no when I was a wee lad when like monster rancher 2 was new I remember going around
the house and like finding all the aol discs to try and get a good a good monster a good mon
but it's always the wolf yeah that that first scene and up I have to take a day off before
I come back to the movie I cry for about six hours and then the next day I can watch the
rest of the movie and I make sure that I don't watch that part I watch it from that part forward
okay so like close your eyes for like some parts of jade cocoon okay and like don't listen to the
soundtrack because it's like good and you'll like cry okay so you've done the tutorial yeah I
it seems like it's pretty easy to get in a game you just do like a join code and a password with
a private match and I I did kind of speed run the tutorial but it did take me about five minutes
and some change okay I'm very quick I'm gonna I'm gonna zoom yeah if I did it in five minutes
you could probably do it in three remember why do you sound like you're acting isn't he always
dude why do you sound like you're acting again what do you mean oh I have to say again no it's
the intro sir do you still do the intro voice kind of even even though it's been like more
than a decade the intro what is going on guys hey guys grimro here with another farming strategy
no no like yo guys what is up dude how do you start your stream like when you turn your stream
on are you like hey what's up what's up what's up have you done um I don't know I don't start
my stream very often it's a hard question to answer yeah but then you like kind of get over
it after like five minutes it's like okay this stream just turned on all right are you nervous
are you nervous right now I mean I didn't mean this legendary star is the call with me
you mean come on I didn't pay attention to hold on okay no I'm good I'm doing the tutorial it's
you know they're like throwing puzzles at me it's so easy he's acting like he's not acting
time zones are wild hey stars do you know that there is a spot on earth where it is
over the course of three days there's there there's a time zone where there is like it could be
January 5th 6th and 7th because of how the time zone works that's kind of messed up yeah did you
know that I I mean I didn't know that I did so I mean that was that's something that you know that
I did not know some knowledge to drop on you everyone's yelling at me you know oh you're not
smart I never said I was smart I just said I was dropping knowledge doesn't smart imply that I kind
of came up with that concept I watched somebody talk about it and then I did I forwarded the email
to stir is knowledge smartness I mean I guess it is yeah being able to deduce things I think I have
I have a general feeling that I'm going to be very bad at this game why because I'm in the tutorial
and I'm like really confused wait how the confusion per minute is too high for a tutorial
how wait you can no you're not confused about this you just have to like
break windows and put out the fires and run through the and turn off the electrical outlets
I've never been in a fire before when he said is knowledge smartness omega low
can you please be quiet I'm watching stir right now um I think I think I did it you know got us
both up in a fucking too modest scenario I believe I'm ready all right so I'm not ready I gotta do the
shop I gotta get my tools and upgrades I gotta buy my ladders it takes two seconds you'd be
ready in a minute okay now I'm ready are you making the game um I I could if you wanted me
to I think it's just yeah yeah you host I need a let's see so yeah yeah okay so let me see
okay I need a decent password see do I even need to okay does that work can you join me
I definitely don't want to show this on stream is this like a join code that's
just pasted at the top of the screen um I don't know okay I can type it to you hold on
there's a join code and a password did you set a password that's the password
and the join join code is this that is the join code hopefully when you do this I can just it
doesn't stay on the screen what's the Nintendo buddy code I think you may did you just join
yeah okay uh how do I get the join code off the screen all right what job do you want to
do you um imagine we're just gonna do this first one I don't I don't know where you are I don't
know what you're looking at do it easy or hard get as many clients out of the building as possible
it's just like a house stop spraying me I can't show the screen guys you guys are gonna get into
the game cover it with like your arm how do is there like can I do it in the settings
he doesn't want to play with us I think okay I'm using this loadout there has to be a way I can
hide this settings uh view bob particle range profanity filter I can't take that I have to
actually cover the top right of my screen I'm gonna put my face came up there um shit this is
bad uh hold on uh-oh this is bad well it's just I have to find I have to cover this like right now
is it showing yours no the top right of your screen is there's nothing there okay hold on there's
nothing there people are gonna see this so I have to do this first so I have to leave I'm gonna
re-invite you why is that why is the room code just sitting at the top of the screen for like
people that like enjoy others company you have an insect mind what that's what somebody just said
somebody said I have an insect my no bro I don't want to show the room code and I can't turn it
off so I have to cover it with my fucking hand okay hold on can you see it I don't want you to
be able to see it maybe the face cam could cover it let's see oh dude my my password I don't think
it's gonna be big enough yeah if this doesn't work out I've been telling my chat we were gonna
play a league of legends until we both hit challenger so we could just do that instead
I would rather I don't know I was gonna never mind okay how do I just make like a solid bar
okay there we go so if I do this and I just make it just like a black bar I just don't want people
to see this otherwise the whole playthrough is fucked up we don't know you don't have those like
where you can take a screenshot of your screen program I'm so slow I'm just like oh what do I
love that shot of your face cam and then stretch it out to be like long to cover the whole thing
and then you're good I got it under control okay I'm just I'm I'm waiting god damn it
why is this locked who locked it why can't I pick it up stop why can't I pick up the text thing
I just need to make sure it's covered first all right you ready yeah is your first time streaming
no it's my first time needing to leak lobby codes permanently all right making the I'm creating a
game here we go here it is I'm gonna use that same password what's what are you laughing at
I've never we I don't I don't weasel laugh I just looked at your stream to see how you covered it
that is gigantic I know but I need to I need to make sure I don't remember where it is so I need
to make sure it's covered and I'll fix it when it's there okay same password I gotta get okay
creating okay there's the code writing code to you right now there's that okay you should
not be able to see this same password same password I gotta make sure I don't fucking
leak this but I need to make sure because will my face cam cover this don't leak it it's close
don't do it oh my god I think I leaked it no I didn't I typed it in your chat
oh no I think I just leaked a little a letter no I didn't I'm fine they're gonna guess it from
one letter they've got the code breakers open okay all right I think I'm good we're good I'll just
keep that there all right all right you ready yeah yeah yeah let me hide it all right let's go
I swear to god if this pops up this if this moves to the other side of the screen
I'm gonna be fucking furious all right you ready yeah get your load out yeah I did
we only have like one loadout I think all right catch pizza are you an old lady yeah are you an
old lady yeah all right so where's this where's this fire I think you have to pick a mission
I think it did not change job this one here yeah we're on it accept job use this low I think we
have to drive the car gather your team that's us right here oh okay here we go I'm into the
zone don't forget the grapple hook I don't think I have that we're new we're new all right get as
many clients out of the building as possible welcome to your first house fire responder make
sure to save it all right it's burning now yeah we gotta go go in front door remember to be careful
if you die on your first job do something I'm watching you you know how every job has this
that actually hurt me that took health off me all right what's going on why is this stupid computer
limit testing limit testing we just have to see how it works uh you're almost dead by the way
yeah I'm aware hey dude stick your tongue on that on what the electrical thing all right we gotta go
yeah we got client vision on three oh okay where are they uh they're dying they're dying
there actually is a timer at the top it's being very generous though how many people are here
oh yep I see this is like uh what's that like really like boring game you play with the the
power washing why can I this is what that's a great game all right I have somebody um can you
not do that I'm putting the can I not put the fire out I'm walking with some guy
I'll find bonus cash we got bonus cash down here I didn't hurt them I don't think there's two people
I got one I got one guy taking about the back door you can also rescue people's valuables
oh wait we can we can rescue other stuff too yeah that's it's there's bonus cash
I'm checking the boxes what about the bed can we take the bed oh this thing's worth 16 bucks
I'm robbing him I'm robbing him I got 100 bucks I found his stash his drug money oh that counts
okay all right we're stealing no we're not stealing they owe us did you get uh
who did you put the person that you rescued uh there's a there's a back door
place to put them oh we're good okay so we now we have a little bit of time I guess we're done
is there anything else upstairs that's valuable I haven't I haven't been upstairs I'll be break this
where you at just let's take let's get the fridge and I know I can't pick the fridge up
where are you uh come get some plates I'm up uh in the kitchen it's good uh some wait wait
make like a hole somewhere right a hole because we can probably throw this stuff out a window
yeah okay right here so get stuff over here and then we'll throw it out the window this way
so find everything valuable and throw it out the window uh are the random things actually worth
money yeah I have 14.99 yeah like vases I found like an actual stack of money I thought that was
the only thing I've got Hamtaro it's too heavy oh holy you throw far you throw a bit too far
here come come outside come outside come on come on come on come on come on follow me follow me a
little bit yeah saw that chair here check this out so we got another one back here oh there is
another one easy access leaders grab all their shit snatch and grab they have like a dish we're
thinking all individually this is two dollars why would we save a like bottle of oil that cardboard
box make sure you save it that's why I love that one well inside that box is the family tree
people are screaming at us they're saying dude fight the fire no this whole room is like collapsing
actually this was a washing machine can we both pick it up I can't get it maybe you need like
equipment to pick up heavy stuff or something oh these explosive barrels are worth 30 bucks
I don't think we should have done that why did it blow up what did you do I don't think we rescued
two people I think we rescued one person what is this oh all right we should probably end it
can we just end it yeah let's go I like the mix of is this not where we go I don't know over here
I like the mix of being a firefighter and also like a criminal three stars that's not bad yes
that's pretty good so how much was the bonus cash for who knows job payout nine that's pretty good
anyway there were five people here oh you press next it gives you the the rundown saved items
how are there three of the people wait I thought it said five out of five I thought we had two
out of two people to rescue three of them died well well we still got a pretty good tip all
things considered that was like a 50% tip all right we just opened up a bunch of new stuff
we got this place here which is a rescue mission salvage we need low house damage
uh this place uh utica av seems like this uh it's pretty low on the danger
you want to do the higher danger or do you want to do the lower danger uh whatever I mean we're
gonna let them all die anyway okay so let's do this so they're okay I think there are six people
here did you unlock new stuff to use oh wait maybe we can buy some stuff maybe go to the shop
tools and upgrades oh okay this stuff here we don't have enough to do it though
you have a ladder right yeah oh yeah you can buy like new nozzles for your uh your thing
cheap metal box vehicle okay there's breaching charges to blow things up
I'm buying the tramp I'm buying the trampoline I'm buying the high impact hose
okay let's do it all right I got the trampoline you have the trampoline yeah I want to do some
jumping all right let's go all right rescue mission get as many people out as you can
ready this is the high danger this is I think this is pretty high danger okay okay so let's
hop to it yeah this game is also permadeath is it it's hardcore mode yeah I didn't lose that right
okay so let's not mess around it's zero to two all right let's go I'm going to top where's my
trampoline this person was on the fucking toilet was that this person wasn't even in danger
did I just break into somebody's house and throw them out of the there's not even a fire here
wait I was driving the wrong apartment huh oh no I know okay good what happened out
electricity electricity I got it I turned it off that's an old reference
that's was that ever even in the video yeah I think so stack of money okay whoa my god there's
a huge there's a hundred bucks here what do I do with it uh you take it to the rescue zone
hundred bucks uh there's still people where wait let's okay why are you just electrocuting
everything I'm not I'm trying to figure out how I can get don't all right just like that all right
just be hop through is there another zone uh there's like this is like a three story building
I remember if you hope you press three you can see where the people are guys in the tree house
that's like not even on fire okay I guess two in there I'm going to the top where's my ladder
I think you only get one you got to pick up the old ones okay this thing is tiny I'm trying to
get on the roof I'm getting tree house guy he's just on his iPad what a loser like go live your
life somebody right here where is this person they're on the other wall honestly where is this
person I don't know where this person is they're inside the wall you know what can you see this
person is apparently like inside of this wall right here did you knock this down what no there
was a whole bridge here that's on the floor now I think you did oh that's you what do you mean
you can see where I am with the the vision and I was chasing you around like what is that
walk around but I that person was supposed to look like they're in the bathroom with my ladder
I'm going up there this thing is so I why can I need a bigger ladder what does this do remember
you can like use your axe on dressers and doors and stuff this guy was like in the closet I don't
know if that's who you were looking for I just turned off like the breaker to the house all right
where are they at did you get them I got one guy uh that's definitely who it is still one more guy
get our mark if we don't save them we can't extort them for cash top floor I think I don't
think anybody oh there is somebody here see what I mean where are they look they're they're like
inside of the sink uh they're on they're not they're on all the way around the other side
them they said walk left Andy where oh right here right here right here what kind of fucking house
what house is this why do you have this this is a danger house what why what is what is that
why does him out of here on that oh shit jump oh it's dead um any valuables I I got
a decent amount I think we're ready to go we have clients find bonus cash yeah we're good yeah
we're yeah getting the escape zone that was masterfully done five star customer comments
you got us all all right 379 that's good it's putting items in the car different than putting
it in the rescue zone I guess because one of them is a salvage car equals you keep it why would we
want to keep it because I'm here for me I didn't do 20 years in fireman school to show up to a
burning house and not rob them all right we got this one Oscar Heights this is complete demolition
missions in under three minutes or let's see let's just rescue you want should I do it on hard
you want to try hard um yeah sure I have one question for all the smart people I put one
the new item in loadout slot five but there was no loadout slot five and pressing five did not
equip it you know what I mean like I don't know I don't know stop asking me questions
good to go the skill issue press you that is the loadout I'm using so these are the first
three missions we'll see what opens after this okay apparently you have to press that okay there
are six I'm going up top okay bottom floor spreading cock dividing cocker I'm going all
the way up this is like a jake this is a huge factory dude we need to get like individual
scores so I can like make it in the pro circuit got someone they were all the way up
was the escape zone uh I'm marking it ah you almost bounced them I put the bounce okay
good I got him I got him another person right here hey how is this TV's worth 30
set all right I'm gonna throw a bunch of shit down to you can put it into the where's the thing
I don't know I'm in the house absolutely nailed it I'm taking this pizza this computer's worth 50
bucks uh find our car we're taking that guys on mac yo I'm hitting this guy with the bounce
it in there come on 100 bucks yes oh what in box chair I'm angry don't don't turn the light
on I'm in here uh what about this side oh I think the time goes by much much faster on hard that's
what makes it hard right yeah right bigger buildings and uh we got all there's two more people
or one more I think one of them is you uh can you throw that person I just threw down her
yeah I got he's trying to go back in the way wait wait wait wait let's put them back down
let's let's make a good path make a path you have to go to the bathroom that bad
at this point just outside why are they going back to the bathroom you know that's that's how
sims are going back up to the bathroom all right who else is around whoa what somebody below
somebody below that's me I'm the one below it's uh someone on the roof third floor like top left
of the building oh no no no I dead I am right next to them hold on oh what you're right I
I hit a door and it turned red for future reference that's bad the door blew up I can't get
building I can't get in here here we go okay wait no they're over here yeah see that's
oh it's closed did you get any uh take that um didn't see the money behind you I didn't
you are right you are I'm putting that in the car where's our car
what do you mean I didn't see it I'm the one that called it out blind streamer
I got their tv all right let's get out all right I get it this game's fun yeah I dig it
oh we didn't get somebody shame we killed Bob we probably walked back in to go piss
is that really our fault this is a chat comment this is what they all they're all going to spam
this 400 bucks 500 bucks all right this is where it gets I think a little real because this one's
a little harder it's a big hotel construction shot it's right and it's it's it's like a medium
rare this is a medium rare mission I think we need to this mission we need to spend some time
making some money okay there's uh there's like grappling hooks and stuff and let's go for it
what mine is too bad you couldn't get us all I know what you're doing you're just you're
fucking up the whole the stocks and that's funny but like that's that's negatively impacting my
stream there there is a deployable toilet which will make the people who have to pee
go to that toilet so you could put it outside and they'll come to the toilet we cannot use
light firefighters might have 85 percent of the North American market but you best not
forget about your Canadian competition at poser and crazy I'm gonna throw this fucking box at
him this construction site okay so what do we do uh oh make a trail from the electricity to us
I think we move it gave me that way for me I just hit the skybox
you just be hopped it's just like no damage one day I will probably like harder difficulty and then
then oh why are you doing this well we're here to directly economically compete with embers
music socialism how to build this uh all right there's a bunch of flour and bricks and electricity
I feel this is uh it's just like puzzle time so you're gonna have to help with this because I
have no idea what the hell I'm doing here I don't know what I'm doing oh you can mark we have to
open this uh all right we need to connect wires like that I did the tutorial right yeah and then
this connects to here what are you doing over there oh I was trying to blow down this wall
look like you could destroy it all right I got it you tell ya we cut the electrical lines
good luck getting back up and running again oh germador I don't know where we're going
ego mania we have to turn this on with the electricity is there an outlet over there I'm
looking I'm looking honey yeah there is I'm connecting them yeah wait I can't I think we
gotta I gotta put objects hurry up I it's a whole thing dude finally
do we even find any bonus we didn't find any bonus cash I was trying to kill us so we have
this competition now okay 200 bucks we have I got a thousand okay this one's apparently pretty hard
but let me look we got money now right yeah oh fire extinguisher
ice accelerator I'm buying this I don't really care about this iPad I mean I guess you can see
how it's important the extinguisher oh yeah you are ready to do this next one I am so ready to
pop in and pop out my guy this one apparently is pretty difficult halfway up on the thing
five extinguisher reaction all right I got my new thing get as many clients you see this thing I got
yeah all right I'll go upstairs you go downstairs oh wait you went downstairs what are you talking
about um you just never mind let's go there's one there's seven people here what's the point
of having that many people um how I don't know this is like a like seven thousand eight thousand
square foot house what happened why do we just both die in here and he died yeah what what
happened can you help me I'm coming this person won't help me I'm lying down I think that I just
killed him you died too I was slightly near the like stove fire I guess you sprayed water on a
grease fire you got us killed man how would I'm supposed to differentiate and other people it's
it's a cartoon game where you spray a bunch of shit oh you you should have known it was a grease
fire what I how am I supposed what we just lost money didn't we replay back to the academy all
right same deal you go up I'll go down I think maybe this time I should go down now let's both
go down considering you murdered everyone I'll take care of the grease fire just get me in there
I'm a different class than you so I can't do that part what see there you get you bought the thing
for that you take him out yeah I do I have the extinguisher the shovel and the landmine so
I have a different loadout that's my class okay oh I have um as an axe and a trampoline that
doesn't bounce what are the games do we have on on co-op sunday uh is is that a like announcement
that you're not having fun uh because when I asked you to play this game and you were immediately
like okay what other games like before we had even played one round of this he was like oh
maybe some other games we can like play a lot like on the same day no I'm just saying like what else
what else did you have do you have anything else in mind I linked you played up which seemed like
a funner version of the cook whatever the normal cookie game is
no I just lost the computer I would we need to sell that
oh I'm gonna turn this off he hates it I mean this really seemed like no I don't I this is
fun I'm having a good time I'm just saying so why do you want to play a different game
I'm just making the argument that you know you and I don't get together that often right like
sometimes we do and there's like other speed run games there's like others like other things we
could be doing no I'm so like how quickly do you think we can get to challenger and league
sir I would rather I would rather be naked on camera than play league of legends with you for
an hour you think it would take us an hour uh you caught me so bad too like you fucker like you
I just feel I feel so personally attacked dude the whole like our timer is almost up
there's three people up here I killed one there's a skeleton near the mattress I
what do you mean there's a skeleton there why can't I climb this is not a skeleton
oh this person's dead you don't like this this place is almost down we're
I this this roof sucks where do I even go put that put that person into the into the into the
pen and then the pen I am saving people left and right man get him into the pen I'm trying
you kill you I watched you fall in the like x-ray thing just a dead body and then your
fucking body landing next to them I'm I'm in trouble too oh my god I'm hurt too I'm getting
out we only have five out of seven this is a this is an absolute failure yeah so what other games
do we have hey uh hey dude look up over this balcony up here if you can put the ladder I'm
up here I don't have a ladder yeah I fell I sprained my ankle wicked bad I just can't get
up I got 20 seconds dude get up here pick me up and throw me over where is the where is the exit
um I don't know it's the blue I don't my ladder is all the way on the roof now I'm not playing
everyone's saying League of Legends I honestly I would not I would rather eat a ghost pepper
than play League of Legends right now all right let's try this one more time we can do it we can
do this we actually made 225 dollars I messed up the trampoline it flipped over when I threw it
down to the bottom you guys should just react to family guy clips it sounds pretty good
that's no it do not start saying that okay let's go let's go let's go I got this person here
you got it you got to get the guy next to the fire but yeah grease fire lucky there's a family
guy how are we already almost at a time this place is like really like this is like a real fire
we did like joke fires before okay go to seven all right let's keep going where's my ladder
there they're almost all of them are on that right side in that building
I'm gonna we're not on bad time here we're doing fine we also do need to like I believe you can
you know put out the fire and the timer won't go down as fast we've kind of just been letting
everything burn oh shit that is what's going on okay like the support beams of the house start
falling down right here you you handled I'm going just to be on fire duty I'm gonna try and get to
the roof and get those people what happened uh I don't know come on no that's gonna kill them
you throw someone off the roof yeah the trampoline down here dude where did he go
you fell I think there's still a lot though there's one more guy I got a murder all right
then we have to find how to get out of here it's it's on the street you got him okay where's it
uh front of the house in the street we gotta leave like right now I'm hitting these boxes
why are you doing that we have to leave right now we have to leave right now because sometimes
there's money in them we have to leave right now let's go I'm taking this chair oh they're
gonna lower our rating why do you have evil spider-man here today 500 bucks yeah I feel
like a house like that we do not have the proper equipment we are understaffed underfunded
we got another one you want to do more how you doing are you not having any fun do you want to
know I swear to god I'm having fun I'm enjoying this game I just don't want it to be like a
wilderness situation where you mess with me afterwards and you're like this is the worst
experience I've ever had do not recommend a game to me ever again that didn't happen
wonder demolition burn the house down and clear out all the barrels was good I bought a breach
charge hold up I'll put words in my mouth that I didn't say well all right I'm ready I think we
just have to uh stand in the thing these are Incredibles cars what's that mean we could try
dota all right burn the house down there's a bunch of propane tanks here there's a there's a grease
fire already I'm just gonna throw some some shit in it oh it's a toxic sludge here hold on I got
this apparently I don't got this blow up did you not shoot it I got it just go grab the propane
tanks outside there's like three fires not spreading I think there's like a torch or something
out there I saw it was like a fire thing well then if you're seeing all these things what are
you doing what I'm just I'm spreading the fire are you putting it out what the heck does this work
what does this thing do maybe we have to like smash something how many things did you throw in
here because the fire is like a tiny little thing in the corner I threw like two or three propanes
in there there's also a roof I'm on the roof right now oh you're on the roof yeah I'll come
up there in a sec I'm throwing a propane in here okay I'm not happy with the trampoline
state in this world where are you upstairs yeah yeah it's like why are you not having fun
I am I'm blowing stuff up okay I was just muted talking to chat for a second I had a
subs came in tonight what are you telling them that you're not telling me no I'm just they would
they were giving suggestions for games and I'm just like I don't want to I was essentially
reprimanding them where are you I'm on the roof because apparently there's one more okay we got
all the toxic barrels we got to burn the building we almost got this almost what all right we did it
it would do all we did it nice got it that was interesting it's like a you it's like a reverse
yeah that's like a reverse we only have one second to do that close uh yeah I was putting out every
single thing you were doing by the way I was fighting so hard to put to like to fix everything
that you were doing you're you're doing you're being me we cut it out we flipped I think we
flipped here I picked a game that normally you would play and you're being me all right let's
actually do this one this one seems pretty hard this is like a barrel factory let's do it
all right this game's I'm not I promise I'm having a good time I'm just messing around
you played the uno reverse card um I'm on edge dude I'm on edge oh it's an escape mission
I don't like these oh hello again we got your personal information off the ember database
it was pretty easy to hack into you've been making quite the kerfuffle for us
of the closer headquarters we had our government buy out this oil barrel factory
when we get you out of our toks we're gonna use this place to store 100%
during those classic videos now just stir is bad you're mad oh fuck all right how do we actually
get out of here wait what are we doing we have to we have to just get out I'd much prefer to have
you work at closer than go through all this trouble careful what your non-compete clause clearly
states ember responders are barred from working for any app-based firefighting companies or
Canadian corporations yeah I still think that would be so fun and funny to do to do the social
like the stir in germa video remastered series it it would we just we pick a video and we just
try to redo the whole video but like without watching it and then one of us makes the video
when we premiere and we watch it on screen and like how close did we come to the original
what was the name of that game that we were gonna do I think it was damn nation yeah I don't know
that game probably isn't even the server is probably I don't know if you can even play that
anymore to operate here instead of ember well why not our socialized after a long time 15
Canadian dollar per hour minimum wage and free K through 12 schooling for your kids
how do we wait I think we gotta get these gases sucked up into the fans
okay it looks like we gotta turn are you so resistant to I just walked in November we just
want to do our solemn duty to just walk through it the United States as is written in the great
Canadian constitution whoa I just mushed hey dude uh don't press that button though I'm like
investigating there's they won't connect anything won't the thing needed to be there
oh you goofed up your own goof and you're still going to commit to the goof
you actually vanished I'm I am gone yet you got turned into pace okay cool now like now like star
gets to be the one who like does the whole game that's cool if you just want to like sit back
and uh why can I not spectate you dude just say you don't want to play I'm
that's not what's happening we can all breathe the situation man
I don't know what I'm doing I am I am a puzzle brainlet
stop gaslighting him play something else I I don't I don't know I don't know what I'm doing I gotta
open I hey dude maybe I can suck it up through the air vent oh oh I got it I got it we have we
did flip we flipped we absolutely flipped personalities today did you just hear what
you just did I'm like I'm jerma I'm throwing barrels at you I'm like putting objects in
front of you I'm like fucking with you and you're playing and you're the noise guy today you're
fucking serious it's interesting I wonder how did why did we flip we just needed a change
you'll never get past our shipping pallets they're going way too fast to just jump across
by the way these will be shipped right out to our leak like what are you what is on your screen
right now I'm in the first area where we spawned just looking at stuff you guys did a soul swap
I think I'm at the exit but you're dead we did a freaky Friday I think I'm at the exit but it
won't let me leave because you're dead I'm not sure uh you probably have to come and get me
where are you at the the spawn of the level ah man it is it is a chore playing games with stir
see now you get it after all these years now you understand when I asked you if you could
have just said no are you gaining health I don't know okay come with me fast we have a minute
we're not doing this again come follow me you can do that jump right where the fuck did you go
wait a minute I'm supposed to start I'm supposed to start today do that jump right I'm supposed to
start today I'm stir today one minute dude I swear German look look at me look at me
now bro you can't do it now either okay go go go okay wow thank you that's like
uh a hundred dollars for the carry service this one is very hard by the way
okay I mean I feel like we have to do the very hard one sure anything you anything you request
my master this one's called empire towers I guess dear I'll put on the dog ears
you are you doing hiding seek oh I have a hat no what do you mean no there's no hat
what I don't have a hat on no how about now pretty cool all right no it's not there's no hat
you go into your loadout and equip it in the loadout I did stir did you get there it is there it is
dig did you get into germa's secret stash and eat all the edibles all right this is just a huge
couple of towers I'm gonna go on the one on the right uh this is the only one oh I thought we hit
you okay I think the other one is an environmental they're all on the way pop all right ready we have
to I don't know what to do I think that's fine because you haven't played a level yes yes I have
check the tapes I can't get in this way I got one the tapes say he hasn't played a level
told you whoa the fire spread through tv the electrified tv I hate they're all above
us but we are dying this mission I don't think we're gonna die but hold on where's the switch
to turn this off this there's a light switch somewhere over here and I just don't know where
it is where's the switch I don't know where it is what do you main in overwatch um uh Santa yada
nice dude oh that's your ladder okay that's that is my ladder uh you're letting people die right now
I'm I'm really like I'm really gaming man sick like I want you to think that these people up here
one of them is like your mother how hard would you be trying you're gonna die is there a limit
to your this person's fine there's one more person up here wait just can you leave without me
objectives incomplete I have to finish my objectives to leave the job got our reload
you can reload look over here oh look at that he wishes he was on reddit right now
hey I want to do like a serial tier list yeah I love those I've already done I've done like
the pause before you spoke I could feel your eyes lighting up
oh all right we're gonna do this one more hey hey hey hey hey hey hey hey hey anytime
get to hang out with stir is a good time we can we you we can do anything you want to do you like
I can leave and never talk to you for like two more years um play a different game I can tell
you about my favorite cereals family guy tier list that's the dumbest thing because it's Peter is s
and every single other character is d what's for that we're doing the characters not like
individual episodes you don't want to rank every episode I mean that would be hell oh that would
be so awful I can't think of anything that would be worse than that well got no imagination I
strongly agree this place is massive huh is there a place to get up here did we did we complete like
the tutorial missions and then we immediately went to like extra hard no hope difficulty
no like these are just in these are I think you can grind missions and you can do the same
mission over and over again that was completely unnecessary I just did ow all right anybody up
top I'm getting them what are you what for real I'm going in here ouchie ouchie ouchie ouchie ouchie
ouchie what is this connecting to across I don't know no one lives in
mazes like this I don't think we can even walk in here it looks like it's going this way hey where's
the ladder I don't know where's the ladder all right it has to be a switch somewhere or
shit damn it and now I'm stuck in here you can do it you can do it I got five we got them but
they're still wait what I think there's still like three people oh I can't believe these people
are on the toilet shitting you gotta go you gotta go uh okay they're already in here
have you rescued anyone I'm sorry that the call what's your account call dropped for a second I
you're in like a bad zone right now what you say you might think you must have just gone through
a tunnel or something I can't get right here uh yeah I don't know whatever you said I'm not sure
this is uh yeah I don't know man maybe try calling back or something where's the thing
do you put the money in I don't know no no I had the money everything was done I was done I had it
I turned that on or off are you dead mother fridge I got a flare just come to the flare
you can see where I am can you see the flare oh you got the money I did get the money oh no
oh that was my buddy oh all right that's pretty good there's one more guy do you care let's go
you know where are they up there straight give you a ladder uh yeah well what the you behaving
like this is why stir is the way he is I mean I honestly I don't know how to act right now
I don't uh I've never been in this scenario before I feel like I'm being held hostage
we're like we can't stop playing but like he doesn't want to be here it's not true all right
now we have to leave uh okay like how about the next mission you just like hang out out front
and like how about this how about this the next mission you hang out out front and I'll show you
what I can do okay I'll uh I'll be your supervisor you hang out and you take you watch I'll show you
what I'm capable of what I can do all right see if you get a raise yeah let's make this uh let's
make this a little interesting you know I'm saying um hold on a second we're at this is a boss
mission I think we're I think we're at a boss a boss what is a boss we're about to find out like
like charizard I don't know it says boss stop your competition and save yourself out of here dude
oh okay I don't usually like to be so direct but you're making me a might upset
I suppose I'll have I think I think we broke his cutscene oh it's their computer right
they're telling me I miss completely missed what is his voice line I don't hear anything
oh man you dude you kind of stink I thought you were gonna do this mission
no but this is a boss mission it's different
just these randomly like to me I got I got I got it tossed nice hit nice hit got him watch out
it's gonna explode all right I got this over here okay you got this I'm putting out a couple
of things over here this one's coming straight over to you oh what's he doing this is so loud
it is wicked loud I thought I'm throwing something from back here
we finished this up quickly I've got a hunky match after this that that turn around was perfect
will you pick me up so we can beat the boss what show me what you got sure right all right you
hang back and you watch I'll take care of it why he's throwing everything at me it's like you
don't even exist no I can't even see he's too much fire where is he why is it electrified over here
someone's like smoking in my ear you haven't heard him all right why is he burping
what the fuck is happening right now okay something electrified the top area
that's like a self-parked voice line step fully socialized firefighting
that was nice don't move I got it are you sure yes don't move
dude the issue is it covers the crosshair I I can't see where he is I have to covering the
crosshair skill issue drop back throw it back throw it back oh we finished this up quickly
I've got a hunky match after this that's racist they're being racist barrel I just smashed that
in the back of your fucking head I'm so sorry he ducked why does he duck when I throw but not
when you throw oh he ducked well we're doing it no we actually are they we're good we're
dude you're being carried so hard what if we just like left you're almost making me a might more
upset time for double trouble I feel like I'm supposed to be hitting but it's not connecting
you are for the record you are supposed to be hitting him I am all right he's almost dead
you just you just sit down I'll pick me up so I get credit for it well you ain't seen the last of me
nice job remember you have a cross aim so you mean very calculated and calm and able to deduce
mathematical equations when I need to that sounds pretty good to me okay so I think we just unlocked
a new zone we did oh not quite yeah so there's a new zone but I like the sound of that
like new zones you want to do some new zones oh the the clothing actually has stats on it
really yeah like this helmet has reduced shock damage taken so wait I just bought oh this is
air conditioned okay oh it does okay yeah they've all got like perks oh this one gets bigger you
dress up like an elf and you get better perks and like the they tip you more because they like
you're dressed like an elf please play this for the next four hours I love it we're just having
fun I mean we're just we're just it's just a little bit of he took that comment personally
and negatively it was a very positive comment and it like hurt you no it didn't I was just straight
I was just saying do the turtle where is the turtle head turtle mask thing where in the middle
oh you're talking about me okay never mind these clothes are expensive yeah they're very uh they're
helpful I'm ready when you are dead so what's your uh what's your game of the year for 2023 so far
vampire survivors I came out last year oh oh I misunderstood the question um I haven't played
anything this year you actually want to do the thing from last year so what was your game of
the year from last year um shoot I wrote something on on the twitter I forget I have like a I really
like a brain problem slice and dice you played slice and dice slice and dice yeah is that a
I think I've heard of it I think I was gonna play it eventually is that the a game that's on um
is that itch yo yeah yep and I think it's on like android I actually have had that since
that itch yo night from like a year ago it's very good but you have to like think so I don't know
if you'd be into it I mean I did you like vampire survivors I okay this is a very stir story so I uh
I I don't I got vampire survivors like this is kind of cool but I feel like the whole thing is
just like you don't actually do anything you can just stand still kind of that's so I got cheat
engine to give me all of the unlocks and then I did a run and then I stood still and realized
that you could beat it while standing still and was like okay I think I'm done wait hold on a
minute you we're not playing the mission yet because I'm gonna okay but but but but but but
have you played like any of the others like soul stone survivors you like you actually like move
in that game and dodge attacks you have this so wrong you cheated after the first time you played
it you're supposed to unlock stuff and slowly get more and more powerful the whole game is just like
like there's no skill expression you know what I'm saying like you don't get to just like
if what you do doesn't matter if you have the upgrades then it's not exciting to me because
you're just you're not doing anything like you you are gated by what the game has given you like
you're predetermined to have lost it's like you're playing the binding of Isaac but your tears don't
do damage but if you don't like I hate it Hades dude everyone in chat's gonna think I'm crazy
but Hades was just like if you want to deal plus 300% you're unmuted aren't I no no I'm
just letting you go if you want to deal 300% more damage then you have to die x amount of times
so you want the game to just when you turn it on just to go like I like just give you everything
no I like roguelikes where it's not about how much stuff you have unlocked it's about
how well you're playing yeah you can I correct me if I'm wrong here but I think you could beat
Hades on your first try if you were good enough do it then it's the same the same thing people
told me about loop hero oh yo the speed runners beat loop hero on their second run when they know
all of the optimal strats and have been playing the game for hundreds of hours so like it's not
it's not about hours of progression that they force you to do because you could beat it in four
hours if you actually like did like the reddit strategy stir people are dying in this building
you're the one that said let's take a minute and talk about this like you're in like a burning
building there's people arguing about vampire survivor the firefighters are arguing about
roguelikes in the have you played rotato I have it's like the same thing as vampire survivors
but like like like you actually get to dodge abilities and it's like quicker I like that a
lot more explosion um so you don't like when a game trickles you content after playing it for
a while I don't like when your chance of success is gated by how much time you've played and solely
how much time you've played well I mean what that so but you probably feel the same way about an
mmo then like mmos you got to play a lot to get anything from it would you ever play like an
I mean I don't really like mmos you know you know I play like path of exile in diablo like I like
grinding games right so what about diablo in diablo you start as a little shitty and you
give you a stick and it takes you hours and hours to level up and put skill points in
but you're still like doing an individual character build and it's like your journey
through and what items you find vampire survivors is there is you will eventually have 100 of these
things you know you can't equip every single item in all of diablo 2 all at once and be like
okay I wouldn't know the fun of vampire survivors is why you kind of roll dice to see what the game
is gonna let you choose from really oh really that's what it does it's like oh what am I gonna it's
an open box it's like what am I gonna get but then you unlock like rerolls yeah you get to choose
exactly the same things that you want every single run I am not going to tell you that there's no
power creep in vampire survivors there is I'm but I it's it's all right dollars I like it
but I think there's better alternatives at this point for it to be your game of the year is
is honestly name me something better start up what else I said bro I think bro tato is very similar
and I think it does it's it's better I don't think so what do you not like about bro tato I just
I just like I like vampire survivors more I think vampire survivors
has I like because abilities you like when you open the chest and it's like a casino and you
can hear all the noises yeah you know what yeah I like the kind of hey the game is going to throw
you some stuff what do you want to do and you got to make a decision and it gets stronger and
stronger I know but like I don't I it's not the same it's not the same it's the loot box noises
it's not the same there's something about this different I tried what was it soul survivors
one of the soul stone survivors yeah survivors I think I streamed that game and I was just like
it was like too it's it's like identical it was too much too quickly I don't like having all the
extremely powerful unlockables immediately I like to grow in power they there's tons of stuff you
can grow in power in that game it's too much it was too it's too much I honestly rare germa l rare
stir l oh stir wins what you're gonna have to put up a poll who wins this argument who all right
put a poll on who's the winner who wins the argument here I'll do it what do you mean you
don't have mod in my channel why wouldn't I I don't why don't I have mod in your channel I
removed like everybody okay what did I do what did I do that you were scared that like this
fucking psycho if you like to start banning people that you don't trust me but I I D wanted
like a dozen dozens of people and by the way you don't have VIP either I am aware that I see that
now you want to know what I do have I have a bit badge because uh you know I've given you some money
on your channel hey dude this looks pretty close but I think uh 54 to 46 all right now do it on
your channel and see if it's 54 46 in favorite view for streamer advantage someone actually did
do it on my channel I am at 78 78 yes yes yeah who wins stir 80 percent right now vampire survivors
got really popular and then here come all the haters here they come oh it's too I don't like
it I actually don't like it I hate it you just hate her I don't hate it I think there's better
alternatives when you're saying it's your game of the year what else did I say was my game of
the year that's all you've said so far to me I don't know anything else we've talked about it
before like in the chat I mean Elden Ring is Elden Ring oh no he chose vampire survivors over Elden
Ring and God of War you play God of War no I didn't play God of War well you don't have to
because vampire survivors was actually the best game last year Elden Ring was the best game that
came out last year but vampire survivors was like different and like indie and you like that you
like that stuff so I was like hey vampire survivors and then you just kind of you just like stomped
all over my sandcastle I thought we were going to have an agreement a friend time and all of a
sudden I'm wrong it's all progression no thought I need something I need something to interact
with I need like a button I can press every once in a while yeah but isn't it fun just to kind of
sit on the toilet and just do that it's like awesome when I sit on the toilet I shit that's
all I do you ever just take a moment out of your life where you don't have to be like on a device
wait you mean to tell me you just you go to the bathroom when you go to the bathroom what kind of
weirdo is this Ashley's the same way she can't go to the bathroom unless she like has her phone
and can read articles yeah because it's it's you know what it is dude if I could do that in the
shower I would if I could have like a thing where I could just be in the shower and like playing
like a game or something hanging out this reminds me of a story of someone who was a professional
clash of clans addict and they were like had like 10 accounts and they would like zip lock their
phone and play it in the shower you're so you're not on that level no because you could you could
zip lock your your phone no but that's I don't know that's weird I don't like that material feels
weird um okay the main problem is when you're that's like a very private enclosed space nobody
else it's just you get to be in there and it's super it's just you and you're just hanging out
in there and it's a super private little spot I it feels good to kind of like oh I'm in the bathroom
just like taking it you know what I mean like there's a lot of that is that because if you
weren't in the bathroom you would be like oh I need to be busy like I'm wasting time like I
got to be productive but in the bathroom it's like no it's acceptable because I need to poop
but you're taking extra time pooping you know playing vampire survivors when you could actually
just like judge yourself a little less and like go do it out in nature like out in nature you know
take a hike but when you are in the bathroom there are no worldly expectations of you like you said
well that's what I'm saying you need to like that's that's an issue that's a problem even dude even
even oh well what about like lying in bed dude you could be like you could be no there's like
a worldly expectation the only worldly expectation you have when you are in the bathroom is nope
private private this is you are you are shut off for at least however long you're in there
this is what you guys are getting that's rough that's rough man like dude because like if your
alarm goes off when you're asleep oh I gotta get up right there is no like your alarm doesn't go
off like when you're in the bathroom it's not like oh shit I gotta get off the toilet now it's but
yeah I gotta I got some I got some stuff no no you are in there what if you're late to go do
something and you tell them like I was late because like I had to go to the bathroom is that like
always acceptable if someone shows up or like doesn't give something to you on time and it's
like I was in the bathroom always oh sorry sorry I had to use the bathroom oh how dare you have to
go to the bathroom no no that you absolutely what if they're in the bathroom for two hours
what if like you're on set filming one of your like big big dramas like a stick of baseball up his
ass and like one of like the guy who's gonna stick it in your ass is in the bathroom for two
hours and holds everything up I don't know I'd be like you you the bathroom is a complete and
total fucking sanctuary if you well I don't know what if they're sick what if it's like I yeah I'm
sorry but like we have to do it's like okay I understand I I guess like oh sorry a bit but and
okay but if I disagree though completely again because like I would shit myself to win in a
quick play match in overwatch I would not let you down if I was on set so I would shit myself on
camera for you but you hold on so what was the last time that you took like anything into like
a newspaper or I have never in my life ever done that so what you just go in there sit down and
just like go and then get up is it like so painful to be alone with your thoughts no I'm telling you
I like being alone with my thoughts so I like that private time in the bathroom are you alone
with your thoughts if you're on vampire survivors or are you distracting yourself from your thoughts
no no I can just kind of sit there and just like all right let's go I can like hang out
and sometimes dude at the end of a vampire survivors run in the bathroom I pause it for
a second and just contemplate when you sit on the toilet do you like today do you cross your legs
like and meditate like that you are talking like style on the toilet dude I drink espresso
when I take a shit sometimes you are talking to the wrong person what makes that wrong why why
why are you the wrong person because I love my bathroom time and like I take baths I sip on
espresso while I shit okay I play vampire survivors I get my switch again to recap just to boil this
all down real quick for anyone who's confused vampire survivors is the game of the year because
you can't play elden ring on the toilet yeah all right okay just to tie a knot on that real quick
we killed another group of people by the way well that's too bad hey we can do it
yeah we got time uh but no elden ring was game did you you went through the whole thing right
yeah orphan a cough and all that so stir dark souls 2 is like the best dark souls
stir underscore right you what how do you feel about that I mean that that was years ago that
I would have said that okay I am a controversial dark souls 2 enjoyer and my reason always was
that because it had a lot of content and elden ring has a lot of content so I'm gonna have you
know elden rings is the tops so you think it's the best that they've made for sure do you think
it's better than uh bloodborne oh I forgot no no you don't think so no I really takes it would
take a masterpiece like an absolute above and beyond to be bloodborne for me I think a lot of
that is just the aesthetic in the world like if elden ring was the bloodborne setting but that
setting does a lot for me that's actually true if bloodborne was elden rings the kind of world the
size and the scope yeah but the problem with bloodborne is because it was 10 years ago now
right that's something like that it's been a while it's hard to say that oh elden rings better when
if you think about at the time that was just so unbelievable when it came out but like elden ring
was so unbelievable when it came out like dude I have not had that a lot of articles would argue
with you about how unbelievable elden ring was on pc when it came out yeah but I know they were
like the stuttering whatever I we everybody dealt with that the first week right that's
just gonna happen that's blocked out of my memory that just happens but whatever it's a new release
I know it was annoying uh but that first when you first opened up the map of elden ring and you
realized that it wasn't just limb grave oh wow cool this is a big map it's kind of like a wow
it's like as big as gta3 oh this is cool and you're in the back of your mind you're going oh cool
all right yeah I wish it was bigger I wish it was a little bigger yeah then you go down the elevator
and there's then the underground world yes and it and then it blows your mind just how big the
game actually is yeah it was a great game I don't think something will come out and now you play no
dude play god of war I don't think it would even come close to me it wouldn't even come close I
don't think the elden ring for me I played god of war of the but uh it's god of war one but it's
not it's like the new god of war from like 2016 whatever it was yeah um I played the first like
five to six hours of it and it was phenomenal it was phenomenal but I don't I don't know I
feel like I still I don't know I I hear let me tell you let me hear what listen to me
yeah I'm listening to you so I have my full attention god of war I was told stand out in
front of this house again and talk about it all right we have to save these people you're going
to like look at where the fire is look at where you went look at what you're doing what now turn
and look up in the sky wrong house all right let's do this and then we can talk can we talk
after this yeah I don't know why this is closing we have to turn it on somehow or just yeah climb
it oh I think I see a way all the way up where'd he where'd you go I think so I don't I don't know
how we're getting in this building hurt we're going around back uh so anyway we were we were
back to um you were shitting on god of war that does not I know I just it was a phenomenal game
all right put that down sir doesn't go lengthwise I wanted to get in this window and you're standing
in the way like you made it fall I am standing like 10 feet to your left yeah I bet there get
that guy you just the person's dead they're not dead they just got a little like a little head
a little headache all right where are they where is everybody uh
everybody else even in here dude there's nobody here all the way up uh yeah all the way up until
this direction I forgot how what was the point button was we need a key we need like a security
key this is yeah this is like the doom of ember level this one is yeah this is hard this one's
no joke oh there you go doors open it really is doomed by the way hey jerma did you save anybody
yep okay congrats can you put out this like grease fire grease flap where we are we're not
complete the where's this not going well we only need one more person I don't even know how to get
past these doors there's a switch connected to here we have to power this thing somehow
so there's like upstairs doors oh there's a grease well I mean this is like the hard
zone this is we're not on like easy zone we're in like a hard area have you found
wait is this a key oh shit I like I'm kind of stuck here I'm I'm figuring it out maybe
maybe not I don't he is a sponsored no oh wait wait I said you you turned on something you
turned the yellow one on yeah it's like I got the yellow key because the yellow front door opened
I don't know how we get this blue one which is what every door is a blue door oh here's the kid
next to I got it okay restart the mission restart yeah like it's it's almost burned down all right so
what were you saying about like god of war is trash pick it back up I said that god the first
one was phenomenal but like not so phenomenal was number one that you would even consider playing
the second one it didn't grab me after the first 10 hours it was what an unbelievable like first
quarter or first half of the game whatever it was it was awesome and it just like I couldn't it just
but it it didn't suck me in true I've never played them the game is like 10 hours long what the hell
wait what do you mean like what the hell was I doing the whole time the game is god of war
is not 10 hours long god war is like 30 or 40 hours long it's not 10 hours what the hell how
are you playing that this place was designed as a fire hazard oh I got it up hey I'm up here
uh Ragnarok is even longer um I died where are you upstairs yeah Ragnarok online it takes a
really long time to level we're gonna get rid of this okay we need the yellow everything is a key
card no uh did you do the tutorial you open a window it sucks it up where's your device
my key fob the orange key card is out why are you spoiling like spoilers and by the way just
to be clear it doesn't have to be a device it should be the back of a shampoo bottle
you're you're sitting on the toilet reading a shampoo bottle it depends I don't know why
just I don't know just because it's like just something to do I don't know you you don't think
I feel like it's kind of weird um I feel weird just sitting there what are you distracting
yourself from I just feel weird just sitting there I'm dead again hold on I'm going the floor
fell apart where where can you ping no ping restart the mission we have three people
rescued no restart the mission no restart okay no we're gonna win you just you're doing the stir
thing where you're gonna now find the optimal route you're gonna find everything you can get
everybody in like 10 seconds we have to rescue six people the building's burning I'm dead do you
have any of the key fobs to even get into the room that I'm in ow you're distracting me with
all of this reading shampoo bottles while pooping commentary okay see like this is the tutorial you
just pick this up you see the key oh yeah all right see that's why we restarted because
that seems very important to figure out and not go all there's all these key cards right here I
thought these were tennis rackets I thought that they were like like when the choo-choo train has
to change tracks and there's the thing in the ground and it goes left and right and that the
train would come through the door I thought these were frying pans tennis rackets I did not know
that's what this was all right I get it I get it let's go and there's red ones in there if you
weren't like interrupting this mission with all of your like oh like oh I'm gonna make like a crazy
take hey type stuff stupid stupid I just opened both doors okay good job stupid we need a blue
key all right there is nobody up they're all kind of this one little floor up here and that's it
you're actually lying not we need green look here last time we need green key yellow key
okay so what is your what besides elven ring and vampire survivors which we already kind of
concluded but what would you say are your top three games last year uh slice and dice and
gotta work oh so you did play gotta work I had watched someone play it which was enough for me
to say that that's a really good game I don't have a PlayStation 5 they actually don't exist
but I I would have played it so you are vicariously giving game of the year through
someone else ah yep okay uh because if I'm not allowed to do that then like the whole
industry of like having analysts and uh you know consultants is kind of bullshit right
what what does that mean I have to have like sports like they didn't actually play the sport
right like a sports commentator like how stupid is that so do you think that the sports commentator
should be on an nfl team I think they shouldn't like be playing the game yeah like how hard would
it be to like break the legs of one of the nfl guys like they get hurt all the time and then
they are the commentator so what should there be a different commentary league where it's just only
the sports commentators against no I'm saying the opposite I'm saying that it's totally fine
for a sports commentator to exist and I in this situation am the sports commentator who watched
someone play god of war and realized that that is worthy of game of the year so you were sitting
there circling with a pen with the that white pen on the glass you know how you can like watch a
movie and say like that's one of the best movies I've watched this year okay uh I did that but it
was a video game so god of war is your favorite movie of 2022 uh I'd have to think about what
movies actually came out because if we're judging by how you mean by that then that then god of war
was a movie to you uh it's it's still objectively a video game I'm pretty sure god of war is a video
game no matter if I watched it or played it get this out of here cut scenes are movies
yeah what other options are there play what other games what other games why are you sitting here
going like I don't know what else should I do about it what oh you know you I said I thought
you were saying like what options do I have I thought you meant like what options do you have
I mean what other games were there last year I beside like I'm not allowed my top three games
of the year I'm not allowed to choose one of them what are what are what are my other options
you've got vampire survivor and elder ring what's your number three you got no you don't even have
a number three excuse me yes you didn't ask all right resume believe oh but is that like a real
game or like a movie that's a game that's a real game what makes it real are video games art I think
so okay you're entitled to your opinion how did you get out of there
are you 2016 ass argument did you jump out the window as an evil eight came out in 2021
oh I don't laugh at me I did a top three what was it elden ring vampire survivors I was shouting
about it during the game awards what was it no it was not scoring no it wasn't it was not scoring
you guys just gave scorn game of the year because of the sound effect that played
during when you complete a puzzle when there's a big a big a new environment that
shows up and I agree that was it was cool uh my my oh multiverses multiverses yep
both diverses for sure really did you even play multiverses I know you probably don't
I didn't I think we talked about this you weren't you weren't like a platform fighter like smash
kind of fan I didn't realize you actually liked it I thought it was uh you know just one of those
things that you did that was good it's actually very good I can't get through this the floor is
electrified I don't I don't have any water stir you downstairs there's like a uh a water cooler
you know what I mean that you can uh you can juice up I'm gonna die I'm gonna die I'm dying
I'm dead because this one this mission is rough okay oh yeah that's that's valid that I uh
there's a guy in here a guy in the room full of electrified explosive barrels what are we
supposed to do I don't why am I getting hurt by that but you're not I am oh you are oh my water
water over there if you need it I think this is where we die uh or we could just get to the exit
because we already did the mission rescue all clients six we have four out of three oh yeah but
I think that's enough we're just okay let them die let's go let them die you got somebody what's
your favorite cereal top three of 2022 uh favorite cereal the cereals is very mood dependent you know
I feel that see we can play I need to get one of those mood rings and see the color before I
can decide what cereal I want uh all right this one we'll we're gonna do this one on easy
and can I ask you an opinion on cereal you can ask me I'm an open book I'll tell you anything
you want to know about me how do you feel about frosted mini wheats love them no I know why we
don't agree with vampire survivors what's wrong with frosted mini wheats frosted mini wheats
are great for exactly 10 seconds and then they are awful you don't how do you don't have a bowl
of frosted mini wheats you just like eat two like I like I like when they get a little bit more
goopy because they're too hard at first they like cut up your teeth they're like razor wire
you like when they get like like you're eating like oatmeal like like if you're it takes you
like two hours to eat them no it depends on if I'm in the bathroom god I thought we were I thought
we were out of the bathroom thought we were in the kitchen you know that complete American breakfast
thing like you know it's up there I got my eggs bacon uh french toast cereal orange juice um and
newspaper two newspapers from two different companies you know a full this 24 ounce glass
of milk like you know I'm a complete American breakfast I honestly have no idea what words
you're saying right now you didn't even take the money I thought you took it don't burn you're
like it's not about the money it's about the chanting I'm at I've actually lost it so never
mind I actually don't want to go get it really uh are you just following me yeah what do you want
to do that's cool check these bathroom stalls these people are all shitting I'll get this guy
anybody else uh you you can see through walls if there's anyone else there's a lot of people
live at home oh there's another key I need a blue key I got a red key in here you can see
the red door anywhere where there's a red door there must be a red key um I okay whoops I have
a red key it's not about the money actually yes it is there's money in here I want it it was
hidden in the plants it is about the money okay so now I haven't seen a red door do you remember
how to point at things uh are when I'm looking for a red door on this easy mission uh I have
a red key can you see the doors or anything through the that lens whatever it is I don't
think so but did someone freaking die yes somebody freaking died no way bro someone freaking died up
here red door red door red door where got it I gotta go find the blue door what was the point
of even doing that money out of what I thought this was you for a second what the hell this person
doing all right there's a you right there yeah there's this one there's a person in this money
you want to take the person oh yeah all right I got a person too where's the exit
uh I don't know over here I think we can go out this way now I don't think we can
maybe we know can we because that's the door I opened yeah we can come out this way
wait no is that just going to circle I dropped my guy where are you oh I went in a circle don't
jump down here oh my god I thought that was the main lobby oh no now what dude hi how do I get
out of here uh you can put a ladder down go over the wall if you have one ow what is hurting me
so much okay so how do we get out of here uh open up your radar by pressing q didn't do anything
I know I was making it up where's the actual way to get out of here what am I doing I'm stuck in
the wall all right I'm up um there's more human beings in here I I'm fucking dead you died
where can you ping where you are I don't know yeah this is a mess I don't get out of here
why is this place fucking peewees playhouse like how do we get out of here
that's it's like a maze they conveniently boarded up every single window just in case of a fire
zero door okay there's a door up here this person burnt to death in my arms they've been cooking
this whole time oh come on and I was right I just did a circle I was your favorite kind of cheese
there what oops is it like an emote can I do like the floss or something that would solve this whole
problem well you can get to the exit zone and we can accept that we saved four people you are
overestimating how much I know where I am right now all right go left okay left left again left
again okay go right all right it's I don't have a door I need a key open the door I don't have a
blue key uh I got the blue key okay go up the stairs up the stairs no I got a blue key okay
that there there that was all you had to do no it was the room I was down in that was the room
I was in and that's the main lobby where you can exit from I just this chlorine flooding my eyes
I just can't I can't see you can't see anything and then every door every chlorine yeah just like
that like you can't see anything it's like all washed out and this like that like like I'm on
the toilet playing vampire survivors like yeah that was a pretty good attempt for a callback joke
a little flat isn't vampire survivors isn't though isn't the round always 30 minutes no
or if you play in the speed mode it's 15 there is a 15 a couple of the places are 15 one of them's
few of them are 20 did you even unlock any of the stages or did you just go I don't like this I'm
unlocking and cheating I played it all I have like most of the stuff I beat it I beat it because
there's like 10 maps yeah okay so yeah you know then why are you asking me this question well I'm
asking you this question because I know like at a minimum it should be like 15 minutes and then
you're on the toilet that whole time not necessarily yeah depends all right let's do a
easier mission I thought that was easy it wasn't didn't you choose easy I did but we just wait if
I have no idea what the hell we're doing um that was I think this one I think we're missing some
gear you know what I'm saying let's go here this place we didn't do for some reason well okay but
I need to can we get a poll can one of the mods get a pull up oh shit I don't know I don't have
mod chat open they might have been trying to talk to me yeah I mean like I could I could help with
that but okay there we go uh can somebody put a poll up for what is it but what is like an
appropriate how do I word this what's an appropriate time where like that this time
period is like you've been it's you've been in the bathroom for too long I would like option one to
be more than 15 minutes option three more than 30 option four more than 45 I can for me can one
option be only as long as it takes to finish yeah okay like as long as it takes and and the other
option is as like finish as soon as possible I'm going in to do one task done get out no matter
what two minutes it could be less than 10 minutes what is that period that's like after this amount
of time it's it's okay this is a little bit you get what are you doing I'm trying to protect
the structural integrity of the building because I'll give you my opinion after we see what people
say and I'll get in here I can't get in that window they already know your opinion I actually
don't think they do I got the two wow really easy missions are saved two people uh I think it's
wow you're right the thing broke the wood broke as I walked across it they pranked me
somebody's still in there I gotta check this hole in a second yeah we got a fire on the fourth
floor coming down into the third uh we're gonna check this pole I just realized you're one of
these guys that is in the bathroom what do you mean while the building's on fire you're still
in the bathroom I would get out I would not stay but what if like you're in the middle of like
you're about to beat like a really hard vampire survivor's level you've been trying to like you
know unlock a character or something okay no I agree I agree okay 41 percent are saying that
like more than 30 minutes is like pretty much a maximum I agree 45 I think really well here's the
thing like I didn't like clarify this that well there are lots of times where I you know you take
a shower and you use the bathroom right like in this you don't leave the bathroom we're not
we are not talking about shower okay so we're talking about purely just going to the bathroom
okay you can't get an out on this situation of like no I was I think a shower I'd say between
30 and 45 is like all right get out like yeah shower shaving brushing your teeth
all right what about is there any try to find the money we have like a minute
half an hour well but in half an hour I would say is at that point it's too long
what do you do for 30 minutes well I I am shocked that 30 minutes was your pole winner yeah I just
fell into the goo I don't I really I don't know what's going on there we should I think we're
gonna leave before this stuff burns down yeah let's get out of here oh my god this is an exit
right should be yeah I got it in it yeah 30 minutes is probably a little too long like what
about like watching a stream or watching like a like something you've never watched a streamer
like no stream when you're on film no you've never like opened up like a youtube video
or like browsed something like oh I'm gonna check no I've no god no why are you so against this
no like what like can't you just go to the bathroom finish then like go back to your tv or
computer and finish watching something what why can't you do both all right we're gonna try the
office building all right after this mission I want to buy some new stuff okay then I will I
will wait to buy things have you watched a whole season of a show no actually I watched
um I the only time I've ever done anything like that well not like this but
I watched an entire season of Breaking Bad I believe it was in one day and I to maximize
the time that I was watching Breaking Bad I did watch like a full episode on the toilet
because it's like I have to I have to because I need to make sure that I have I'm getting the
most out of my day watching this so in mid-episode I had to go to the bathroom
and I just paused it went right in turn it back on here we go I while making breakfast while
making dinner eating and I remember lying in bed at the end of this day and this I was like nine
ten episode whatever it was like almost 10 episodes into the season and I my whole body hurt
I was lying there like my eyes hurt I was like oh like I had only been looking at this
screen for like 10 11 12 straight hours it was like almost a season plus and I remember just
being I was lying on my side and I had the lock on the iPad so it wouldn't tilt to go vertical
I was lying on my side holding it like this and so to make sure it was still horizontal and just
going now and I was like almost done hey hey hey hey hey hey I'm I'm I'm confused at the moral
of the story I mean there was none the moral of the story was I've somebody said have you ever
watched like a season of TV on the toilet and my answer was no but I've done something kind of in
that same world how do I open this door there's a bunch of pressure pads everywhere
I feel like I missed a part of it because all I really heard you say was I watched breaking
bad until it hurt you know we have okay that's isn't that just kind of it's funny how that's
sort of weird proof that like you know weekly episodes probably you know I it's spacing stuff
it's really not necessarily a bad thing because I'll tell you I binged breaking bad I didn't see
it when it was on the air I watched it years later in like 11 days the entire series and I
don't think I can tell you I don't remember anything it is just melded together into this
mush in my brain I don't even know what happened in the show and I think when you say out loud oh
yeah I watched a whole season of Breaking Bad until it hurt my head it's like maybe I should
have faced it out like once a week or something maybe not that much I'm speechless I wish I had
comments worried about you and I've been stuck in the same room for the last five minutes here
yeah I'm not saying anything about it these things need a face scanner but it's not working
do we have to bring somebody over here do you think that it needs your face the person who's
never been here before but I can't leave because I don't have somebody else's face
oh there you are hi hi what was that the Muppet movie ah general we have our new
retinal scanner and he like back the bear how classic Muppets oh oh we do need a face scanner
okay that's what I'm saying I haven't been able to leave this area
well just walk out you forgot to say forehead I think we've like already rescued everyone else
so we'll have to like go get one of the people we've already rescued so just walk out
go on just walk out okay just walk out okay all right all right all right I thought that
was gonna take you a little bit longer a little bit longer than directly to exactly where you
need to go okay I'm bringing in I'm bringing one of these four steps back into the fire
why are you so passive aggressive what we're not you can't where is this last person I think
they're behind that door where you need the face scanner but we we can't I think we kind of did
this wrong I do think we kind of did this wrong burning I'm burning I'm burning I'm burning
come on axe the top door can we feel like it was uh closed I can't axe that door
no I'm out of I'm out of juice I even have one of the breach charges to blow up doors but I
don't think they work on anything other than doors you can already blow up I do not understand this
item I'm out I'm out of water I'm in a fire he didn't do it either let me just make sure
that's very clear he didn't do it either he didn't do it either do what I got in the door
you just had to knock it down I was just at that door
not that no the one we walked by and we tried to go in with the button it didn't work
I get what we afford for okay I'm gonna die though yeah I'm fine I have a I have I had no water left
um where are you in like the basement in the basement oh no oh dude they're seriously
sprinklers on everywhere and they're doing nothing hang again I thought that was an ice
cream truck oh dude I just hit the bonus on the slot machine dude there's so many coins
I just hit you I'm so sorry um I dude you are you are engulfed in flames I don't think I can even
get in here there's a hole in the ceiling above me you could be in that room I need water is it
water out here I need water that's what I'm saying man that is what I am saying okay I'm coming in
yeah that was I thought that was one of those missions where we had to burn the building down
all right so what's next what do you want to do next what do you mean what do you think we
should do next what's next I I'm down for more I like I'm I'm gaming I don't know like you're
the guy okay you know what I mean I just what else is on steam you tell me let's see portal
two no I recommended another game is that one also off the table no I'm just looking to see
what I have right now there's um what else we got do you want to try plate up you guys think
that'd be fun is played up fun plate up plate up plate up plate up plate up people are spamming
it right now dude plate up plate up plate up plate up okay you want to you want to keep doing
this but like how about like another mission or so and then we'll move to plate up okay okay you're
talking to me like I'm a three-year-old how oh uh by the way my uh my stream is gonna crash because
I'm about to download it so just be aware is that how that works kind of okay then I will also
download it okay I got it let's do a full uh playthrough of uh elgin ring co-op you know that
would that no well everyone's yelling at me now because I said no can you even do that I think
it's kind of a pain in the ass as they always are you you excited for this you do you play the old
armored core games I actually did not but I know a lot of people were really waiting for that so I am
vicariously happy for them I'm one of those people so yeah that's awesome I hope uh it's good
they do have a mod where you can do it how hard is the mod to set up is it pain or is it easy uh
I've I've modded stuff for before it's not very hard people do co-op with randomizer
actually that would be kind of funny sir do you want to do uh co-op elden ring with randomizer on
uh random enemies or random items or both I think just just randomize the whole thing so we like
like margaret can just like be in like a dungeon just walking around yeah I I played a little
bit with that early on when it was a lot less functional but it was fun there's also one that
randomizes like every item drop in the world I think it's part of the same thing feel like
you'll go like you don't like pre-plan like oh this is the spot where you get the sword like
you'll kill margaret and get like a pocketful of sand really okay yeah but also like the first
item you pick up could be like you know void forage drop from shaper yeah all right let's
do it soon what's your schedule like okay uh I'm myriad's returning on Thursday so I really need to
like be ready for that this week but after that what day next week what is myriad there is this
tabletop show that I run on my channel you know I got some known gamers from twitch streamers
you know just you know playing along interesting I'm the dungeon master and also I made the whole
thing and you know you ask me that every time and it's like uh one of these days you'll know
because you'll get to play and it definitely will happen one day yeah and where could they find you
not stir like a bowl stir like the Dutch word for star wait is that what that is it's not it's it is
star in a lot of different languages really yeah I didn't know that that's a little bit of lore
there now I don't hear the switches I got it I got it I got it oh my god we're getting electrified
uh now you're thinking with portals oh clever boy but yeah too long didn't read I could play next
week okay cool or after Thursday let's uh let's figure out how to set it up oh that hurts me
I'm surprised I'm surprised you're interested in doing it
well I mean you played elder ring but like normally I feel like we did switch personalities
because I'm the guy who will come to you like do you want to play this game also install all of
this random shit yeah I mean I'll be honest if this was any other from software game then
put down your summoning stone hold on wait no that's not you are we on the same password
um I don't know there's eight summoning stones here oh no I just I just uh sorry I just brought
in this guy a ball fondler oh yeah whoops I'm sorry we just got invaded five times oh whoops
that's why it's more fun all right yeah like we can actually potentially do it
oh wait you died oh shit time to spend 20 minutes resetting that whole thing up again
that that's why that was always never fun to do all true what a dogshit game okay there's people
in where are these people oh on the ground the seamless co-op mod is really easy to okay that's
encouraging it's good to know yeah souls modding stuff is always pretty simple we've got like
thousands of people on the job so do you want to make some rules here some rules because I imagine
in here get the money I imagine if we if we pull this off and we do this right do do we get okay
let's say we start and where you know when the first place you spawn where like the tree sentinel
is is like one of the dragons like do we have to beat that or do you like what are the rules like
can we reset and like redo a seed like what do we have the rules you can run away from things
but then chat's gonna spam but then like serious like if if the first boss in the direction we go
is like millennia right there is a degree of like why are we here like we just physically can't do
it the enemy scales the dragon is just as powerful as the tree sentinel really okay if that's the
case then that's kind of funny that sounds good it sounds good to me they scale all right okay
time to leave we got all the guys health and damage bowl skill I'm done I'm down all right
you ready to play it up sure you want to take a quick BRB uh sure I'll go you know drain the old
you know what I'm saying you know what I'm saying hello why do you still have that hello I don't
know dude sir you recorded that like four years ago it's still just sitting on your go xlr just
ready well I would I would have to replace it with something else I would I haven't I haven't really
been doing that anymore so sorry hello hello hello hello wouldn't you have accidentally just
like overwritten it at some point in four no because you have to like you have you have to
like overwrite specifically that there's like 32 buttons or some like 16 options I would have to
overwrite that one and then save it I don't know what I got other ones it's not like the only one
I got that for connecting a fax machine I got some alex jones last order was well I got that
come and they came all of them that's not alex that wasn't alex your blood you understand that
I will I'll eat my neighbors I'll do it so that one was uh what was the name of that cam
you have all these got that one's from gothic that's a favorite I will eat the good girl
and cocks collide come erupts the desire for gay sex leads the warriors to the penis desert
so I got a few you have all these I don't know I do the one that I'm surprised I still have
is even longer than like four years like five or six years ago some random guy in my overwatch
game said destroyed idiot get the fuck on orisa and that's been on there for years I don't know
what's wrong with you I don't know I don't replace them
well go go take a 30 minute shit and then recalibrate please all right all right we'll
be right back what did you call me