I'll get that medic. Get that med. Let me get his uber. I'm punching this guy right in the fucking. Oh, watch it. Watch it. Watch it. Watch it. Hold on. I'm backing up. Nice. Oh, the meds over here. He's rushing. I'm picking up his needle gun. Sentry right here. Take care. Come on. No fall back. Oh, they crits. They crits. Oh, that's going up here. Oh man. I had to use that uber. Sorry. I'm coming. This guy. Hey, come here. Come here. Come here.
Oh Jesus. That guy has an uber. Oh my God. What happened? Wow. Sure sounds like you guys are having a lot of fun on the friend team. I'm just going to sit over here on the team that's missing two people and wonder where my friends are. He's very dead. He's very dead. And this is this is stars. Sentry is in here. So we need to be very careful about this. All right. So we need to. Got it. You guys are having some fun over there.
On the friends that sentry just one, two, three, four. Go that guy over there. He dropped. No, no, no. This guy dropped the gun on the ground. Hasn't the thing. Oh, do it up. Quick fix. Free quick fix over sick. There's another century. Why is this many centuries? What is happening? Got to pick up the crits. Hold on. I'm about to have crits. What does this guy have? Do you guys have like nine century guns? Yes.
What the hell is going on? Hold on. I'm about to have this crits. You're going to tell me when you need this. I'll tell you. I just got it. All right. Hold on. There's a medic. Going up to your top left. Top left. Top left. Top left. Top left. Use it. Oh, I'm dead. You think you're going to get away from me? Is that what you think? You're going to run from me? You made the mistake to not be on the friend team, didn't you? Look at this guy.
This guy's fucking AFK. I got to kill him before I got to get him. I got to kill him. We have seven engineers. Hey, look at that. All right. I got. Oh, I got bullet resistance. Let's go take out this gun. Top. It's over on the left side. Left side. You're going to have to walk over this little incline. Oh, I see. I'm using it. I can't. I have no idea what's going on. I can't see anything. I think I'm shooting in the right direction. I have crits now too. Shit. Where? I can't see anything. Move up more. What are you doing? Dude, there was something.
Look at this. Oh, my God. Even in the right corner behind the one. You got to go. All right. Fine, dude. There was so much blood in my face. I couldn't see anything. I was taking so many hits from every direction that I couldn't see because there's too much blood splattered over here on the friend team. There's one top right. There's one over the left incline. And then next to top right, there's the little alleyway and there's like
three century nests in this little alley. All right. Where are the three? There are three following the track. All right, there's one. I'm using. Get that. There's two. Oh, nice. Left, left, left, left. Oh, my God. I'm stuck in here. I'm stuck over here. All right. Okay. I don't even know if this is possible. I'm so like. Where are you? I'm in this right little room. I'm so stuck.
There's two sentries looking at me. This thing is so spread out. Do you see where I am? Can you spectate me? I can't see you. If I just go over here. Oh, my God. Okay. Seriously, there is a sentry gun every 15 feet.
They are spread out far enough where it's not possible for us to kill them. Are you just arrowing me? Yeah. You, you, you. 600 health points worth of arrows. Help me. Help me. Shut up. Help me. Friend team.
I'm standing behind you. Not on friend team. You kidding me right now? I don't know what class you are. We're going to die. I just told you I was a spy.
I'm dead behind you. I'm dead behind you. Who helped me? Who helped me? Who was there? Watch this. I got it. You want to see who's going to help you?
Hold on. Give me a second.
Pyro behind us.
Pyro behind us. He was in this doorway. He's he's he's coming out. Oh, my God. Spy behind you. Jerma, can you take care of these spies?
I can't be a counter spy. Me and Mila are working together and you aren't. Hey, who's got a c-note?
Huh? That's what I thought.
Where uh, where are you guys? We're on the tracks. We're on the same team and now you guys are complaining about star being not in the friend zone.
Hey, shut up Mila. I mean. Heal me. Jerma.
Heal me.
I'm healing you. Yeah, I need to be included too. You can't just not include somebody on friend team. I don't know what class you were.
I'm I'm a demo. They keep changing.
But they're like we have them in the spawn.
I've got uh mini crits.
You guys ready? All right. That's that's a good sentry spot. Oh instantly destroyed.
No one could stop the guy floating in the sky. Thanks a lot you fucking dickholes.
I missed him like four times.
That guy was so easy to hit and I missed him over and over again.
Oh, thanks for like picking up that ammo you. I'm not even gonna say what I think anymore. What?
What are we gonna hit some more shock jock comedy from you?
Yeah, nice shock jock. We have it as a shock jock humor we got here. A shock jock.
Wow, I'm usually not this spicy without a couple of martinis.
What the fuck?
All right, Jerma, you're going in. You ready? You're gonna shock jock him.
You're gonna shock jock him. With the bizarre bargain? Yep, there's a spy here.
Where? I just shock jocking you. All right, you ready?
Well, it's not gonna happen. This guy's gonna shock. I don't we're gonna be all right. Come this way.
Get ready for a real jock shocker.
Where did you even go?
Are you alive? A jock shocker is like your nuts getting electrocuted.
I just like realized what I said. Yeah, it is. You want to go jock shocking? Some people are into that.
All right guys, this is this time we move. It's time to move. What the fuck? Oh, it's time to move.
I'm doing I'm shocking some jocks here guys. You guys I'm looking for some movement here.
I'm going to their spawn. Oh shit. Oh, yeah, me too. This guy's scaring me.
We're gonna win. I don't like you. We got it. Keep it moving. Yeah. All right, so where are you?
You ready? There's a bunch of people over here. Oh, well, I'll let you know. No, no, no, no, no, no, no.
No, no, back it up, back it up, back it up, back it up.
You have to say,
Jerma, give me the shock, jock, jock, shock me.
Jerma, give me the jock, shock, shock, jock me.
You're gonna die.
You're like 50 health now,
because you've been fucking around this whole time.
We're gonna get one medic now, maybe.
Get that spy.
Like it was a really good time to use it
until you did that joke.
Dude, we already did this joke.
Yeah, I know.
This is like 50 videos ago.
Are you using the fucking stickies in a pub, too?
Like I'm surrounded by morons.
I'm using a regular sticky launcher.
I'm not using the quickie launcher.
Oh, so like the completely broken thing
that does 100 damage per shot.
Hold on a second, so I am not allowed
to use the sticky bomb launcher,
because you said it was too strong.
No, because you, oh fuck.
It's actually broken now.
I hate the try hard, oh try hard, broken weapon,
try hard cheater, practically glitch, glitch abuser.
Glitchers. Exploit, exploit.
Hey, how about you suck a fart out of my ass?