Hey, what is going on everybody? Jerma here with a Team Fortress 2 gameplay commentary, and tonight, gonna be playing as the Spy with the Default Strange Revolver, the Spycicle, and the Default Invisibility Watch.
All this stuff is soon to be given away in my backpack giveaway. If you do not know what I'm talking about when I say backpack giveaway,
then go back one video and watch that vlog that I did so you can be entered into potentially winning 20% of my backpack. All the proceeds going to you, baby, going to you.
So let's bring up the gameplay a little bit. I want to talk about a couple of things, specifically about the Spy and how this is probably the best Spy gameplay I've ever uploaded to this channel.
Now, I only kill about 20 people. I think I kill 18 people total kills at the end of the one life. By the way, this is a one life gameplay. I don't think I mentioned that.
But I get a total of 18 kills, and I destroy nine buildings. Now, that's very, very good for me. I know we all hold ourselves to different standards.
What's good for you might not be good for someone else, but 20 kills in one life for me, or 18 kills in one life, is very, very good for me.
And the reason why I think this is the best gameplay I've ever recorded, everything seemed to go my way in situations where I knew I should have died, in situations where I was certain when I was playing, I was certain I was not going to get out of them.
I got out of them, and it happens at least four or five or six times pretty much every minute that you're watching this video. I should have died, but I somehow weaseled my way out.
And especially for Spy, when you get yourself in a bad situation as a Spy, it's hard to get out of it, and there's a lot of people looking for you, a lot of people chasing after you.
But that's where the Spycicle comes in, and I have never really been a big, big upper of the Spycicle. I thought it was really cool. I thought it was an interesting item.
But it really can save your life in so many different situations, because if a Pyro lights you on fire, it's really a second dead ringer.
It's a way for you to be able to get away, and not have to let anybody know that you're around. Sure, it makes a very loud noise, but this game is loud as hell anyways.
So there's a couple of situations where you're going to see where I pull out the Spycicle, and I don't die, where I definitely should have.
And I'm going to give you a Spy tip right now. Nothing really too major, but it really helps me, and it really gets you in the right mindset when you play Spy.
Because I know a lot of new players, when you just join the game, you just install TF2 for the first time, Spy is a really, really intriguing class.
And it's one of those classes that you load it up and you go, oh man, that's awesome. I want to go invisible and stab people.
It's a really, really drawing class. It draws you to it very, very easily.
So if you're looking for Spy tips, the number one thing I can give you in this video, I know I've talked about stuff like this before, but really in this video specifically,
and it's something that I just recently started doing, and I never really did it before, run away, just run away.
If you think you're in trouble, don't just start chaos stabbing and start pulling out your revolver and shooting everybody around you, just cloak and get the hell out of there.
It's hard to do this because we innately want to kill things in this game and attack people and shoot people and stab people.
But if you miss a stab, you really need to learn to run away and get to a better position, because playing Spy is really all about positioning.
It's all about finding the entrance way, finding the correct route, and leaving if you are in trouble. It is very, very important.
So take a look at this situation right here. This is a very, very big thing. This is exactly what I'm talking about right now.
Old Jerma or Chaos Jerma would have stayed in that room and attacked and just started shooting and punching and kicking and screaming.
But if you just calm down, run out of the room and get out of there, if you know that you're in trouble and you know that you're overwhelmed, just get out of the room.
You have a cloak. If you have the dead ringer, you have that.
But in every other situation where I've played Spy, in that room with those two engineers where I didn't kill anybody, didn't get anything done, I would have stayed in that room, pulled out the revolver, and just started shooting holes in the wall.
That's like what I used to do. And even when you're in a situation where you're 100% confident that you're going to get a bunch of kills, only go for the sure thing and get out of it.
Use your cloak. You're a Spy. You're not a soldier. You're not a Demoman. You're not a heavy...
You don't have a whole lot of options to unload and kill five people in a row.
Now, if you get a chain of backstabs, that's fantastic. But the options that you have with a backstab chain, they're only in a few different situations.
Most of the time when you're playing Spy, you're going to be trying to get behind enemy lines, kill medics, take out buildings.
Those crazy chain stabs where you get four, five, six people in a row, they are so much fun and amazing.
But at least for me, they don't really set themselves up that often.
The only places I can think of where that can happen is around the corner of a control point or on the payload cart when no one's really paying attention.
Just one, two, three, four, five, six, seven.
But it doesn't really happen in a real spread out game situation, especially in a place like Upward where there's five million different places you can be.
Now, of course, there are exceptions to this.
There are probably some of you guys watching right now that are so incredible at Spy that you do this every day.
But at least for me, though, it's a little bit different.
And one more Spy tip before this video becomes full circle and is over, I want to talk about deception.
Now, I've talked about deception before a long time ago in my first ever like Spy dead ringer tip video.
And it was walking backwards with the dead ringer.
Now, the same type of spectrum where you use deception as the Spy can be placed in this little thing.
And that is taking out different weapons when you are disguised as the enemy.
For instance, if I'm disguised as a medic, I should not have the syringe gun out.
If I'm running around with the syringe gun, I am definitely a Spy.
That is like the number one way to tell if somebody is a Spy.
If you see a medic like walking around your spawn with the syringe gun with no enemies around, he's a Spy.
Like he is a Spy.
So here's what you do.
Pull up your secondary item, which is the Sapper, and hit B.
What that's going to do is that's going to bring up the Medigun for the Medic.
So obviously, that's a lot less suspicious.
So a guy running around with the Medigun, of course, he's a Medic.
He's trying to heal people.
Same can be said for other classes like the Demoman.
I know it might not sound like a lot, but if you pull out the Sticky Launcher rather than the default Grenade Launcher,
you are much less likely to be thought as a Spy.
Because most people don't do that.
They run around, I have my Grenade Launcher.
They don't have the Sticky Launcher route, and it can be a little bit more of a layer of deception you can use.
And again, you pull that out with the Sapper and hit B.
And with that, it's going to wrap up the video, guys.
So thank you all so much for watching. I really do appreciate it.
And I'll catch you guys all next time.
And of course, take care, everybody.