We're gonna need either old-fashioned Uber charge for this one. Where are you?
As soon as you start healing me and we leave the door, we got ten minutes to do this.
Alright, wait, so the second I start healing you, we have ten minutes?
Yes. Start like the split.
Ten minutes.
We're not gonna make it across the field here.
We're on the right team. Don't get backstabbed.
I won't, I won't. I think that's real.
Wow, we're actually making some progress here. We're gonna go up into the vents and see if we can get in here.
Oh my god!
I think there were 32 people in there.
This heavy's gonna burn. Hold on, hold on, be careful.
Okay, I'm in. No, no, forget everyone else.
I'm gonna die.
I love your name, CTF Chaloge.
Let's go.
This heavy is so pissed.
Okay, the heavy's going first.
He is so pissed at me too. He's like spamming E. I feel like bad.
I almost got an Uber. Don't die yet.
Time check.
We're just gonna wait for someone to come to this corner because they're going to.
I don't have the time. I don't actually have a timer right now.
I thought you said you were running splits.
I'll edit it in after. Oh my god.
Oh god, tell me when you want it.
Oh, we have it. Let's go, go, go.
Oh my god.
There is so much.
How do you do this?
You don't, you don't. Okay, we've got them like locked in.
There's like 12 people up here.
I don't have ammo. I don't have enough ammo. We're gonna get this.
Watch out for this crit pile. This crit pile is gonna kill everybody.
Okay, okay, okay.
We gotta get back in the vent. Back in the vent.
This is tense.
They're gonna follow us back here.
Oh no, it's fine. It's fine. I'll lay some stickies.
Oh, you're gonna lay some shit?
There's gotta be a sentry down here.
We need to just build Uber and then go down and we can get this.
Okay.
So I'm gonna lay like a hundred stickies here.
A hundred? You mean, you mean eight?
It's five. Shut up.
One, two, three, four.
Four, five. Build your Uber.
When is Valve gonna fix like the fucking Medibeam bug?
My Medibeam is going like into the wall.
I can't even tell if I'm healing you or not.
Um, well, deal with it.
I got you. Look, now it looks like I'm healing you.
I just have to like move it in a weird direction.
Okay, okay.
Where are we going? Are we going down?
We're going straight down. There's definitely a sentry here.
Alright, you ready?
Go, go, go.
Look at this mess of a room.
We're so dead. We're so dead. Get it.
There's no way. There's no way. Look how many people there are.
And at that moment, I think the reality dawned on me that no, this isn't possible.
I thought, okay, no, maybe with this Uber, we've got Uber, we could do this.
Let's go. Two eggs scrambled.
At least we're on the red team, who's like the one who's up there.
I really don't know if this is...
Someone has it. There's a medic running back with it.
What a champion.
Wait, I have to make sure I hear these.
Mountain Dew, boy.
Well, I mean, I did destroy every sentry, so I'm going to take a little bit of credit.
Alright, well, let's get the third one.
We only got to get one more. Oh, we got crits.
We got crits.
Don't die. Don't die, Chalonge.
Anything in there? Anything in there?
Can we clean this up now?
Oh, there's a sentry.
I'm dead.
I'm not. I'm not. I'm not. I can do this.
No.
Would you get Huntsman?
Yes.
Why didn't you shoot the heavy that was right there?
I would have. I would have, but I'm playing Migi.
Dude, I don't want to get outplayed by Mountain Dew, boy, right now.
Dude, Mountain Dew, boy, seriously, like, is the reason why we're going to win this.
Okay, I'm here behind you.
Scout's getting in and getting it.
That's it. We're going to win.
Is it three? Yeah, it's playing three.
Yeah, we got this.
Has it been ten minutes? Have we, like, do our initial challenge?
It's got to have been, like, five minutes. That's my estimation.
Well, we did come in here and there was one tapped.
We didn't actually get it.
No, we didn't actually do anything.
I don't feel satisfactory about this. That's not even a word.
No, he hasn't actually gotten the thing.
Did he get killed?
We've got to go back and get it.
I'm bumping into a Spy. I don't know where the hell he is.
We've got to come back to the mid.
Watch out. Watch out. Watch out. He's going for me.
He's going for me. He's trying. He's trying his hot. He's trying his hot.
Jeez! I'm so screwed.
Uh, I think Mountain Dewboy has it.
Mountain Dewboy.
If I'm going to be completely honest with you, I think Mountain Dewboy is about to capture this.
Yes, he is. Mountain Dewboy just want to...
How could one person be that good?
And he's a medic.
Like, why is no one shooting him?
Mountain Dewboy. That's your answer.
Fuck. Fuck, fuck, fuck, fuck. Fuck, fuck, fuck, fuck. What the fuck?
I feel like that's not going in a video.
Watch out. We've got to... Never mind. He's dead.
He instantly exploded.
Because of the two centuries that...
What are these doing here?
There's two door centuries.
Have you ever seen a door century before? Like, work?
A door century? Oh my god.
There are door centuries here.
Can they even reach the corner?
I don't know.
Well, they just killed somebody.
Look at them.
Why is this working?
There's laser beams coming right out.
Why is this strategy working? This should not be working.
And look, you can see through here, there's another heavy with the brass bees just revved up forever.
Oh, yeah.
Come on, move up that door century. We need that hallway century pointing down this hallway.
I know, we're creeping it. This is called the slow push.
I'm barely aiming too.
If I shoot in this hallway, something is going to die.
I think four heavies.
I think all 16 people are standing in this hall.
I know, no one's going the other way. Maybe we should do a rotate, do a flanking maneuver.
A rotate?
I'm feeling confident about the flanking maneuver.
Well, I got 72%.
This guy's trying to cheeseball this century.
Do these heavies like not...
Okay, let's go the other way, other way.
There are too many, there are so many people in that hall.
It's like disgusting how many people are in there.
Again, you'll have double uber again.
Use it.
God, I died right when you said it.
You're so good.
It just spammed down that hallway.
Sorry, I can only handle so many fucking grenades coming down a fucking hallway.
Jeremy's mad about two free backstabs.
Are you still alive?
I'm at the hallway where the endless fight is happening.
You're at the endless hallway, okay.
And I'm ubered, apparently.
So you're at the hallway in Mario 64 where you go up the stairs.
But the stairs never end.
I never played that game, top comment.
Star never, what?
Wow, Star never played Mario 64?
What a...
Yes, yes, yes.
We could really have like five ubers coming through here.
There's still the sentries, there's still the sentries to deal with.
How many other?
Maybe just two.
We have two or three medics in this hallway.
I think we might get it here.
Heavy to the right, heavy to the right.
Overheal me, overheal me.
Is the heavy dead?
I can get this right now.
I can't, there's so many people, they're just not, back up, back up.
This is just going to jump in, jump out, do that kind of thing.
But they're already building sentries.
Like there's three people trying to build a sentry again.
Does this guy have an uber or does he have crits?
Heavy is dead, he has uber, we're ready to go in.
Alright, I got crits. Let's do it.
You got crits and uber.
Make it happen.
I'm getting the domination sound once a second.
You're still alive, how are you still?
I can't, there's...
Get that pyro.
Make that pyro wish he was never born.
I just killed him, I don't know if that's what we're looking for.
Well no, because now he's dead so he can't even know he was born because his brain is gone.
I wanted you to make him wish he was never born, not like make him kill him.
Okay, well we need to go up top.
You didn't follow my instructions.
Oh, that guy has an uber.
Okay, go, go, go, go, go, go.
Is that what we're doing?
What?
Take it off me, take it off me.
Insult to injury.
Oh, it's over here.
That's interesting.
No, kill it, kill it.
No, crit.
I think we got it, yeah the pyro has it.
That made no sense.
No, see it's a flawless strategy.
When you go down the drop down it works every time.
There was nothing down there.
How would that many people that were just in that room, was there nobody there, is what I want to know.
That's what I want to know.
We are done once we get this last cap.
And then once we get the last cap is when we do some celebration.
We can celebrate the victory.
Look, everybody jump.
We did it, we did it, we did it.
Oh shit, we didn't do it.
Oh yeah, we did.
I got it, don't worry.
We have to think about celebration first.
Celebration, what do we do?
Look how dusty I am.
Oh, look at how dusty he is.
You're so dusty.
No, you exploded.
Watch out.
We did it.
Congratulations, I can't do this anymore.
We stayed here way longer than we should have.
Yeah, we did.