Hey, somebody said sup loser. Sup butt head. Hey sup butt head. How you doing? What's up? You're doing good. Cool. Cool. You're late. Yeah. All right. No, I'm not because you're not putting the German 985 on time formula. You're not putting the variables in. Two o'clock means 2 30. You didn't put the you know parentheses like exclamation point 30 minutes, right?
I've been hey, I've been pulling the time back to make sure that I'm here before four o'clock. Think about that, right? It's 2 30 p.m. right now. I usually stream at four. We've pulled back an hour and a half. Look at this. Look what time it is right now. Well, it's unbelievable. 2 30 instead of 4 p.m. an hour and a half. Are you seeing this? You've done this for one day. Shake this up. What an accomplishment.
I know, right? We got a lot to talk about. I've got wondering where I've been the last week. My head is my head has been down. I've been writing. I've been working on the phone with hundreds of people. Mine is probably like 70. Maybe like 30. I've got some things to hype up to you now. One of them I can't I can't talk that much about but I'm gonna because I don't fucking care. All right, first things first,
Look at this list. All right, first thing. Are we people here? Are we here? How many people here? There's only three people here. I'm waiting till at least 10. There's only just three people there. I need at least 10 people. 3k Andy. That's a lot of fucking people. That's a huge amount of people. That is a massive audience. He's getting washed up. No, don't not. That is a massive audience. Even if okay, okay, let's just say for instance, that like for some reason,
the next, I don't know, whatever, I don't make me think like this. 5000 concurrent viewers is a shitload of people. It's an insane amount of people. I would start to feel concerned if it was like, I don't know, maybe like 1000 500. Maybe I'd start to get a little concerned that like, what did I do? Dude, you fucking fell off. Let's get it to 1k. No, you know, let's take a minute because I've there's a lot we're about to talk about. And I want to be able to announce them with a
everybody here. Give it 10 minutes. Yeah, I don't I don't I don't do a countdown. More fucking delays. Stop saying fucking okay. Stop. So good. Oh, let me know. Here's what I can do. For a second. I was just Oh, let's talk about my tweet from last night. I was okay. So I was let me give you some backstory here. So I was I was kind of high last night. I had some marijuana products, which
you're the legal age. And you don't go overboard and you and you're very good at moderation and you take care of yourself, right? Okay. I was sitting there. And I saw that there's this meme of monitors or something. It's like, what, what are you? What kind of monitor? The kind of
Dungeons and Dragons kind of character are you right? And I was looking at the ones where people put a monitor on top of another monitor. Like you have your monitor here and then a monitor up or down below or above it. And I was sitting there talking to Holly and I'm like, there's no way I could ever fucking do that. And I just started writing up a tweet. And I asked her, I was like, is this funny? Is this tweet funny? And she, she kind of laughed for a second. She was like, Yeah,
I mean, it is. So I was like, Okay, hold on. I'm gonna get up and I'm gonna get up. And I'm gonna make sure this is funny. Right? Because like, I'm kind of high. Maybe it's not that funny. So here's what you guys tell me because I had to sleep on it. You tell me if you think this is funny. I can't do monitor on top of monitor. They need to be side by side. Can't handle that McDonald's menu bullshit. Is that funny? Was that like funny enough for a tweet? That was a little funny.
She also did say it was adorable too. Oh, the idea is funny. That's trying too hard. But the thing is, I wasn't trying too hard. I was just kind of, I was fucking zonked. You do not try hard when you're zonked. I'm sorry. There's no like, Oh, man, I gotta do something funny. I just started writing. I was like, I think this is funny. So I'm like, I wasn't trying hard with that tweet. It was just kind of coming out. It's funny in theory. Okay, but not in practice. Does
Okay, does that mean that it was funny? The idea was funny, but it needed some better kind of more funny, maybe language or something to make it funnier? Okay, what if I put fucking in between McDonald's and menu? If you know, for instance, if it's like, oh, they need to be side by side, I can't handle that fucking McDonald's menu bullshit, right? I think that might be funny. That might be actually a comedic take on things. All right, shut up. Let's move on. Anyways, today we're going to play ultra kill.
It's a game that's been requested a lot. It's a FPS game seems like fun, I guess. It's an old boomer shooter, or it's kind of like, in that realm. It needs work. I'm not ordering out of McDonald's for God sakes. That would have been funnier. Hold on. Let's read that one. Okay, hold on. Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait. Shit. I think that might be it. I can't do. I can't do monitor on top of monitor. They need to be side by side. What was the joke? I forgot it already.
What was it? So you have to write it again. I actually just forgot the whole thing. I'm like looking at my phone. I would give booed at open mic night if I was there. What was it? What did you say?
German there's 10 people who make the announcement or we're gonna leave. Just wait. I haven't streamed in like six days. What was it? Okay. Okay. Okay. God, I can't do monitor on top of monitor. They need to be side by side. I'm not ordering at a McDonald's for God sakes. Now that's worse.
I think there needs to be more time. But before you get to the punchline, I think that's too quick. Hurry up and make the announcement. Guys, we have like 30 minutes of announcements. I'm not like I'm not about to announce one thing. Let's what is it? The line just isn't funny. Hmm. That's all right. All right. Whatever. You get the idea. Okay, what? Okay. What about at the end? I said it's more than time. I guarantee you, you'd click like on it. You understand how stupid fucking you know, you understand? I'm sitting here trying to craft a fucking funny tweet.
Trying to craft some comedy and observational humor. Nope. No, I just just write it's more than time at the end and it'll get 100,000 likes. You understand? Actually, that would be kind of funny.
Let me try that one.
That's actually kind of funny. I can't do monitor on top of monitor. They need to be side by side. Can't handle that McDonald's menu bullshit. It's more than time. Actually, that makes it better.
Why does that make it funnier? That sucks. Why? That's so annoying. Oh, there it is. Oh, that's I know it shouldn't be funny. That's that's annoying to me. It's annoying me that it's funny. It's annoying me. But that is funny. Damn it. All right. It is fun. Okay, so here's what we're doing. Playing ultra kill. You know that. That's what you know. Here's what you don't know.
Submissions for the green screen actions are going to be closing this weekend. This is the first of many announcements we're going to be talking about on the morning announcements here. This is you have two days you have until Sunday night, Monday morning, maybe another like two days or so. I mean, it's been open for a week and a half or so. It's been up for a week. There's already so much shit. So you got if you by the way, what is it? What are we talking about? I'm going back to the
back in front of the green screen one more time to complete the green screen trilogy. Where's the tweet? I don't tweet. Guys, one day I will tweet out all of my drafts. I'm just going to tweet out like five images on Twitter and it's all going to be all my drafts and you can just laugh at all of them. I don't care. Do that today. No, I'm holding them. But anyways, yeah, you have another about 48 ish hours to give a suggestion of an action you want to see me do in front of the green screen. I will be getting in front of the green screen.
I have a date. I have a date in mind, but I might need to change it. So I'm not going to tell you, but it's going to be within the next week and a half. Depending on how many props I need to get. I'm going to have to maybe move it to like a week and a half from now. So I will be getting in front of the screen within the next 10 to 12 days with all the suggestions. And by the way, I got to make this really wet. We got to go over this because I know this is going to be kind of tricky to kind of deal with this maybe.
But the last time we did the green screen stream, we had a lot of submissions. There were a ton. The channel has grown by about three to four hundred percent since that stream. And it's I'm imagining there might be potentially thousands of submissions to this. So if you submit something, even if it's good, it's going to be so hard for us to vet out a ton of videos. We're going to have to pick.
We're going to have to narrow it down by a lot. So if there are if there are like five thousand video submissions, it'll be physically impossible to watch them. So what's going to happen is we're going to be narrowing this down to maybe only six to seven hours worth of content, maybe 12 hours to be able to do it a couple of nights.
Have an encore night. So if you submit something, it's not guaranteed to be put in any action. You say it's just not you just put it out there and hope for the best because it's going to be really difficult to narrow down like three or four or five thousand video submissions or even submissions in general, only six to seven hours.
That's a lot. And if you were there last time, we do get to a point where there's sort of after like three or four streams worth of green screen stuff, you can kind of like come in with infomercial exhaustion.
Do you remember that? I don't want to get to a point where we're just kind of blinking our eyes sitting there going, geez, OK, I guess here comes another one. Here comes another one. It's you can get green screen exhaustion.
So I'm looking for like 10 to 12 hours of footage to show over the course of two or three streams. I ain't showing 10,000. I'm not showing 10,000 green screen videos. It's not fucking happening.
All right. But that will be happening in June here. That's like the thing that we're going to do in June. I'm going to get in front of the screen.
You'll have, I want to say, maybe two weeks to put something together and then somewhere in the want to say, third or fourth week of June, we're going to do that. We'll do the night. It should be fun.
Hard dates will come out in the next three or four days, I would assume. It's an assignment. Yeah. So that's that announcement. There you go. That's green screen somewhere in the middle of June.
I'm getting in front of it. And then in the end of June, we're going to watch the videos and it's going to be fucking PogChamp.
I want to see PogChamps in chat. Giving us homework. That's right. Do this IRL. Yeah, I did it. Okay. Second thing.
Announcement two of four Grotto Beasts. Ladies and gentlemen, Grotto Beasts is, I would say it's the train is kind of pulling into the station.
There's still needs a little bit more time. It looks insane. I haven't really talked that much about it because it's I don't it's fucking ridiculous. Let's just put it that way.
It's going to be probably ready for I hope we can figure out some, you know, whatever the fulfillment that we're going to be using.
The idea is that this will be something that we can get off the ground by the fall of this year.
Like that's it. I said March, I said February, March last year, and it was just not even close to being a realistic thing to do.
So we're hoping that somewhere in fall, it'll be actually be able to get it. Have it on your desk. And there it is Grotto Beasts.
They are going to be the Grotto Beasts team will be start being more active on Twitter. So go follow the Grotto Beasts Twitter.
Can we get some of the mods to put that it's not NFTs. What are you talking about? No, what? Why? How many times do I say this?
It's not it's not NFTs. It's physical. You're going to have the card in your hand. It's a physical card game.
It's not NFT. What are you talking about? It's all right. So when people were talking about Grotto Beasts like six months ago,
it's like I've got this thing Grotto Beasts. Jerma, is it NFTs? No. OK, good. Another two months go by.
Hey, yeah, Grotto Beasts is coming along. It's German. It's not NFTs, is it? No. No, it's not. No. OK, good. Good.
Just making sure. Hey, Jerma, are they NFTs? No, they're not NFTs. OK, sorry. I just had to scream into my into my shirt there.
No, they're not NFTs. It's a physical card game. It's a physical card game. There's nothing to do with that.
There's not anything to do with NFTs. Understandable. Yeah. MonkaW calm down.
Oh, that's worse noise. That was that was no, you can't have another scoop of ice cream, baby.
Why not? Dandrum. Toddler. That was loud as fuck, was it? I can't. Whatever.
All right. No, they're not NFTs. It's a physical card collection. You're just going to buy it and
you can have it. And there it is. That's it. But trains coming into the station, you should be able
to keep on the lookout for follow the Grotto Beasts Twitter. Follow me on Twitter. You know,
I might have something to say about it. But yeah, that project is going to be coming to
a close and I'm really excited about it. It should be really cool. Might have a stream
that is kind of based around that project. No details for you now, but just know that
it probably will happen. OK, announcement three of four. You already know this one,
but baseball is pretty much locked in, ready to go. I'm incredibly excited for it.
It's going to be like the most fun I've had on camera. And I keep saying that every
event stream that I do, but I'm willing to give you a few details.
So this is the German Baseball Association. It's going to be an exhibition game between
the Cincinnati Clowns and the Maryland Magicians. That's all you really need to know. But you see,
I mean, it's going to be in the middle of the they're currently going to be in the middle
of their season. So should be should be an interesting, interesting time. That's July 14th.
Mark it on your calendar if you have to. Can we bet? No, I mean, it's just an exhibition game.
Let us gamble on that. No, I know. Well, maybe. I don't know. So that's a yes. No, I don't know.
I don't want you betting on the game. But yeah, that's that is the stream. I'm very excited about
it. I've been waiting to do this stream for two years. If you've been following the channel for
a long time, you know that that project has hit multiple COVID snags. Two years ago when I wanted
to do it, we physically couldn't because of COVID. And then a year later, we still had issues with
can we do this because the the whole idea with that stream remember is it is going to be it's
not just going to be like a couple of people hanging out and playing a game. It's it's two
baseball teams. It's gonna be like 30 fucking people there. So that's a there's a lot of people
and it had to keep getting postponed and postponed and postponed two years ago because of COVID.
But I'm incredibly excited for that streams. I can't wait. It's gonna be so much fun.
And you'll see why I feel that way. And I'll be hyping it up because I don't want people to
not know that's not that that's happening. Right. July 14th. I'll get a time for you. We're probably
shooting for the afternoon. But yeah, I'm very excited about it. The fourth thing that I'm really
excited about. Why is it city versus a state? Well, let me tell you about just pulling random
fucking city and state names out of a hat to come up with names for these teams. Because that's what
pretty much I was doing. I was just like, okay, I guess that's what it is. City versus state.
That's actually really funny. Cincinnati versus Maryland. Yeah, but that's no that's
bullshit. Okay. What about the New England Patriots? That's literally just a general
area of the world. The New England Patriots. The Florida Marlins. Yeah. What are you talking about?
They do that already. Yeah, I'm fine. Everything's fine. Don't worry about it.
Yeah, there's tons of this. Yeah, come on. Come on, Gwen. Give me a break. They're the Miami Marlins.
I don't care. I wasn't sitting here when I was coming up with the team names going,
hold on a minute. Oh, yes. No, I was just like, what? What? I need a name for the clowns. I don't
care. But that makes it funnier. I don't care. It's funny. And there may have been graphics that
have already been already been made. So who cares? But anyways, ladies and gentlemen,
the last announcement I'm going to make for you today is the announcement of an announcement.
I yeah, I love doing those. There's another huge project that's going to be probably somewhere
between August and October. It's going to be massive. Currently spent the last maybe four or
five days reaching out to certain people getting interest getting gauging people's opinions on
things. But there's probably is going to be a major project that's going to happen between August
and October. I want this summer to be nuts. You know what I mean? Is it like a dollhouse level?
Yes. It's not dollhouse two. I don't do sequels. I don't do sequels. It's a prequel. So
a green screen three. But that's different though. Yeah, I'm fine. I do trilogies. I do
trilogies. I don't do sequels. There you go. So dollhouse was never supposed to be a trilogy.
Green screen was supposed to be a trilogy. So that's different. But yeah, I'm so excited
about this. I will tell you I don't it's so hard to tell anything because if it has to change for
some reason or it doesn't work out. But just here you go. Here's all I'm going to tell you.
But just be ready. That stream is going to happen somewhere between August and October.
There's a character on the stream that a lot of people like. I'm sure you will see them again
for something. Whatever that is. Who knows? Whatever that could be. But there is going to
be a stream. I hope I'm hoping that we can get it together. I don't know. Who knows? There you go.
Oh, thanks for the announcement, dude. You literally just said, hey, a project,
big project August. Bye. I know. But I'm just so excited for it. The last like three or four days,
I've just been like fucking just like writer Andy just like writing a fucking novel about these
things. So in due time, you will know. But I'm very excited for it. But I'm really hoping that
it's going to be by August. I mean, by October, without a doubt, because there's no I can't do
it after October. It's no way. So there you go. That's there's your like, let's catch up
because you've been gone for like, five days. All right, I'm going I'm going to squelch some
rumors here. It is not catboy related. Sorry, I'm gonna have to squelch some rumors. I'm seeing
some rumors in the chat. It is not catboy related. squelch. Yeah, it's like an old
World of Warcraft term where you've muted somebody. How do you guys not know that?
Is it a rat boy stream? No, it's not. It's not a time. All right, we gotta go. I gotta I gotta
stream. We gotta I gotta go. No, I gotta go stay. I haven't even started. All right, let's go.
But TLDR. Holy shit. I'm excited for the summer. After the summer. Wow. The summer should be full
of fun stuff. I'm very excited. Let's go. Let's play ultra kill. Should be able to see me now.
Can you see me? Can you guys see me? They can't say anything. Well, oops. Can you see there you
go? You can see that now, can't you? Now, what about me? Can you see what about me? Can you see
me? What about me? Can you see me now? Hey, kid. How are you? Hi. So I ultra kill is a first person
shooter game. You're gonna squelch me? All right, that's fine. Okay. All right. So ultra kill. I
don't know anything about it. I know it's a video game. It came out two years ago. Oh, well, so
okay. Is that a problem? This game came out two years ago. I play games that came out 10 years
ago all the time on this channel. It's still in development. Too loud. Should I put both headphones
in? This is a gamer game, right? This is from the very beginning. I've never I don't know. I've never
played this. This is a gamer game, isn't it? All right. If it's a gamer game, I think I can handle
it. How did how did the three stooges used to do that? It was like did it did did it. I don't know.
They were fucking professionals. All right, keep out mouse five to punch. This is really fucking
loud. I gotta turn it down. Like it's too loud for me. Like way too loud. Okay. Now is it too
loud for you? What do you what do you guys think? How do you have five buttons on your mouse? I don't
I have three. I don't know why it's called mouse five. It's weird. Okay, so that's punch. Left
control is slide. That didn't work. I have to hold it. Okay. Shift to dash consumes stamina.
You can dash in the air and you can double jump too. Okay. All right. So now do I have a gun?
Deal close range damage to douse yourself in fresh blood. This is the only way to regain health.
I don't I feel like gonna make a comment on it. So like I'm just gonna show you that I'm drinking
this today. This is like I know people gonna say it's like fucking sewer water. But like look,
here you go. Get it out of your system. Okay, I just I literally just took a sip out of it. I took
a sip out of the sewer water. So you can laugh about it. Okay, jump well near a wall to wall jump.
Okay, control in the air to ground slam. Okay, there's a lot of things that you can do.
Jesus, this is still loud somehow. Most levels have secret soul orbs. Touch them to get point
bonus. Ow. That it? All right. Where does the where does the gogoda gogoda start?
When does it when does it start? It's got I know it's gonna start. When does the gogoda gogoda
start? Come on. New blood presents. Come on. Where's the gogoda? Come on. A game by RC.
Hakita. Where is it? Here it comes.
Oh, all right. So this thing looks chaotic. So wait, do I have to? Okay, well, this thing
charges. Do I deserve reload or no? Get the fuck out of here. Turn the music up. But I don't like
music. Like that. I'm gonna turn the sensitivity up just a little bit. I put it way too down.
Where is it? Okay. Maybe like 15. It feels a little better. Hold right button to charge. Oh,
that's how I did it. And then do I let it go? The music's good. I know. But I just don't music.
I'm a fucking weirdo. All right. I don't really listen to that much music. All right. That's
fucking sick. How am I getting a C? I should be getting one that. Oh, shit. That sensitivities.
Sensitivities still high. 12. C for cool. Hit control. All right. That feels good.
Oh, come on. That's a B. That's an A. This dude's morbid right now. I don't even know what that
means. Punch to deflect. I didn't get it. I don't get it. What's going on? Okay. That's very
specific. I'm just gonna do the bloodborne technique and that's just dodge everything
and don't ever parry. This is chaotic. Yeah, it is. It's fun though. This is really fun.
Any secrets? Oh, shit. I'm sliding. That's pretty fun. Nice. Oh, you're so glad I'm playing this.
I mean, it looks fun. Ground slam deals damage on direct hits. Where'd they go? Whoa. Oh,
you can launch them in the air. Oh, you can launch them in the air. Why did my Boston just come out?
Oops. I died. What happens? Do I get to keep going? Fuck you. What the fuck?
I'm literally hitting it with my hand. Nice. Got it. Boss? My hands are like all sweaty.
Why am I having a vampire? I'm waking up. I'm where we're then. Off beat. No, I'm not gonna do
it. All right. How do I go? Why did this crash? No, it didn't. I'm an idiot. You know one song.
Tip of the day. Hits game weapons like the revolver do locational damage. The headshot
deals two times damage and a limb shot deals 1.5 damage. Cool. Weapons. Revolver. Oh, what? Really?
Whoa, this is cool. Can I upgrade this? Okay, so let me see. Cycle through equipped variations
with E. So what is this? This is a... Okay, so if I throw the coin in the air, bing, boom. It'll
and it'll hit somebody's weak point. Okay. What about actual just kind of damage and shit?
Are these the same exact weapon with the only difference being the right click? They're the
same. Okay. All right. That's cool. What about the other stuff? Enemies. The cyber grind. I don't want
to do that yet. Sandbox. Okay. So do I just go? What do I do? Can I just go? Let's go. That's
fucking cool. That was... That's really cool. I got an S on this one. Oh, double S. That's double S.
I didn't lie. Sorry. That was probably really loud. I'm sorry. That was not so loud. I'm sorry.
I got to like go like this. Like, oh, I'm all right. What is this? Was I already in here? What is that?
I don't get it. I don't get it. It's for a secret level. Object. I got to turn this down, man. I
can't fucking hear it. I'm sorry. I just... It's good. I have to find something and put it here.
All right. Whatever. I'll find something and put it here, Andy. Right? Okay. Who's this? Ultra,
ultra, ultra. Oh, I got it. Why are you speaking like an AI today? How am I speaking like an AI?
Under construction. Okay. Should I just keep going? New camera angle means fake germo. Oh,
it's the camera angle. I see. Oh, all right. I see. People are concerned about the camera.
How come I'm eating something? I'm not. I'm drinking fucking sludge that I got from the sewer.
Look, this is sludge water. I'm drinking sludge water. Okay. I kind of like this better, but
we'll see. This is... This game's fun as hell. Oh, wait, wait, wait. No. Wait. Can I get up there?
Oh, okay. Ooh. So what does this do? I get bonus points. I don't know what that does,
but cool. I got it. Boss door. Wait, don't go in the boss door yet. It's probably other stuff.
Go up. Is there a shotgun in this game? Insufficient firepower. What? Bullshit. Bullshit.
Is there fall damage? You can throw multiple coins at once. Do they both shoot out? Wait,
what? Turn up the volume. Got you. I got you. I got you. I got you. Wait, what's this?
Oh, it wants to know if I want to change weapons for the boss. Nah, I got this.
Holy shit. That was... Whoa. What's going on? Shotgun? The blood heals you. Oh, that's right.
All right. Well, I don't want to go that way yet because I want to... I want to go back up.
This is going to be my favorite. Should I blow these up? Can I get points or money or anything
from those or no? Punch the shotgun bullets. What? Are you serious? What are you talking about?
Oh, that's fucking loud, but it's good. Shotgun is the best item in the game.
Supreme. Anarchic. Brutal. Anarchic. Brutal. Chaotic. Destructive.
How do I take a new weapon? Announcer Andy. League of Legends announcer pack.
Don't go over there. Brutal. I need to get over SS. This is probably a secret. I wasn't even
fucking close, dude. What are you talking about? I wasn't even close. It's sadistic.
That was probably loud. I'm sorry. Oh, I can't do it. It's going to be loud. It's going to be
too loud. I can't do it. It's going to be way too fucking loud. I can't do it. It's going to be too
loud. I was going to scream ultra, but I don't have a compressor on this mic, so it's going to
be fucking horrible to listen to. Oh, yeah. Anarchic. Supreme. Oh, I'm ready to say it.
Shitstorm. Come on, play better at the game. I want to say it. I want to say it so bad.
You have no idea how badly I want to say it. Brutal. Not good enough. Come on, you piece of
shit. Hurry up. Brutal. No. No. Just chaotic. It's okay. Come on. Come on. You can do it. I know
you. I got it. Fuck. Brutal. Sabre Wolf. You can flip other weapons. What? Play on a higher
difficulty. I'm on normal. Is normal too easy? That didn't feel easy. I have money, right?
Revolver. Shotgun. Ooh. What does that do? That was weird.
You can do that four times. Three times. All right. So, but it just kills you. I can't.
It can't do it four times. Three times is too much. What if I jump? You can't do it four times.
It's one, two, boom. One, two, boom. All right. I can handle that. I can handle that. Switch weapon
before it explodes. I don't know if I got anything. It could be like a rocket jump.
I'll try it. I like one, two, three, one, two, three. We'll try it. This is going to start to get
confusing. Time it with the... All right. I don't do those advanced. I play on normal. I don't do
advanced techniques. New enemy. New enemy type. What the fuck? Why did it bounce? Fucking die.
Die. That thing was ridiculous. That first boss is now a regular enemy. Sadistic. Okay. Wait. What's
up here? Found a secret. What's the red? Holy fucking shit. What? What the fuck? Huh? No way.
What is hitting me? Should I try it again? What if I can't do it? Oh, that's fucking impossible.
That's literally not possible. That's impossible. That's not even possible. That's physically not
possible encounter. You're an old lady. I'm not an old lady. I'll prove it. I don't think I can
fucking do it. I'm going to head to bed. Can you wish me a good night? Have a good night. Whatever
that was. Who is it? Fuck you. No. What the fuck is this bullshit? What is this bullshit?
Okay. I did it. I did it. I did it. Red soul orbs give 200 health. Overheal cannot be regained
with blood. It's just an overheal. It's just an overheal. That's it. You're scary today.
I'm not. I'm fine. Don't scream into the mic. I'm trying not to. I promise. I'm not trying to be
loud. Is it loud? What should I do about it? I'm trying to like, just not scream. Is it fine?
Is it big? Can I go up here? Why can I go? Can I do it now? You're fine. It was one guy. Okay.
I missed. What? What the fuck? Oh, the glass is. All right. I got to stay up here.
Oh, Trump. Oh, Trump. Oh, Trump. Oh, Trump. Cool. All right. I got it. I think that's it. Right.
Did I get it? Please do a funny scream. I'm not. I don't want to scream in the mic. It's going to
hurt somebody's fucking ears. Derma. It hurt my ears every time you say fuck. Does it? You look
like a chicken. What are you going to do with that one? Fucking internet. Deal with that one.
All right. I can't buy anything else. He's, he's high. I'm not. I'm literally not. Cerberus.
How long is the game? What's wrong with him today? Nothing's wrong with me today. That's any
different than. Guys, the chicken noise was nominated for like worst sound of the year in
like 2019. I feel like I haven't done that before. Is this, can I stand on this? Okay. For a second,
I can. All right. So I like the, I like this. This is so loud. I like the, um, the coin.
It's hard to hit, but it's fun. So I'm going to do coin and I like these.
I wanted full health. All right. You guys ready? Let's go. Oh, I can't keep them on the green. I
have to swap it. I can't leave it on the green. Oh, okay. It's cute. You can do that in the
settings. Q works. Although if I get sick of Q, I can do a mouse scroll. I'm assuming. Oops.
That's a death. That just looks like a little spinning log that wouldn't kill you.
Why would that kill you? That doesn't hurt. How would that kill you? That was just a spinning
log. Why? How does this kill you? All right. I got a boss already. Attack sound cues allow you to
keep track enemies off screen. This is a boss already. Cyber grind. Not yet. Abandon hope all
who enter here. Oh shit. It's these things. Is it both or just one? Oh, God damn it.
Fuck. All right. I got to get the timings down. I need blood. Damn it. The AOE hurts.
All right. I'm going to swap to this. Let's go. You know what? Let's go like this. I got an idea.
How did I kill this thing instantly before? I killed it instantly. How? I don't understand.
Fuck. Fuck you. Fuck off. Why am I crying? Holy shit. That was crazy. Jesus. You need to
put a shawl on you, old lady. Use the slide. I keep using shift instead of control. I keep going
like this. This is actually the dash, but it lasts way longer and covers way more surface area.
I keep trying to eye frame dodge. This is fun. I like it. Why is chat being so mean today? Because
I haven't been around for five days. They've boiled up like five days worth of insults.
Wait, anything else I missed? I don't think so. It was actually six days. Thanks for keeping track,
but I actually hate you. I'm just trying to find something you like, you enjoy, it makes you happy,
man. Find something that you like. Don't watch me because you hate me. Don't hate me. Find
something you enjoy doing. Hating you makes me happy. Well, I don't know what to tell you.
Nothing new. I'm starting to get the hang of it though. I'm starting to understand.
I almost want to switch. I almost want to switch control and shift. I feel like I would
because hitting it with my pinky kind of hurts. This is nice. I don't know if there's something
in there. There's a coin in the fountain. Where? Well, that's very specific. Okay. I guess we're
going down here. What? Complete the level in under 10 seconds. I could do that. Just run and do the
well. So now what? You found a secret mission. What did, what do I do? Um, okay. This is on.
Oh, okay. How's that wrong? What do I do? What is this? Okay. Don't touch that one.
Easy. There's way more of these. All right. Let's fucking go. Let's go. Ultra kill. Ultra
kill. AKA the witness. Back it up. Back it up. Back it up. No, I didn't mean to. Whatever. I'm
not supposed to scream. I got it. Stop. What more of this bullshit? I don't get it. Oh, I can do
that. I get it. Okay. I was going to say, how's that possible? All right. Open the door. Oh God.
There's more. All right. I got it. We're going to do this quick. Is it a tweet from the dev?
I'll have to look at it in a minute. All right. Wait. So the, so red and blue can both touch
white. I'm assuming, right? What are you talking about? Wait, they can't? What? What? Why? What the
fuck? Huh? How old are you? You, you don't, you didn't get both red the first, but do I, um,
this is a new mechanic. Everybody call me a dumb ass. It's a brand new mechanic. I haven't seen
what, why would I know this immediately? I'm asking a simple question. I've gotten this far
in five minutes. Okay. So, okay. So I was right. Guys, what? How would I, how do you do this one?
Cause I can't, I can't go either one of these directions. Can I? I'll come back to that one.
This is an iPad game. I'm fine. How would I do this? So this, okay. This has to go here. This
has to go here. Okay. How do I get that one? How do I get the top left one? Blue has to go. Okay. So
blue has to go this way, but what the fuck? How do I do this? Blue hat? No help. Like, does that
work? Yeah. Okay. I don't, I, I don't know why my brain was saying that the white balls had to be
touched by each of the three colors. I didn't. Yeah. Okay. All right. What was this one again?
Yeah, this one's weird. So now that I got that, that one's easy. All right. Now I understand. Okay.
Let's go. What? Oh, why is that wrong? Oh, fuck. I didn't mean it to click that. All right. One
more. That was the easiest one. No, no, wrong. It's this. Wait, what if this just does that?
Right? Do I, I don't have to do any bullshit, right? Fuck. Shit. It's close. Got it. Testament
two, failure after failure after failure. Results refuse to alter again and again and again and
again and again and again and again and again. And my faith begins to falter. Now what? That was
nice. That was actually kind of fun. Those puzzles were cool. I mean, that's, I liked it. That was
fun. It was called the witness. Oh, the witless. Okay. Wait, what happened? What does that mean?
Did I get any points for that? This is a dev tweet. Where's the dev tweet? From the dev. I think more
than anything, I'm surprised that Jerma is actually good at the game. What? Followed by
unprecedented. A streamer is good at one dash S puzzles. I'm so happy he gets through hard puzzles
quick and get stuck on easy ones. It's wonderful. I did a fantastic job. I think I did a fantastic
job. I think I did a fantastic job. Hey, DM me where the fucking secret weapons are. I am good
at the game because I have to prove every so often to all these, all these kids that I am good at
video games and I'm not just like an old lady shuffling along. Nope. And let me show you right
now what I mean by that. Explode. I'll do it with my eyes closed. What the, I, whatever. All right,
that's a cool weapon. How do I use it? Wait. Use the attractor nail guns magnets to form concentrated
orbs of nails that can be moved around using the pull force of other magnets. What are you talking
about? What do these do? Oh, they're magnets. I get it. So you go like this and then that's
a cool gun. I get it. So you stick it on somebody and you just, all right. Okay. Let's, huh? My
fingers are slipping off of my mouse. Headshot. Cool. All right. I need to like pull this thing
out more. Where are they from? Is that it? Where's the rest? Another dev tweet. He's stuck on the
hardest one. This has taken some people like 40 minutes to solve. Yeah. What you don't understand
I came prepared. I'm an iPad gamer. And what that means is I lie in bed like this. You see these?
Let me show you something. This is, let me show you this. Do you see this? Do you see my neck?
The lines on my neck. You see, I have like line, line, line. See? Maybe you can't see because this,
I have lines on my neck and it's because I go like this. You see, I lie in bed with an iPad
and I just, I'm like this for six hours straight. And it gives me these lines here. So I play games
like that. And sometimes I go like this because just like, you know, saliva is coming down.
But for the most part, dev said, you do DMS aren't open. Yeah, I know. No, I don't have my DMS open.
I, I would never have my DMS open. Do you understand? I would wake up every morning
and they would be 99 plus sign next to that little thing on Twitter. And then just be like,
I don't, what the fuck am I going to do about this? It would just be,
people would send the most ridiculous fucked up shit. No way. I skipped a level. I'll go back.
So what do I go from here? I can go up there. Is this a puzzle? What an ego? No, I'm, I'm,
it's not an ego. I'm literally telling you real life. Like that's just what happens.
Are you trying to tell me really, really? So you're trying to tell me that one of,
one of you goofballs in this chat wouldn't be somebody that would just send me 99
plus messages in one day. You don't think that would happen? You don't think that I would wake
up and then one of you would send me two to 3000 messages just, just to make sure that I would see
99 plus? Of course you would. That's not ego. All it takes is one of you to do that.
All right. How do I get up there? He's goofball. I mean, come on, just don't fall. All right. I
got to pay attention. There it is. And here it is. And here you go. Don't scream. It's going to be
loud and it's going to hurt somebody's ears. Took 40 people. What? No, it took, everybody took 40
minutes to whatever the dev said. I don't care. 40 minutes for people to do that. Get off me.
That's a new enemy. I don't know what it does. Holy shit. What's that?
Bop, bop, bop, bop, bop, bingo. Do one of those custom announcer pack things like
quadra kill, triple kill, pentakill. Wow. That was crazy. Where do I go? Triple kill.
I'm going to give you guys a custom announcer pack. You can put in like, I don't know, like
source games. Where do I go? What? Should I put this down here? Oh shit. I can't leave.
Bugleberry. After every kill it just goes. Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh. That would be every single line.
So I just, what the fuck happened? What? Guys, guys, how do I do this? How do I do this?
It's important. How do I do this? It needs to be this goes in like this and the game does too.
I need to zoom the whole thing in. Hmm. Interesting. Interesting. Okay. Give me one
sec. Give me one sec. Interesting. Interesting. Very interesting. Incredibly interesting. Okay.
Hold on. Very interesting. I need to macro this because I want it to be this goes in
this. Hold on. I need to lock these. Okay. Guys. Okay. That looks all right,
but I need to make sure this gets a little bigger. Oh, I lost my game capture. That's bad. Okay. So
how do I tie? I got to group these together this way. Hold on. I need to make a new group here.
Hold on. I need to come on. Where is it? Group. Okay. Let's go like this and like this. Group.
Group into a folder. That's fine. Now. Fuck. Hold on. I'll get it. I put the wrong thing in the
folder. Fuck. Hold on. This is going to be worth it. I promise it'll be worth it. Is this the regular
game or is this the zoomed in one? That's right. Okay. That's regular. These are both regular.
So I just need to go like this. It's going to piss a lot of you off, but that's whatever.
Okay. All right. Here we go. I just need to make this a button I can press.
We need to get some music. We need to get very important music. Hold on. I got to get my stream
deck. Okay. We're looking for, just put a source here. Source. And this is going to be, uh, the
fuck. Come on. I need to, come on. I'm not Googling how to do it. Streaming. No, I don't want it to be
a fucking scene. Okay. Here we go. All right. I'm ready. I'm ready. I'm very close to being ready.
You have no idea how close I am. Can I get it? Let's get a countdown here. Okay. What the fuck?
What am I supposed to do? Guys, a blue flash means an attack is unperiable. What does that mean?
Whoa. A guy. Hold on. Watch out. I got it. I got it. I got it. I got it. I got to get this kill.
Got to get this kill. Got to get this kill. Oh, I died. Shoot. Wait, wait. This is going to get
better. I promise. You don't need to edit it. Hold on. Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait. I just,
I'm having trouble. I'm having trouble understanding where to go. I think it's the guys.
Is it this way? What happened here? Why is this place on fire? What? I think what I'm going to
have to do is go down this way. Oh, bad guy. Bad guy alert. Bad guy alert. Whoa. It's all right.
We got him guys. Maybe I'll try the shotgun for this. Oh, get absolutely lit up. Okay. So I think
I'm going to stop for a sec. Where is this even playing from? Is this still playing? No. Okay.
We're good. So where do I go from here? We need more. We'll do more later. Okay. I'll do more
later. This is an elevator. This is red. Red, right? So what's the problem? Where do I go?
Take the red skull with you. But isn't this a red platform? Oh, it's, I got the red skull from here.
Sorry. I was doing a thing. Sorry. Where's the red? All right. Sorry. I was doing a thing.
Hell yeah. Supreme. Nice. Can we get a German 985 break court remix? Nope. Oh, that's it. I'm
really good at the kills. Oh, I can go lower. I'll fire while shooting to overheat it. Let me try.
Whoa. Holy shit. Wait, how much has to recharge? So you shoot, shoot, shoot, shoot, shoot. I like it.
Thanks for making me laugh, E-clown. Hey, that's what I'm here for. That's what I'm here for. I'm
here to make balloon animals split color doors only require one skull to open. If you do not
seek hardship, stay indoors. Okay. So I only need one checkpoint. That's definitely a boss killer.
I would say you block that either blocking that block that, you know, I keep thinking there's a
double jump and it just isn't there's a dash statistic, ultra ultra brain, the head in the
head in the head. What's next? Please scream ultra. I don't want to hurt anybody's ears.
Oh my God. I'm going to die again down here. Fuck you. Ah, just to save it. Save, save it.
You piece of shit. I need help. Where is he? Fuck out of here. That was crazy. Ultra ultra.
I need that help. No, give me the blood. Jesus. Okay. That was tough. What the fuck?
Honest to God, what happened? What? What's going on? Do I have to do this again? What happened?
I need help. I don't understand what happened. I really don't get it. Can I leave? I can't leave.
You stupid. I don't want to do it again. There's not enough blood to go around whatever it is.
Dude. Oh my fucking God. Dude. I'm going to rip this fucking thing off. My. Okay. My keyboard.
You know what they need to make? God damn it. If you're a manufacturer of like gamer
peripherals, we don't need keyboards. Stop making keyboards. Stop making new keyboards.
No, make a gamer little mini thing. Let me, let me collect myself. A place for me to put
my keyboard. That's not like a piece of shit. I need a place for my keyboard. That's not like
connected to the desk. I need like a little separate desk for the keyboard that I can move
around and is customizable. You know what I mean? These like slide outs, they only slide out so far
and I can't go, I can't get in there. I need another desk that's underneath this desk. That's
like a whole keyboard desk. Do you understand what I'm saying? Cause this under the slider thing,
it goes out so far and then I can't get it out even more. I hate it. I'm going to rip it out.
I'm going to rip it out. I'm no, you're in your thirties. You can't do that. Stop. I need blood
right now. I need blood right now. Oh, that's not going to give me any blood. I just got,
I got rid of more blood. No, don't you dare. I need fucking blood, man. Okay. My goodness.
Now don't mess it up. So I don't want to go here. I don't, I'm not going in here again.
I'm not going in there. What's the, I have to go that way. What? I thought there was a,
there's two doors. There's a blue door and a, and a red door or something. Right. I have to go this
way. Wait, where's the, where was that? Right. There was like, Oh, blue door. And then you only
need one, right? You only need one skull. So I can just go back. Yeah. There it is. Walk into it.
Okay. I'm dead. Well, whatever. Where am I? Oh, it's something about it is making me fucking angry.
What the fuck? It's everything just moves so fast.
What the, I need fucking blood. What the fuck? I can't, I don't even, I can't even tell where
anything even is. This looks like you know what? No, it doesn't. Oh my fuck. This guy's the whole
screen. He, this area is just, get off me. Get out of the fucking way. I'm going to eat it.
Give me this fucking keyboard. You know what it is? I figured it out. Gamers, my arm rests,
my arm rests are at the point where the tray comes out and is hitting the arm rests. This,
I, I need this to be an, I don't want arm rests on my chair. Like this is, feels weird. Now
these big ass arm rests, I feel like I'm sitting in a law firm taking fucking calls for clients.
Get these things out of here. I don't want arm rests. Now I feel like I'm tiny. I hate this.
I'm in the right spot, but I feel like I'm small. I'm so mad. God, I want to unlock the camera.
You fucking idiot. I'm so, oh, I'm so flustered. Okay. Are we good? Okay. I, this feels strange
though. I feel like I'm sitting at like a high, like a high chair. Okay. Check this out. Watch
this games. I'm going to do good now. Ready? One, three, one, four, one, three, four, one, two,
three, go. Oops. Oh, shut up. It's such bullshit. It's a, it's so dumb. It's a stupid fuck the
coins. Why am I even using them? That was so much blood. How come I get the fuck off me?
You gotta be fucking kidding me. This whole area is too small. Oh my God. The area is too small.
Shoot him. Shoot him. Oh my God. Shoot. Well, I jumped over it. Oh my God. I don't know what,
I don't know what it is about this. I fucking hate this. Oh my God. I need help. Get out of the
fucking way. I'm in his body. God. I can't, why did I not get any blood for that? Oh my God. I
feel like I'm fucking way over the thing. How am I not? How's it not getting blood on me? Okay.
How am I not getting? I honestly feel like I'm like, I'm looking down at this big explosion
and I get hit by it. I feel like it happens every day. What the fuck are you talking about?
How am I supposed to avoid that? Oh, that was stupid. This is so fucking hard. This is so hard.
This is so hard. I hit space. Don't be that close. Dude, I can't even fucking see
man. This is fucking crazy. Shut this off. You know what? Just get this like,
don't you fucking dare. That's fucking hard. This game's really hard. I don't even want to.
Okay. That was fun. That's fun. That was actually really fun. You know what I'm saying though?
I, I need something for my desk. I need another second desk that's underneath that like goes like
and then comes out into the keyboard and I can put it wherever I want.
It's always the keyboard is under the desk and sometimes that's not in an ideal location.
Sometimes that's not an ideal location. Hold on. Sorry. How's this up? What's still alive?
Put it on top. No, because then you end up like this. It's like, it hurts my wrist. Only boomers
put their keyboards in the desk tray. It's not in a desk tray, man. It's not a desk tray. We got a
new tweet from the dev. What does it say? We'll find out. Says, I don't see it. We have a tweet
from the dev. What does it say? It looks weird. Whatever. Yeah. It's uh, at Hakita dev. Whatever.
It's fine. Why am I laughing like butt head? That was funny. There's only world one. I'm never going
to beat this game. I know that music. Have I heard this music? Hey, this one's for you, man.
Claire de Lune. It's all right. Bring it on. Forgive me. Do I have to do anything about this?
Turn this shit up. I don't know. There could have been something down here. All right, let's go.
I need three blue skulls to open that door. Let's go. Pick up to read. Somebody else can
read this. This one doesn't open. Okay. What's that? Whatever you are, you're about to get.
Wacked. V2. Fuck. Oh, where'd you go? Huh? Where'd you go? I don't understand.
No. I'm never going to win. I'm never going to win. Try jumping. I've been in the air 50% of the
time. Dude. Holy shit, man. I, why the, I, what do you want me to do? This game. This game. I'm
telling this game's fucking hard. Why am I different? I'm in a different language. I'm
speaking a different language or something, Mike. I don't know what this is. I'm speaking
a different fucking language, Mike. Come on. Get closer. The guy is flying around the map and
dropping missiles everywhere. I don't, there's no get closer reliability here. He's very fast.
I can, he's very small and I just got point blank and didn't get any blood on me apparently. So I
don't get to win. I got a better idea. I got it. It's gotta be this. That's the closest I got with
this. Not too much. I get halfway and I'm just like exhausted. I get halfway and I get exhausted.
I get halfway and I get fucking exhausted. Come here. Where'd he go? Where'd he go? I was fucking
freaking out. I was actually freaking out. It's just, I get exhausted. I can't, my brain goes
like, all right, man, that's enough. There's no humans are supposed to be doing this.
You know what fucking humans are supposed to be doing? Humans are supposed to be fucking picking
up like a wheelbarrow full of like logs and just like slowly walking with it. And then,
and delivering those logs to the community. And then like those logs are used to build houses.
And then there's also like a baker and like a butcher and no humans aren't supposed to be
doing what we're doing right now. Humans aren't supposed to be doing this. Like we're supposed
to be like, oh, howdy, how are you? Good to see you. We're not supposed to be like,
humans are supposed to be like, we're supposed to be fucking relaxing with each other and having a
good time and taking care of the community. It's amish. It's not amish, man. Just humans
are not supposed to be doing this. Guys, when Ben Franklin was writing up the goddamn fucking
Declaration of Independence, there was no guggity guggity in there. There was no, oh yeah, we also
need to make sure to leave some room for guggity guggity guggity guggity guggity. There's no room
for that, Ben. Quaker Oats Guy? What are you talking about? What do you mean? What are you
talking about? Why are you saying Quaker Oats Guy? What do you mean the Quaker Oats Guy? I don't
know what that reference is referencing. What are you referencing? I don't know what you're talking
about. No, there was no time for guggity guggity. I just beat it. I just beat it. Oh, all right.
Oh shit. Which one of these has been here longer? Oh, this one. The Quaker Oats Andy? What did that
do? You know, humans are supposed to be just like, it is amish. Fucking really is amish.
We're supposed to be like cutting wood and like growing beards and like, oh yeah, absolutely.
I'm the builder. I'm the butcher. I'm the banker. I'm supposed to be sitting here at this shit.
I got a D. The Quaker guy is calling at 3 a.m. We're supposed to be
holding up. Okay. Shockwave. Okay. Can that do it? Can this do anything different?
Okay. But there's no Amish bankers. You know what I mean though? I hope so that how does that do?
Boom. Okay. The Quaker Oats Guy pretty much hated everything. Fun. Wait, really? Why are we calling
him the Quaker Oats Guy, by the way? What's that guy's name? The Quaker Oats Guy. You don't know
that. It's a Quaker. What's a Quaker? I know a Quaker is something in something out. What is it?
His name was William Penn. He sucked. He sucked, dude. No, you don't want to know this guy. He
sucked. Oh, he sucked, dude. All right. How do I get out of here? Derma failed 10th grade. No,
I didn't fail 10th grade. I just haven't been in 10th grade in 20 years. I don't wake up in the
morning and go, oh, William Penn, the Quaker. He was a Quaker and he hated fun and he sucked.
I don't do that. I'm an adult. I don't think about school or history books. What are you talking
about? What are you on about? This guy's on something. Whatever. Whoa. Weren't you a teacher?
I wasn't a teacher. Guys, I think you severely underestimate what a substitute teacher is doing.
Oh, that was a big one. Ego Maniac says everybody underestimates his work. Now that I was saying the
opposite of what you're thinking. Okay. We're good. Oh, shut up. Not you guys. This guy.
What are you? Could I have survived? What's going on? What's going on? What happened? I'm fine.
I'm alive. No, dude. What the fuck happened? I freaked out because I was. Okay. Wait, wait,
wait, wait. Don't freak out. Nobody's nobody's nobody here. I saw an orb. We're dead.
Are you fucking kidding me? Where is he? Shut up. Oh my God. Okay. We're good. Thankfully,
this check my writer. Oh man. This is going to be hard. It's hard, man. It's hard to do this.
It's so easy to still like bunk bunk bunk bunk bunk bunk bunk bunk bunk jump jump jump.
Can I not do that with this thing? I don't think I can do it with this thing. Okay. Let's get up
there. Oh, I don't want to use that thing. That thing sucks. I touched it. What the fuck? What?
Okay. Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait. Who's left? We're good. Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait,
dude. I got it. I got it. I just scared the shit out of myself. I looked over here. Whoa. Look at
that. What are you doing? Was I supposed to do that? I think so. Okay. I got it. You have a
runny nose. Whatever. That was hard. This dude is going insane. That was this epic high octane
gameplay. Wondering when the stream of Ratchet and Clank is coming for the PS2. I don't like
any of those games. They're not for me. I'm okay. Ratchet and Clank, Jack and Daxter. I don't
really play them. I didn't really care. I know. I'm sorry. But it's true. I didn't really care.
It's not that I think they're bad. I just really didn't get into it. These guys have guns.
Who else is left? Where is this person? Secret? No. Give me the shotgun. Yep. No, I'm not going to
play. I don't know if I'm going to play Sly Cooper either. Oh, wait. Did I have to do I have to power
it or something? Why is the music so weird? Because it's an intense game. Well, what do I have to do?
Is there another one of these? Oh, of course. Okay. Ultra Kill is so good. This game is really good.
It's really intense. All right, there's one more. Where is it? Over there? Yo, where's this last one?
I don't know. Where's this last one? There's one down there, one over here.
So where's the other one? Follow the line. One, two, that one leads to here.
I got this one. So then this one leads this way. What? What? Headshot. Come on. Oh my goodness.
You're here. Checkpoint. All right. Those guys melt wicked fast. Oh, it's trying to be cheeky
with it. I'm trying to slide up the whole thing. Only the feedbacker can parry projectiles. Yeah.
All right. Why parry? You can just fucking annihilate them like that. Whoa. What's that?
Hey, it zooms in. Recharges even when unequipped. Switch weapons to keep fighting between shots.
Oh, shotgun. Shotgun is the best. All right. There's one power. There's a power over here.
Power. Uh-oh. Wow. Get out of here. All right. I need one more of those electricity things.
Holy shit. I need some. Look. Look. Look at us. What? I'm concentrating. I'm concentrating.
Shoot the coins with the rail gun. I ain't reading that shit. Why does he look like this? I don't
know, dude. I don't know what you're talking. What do you want me to say? Shoot the wall. Oh,
this one. You mean, cool. All right. Where's the last electricity? Don't even fucking think
about it, bro. What? No way, dude. What are you talking about? You shitting me. Fuck. Bad.
Stupid. That was so stupid. Before you die in the game, honest to God, this is like what I don't
like about games now, seriously. When I get to zero, it should go 10, 9, 8, 7, 6, 5, 4, 3,
2, 1, and then go to zero and then I die. And if I get one hit on anybody, it refills me to a
hundred percent. Like that's so fucking annoying. Like why? It's like, God, they don't make them
like they used to. You know what I mean? All right. That's two. The last one's down here.
Somewhere. All right. Wow. Somebody said, it looks like he's high on psychedelics.
I'm just like sitting here, just like freaking out. Oh, that's funny. Whoa. Screwdriver malicious.
I don't know. How much P do I have? Definitely not enough. Dude, you're just like rolling right
now. What the fuck, dude? What? This is insane. This looks fucked and not even real. This is
fucked up. Hold on. What on earth is going on here? Why is this? What are you doing?
Why is it doing that? Why is it doing this? Okay. I didn't want to do that. I don't know. I look
like a different person. That does not even look like me. It looks like a different person.
Cover the cam with that. That's a stupid thing to have there.
What is the sound? Super heart attack. This is okay. This level is called heart attack.
Leave it on so the Twitch thumbnail gets it. All right. Fine. Wait, you mean like do this? How
long does it take to get the thumbnail? How long will it take? A minute. It's going to take five
minutes. I look like fucking 70. I look 70 years old. Watch out. It's there. It's just two minutes.
It's there. Do we have a screen cap? It's not there yet. Well, why are you lying? Put a webcam on
the bottom of that. You want to put my webcam. Hold on. Oh, I got a blue. Where do I bring this?
Where do I bring this? Isn't there another pedestal somewhere? That's red here. This is red.
Where do I put it? Shit. Where does this go? Into the water? Jesus. Can you drown? I can't drown,
right? Where's the blue door? Where's the blue door? It's there. All right. Let me see. We don't
need this anymore. There we go. Okay. Hey, we're back to normal. People are going to click on that
and just not the kind of understand what's going on. I know I'm not keeping it. No. All right. So
where where do I put this stupid thing? Where do I put this dumb thing? It's underwater.
We're underwater. There's nothing here. Oh, fine. Bring it back. It's not there. Yes, it is.
Yes, it is. I can prove it. I can prove that it's there. I have a screenshot right now. So this is
what it looks like when you go to this category. Why is it so huge? Why is it so huge? Groggy Gary.
Groggy Gary makes it sound like I'm just zonked. That's what that means. Hold on. Why is it so
stretched out? What does the three mean? What is the three? Is that how long? It's been three
minutes. It's been three hours. Oh, okay. Make this the thumbnail. No, dude. What the fuck?
Okay. I need the judges like this. Crop this. And dude, cropping this is going to take an extra.
What? What is that? What the fuck is that? What did that say? Why did that just say something?
That's my name. What was that? What was that? What was that? What happened? Yeah. But wait,
if this is the thumbnail, won't it just be the fucking thumbnail? I'm so confused by this because
won't this just be the thumbnail? We're not doing anything different. It's just nothing's going to
change. Yes, it will. It'll be layered. There'll be two titles. I can't, guys, I can't even see
this. I need to make it a little bigger. Does that work? Am I in the right spot? Am I in the right
spot? If I go right here, is this like this makes sense, right? Okay. All right. Let's go.
Oh, there's a meat grinder right there. Shit. Headshots, headshots. Shit, I wasted it. Okay,
we're good. Good. Good. This gameplay is whoa. Do we get an update? Update? Is it there? What is
what the fuck? This is so weird. This is strange. This is gonna start to get fucking weird, man.
Hold on. No, I just replaced the game capture with a fucking image. Okay, there we go.
Where is it? Oh, it's huge. That's why. What the fuck? What is happening? There it is. This is
fucking insane. Even with like the view count, people are going to think that there's nothing
wrong with their computer. I don't think I can go anymore. Should I put hold on? What if I start
putting it down here? I have an idea. Okay, where's the game? I need the game. All right,
this needs to be ahead of this. Like here, right? And then I need to be here. Like that. Okay. All
right, let's go. I think that should be good. Okay. High pitched voice. What? Pitch up your
voice. Why would that matter? Pitch up? Why would that matter? It's an image. I don't understand.
Just do it, please. I don't get it. Because I'm tiny? But I can't. You don't understand. I can't
do that. I don't have my GoXLR plugged in anymore. So I can do this, but I don't know if that matters.
It's because I'm tiny. Oh, okay. I see. Watch out. Okay, I'm gonna go this way.
This meatwad. Oh, red. Red, because I'm a Sith Lord. Uh-oh. What is that? Whoa. Where'd it go?
Do the voice. No. Where is he? Holy shit. Did I get him? Get out of the fucking water.
What's he doing? All right. I'm good. Do the voice. I'm not doing the voice.
We got an update. Shit. We got an update. All right. What do we got? This one's a bit better.
Okay. All right. I don't know. How much more of this can we do? Like, look at this shit. Like,
I don't know. How much more can we actually? Well, the viewers keep going up. The viewers
are increasing this whole time. That is so funny. I think that's the funniest part of this is the
fact that the viewers have been going up by what looks like they leased into the thousands. Will
that keep going up? Will that be like 18.5 next time? That's a great question. I have no idea.
Okay. I'm going to move the game capture window again. This one, the game capture can be a little
bit bigger this time, right? Look at, like it can be that. Cam needs to be changed though.
Okay. All right. Let's, is it going to keep going up? All right. Let's go add an I funny watermark.
No, no, I'm, I'm into this right now because I want to see, this is important. I want to see
the viewers keep going up. We're not quite there yet. Put scratches on the screen.
Guys, you're going to have to give me a second. At some point, I'm going to have to react to it
with a big cam. Shit. That's gotta be it. Okay. I think that's good, right? Got it. Yeah. I'm
going to make a clickbait face. I will a hundred thousand. That's so much. Put a red arrow court
of the corpse king. Put a clickbait red circle on it with an arrow. All right. I'll put,
I'll put a big red circle. We've got an update. All right, let's go. There's another one. Let's
go. Did the viewers drop or did it keep going? It's the same 18.2. I need to, okay. I need a,
I need a red circle. Anybody got an image? 18.3. It's 18.3. Oh my God. No, it's 18.2. We're still
there. We're, we're still, it's 18.2. Okay. Now I need a red circle on this. God. Okay. All right.
Now where's the red circle going to go? I need a red circle. I need a, it's an empty circle, right?
Make, put it on your face from two times ago. That's what I was thinking either or the first
month. All right. We're going to do the red, a red transparent circle.
Okay. I'm going to call this circle. Okay. Here it comes. We need to carefully craft this guys.
And I hit an arrow pointing to the circle. Transparent red arrow. Oh my God. Okay. New image.
Shit. This is fucked up. It's not transparent. Why is it not? This is not transparent.
Huh? Hold on. It's got to be transparent. Okay. What the fuck? All right. I'm going to, I'm just
going to get the white out of here, right? Shit. Okay. I got to, I got to, it's a, what do I do?
What do I do? What do I do? What do I do? I got to add a mask, a mask, right? I'm going to key it out.
I'm going to key out. I'm going to key the white out. Okay. Got it. All right. Let's go. Let's go.
Let's go. Let's go. I got to go. I got to go. Let's go. I don't even know what the hell I was
doing in the game. You put Goku on it. No. What? Yeah. After this, I'm going to do a react cam
where it's big and I'm, I'm, wow. Am I fucking concerned? Why would I put Goku on it or put
master chief on it and then react to it? Do I have to go backwards? Is it going to kill me?
Add a red imposter. Okay. I'll add a red imposter and Goku. Okay. What happened? What the fuck? Oh,
that would have been really cool if you had seen that. This is like a crazy fight. Okay. I'm dead,
but is it, is it there? We got an update? Not yet. Okay. I think I have to go backwards. Oh my God.
Okay. I, I think I get it somehow. Oh my God. It's like playing a game up. It's, we got an update.
It's there. All right. Let's go. This is important. Okay. I need, I need a red imposter and Goku. This
is the culmination of the whole joke, by the way. You guys ready? Not yet. What do you mean? Not yet.
I thought it was there. Okay. Okay. Here it comes. I'm going to do this quick. It's not there yet.
Wait, it's actually not there. All right. Wait, wait, wait. I got, I got the images that I need.
I'm ready when it happens. This is the culmination of the whole joke. I'm not going to add any more
yet. Not yet. Oh my God. This is fucking hard. All right. Do I, do I got it? Okay. I need to,
I need a clean image. Oh, you put Goku in that one. No, no, no. Goku's got to go on the top left.
That's not the new one. Wait, what? The mods are putting Goku in already. Oh, that's not the new
one. Okay. Okay. It's still not there. Oh, did I break it? Maybe I just shouldn't be. Okay. I got
an idea. I got to jump over that. I need to get health. Oh, that goes fast. We got an update
because I got to act fast. Let's go. I got to act quick. I got to act quickly. Wait, hold on. This
is going to get messed up because of the, hold on. Wait, wait, wait. This is going to get fucked up.
This is going to get fucked up. Okay. I need to get rid of this. Wait. Yeah. Okay. Get rid of this.
Whoa. It's, we're getting perspective with this. Do you see how weird that looks?
Okay. Goku. Where should he be? Should he be coming up from the bottom? I don't know. Should it be,
should it be the whole thing like that? Like he's kind of looking at the video. He's checking it
out. He's checking out these, his subscription feed like this. And then let's get the imposter
in the top left. Like here. I don't want to get up like right here. And then I need to be like this.
Right. Is that good? Put Miku on the top left. No, no, no. I gotta be looking this way. Right.
Wider. Hold on. Like this. Hold on. Wait. Like this. Right here. I have to do this for a long time.
Don't I? Update. Update. It's there. Do we actually have it? Are you lying? Oh shit. No,
it's not accurate. It's not. No, no, no. It's not right. It's not right. I wait. I need that. I need
this. I need this. I need that. I need that. I need that. I need that. I need this one because
I'm going to look up at it. Oh, we actually, I got it. I got it. We got it. We got it. We actually
got it. We actually got it. It actually did come through. Hold on. Did it actually come through?
Hold on. I need to wait. Are they in the right spot? What the fuck? Hold on. Well,
it says 20K viewers now. Where is it? Fuck. Hold on. I got to get up there. I don't know.
I'm losing track of shit. I think we're going a little too far. I think we're going too far.
Add question mark. Okay. All right. One more after this and I'm done.
Add Saul Goodman. I can't. I'll add Walter White. The one where he's like,
you know what I mean? Did we get it? Update. We got one. All right. I don't know what else to
do with this though. Like, what the fuck is this? Okay. Hold on. Wait, wait, wait, wait.
There's too many things on the screen. I don't know what's real and what's not real right now.
You know, I don't know what is and isn't real. It's actually kind of hard to figure that out.
Okay. I'm going to go away. Wait, what happened? What happened to the other one?
Wait, this one just got up. No, this is not even an update. This one. What happened to me down here?
What? I'm fucking. I'm so confused. What's going on? This is a different one.
I'll put this here. Okay. Let's add this one. This is all right. I have to stop after this
because I have to go. I have to play a fucking video game guys. I can't just keep adding things.
Um, okay. Was that one more? This is going to be it after this. No more, no more.
Okay. Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait. No, I don't want to screw it up. I don't
want to screw it up. Hold on. I'm going to make this be transparent in the background. Like he's
like, what the fuck? I can't believe this video. All right. Hold on. I'm going to make him transparent.
Is that good? Where's the game? I lost the game. Okay. I just burped. Isn't there? Wait,
is there another one? All right. This is it. This is the last one. Move the face. Are we good?
Somebody said a worst joke at this point. I kind of don't care. At this point is like,
I have to finish it. I need to add Miku. My lips just stuck together. I've been,
I'll have my mouth open for so long. Okay. I got this. There's a Miku in,
in the mod chat right now that I'm going to use and it's perfect. Okay. We have an update.
There's an update. I got the update. All right. Update is here. We're good. I'm going to add this
one more and then I'm done. We're going to get one more thumbnail at this and I'm done.
What the fuck? Hold on. Where is that? Oh yeah. Walter White needs to be. Oh, it's because Walter
White is already on it. What's going on? Okay. Walter White was already on it. That's why it
was fucked up looking. Okay. I need, um, uh, I'll use that one. I'm not using that one. All right.
Fine. I'll use it. What do I care? But why would this even be on here? Why would this even be on
here? Why would that image be on here? Well, let's find out. Okay. You guys are going to laugh,
but I mean, whatever, I guess we're going to use this one. I'll use both. Fuck it. I don't care.
Okay. Um, and then I'm going to use this one. I think this is going to be the,
this is going to be the end. All right. Let's add that. My OBS is so fucked up right now. It's a
joke. It's such a mess. Okay. Oh, I just need to be transparent because she's going to be like
peeking over. Wait, hold on. Shit. Get it out of the way for in case it takes the thumbnail.
Okay. I need to do some editing on this. I'm going to keep a face here though. So I can make sure
just in case. Okay. She looks kind of fucked up, but I don't, that's okay. I think somebody just
said, why do people watch this? I don't know. I don't know, dude. I don't know. I'm sorry.
What do you, I don't know. Pog face instead. Add your soy pointing meme. Okay. And then we're done.
Update. Do we have an update? And then, okay. Then we're going to add the soy pointing meme.
Is there a, is there a transparent one of those? I don't think I have one. I don't have one of
those. The live is covering my face up here. It's so stupid. God damn it. Where, but I can't. Okay.
We need to move some shit. Um, I don't know where else to put this. I'm running out of things to,
I don't know where to put this fucking thing. Okay. Wait, you, you have this? Oh my goodness.
I'm done. I actually am done after this. We are done after this. This is it. This is the end. Oh
my fucking God. But they're too big. They're so huge. They need to be smaller. They're too big.
Come on, come on, come on, come on, come on before it changes. Make them pointed among us.
Better idea. You're right. You're right. You're right. I need, I need an arm. We get it. It's
there. All right. We got it. Got it. Got it. Got it. All right. Let's see. What, what does the
culmination of this whole thing look like? Cause that's it. I'm done. I'm done with this. It's
fucking crazy. Okay. I need to turn everything off. Everything has to go off so we can see what it
actually looks like at the end. Okay. Are you ready for the culmination of what is the thumbnail
right now? Here you go. Welcome to hell. This is what people are seeing. It only took us like an
hour to do this. You can't even see the Miku stuff. Jesus. Okay. That was fun. The best part about
this honestly is the perspective changing. It is everything is flattening. The whole game category
is fucked up. What is going on here? What are you guys doing? What are you guys doing? This is the
all right. What the fuck are you guys doing? This is the ultra kill category right now. Oh boy. Well,
the dev was here. Hopefully. Sorry. We're not playing the game. Okay. It's whatever.
Derma's Odyssey. What is going on? Ultra kill world record. Okay.
All right. You guys come on. All right. Come on. Come on.
That's you're not even in the right category. You don't even in the right category. All right.
All right. Let's get out of here. You're in the wrong category. You guys cut the shit. Okay.
Where's the game? All right. That was very interesting. What is this? Oh my goodness.
I have to navigate through all this shit on my hold on. Oh my God. Can somebody get me a decent
screenshot of that so I can put it on here because I can't follow through Twitter. Where's the actual
camera? I don't know where it went. Okay. There's the cam. Let me just let me go one by one here
and get this fixed. What? How long have I been sitting here for? Why does this look weird?
Something's off about this camera now. Why? Something's weird about it. Is it squished
or something? Something's off, right? Something's off. Is that better? I think I fixed it.
Was my head that long? I actually don't know. I think I got it. Okay. We're in a good spot.
Now I need the game back. Just the video game, wherever it is. Okay. Oh, that's not right. All
right. Okay. We're back to normal. Things look okay. We're good. The dev tweet. Okay. Hold on.
The dev tweeted a picture of, okay, that says, the dev's here. Sorry, I'm not playing the game.
My brother in Christ, I made the game. I've seen it already. I'd rather watch whatever the fuck this
is. Oh, sorry, I'm not playing the game. Yeah. All right. Let's check this out. Look at this.
Look at this insanity. What is going on here? Is this a smoking image? It's cyber grind textures.
I don't know what that means, but all right. I'm going to attempt to do something here. I'm
going to attempt to play the game again because I'm going to play the game. That seems like a fun
idea. I think that's what we're going to do. We're going to play. Okay. So what was I doing?
That was fun. I forget how to play the game. I actually do. I really don't. I don't remember
how to play. I don't remember how to play the game. I have to relearn the game. Okay. I'm
fighting a boss right now. Let's fight this boss. I should probably take a break. All right. If I
don't do it right now, then I'm going to take a break. Shit. It's hard. Oh my goodness.
Fuck. How am I supposed to do this? Do I have to get close? Got it. I'm smart. This is going
to be a part two. Nice checkpoint. Good. Hold on. I'm going to move this. You ever thought about
making your own game? Maybe over the years. Yeah. It's just, it's a lot of time, a lot of work.
Devs and getting PI. It's just, I had an idea at one point. Why do you look rendered? Because
it might have a greasy oily skin. How am I going to ever afford that? I need a red skull to get in
there. Sounds good. So we're going to just keep going. Right. Let's just go. Am I going the right
way? I hope so. Oh, there it is. That was easy. Oh, it's time to excuse me. Wow. That hurt. I need
to get, what's that do? I don't know. What do I do? What happened? I need to get help from the hand
over there. Yikes. No shit. Oops. No, I don't understand how to get up that high.
Yeah. I tried to hit the button. My fucking finger wouldn't do it. Fuck you. That didn't fucking work.
I tried to dodge it. That shit just fucking killed me in one hit. What's going on? He's too big. I
don't, but if I stay up here, he just like goes like this and I can't dodge it, bro. It's fucking,
he takes up the whole map with his swing. Why did that? No parry. He's not, he's not glowing
yellow. You can't parry it. I just tried. You can't parry. That was stupid. Just shut up. I
didn't know you could parry it. I thought I had to be a projectile. I'm not grunting. What sex noises
are you talking about? I've been silent the whole time. I don't understand the parry, man. I just,
that looked fucking pretty clean to me. What the fuck? Where am I? I can't fucking move, man. No
way. It's like, and you fucking float around like fucking low gravity. How was that not a parry? I
don't get it. Oh my fucking God. You slug. What do I do? What do I do? Yeah. Fucking right. How?
What is the frame? Is it one frame that I get to parry? Dude, excuse me. How are those wrong?
Excuse me. Excuse me. I don't understand. I'm, I am, it's like, it won't do it. Am I doing it too
late or too early? Fuck that. Fuck that. What do you mean too late? He's not even up, bro.
No, it's that I don't understand the timing. Does it make any sense?
Shut up. What the fuck, man? What are you talking about? This is not the easiest boss in the game.
Get out of here. You played on fucking easy. You played on easy. Now, right? I don't, it doesn't
make any sense. It doesn't, it doesn't make any logical sense as to why these aren't hitting.
That's a parry. That's a parry in every parry game I've ever parried. That's a, that's a parry.
I parried that in any parry game. That's a parry right there. I just did a parry. That's a parry
literally in every single parry game you've ever played. That's a parry right there. That's a parry
in every single game that has a parry, no matter what it is. This is literally impossible. I did,
I did it. Time it. Go back and slow down. Go back and do slow motion. I did that. I did it
perfectly every time. Go back and slow motion. Quiet. What? I hate falling off. And you know what
it is? Dude, like falling off the legend, like floating down just makes me want to fucking bite
my fucking hands off. This is so hard. It's just the timing with the stoop. It's just, I have such
a small area and I float around like a fucking, I want to jump. Where's the double jump? I don't
want a triple dash. I want a double jump. Where's the upgrades if I can put that shit in the game?
I want a, what? I got a heal right now. What? Stop falling off the stupid tiny platform.
The game, there's so much fast movement that like, oh wait, be careful. Don't slide up that son. It's
fucking two inches. Quiet. I'm fucking losing it. Relax. Now get up there and stop it.
Get back up there. You stupid piece of shit. You have to be kidding me. You can't, I was in,
it was the end of the fucking game. I don't get it. I don't get it because it feels like I'm landing
those well. The speed run for that fight is two seconds. I'm trying so badly not to make like,
yeah, sounds, but I fucking can't help it. I got a D. I don't care. Oh shit. This is it. I got two
more levels. It's all right. Relax. Whoa. Get out of here. What is this bullshit? You need to watch
the clip. What clip? What clip? I'm just not good enough to fucking do it. Oh, what? Oh,
monkey ass. Shut up. Oh shit. That's not it. That it? Woof. Best of luck. Vod watchers. What happened?
You just went goblin mode. I am making weird noises. Aren't I? What? I'm going like,
that's what I sound like when I'm concentrating. What? Is it because I have the audio in my ears?
That was really loud and horrible, but like, what do you want me to do?
That was like loud and horrible. This looks like, this looks like an actor watched, you know,
like maybe one to 200 hours of Twitch streams to research a role where he plays a Twitch streamer
in a movie. And that's what I'm doing. Yeah, that's interesting. My voice is like gone now too.
Breathing is definitely noticeable. That's because I don't have a noise gate anymore.
Oh, look at this. I really do go like, fuck, I got to fix that by next stream. Why can I break this?
Can I not break that? I don't get it. What's going on? Holy shit. Did I win? I've been silent. What
are you talking about? I've been silent the whole time. What? What the fuck? Huh? Is this what you're
talking about? That's fucked up. Why am I, why do I do that? Why do I do that? I'm serious. Why
am I doing that? I'm going, what? I'm going, look at the dev tweet. Honest to fucking God,
I didn't even know I was doing that. I swear to God, this is what's usually blocked. What did
the dev say? I don't, I guess I just make weird sounds. Grunt Gary. I guess I just make weird
sounds with my mouth. I guess I thought you guys would seriously just messing around. 40 year old
man. I did not, I, I didn't, whatever. I'm just going to keep playing the game. It's because,
you know what? I have both headphones in. So, and it's loud and I'm really gaming and I'm just,
every so often I'm kind of like, Oh my fucking God guys. I swear that's actually embarrassing.
Whatever. Who cares? Supreme. Oops. That don't die, right? Did I do it? Did I, did I just do it?
Did I just do it? No. Are you sure? I kind of sounded, I felt like I did. I have to climb all
the way up. Goodbye. Holy shit. There's so many. No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no,
no, no, no, no, no, no, no. Fuck. This is hard. Stay with the shotgun. There's nothing. This is
the best weapon in the game. Nothing is better than this. No, no, no, no. Don't you dare. Don't
you dare. Let's go. Checkpoint up there. Oh my God. Get to the checkpoint. Just touch the checkpoint.
Touch it. Yeah. Get up. Get up. Stop going in the water. I fucking hate the water. Get the
water out of here. Delete it. It's going to kill me. This fucking poison water is going to kill me.
I hate water in video games. I hate going into water. All right. Water sucks. It's so annoying
to play in a video game. I hate water. Yeah. I need a checkpoint, right? Ooh, that's it.
I did it. All right. This is three, two. I think this is the end of the game.
Three, two. When are you going to play Freddy Fish? Curse of the Fish or whatever. Whatever.
Stupid fucking kids game is. I don't know. Next week. Fire is a powerful drill that sticks to an
enemy and deals damage over time. The drill causes enemies to bleed with continuously with extra
healing range. Okay. What's the other one? Fires an instant beam that causes a large explosion on
impact similar to a certain familiar face. Wipes out groups of weak enemies with ease.
I think I want this. So that sticks on them. I'll try it. Okay. Now what? So I'm a robot
and I'm defying my maker. What the hell is that? What the fuck? I missed. No, I didn't. That's
holy shit in my fucking pants. Oh my God. Dude. I think I got him. Dude. It's so
fucking ridiculous. Yo. Should I block him? Can I block those? It's happening too fast.
I'm 37 years old, guys. I don't think I can do it. I'm 37. This is like a 19 year old's brain
can handle this. I'm too old. I think I'm too old to do this. Oh, how did I miss from relax?
I don't even have time to think. It happens so quickly. I just like by the time he dashes,
it's like, I don't even know. What am I? Where do I go? What should I do? What the fuck, man?
Well, what? This game's on times five speed. I can't even turn around fast enough to fight this guy
where I, I, no way, man. I don't think so. I don't fucking think so. I don't think I
suffering. Fuck it. I don't think I'm going to be able to do this.
Guys, you know what? Okay. In the time for me to move my, my ring finger to hit shift,
he's already hit me or control. It's like my brain can't go faster than he can. He's like,
just he's like programmed to go fucking faster than me. I, dude, I don't even, where are you going?
Come, come, come, come, come, come, come, come. Fuck you. I missed.
I should be fucking picking a wheelbarrow and filling it full of wheat and bringing it to the
fucking town center. Okay. You imagine a fucking person from like the 10 hundreds being like,
seeing this shit. No, I should be like, I should be baking the fucking muffins.
I shouldn't be doing what I'm doing. No. Fuck you. Get it, get it, get it, get it, get it, get it,
fuck you. Come on. Oh, come on, Morty. You're going to get out of here. You're going to get out
of here. You're going to get out of here. I missed. I missed again. I missed again. I missed again.
Just keep the shotgun out. Fuck. It's not fair. What the fuck are you supposed to do about this
fucking guy? No, I don't want, all right. Can I just delete all the weapons besides the shotgun
in the, I don't want to like, Oh, I don't want to use anything but these two weapons. I'm fucking
dead. I'm dead. I'm dead. Oh my God. I, I, I only want two weapons. How do I delete them right now?
Get rid of them. I don't want them. Delete them. I don't want this stupid. Why is it even in the
game? Oh, wow. It's what a great. Yeah. Unequip. I don't want that one.
Let's go. Let's go. Come here. Come here. Come here. You can't be.
Where is he? Oh, get this shotgun away too. There's no point in me having this equipped.
What's the point of me using the shotgun? It doesn't do anything.
Just delete the fucking shotgun. It does no fucking, this has no purpose.
Go. That's this guy's fucking head. Where'd he go? My boogers.
Where's my sound effects? What the fuck? What are you talking about? He can't do it.
Yeah. I'm sorry. I screamed so loud, but I missed.
I'm sorry. I'm so fucking loud. I'm so sorry. Oh my God. Can I ask a question? How the fuck
are you supposed to do this? Reliably? Are you supposed to just spam at this guy? I,
what are you supposed to do about this motherfucker? I'm going to save it. Hold on.
No fucking way. You're doing everything wrong. No parry. I like, I like you to parry this for me.
Oh, I'm sorry. That was loud too, but fucking, you know, fucking my,
I'm from fucking Boston. Did you guys know? Eat shit. Where's my,
get down here. I need another weapon. I need another weapon. Okay. I need another weapon.
No, dude. Come on. This is a fucking impossible. Oh my God, dude. All right. I'll only try to
parry this impossible dog shit here. Okay. Here we go. Ready? I, dude, he's like just
teleports behind you. Oh my fucking God. This is impossible. How would you do this on the harder
difficulties? It's not even human. It's inhuman. How hard this is. Come on. Come on. Come on. This
is it. God. I don't. Yes. Oh, sorry. That was loud. Unequip all of your weapons. That is
definitely the way. Yes. Unequip all of your weapons. That is definitely the way.
As the voice actor for this fight, making fun of me in the face of all the haters. Let's go.
Give me the little beatbox. Shoot it Adam. I don't know what to do. What do I do? I've
never been this far. I don't know, dude. I've never been this far. My hands are falling apart.
I can't even touch my mouse. They're wet. They're wet. They're wet. Holy shit. What's going on?
Let's kill me. Fucking kill me motherfucker. I don't care. Okay. We're good. We're good.
Everybody relax. Relax. Relax. Relax. Relax. Everything's fine. That's it. Okay. Ready?
Just relax. Everything's fine. I think you have a liver problem. Okay. Because my hands are
sweating because I'm playing a game that's literally impossible. I'm playing a game that's
literally not completable. It's impossible. And of course I'm going to have a little bit
of a sweaty scenario. Okay. Everything's fine. You're getting me riled up. He's so bad.
I missed. Oh my God. What's a steam? Fuck you. Fuck you. What is it on steam? What's the
achievement on this one? What's the achievement on this one? You there. I'm talking to you. You.
What's the achievement on this one? Percentage on steam. What is it? Okay. If it's, if this is
more than 20%, no, if it's live, this is wait, if this is more than 20%, I will eat two shoes on
camera. This fight on normal or harder. There's no achievement for this one. There's no achievements.
Okay. Nevermind. No shoes. There's no achievements in the whole game. Oh, oops. All right. Let's go.
Okay. Stop eating shoes. Everybody relax. Just calm down. You need to, you need to calm down.
You're concerning me. You need to calm down. You can't be fucking serious, mate. Guys. I don't
think this is possible. What the fuck just happened? I parried him accidentally. Huh? Huh?
This is what animal does. Animal from the puppets. Whenever he runs around, he goes like,
huh, huh, huh. Wait a minute. I missed. I missed. Just kill me.
Jesus Christ. It's, I, I don't, dude, I don't, it's just everything is happening so
quickly. And so there's only explosive shit he has. And then he gets angry and everything becomes
one hit kill. Oh, what are, who, why? What? I got it. I got it. I got this time. I'm going to win.
I'm going to win. I'm going to win. Bro, bro, bro, bro, bro, slow down. I just need to hit you with
this. I got it. Oh my God. It's so ridiculous. I can't fucking believe it. It's just like,
it's just,
the fuck am I going to do with that shit? What the hell was that for? Oh, fuck off. I don't even,
I don't even know where the fuck the guy goes. It's just, it's just loud sound effects and
I can't, I can't block them. Increase your FOV. What the fuck is this person talking about?
That's not going to help. This feels off. I missed. Just kill me. Shut up. That's the problem.
It's just like click, click, click, click, click. It's fucking so ridiculous. It's,
it's ridiculous, man. This is the end. This is the end right here. No, it's not. Oh my God.
Damn it. I don't even, I'm just going to dodge and shoot them. I was actually, it's pretty easy.
It's still fucking, it's still fucking impossible. It really is still fucking impossible.
There's a fucking thousand volts in my chair. No, I have to get them down to half with just
the regular revolver. I have to. It's not fucking possible any other way. And like the amount of
buttons guys, I probably press the buttons 5,000, 10,000 times. Humans were not supposed to be
doing this. You understand? We were supposed to be drinking water and not like, like no fucking way.
We were supposed to be doing this shit. We're supposed to be, Amish had it right.
What did it switch? I hit Q accidentally. I touched Q and it switched fucking weapons.
Oh, unbind Q and just unbind it. It's going to accidentally be pressed. Fucking God.
Just take it off. I don't want any of this shit. Delete it. Delete this. Delete it. How do I remove
it? I'm going to make it like fucking equal sign of something I'm never going to touch.
So we're going to do some breathing exercises now. That feels good. It feels pretty good.
It feels pretty good. I wish I was using one of these. Not like this.
I just had to hold my breath for fucking few minutes. 89 restarts. Yo, this is a meltdown
stream. No, it's not. It was a, it was an intense gaming stream. Disgrace, humiliation, unseeming,
unseemingly, unseemly and unwelcome at the feet of the council. Their eyes ablaze with bitter
resentment glaring through Gabriel's wounds of body and soul bore outward for all to see.
Has this one abandoned the way of our creator? It is unworthy of its holy light. The father's
light is indomitable. This one sees fit to squander it. Their words resonated in Gabriel's limbs
coursing through as lightning upon wire searing his that would strike lesser's death and blind.
The holy light within him an unstoppable storm of divine fury insurmountable for mere. I'm not,
I'm, I'm, I'm a normal person. Okay. Let's just get that out of the way. This he knew.
Holy council. My devotion to our creator is absolute. I have never strayed from the
will of the father, but a machine. You dare imply the might of the somebody will read this
impossible hearsay unspeakable heresy silence. Your treachery will not be tolerated as punishment.
The father's light shall be severed from your body. You have 24 hours. I'm like objecting in
a courtroom. You have 24 hours before the last of the embers die out and you with them prove your
loyalty. Unmake your mistakes. As the light was ripped from his being. Gabriel's screams were
silenced in the hyst of gospel and praise of God, a boiling Anguish to which even the fires of hell
could not compare pretty fucked up. If the machine seek blood, he would give it freely.
And with such fury, even metal will bleed. Go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go.
Whatever act two. Imperfect hatred coming soon. Do I have act two? Do I own it? Do I have,
do i have active there's four more levels oh great can't wait
these are gonna be a breeze are they i keep the voice actor from that character who made fun of
me that's funny all right turn the music back on yeah greed shit storm i got ultra kill i'm fine
put the music up louder stop complaining oh shit and he's uh he's using a hundred percent of his
brain be careful oopsie oopsie am i dead take a break i'm i'm gonna this is a there's a bug in
my ear there's so much shit in the way get out of get these fucking pillars out of here
anarchy right where where where are you where the fuck is this person what hey what did i just do
itchy armpits you need to do some you need to chill out i'm chilled right now i'm chilled out
i'm chilled out right now oh my goodness oh i missed where where are you oh my god these things
are stupid where the fuck is this stupid motherfucker he's like oh i'm hiding underneath
a thing i don't think over here my webcam's gotten darker there's a lot more left this is bright
oh okay that hurts if they're in sand they won't bleed tell me something superman
do you bleed this is such a terrible fucking place to fight you i feel like playing mario 64 oops
sorry that was loud shut up no way why would i use this gun like what's the point of using
that everything else is better how come i don't ever slide because it's because because using
my pinky to go like this to hit control i can't do it i can't hit the orange button on a guitar
here controller either i've i physically can't do it oh my god what's that what is that what oh
shit did that miss what the fuck are you talking about oh so many buttons i gotta get over there
and shoot them got it checkpoint no which way should i go this way oh shit double double double
double double double double the bit rate is fucking up bad bit rate um what do i do with this over
here i want to put this thing down oh there it is now i need red my voice is so junk right now
holy shit turn up the game's volume maybe it's probably like the fucking screaming i was doing
how's that better i was doing a lot of screaming yeah i gotta stop screaming dude
what was that there's something over there that's gold no can i get it from the other side
where is it over there uh excuse me i wasn't ready uh i'm starting to become exhausted i'll
be honest i can wall jump over there yeah oh it gives it me a double for how long i already
get a double from here you're almost done with the game yeah but like i know i can see i can see the
end but like i i'm so wrecked right now my like brain hurts okay i'm gonna go this way where should
i go pick up the second double how long does it last i'm just gonna go over here they stack
what the fuck um where am i where i am i'm gonna i fell off the edge i'm dead man i i can't even see
i would rather not have that on i have slowed down significantly i fell off yeah man
well i'm doing the equivalent of like i don't even know what this equivalent is i'm fucking tired
you know this has got to come out yeah granny mode is absolutely activated right now i'm fucking done
take a break no we push on i'm a gamer groggy gary's back it's going back in
oh my goodness get him pretty big damage yeah oh yeah so i am i is this how much more do i have
left oh two more that was so cool this game is really this game's awesome no that's not good
okay okay all right just to light everything up okay uh-huh i was gonna just i was gonna do
a joke where i picked my nose and ate it but i people probably grossed out by that let's freaking
go i don't think this is gonna work actually i did it i actually did it holy shit okay i like
this music this music awesome oh oh come on gwen okay i got it okay yes excuse me coming through
oh my god fuck fuck fuck fuck fuck fuck fuck fuck oh my god that was horrible that was actually
horrible that was fun so am i the boss am i about to beat this game i'll beat what's up to this
point right i still have the torch no okay okay all right what what are you doing oh i get over
there um okay hey where you going where you going what where you go i beat him did i i got him this
what does this sound like what does it sound like pretty cool so wait did i did i beat it did i do
it is there actually anything left i'm gonna get beat for this one did i do it thanks for playing
wrath is currently still under development for news on its progress follow us on discord twitter
and youtube really cool okay i did it that game was that was crazy i don't know how you do this
on this um difficulty i don't know how that's possible fight the secret boss go to all right
where is it yeah zero two can i pick what level i want to play on can i zero two you said is that
you have to perfect all the levels that ain't happening zero two oh i have to get p rank on
every stage that's not gonna happen that was awesome this was brutal i don't even know how
you do this on the harder difficulties this is a great game i understand why everybody wanted
me to play it all right with sandbox mode and what is sandbox mode this is just gary's mod
so now what what should i do spawn with physics how do i spawn something now i have to do tilde
can i pee i mean the streams should i go pee real quick i mean i'm turning the stream off in
literally like five minutes should i can i pee no no never mind what's the point all right what's
this okay spawner arm teleport menu no clip okay manage cheat so how do i spawn stuff i can just
spawn the secret boss press p spawner arm and slot five oh where's the secret boss ah okay that's
fun oh no what was that what happened it was sand i thought it was gonna be explosion whoa
why won't these explode okay see you guys later zoomer humor zoomer humor okay i'll see you guys
later actually what are we gonna do what are we gonna do what should we do what do you guys want
to see on on what i mean monday tomorrow what should we do tomorrow or monday friday fish oh
yeah that's right this cam looks really weird now this looks weird doesn't it it's weirdly
dark in all the wrong places well that was a lot of fun that was quite a stream thanks for joining
me we'll figure it out i'll be in pre-stream you know we'll go from monday monday at two i'm gonna
keep 230 two to 230 ish but i'm gonna say two but 230 ish you know you never know i will do monday
at two o'clock that sounds good i think that i got all the dread ex stuff maybe i'll do dread
stuff either that or i don't know sorry i'm so loud i don't know what do you guys think
we'll figure it out in pre-stream i'll be i'll be ready i'll be here on monday i'll be around
at like i don't know 130 years old do online quizzes you promised to play freddy fish yeah
but are you guys gonna actually be here for freddy fish are you just telling me to play it so then
you don't show up and you laugh because nobody's gonna be here we'll hit well there'll be 15 to
20 000 people here watching freddy fish and 10 000 of you are going to be begging me to play
a different game that's how it works you need to convince everybody that freddy fish is a good idea
all the demos too yeah vr joshua just saying it they have this curation of a ton of demos
on steam right now maybe we should just play a bunch of demos that might be fun maybe we'll
do that we'll figure it out should be fun appreciate it though thanks for watching everybody
a lot of stuff is in the works right now i hope that by the end of the summer we can look back
and kind of be like wow look at all that stuff that happened so i'm really looking forward to
it kind of a meltdown stream today but you know as it happens when you play these games that require
an intense amount of thought and focus yeah there is it there's a new bttv pride emote if you want
to use it happy pride month obviously here is it is it there is a drop yeah i've seen it yeah we'll
see you guys on monday monday monday monday check the category why is it all fucked up somebody at
twitch it just probably sees this category getting like there's probably some alert that they have
and they're just like what the fuck okay so sorry for lack of gameplay currently learning the
alphabet please click on this stream i'm begging you okay well the cbd sippy we do a little demon
killing keeping the germa oh god for a second i was like who's this and it's me fps gamer gra oh
that's me all right good night guys see you later thanks for watching as always i'll see you monday
good night goodbye take care of yourselves holy shit i had there was there was a lot of
friday gave a hundred community subs earlier how long ago did this happen
there's a huge raid too sorry sorry sorry am i saying that right well thanks for the raid
i missed a lot i'm sorry i was i was very much gaming it was literally at the beginning of the
stream sorry sorry that was a big raid i always miss shit i'm so fucking bad at streaming
i really am i get so locked in i just don't even know what's happening on my own stream
oh wait before i forget how's auto auto is good how come bostonian say sorry weird sorry
sorry sorry what do you mean it was during the tuber bit oh but yeah that no thanks if you're
still here thanks i i sometimes have a tendency to not pay attention to anything
but what is directly in front of me have a great night guys i'll see you monday good night goodbye
see you later call you mother