Hey, what is going on everybody? Jerma here with a Team Fortress 2 gameplay commentary, and today I just want to do a brief video talking about the new Man vs. Machine update.
Now, what this update did, I want to be really clear about this, because when I woke up this morning and I saw this, I was like, oh my god, we're gonna get, there's new maps, there's new stuff.
No, no, no, no, no, no. The only thing that this update brought to the table was new difficulties. As you can see on the screen here, the tours are now separated into three different difficulties.
And if you notice the one in the middle, Operation Steel Trap, is the original one. That is what they're calling the advanced difficulty.
So I'm assuming that Operation Oil Spill is going to be a lot easier than the one we are used to. But Operation Gear Grinder is only three missions long, and it's supposed to be expert difficulty.
Now, I will get a gameplay up eventually here in the next couple of days of us playing on the expert mode, and we will see how that goes.
But now I want to talk about the new loot that they've added. They have not added any new maps. I want to say that again, there are no new maps to play on in this update.
But there are going to be new Bot Killer items. As we are used to, we have the gold Bot Killer, which is the rare one, and then the silver Bot Killer, the regular one.
And now there's going to be four more. If you complete Operation Oil Spill, you're going to get a Rust Bot Killer weapon or a rare chance to get a Blood Bot Killer weapon.
They will be on the screen so you can see them right there. If you complete Operation Gear Grinder, you're going to be able to get a Carbonado Bot Killer weapon or the rare one is a Diamond Bot Killer weapon.
They all look pretty cool. I think the Blood one is probably my favorite at this point in time, just because the blood dripping down the robot's face. I just think it's really cool.
So how do you get this stuff? How do you get these Bot Killer items? You have to get the Tour of Duty tickets again. If you don't want to, if you do not want to buy the Tour of Duty tickets again, you do not have to.
You can play this whole update, all this stuff, without paying one single cent. The only thing the Tour of Duty tickets are going to do are allow you the opportunity to get the new Bot Killer items and to get the man up mode specific hats and miscellaneous items.
So if you don't care about those things, you don't have to spend the money. And speaking of money, it's going to cost you nine dollars, nine Tour of Duty tickets to complete the new tours one time.
And if you want to go for the rare items, you want to go for the Diamond Bot Killer, it's probably going to cost you a little bit more than that.
Or I guess you could get really, really lucky and on your first tour, you get the Diamond Bot Killer, which would be really, really awesome and I wish you guys the best of luck in your Tour of Duty journey.
But that's going to wrap up the video. Like I said, just a quick little cap of what's going on in this update. And I really want to see more maps. Hopefully Valve introduces some more maps into Man vs. Machine.
But I will take this update because it's awesome being able to get back into Man vs. Machine, get some new challenges, some new loot opportunities.
And that is going to wrap up the video. So I'll see you guys all soon. Go have fun with the new update. And of course, take care, everybody.