Hey, what is going on, everybody? Jerma here with a Team Fortress 2 Grain Play Cromontary.
And tonight, I'm gonna be playing as the Devil Man with the Lock and Load, the Shield of Righteousness, and the Islander.
I don't know why the Islander's on. I mean, I think I killed maybe one person with it.
It doesn't go through my brain at the given time that maybe I should probably take this thing off and put on a sword that's not gonna gimp me for the rest of this game.
But I didn't. It stays on, whatever we're gonna move on.
And the first thing we're gonna talk about is my new computer. It's sitting up here on the shelf.
It looks beautiful. It looks pretty. I wanna kiss it right in the face.
Now, I'm gonna show you some pictures because I promised that I would show you what it looked like.
You know, people wondering what the case looked like, how does it look, what lights are inside of it.
There's one thing that I kinda don't like about it, and it's very, very minor. It's a very stupid thing to not like.
But the light on the graphics card, if you can see there, it says GeForce GTX in like a bright lime green.
That's cool. I think it's interesting, but sometimes it kinda catches my eye because I'm looking straight at it.
I'll show you a couple pictures here. You can see how it's just GeForce GTX like right in my face almost at all times.
And there's probably some way to turn that off in the bios. I just don't know how to do that.
But I love this thing. It's great. It's amazing. It allows me to do 1080p videos, 100% reliable now.
There will never be a 720 video on this channel. It's always gonna be 1080p from now until the hour of our death. Amen.
But yes, if it looks better, please let me know. If it looks worse, then that would be pretty odd,
considering that this is like one of the only times I've ever been able to reliably record 1080p.
And I don't know, you'd probably have to stuff a thermometer up my ass and I'd probably have a fever at that point because I'd be very steaming mad.
Anyways, why did I just say that? That was a very weird thing to say.
So what I want to talk about in this video is not so much the computer. We already kind of went over that.
But I want to talk about this gameplay and getting mad at video games, getting angry at games.
A lot of you guys know that I happen to do that from time to time. I swear. You know, don't say swears.
Look, I said it. There, I said it. I said it. I actually said it for the second time in my life.
And we're going to talk about swears. We're going to talk about swearing.
We're going to talk about energy coming out of your body when you're playing games.
And this gameplay right here is one of those times when I was a little upset.
I might have been a little angry. I might have been, you mad? Yeah, I was.
And here's why. What you haven't seen in this gameplay so far is us getting steamrolled.
We were getting destroyed for like 10 straight minutes.
Like there was two rounds before this or three rounds before this where we were losing substantially
and not even to the point where, oh, there's like two people on your team that are okay
and there's like three people on the other team that are doing great.
No, we were just getting crushed. Like, you know, you've had those games, we've all had them,
where the cart starts at the starting point and in like two blinks of an eye,
you look over and the cart has passed like the second goddamn point.
It was one of those games and it happened a couple of times in a row.
And it's very frustrating.
And I don't think getting mad at games is particularly a bad thing or getting frustrated at games.
But when you get mad at other people, that's when things start to get a little out of hand.
And let's say you're like, oh, this medic on my team sucks. Fucking kill him.
Like, no, that's not how I get really mad at games.
When I get mad at games, I get mad at like the stuff in the games
rather than the people playing them.
Except if your name is Star, then like fuck you because like you do it on purpose.
But what I'm getting at here, the real purpose of this video is when you get flustered
or when you get mad at a certain game, it doesn't have to just be Team Fortress 2.
It could be anything. It could be a MOBA. It could be an FPS. It could be an RTS.
It really doesn't matter what it is. You lose your edge.
I mean, there are probably some people that when they get mad, they play better,
but I'm not one of those people.
When I get pissed off at something, when I get really annoyed at something,
my skill level goes down like 60% because I'm just sitting there like fucking good.
Oh, you think your stupid game sucks?
And you can't even focus on what you're trying to do.
And if you just took a second, one second or two seconds to just sit back in your chair for a second,
let it run its course, and then go back into what you were doing, you'll be much better off.
This gameplay you're watching right now is that exact case.
I was playing like shit. We were getting destroyed.
I was playing like shit pretty much all day as well, trying to record some stuff,
trying to get some cool footage, and then this happened after I just calmed down.
So the moral of the story is this.
It's okay to get frustrated. It's okay to get mad at games.
Because the more you get frustrated, the more you will actually learn
because that means you didn't do something correctly
or you learn about a new game mechanic or a player was just better than you
and you can learn off of what they did.
So it's okay to get frustrated. Just try not to go totally overboard
because once you fall off the boat and there's like a storm like lightning striking and stuff
and it's like the boat is going up and down on the waves,
once you go overboard, that life vest ain't going to help you.
You think somebody's going to throw it to you and it's going to land in front of you.
You're going to be swimming to it like you're going to go under.
That's what's going to happen. So don't go overboard. Just stay on the goddamn boat.
Yell at the captain. If the captain's like going over these waves like shit,
he'd be like, hey, captain, fuck you. You suck at boating.
All right. Well, you don't have to. That would be kind of mean.
But just don't go overboard because once you're there, it's hard to come back.
And with that, I'm going to wrap up this video, guys.
Thank you all so much for watching. I really do appreciate it.
And I'll see you guys all next time. And of course,