Is it? It is.
My dad had over 100 hours in that game, he'll crush you.
I'm sure it's fun.
The online play probably takes it up a whole another letter grade or two.
I would say. At least.
Black screen, it is.
Yes, it is.
Okay, you guys ready?
All right, what do we got here? Let's see.
I did a couple of these already, as you see.
This one's five by five, let's just go for it.
It'll be simple.
It's just gonna be simple.
Use the hint roulette.
No.
Okay, so how does this work?
Well, with the controller.
How do I like move?
How do you move?
Uh, is this the stick?
Okay, left stick is select because this is...
Okay, that's up?
Maybe.
Right?
No?
Touch the screen.
It is a screen touch game, but I have a controller, so I wonder how this works.
Push in the stick?
This is a touch only game.
I have to touch the TV.
The d-pad does the same thing.
Hold on.
Oh, here we go.
Yes.
Uh...
How do I do this?
Hint roulette.
Navigation.
Auto-correct mistakes.
Also controls.
Input mode.
Touch.
Buttons.
There we go.
I think that's good.
All right, we're good.
There we are.
All right, very cool, very cool.
Okay, so here we go.
Those who don't know how to play Picross.
Watch and learn.
It's about marking stuff down.
I actually can't even describe it.
My brain's like really slow today.
All right, let me explain it.
Because these people have no fucking idea what's going on.
I know this is like a channel meme, but there's 13,000 people here.
Half of them probably never heard of this.
Maybe even less.
Okay, so.
In each one of these, see the number three on the left?
That means that there are three squares filled in somewhere here.
Right?
See this one one?
That means there are two ones filled in here.
And it's not, oh, that means they can't be together.
There has to be at least one space in the middle of those two ones.
Has to be.
At least one.
But that could not be two in a row.
It'd have to be like here and here, for instance.
So let's give it a go.
As you see, one space, three.
Therefore, there's only five spaces.
One space, three.
They have to be here.
You understanding?
Are you getting it?
Okay, so I want to mark this as an X.
Because I don't want to mess with that.
Because I don't want them to see that.
Again, there's only three spaces.
So one, two, three.
One, two, three.
It has to literally be, it can't, it has to be here.
This can't be here.
I don't know that yet.
But this is, I know that.
Mark that one.
Very, very interesting.
By the way, you can do this as well.
Because there's obviously not a one there.
There's obviously not a one there.
There's obviously not a one here as well.
So, class, where can this one be?
It's only in a couple of places, as you've been able to tell, as you can see.
Very, very interesting.
What am I doing?
So here's the thing.
Anytime I play these games on stream, I just, I can't, I just can't do them.
It's something about like this, I see colors, but I don't see what to do.
Does anybody else get like that?
I could lie in bed and do like a 20 by 21 of these.
And just sit there and be relaxed.
But like, I know I'm on camera.
Like, I know I'm on stream.
And I know I have to talk to you.
Like, I can't do it.
Like, the part of my brain that does puzzles is the part of my game,
part of my brain that communicates with humans.
So like, I can't do them both at the same time.
Let's see if it happens if I just stop talking and turn the volume all the way down.
This part of your brain communicates with the mothership.
All right, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go.
You ready?
I don't want the hint roulette.
It's 10 by 10.
Here we do it.
Let's move.
Here we go.
This is a full row of 10.
Just get those, get the ones you know you can do.
This is a nine.
What that means is it has to be filled in all the way except for the two ends.
Get it?
Throw this one all the way in.
Very cool.
One, two, three, space, one.
We don't know that yet.
We know it's these two because one, two, three, one, two, three.
There's your one.
There's your two.
There's your second two.
We don't know where it is though.
We play with heat maps.
No.
There's your two.
There's your eight.
There's your one.
There's your other one.
There's your full row.
OK.
There's your two.
There's your one and there's your other one.
This row is done too.
Where's your other?
I don't know yet.
Not sure.
But actually, I do know because it has to be over here.
There's your two.
Here's your row.
Alright this is your nine.
Your nine is complete.
There's your two.
We don't know where the one is at this moment.
There's your three.
Alright.
Where's your three?
There's your three.
There's your two.
There's your other two.
Okay, there's your 3, there's your 2, there's your 1, and there's your 1, there's your 1,
and there's your 2, there's your 1, there's your 8, and there's your other 1.
Hope you were taking notes.
The game still says Mario Golf.
Oh.
You're gonna lose 90% of your viewers.
I'm gonna be fine.
This game is really chill.
It is actually really chill.
The best part?
Oh, this is the best part.
If you get...
So, remember, we're filling the whole thing because it's 10.
I love this.
This feels the best.
Because you get...
See?
Okay, look at the people that are confused.
So, because I know that this whole bottom row is filled, so the whole is 10 by 10, it
has to be every single one.
These are part of these columns, right?
So I know, see 1, 6, 1 over here?
This is the 1.
So, there is no other place for that to be, so you get to mark that.
Take a look at that.
See the 2 at the bottom?
This has to be that 2.
There's nothing else it could be.
Then you can mark it.
Again, 2.
Mark it again.
See, it has to be that 2 in the column.
Because it's already here.
2 again.
Mark that.
Because there has to be a space in between.
Make sure you mark it.
This is a 1.
Nothing else is coming after that because there has to be a space.
Make sure you mark it.
I tried to mark it, and I got it wrong, apparently.
I hit the wrong button.
Okay.
2.
Again.
1.
Mark it.
2.
See?
Now, look what we've deduced as a classroom.
This is 4 1s.
1, 2, 3, 4.
Nowhere else they can go, ladies and gentlemen.
Please you mark them if you could on your worksheet.
Opened up some more interesting stuff, as you can see.
Now we have another row to work with, as it seems.
So again, this is 1.
1!
Mark that on your paper, please.
There's now only 1 more 1 somewhere here.
I don't know that yet.
What's this look like?
There's another 1.
Mark that on your sheet, please.
This is a 6.
See?
1.
6 is next in line.
It has to be 1, 2, 3, 4, 5, 6.
And there's your 1.
1, 6, 1.
Done.
2, 1, 2.
There's another 1, 6, 1 over here.
And I think it's the same thing.
Which it is.
You get it?
Hey, past the snow.
Mr. Smith!
Oh!
You're handing out notes in class, are you?
Very interesting.
Give me that.
Give me that!
What's it say?
Mr. Albertson is a dickhead.
You know?
Okay.
Yeah.
You know what?
You know what, Mr. Smith?
That shows gumption.
You just got yourself a promotion.
Good luck in the 7th grade.
You're going up a whole grade.
I'm gonna call the office.
Head down.
They'll get you your new textbooks and your new classes and everything.
That shows management skills.
That shows drive.
You're going up a whole.
You're going up a grade.
All right.
Stop distracting me.
What am I doing?
Okay.
2.
This is...
Oh!
Class!
Give me one second here.
I would like for you to understand.
We've got a 5 and a 1.
Where's the 5 go?
Where do you think that goes?
It goes right there.
Would you look at that?
So you get it.
That's 2.
Okay.
This is done.
The reason why you put the X's there is because it's really easy to fuck up and forget where
a space needs to be.
Very cool.
This one is just 5.
Fill it in.
This one's done too.
4, 5, 6, 7, 8, 9.
This is cool.
So add those up.
2 plus the space 3.
4, 5, 6, 7 plus the space 8.
9, 10.
Get it?
No.
I didn't want to press that.
I wanted to press the...
I gotta remember what that is.
B is the...
I'm gonna screw that up all the time.
Okay, so this is done.
One has to be there.
This is also...
This would be done right now.
This is probably...
This is 3 right here.
It's a gum on the bottom of the desk.
That shit's disgusting.
Looking underneath the desk in a classroom was always just...
That's fucking gross.
Just wads of gum stuck there.
I would never want to put my hand underneath the desk and like push up and touch somebody
else's gum potentially.
That's...
That's awful.
Keep going.
Ooh, this is gonna be a chunky one.
Look at this.
That's a chunky one.
I always love when you get two rows.
When you get a full row removed.
That feels good too.
How do we make Picross the new stream meta?
That's an interesting thought.
You're playing easy levels.
I'm just getting...
I haven't played this in a long time.
Picross Tournament.
2, 3, 4, 5, 6, 7, 8, 9.
1, 2, 3, 4, 5, 6, 7, 8, 9.
1, 2, 3, 4, 5, 6, 7, 8.
1, 2, 3, 4, 5, 6, 7.
2, 3, 4, 5, 6, 7, 8.
1, 2, 3, 4, 5, 6, 7, 8.
6. 1, 2, 3, 4, 5, 6.
2 this way or 2 this way? Do I know that? Yeah.
Okay. Okay. Very good. Very good.
Aha! Ha ha! Spider or pumpkin?
This one is going to be tricky I think. 6, 7, 8.
So if there's six it has to be these middle ones and be filled in because obviously you
go one two three four five six one two three four five six and there's no mathematical
way that it those cannot be filled in.
One two three four five six seven eight nine oh it's either here and then forward or starting
here and then forward.
I just don't know.
Don't you wish you were playing Elden Ring?
I mean I don't need to wish for much longer I'm gonna be playing it soon.
Or this one's gonna be tricky because look it can be this one one one two three one right
oh I I didn't mean to do that but I was getting it right okay just like I said you got that
wrong this is the correct place for it to be although I know it now three two all right
that helps.
It's playing a wordle a wordle this is I would assume this is the two it has to be yeah.
Oh that's a big deal one two three four it helps and we know this can't be part of the
three because three doesn't fit there that helps too so can't do any more with that.
No this was this was cool before wordle I'm a hipster I like things that people don't
like that people don't know about what does that do that's this is I guess apparently
the one this was never cool this was act this was huge this is like one of the most popular
things this has been a huge deal for like 20 years you don't know what you're talking
about well this is the two and then nothing this is all nothing over here I need to be
able to fill in some of this okay oh I can fill that in nice call it you have to call
it I can't call it for you I did that's like every like two months I just start doing that
don't get me started oh I believe I can do it's technically the one one two three four
five now they can go all the way this is the two oh it can't be here this is also the two
but I don't know he's got some strats well they can't be here right that's one and then
three is after that so it can't fit here so that helps us with the six a little bit two
is the other two finished that row very nice please say something quirky I don't think quirky
to say right now how do I have to pee again already one one two could be anywhere one two
one they could be anywhere one could be anywhere one is either here here I don't know this no
this no okay actually yes is this it can't be anything here got it doesn't help with this
though I imagine this is one of these three ones but I don't know you need to go piss I'll be all
right well I can do this all right this entire the whole bottom is done and then I don't have
to look down here anymore I'm looking for one one two three one one two three it has to be
it has to be one here though ah look at that very very good this is the three that was the
one this has to be the three this is one this is a two what even is this image what the hell
are we looking at here to be there can't be here I'd love when you just get on a roll I'd love it
there's three oh there's two oh there's your two there's your three there's your there's your two
and there's your one what is this sword a missile oh okay from far away I can see it looks like a
sword a fire sword all right one more than I'm gonna go I'm gonna go pee go back and do this one
seven so you can do this because remember seven eight nine ten right you get it
shit that didn't help that didn't help well actually yeah it did please give an answer
on brain age what do you want me to say am I gonna play brain age no I think so yes please
do it do you really want it I figured that would be a game you guys would not want to watch okay
these are all just ones one this is gonna be a really small one okay seven one two three four
five six seven one two three seven has to be here that has to be there there's your five
narrowing it down ever so gently ever so slightly just narrow it down
on gently narrow it down you don't have to be excited don't it be crazy
be gentle be calm looks like I can go here oh do a poll all right throw a poll in there for if
people want to see brain age by the way if this doesn't have at least 65 plus percent I'm not
doing it like this has got to be like near 70% yes all right I'm not gonna do it shit what do
I need to do here four one two three four what can I do from here I think I can do this one
because that the four has to be in the middle here and here too yeah okay I can't do any more
than that this is part of the four one three four or one two three four
okay all right so poll do you want brain age yes or no yes no it's per vote all right it's
only gonna be I'm gonna look just for two minutes see what you think you don't really want brain
age do you I just go get it should I just go buy brain age right now and just play it right now
80% of you want to see brain age yes yes yes okay all right all right hold let me finish this
puzzle no I'm gonna do pick Ross for like another 15 to 20 minutes I'm gonna go okay first here's
important I'm gonna finish this puzzle I'm gonna go pee again I'm gonna come back and I'm going
to play another one or two puzzles and then we're gonna play brain age okay that is unanimous 80%
of you said yes let me finish this one though this one's tricky I mean it has to be even if
it's one yeah one two three four five it has to literally be like this there's no way it can't
like it has to be that still doesn't really help me that much one two three four one two three four
I can do that oh okay oh
I said it has to be this way too one two three four five six seven yes I do
it's good can't be this way two four trust me I love Elden Ring but I want brain age
I mean I'm gonna play Elden Ring tonight I told you this is no mega spring
question is one space okay so here we go it has to be this to be that way or uh-huh uh-huh oh
uh-huh it's a geeked out impression all right here we go BRB I'm gonna get brain age and I'm
gonna install it I'm gonna go pee we're gonna come back play a couple more pick Ross puzzles
because I'm into it and then we'll do brain age and then after a little while brain age I'm gonna
take a break I'm gonna take like a 20 plus minute break I'm gonna eat something I'm gonna get some
food I'm gonna relax for a little bit and I'm gonna come back without turning the stream off
and we're gonna do Elden Ring for the rest of the night I'll be right back with brain age no
with I mean I'm gonna get it but you know what I mean I'll be right back