So this is Coaster Crazy. This is a game that was made by Frontier. If you don't know who Frontier is, they're the guys that are responsible for the Rollercoaster Tycoon franchise.
And this is their, like, new game. And I have to make this coaster sick. And I'm gonna try to do that as best as I possibly can.
I really, really hope nobody pukes. Let's do a different camera angle. How about this one?
Yay! Woohoo! This is so much fun!
Ooh, I love candy! Yay!
Oh my god! He just, like, threw up in his mouth! He's doing it again!
This coaster sucks! How's that? I kind of want to make something like this. There we go.
That's a little more ridiculous. I want my fear rating on this coaster to be through the roof, because you'll see that there's gonna be meters down here.
I'll show you in a second. So you see the E, F, and the N? You gotta keep those in the green, or else the coaster sucks, alright?
That's, like, the rule of thumb. If the coaster's not in the green, then it's a piece of crap. That's all I really know.
Oh my god!
Somebody-
No, are you okay? I'm sorry!
Here we go. We got some excitement here. We got some excitement here. Lost somebody.
What? We went through? Look at this guy!
What? What just happened?
Wait a second! Why is this intertwining like that? I didn't do that! I didn't want that to happen!
Oh, damn! I gotta move that!
How many people have to die?
Here we go!
I hope this is exciting!
His, like, girlfriend just got launched off, and he doesn't even care.
Alright, I have added so much dumb shit to this track.
Look at this. This is almost a 90 degree- I'm gonna kill someone. Someone's gonna die from this drop.
This is just- You don't wanna ride this ride.
If you're at Six Flags or whatever and you see this, you turn to your buddy and you go,
Look, we aren't fucking going on that thing. I don't care how much of a daredevil you wanna be.
It ain't happening.
I think, I'm pretty sure every single person throws up on this ride.
From what I've done, every single person is gonna throw up.
And that was the goal, I'm not gonna lie, that was the goal from the very beginning.
Was to make everybody throw up and, like, kill everybody.
So let's just see how many-
Who has that much stomach acid?
Did that guy just get back on the- Did you see that?
That guy flew off and went right back into the cab.
That guy- I'm so confused right now, I hope I got that.
Some guy flew out and got put back in the seat.
I wanna zoom in, I wanna close up on that and do a slo-mo. I really think that just happened.
That was unbelievable.
Just having this view and all the horrified reactions to things.
See, he landed again and he got puked on.
He landed again.
This king, this guy in the front is seriously a trooper.
He's the only one that ever succeeds to-
No, the king.
The king is dead.
I don't even know what's gonna happen. It's gonna be a horrible crash.
And you know what? It's okay.
Because this game- Look at that bump right there.
Alright, here we go. I have no idea what's about to happen.
All I know is that I wanna keep it at that.
Coaster Crazy, guys.
Coaster Crazy on the iOS app store.
Go get it.
If you like games like this, go get this goddamn game.
What you just saw is reason enough to fucking pick up this game. It really is.
Let's-
Instantly.
Hmm, something ain't right here.
Something isn't supposed to be there. I wonder what it is.