Hello, I'm very early. Yeah, I'm very extraordinarily early by like an hour. Hi everybody. What the fuck dude?
I was making food and now you're live and I can't even make my food anymore. No, you can't we're gonna hang out
We're just gonna chill for like a few minutes. You've got time to microwave the hot pocket. What do they take two minutes?
You're not making like spaghetti and meatballs or something. Are you? I mean that takes a long time. That takes like an hour or two
I can't even read this
It's it's too fast
This is the it's too fast. I can't read it. It's too fast
uh
Jerma, hi. Hey, how are you?
Jerma sucks. Hey
Hey
Happy new year. Yeah, happy. Well, not yet. Not yet
I figured I would start a little early just because I was thinking about it
and
If I started at 6 30
Because I want to hit eastern time right like the new york city. That's when the ball drops the big ball in new york city
right
I want to hit eastern time
so
That's only like two out what six thirty seven or eight nine thirty ten thirty eleven thirty. That's only two and a half hours
This we got 19 categories to go through and an entire rumble card
So this might be a little longer than I initially anticipated. So let's start early
Get going
I can't even count these subscribers. Oh my god
five
I can count them
This all right. I don't the number just jumped up
Anyways, let's just hang out for a little bit. I've got all the categories got everything ready to go
And I hey
Uh, how we doing?
Got the suit on
Oh, oops
Happy new year
He's got a 20 year old suit on
Shit
Uh anyways, hi. Happy new year guys. I can't be trusted with the camera
Don't you cannot trust me with the camera on anyways, uh, we got a lot to do
Happy I mean, can you see it?
Happy new year. It has lights on it, but they don't work. So
I the battery's like died or something. I don't know you press a button in there and the lights up the leds
But I whatever, uh, he's transforming no and the shelf is right there, too
That was like in part and I got like a fucking suit on
anyways
Uh, we've got the rumble to do
They're almost understand. Listen, there's there almost 40 characters in this rumble 40 a lot before we even get started
I gotta thank a few people. I gotta thank crowsky nail leather jacket
Vr josh cad btt me grump clump and all the other mods without their help
This stream does not happen like without their help at all. It just this physically would not happen
So they worked on characters they helped with like the pull and shit like is this doesn't happen unless they helped so
Please give them a round of fucking applause. The stream isn't loading ban them all
You look sexy as fuck. Ow, I just like popped my shoulder that like fucking hurt
I'm falling apart. Whatever. Uh, so we can get started. I mean, actually, no, let's just wait. Let's just wait
Can you pog that good enough?
It comes a four month break fedora. Uh, we have i'll tell you with the first category coming up. I'll show you
Gonna be this one s new character. That's the first we're not doing it yet. Hold on. I'm gonna milk this
Uh
Not really flashy this year
These are just on security envelopes written in crayon and I spelt them and I spelt it wrong after a great start
All right. Listen to me. I i'm drinking a cbd drink. All right, it's cbd thc
Mean alcohol. I don't want any alcohol. I spelled character wrong, but I you know, I knew it
I didn't even care because I didn't want to make a new envelope
So I was just like what if I don't want to cross that out? I don't care. It doesn't matter
Uh, people give it a shitload of subs what we got here. Oh and also
Super daza making fucking all these videos
It's a shitload of videos like 19 videos. So
Unbelievable work. We had 10 community subs from lexie's five from cast tax five from hole of one zombie 50 dollars
50 dollars from
Am I i'm a 10k andy now? Yeah, whatever. No, I want to do the thing
uh
50 hair I put a little gel in it today and that's a lie. I didn't
Uh, there's so many community subs coming and I don't know what to do
Thank you for the insane amount of support completely unnecessary
Don't have to do this. You guys give me fucking trillions of dollars
That asterisk there's an asterisk on that because it's not actually trillions
But you know, it's as an asterisk. It's actually like it's not that much but it is a lot
It's not over a trillion though
If it was I would I would buy a fucking island and make videos on it. You're the richest streamer on twitch
That's not true. Well gonna need to pay off that debt somehow. I don't like this. I don't like where this is
I'm moving it. I don't like where that is. It's gonna keep hitting my cbd drink. I don't like this
It's gonna keep bumping into my drink. Whatever i'm gonna have to i'll put the drink over here. Yeah, that makes sense
Let's fill it up drinking bong water. All right, so you want to how this is gonna work?
This is how this is gonna work
We're gonna do four categories
And then we're gonna do a match in the rumble after a match
We're gonna do four categories match four categories match four categories match and we'll be done. Are you ready?
Are we I have we all joined is everybody here and accounted for everybody pogging i'm getting lots of pogs
Thank you for the insane community subs guys. I don't even know where to start. Thank you. You ready?
Well, if we're ready, I gotta put my headphones in let's go. Oh, let's go
Let's go. They said you didn't you can't even hear that. Let's go. They said and the winner
A best new character. I didn't even show the nominees yet. Relax. What if I just started reading out all the answers, uh,
You ready? Welcome to the stream. Happy new year everybody. Let's uh, take a look at the nominees for best new character
There was a couple of good ones this year. See you in a minute
The cow's name by the way is murius if you were not part of the pre-stream chat
And unfortunately
The voice actor from frog detective one was did not move on to frog detective two
He was in the middle of other projects. All right, you want you want me to mute his sections and I hold on
I know that voice actor. Do you want me to call him?
Hello. Hey, what's up? It's me
Oh, hey, what's going on? How are you doing? I'm doing good. Did you get my messages that I sent you? Yes, I did
Green more like it. That's me
I'm invincible
I am untouchable
No one can fuck with mr. Green. Oh, jesus christ
Oh
Dave yes, mr. Green. Give me that t-shirt. Oh my god
Yeah, and when when you guys come back remember, it's me the fat fuck irl
Come back next week and i'll shake my stomach around for you more after drinking three gatorades. Hello everybody
Welcome back
Two juggles are great same character 140 stream of his career. This is going to be a good one. Hope you're all ready
Same guy just one of them's drunker
Oh you want to do it do it. All right, you got it i'll take some right now holy shit
Holy shit
I think the work at my local walmart is actually jesus reborn
And here are 200 reasons why
Hey, whoa, man, you gotta settle down on dmt
Like i'm asking because like a friend of mine asked me one day like yesterday. He said hey, dude
What's the button combination if you have?
Uh, like a computer and you have a program on your computer that emulates video games
It's like hey, what's that button combination to save a state and I was like, I don't fucking know
Leave me alone dave's piss dave's like a wicked powerful senator
I get this wrong
Like introduce a bill to remove my fucking stream. Hey, uh, jeremy. I got really
My my my aspect ratio in swordfish one two
It's going crazy fix it
Okay, I think uh four four by three. I think that will help if you do if you open up that program
All right, i'll try they're all just like fuck
I spy with my little eye
Orange
You got it that's my son he got it it's the sky and everything else you got it all right
Try to keep my eye on the road son yellow power raid
What's up son we got a problem here son up son
So
uh the best new character of the year if you couldn't differentiate between the
Four of them that were on the list
is
ladies and gentlemen, hey
the winner is
With over 50.9 percent of the vote
Mr. Green
Mr. Green at number one with 50 almost 51 percent of the vote
Long drive dad was number two at 16.6 percent of the vote and I got too lazy to write the third one on this one
It was the first one
Sorry about that. He he destroyed it, but they're all the same fucking characters. They're all the same character
And you know hearing it and seeing it and while i'm sitting here. Yeah, you ready? Here you go
Hey, how you doing everybody? It's that's me every character the german does that's a little bit weird
It might be a little fat
You know if you if you if you if you gain some weight and you talk like this and you have like a beard
Ah, then all of a sudden all of you you're like a bad guy
Yeah, I I gotta tell you something about that goku
Gotcha, but but fuck that they're all the same. That's they're all the same. Anyways, we already went over this
That was fucking funny. Anyways, like congratulations to mr
Green this is way louder than I thought it was going to be on the microphone. I'm sorry
All right coming up next this is gonna I this is my favorite category of the night
Can I just tell you this is my favorite category coming up next we have best cat puke
You don't know what the cat puke is
A year or two ago. I think it was last year
Uh, I I did a noise and I I kind of do a noise sometimes where I'd like pretend to throw up in my mouth
And swallow it really quickly. I've done it like probably 30 times in the last two years
And um, I don't know. I don't know why I do it. I just think it's funny. So here's a compilation. This is this is uh,
Is the best one of this year apparently and I didn't even realize how many nominees were on this list
I do this too much. I I don't care. I'm gonna continue to do it. So that's that's just the way it is
Ladies and gentlemen, here come the nominees for best cat puke of the year
This is a water tank. What?
That's my special it's my
cotton arm
And cat puke pizza. You have to make the noise now. No, I can't I can't
Finally a free drink
Come on I can do it. Come on
This one was just one over the road
I I don't I I don't know why this that was my favorite category. Ladies and gentlemen, the winner of best cat puke for 2020
Oh, it's I don't even know which one this was I forgot already
it is
One more for the road from bug snacks at 20.09 percent of the vote
Underneath that is the water tank
with the 15.5 percent
And then underneath that one is trying to stop the water
At 14.4.6 percent now you might be asking yourself. Why is that category on the list? Hey
There ain't no worse peter this year. I can say peter as much as I want now
I can say peter every I could say it as much as I want. It's not even it's not on the list
It wasn't a category replaced it with something even worse
All right, this next one is uh, this next one is going to be very very fun for you not for me
Let's take a look at it. Now. What do you think? See i'm a human. I'm a normal guy
This is what my hair looks like sometimes
Uh, it doesn't look very good
Sometimes it looks awful. Sometimes it looks so bad that I didn't i'm embarrassed
And a lot of people keep track of these and every year we try to find the worst case
Of bad hair that i've had for the entire year and there I think this year out of all the years
I think this is the worst year ever for this category. I think there was so many good ones
That this was tough. This was a tough one. Here are the nominees
worst hair of the year
Career is over. My my looks are over. It's over. It's over
It's over. I can't get a fucking haircut right now guys. Didn't you understand?
I didn't get a haircut in fucking february
and
You look like hillary hillary clinton hair
hillary clinton hair
Airline check
That's all right
Why is that even nominated every single fucking stream?
This just sand outside and I just i'm like, all right. I'm done with the broadcast today
It's been swell. Okay. Good night everybody
And then 12 hours go by
Ah
This overexposed camera too. Hey who who ordered the pizza?
Who ordered the bird's nest?
Okay, so
Uh, those are the nominees
I don't I don't think I really even have to uh
We don't even need a drum roll
Um, I don't do I really need to tell you guys what the worst one was. Do you really not know?
Should we even put it? I mean I guess uh for sure
But it's the it's the worst hair i've ever had in my life not just
This year is the worst hair ever in my entire childhood all through my adult life is the worst hair i've ever had
Uh with forty four point six percent of the vote the winner
My career is over
when I took
the uh headband down
My career is over
with forty four point six percent of the vote in second place was the mop comb over
Which was the one that was all that one was gross
Uh, that was nineteen point one four percent of the vote and then in third place was hillary clinton at thirteen point nine percent of the vote
There you go
Hillary got robbed
No, it didn't no it didn't. Oh, that's why i'm sorry. I am sorry, but 45 look at this
Wait, what? Hey, that's so fucking bad guys
Like hillary clinton was my career is over my my looks are over my career was over
My career was over right there, but I built it back
uh
Yeah, that was that there's no question that you look 60. I looked 600
Like I was mummified and they found me buried in like a tomb somewhere. What's this next one?
Oh, all right. So we're gonna stay on this cat. We're gonna all right. We we've we've got four
This is fourth, right? Uh staying in the same realm of worst hair
We have worst face and I held this up last year in a way like this
And people have tried to nominate that but i'm sorry that was not even a bad face
So we're gonna do this is we need real worst faces
And what is the worst face if you don't if you're new to the channel or something?
Uh, well sometimes when I go like this like if i'm scared at a video game or if there's something bad happens
There's something scary or something weird or i'm losing my mind and I go like this like like you know
I mean or I like freak out and like my I cringe up and stuff
Or it's just like somebody decides that I was ugly today and they take a screenshot of me
You're in the nominees for worst face of the year. See you in a sec
Oh, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no too big
Too big and too bright too big and too bright too big and too bright
That's the worst face 2020. Oh, yeah
You sure?
How about now? It's pretty bad
No, it's just weird. It's just gonna get like fucking weird
if i'm like
Not even that bad
That's what a toddler does when they know they did something wrong
That should be an emote stanley kubrick kubrick stare
It's fucking dark in here
So we were just sitting there and you're just spinning the thing around like all right. We win. We did it
What? I mean, I don't know
Go go go
God
That's what I can't explode
Holy shit
Uh, so the winner of the worst face of the year category
This was uh, it wasn't that close. It was it really wasn't that close the winner
What do you think?
What do you think with 28.8 percent of the vote? Who's the easy bake oven pizza face?
Coming in next at 14.7 percent was the kubrick stare
And then the wide grin was for 10.2 percent of the vote goblin got snubbed
Pretty hard. Yeah, I mean that's I mean the easy bake oven
Pizza tea thing that would mean it was it was revolting. It was disgusting. That was what lost by the most
Um, I don't think that's fair to that nominee
I don't think that's fair to that nominee
And hey time is it we got a rumble
We've got multiple matches. Hopefully, uh, 2k20 does not uh fuck up on us
I would be very disappointed if it does but i'm ready to start the first match of the rumble
We have five matches including the rumble. We're going to be starting with this one first
Uh, just give me one second while I get it going and we'll get it on the first match of the rumble
Is coming in. Hold on. I don't want to I don't want to spoil it. I don't want to spoil it
I don't want to spoil it
Oh, i'm okay
You thought just the new year's eve awards was the only thing we were doing here
Of course, we're going to do the germa rumble live
In beautiful las vegas nevada also where i've been standing tried to make an official germa arena
Uh, but the game crashed every time I tried to change
The rope whoa don't want to spoil anything
Uh, the game crashed every time I changed the color of the ropes. I couldn't do my own arena
2k20 is horrible. All right, you ready for the first match?
This one's I I think a lot of you guys are gonna have a lot riding on this one
You guys are gonna have a lot riding on this one. This is a
Tornado tag match and this is it's gonna get heated in the chat here 2v2 while it loads
We're going to have turn on predictions. Oh shit. I'm not ready for that
I'm not ready for that. I'm not ready for that. I'm not ready for it. I'm not ready for it
I'm not ready for it. Is there any mods that can help me? I'm not ready for it
I don't know what to do. I'm not ready for it. Are there any mods that can help me?
I'm not ready for I don't know what to do. I don't know what to do. Um, oh fuck. Well, you de-modded me
I'm sorry. No, I need to be
Hold on
Shit, hold on. Hold on. Hold on. Is that something that we can easily do? Can we easily do that? Uh, what?
Yes, yes, yes, can we mod mod mod mod everyone
Uh, how come this is not loading? Tell us the characters in discord. Tell us the character. Oh shit. Oh my god
Oh my god. Oh my god. Good. Good. Good. Good. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah, I need my discord
Hold on. Hold on. Hold on. Hold on
Hold on there you go. All right, they have the first match. How come I can't why is this not loading?
Wait, I didn't just like play the game. Did I?
I hope i'm not playing the game
The first match of the evening is going to be a tag team match. Hey, i'm talking
I'm talking
They're all from new york
I'm gonna have to turn
The it's gonna be kiryu and majima in a tag match
versus
Two other characters and by the way, this is a stipulation on this one
stipulation on this one
Whoever wins this match gets another stream
Really important to mention
as majima comes in
This tag partner will be coming in too
Kiryu as you know from yakuza who's a zero to be exact
Gotta shut this guy up
Also from new york
Yeah, why does it say you suck
I think by the way, I gave him andre the giant's entrance
I think that's why he's walking so slow
They're all from the bronx. They're all from brooklyn
I don't think we can even do the betting right now. I like didn't set it up. It's all right
Do it later do it uh, do it on uh betting
But uh, but who are they fighting against though? That's important
Who are they gonna fight against who would deserve another stream? What do you guys think?
There are two characters. I know that people are really really would love to see come back
It's not bugsnax
Not godhand
Not la noir
Two beloved characters
You see one of them right now
The lights have just turned off
Introducing for the second team of the who gets another stream match. It's salmon maps
I know a lot of you guys got stuff riding on this
So who's gonna win this is tornado tag, by the way, they're in the they're in there at the same time
Oh, wait, we got a wait. We got a prediction
Win channel points. Oh shit. We got it
magima and kira versus sam and max
both desperately want to see their
respective franchises continue
Let your channel points if you want to
Who do you think is going to win this match? Oh what an entrance there?
Flipping over the top rope
Just flying in
Taking his time with his bird feet
Has to be a dog
13 14
14.8
To 11. Okay
Here comes sam
I mean max who's the bunny?
I really hope i'm not controlling a character because like I don't I didn't set it up that way
All right, get your drinks going
Alcoholic or non-alcoholic and here comes max
They all just live in a high rise in new york
all of them it's like
60 apartments
It's the germa house, but i'm not in new york
I'm gonna laugh so hard if I have to control a character because i'm gonna be pissed because i'm gonna have to restart it
He didn't have a shirt on
Well, wait, he's a bunny so he doesn't have a shirt on
Okay, ladies and gentlemen, here comes the beginning of this match. We're gonna have sam and max versus kiryu
And how do I say that name?
I'm saying it's so wrong
He has it kiryu. Okay kiryu
Kiryu and majima versus sam and max again the winner of this competition gets another stream
Bonito tag matchup. They all have health on the bottom and here we go
All right off the bat sam with a flying leg kick
Right into majima's face. They're also huge
Look at the referee
Now there are rules here. There are rules
This is not a hardcore match
Snap suplex by majima onto sam right in his back and taunting is kiryu, which was a very very bad idea with his max
Kicks him completely out of the ring in one boot. Is he gonna suplex him out of the ring? I'm not sure
No, he's going to throw him on the on the top rope
and
Knee him directly in his skull
Majima taking a little bit of punishment here. Well, kiryu comes back in and max is
Absolutely destroying right now
I don't think max has taken one punch
Sam has though
Nice dodge by max with the reversal into the triple shin kick
He's going for the pin
It's no way. It's way too early for that
Wait, did he just hit his head?
Now you would think
That hurricanrana
That's a good reversal there from kiryu
Max now in a little bit of trouble on the outside of the ropes here. Well sam and majima is still outside
And I think sam has just thrown majima back and forth three or four times
Why is nobody here?
Why isn't nobody in the audience?
This event like
Max is carrying
I think I want to turn the I want to turn the hud off. I don't want to see the information
Looks like kiryu sent her for a powerbomb. Maybe no. He just let him go
He let him go
He keeps taunting
Now what I was gonna say earlier is you would think that sam and max would have the disadvantage here
Because they're not really fighters
They're more investigators detectives. Although sam does have a gun
Ice suplex there by sam out of majima
Kiryu working that skull cap of max majima looks like he's in a lot of trouble max isn't a lot of trouble too though
Setting it up here looks at onto the top rope. No, well, he's trying to think about what he wants to do with him
He's gonna throw about side of the ring
Nope just hit his face on that corner turnbuckle
Both of them want to see another scream so badly
Is sam going to submit here?
We might see a submit no reversal punching a couple of times in the face right in the nose and then getting on
Top of them doing a little twisty turn he can run up
A lot of reversals
If you take a look at the health bars down there you get to see max is in a lot of trouble big ddt
Doing a lot of taunting
We see from kiryu and majima
This does not look good for sam and max right now
Big neck breaker, although kiryu is bringing him over into the corner here. I'm not sure what his plan is
Max blew all of his energy in the first 30 seconds of the match
And he is almost toast
What?
Why did he fall down?
Are they gonna set up a double team move?
Majima win the first match of the evening
Oh my god
He just broke every bone in his body
What?
When did he give him the stunner?
Congratulations to kiryu and majima yakuza zero is going to get another stream
We will see another stream from kiryu and majima. Sorry sam and max max. I think is dead
Oh
Oh, man
Did I heard like a bunch of bones break?
He weighs so much
Kiryu is like a 200 plus pound man
And max is a bunny rabbit
He weighs like fucking four pounds
That was horrible
Okay
Well, uh, we can move on to the next match in a minute here
We're gonna do a couple more categories. That was the first match of the evening. I'm gonna turn this off
We're gonna keep this right here
And I just like I blew schnauz out of my nose when he landed on him
I I really did. I like blew my nose like hard
I don't want to don't wipe it on the I don't want to wipe it on the jacket. Hold on. What do I do?
38.7 million have been traded hands here. Congratulations. Those that have bet all right. Hold on a minute
I can't turn the camera until I I gotta oh, here we go. This is afghan writer
I brought this up for a very specific reason use it as hair grease
Oh my god, you're disgusting
All right, let's get back to it. Hi. Thank you to the mods, by the way that kind of jumped in there
And fix that up. Uh, are you guys ready? Oh, I have to do this real quick. Hold on
Uh, we're gonna do next category reddit shelf. That's right. I need to open the mixer
There we go. Okay. All right coming up the next category the next two in a row actually
Uh for the awards are uh singing so some of the best singing some of the worst singing
We're gonna start with the worst singing. What do you say? I lost all my money. You got villain hair tonight
Do I I don't think it's villain hair right now. It has to be like slipped back
dude
That fucking crunch. I'm gonna need a second. Uh
Protagonist hair whatever it's getting hot in this room, too
It's gonna get i'm gonna take this jacket off in like 10 minutes
All right
so we're singing here are the nominees for the worst singing sometimes I I decide to go into some song and
Sometimes it's good. Sometimes it's bad. The worst part about these categories is pay attention because it really doesn't matter
What which one is worse than which one is best?
It could be just flip them to any category you want there. It's all just kind of bad
So here are the nominees for worst singing of the year. This is worst singing keep that in mind
That wasn't funny that wasn't funny that wasn't funny that wasn't funny that wasn't funny that wasn't funny that wasn't
That wasn't funny. That wasn't funny
That's bad the speed of sound
The places to go gonna follow my rainbow
I don't know the lyrics
And the home
Oh
Thank you for the rate really appreciate it I am so happy
Thanks
There's uh hair on the fly in the water the fog
There's uh
There's uh, yeah, there's a hair on the fly in the there's a hair on the fly on the water the leg of the frog
At the bottom of the sea
There's a hair on the fly in the water the frog in the log. Fuck
Hey, I know you're new welcome to the stream
Pull up a chair. It's quite the dream
It's your first time here. Oh, what a joy
But don't act like this dream is a toy
That was the worst
Put the kingdom hearts music back on oh
I can't my voice is still fucked up
I can't do it
I i'll tell you
I'm a i'm a little irritated with this one a little irritated with this one. I don't know why this was so bad
I don't know why this one was considered to be so awful
Slightly irritated by this one
the winner
Of the worst singing of the year
Damedane with 18.5 percent of the vote. What was so wrong with that?
Dameo dame dameo. Well, I don't what that's what I did. What was wrong?
The raid song was in second place with 14.5 percent of the vote
And then the yoshi happy song was at 13.2 percent of the vote there
You top three the raid song was like four seconds long. I guess it means that's why it was the worst
Just like we do the worst. We're also going to do the best. Is it too connected here? Yoshi was good
Um, well, we're in the best now. We'll find out what really was the best. I'm just gonna peek. I mean
I peeked why does it matter if I peeked? I wrote it down
The person who wrote that I it's my handwriting. All right, uh coming up. We got the best singing. Here we go
Here come the nominees for best singing of the year. Aren't you prepared?
Talking quarter pound of beef on the hot hot side
Stays hot new mcdlt
Crisp lettuce and tomato on the cool cool side
Stays cool new mcdlt cool crisp the hot stays hot the cool stays crisp put it together. You can't resist
My ex and my bum and my ex and my bum and my bum
It's not even here
Uh
Audio jungle good. Oh, this is my favorite part. I love this part coming up here. Uh
Oh, that's my favorite part. I love it
Me
Hello
My love
I am here
To have some fun with you
And me
We'll see our destiny while we're in love
It's me the comedy guy. Hey, look at that bitch. Excuse me. Where are you going? Hey, don't hold up for me
It's me the comedy horror guy. I just make fucking jokes. Well, i'm scared. It's me the comedy guy
I'm ruining your fucking enjoyment of my playthrough
Shine
Yummy banana, I can't wait to eat. Okay, where do I find a car? I just love delicious banana
What the fuck
Uh, so yeah, of course firework is on both best and worst singing
Because you could I guess I hit some of those notes, but the end was really bad
And there and I really sounded like kind of like a horn with no air left in it
So, I mean it could have been both
But you know, we'll see
We'll see what the people have voted for the winner of best singing of the entire year goes to
You probably could guess it at one pious shitload
Oh my god
That's not even good
It won it won by it won 53
percent of the vote
More than half of you guys voted for that
underneath that at
15.4 percent. So you got to go really far down
Uh was the mcdlt song and then at number three was firework at 7.6 percent of the vote
53 percent of you voted for it. Uh, what's next?
We got a couple more to do, right? Yeah, uh, this is one of my favorite categories that has been added. This is
Uh best one guy moment and best one guy moment has turned into one of my favorite things on this stream
It's when somebody one of you is able to be to derail the entire stream and almost
Sometimes change everything we're doing by a simple comment or something that you have said
Uh, so here are the nominees and I think there are a lot of them for the best one guy moment of the year
Seriously, what does this have to do with anything what does this have to do with anything?
You put the dough in the pan and put the pan in the oven
I bet you i bet your bread is real gross. We got to do a public apology
So a lot of you may have been aware of some of the things that I may have said on stream recently
Um, I really don't mean that I didn't mean that at all and yeah, I just kind of want to go back to
Uh the kind of way it was beforehand
And i'm very sorry
New offer read to us green eggs and ham without fucking up once remove 75 million
Hello, everyone. Welcome to fairy tale readings with me. Jeremy today. We're gonna be reading green eggs and ham
Oh, it's so wonderful. Would you eat them in a box?
Would you eat them with a box?
Not in a box not with a box not in a house not with a mouse. I would eat
Music is like over each other
Is did somebody just make this account and start broadcasting in the screen cap it or fake it or is this the real account?
That's real
Chuck E cheese is here. What are you? What's what is chuck? He's doing here. What have you got?
What did you guys do? Why'd you do this?
Yeah, he's this is high germa in the thing but
It's because you gave him ten you gave him ten dollars to do that
You literally won't get past the first part of fellowship. I guarantee it
All right. I wouldn't
All right, i'm gonna remember your name because when I get past level one in fellowship of the ring i'm going to fucking scream your name
You can't let this person be right
I guarantee
I guarantee you're not gonna get to the first through the first part
The fellowship of the ring with the guarantee fucking they can't be right. They can't
I saw I just saw in the chat the funniest thing i've seen all week
The funniest thing i've seen all week. Absolutely without a doubt in like the in like the last
Five plus fucking streams the funniest thing i've seen all week. You ready? They said all of garden music
That's perfect
That's fucking perfect
Smarties and tootsie rolls from like 1993
Smarties are great up your urethra
Why did I read that
I jeremy elbertson will not make any reference to
the binding of isaac
world of warcraft
Hearthstone or dark souls during this stream
If I do
I will gift five community subs per reference fury vanquished
Five subs
There's one there's a second stream right now. It's gone and the title is high germa
You got 13.2 clicks per second. He's also cheating like you're also cheating
Like you can go download an auto clicker and have it just click
Wait, you do 13.2
I gotta be 13.2. I can't let this guy be a better streamer than me. I can't
Somebody said why was he so out of breath?
Is that you understand how much energy it takes to click that fast with your finger to be able to do the rapid like?
16 or like 20 it's between 16 to 25 clicks per second
But depending on the day you use so much energy to go like this
takes a lot
okay, um
with
62 percent of the votes 62.5 percent. This is not even fair. It should have been in its own like category
It should have just been like we should have just omitted it
It was it's thick germa like with 62.5 percent of the vote. It spawned a lot of shit right underneath that
You gotta well, you gotta go pretty far. You gotta go down to uh with 11.8 percent of the vote
chuck e cheese's appearance
um
I mean that was that was pretty that was pretty wild chuck e cheese's appearance
Had I mean he raided me he like hosted me and like somebody linked a picture of me kissing him
I mean like that it was it was a wild stream. Uh, and then smarties are great up your um
Somewhere with seven point two percent of the vote, but it was wasn't even fair
It just it seriously wasn't even fair load of the rings got robbed
Snubs snubs all over the place not photoshopped
And it could have been uh, we're gonna do actually two more
Because I feel like these need to be back to back before we do the next match. So, uh
Oh, yeah coming up next are worst impression and best
Impression again these categories I could go like this and open it and you wouldn't even know which one it was so
We'll do worst impression first. Here comes the worst nominees for worst impressions of the year
I still can't get over that like for voice andy in the beginning of this stream. There are 21 000 people here
What's up at welcome? Hope you're having a good time. This is an award show and it's a rumble. You're gonna see that too soon
CBD all right here are the nominees for worst impression of the year, whatever pick whatever
I don't understand
Why?
You're an idiot and i'm gonna throw this thing on the floor and it's gonna explode
And I don't know what you're talking about bill
I think you're gonna shut your mouth
The little guy has a mouth on him. I think
That's too bad. What's going on in here? I hate you
Okay, all of them at once so we got marge
And then uh
Lisa
and then
Bart yeah, and then
And then okay
I did not steal anything from jim gaffigan. He did he stole so many things from jim gaffigan. I didn't steal anything
That's just that's baloney
If anything, I have all my material completely not made. It's all mine
He really thinks that doesn't he?
Diva is elmo
Is golem we want shit. We need shit
Diva reporting for duty. It's also one of the ed brothers. It could be anyone eddie
It could even be elmo
The herd graders can speak they talk like this
Have you ever heard a third grader talk?
They talk right can I have some of that please?
I'll take they don't all talk like that. What?
It's all like this. I'll take one dust, please
I want one, too
Yeah, they do
No find somebody that can make a good cow noise
It's really hard to do that. Everybody always does that go
No, dude a cow actually goes like
Nobody can do it
Almost every category
Hey rick, hey, hey morty
Turn yourself into a green screen. Oh, no
Yeah, morty you can be whatever you want in front of the green screen
I don't want to be you rick. Yeah, didn't morty get over there and be me
No, I don't want to morty
Tell yourself who's in that room
Ah
Probably me in that chair
That was not good
Was bad
That one. Hey, stop playing that. Why does it keep doing that? It wants to play one guy moments so bad over and over again
Uh, baby bop is in almost every bad category
Worst noise worst singing was it in best singing too? Why is baby bop in every category?
So I have to say something about this winner
This is just proof to me
That I need to stop
Doing any of the simpsons ever again for the rest of my life. I'm never doing a simpsons impression
Uh all of the simpsons at once won by it was 30 31 percent of the vote
It's gonna be on here every single year
It's been on here every single year if I do homer even for a second even for one goddamn second
It's on here. If I do lisa or marge it's on here
every single year
Try homer now. No, it'll be on here
No, the best part about this stream is like a bunch of you guys forget the fucked up shit
I'm gonna do tonight. You know what I mean?
And it's tech wait and here's the next best part about this stream
It ain't even january yet. So I I can do whatever I want on these award streams
So it's the last day. You can't even nominate this. It's it's lost forever. It's lost in a void
So, all right, here we go
Hey
Hey mark, it's me
Ooh, that's what I look like when I do that. Uh, in second place was rick and morty greenscreen with 11.4 percent
And and then a cow at 10.7 percent
I could understand the cow one and I could understand the simpsons one
But the rick and morty greenscreen one I thought was like kind of good. I like thought I did a good job
Sometimes you think things that are not right. It's january here. What's wait? What time is it right now?
nine
It's nine thirty
Okay, it's nine thirty right now. I got we're dropping it on eastern time. It's six thirty my time
But it's nine thirty eastern. We have two and a half hours. Okay, so uh, just like the bad ones
They're also the good ones too. This is best impression of the year. Actually what?
Okay, auto there there joe auto. He's right there. He's under he's sleeping
I'm not gonna go wake him up. Just get him on camera. Okay. What if somebody walked into your bedroom and
Fucking just opened the cupboard and was like hey, hey come over here. What's going on?
Come here. Come here. Look. Hey. Hey, what's up? Hey, look at the camera. What the fuck are you doing here?
I don't want to do that like he's sleeping. He's having like a nice rest. I don't want to like go disturb him
Just rotate the camera
He's under the blanket though. You can't see him. All right, here come the category the nominees for best impression of the year
Uh, let's see. Let's see if your favorite got selected. See if your favorite got fucking selected
That's the right button jeremy. Don't press the one guy one again. Here we go
I don't want to do that. Mr. Turtle. I don't want to see that and I don't want you to come into my house
Okay, aim on do an okay acting challenge r2 d2 dying easy
But there's a storm
Uh, it's not raining yet
Uh, besides it's not actually that unsafe to swim in the storm
everyone, uh
Keep telling me take it out of the sea
But it's safer in here and it is up there
uh
Bernie, how would you like to respond to that?
I just uh want to say
that I think
That answer was cringe. The following has
Encouragement that's what it is. It's a bunch of compress the following has
encouragement
and love
We want to thank you for being here
You're the one that gets things done around here
well, tell him a
great job
Like I think that we can maybe get some quality entertainment here scoop
Like maybe we should stop streaming scoop, I think maybe that's a good idea
We are not ready
To move forward on a stimulus
Not yet, maybe soon we will move forward on that but my
Tell me everything, you know
Like a parakeet
Yeah, it makes sense. Right? Look at half of my mannerisms just like
Step on me step on me
Steady diet of like captain crunching baloney. That's how you end up like that
the winner of best impression of the year
is
R2 d2 dying sound with 34 percent of the vote
Second is bernie sanders with 18 percent
And then rounding us off at the end at number three was mitch mcconnell at 12.7
mitch mcconnell
Coming up next we have oh, no, no, no, no. No. Whoa. Whoa. Whoa. Whoa. Whoa. Whoa. Well, we're done
We're done. We're done. We're done. We're gonna do it. We're gonna do a uh match
Political how's that political mitch mcconnell right now is like more hated than the joker is in gotham city in the fucking dc universe
Really?
Is that politics?
It's still political
Yeah, whatever. It's the cbd coming out. It sure is
I promise i'm not pissing
You probably might my noise gate probably didn't pick it up
So by the way, somebody said cbd is unregulated
Okay, and bananas have radioactive poison in them, whatever
Uh, we're gonna do the next match of the rumble and make sure I get it. I gotta hold on. Let me turn this off for a second
Let me just let me let me see if I can make sure that I don't want I don't want the hud be gone
I don't want to hud
Yeah, uh, I I know I know we're gonna do the betting
This is gonna be the second match of the evening and this one is gonna be very fun
It might even be funny too. Let me just give the mods who it is
So they can do the prediction. Uh, I could
Hold on
Uh
Uh, wait, can you only do?
Wait, you can only do one. This is a three-way extreme rules match. I'm not sure we can we can predict this one
Yeah, we cannot we can't do the predictions on this one. You can only do uh, two. It's only two
Yeah, it's a three-way
It will
Oh when there are only two left. Well, whoever who have a pens wins and you know, it doesn't even matter
I'll just I'll show it to you right now
Ladies and gentlemen coming up next is the uh, the ritz brothers comedy routine al ritz jimmy ritz and harry ritz
Extreme rules a little sneak peek and uh, let me just make sure I can turn the hud off. What is the gorilla?
Oh, should I turn the volume all down? Oops. That's right. I had to do that
Introducing first in the ritz brothers comedy match. They're gonna do some uh, some slapstick for you is harry ritz. I think he's the oldest
Also from new york
Harry richie what?
All right. Let me see if I can do this
Can I can I turn off the hud?
What? Go get him
Here's harry ritz pointing to the ceiling thinking he's gay. I don't I think all these guys
Why does it say that in the bottom right corner? I just I think I just put it there
Yeah, these guys are from the the public domain movie night
earlier this year
Was that even not even been 2019?
They don't hey, by the way, they don't have to be from this year
We have like two years of characters to catch up with
When you see one ritz brothers entrance, do you really need to see the other two ritz brothers entrances?
That's what I want to ask you guys
I guess the answer is yes
Why do you get opponents first?
From new york weighing in at 200 pounds
All 200
Which is like a oh
Oh my god, I can't even
See this showing his armpits
Hey, what do you think of these ones boy?
Uh, did they somebody ask did they remove custom arenas? No, I tried to make one but 2k 20
is such a piece of
steaming burning shit
That the game would crash when I change the colors of the ropes
It just you just can't do it. Apparently. I I can't make it through the
Explosions coming out here
This who is this? Oh, of course. It's it's it's the youngest brother
That's jimmy ritz and
From new york weighing in at 200 pounds
jimmy
richie
The other entrance is so long
So what do they get this is an extreme rules match there's no stakes here, by the way, they just wanted to come to
Term a rumble of 2020 and show us their comedy routine
Ritz brothers are like the three stooges
But um sort of like the off-brand serial version of the three stooges and i'm gonna make a statement here
I think the ritz brothers are funnier
Than the three stooges. I think they have more comedy
I think they have much more style
Because I mean the three stooges simply just hit each other in the head
With their fists and like poke their eyes with their fingers and stuff the ritz brothers go on detective searches. They cook food
But hold on one second here. Can I pause it? I can't even pause it
On stage and well put a beautiful beautiful slap to the chest
I don't know who is who so this is the extreme rules comedy routine
I think that was jimmy ritz
I think that was hal al I don't even know who they are
And jimmy ritz with a ddt onto al ritz's skull going for a pin automatically. He's not gonna get it that way
as bob ritz
Sticks in here going for pivot a piledriver or something powerbomb or what a reversal like jim ritz
Is he gonna let it happen? No way, you can't just let that happen like that
Now ritz gets grabbed by german suplex onto al ritz
Full punch in the face from harry ritz another one
No, a reversal by jimmy ritz
So funny
I love how they like bop each other in the head and stuff
Oh, there he goes
These guys are so god damn funny
What's he gonna do? Oh a little slap in the face
As jimmy ritz is outside the ring
Currently grabbing on for dear life
As one of the I don't know one of the other ones jimmy ritz is going into this corner here
It looks like he might have been looking for something
Jimmy ritz is going underneath to get a comedy utensil
And he's got a chair
The funniest object there is and he doesn't even get to use it
He just gets punched in the face by harry ritz
And a belly to belly suplex for his trouble
Only one comedy utensil in the ring right now
Jimmy ritz. Oh, no all of them go outside
And al ritz has a sledgehammer
Oh, and he misses completely. They don't really want to hurt each other. They're just actors
And jimmy ritz takes an eye poke a classic comedy eye poke
I think al ritz is I think harry ritz is bleeding
What is that a pool cue
Do not let him pin him
There are now three comedy utensils you see he was like, ah, i'm gonna get you watch out wise guy
Dropping him right on the tailbone
That's gotta hurt
Into the ropes here misses the punch great comedy duck
Oh, they they do that so well
They're so good at this
By the way, everybody needs to know this they're not actually hurting each other
They're doing just enough damage and just enough pretending to make it look good on camera
Although that one looked real
So did that one
That one this looks pretty real harry harry harry you've been going a little too hard cameras aren't even rolling anymore
And I think that's gonna be it
No way. Oh my goodness
Jimmy ritz going to get another comedy utensil down here
What do you get? He's got a baseball bat
They're just pretending folks. It's okay. Nobody's actually injured right now
As jimmy ritz breaks it up
You're just masterful comedian
Gonna bring him up to the corner here up to the top turnbuckle
What is jimmy ritz planning to do to his brother harry ritz?
He's got him all the way up here. He's gonna go for a suplex
A suplex off the top rope
Oh, and there's no way harry's gonna get up from that one
So many reversals by jimmy ritz i'm gonna go for a forward wow beautiful flipping backwards neck breaker there
There fantastic stuff jimmy ritz going for the pin can al get in there quick enough to he completely missed
Not the bat again, not the comedy bat
DDT by jimmy ritz onto al al is in bad shape
He's in really bad shape right now
As now jimmy harry seems at the most hp out of the three of them
Big dropping suplex there gonna try to go for a pin. No bring him to the center of the ring
Lying next to his brother
This is a little weird
Ooh face stomp right in the front of the forward part of your face
Nice reversal by jimmy ritz that hurt his hand. He actually hit him
We might have to cut here. He actually punched him in the face accidentally
Put down the sledgehammer. No, he
This looks like a finishing move
No, it's just a throw
Just a throw and now he's taunting
That's harry ritz, by the way, the strongest of the three brothers
Taking it outside
Now he gets thrown right back in
This is al I believe and harry is now stuck in the ropes
That may have just been a broken neck
There's no way that this is gonna work out this way jimmy ritz is still outside. We got a one count
We've got a two count hit no
and just like
Every three stooges movie and every ritz brothers movie
This is going on for way too long
It's only so many times you can poke somebody in the eye for 97 straight minutes and jimmy ritz
Comes in with a victory
Finishing the comedy routine for the germa rumble 2020
I love how we're watching the replay of a pin that didn't work
Not even a mention of the bat that was involved earlier
They're all dead
What please remember predictions?
Well, we couldn't do predictions for this one because you can only do two
Um like one versus one
So with a three way, it would be hard to do we'll do for the next one though. I promise. Um
You know what the funniest part is I I thought that that was gonna be like the lamest
Match of the evening, but that turned out to somehow be like the best one so far
Match two is now over. We will now move on. What do they look like?
Why does it look like herman munster? I don't know
The the bat when they just kept trading the bat back and forth and hitting each other in the face
Oh god
That was funny. All right moving on we got some more categories to do obviously
Uh, we actually you know what we'll take a break after this next run of categories
How does that sound let's turn that volume mixer down and we come back to this
Uh, the next one we'll take a break after this. Yeah, welcome back to the awards section of this stream
Like maybe should I get some light on me? I got jump scared. Oh, i'm sorry
Uh best joke taking more than five minutes to set up and you're probably wondering
What happened to worst joke taking more than five minutes to set up?
Well, there really wasn't very many or they were so bad that they could not even be nominated
So we only have a best of this year for 2020 it just like burped so loud inside of my body
If there was a microphone inside of my esophagus down here, you guys would have freaked out. It was really loud in here
I could hear that internally. What is up?
gas
Well, I didn't no no, I didn't do the nominations yet. Uh, oh cbd's kicking in
Uh, all right. So best joke taking them with a five minute setup. What this means is uh, I kind of
Just take a few minutes to do something and I set it up and I try to make people laugh and
Let's say four to ten times it works out the other six I get ridiculed off the stream
But here we go now here are the nominees for best joke taking more than five minutes to set up
What's in the cup? It's just a little it's just a little cbd thc
Sippy, you know nothing major just something to have fun and relax. All right, here come the nominees for
Uh best joke taking for the five minute. Okay, it's it's hitting me
Oh, there was an estimate that there was going to be a speedy stimulus package and it didn't happen
Oh shit, all the investors were expecting it. It didn't happen ceo tweeted out
picture of asshole with two middle fingers on it and said fuck all investors
Oh, that holy shit. That's the only way this would have happened
Hello. Hey, what's up? It's me. Oh, hey, what's going on? How are you doing?
I'm doing good. Did you get my messages that I sent you? Yes, I did
You know what to do. You know what to do man of the hour
Say it say the line. You came just in time
It's time to solve it. Oh
Are you all right? Are you okay? My leg that was my leg this next room is terrible disgusting
Dastardly t-shirts the way they do that old baby. Will you stand the smelly smells for 10 minutes?
Or will you puke into the toilet?
Yeah
Audio jungle
Audio jungle good. Oh, this is my favorite part. I love this part coming up here
Uh
Oh, that's my favorite part professor michael's
paternity test
to find out if they
Were the father to stevenson's baby join us
Today for a new episode
Of the morning announcements and by the way, hey, mr. Mr. Whatever your fucking name is
I can't believe you you want to tell me this vibes baby
It's your baby
Another cctv
Holy shit jerry
It was started as a small confrontation has turned into an absolute bloodbath brawl outside of the 7-eleven
It looks like they're upset that
mcdonald's
They have something
Roger i'm not even entirely sure what they got these weapons
The battle for the battle for home depot
Roger people are people on social media are calling this the battle of home depot
Mom, i'm really my mother's probably watching the stream going. What the fuck is this kid doing? I didn't raise him like this
Hey, um
Yeah, i'm all right. I just had some work done
This is what a toddler does when they know they did something wrong
That should be an emote stanley kubrick
Kubrick stare
Yeah, i'll take i'll what can I take a bite and will you guys get over this
If I take a bite of this will you get over it?
Fucking sans
It should never have been in the game. It's not a nintendo character
Right behind you right behind him shit. I fell down
I'll be up in a minute. Okay. We'll be up here. Need heels here. Need heels. I'm out of mana
Need heels
Hey, where do you guys know where I am?
I don't know where I am. I'm in the water need help to me to me to me to me
I got two. I got two
Fucking idiots. I have two
Come on. We're on our way
And i'm gonna die like i'm gonna die here and that's fine. I'll fucking take it up with the guild leader later
This is like this is the type of shit. This is why we can't get the fucking top 100
Well, uh, so
This one is the I believe the closest one of the of the entire evening
Uh, this one was by a margin
of
Like seven tenths of a percentage
So the two top ones are both 20
Percent and then something just to let you know, this is the closest one of the auto. Yes auto has awakened
Uh, I'm having fun
You having fun over there? He's just like rubbing his back like a bear on a tree and he's just sneezing
What are you doing over there?
Also, who do you think's gonna win?
Who do you think what do you think's gonna win best joke taking more than five minutes to set up cookies?
Uh, well, that's not that's not on the that's not a category auto. That's not a nominee
The winner of best joke of the year taking more than five was just pretty much best joke of the year
Let's just go for it. Ladies and gentlemen the winner with 20.86 percent of the vote
jigsaw house with
20.08 percent of the vote
Eating the shoe lost
Very close very close in third place was ah eu which I know that it's supposed to be five minutes
But I think that bit went on for like 30. So it was allowed just chillin
Uh, yeah jigsaw house 20 well 15.7 percent for ah eu by the way recency bias recency bias
Probably but you know, it's still fun. All right coming up. We have uh, let's take a look
I got another match to do but I want to take a break first. So we have how many was that?
The best joke so we had one two, three four one, two, three four one two. All right, so we have
Uh, we'll do two more cookies was robbed. Yeah, well, whatever
This is the two of the night that I think are going to be the most irritating to sit through
For a lot of you guys
So I just want to give you warning now some of you guys that might be new here
You might leave the stream in about two minutes
Uh, the next categories are going to be worst noise of the year and best noise of the year
And there were a shitload of nominees
The I there's like 20 nominees in worst noise
So strap yourself in and get ready to hear some of the things you don't ever want to hear ever again
There sure were yes, they were. Uh, so here are the nominees ladies and gentlemen for
worst noise of the
Year, you didn't even see me. I didn't
Okay, somebody squeezed a little too much air out of me
All right, this is cool. I'm gonna sneeze but I cannot mute my microphone
Uh
Funny man make a funny noise funny man make a funny noise. All right fine
I don't think I could hit a bong man. I really don't think I could in real life. I would probably fucking fall down
I would hit the bong. It'd be like
Also nominated for worst face
What are these um, well these like little like white things in the ground dude
These like flexibles
What I didn't get that guy give us a joke you got it
Did I do it
I think it's hitting him now. I got it
Cover it with cheese. The ooey gooey cheesy
Oh, yeah. Oh my god. Does it have like a bunch of fucking nacho cheese on it? Oh,
I know I get it, but it's still good
Oh, how can we make a how can we make like a caesar salad better?
Cover it with ooey gooey yummy cheesy cheesy
Cheesy
Germa is just a scary motherfucker. No, but I am I though I completely disagree
I disagree lick whale lord. Oh dude, that wouldn't be so gross
Where's he
Good
Oh, come on
No, excuse me. That was not a donkey sound
This is a donkey sound
Oh, that's one of those ducks at the store that you squeeze the dog toy never mind I tried
So many nominees
So many nominees for this category
But they can only be one winner, uh, they can only be three that are even listed so the winner of
The best noise of the year. No, no, no shit. That's wrong
It's worst noise of the year the winner of worst noise of the year is going to be
With 11.66 percent of the vote. We have ooey gooey
ooey gooey one with eleven point six
Six percent. Um, I think I you know, it's not even a noise. I just talked I just said a sentence
Um, I think it's just everybody hated the sentence therefore nominated it so often everybody voted for it. Um,
So after that very very close though with eleven point one six percent of the vote
So another very very close one even closer than the last one was the horrendous pig
So if you want to be a purist here
You could say that the horrendous pig was the worst noise of the year
And ooey gooey was the most hated phrase of the year after that at nine point. Oh five percent is chubaka transforming
I could see that I could see that. Yeah, I could see that acceptable. Yeah, that's that's an acceptable win
There are your winners. Uh
What's the next one right here? So just like worst noise we have best noise now best noise
Um doesn't no doesn't include anything like singing or anything. Uh, this is just what people
Thought was a better sound. I thought it was cooler thought it was funnier
the only thing I can't believe about this one is
There's a there's a nominee on here that is so
Ear screechingly horrible that I cannot comprehend why it is not in the other category
So just be aware. There is like ear scraping
There's like ear like a like a q-tip going in there and just like it's i'm just warning it now. Here we go
Nominees for best noise of the year wanted to warn you where's best noise
best noise of the year
You're never gonna get painfully clean like this
What's over there
And stop no whammies nobody tell her
Him i'm telling you what i'll hold that shit for me take a look at this scrumptious
cheese
Pizza
Neck thickness
Oh god
It's like I swallow. I like cartoon python swallowed a plate or something
My character right now is going like
And I want you to listen to that crunch
You were wrong you were wrong
Okay
The winner of the best noise of the year, I think
Won this like a year or two ago
I can't do this anymore either because when I do this people just vote for it people just nominate and people just go
Yeah, that's the one
Uh, the winner is
Well, I gotta play the fanfare
Didgeridoo at twenty point three six percent of the vote. So more than twenty percent of the vote didgeridoo won
Uh, and then doy doy which got fourteen point five percent of the vote
Which confuses me because the first time I ever did the doy doy thing
People screamed at me. They said stop that hurts my ears. I hate it never do that again
Don't ever do the doy doy doy thing ever again. And then two years later
I do the doy doy doy thing again
And all of a sudden now it's just second place for best noise of the year. What happened your tastes change
I'm gonna do it right now
There you go, oh and my ears won uh with eleven point five percent in third place i'm leaving don't leave please
uh
Eleven point five percent for my ears, which is the one that would hurt. That's the one that hurt
I think um, does that catch us up weird for another match?
After we take a break, let's see how caught up we was that was that four? I believe that was four
We had one one two three four one two three four one two three. Yes, we did. Okay. All right, let's take a quick break
I'll be right back. I'm gonna just get another maybe another drink maybe
Uh, see if auto needs to get anything see if auto needs to go out and i'll be right back. See you guys in a minute
Hey, hello
Hi everybody. I have returned to set up the next match in the rumble
So the next match is going to be a four-way
Uh tables, I believe tables ladders and chairs match be sus. Oh god
There always has to be a tables ladders and chairs match
Hear the crowd
Let me make sure the next one is set up
Yeah, here it comes
Uh, hold on a sec. Let me get that over here. Okay
Where is this? I need to move this
This light is oh shit, okay, I don't want to break anything
All right. So again, this is a tlc match
god
Tlc and it is between
a lot of different fandoms a lot of different fandoms here if you could think of a
certain group of people
that love a certain
franchise or certain characters you'd put them into a
Into a crew wouldn't you and we've had quite a few crews over the years, especially considering the last couple of years
The next match is going to be a four-way between those crews. So let me uh, let's go
Welcome back to the rumble portion of the stream
First character being introduced
Is murius
Of the moo crew
Also was nominated for best character of the year
Ooh 220
That's not the name of that animal is not mega milk. It is murius
representing the moo crew
Ladder back there. Whoa
Somebody in the audience. He must have he must have that gray
Leash attached to him
I know how he gets when that's on him the anger leash our next competitor
Coming in here to challenge the moo crew and the other two
Are the wink dinks germa wink?
superstar, okay
So yeah, 75 000 channel points a lot of you got really into that. So obviously germa wink wanted to come and represent himself
To represent the wink dinks
Can you guess where this guy's from?
Coming up next
I wonder
I got you know, i'm gonna put my money on the dinks tonight
I think they have a lot riding here
They've been waiting for winks to come back for like a year and a half and they're just not coming back
Most dedicated fan base I think is but wait a minute. I'll be talking about dedicated fan bases
We're having a talk about dedicated fan bases. I think that's nancy dru
That's nancy dru
Representing the true crew
Nancy dru
With her atv looking to find a new part of a new clue for an old egyptian temple
Stumbled her way in here. She she knew
And she needed to be represented
But that's not all there's still one more group one more incredibly incredibly important group in this
channel in this universe here
You know, I talk about it all the time. I say it all the time. I address you guys as such
Still on nancy dru though
It's the banana brothers. Oh
And nobody seems to like the banana bros
this is
Everybody hates the banana bros. I why they boo with the banana bros
Somebody wrote oh my god, fuck this guy. All right, can I skip this? Can I skip this shit?
Everybody hates him
I love this guy
I love the banana bros
Murius the wink dinks moo crew wink dinks true crew
Versus banana bros fatal four way tables ladders and chairs match
Nancy dru is not wasting a single second of her time
Throwing murius into the ropes over the ropes now. There are I don't there are no rules here
zero rules
It's just whoever loses. Where wait, where are all the items?
Where are the items?
It's supposed to be tables ladders and chairs. I don't see a single table. I don't see a single
Ladder I don't see a single chair
You forgot to put them out
What are you serious?
Oh the banana the banana is getting absolutely bruised right now
Am I blind?
What do you mean? It's under the ring. Where are they going? No. No, I see up top up top up top
Holy shit. That was a big right hand overhead smash from murius out of nancy dru. By the way, whoever wins this
This is what I will call this channel's community for the next six months
so
Uh, there's a lot riding on this one
Big punching match here in the middle of the ring murius seems to have missed that double
twisted kick up
Boozled
What?
I kick a paloozle
Somebody get a table in here. Oh finally the banana bro is always taking the initiative
Reaching under the ring getting the first ladder of the evening
Yeah, one of the most dedicated one of the most passionate
fandoms on this channel the banana bros
He's gonna know he's not gonna be able to have any time the ladder was stolen by the winktinks
Winktink just wants to get up there. I don't think he was supposed
No, they're just setting it up ready to go
Nancy dru and murius have been outside this whole time just punching each other in the face
Oh, and she heard me. That was a huge kick from nancy dru
Leave oh ddt onto the ladder might see another uh might see a ladder set up here. Nope
Oh
Of all the things you could have done banana bro, that was probably the worst one to do
Murius setting up the ladder though murius thinking about get no murius is getting something else
Murius is going to get
One of the chairs over here. He went a long way to get that single chair
I hope it was worth it
Just like in black and white the ai is so bad with their pathing but he gets the hit he gets two hits
and
Nancy dru was just concerned about what was currently happening and murius
Fleeting up right now the new crew
Big elbow drop nancy dru was just trying to stop. She was looking at her dialogue options
One of them was please don't hit him. The other one was how much did that cost and the other one was
Where can I find the bar?
Murius is getting up to the top. No nancy dru throws him down
Kicking him right into his sternum both going outside again. There's an opportunity here for banana bros
Doesn't look like they're going to capitalize though nancy dru with a swinging neck breaker
But wink dink from behind nancy dru
Shit
And the wink dink he's he's signaling his crowd to do everybody to wink in the crowd banana bro. What are you doing?
He wanted attention. They're all just craving your attention. They're all just trying to get attention
They so badly want you to look at them
Moo crew moo crew banana bros. Oh this way banana bros banana bros out
Ladder set up again murius going in for a swinging ddt tornado style
Moo crew signaling his fans now to spam the chat room
Big right hand onto nancy dru swinging her around dropping down
And this opportunity is being taken by the wink dinks
Wink dinks are going up but murius
He's almost gonna get is he gonna get it
Murius going for the punch in the stomach is the wink dinks gonna win can the wink dinks possibly secure this
Three punches four punches in the stomach and here comes the banana bro
No, he's trying to push it down
Why is nobody trying to grab? He can't even push it down. He's not strong enough
What did he take it why did he take it
They're just running into each other
Big belly to back suplex by murius
Signaling the moo crew. He's ready. He's ready to have you guys be called that for the next six months
Nancy dru has finally gotten up
Finally getting back into the ring
It seems like ages ago that she was in this and she's gonna take the opportunity to go up nancy dru with the dru crew
Going up to the top rope going on top. She's got the briefcase
Is nancy dru gonna pull this off in the in the?
In the the absolute calamity going on nancy dru might have actually just gotten this
She can't do the mini game. Oh, she was always so bad at this one
Grabbing his arm wink dinks is throwing down murius
caught in the ropes
Wink dink is very strong right now murius has the most health
but uh-oh
Now wait, no, no, no, no, you got to get back in there banana bro. You can't just just you've got to get in there
You got to push that thing over right now
You almost got it
Push it over push it over. I don't want to call everybody wink dinks for the next six months. Don't push it over
Somebody get up there, please
Murius, please
Somebody stop it nancy dru run your atv into here and run it over. How is he still got this?
Banana bro's just like yeah, I don't understand this is fucked up big powerbomb
Why is she on the top rope wait, why is she sitting on the top rope banana bro got the ladder
Setting it up. Is this the banana bro's victory lap right now looks at nancy dru does not
Does not attack her she's on the top ropes. Is she gonna go for no?
That was the worst thing you could have done nancy dru. Oh catches him
Oh the skill the the app the just the necessity of that moment
She investigated
She took a look at her clues
And she found out that that was probably the best idea and maybe it's going to be a good enough idea to win this match
And be called the dru crew for the next six months nancy dru ladies and gentlemen has unlatched it
The dru crew prevails once again as they always do
Dru crew has prevailed nancy dru with the win
nancy dru
Well, congratulations to nancy dru dru crew
That's what you guys are gonna be called now. You're the dru crew now for at least six months
That was a huge clutch the big jumping two-handed two foot stomp kicking off the top rope
That's a deserved win for nancy dru banana bros. You had a chance, but you really blew it
All right, let's keep going
That was match number three. There is another match before the rumble. We got some more categories to do though turn that down
Yeah, I will be joining you back here in a sec like this
Hello, so coming up on the next nominee the next nominees
Uh, a very very I like this category a lot. I feel like this happens all the time
So there's a lot to choose from it is a best scare moment
Best time that I was ever scared on stream whether a jump scare or uh, or likewise. Is he high?
Probably a little probably it's new easy. Whatever. What do I what do you want? Just maybe this is a little maybe just a
Little bit. It's a small amount. He's fucking zonked. No, i'm not the wink things did all the work
Yeah, the wink things did all the work and then nancy dru, uh, just kind of nancy dru and the banner bros really just capitalized
So hey, what can I tell you? I don't make the rules. We just watch
Uh, so here are the nominees for best scare of the year. I played vr this year
So, you know, there's gonna be at least like 10 of those. So here they are best scare of the year
You do make the rules. No, I don't what the fuck. Oh my god
I thought that was in real life that scared the shit out of me. I was like who's here. Why are you here?
What the fuck
Okay, that was fucking I that that was that was one of the scariest things I've ever seen in my life
That's one scary thing that I've seen in my whole life. I didn't that was
That's horrible. That's terrifying. That was the worst thing I've ever seen in my life my whole life
There are more copies of wii sports out in the wild and there are ants I know but why why I didn't want one
That was the warning
What do you mean? I just got warned for being
Oh
I'm getting fuck out of here
Even to the hallway down the hallway
Does that sound
All right
Oh my chest
My whole body hurts my whole body hurts. Oh my god. What the
Oh my god, dude
Okay, so
You've seen the nominees
Uh the winner of best scare moment of the year. Let me see what won first pretty good
Uh, what do you think? Let's see. Let's see. Let's see what the what the what the people think here now
Cheater
You know, you can't cheat in an award show. Oh, you probably actually you can yeah, you can you probably can or shows
The deer the deer the deer i've seen a lot of deer hate to disappoint all the people that are saying deer
the winner of best scare moment of the year
is
Peeking down the hallway at 17 percent of the vote in five nights at freddys. I was lied to
Uh, I was told that that's not supposed to happen
I was told that that was just of like a 0.2 chance and I was told to do it again
And it happened again, and then I realized I was very angry with you
Uh, so yeah, then you got me twice
Uh, that was 17 percent. They were all still pretty close
No air left was 12.82 percent, which i'll be honest with you
That was probably that was probably the for me at least if I if I if this was no
Voting allowed here. Uh, that would be the worst one for me. I remember that very vividly
It was fucking horrible and then bunny in the room at 12.5 percent that one got pretty high because I mean I was like
Drinking right I had been drinking and it was just so easy just to get the shit out of me
So that I could understand I was pretty jumpy. So yeah, that's uh peeking down the hallway wins the best scare moment drunk
Yeah, I was I was yeah, I was he took the headset off. He was so scared
Okay, let's uh, what do we got we have i'm gonna make sure there's enough left to do the end too
Oh, yeah, there is let me get the all right. Let's get this one out of the way now
Because uh, I want the top categories to be the last thing that we do before the rumble or after the rumble
Okay, so the next one this is best accident. I I tend to have lots of accidents on stream
Uh, whether that's falling down somewhere irl whether that's
Messing up something uh saying something. I shouldn't say this is a new category. Uh,
I make mistakes all the time. I'm only human. I make mistakes and I have to live with them
Okay, so here are the nominees for the best accidents of the year
This is not the way i'm going out this is not the way i'm going out on
All right, long story short
I can bring the switch to the bathroom and I can shit on it and keep and keep my hands close
And not have to worry about my legs tingling so I can get up whenever I want and put it over
Okay, my nieces and nephews
Love lego star wars. It's like their favorite thing in the world
And I got a text
from my parents
and from my sister
that said
Hey, um
Just want to let you know the kids were watching your stream because they love lego star wars and we had to mute you
Because you kept saying fuck so much
Oh, it's the console. All right. Hold on. Let me show you the console
I don't whatever am I wearing beads on my wrist?
shit
Shit that you saw it
God damn it. It's
It's black tourmaline
It's like a crystal bracelet. I I i'm just wearing it because um, uh, it's a crystal bracelet
And it's uh supposed to help with your energy. It's not it's made up like it's literally all made up
This is kind of how it's just kind of how I feel
It's like 40 percent of every day. Can I tell you that not like that? Not like that. Not like that. Not like that
So
What can I do for you?
Paseo del mar high
No, no, no, no, no
Oh my god, it's too bad. No, this is gonna be
I'm gonna make it more expensive. I'm gonna make it more expensive. All right, i'm gonna turn it off. I'm gonna turn it off
I gotta make it more expensive. I I I I remember i'm mid piss. I'm peeing. It's mid piss
It's like a 20 to 30 second full piss. This didn't even have it on stream 10 seconds into the full piss
I drop it right right it and i'm pissing on the phone
I'm pissing on the phone and it's in piss water into the toilet peeing on it
There we are
What happened okay, so
So what has happened is I press the back button
And this is when I uh when I searched for ai dungeon an hour and a half ago to play it and I spelt it
uh
Just a little a little incorrect
What what's this doing on here what's this doing on here oh shit
Where is this picture? What's wrong with this one? It wasn't on fucking purpose. I swear to god. I swear to god. I swear to god
Why are you doing this?
No, no, I just I just I just I just own the raving rabbits fucking ultimate party collection, which is every single video game they made
Come on what
Hey german on 85 here
Lee shit, this is something I can't show on stream
As you see
uh new category new, uh
new thing to
feed through right
feed through
Oh, he's getting zonked on stream
Uh, so the winner of the uh, best accident
He's fucking zooted
Best accident was you
Oh
Mother fuck
Okay. Anyways, the winner of
the winner of
best accident is
Wait, you didn't hear it. Come on at 18.5 percent of the vote chuck e cheese
I just keep thinking about that guy said over and over again, uh kissing chuck e cheese was at 18.5 percent of the vote
Uh, that was very bad very bad accident
If you were not here for that stream, like I said chuck e earlier chuck e cheese rated the stream
And was here and we were being fucking weird
And then somebody linked a picture of me kissing him and I showed it on stream accidentally
And he was here and he was hosting the channel. So that's a pretty big accident. Uh, that was 18.5 percent and then naked
Was 16.9. So that was it's still close. So just under 17 percent for naked and
Streaming and driving was 12.6 percent number three. Uh, I don't know. I'm not sure I agree with number three
I think i'm gonna put something else there. Uh, lego star wars was robbed
Uh, yeah, kissing chuck e cheese is the winner, which I mean that was a pretty horrible fucking accident. So, uh
What do we have left? That's not the final four. Okay, here we are. So this next one coming up is
worst meltdown
Which worse meltdown is different than a lot
it's it's hard to do worse meltdown because
So many of the nominees could be entire streams
so it's not necessarily just one moment or two moments or
It it could be the whole entire broadcast
So we kind of let it things pass where it could be just a full stream
So keep that in mind when you're watching these nominees 13 straight hours of it potentially
Yeah, uh here are the nominees for worst meltdown of the year either moment or stream in particular
I'm gonna lose
Oh my god. Oh my god. I just broke something
He's having a little cranky wanky right now
Oh
But we're at we're on the last fucking disc i'm so close to ripping it out and just
Frisbeeing it. How come my game's not doing that?
Flying fuck what the hell are you talking about?
Shit just you
I don't I don't know what happened
I didn't do anything. I just went left three times
I've already fucking lost my place. Oh, I
And then I don't know. I don't I don't I forget
I forget already. Oh
I'm gonna eat my fucking hand
Add this to worst meltdown of the year. I don't care. This job. I have to i'm gonna eat my fucking hand put it in the other
No, my god, i'm not pretending i'm not i'm swear to god
No, i'm gonna just do
Holy shit, dude, i'm holding up holding let it don't matter i'm i'm tilting i'm dying. I'm like i'm finessing and
tilting and tilting a little
Dude
I was trying to roll it over to the fucking stupid time
Don't kill them kill them kill them kill them
No, oh get this away from my house
Right there bingo just land. Holy shit. Okay. I got it. I'm good. I did it I went
Oh my
Huh, what what what what what why what? Oh my god. Oh my god. Oh my god. Oh my god
Oh my god, so i'm going back home now. What he saw us boss. We gotta try again. What do you mean?
He sucks. Wait, what?
You follow me sir. It's got this is ridiculous
Boss
This oh my god, you can't you can't but i'm do you see what's happening
Oh
You see that button right there how it's made out of the most slippery fucking plastic notes, man
You see that button?
You see that shiny plastic ass fucking a button
Cranky wanky, right?
Uh too too many good ones. They were a lot this year. There's a lot of bad ones
Uh, but they can only be one winner
And I could have guessed this was going to be the one that wins
This is also, uh, not only does this win worst meltdown of the year
It also takes the cake for being the longest stream i've ever done and ever will
Lord of the rings the two towers, uh, that was a 13.4 13 and a half hour stream
It uh was hell from start to finish with 24 percent of the vote
Lord of the rings two towers underneath that you have super monkey ball with 19 percent and then super mario sunshine
At 17.7 percent cranky wanky
So there are your uh winners for worst meltdown
and now
We got another match. Let's move over to the uh wwe game
Match number four of the evening. Uh, this one you will be able to bet on I will just make that really clear
Let me just send the mods what they need to get you will be able to bet on this one
Let me just tell the mods who it is. I had to write that like six times
Okay, so this is a one-on-one. This is gonna be a one-on-one backstage
brawl
From what I have heard someone's going all in all in i'll be careful be careful
one-on-one backstage
brawl between none other than
Well, you're just gonna have to see aren't you?
Just gonna have to wait and see for it to load
And I will turn it back on I will tell you that this is uh, two very powerful beings
We have one of the most powerful current memes on the channel versus the potentially most powerful being on the channel
We're gonna have to see why don't we take a look right now?
uh
Wait, what they didn't even do it in the entrances
that's
That's germa dump truck versus jex
In a one-on-one backstage brawl. This is like an apahara movie
The dump truck versus jex
I
Don't know why they're out back and why he's just murdering him out back
Uh start the prediction, please. Who do you think is gonna win this match?
Why are they in some weird?
Germa dump truck seems to have all right into the table
I hope they use the outhouse to their advantage
Jex wearing his uh, his jex suit which gives him plus 25. Okay. He's already through the table
Do you have a dump truck just dumping on jex through the table?
Jex is he got so fucked up. He's got gray hair now
What?
He just broke his neck
You're going to have time to
Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait
So many you guys just got so screwed you guys got so screwed
It happened too fast
You got destroyed
Oh my god, I can't what am I supposed to do about that? Some of you guys just got absolutely decimated right there
Oh my god, that's so funny
Um, okay. I can't
All right. That's what I kind of want. I just I kind of want to see it again. Oh, wait, hold on
We'll go back. We'll go back and do a regular match after
We'll do a regular match
after
I can't refund he lost
You guys don't accept anymore
Uh, do you pay out? I mean
All right. I don't pull it out pull it out. Send the money back. Send the money back. Send the money back
Send the money back. I think I don't know. I have no idea. This is a horrible scenario
No, pay it out pay it out pay it out pay it out pay it out pay it out pay it out
What happened? Did it do pay out?
I don't know, dude
I don't know. I don't know. It was because people could still vote
All right. Listen, listen, listen, listen, listen, listen
We're gonna all right. Listen, we're gonna refund the money. We're gonna refund the money and we're gonna do it again
It happened too fast, dude
Oh and fade out
Okay. Well now that you saw that it's time for a rematch
It's too late. Okay. Well, whatever if we look at the ship that shit's gonna happen
Hey
All you guys that just lost right there. Here you go. You've got another opportunity because we're gonna do another prediction right now
We're gonna do the one right now same match, you know, what just happened. Do you think he can do it again?
Dump truck is too powerful. I don't is he though
No, there's like errors
on predictions
Whatever. Are we ready to do another prediction though? You guys let's do it again
This is for a german dump truck versus jex
Same place and i'm gonna give you time now
So you have an opportunity here if you think that jump truck's gonna do that again
Or if jex is gonna snap out of it here lose a little bit of that gray hair
And go for it
What do you guys think?
We're gonna close the prediction here
uh in about
I'd say a minute
One minute we can maybe close it out
You guys all know what's gonna happen
So are we ready? Are we ready to close it? Have you made your bets?
All right
Close that up
I'm gonna start it right now
Okay, are we closed?
my safe
To press this button
It has to run down the timer. Oh
All right. Well, I don't think that's gonna happen again. So I think we have I think we're good
I'm gonna wait till it gets down to like a third. Okay
Now i'm like scared. Okay ready in three
two
one
go
Rematch
Right off the bat jex with a clothesline all you have to do. You have to kill your opponent
All you guys that just bet against jex
Oh, I don't know. You still have an opportunity betting against but we saw dump truck kill him in two moves
just carrying him and
Dropping him directly onto his onto his big bulbous
Bunger burger, but that doesn't hurt him very much going over to the trash can here picking up a sludge hammer
completely misses
Ankle lock. No, no, no, no. No, he's going to what's he gonna do?
Take him right in the chest. They're being a lot more timid this time. They're not like instantly hurting each other
So maybe that this is better
dump truck versus jex right onto the sludge hammer
Why what was that sound?
That was like somebody getting shocked with a taser
It's like a stun gun
Uh-oh
This does not look good for jex
Remember, you just have to kill your opponent
With the steel no didn't steal it but he still hit him with it
That might have killed him
Nope, he's still alive
Jex is not even transformed by the way into super jex. He can only do that once every five years
Takes he's hitting with a skull
Big reversal by germa's dump truck. This looks pretty even
Look at those health bars. This is of anybody's match right now
I would love to see you outhouse
I would love to see going over to the outhouse and just like giving him a swirly
Punch right hand. No reversal right elbow
Triple elbow he hit his head on one of those he hit his head on one of those
He smashed his head on like a rock at one of those skulls
Completely missing a few times dump truck does not have eyes. He's just an ass
Remember he has to go by smell
Yep, I just said that I just did and I apologize to 22,000 people
This is looking bad for jex. That was a neckbreaker on the ground. The neckbreaker always is just deadly
Uh-oh jex is in a lot of trouble
For the second time in a row unless he pulls something out right here
Can we get any momentum at all from jex? He's just getting absolutely destroyed his health is almost at zero
And he's going to
Okay, jex's
Jex seems to not uh
Man, maybe jex is getting old too
Oh, no
Is my ass more powerful than the rest of my body at peak pinnacle condition?
That's what that whole bit was
Oh, well
Uh, that is it. That's open. That's another win back to back there from uh derma's uh derma's dump truck
Time to bring out super jex
He's screaming
All right, that is gonna take us guys
to
Uh, let me lower this we have the final four categories
They're pretty big ones
We have worst gamer moment best gamer moment
Worst stream of the year and best stream of the year coming up. These are the bottom four categories for
Uh the awards at least
And some of these are pretty close from what I remember
Yeah
So let's start with uh, hold on this side of the way
I'm working on it. Relax
We're gonna start with worst gamer moment
Go over here. Yeah, did it pay out 66 million channel points?
my god
66 fucking million
Okay, pull this back here
I am back
Uh, should I put the new year thing on wait? Wait, what time is it? Oh, we have one hour, right in one hour
I think it's gonna line up perfectly
Uh worst gamer moment of the year. This includes
Um just tasks I couldn't do
Bosses I couldn't beat things. I couldn't do basic, uh, basic literal human basic human instruction
Uh not being able to follow so it's um, just really really bad shitty
Gameplay and ideas that I have over the years. Let's see what the nominees are this year for worst gamer moment of the year
Tape it
I I could tape it like around my neck. I've got an omega symbol. I don't know what that is
I don't know what that is. I'm not kidding. I don't I don't fucking know what that is. No omega symbol for real
I don't know that I have no idea what that is. I have no idea. No, no, you know, you know, what a fucking omega symbol
I played like the first four hours
I played that wasn't in the god of war game symbol upside down quake symbol. I don't know what all the video games
I can't get this wrong
Idea
Okay, if I do not direct hit the next enemy if I don't not hit the end next enemy directly
Then I will give 500 million community subs
Get this away from my house
Oh shit, it did work
All right, just make the jump. I gotta make this jump. This is the biggest jump of the day so loud
Just a regular jump. Nothing crazy
Just a regular jump. It gets close
Right there bingo. Just land. Holy shit. Okay. I got it. I'm good. I did it. I went
Oh my
What what what what what why what
nice
Ride the wall
I don't care
Is that uh eight?
8 55 8 55 8 35 god damn it, man
What time is that?
Eight
This is eight
I people think that there's no way that that's real and I swear to god it was I the winner of
Worst gamer moment of the year
Is gonna be let me get the audio read a clock right now
Don't do this to me. Don't do this to me right now. Don't do this to me now, bro
Don't do this to me now, bro
Don't do this to me right now, bro
Don't do it. Don't don't
Give me a clock. Let's go
Give me a clock right now
Give me a clock. Let's see. Let's see a clock. You got an analog clock with a time on it link it link
Let me see it link me it
Somebody link a clock
Look at the clock
You think I i'm a millennial. I don't have an analog clock in my house. I have an iphone. Here we go
Okay, large online clock
Okay, let me save that image
Okay
Now i'm gonna read this
I'm gonna read this analog clock right now
this clock
says
Okay
This is
That is eight five
eight oh five o'clock
What do you mean I cheated?
Wait, it's eight oh five right now
What?
Wait, what the fuck is happening?
Where did I get this from? You somebody link this image?
All right, that's it streams over stream is ending right now
Go back to the awards. No, i've all right. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Uh, worst gamer moment of the year
Uh 49 of the vote it was just it was an absolute landslide a 2.5 billion dollar miss
Uh with 49 percent of the vote an absolute landslide
In second place, it was can't read an analog clock for 10.8 percent of the vote
And then one dpi andy for 9.8 percent of the vote the debt by the way, I believe has increased since this uh
That happened so with every worst moment. We also have a best moment, right?
You can't have the worst without having the best
Here come the nominees for best gamer moment of the year
And you know, it's supposed to be gamer moments if I can't read an analog clock. That's not a gamer moment
that's me having the intelligence quotient of a four-year-old you're the nominees or
Best gamer moment of the year. There you go. Satan. It's time for you
I'm gonna die. I'm gonna die
Oh
Okay, get fucking decimated get absolutely decimated I don't even know what your name was
I don't I i'm not even gonna read it. I'm not even gonna read it
That was like I was about to get into a car accident
I gotta push I have to press this to move out of the way
Use both hands and foot dog next to my chin
I'm getting tired. It's tiring me
Well, I understand
Whoa
Oh
What am I supposed to jump?
Holy shit
Somebody said this is not impressive at all
It's like a regular level
Is that record on that level? What's the record on that level? I want it
What's the world record on that level without terms assisted bots?
And then they're gonna wrap around okay, I got it ready three two one
Okay, here they come. Oh shit. Oh my god
Used slow doesn't count
It's over on a tower i'm all right. I'm all right. I'm all right. I'm okay. Okay
Okay, this is gonna be really hard one
It's not t's either. Uh, does anyone want to start with w?
Yes, yes, it's true that it could be could be that
I got it. The word was world. Okay. Uh, Simon says what the fuck? Okay, Simon says
Get it get up. It's okay. Your knee is gonna be fine, honey. Your knee is gonna be fine, honey
Oh
He's got one hp come on come on put all of your destructive power
So somebody made a pretty good point
Uh, which is actually very funny half of those moments
Are just sort of normal things that like a good gamer could do
but for us, uh, it's
Spectacular
the winner
Of best gamer moment of the year
I'm gonna pat myself on the back for this one. I think I did pretty well in the streams two of them, right?
Uh, the winner is
hades
Beating hades go not beating hades, right?
Killing hades the boss on my third attempt. That was 26.6 percent of the vote
I mean, I think come on that that's worth a little bit of celebration
Just a little
Uh 26.6 percent and then rhythm heaven shooter pog was 14.9 percent
Also, I think I gotta give myself some credit for that one and then binding of eyes a god build
To kill mega satan with 10.8 percent of the vote was in third place cat sucks at hades
Uh, we have the final two categories here before the rumble and we have about 45 minutes before the ball drops in new york
Perfect timing because everybody is from new york on the rumble. So that's good
the last two categories of the year are
Worst stream of the year and best stream of the year two categories that could be a lot in them
I don't want to accidentally leak who wins. So we're gonna start with worst stream of the year
There's a few I could think of but I don't want to uh spoil anything for those that may not have seen
Uh, so here we go. Here comes the worst streams that I did in 2020 according to you
I didn't do it supposed to kill these guys
Impressed
Did I crash oh shit, I think it just needed a few minutes to load dude, this looks fine
I'll be back. Give me five minutes fucking turn the computer. I'm just turning the computer up
I'm not even gonna turn the stream up. I'm gonna just i'm just turning off the computer. I'm restarting. I can't even restart my computer
Okay, don't buy this game
This is horrible. Yes. I know this game is absolute utter dogshit
I know but i'm at disc four and i'm gonna i'm gonna win
No, I have to go back on full disc
I can't I don't remember. I don't remember. I can you imagine making this game?
Oh, just stop don't like talking shit and just do it. I'm not i'm telling you right now
I'm not going back and doing this shit again
I would rather eat my own hand
I'd rather you cut my fucking hand off and put it in the oven and cook it at like 350 for two hours
And I eat it on stream i'd rather do that than go back and do
the like last 45 minutes
Jeremy you can't play beautiful joe. You haven't played vr in so long. Why won't you play vr beautiful joe goes?
brr
Okay, I have to pay attention. Why do you guys hate this game?
Why does everybody hate this?
What this game is like fun and exciting and there's like characters and what you guys hate this game
Do you want me to do it again?
Don't kill them kill them kill them kill them
No
Oh
Get this away from my house
He's training psych with somebody's dead
Wait, what?
No, it's the tournament
Don't kill each other
Okay, if a stream is the worst stream of 2020 guaranteed
We can remove it from the list, right? Like yeah, this is everything else is an honorable mention at this point, right?
Oh shit, I fell through the world
Oh
Please tell me you can see this
I'm killing everybody. He was torturing his fans
Oh fuck. I keep I keep like laughing. I was too much today. I'm gonna be in pain
Somebody likes this here
Somebody likes this. I know they do
All right. My tongue's fucking fucked up. Come on. Say it. Oh my god muck ass
minus 300 viewers
Look at it
600 people left. It's my fault
No, that's that's on them
Guys for all you know, 600 people just got like a fucking call and they had to get on a phone call
They had to go to like the doctor or something or they were going to eat dinner or it was not to go to bed
You don't know it's my fault. I had nothing to do with it
So yes, um, so hold on there we go. So yes, sometimes I have bad streams
Sometimes they can't all be good ones
They they can't all be good
Sometimes you have to have a couple of stinkers but uh by
No, you don't sometimes sometimes sometimes
Sometimes i'm gonna let that slide
It's your birthday
The winner of the worst stream of the entire year of 2020. I mean, okay
If it's the worst game of 2020, does that matter?
Does that actually matter too? Like what if it's the worst fucking game that came out in 2020 watch dogs legion?
Uh at 38.5 percent of the vote watch dogs legion
Took that by a lot, but the died allison counter was at 31
so
Really like almost 70 percent of the entire vote was those two streams
So you have to imagine that those are probably the worst ones
Uh ftk 2 was there at 13.2 percent way lower than the 31 from died allison counter. So 70 percent of you thought those two
I could probably agree you did tearless after watch dog. You did you did you did tearless after watch dogs
Did I but only like a few minutes though, right an upset. Well, then it's died allison counter. That's the next one
All right. We've made it to the final category of the evening and it's
It's the big one. It's the one that's worth all the money. This one's worth all the cash all the money
Best stream of the year i'm gonna peek might surprise a lot of you
This is probably going to surprise a lot of people here
It is going to be a lot of people that might be angry a lot of people that might be upset at this
Uh at what has happened here. We'll see it was very it was very contested
We'll just say that here are your nominees for best stream of the year
Hey german on eight five here
Moving stop. No
How do I get what I kick it?
Hey
Try to keep my eye on the road son
Son, we got a problem here son up son
Is that the new waiter that we just hired?
I think it is
Pulling a car. Okay
Yeah, when you guys come back remember it's me eat a fat fuck irl
Come back next week and i'll shake my stomach around for you boy after drinking three gatorades
All right. Now let's play a fun game called chase me
I'm not the dog. This is not like i'm not the dog if you just got in here like a minute ago
Sometimes we do this
And he'll just sit here all day
Hey
Okay, yes, we're gonna get you that new trailer
Come on
Hey, jimmy the fish sends his regards
And the fish family, I can't do it. I'll do all the 30
Oh shit
I have to stand here
This is him. He's gonna bust on he's gonna bust on it
Oh my god. Oh, no
Oh
Mr. Green you can't just throw up on the table. I know I can't
Mr. Green, you can't take your shirt off
I'm just gonna hold it. I'm gonna hold it
It's blue. What do you mean? It's blue
Frk
Fuck it. Fuck it. Don't do that
Okay, press, uh press and hold it
I've got an omega symbol. I don't know what that is. I don't know what that is. I'm not kidding
I don't I don't fucking know what that is. No omega symbol for real. I don't know what that I have no idea what that is
I have no idea. No, no, you know, you know, what a fucking omega symbol is
I didn't I played like the first four hours
I played that wasn't in the god of war game
Oh
Yeah, roger i'm up here in the channel five news chapter
And we're getting word that there seems to be some type of altercation going on outside of the mcdonald's
Not entirely sure exactly why this is starting
But i'm getting sources in my ear right now that apparently somebody threw mcchicken out the window
Get up, it's okay. Your knee is gonna be fine, honey. Your knee is gonna be fine, honey
Turn it off turn it off turn it off
I'll take a large number nine, please
once
All right, I gotta go i'll gotta go all the way around
Oh my god, oh my god
What's the uh, what was the what's the context of the of like the memes in the background
I forget why well during mario sunshine. Why was that happening?
Like the open up like the why are you running? But wait, why do I what was I doing that for?
Oh is autoplay because I was jingling the keys right? Okay, right, right, right. Right. Well, anyways
The best stream of the year apparently
Oh, this is gonna be contested people are not gonna be happy about this
Well, let's just see what happens
the best stream of the year
goes to
With 27.4 percent of the vote
Long drive is the winner of the best stream of the year
Beating the auto stream
with
19.2 percent of the vote
Beating all those those two beat casino inc at 11.7
11.7 percent for casino inc. They're your top three the auto stream. Um
Didn't win a lot of people thought that was gonna happen
Uh long drive with 27.4 percent
And I learned something about this channel
I've got to play more games with just fucking cars in them
Just need to be able to drive a car right up to the top of the list casino inc and third
I was surprised by that. I was um
So that's it for the new year's awards
But we now have the main event of the evening
What are we what we're about to do right now is finish the germa rumble 2020
With the actual rumble 30 participants the first rumble that has been on this channel in like two or three years
And i'm really happy that it could be done and be here for you guys to watch
Because i'm gonna enjoy it too. I'm gonna be watching right here
So let's take one more break before we're gonna count the the ball down too
We have like about 30 minutes that might actually happen in the middle
Of the game, so we'll see i'm gonna be right back one more time and when I come back
Rumble will begin see you guys in just a few minutes. Okay, so it is time for us to do
The rumble 30 participants enter only one can win
Hope you're all prepared
Maybe gotten another snack or
And I gotta actually pay attention here because the ball is probably gonna drop in the middle of this rumble
So I need to be able to have like a timer out here. Here we go. Give me a clock
All right. I have access to a clock
I do not want to show the game right now because it will spoil everything
So i'm not going to do that
I'm just gonna turn it on. Uh, if I can hold on a sec
I think i'm gonna have to resize the window
Let's see
Oh, come on
There we go. Okay. I need to get down here and turn the volume up because you guys can't hear it
There we go
Okay
All right. Let's go
Are you ready?
It is time the time has come
For the rumble portion. I'm about to turn it on in three
two
One
Here we go
Ladies and gentlemen, welcome back to the wrestling portion
You know the rules
If you get thrown over the top rope you are eliminated
There is no re-entry and you have a random number
He will now explain everything I just explained
Superstars occur when a superstar is thrown over the top rope with both feet landing on the floor
The last superstar in the ring he's not even talking
Animatron up here and somebody's doing that from the booth upstairs
So who are the first two contestants in the 2020 rumble?
I don't know. We're about to find out. Oh, that would be the cheers to ucd
Gonna need some of that crowd
Hopefully does a great job
He's really hoping that he the crowd will get behind him for a change
Not him needing to get behind other people
with his audio tape
Cheers to you
We believe in you
But you're number one
So you probably won't do it
I will be shocked if you do cheers to you. Good luck to you
in this competition
So who is number two?
First two into the ring at the first moment of the rumble
Here it comes
Are you ready?
They're looking for the next contestant. I don't know where the next contestant is
Where why are they looking for the next contestant? They're supposed to come down
Well, no, everyone's excited. Of course they're excited
Because that's the mcdlt briefcase guy
Nailing all the way from 1981
During the pinnacle of the mcdlt
The guy in the front row that goes down drops to one knee with a briefcase in his hand and looks over and says cool cool
hot hot
incredibly powerful
And apparently incredibly sweaty
There's the mcdlt briefcase guy
I'm talking quarter pound of beef
Why is he out of the ring?
Did he just eliminate himself?
There's a serial killer behind those eyes. Well, I don't know much about that
I I just know that they're the two that start
USA here we go. Ladies and gentlemen, welcome to the germa rumble 2020
New year's eve don't let oh, come on mcdlt is my favorite character
Mcdlt guys my favorite character don't get eliminated instantly. Oh my fucking god
Why?
Oh, he's my favorite character
Favorite character somebody get here and just eliminate cheers to you. Oh, it's the pencil
The pencil is in the 2020 rumble. How is it possible?
the most hated character
The pencil was in the rumble
It's been like four years since we've seen the pencil
And cheers to you as just has so much power so much strength and nobody can even touch him so far
Oh my goodness a huge clothesline onto the pencil
We're gonna fill this ring up a little bit here. Someone's coming in at about 10. Good sweeping kick to the groin there
pencil has
Starting to dominate
And of course glue man coming in next
Glue man is your number four
There he is
With all of his glory
With his boston celtics boots
As the pencil rakes his eyes glue man now stuffed into the corner
Takes two three punches. It didn't even get a chance to show everybody
Now he's gonna reverse it cheers to you taking a breather here
After instantly eliminating my favorite character can the pencil be removed pencil is a former champion of the rumble, by the way
Really important for you to know. I think they're gonna double team
They are not going to double team
Dr smoochson coming in next at number five
as they're gonna oh
What?
No, that doesn't count. Is glue man eliminated
Okay glue man is not eliminated
Dr smoochson comes in we now got four competitors into the rumble
A lot of you guys probably would hate to see the pencil win again. So would I
The crowded ring here it comes who is going to be number six
Toss him over toss him over. Oh, it's germa thing
germa thing
Being eliminated germa thing coming in from the game the thing see if we can get a good
View of his face glue man. You're never gonna win man
Glue man's just never going to win
We all have to be completely honest with ourselves. He's just he's a lovable loser
I'm sorry glue man
It doesn't matter if I give you a hundred in every step. You're gonna get thrown out in the first five minutes
Cheers to you is still holding strong
well germa thing
Maybe not for long though. We'll see
I can't believe i'm seeing I cannot believe what i'm seeing right now
Gabe newell is coming in next and they're gonna double team eliminate him possibly
Cheers to you looking and he's got a valve index on he didn't
Instantly eliminates dr smoochson. Gabe newell is back and he is angry
For not being invited for the last three or four years in a row
showing off that index
Dr smoochson taking a huge. Oh, what is he doing?
Uh, dr smoochson dr smoochson just breathes in his own hand. Okay, that was weird
But gabe newell is looking for redemption in this rumble
If you remember the pencil and gabe newell
Had a huge rivalry and it looks like it's going to continue here as he gets dropped onto the top turnbuckle there
Number eight coming in is jigsaw with the gas the jigsaw doll
Derma thing on the edge of the rope there germa things gonna get eliminated. Oh, he's naughty holds on for his dear life
Pencil is going to eliminate. Oh, it's it's good
See his face
Cheers to you is still in it. He was the first competitor by the way
He got instantly gassed. He was coming to exit number nine. We got pac-man
Pac-man has entered the rumble
Gabe newell is still
Doing very well
Still got good green health
If I were him, I would go over in that corner. I would open up half-life alex and I would start chapter one
What a great game that wasn't what a great thing going after pac-man's back here
We're gonna have six competitors in the ring. And of course long drive dad is gonna make an appearance. He won best stream of the year
Why wouldn't long drive dad make an appearance
Can he sweep another category?
Called winning the rumble
big ddt there
Rings getting crowded. Yeah, it is cheers to you still in it
Big right hook onto long drive. Are they gonna fill more people in here?
Do not let this rivalry end this way game
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, it can't end like this
It can't end like this
Oh game newell holds on for dear life as travis touchdown comes in
Making his way in
Can't wait for that new game and he'll be playing that new game as travis touchdown comes on in cheers to you
Did cheers to you is gone
Long drive dad has eliminated cheers to you the longest person inside the ring so far
He made it 30% of the way through
It's sorry
He didn't win
Because now gabe newell has got long drive dad using the groin drop long drive. That's gonna get tossed up by gabe newell
He's got extra strength so far and who's coming in now this is
fortnight jimmy's coming in next
fortnight jimmy on his way in
as
As gabe newell and the pencil both try to eliminate long drive dad
We were talking shit and he's ready to go
It doesn't matter
I mean, it doesn't matter. I mean, he's he's he's only 13 and he really shouldn't be in here with a bunch of grown like
44 year olds and like 29 year olds, but um, like whatever
It's okay
It's a full ring right now
Reversal by germa thing onto germa pencil. That's not a germa pencil. That's just the pencil he sucks
No eliminations somebody has to get eliminated
That's a fake up from germa thing if i've ever seen one. I told you
Long drive dad's going out right here. No, he got distracted by travis touchdown long drive lives again to see another minute here
Fortnight jimmy like in math class
Through his pencil down after getting a 100 on it long drive dad. He's dealt with he's here. He has kids of his own
He's upset about that one
He has a dad for god's sake. No, he can't eliminate him
As germa 985 enters the arena, but no long drive dad cannot
Eliminate fortnight jimmy but germa germa with a full body cast on
2020 has been a little rough on germa 985, but he still has got the strength of at least 10 people
He still has the strength
long drive dad
Long drive dad needs to be
Just drops down an elevator shaft germa 985 you weren't gonna win man. You're at like 60% still
Travis touchdown now is in a lot of trouble with gabe newell
Travis touchdown is stuck on the ropes. Somebody get travis touchdown out of here
I can't man
Fortnight jimmy's just
Long drive dad in the corner the right hand side corner travis touchdown trying to get rid of him
No, he cannot do what is necessary to throw him over pacman still with a lot of hp
Lots of health still
Germa thing's been in here for a long time
Gabe newell's been in here for a long time
And somebody else is about to enter while gabe newell's and nancy drew's coming in hot here
Earlier this evening nancy drew
Won the crew battle
Drew crew prevailed and obviously she's celebrating for it
big suplex here
On fortnight jimmy by germa thing
Yeah, drew crew has taken a few wins today and that's it for fortnight jimmy germa thing freaked out
And then another elimination gabe newell just destroys long drive dad people are gonna be really upset by that one gabe newell on the hunt here
Maybe going for a second elimination in a row
Nancy drew with a big boot getting some taunting by gabe newell
i'm, not sure what what he's doing here, but he's
Maybe they're gonna work together and try to eliminate travis touchdown while germa thing's in a lot of trouble
An incoming nexus from lord of the rings
You know him as the dwarf
Here comes gimli
Nancy drew that's a really bad place to be right now. You don't want to be taunting up there
And my axe and my what's going on with his hair his hair is a life of its own
Big maneuver big double punch into the elbow drop right on the top of the skull
Gabe newell is just working on to gimli
For some reason gabe newell has it up with the lord of the rings
Huge elbow drop wait what?
pac-man has been eliminated
pac-man has been eliminated from the rumble and travis touchdown might be right after
Oh, no
Gabe newell has just been eliminated by germa thing and so has travis touchdown. We're getting down
To the to the few here
Nancy drew you got to get rid of nancy drew she's currently running on the high
Of her victory with the drew crew
I think gimli and germa thing have to work together and get her out of here
Unfortunately, gabe newell could not get the redemption that a lot of you think he may have deserved
It's okay his wall dad's coming in an older competitor from the last rumble
Wall dad going right. Oh, no, what a reversal by nancy drew. What is germa thing doing?
He's just pulling his hair
He's not gonna just
He is wild he is very wild and untamed is gimli gonna get dropped here
No, not quite not quite
next competitor is
Of course a jar of mayonnaise one of the most delicious snacks one of the most delicious additives you could possibly put on any food product
good on
French fries, it's good on turkey sandwiches. It's really good in tuna if you make like a tuna sandwich
Jar of mayonnaise it'll in a little goes a long way by the way, you don't have to use a whole lot
It's really good on some other stuff, too. It's good. Well, hold on. We got some action here
Gimli is about to eliminate germa thing is wall dad gonna let this happen. He is there he goes
That is the end for germa thing and here comes a pasta italiano chef from casino ink
Fuck somebody said fuck nancy
pasta italiano chef
You don't know they've had plenty of uh, plenty of really bad things happen to the restaurant into them always the subject of
attacks and
uh mob hits but here now to try to
Use some of their own firepower
That was a really really big move by the jar of mayonnaise and bf bugleberry is now number 19 coming in
Please don't all of you leave
Oh, yeah
Going right for wall dad. It's gonna be instant. Yeah, there he goes
That was very violent from bf bugleberry
Trying to get rid of the jar of mayonnaise nancy drew and bf bugleberry working together
And nope, it's he's very thick. He's very full of vitamins and minerals
You can't just get rid of mayonnaise that quickly don't pour it down the drain either
Throw it in you gotta like scoop it up and throw it like the trash and stuff. It can't go down the drain
Beanbag sonic has just entered the rumble and he's grown up now. He's not just a little shit anymore. He's a huge
muscly
fully evolved level 10
Monster rancher monster. It's been quite a while since we've seen beanbag sonic
He's been training and there goes the pasta italiano chef by gimli gone almost as fast as he came in
And here comes mr. Green
What is the jar of mayonnaise doing mr. Green coming in?
Looks like he lost his pants
In a game of poker, but he's here
Bf bugleberry gets dumped over and nancy drew gets eliminated. Oh no
I had high hopes for nancy drew. I thought she was going to go a long way
But mr green is on an absolute tirade here
He was so strong
He just picked up a level 10 monster rancher fully developed monster and just drew it like it was a fucking piece of cheese
Gimli is still sticking around. Look at that health though. Not doing well
Oh, nope. What are they doing?
What was that?
And here comes chuck e cheese at number 22
Big power bomb on mr. Green from the jar of mayonnaise chuck e cheese
Everybody's favorite rat. Well, not everybody's favorite rat. I don't not really I don't think anyone
Favorite rat I could probably name a few that go in front. Um, jerry from ratatouille
Giant rat that makes all the rules. Um
Tom no jerry from tom and jerry
Well, it's from walson grommet. There's that one. Uh, there's that one rat short. It's a mouse whatever
Welcome chuck e cheese to the rumble. I hope we get instantly eliminated and murius is at number 23
We're getting down to the final eight
Final seven coming in here
Oh boy, would you love to see a murius gerba rumble 2020 win?
I'll tell you that's a good new year's eve present for me one of my favorite characters
That chuck e cheese is getting stomped by gimli gimli by the way still in here. There goes mr
Green by the jar of mayonnaise jar of mayo looking to be a pretty high seed here
And also representing the wink dinks here comes germa wink saw him lose earlier tonight, but that's okay
Still coming in to represent for the rumble
No, god damn it gimli fuck
No, why he's so good
All right
There's only one opportunity where i'm gonna say chuck e cheese is better than the lord of the rings and it's right now
This is the only time you'll ever hear me say that
Get rid of gimli. He's doing too good
Darmaio is just taking a little breather here. Who's number 25?
seaman
Here he comes from the dream cast seems to be also a full-grown adult and not just a little baby. Uh tadpole anymore
Beanbag sonic with a big suplex
Yeah, this is what you gotta get rid of gimli. You know, you get hey dink. Hey you fucking dink
Get rid of gimli together. He's he's like the top seed right now. You want it chuck e cheese?
Come on, go for it. Go for it. Go for it
G red is there he goes. Thank god for chuck e cheese
G red from gotcha force
Is the next competitor if he comes in I for some reason he's not coming down
Somebody needs to like turn the toy on
There he is the strongest of all the gotcha bots we have g red
Okay already already showing that he is very strong. Okay. He's like god
The gotcha force has made it to the germa arena
He's also
Weirdly enough weirdly enough. He is about four inches tall
But in the germa rumble universe, he is like eight feet tall and what's that? I see at number 27
What's that I see number 27 that is catboy germa catboy germa
Making their appearance for the first time in the germa arena just trying to see
Who to attack who to scratch who to bite at?
Going right for beanbag sonic. What an excellent idea catboy germa. No gets reversed
C man got your red
Catboy germa beanbag sonic a jar of mayonnaise and chuck e cheese
Are your potential final competitors potential final competitors?
Catboy germa's got the upper hand on beanbag sonic beanbag sonic. Yeah, you got it. You gotta do something
You gotta reverse it. There's a reversal there chuck e cheese. I just like choked himself
Double punch there onto they're just punching each other who comes in at number 29
Oh number 28 that would be
An andy mark robot from the carnival stream also dressed as the goat to andy mark for all your robot needs
You got a project going on andy mark. They're the ones
Coming right into the jar mayonnaise. They both have the same like color scheme
This is going to get really interesting because this is it after two what the hell is going on
Jar mayonnaise has a bunch of awesome moves catboy germa. No did not fall off of the top ropes and germa's germa's dump truck
One of the final competitors we could see an upset here
This could be very upsetting. Oh gotcha red coming in and there goes the jar mayonnaise unfortunate very unfortunate
But there he is. Why did the gotcha red just run over the ropes to eliminate himself?
No, he's still in what was that catboy germa into the end of the turnbuckle as chuck e cheese now trying to get some work done
Germa's dump truck gotcha red. Holy shit. It's almost midnight
Uh, what time is it? Wait, wait, wait, wait. It's almost midnight eastern
I don't even have the song queued up
The ball's dropping right now catboy germa playing to the crowd is the boss gonna drop like right now here it comes here it comes
Here it comes. Here it comes. Did andy mark just got eliminated. Oh, no the andy mark robot
The power of of a hundred asses
No gotcha red still in the fight and is it new year yet? Not yet. Not yet. Not yet about 35 seconds
One of these is going to be the winner of your 2020
Rumble, you understand one of these is your winner
Catboy germa trying to get seaman into the corner. No, he throws him right into gotcha red
five seconds
three
two one
Happy new year everybody
And the final contestant of the night is juggles the greatest streamer
Juggles the great is your final competitor
Looks like he's got a full belly
Sitting in his underwear
And who did catboy germa just eliminate? Who just got eliminated?
Seaman just got eliminated by catboy germa and goodbye catboy germa gotcha red with a major big elimination there
A high hope for catboy germa, but it didn't happen
Unfortunately
And juggles the great comes right in against a ddt and germa's dump truck is just like splitting that ass right on the turnbuckle
He don't care
nice twisting arm flexing smash glass breaking attack
Onto chuck e cheese as gotcha red juggles the great it's going to be shaking him up here over the top turnbuckle
No, I don't think he can do it. He's not strong enough
Not strong enough
Gotcha red is still holding on for dear life
And he still has pretty decent health
His health is pretty good
It's going to be really hard to eliminate gotcha force g red
Greatest game cube game ever made and it's also the most expensive
It's like three hundred dollars to buy that game goodbye beanbag sonic. That's it. That was such an opportunity
That's such a disappointment huge disappointment beanbag sonic is out
This looks like it's going to come down
to
g red and somebody
Juggles the great going for a big punch not enough to knock him down though chuck e cheese
Just overhead through
Wait, what he just did it twice
He just pulled him back yonked him back and did it again
Your final three competitors are chuck e cheese gotcha red and juggles the great this is anybody's fight here
Oh, no
Gotcha red with a big comeback. He's gonna dump him g red
Is he gonna just sit there and let him do it or is he gonna break it up? I don't know
No, he's it's not enough to dump chuck e cheese
Here it is being back sonic in the background. Here are your final three who could be crowned the 2020 champion of the 2020
Derma rumble chuck e cheese is gonna get dumped here and it's gonna be it's
No, is he gonna let him do it? Is chuck e cheese gonna fight back? Come on chuck e cheese
No, there goes chuck e cheese juggles the great and g red
Juggles the great is the last person to come in. Let's see if g red gets. Oh my god
I thought he was gonna throw him directly over the ropes
Did you see you see the momentum you see the excitement in that grab?
He's gonna prove to everybody once and for all
That this was worth streaming
And then it was a great game. Is he gonna do it?
Can he dump him? Can he dump juggles? Is g red going to win the rumble? No, it's not enough juggles with the reversal
Oh, no, he's getting slow
He's slowing down. It's gonna take a miracle big belly to belly suplex, but juggles is red, too
Uh-oh, he's going for the fucking belly shake
Or he's going for the human brick
Oh
That's three belly shakes three belly shakes in a row, but wait a minute
Wait a minute
he
He reversed it
huge clothesline
Gotcha red. He's got only two percent battery left on his fucking phone. Please plug it in for god's sakes. You're killing us
I'm sick of you sending me screenshots with four percent battery, dude, please
Could this be the end?
Big reversal by juggles. Oh, no. Oh, no. No. No. No, can he he's no
He's still holding on for dear life
G red has no hp left. He's just floating there
It's gonna happen. It's over
It's over
No
No, you can't let him do this to you g red. That's it
juggles number 30
Bastard comes in at the very end
Oh, I really thought he was gonna pull it off too bad too bad juggles the great is your 2020 germa rumble winner
I mean, you can't come back from three
Massive gatorade fold stomach frog splashes. It's not it's not gonna happen. It's just not gonna happen
You gotta be realistic juggles. The great, uh is your winner, unfortunately
Unfortunately, I really was rooting for gotcha red
I want the catboy germa timeline
You want to do another one encore for fun. We'll just well, yeah, just for fun. Watch it. Oh gee red got robbed
They really did
encore
Just one more for fun. I just like blew my voice out. Yeah, let's do it again. Why not? Let's do for fun
I can't believe the mc teal the mc dlt briefcase guy. He got eliminated instantly
I want the mc dlt briefcase kind of win so bad double or nothing
Uh, no. No, that one is the one this one's for fun send in the green screen
Happy new year guys
Happy new year. Wait, it's just the same exact thing
Wait, it's not gonna do the same exact stuff, right? It's the same exact participants coming in
Yeah, we gotta shuffle this yeah, we gotta shuffle this so that we can't have the whole thing happen
All right. Give me a sec. What do you think should we add you want to add a couple of ritz brothers?
What do you think add add majima and kiro? Okay, we'll we'll yeah
We'll just just watch me do this. All right, so it doesn't really matter who comes in first
What do you think we'll add? I mean beanbag sonic you can do random. That's good
Participants, let's add everybody. Uh, if you add big banana, you see like this that's
Big banana go in. All right. This by the way, this is not the order. This is i'm just putting people in fortnight
Yeah, oh andy mark's already in it. Okay, let's go like this
Put the green screen in uh, the green screen is not in this game. Uh, this is i've got 2020
This is not 2018 anymore, which is kind of funny because 2018
Uh, it's probably like a better game. What about glue man? Yeah, i'll put him in
Just make him make him now leave roman reigns in
No, why?
Just make a big green guy. That's like has a hundred in all stats
Uh, jex is already in true. Let's put one of the ritz brothers in it. Let's put al ritz in it. Why not?
Please germa, please do it do it now. Where was he? Why was he not in the rumble? What?
I was wondering there are two or three people that were missing
Who else was missing from the rumble? Oh no longer counts. We didn't have all the competitors. Oh shit
All right, that's no that's accurate. I yeah, I was wondering like what way did what happened?
What happened to joel? I made joel and like put him in yeah, it's time for a rematch. I hope joel fucking wins now
oh, you know what it was it's probably because
Wink dink was not supposed to be in the rumble that was supposed to be joel because they already had their match
So yeah, that's what happened. All right, what do you obviously long drive dead? What about cat boy?
I know i'm getting to it. I'm getting to it
No roman reigns is not staying in over maxon gotta put the pencil in get gimli out gimli out
Should I throw out gimli put a majima?
Yeah, get rid of yeah, germa wink was not supposed to be there. Okay. Does this look good remove the jar of mayo
He eliminated like five people. It was really good. I think that looks good
Now just you know, just remove me for gimli seriously dlt briefcase guys 100 and what about it?
But you don't think that he's like one of the strongest people here. What are you talking about?
Is that seriously a question that you're asking put germa back in?
Remove the writs brother. All right, fine. Take juggles out. He already won. That's a good idea. That's a good point
All right travis touchdown pac-man or sam or max we'll cure you travis touchdown get the pencil out
All right, get the pencil out of here. Fuck this guy. We'll cure you in
And big banana. I think this is good. This is fine. This is all right
No, I want to watch that fucker get snapped in two. Well, this is good. What about pac-man?
Uh, we can get rid of jigsaw. He he was shitty. He came in and got eliminated instantly
We'll put uh, we'll put max instead of jigsaw. I mean it's hard to do there are too many characters here. What about murius?
Oh shit, that is like my favorite character. All right, uh, we're gonna trade. I can't trade dr
Schmoyson. I'm not getting rid of catboy derma. What are you nuts?
I don't know. I can't remove anybody get rid of the pasta taliano chef get rid of mayo. I like the mayo
It's like my favorite food. I think this is good. I think this is all right
I'm okay with this get rid of fortnight jimmy. No get gimli out of here
All right, i'm gonna here's what i'm gonna do. I'm gonna get rid of
Cure you we're gonna have only one person represent the franchise, right? We'll put murius in
Uh, we're gonna get rid of sam is not here, right? And then we're gonna get yeah. Yeah, fuck gimli get him out of here
Uh pac-man. Yeah pac-man. That looks good to me. That looks good to me. Let's go
Uh, we'll enter the turn entrance is off. We don't need it. Uh-huh. Okay. Here we go. Let's move jigsaw
No, he's dead. He got knocked over the top rope and landed on his head. He's not coming back. All right, let's go
Here comes the redo. Well, not really redo more of a an encore
Jigsaw is going to have fun in it looks like mr
Green and germa thing are the first two contestants in the ring
And in all these wwe games, uh, if you're not in the last like 10 to 15 people
You're not going to win
So enjoy the time they have in here now because they're going to be gone in about two to three minutes
But that's mr green and that's germa thing
No green screen. Well, look at he's green just imagine he was the green screen. It's usually one of the last four
Yeah, usually
Andy mark robot andy mark goat again. These are the these are the guys that did the carnival stuff
They made all the carnival robots, which were incredible
Everybody loves andy mark trying to get rid of mr. Green and they do
Nobody fucks with mr
Green
Unless it's multiple people fucking with mr. Green and he gets thrown. God damn it. I want him in like the final 10
How do I give him like extra points?
The mcdlt briefcase guy is in at number four
I mean, they all have good stats. The only one that didn't have good stats was um
Like fortnight jimmy has like under 70. I think he's the only person a hundred stats
No, he doesn't have a hundred staff dave newell at number five
You should play long drive
again
Who had the most eliminations like cheers to you?
Cheers to you eliminated at least three or four people at least ice ddt under the ropes
By the mcdlt briefcase guy
Long drive too. Well, I mean I kind of have to it won best stream of the year, but that's kind of scary
Because what if you guys thought it was so good? What if the sequel is not good enough?
What if I play that game again and stream it and it's just i'm just not it's not as funny
It's going to get multiplayer soon. Oh shit. Nice
What the hell was that?
Yeah, I feel like lightning struck. I don't know if lightning can strike twice
Uh gabe newell going for an elimination here on andy mark
Germa thing getting involved
And there's the dump. See you later andy mark
And pac-man by the mcdlt briefcase guy g red coming in
g red making the appearance for the second time almost won the
Quote unquote official one, but we can have more than one. They can be two official winners, right?
Big power bomb that was huge pac-man got ghosted
Yeah, he was gone instantly, huh bf bugleberry at number eight
You know, i'd really love to see gabe newell win. I really would he was in all the original ones
He always got so close. I'd love to see a gabe newell victory here
Or how or a catboy one?
I would love to see a germa catboy rumble victory
Catboy
Big suplex from gabe newell on to germa thing as chuck e cheese coming up at almost number 10
Hey, there was also a pretty equal chance that chuck e cheese was gonna win too. So why you tell me what's worse? And there he goes
There he's gone and my favorite characters get a fucking hundred in every step. That's how you know that it doesn't matter
He has almost 100 in every step
Are they gonna dump gabe newell?
Uh, what's the worst outcome?
chuck e cheese or
Is chuck e cheese almost won?
There goes max
Catboy is the worst outcome
The worst outcome
Every time this ticks up and it's not catboy is a higher chance at a catboy rumble victory
Or even a bf bugleberry victory because look he's still there
Chuck e cheese on the ropes max
I love max max looks so funny
Germa thing looks really funny, too
Germa 985 in his full body cast. Come on out. Let's see what you can do
Am I gonna win? Can I win?
Uh
Germa thing how much health does germa thing have he's okay. He's gonna powerbomb over the top rope max is fucked
See you later
Is he gonna go for chuck e cheese too?
Oh, I don't know
Dr. Schmoyk's i'm coming to number 12
good doctor
Germa thing has pretty low hp, but he's still there
Just hammering on the back of chuck e cheese right in his spine
Dump him dump him get rid of him
Get chuck e cheese out of here right now because no get like get yes, please. No, okay. It didn't work
Yes, it is. They're both trying as hard as they can
Did he spit on him did he just get spit on
Big scoop up by g red
Oh fuck i'm getting i'm getting a little zonked
Why are they lying on top of each other?
Why are they all lined up together?
They're lying down like sardines
Long drive dad coming in
Takes a headbutt from the biggest mouse i've ever seen
Everybody's favorite character is about to go buy chuck e cheese, of course instantly or gabe newell, which everybody likes gabe newell
Chuck e cheese you maniac
Absolute maniac the f bugler with a sliding tackle
The name drew crew is better than catboy crew
um
That's a debate that you guys can have here
Yeah
Bugleberry going on the top rope
What is he going for?
Oh my god, and I was right in my chest really
Really bugleberry
You're gonna like you're gonna kick a man when he's down
Really?
Get him out throw him out of here
Oh
He felt my anger he could feel it
German 985
Letting the adrenaline take over
Little does everybody know that after this adrenaline wears off
He's gonna be off for about three and a half months
But at least he might be able to pull the victory
Is uh, dr smugson going down what just happened to gabe newell?
Is that a punch or is it a
He's just punching him in the face over and over again
Can I get rid of chuck e cheese too?
I'm I'm fucking angry right now guys
Look at my face
I mean absolute business right now
Holy shit
No, no g red's putting a stop to that right now
Oh, it's good. He's just dumb. He's gonna dump me. He's gonna dump me gabe newell, please get up and help me
All right. Okay. Come on gabe get up and help
No, no, I mean like help me. I'm gone. See you later. Still fought it off somehow
You're kidding me
Why is it just standing there?
Oh shit
Gabe newell has been eliminated by a huge lariat by long drive down and here comes joe
varg skeletal
Big elimination on g red first time we've seen a crossover here on this channel representing vine wrestle joel
Vine sauce joel
I don't know what happened. That was like too many are they double teaming?
Germa thing is still in this
Germa 985 is also still in this
And so is dr smugson who's been here for a while as well
Big slap by germa thing onto joel
He's looking for a place to dump me. That's what this is
Oh, no
No, no, don't let the doctor eliminate you
No one's throwing me out man. I'm staying in this for a long time big stunner
Can't capitalize but they cannot follow up with it and then pasta taliano coming in
Chef from that delicious fine establishment
Just flipped up like a pancake
Juggles coming in if juggles is 30 again. I'm gonna be pissed. I'm gonna be so mad
Murius the cow from the drew crew. I mean the moo crew dome. What happened?
Joel get just a what?
Why was that like times two speed? That was weird
Joel just got eliminated by dr smugson
to a thing
With another attempt on long drive dad
Uh, well, thank you joel for joining us
At the germa rumble 2020
Bean bag sonic coming in next i thought joel i thought joel was gonna be in it for a while
i'm surprised
Can't like stick him with those horns
Dr smugson completely misses
Completely. I don't even know what he was punching but and now he's in trouble being back sonic in a good spot by the way
Coming in
um, okay
Okay, goodbye
He just ran
Pasta taliano is gone
You threw him so hard that he is continuing to run by himself on his own
Jesus
Bean bag sonic absolutely crushing it right now eliminates
two people in a row
There goes germa 985
eliminated
Four fan favorites are in the ring right now. Just want to make that clear
There goes long drive dad and in comes glue man at number 18
Is this the opportunity for glue man to at least get a win here? Is this the opportunity?
So far not so good
This is the spot you want to be and it's going to be one of these people here
All right, you know what? All right, here you go. I think a bean bag sonic's gonna win this I think
Really good position just kind of just beat up the horse the cow
Travis touchdown is number 19 still no sign of germa cat boy
which
I think is concerning a lot of you
By the way, anybody see travis touchdowns shirt get a good look right now
Anybody know what that is?
That is cat boy germa on that shirt. Yes, you are right
Here comes majima number 20 good place to be in
Germa thing is gone
Big right hands by murius onto bean bag sonic looks like majima's gonna finish the job with some shin kicks
No, he's gonna get from behind glue man
He's gonna keep just punching him over and over and over again in the corner
What did you do
Big but
He's I can't even talk
He jumped over him and went way too high and flew over the ring
There goes travis touchdown majima with elimination
Uh, but big big banana bro
Is in here in a good place
blue man, though
glue man's ear glue man's ear it could be
Jax is coming in at 22 nice backflip by majima. Holy shit. Did you see that? That was unbelievable
We got jex though
Why is jex already at like half health?
Did he fall down on the way in here?
Big banana bro looks like he's gonna be throwing up majima
No, they both want to get rid of majima
Very strong character very strong competitor
Not gonna happen this time jar of mayonnaise is coming in at 23
Oh boy
Y'all want this to be the cannon one you sure
A jar of mayonnaise coming in
Drew crew that's possible juggles is also possible. No, he's not he's gone
Get mayo out of here
The more that I look at that container the more that I want to eat something with mayonnaise on it right now
fortnight jimmy number 24
The more I look at that jar. I just want like mayonnaise on so I want like a turkey sandwich with mayo all over it
the backflip shin hit
verb noun
I'm just saying i'm thinking that the the body part that had happened and where they hit
chin head hit
There goes majima by fortnight jimmy
Catboy germa at number 25. It's possible
It's possible for a catboy cannon win
Too early. I don't know. It could it could whoever comes in over the next five
It's very possible
Catboy eliminating murius. Oh, no, there he goes murius my favorite character
Besides mcdlt briefcase guy
Still going after fortnight jimmy
Nice reversals from banana bro
What is that? Is that a fanny pack on his back?
There goes jex eliminated by glue man
Blue man's year could be this year. He could win at least one and even if it's the encore
Stop the catboy anything but catboys stop the catboy
I don't know. We'll see we'll see. Uh-oh fortnight jimmy's in trouble
He's gonna get tossed over by germa catboy. Look at the health on catboy germa, by the way
Oh
Jara mayne still can't get eliminated even with two people trying to push him down
Holy shit, that was brutal
What is going on here?
Just pancaked
Glue man is on the ground in bad bad state right now wall dad coming in at 26
No protect fortnight jimmy
All right, dad going after fortnight jimmy. Let's see is glue man gonna stay in
Yeah, he is glue man's still here
It's possible. It could be the year
No, keep him in
He's gonna turn he's got he's okay
Cheers to you cd coming at 27
Uh, yeah glue man's are gonna turn to the undertaker
He's gonna get to be like 74 years old
And still be wrestling
But the difference is the undertaker won
WrestleMania like 30 times glue man has done nothing
Catboy play wall dad eliminated by
Fortnight jimmy really? Wow. Okay, that's unexpected
Oh fortnight jimmy is pissed. He's full of g fuel
He's full of fucking monster energy drinks and snickers bars
Nancy drew coming into 28. We've got two different crew. This is crew matchup rematch again
Oh
I really wanted mayo to win
If I had to pick somebody in this ring, it'd be mayo or glue man
Or nancy drew
I've seen a lot of banana bros people looking for the banana bro to win. It's possible. He's got pretty good health. Maybe he doesn't
Germa's dump truck ass is coming in here at number 29
So who's 30 who've we not seen yet?
C man. Oh shit
It is c man
Oh gimly
This ring is full
Of just memes right now
If I had to put a bet down, I'd I would put it right now on
Um, well wait, I'll wait for the last one
I don't think it's gonna be glue man. He's been in here for too long. Look at his health
It's gonna be dump truck
Just watch or nancy drew
Wait, is catboy regening health?
Yeah
Banana broke gone
Final competitor is c man at number 30. Here is one of your winners in the ring right now
Cheers to ucd glue man
Germa dump truck nancy drew forget about glue man. It's not your year. It never is
One of these will be crowned catboy. Germa has been eliminated by fortnight jimmy
Jimmy has gone nuts
I actually I think I might change my vote here. I think i'll put it on fortnight jimmy
Beanbag sonic didn't eliminate himself
Come on
All right
I think it could I think it's gonna be nancy drew
Dump truck c man cheers to you murius
One of these will be the other winner
C man wins then that that's stupid and he just comes in at 30 nancy drew cannot let that happen
Oh, no, okay
Get rid of c man
Get rid of c man. There you go work together
work together
What are you doing?
He's got the most health. Well dump truck actually has a lot of health
Holy shit
He just completely
He completely took him off guard. He wasn't even ready. He wasn't even ready
Oh my god
Oh, no
Nancy drew and dump truck are the last two
Who will win the encore?
I got my money on nancy drew. It's gonna be nancy drew. This is it
This is gonna be the end. She's gonna dump him. She's gonna dump him over. It's over
That's it
Nancy drew is your winner
of the 2020 encore rumble
Dumped the truck now. It's nancy versus juggles for the real winner. It sounds like a good idea to me
What are the rules?
Congratulations. Uh, congratulations nancy drew put him in a cage
And this is a bet. This is gonna be a big bet guys. Here comes a big prediction put him in a cage match
Hell in a cell, okay
Put him in a hell in a cell nancy drew coming in versus uh juggles nancy drew seems to have the advantage
Select arena sure why not run down high school gym here comes the person
I mean you can this is probably gonna last a little while hell in a cell this determines the real
Victor the real champion of germa rumble 2020 our predictions live right now. They are this is a big one
Go to match options
No, we're not doing big head mode. You went all in. All right, do big head mode do it
We can't do big head mode. Not right now. No big head mode. No, this is the championship
36 million on who what do you get you get? This is a major major difference here
68 percent of you guys are putting all your money on nancy drew. Okay, see if you guys are right
I'm gonna get started now. Let me bet. Oh, you gotta bet right now. You gotta use channel points man. It's closed
Let's go here comes the champion
Of the 2020 rumble nancy drew or juggles the great
main event
hell in a cell in a random rundown high school
Nice start by nancy drew didn't even wait a second kind of hard to see through this cage though underdog
Uh-oh
How do you win a hell in a cell you have to pin right?
I would laugh so hard. That was it. I would fucking shit my pants if that was seriously how it ended
Oh man, nancy drew even has better stats. It doesn't matter. Sometimes momentum is all that matters
There we go. Nice reversal
Switching it up a little bit here
What?
The silence is deafening
Yeah, it's just like, you know, these two people are kind of just throwing kind of just moving their bodies around and like landing on their backs
Health is not that big of a deal though
This is depressing
Quite the main event
Yeah, let's go
Get him
Why is there even a referee in here? Why is there a referee in here?
The fuck
That would not even hurt
You just landed on your back while holding his legs
Going for the pin. Is it possible?
Will they use the cage?
Somebody get up on top of the cage
oof
Get on top of the cage somebody climb the cage
It really is so depressing without like fans and
like
sounds besides
On the undertale ost. I think this is it for nancy drew by the way
This is it
Yeah, that's it. It's laughing the belly
You know cc's victory juggles has the momentum though
That could be it
One no one count. She just did the undertaker recovery
Come on nancy
into the cell
Not I guess not strong enough to knock him. Oh
Oh
Not good
Not good for nancy drew
What are you doing?
It can't be how it ends
Oh, this is so dumb nancy fight back
Fight back nancy
fight back
No, that's it
Juggles the great ends up winning and ends up taking the crown
Or actual germa rumble 2020 winner
Oh that what an upset 70% of you guys got it wrong
That's it
That was like the weird dog crawl
He is a superstar juggles the great congratulations
Oh, man
Do a best out of three. No, no, no best out of three
Worst character what juggles is a great character
How about super juggles versus super nancy drew?
No, I want to talk about this for just a second
so you probably noticed
that the
Awards this year. There was a lot more categories to put uh nominations in
But you didn't see a bunch of those categories
It was like another eight or nine categories that uh were not added to this particular stream
and the reason why
is
It was gonna be like too much to do
I didn't want to put a bunch of that on the editor and editors to make like 30 plus videos. So what we're gonna do
Is stalling but uh, i'm describing what we're gonna do
We're gonna do an encore awards night that are the sort of extra
Categories that's probably not gonna happen for a little while because I want people to be able to vote on it
So I would assume probably in the next like week or two. We'll do a sort of like little encore
For like an hour or so and we'll just do the other ones not like as flashy or anything
We might not even need videos for it. It'll be just fun to kind of look at it though
We'll see give us back our points
Give us back the points
I kind of like the idea. Hold on. Let's do
Let me see
I kind of want to I want to see someone so you can do like a custom match
Oh, wait, and he can't didn't they add something?
No, I want to do a table match. Who's like the strongest in here. I want to do a no not fortnight jimmy
No, no, no, we're getting away from fortnight jimmy. Well, you want catboy germa versus me? Okay, we'll do that
Catboy germa versus germa nine eight five
Oh, no, no, no against mcdlt. That's a good idea 100 fucking stats
Okay, so no against me die, but mcdlt is my favorite character fine fine fine fine fine fine fine
Look, i'm so terrible. I'm still gonna win
Catboy germa in all capitals by the way
Bets
You want to do bets? Let's go go for it. Let's do another prediction catboy germa versus germa nine eight five
I mean you saw the stats. This is going to be an absolute shit show. I lost everything
No
You lost everything
With nancy drew we said that with nancy drew. That's right. I could just come back here
And by the way, it's if you get broken through a table
You just have to go through the table. There's no pinning to whoever goes through it first
Yeah, we were in the middle of the rumble, but happy new year guys
I know that this year has like sucked
For many reasons. Let's really hope that 2021 is better
Let's put it off to a good start. You know what I mean?
Because shit was rough was really rough in 2020 catboy germa is gonna win every time
You have to you have to cosplay as catboy germa if he wins
I have to cosplay as catboy germa if he if they win
Um, i'm going up against my like broken
wrapped up body cast
Character what?
Oh, hold on a second there. Wait a minute. Let's make this interesting. Why don't we make this interesting?
Why don't we so if
If catboy germa wins, I will dress up like a catboy if germa 985 wins
You shave a billion dollars off that fucking debt. I want a billion off that debt deal a deal. We got a deal
Okay
Oh, i'm fucking ready for this one. Let's go
Let's go. Let's go. Let's go
Come on jeremy
Three two one do not lose this fucking match. No, no, don't restart
Let's go
I don't want to dress up as catboy germa. Good start germa 985
Shave a billion off this debt for the love of god. Good start. Good start. Very good start
Just throw them around the ring
Just toss them outside toss them outside toss them smash them through the table right now
Cheating what do you mean cheating? I'm not cheating you saw the stats through the table right now, please
Through the table right now
I am destroying
Oh
Right into the chest this weak point the sensitive spot
Come on come on do it do it do it do it
Catboy, I mean that was a catboy. I just hissed. I just hissed in catboy germa's face
Oh, look at me. Oh my goodness
I'm going for it. That's me saying i'm going for it. Whatever it is
Holy shit
No, no, no, no, no
No, you you're doing fine
You're doing okay
You're gonna be just fine
Just over through the table
Not much health left from catboy
Get that table germa get it in here
Do not have this blow back in your face
That's not what should be happening right now
Okay, whatever set that table up and one of you
When I say one of you I mean me
jeez
Catboy redemption incoming. No, I hope not. I really don't want to dress up as catboy germa on screen
Going for the table
Oh
Shit
Oh shit. Oh shit. Oh shit. Oh shit. Oh shit. Oh shit. Oh shit. Oh shit. Oh shit reverse it
Yeah, yeah. Yeah. No. No, that was a double reversal
double reversal
Okay, get what are you what are you doing? What are you doing?
Do not
Get up and fight
Nice reversal. This is it through the table. Do it power bomb suplex suplex to the table, please
Do something. What are you doing?
You fucking idiot
Oh my god
Just roll off the table
Good good good good right in the gut right in the gut again again do it again
Onto the table
What you didn't put them on put them on the table put them on the table do it do it. Good. Very good
This is it. This is it, right? This is it. This is it. I'm gonna win I win
Take a billion dollars off that debt right now
Take a billion dollars off right now
Bang bang bang bang bang. I win. I win. I win. I win. I win
That's one billion dollars
Ooh, and I I put a lot up for that one
I put a lot up. I was gonna dress up like germa catboy on stream the entire thing
The whole thing double or nothing. Wait a minute. Wait a minute double or nothing. What do you mean?
How does that work two billion off the debt or I have to stream two days in a row as germa catboy catboy for a year
That's not happening. It's not worth it. No, i'm not doing it. It's not worth it. I know
No, i'm sorry. I just I just tapped you a little bit. I'm not doing that. I know when to stop. That's it shave it off
Not doing that's too nope I win so many 50 million points. Oh my god double or nothing to wipe the whole thing
Oh, I don't know about that
Are you kidding me?
To wipe the whole thing the debt is clear if I win here. Can I call in a wild card?
Does it have to be germa 985 but can I call in a can I phone a friend here?
No, it has to be me. This is for all the marvels right here. It's it's me
It is me go and it has to be this high school arena. No deal. No deal. What do you mean? No deal
We're gonna have to pull this. Okay. All right. Fine. Fine. Fine. Fine. Fine. We'll pull it
Remember, this is two catboy streams in a row back to back. So this is so this
It's just is this deal or no deal. This is if I win the debt is cleared if I lose
I have to be germa catboy for two days straight. Let's go. Let's see what the people want. Okay
This is looking pretty unanimous. This is looking pretty unanimous to me
Either we put an end to the debt arc or we win
It's true
2020 we could put a close on it right now or
It might bleed into 2021 and I have to dress up as a cat person
Uh, I don't think you guys really lose here. It is set in stone is the deal is the deal
That's it
67 of the vote. It's over
This is either all in this is either two streams in a row. Okay, let's go
Go go predictions. Oh, I I didn't know we were doing predictions for this one careful on your betting
Fuck okay right at the bat. Not good
Let's go get a weapon. Just go it's an extreme rules match go get a knife and just start stabbing catboy
Just go back there go grab a bag of trash and do the danny devito
Oh my god, it can't end like this
Go get a weapon. You can take the health down very quickly
reversal
Oh fucking jesus
Don't even
Up up up up. Come on momentum
momentum
You idiot. Oh my god had you missed was point blank punch
You missed a point blank punch
Don't do a flashy move off the top turnbuckle
That's not going to do anything
You're not going to have time to do this. They're going to reverse it
It's pretty big deal though. That was a big move go get a weapon
So much riding on this
This might be the biggest bet of my online career
What are we doing?
Yeah, the cat boy's health is not going down
Um
Get something big
It's okay a bat good good right in the fucking head
Right in the head. Yep. Go on. Come on clear this shit clear this death beat beat with a bat
No
Get up get the bat. Oh
Nice pick up the bat. You're so much weaker than catboy germa pick the bat up pick up the bat you idiot
You're just being so stupid pick the bat up. Oh, man
reverse
No
Get up get up
Why are his armpits exposed? I don't know dude
Get the bat hit
No, please do not hit him
Run run away. Just run right in the head quick
Yes, good good good
Good good good again again again
What are you doing?
That was a pretty good comedy routine. It's still anybody's game right now
The health is pretty comparable. It's not a blowout in either direction
That's a big move
Pick up the bat forget about taunting finish it finish it finish it finish this
nice
All right, pin pin pin clear it clear the debt once and for all do it cat boy. He sucks
Um, don't speak so soon
Oh, no
Good dodge
Steal it steal it steal it steal steal steal steal. Good. Good. Good. Good. Good
Oh, thank god
Thank god
No
Get up get up
It can't be you're gonna get out
No, oh no
Oh, no
Oh no
Who the fuck said that?
Who the fuck said that for me to do that?
Who said that? I'm very upset with you. Oh jesus
Oh jesus christ
My god, I I can't catch a break here
career's over I
For two streams in a row, too
I don't want to do that
I can't believe I lost again
See you in 2021 guys
Where cat boy germa becomes? Uh a real
shit
Well, i'll have to figure that out
And that's probably where i'm gonna end the stream for tonight
I think that's a pretty good place to stop
oh
That was uh, that was a lot of fun
Thanks again to all the mods that really made that possible
Because this shit was not going to be possible without them
And thanks for watching everybody
Hopefully 2021 is better than 2020 was
Put on the fedora hat. Yeah, I'll get i'll get on cam. I'll get on cam
I'll get on cam put the fedora hat on I took my
Let me turn this off
It's cat boy time. I don't have I don't have the cat boy materials here. You think i'm gonna do that
How am I gonna do that?
I can't do that
Loud the game. All right, let's turn the camera back on can you see me? Why is it so bright? Uh, hi happy new year
um
2020 was kind of difficult. I
I know a lot of you know that I took like three months off
uh because I had like the medical problem stuff and
um
Obviously the pandemic was really really fucking annoying and horrible. It's still going on too
Uh, so I really really hope that 2021 can just bring so much more happiness to people because 2020 has brought
A lot of shitty times. So, uh, thank you everybody for making at least the 2020 for me fun
Uh, i've had a great time when i've been able to stream when i've come on streams and everything. So
Um, it's a bright spot for me. So, uh, thank you
Uh, i'll see you guys next year. It's already next year for some of you
It's not I gotta wait for pst though for you. I'm not gonna like not for two hours, but um
2021 will have there's a lot of streams that I was gonna do in 2020 that are gonna happen in 2021
Uh the baseball stream a couple of secret ones that I can't talk about
There's at least two or three of them that are just ready to go
uh, and i'm
Excited to try them try to try to do something and try to have fun. Uh, there were a lot of subs tonight
Um too many for me to even I just I wasn't I couldn't even keep up with them
Uh, the channel is just about to cry. It's all time high
It's almost a 12 000 subs on the channel, which is fucking unbelievable. I
Never thought I would ever deserve something like this
I sometimes don't think I do and i'm just really happy that you guys think this is fun
Uh, it's a lot of fucking people. It's a lot of subscriptions and
I'm just happy that you think it's fun. No one's ever obligated to give any money
I don't read donations anymore. So you don't have to give me any money if you don't want to but it's it's been wild and
On top of that, I hope I can spend the money that you are giving me in a good place
I hope i'm I hope i'm doing these good things with it. I hope
He oh and and and just like that he goes into the telephone booth and he becomes the redditor
Types faster than a speeding bullet arguing with people online
And a hundred community subs. Holy shit, dude, that's too many
Two that's too many. That's a hundred
From john cena. I can't even read them all I i'm use it to buy the catboy costume
A catboy costume is like from the dollar store
It's like two dollars for like the ears and then I just need to get like a skirt and a and a collar
And fishnets
Oh, no, i'm in trouble
I'm in a lot of fucking trouble
Buy a quality one you bitch
quality what a quality
Collar, this is gonna haunt me for the rest of my life. You know, this is gonna follow me forever
Remember I told you that that like germa sus face. I was like I hate that face and and that you turn it into a meme
And nothing to do with that one
I just said I didn't like the face and you made one eat you made one way more popular and way more spammable
I was gonna do like now that'd be worse face. Um, hold on a second. Uh, but anyways, yeah, I
Fucking impot. Whatever. I kind of like this. I like this look without this here
Wayne the rock just lob just gave 50 community subs. It's two. That's too much money to give me
That's an insane amount of subscriptions
Catboy made that was not part of the deal. It was not catboy made
It was just simply catboy not part of the deal
Are you trying to tack stuff on and i'm not gonna work that way. I want you to see this. There we go
Happy new year the rocking chat. Holy shit
Uh, but yeah, thanks guys
Let's let's go for 2021 over the next few months
Let's hope the world kind of can start to heal a little and get back to normal. I hope so
I don't know. I don't have a crystal ball
But it's gonna do the best I can because that's all I know how to do and that's it much love to all of you
Happy new year. Uh, we're not in pst yet, but for eastern time. Thanks a lot guys. Uh, we can go somewhere
Let's let's raid somebody it's new year's eve who's on pst. That's still streaming right now
You gotta catch like a second ball drop. Who's on pst. Is neanderth is on pst. Is she?
omega lull again
We know we do we did we did just raid neanderth who else is on pst
Oh, you know where I could send you guys. Yeah, I could send you to I could send you guys to uh to ross
Rubber ninja. Yeah, I think he's he's on pst, right?
2021 new year's vr party. Oh shit. All right. All right
Every shit i'm not gonna read that you're not gonna get one guy moment right off the bat in 2021 not gonna happen
Uh, yeah, we'll we'll go to we'll go to rubber ninja vr party. What's I was sending you to nanner nanners, but i'm saying nanners
Uh, you know that guy nanners
um
Yeah, I would send it we we will hey I we we jump around with our raids here
We jump around with our raids. I look big. Don't I don't I don't you be scared of this guy?
If he was running up to you
Yes
I have pants on yeah, I do. Okay
Uh, yeah, say hello to uh rubber ninja for me. Happy new year everybody. We'll see you. I'm probably not streaming tomorrow
I'll be back on the second. So we'll do like two three four
And we'll go from there. So see you when I see a catboy germa 2021. I'm looking forward to it. Uh, good night guys
We're gonna do the uh credits first just because I want to see how fast it's gonna roll because it's gonna be fucking crazy
So let's take a look here come the credits laser like speed. That's insane
That's
Fucking ridiculous. We're not even through the bees. That's the fastest it's ever been. I really think it might be
There's been a couple times it came close last year. Uh, new year's eve came or yeah a year ago came pretty close to
Being just that fast
You guys just spoiled the absolute shit out of me
um
I'm forever grateful. I want to give a very special shout out to all the mods. I mentioned previously like crowskin nail
Uh leather jacket
Cad grump clump vr josh
They did so much work and they helped out so fucking much for this stream. So and uh, often by manager jake
You guys know member jake a dude helped out a lot carnival producer. You guys know and uh, also the super daza too for
Just absolutely burning out
19 videos and there was a lot of other support too. It's just like thanks because it would it could not have happened without them. So
Thanks guys
And you shout out my cat. What's your cat's name?
Ola. Hey ola
Thanks for watching the stream. Hope you have a good 2021
I gotta get into the I need to start learning cat, right? I don't even know how this works
I don't even know what the meme is. I have no idea. Happy happy new year everybody. We'll see you soon
Thanks for spending your new years with me of all people
Honored that you would spend it here. Take care of yourselves
Let's hope 2021 is better
Much love to you all and i'm gonna send you guys now. We're gonna send you to rubber ninja good night everybody
See you in a day or two
Thank you for participating
And good night