Hey, what's going on guys? Jerma here with electronic shiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiii
then get out of the kitchen ladies and gentlemen DJ go hey jumps hey jumps get to the checkpoint check to the checkpoint go go jump welcome we've been waiting like forever for you welcome to Super Meat Boy that's not Super Meat Boy fuck you go oh yeah oh yes welcome to this huffin' fest this is where we jump all over the place alright so let me uh let me go back here it's a game about jumping it's a game about uh not jumping and finding your way
over platforms what the fuck oh right right okay let's see i'm going to blow through this whole game by the way just to let you know i have a feeling i'm going to get through this whole game in less than 10 minutes are you ready stop counting this music is like pumping me up man this is sick alright here we go this is the real game here we go let's do it baby boink uh dude nice day yeah it isn't a pretty nice day out except for like the weird trees that are growing instantly that's a that's highly
inappropriate but you know what let's just go oh i played this game of packs like i said it's a very in your face platformer i'm sure you're aware of that boing boing boing i like it i like the checkpoint flags that's a very big deal because that means if i die i can go right back to right there am i is this going to kill me if i touch this no it's not it's just there to like give you a seizure okay cool oh the world okay the world's moving now we're gonna we get a procedurally moving level feels bouncy around
okay whoa look out look out there we go just gotta feel the music feel the beat and you'll be all set
damn it okay okay i know what to do no i don't shit gotta go fast that's the most important thing
stay on top of it just like super meat boy oh my god i keep hitting the top of that stupid thing
i feel like i've had a rave all right be careful careful careful where am i oh press y to quick respawn oh all right i got you oh i'm losing pace here
there we go i can catch up now this is like level two oh shit i'm good i'm good oh dude quick respawn go
god damn it can i make it can i make it uh-oh is this gonna be a rage game i think so
so you keep your forward momentum when you go through those things good to know
good to know that i don't know i shouldn't have done that because i don't know what's ahead of me
there it is all right these walls are all sticky gross here comes the super meat boy platforming
i didn't even need to do that whoa whoa whoa whoa okay slow it down here i can't
i can't even breathe right now this is horrible i can't i can't do it i need to like squint my eyes
to do this jeez where am i stick on the sticky walls get on like the cream cheese come on stick
to like the cream cheese oh all right i got this what i say i was gonna beat this game in 10 minutes
i would like to uh formally retract that statement because this game is a lot more difficult
that's a bouncy thing bounce checkpoint i don't oh my god i don't think i can get used to that
lady going like oh yeah there it is there's the exit holy shit that's not the exit that was not
the exit
okay there we go oh my god give me a break i can't even tell if i'm stuck on this thing right now
oh i just can't even i can't even like i can't this fucking level with like the spinning like
windmill behind the background is really gonna make me start to throw up so i can't even
hold on i'm being quiet let's get this done
jesus how do i get up there you tell me i gotta pick one of these and it's gonna okay
this game i kid what the hell man music's great i have to yep i'm gonna hit these what stop sending
me back here that's how you kill the enemies you gotta like do like the jump smash on them you're
gonna do like the donkey kong ground pound thing when you jump in the air is that yoshi i forget
one of those like dumbass nintendo characters i don't remember which one i did it thank god all
right at least we're back to like having color in our lives and not like the spinning dumbass shit
so this is really bringing me back to memories of super meat boy when i would you know oh
oh did you hear that did you hear that
i can't concentrate yes
damn it we got like hannibal lector in the game apparently yes holy shit i didn't even know
these are stickies right no no they're they just make you move really fast and you can't stop
it's like ice thanks for telling me there was ice you son of a bitch i didn't even pay attention
to that i just fell right down oh boy oh boy oh see i'm like all like hyped up right now and
i'm just pissed pissed so those of you that remembered the super meat boy series where
like i would play super meat boy you probably will get a kick out of this series as well because
the same shit's gonna happen oh no missiles you can smash missiles with b yeah you jump and you
hit them i get you okay so as long as i don't hit you what okay oh my god i gotta be patient
stop being such a psycho and just wait a second damn no no all right waiting patiently has like
really done nothing for me just go there it is that was that was a skill shot where the hell i
were oh okay it's a procedurally another procedurally moving level fell too far behind on this one
how was i supposed to know what that thing even did there was no indication what that was even
gonna do was like my tutorial for that bullshit huh can i touch him no i can't he's an enemy okay
cool very cool no motherfucker oh there's so many swears in this video i
this like series is just a whole one big giant swear i'm sorry don't go down there man yeah no
kidding huh whoa whoa oh okay he told me not to go down there i want it i can't get it never
mind turn back right away watch out hey this like tilted world thing is really not cool
oh bring on oh yeah bring on the dubstep
yeah
yeah yeah maybe i should move to like the beat but that will that help you think
here we go i'm gonna move to the beat that didn't help at all
no more messing around no more jokes just do it i gotta make like burger boy proud
me and burger boy like no life to super meat boy so oh that was risky how am i gonna get through
this oh oh you gotta make it up you gotta make it up here before that comes out there we go
get rid of these before i go any further oh i thought i was gonna miss it to the developer
that made this game seriously thank you for the checkpoints thank you for making the checkpoints
if this game had no checkpoints my controller would have already been through the wall and this
video would have ended well these videos would have ended i'm not even sure how many there are
going to be