Hey, what's up? Sorry, I'm late. I had to come up with a funny title.
I'm sitting here going, I gotta think of a funny title. And I came up with one. I came up with one.
You think it's kind of funny? Okay, 15 minutes. Yeah, I've got to come up with a title.
I thought it was VR Josh. Nah, nah, nah, nah. Yeah, it was. What the hell is going on right now?
What is this? Why is there a purple box over people's messages? What is this?
First time chat. What is this? I don't want this. How do I delete this? Immediately. I want to delete
this immediately. Are the edibles kicking in? No, dude. All right, fucking stop. Since I turned 37,
it's been nothing but weirdo streams. I have to stop being weird. I'm going to say I'm going to be
fucking quiet for the next hour. But no, it's a new chat appearance.
Why do you sound like you don't like the real German? Well, it's because I'm a little winded
because I was running around the house. I was okay. You know that you're late for something
when you start taking corners in your own place. You don't know you understand that.
But I'm taking corners. I had to get my tea. My tea wasn't even ready. Why were you running?
I'll be fine. Just give me a minute. You made us weird. Sad. What? Don't you guys understand
that? You come observe me. You don't want to be like me. Come observe me. Be like,
I don't want to be like that guy. I'm going to do good in school. Observe. How are you? I'm
doing good. I'm doing good. Sorry we delayed a couple of days, but you know what happened.
Actually, we should go over this because it's important. So today we're going to stream here.
Listen, we're going to do Splatoon three. And then after that, Breath of the Wild.
And then on Sunday, we'll take a break from the switch. Why did you delay? I woke up on
the wrong side of the bed the last couple of days and I was like, nah, I just take care of
a few things too. All right. I literally ran around. Can I just let me just not be winded
for one second. Listen to this voice. What's going on? No, I had to. There were some things
I had to take care of. What is going on with my voice? I promise you it was not like this
five minutes ago. So what's the story Sunday? I don't know. I want to get away from the switch
for a little bit though. Is it allergy season? It actually might be. Did you hear that? I just fake
sniffed. You just implanted that in my head. Did you hear that? I hope you did. Did that come
through? I was like, oh, you know, maybe, maybe, um, he's allergic to streaming now. All right.
Yeah. We're going to play Splatoon three. Let me tweet though. That's good. Okay. Um, I
don't really know how to play Splatoon. It started with motion controls and I turned that off.
I did the tutorial and I made my squid here. Look, I'll just show you whatever.
Apparently this you can make different. Um, hold on. Can you guys hear it? There we are.
I don't, I don't know. I don't know how any of this works. This is, this is my character
and this is, uh, are these players? Are they? They are. Okay. How's that? Wait. So this,
this is a player right here. Why, why are they NPCs? It's not in real time. Uh, okay. Okay.
All right. So, so where do I go? I took them. I took off. I don't want to do motion controls.
I don't want to do it. I'll be okay. Let me be very, very upfront with everybody. Um,
I installed Splatoon three and made this character and then never opened it again.
God, it's, it's had to have been at least three weeks. It's had to have been at least two weeks,
at least I don't, I have no idea. All right. Go to the menu. Lobby stages. Oh, okay. Regular
battle. Anarchy battle. What's salmon run? Turn on drawings. You coward story mode to salmon run.
Yes. Yes. Yes. How do I do this? I should do this right now. No, this is definitely like
hard mode. I'm not doing hard mode right now. All right. Let's just do lobby. How do we look
plastic today? I'm, I mean, I don't feel plastic. Welcome to the lobby. It's your portal to online
battles and where you stash all your gear. As you splat forth and online battles, you'll level up
and earn cash. Why level up and get cash? So you can access a gear and some battle modes are
restricted to players at a higher level. Okay. Why don't you check out the battle pot? Okay.
Less chat, more splat. That's what I mean. Oh, when you play online, your nickname and player
data may be made public. All right. That's about this way. Okay. That's those taunts. Listen,
let me just do a regular fight. I'm going to be the literally bottom, uh, bragging person,
but that's fine. Okay. Bro, what's your haircut? Uh, the haircut is a 37 year old man that has not
been to the hair salon in two and a half months. That's it. And sometimes shaves, sometimes shaves.
All right, let's go. Both headphones in. Which one is me? You, that's me. I don't know how to play.
I actually don't know how to play. Is there a sprint? Okay. That's how do I, how do I, um,
how do you do the squid move when you jump in the, in the squidding? Oh yeah. First frag.
Do I have to like paint the ground? What? Well, you can hide. Okay. All right.
There's different weapon loadouts too. What's that? Oh, grenade. I think I'm doing okay. Am I
doing good? Is that a player? Who is that? All right. Shoot the ink, the ground, shoot the ground,
shoot the ground. Okay. Shoot the ground. I mean, the whole ground is green. What's up? What the
fuck is this crab? What the hell is that? Should I pick this up? What the fuck was that? Oh, is there
a healer? How do I check the stats? Press right stick. That was actually kind of fun.
That was actually pretty fun. I enjoyed that. That was fun. All right. So we lost. What happened?
That's the first time I've ever played the game. So it's only based on what's on the ground. That's
it. It was basically a three v four. Okay. In that mode. All right. That's what battles are like.
Hey, did you happen to notice how some of your opponents had cool looking name displays?
They're called splash tags and they're fully customizable to show off your personality.
Wait, you haven't even set up a nickname for your splash tag yet. You got to show up in style to
your next battle. What do you want to call yourself? Yeah, we'll see. I want it to be a reveal.
I don't want you guys to see it. What should I call myself? What's the objective? That's so bad.
That's the worst nickname I've ever seen. Is this permanent? Is it permanent or? All right. Hold on.
No. Okay. Okay. That's all right. You know, you can use the Sheldon license you got on shiny new
weapons. I can't wait to see what I did. Ammo Knights. Okay. Swap. Okay. Cool. So the whole
goal of Splatoon is you want to get more paint on the ground. Oh, this is cool. What's the range on
this shit? Let me hold on. Let me see something. All right. So this is a massive arc. So you
realistically need to be really close. LZ makes you fly around. That's also how you get more ink.
Right. Get a new weapon. Try the charger. All right. How do I? That's not my name. My name's
not Splattershot Jr. I know a lot of people before I think that. How do I buy a new weapon?
Let's go to the ammo shop, right? Grab a bite. Hello there. Welcome. This is your first time
here, isn't it? How splendid. I do hope you become a regular here at the Crab and Go. This voice is
stun locking me. I can't even think. What did it say? Crab? Crab sandwich. Battle? Okay. So this is
probably cost real money or something. It's like gumballs too. All right. So let me hold on.
You think it's to try a new weapon? Do I have enough money? Let me try. Let me do another match.
Let me just get a feel for the game. Just regular battle. The story mode. I know. I will. I get all
day. What does it menu? Then ammo shop. All right. Well, hold on. Let me just play one more time.
I could be a bot. Try act like a bot. Just walk around like a World of Warcraft NPC.
All right. No, no, no, no, no. We're playing to win. What the hell was that? We just got hit
by a hammer. X is the map. Oh, shit. All right. Cool. Over the gank. Got it. Get that shit out of
here. Oh, shit. Right stick. Right stick. What does the right stick do? We're winning. Wait,
we got, we got, we're good. Right stick. Right stick has moved my camera, man. Sorry. R3. That's
what I'm... It doesn't do anything. Oh, bullshit. Press right stick when you have a special. Top
right is special. All right. Right stick. Here we go. Ready? What's it do? What does it do?
Come on. We get it. We're doing all right. It's a shield. We had to have won that one, right?
Yeah. 26 point. 40 point. What does that mean? We lost by 1%. All right. I want that roller. How
do I get that? I want the huge roller. It's a shield. All right. Turn motion controls on. I would,
I will throw up into my shirt if I do that. See, let's get it. I did fine. All right. So menu.
Weapons. I want the roller. Okay. Yeah. I didn't read any of that. All right. You get Sheldon
license by battling and leveling up or even just developing your skills by... All right. So I want
the roller. The splatter shot. This is actually locking up my head. Okay. So the Tri-Zuko. That's
what I want. I'm going to fucking destroy people with this thing. Ling ink or hold ZR. Curling bombs.
All right. No, don't buy that. I just want to skip the fucking lore. All right. I want this.
This looks fun. You can test it out. I feel like I'm playing as a... I feel like I have like a
dragon great sword in Dark Souls. Yeah. Oh, this thing's amazing. I feel like you can just get
killed really easily here though. All right. What does this, what does this do? Oh, you should
shoot it like a Roomba. Oh, all right. So that's, that's right bumper. What does left bumper do?
Anything? No. I guess. Holy shit. Is this the strategy? Isn't it? This is probably the strat.
That's the strat. Whoa. It is a dragon great sword. That's how you start every single fight.
All right. Jump special. And what does this thing do? This is just a shield. Okay. Let me try the
other thing too. How do I get out of here? My game's bugged. My game's bugged. I can't leave.
My game's bugged. Let's try this. So how does this one work? Okay. I could, this definitely needs
motion controls. Otherwise you end up doing the thing where you play every console FPS,
where you go like this. The target's right there. I'd like to shoot that person. Not happening.
It's a cool weapon though. I like the grenade better. Try out the gyro controls with it. Let
me see. I don't think I can do it right now. Can I test anything else? Oh, I can. What's this thing?
This thing kind of sucks. That range is awful. Is this supposed to be like a shotgun? Actually,
nevermind. This is cool. It's in the other settings. Okay. Let me try this. Bro,
no fucking way. How does anybody do this? I feel like when a 70 year old lady, a 70 year old woman
was handed a Wiimote for the first time and she'd never play a game before in her entire life.
That's how this feels to me. How do you turn? Oh no, no, no. It's not, this is fine, right?
Up and down vertical is fine, but it's the going side to side and having the right stick too.
This is no way this isn't going to happen. Actually, hold on a minute. Actually. So should
I be using the right stick at all? Press Y to reset. Oh, it's weird. Let me try the sniper with
this. I mean, it's way better, but like it sucks at the same time. It's still weird though. It's
the side to side motion that's still fucking me up. Be the worst sniper ever. Change the sensitivity
on it. I just tried to do it with the, okay, sensitivity higher. I mean, it's better for aiming,
but it still makes me want to puke. Lower is easier to get used to. I changed it. That's good.
Look, sensitivity and motion. I did it. I, this was down here. I put it up. This was the controller
sensitivity. I don't want that to be high. This is where I wanted it. I'll try it like this. All
right. I'm going to try the sniper. I'm going to try it with motion controls. No, I like it high.
Are you going to handheld? No, but wait, wait, wait, wait, wait. If I'm just going to be,
if I'm going to be Roller Andy, then why would I even care? Let me be, let me go back to,
hold on, because this isn't going to be, I don't like this. No, no way. Yeah. I'll try that later.
This makes way more sense in my brain. Let me just get used to the game like this. Okay, leave.
Okay. All right. Let me get it. So I got a roller. I'm ready. Roller main. I mean, yeah. Maybe a
little. Okay. So this is cool. Let's go to the lobby. Split joy cons are actually better for
this game. Really? What's this? Get advice. Is it a cat? No. Oh, here we go. I'm going to top frag
now. Motion controls are better. Yeah. Maybe this is my third game ever on Splatoon. I've played as
many games in Splatoon as there have been releases of this series. So let me get used to the game.
Go. This is my job, right? Oh yeah. We're going to do dual coats. That's right.
What happened here? I'm going to make sure we're covered. Every little percent counts.
You've seen it every time we've played. Does that mean that somebody died there
on my team? Sorry. I was tank. Come on. They wiped us out. I have a special. You're right.
Fuck. I keep forgetting. How do I die there? What do you mean just happened?
Out of ink. What? That's going to be the game changer right there.
Nevermind. We lost by a lot. Holy shit. We got destroyed. Learn how to spawn on your teammates.
How do you do that? This was a three V four. It was. That's not fair. Press X when you respawn.
I like the roller. Oh, somebody DC'd. All right. That makes sense. The arrow thing was a teammate
jumping to you. Oh, okay. Rollers are fun. You know, I wrote this game off and thought it was dumb.
That's my mistake for like the last five years. Splatoon one came out. I was like, nah,
Splatoon two. Didn't even know it released. Splatoon three. Where have I been all this time?
What was I doing? Oh, it's because I was on the Wii U and that was an unbelievably awful experience.
Now I remember. I wrote the whole series off because the Wii U existed. All right,
I'll get this. We go. I helped. I'll get this corner. I get this corner. You get that one.
Somebody ulting. You're going to be real disappointed when you realize that I was
back here cleaning up your mess. That felt like an ad. That felt like I was on TV doing an ad.
I got it. No, I didn't. And then right after. Splatoon three. Coming soon. Yeah. All right.
How do I spawn on teammates? Is it X? Oh, shit. Okay. Like that. It worked. Why can't I jump up here?
I just got a fucking pentakill, I think. Am I doing all right? Oh, there's no way we're losing,
right? I got a little bit. All right. I got it. There it is. You can jump to anybody at any time.
Really? That's cool. I can see your circle. I mean, my circle. Let's get it. And my eyes.
You can see my eyes. You can also jump back to spawn. Oh, yes. All right. Wait, wait, wait.
How does story mode work? How do I do this? Should I do one more? I have to piss so fucking bad.
I'm sorry. It's been like 20 minutes. I'll be right back. Two seconds. Okay. I'm back. I've been.
I've been just slamming fucking teas and water. Did you wash your hands? Of course I did. What
do you mean? What happened to the BRB music? Yeah. I don't know why I got disconnected from
my scream deck thing. I want to do one more. Can I do one? I'm going to do one more and then I will
do some other stuff. Let me do one more. I'm just barely getting the hang of the game.
Talk to the cat. Fresh meter in the match. When you measure your performance,
when you win, the meter goes up. But if you lose a turf or battle, it drops.
Meter also changes the color of the flag by each weapon. Use the fresh meter to see your personal
records for each weapon. I mean, that's cool. Private battle. I don't think I could even do
this yet. Turn on the gyro. No, not right now. I really don't like motion controls.
So this the when I press in the right stick, it makes a shield around me. It's a big shield
for the team. OK. Is there a double jump? Stop. Oh, fuck off. I thought I was going to go further
than that. What's this? What's this fucking weapon this person has? What was that? What was that
thing? Why don't I have what is this fucking hammer? Oh, we're in so much trouble here.
What are these kill streaks like Call of Duty kill streaks landing on us?
Where is this motherfucker? Holy shit. Use your ult. We didn't get to play the game.
Can I move the ult indicator to like in the middle of the screen? I feel like I just don't
know when this happens. I feel like I have to look at where the face cam is. When it fills up,
I want it to be like, whoa, your ult is ready. Can I mod the game to do that? Try a different
weapon. I will. It already does do that. It does that. Your hair glows. Oh, shit. That's
what that means. All right. Hold on. I thought I had like a buff from a teammate. All right.
We're going to win this one. Group up on me. I thought it happened again. I was like, oh shit.
All right. Well, I'm glad that happened in the very beginning and not at the very end.
I started to understand the game. So as a roller, should I do what I'm doing? Is this
am I helping? Is this what I should be doing? Don't go right to like the front lines. Just
do some painting and shit, right? That's what I'm supposed to be doing, right?
I mean, it makes sense that this is what I should be doing. Oh, this is my favorite song.
Oh, you on the wall. You know the one, the lyrics that go like this.
Can we not even kill the AFK player? Are you dropping here? I know what that means now.
Why am I going to kill him in one hit? What? It's killing me in one hit.
Oh, I got to go back to the other weapon. I'm switching. I'm switching weapons.
Did I actually scream in your ears? I'm sorry. Give me the default. I feel like I was doing
better with this. Buy a new one. I need another. I want one of those alts that drops a fucking bunch
of grenades on everybody. Play to level four. Every weapon has a different loadout. The roller was,
you know what I mean? Oh, let's go. Watch this. What the fuck was that?
Oh, what's that? What's that?
I looked over thinking I was going to see like Omega Lulz and it's just all monkey ass.
I was like, oh, they're going to think that's funny. It's like, holy shit. Everyone's like,
what the fuck was that? This is what Splatoon will do to a motherfucker. All right. Hold on.
One more. I had to go all in. I did it once and I'm like, all right, that song has that happened
twice. I got to go all in. That was a Tasmanian devil moment. I was like, I got to go all in.
What song? That's what I, that's what I was doing. What are you talking about?
That's not what it sounded like. It was, it didn't wait. You guys did not know. That's what I was.
What? That makes it even funnier for me. That makes it way better. I'm so happy.
Double shield. What's that mean? What's this mean? What's that thing mean? It sounded like
Woody Woodpecker. No way. No way. I should have. I'm an idiot. What the hell was that?
I need ink. Shit. Got it. Oh, come on, man. We may have lost. Yeah, we lost. By a lot.
Somebody called me an idiot. For what? If you use your special, it refills your ink.
Fucking idiot. I didn't know that. Man, I'm learning how to play the game.
I want to hear the Woody Woodpecker. Can I hear it? Do we have a clip? Hold on. I need to hear
because I was doing the Splatoon theme song. Does anybody have a clip? Oh, is that not the
theme song? I'm trying to understand how you don't know that. That's the Splatoon theme song. I was
so accurate. That was like perfect. People saying, oh, that wasn't even close. Yes, it was.
God damn it. All right. I have to play one without the headphones on. Woody Woodpecker is
a-ha-ha-ha. That was ha-ha-ha-ha. You got it wrong. It's coming up. The volume is coming out of my
speakers here. All right. This is the one. And then I promise after this, I will stop and I
will do story mode for at least 10 minutes. Good. Control the middle. Control mid. Make them way up.
That was a pretty good life. It was all right. Oh my God. That was a fucking explosive.
Too much going on. All right. We're actually starting to lose pretty bad now.
Shit. Oh my God. My ultimate. I had it right at the end. All right. I got the yelp off.
Just go, go, go, go. We only have 20 seconds. All right. All right. I mean, we got dominated,
but that's fine. Oh my goodness. We didn't even play. You're actually so bad. Okay. I'm going to
go to the store. I was number one on the team by almost twice. There are a few shops around here
with gear. Okay. I have a store now. So what about head gear? I got 10 grand. We sell stuff
that you wear on your head, you know, like hats. They've got gear abilities. Okay. Quick super jump.
Run speed up. Come back. What's that? Boost some of your abilities for a short time after respawning.
Quick respawn. All right. Well, this is why I didn't have any of these. Reduce damage taken
and improves mobility when walking through enemy ink. That's actually pretty good. This is the only
clothing. These are the only pieces of head gear you have. All right. I'm buying it.
So I'm going to put the umpire mask on. Okay. I can unlock some stuff. The slosher. Oh, this is the
pail of ink. Okay. Okay. Okay. Okay. Dual welding pistol type weapons that let's be honest look
pretty sweet. All right. That actually looks really cool. I want it. I have this dodge roll.
All right. All right. All right. All right. Too much info. Too much info. Too much info. I'll
just go play with it in the uh in like the platoon room. Sprinkler. Okay. Cool. Yep. All right.
Okay. All right. I'm just gonna I'm gonna go play. Did any I went did one person um actually sit
there and listen to that whole thing? All right. I want to try the slosher. So how does this work?
Yeah. This thing's crazy. This thing can have. All right. So I gotta explain this to me. Why
would you use the roller brush? This thing has more surface area. Just go like this. Actually,
maybe not. Twister time. That's amazing. Different rolls for different weapons. Okay. I kind of like
it. There's three twisters. Really? It's time to get used to the motion controls. Yeah. I don't like
it but it's just way more effective. I'll actually be actually hitting things. All right. I want to
try the other thing. I got dual pistols, right? It's kind of like the default weapon but better.
Sticky. Oh, it's like a sticky bomb. They're good. B is dodge roll. B is jump. How do I do it? B while
shooting. I mean this is incredible. All right. I'm thinking that's probably the best one I like
so far. What about this? Big staff. This runs out of ink really fast. This is all about burst. You
got a group up here. If there's a group. Let's say there's two or three people. You just go.
That's what kept killing me before. Whoa. Yeah. Somebody would just walk up and go
and three of us would die. All right. What's the uh. Okay. I have to sit back for this.
For this to make any sense. Okay. I have to have. This has not been plugged in for about
20 straight minutes. Hold on. We didn't hear. You guys did not hear that. Too close. I don't
get it. We heard the end a little bit. Oh, I was doing that. This is plugged in now. All right.
I'm ready. I'm ready to do a few more. I feel like the crossbow is going to be fun. Oh my goodness.
That goes far. The trajectory on these bullets are weird. Clean the room. Clean your room.
Bloody fire. I definitely want this eventually. Oh, a sprinkler. I like that. Cool. All right.
So what am I going to buy? What am I buying? Do the ult. Make waves. That's what this thing was.
This game's cool. I like it. All right. What am I doing? Should I use the heavy thing?
Paintbrush seems really good. I'll do splat uh. Splat dualies I think. Dodge roll seems too good.
Now what about other gear? You can buy two things. I don't know what I want though.
I don't want to spend. I don't know what I want yet. All right. What do you got? Respawn
Punisher. Okay. That's actually pretty good. Super jump speed. How do you do a super jump?
That seems good too. Should I buy this other stuff? Somebody said this resets daily.
Will I lose out on this? Don't worry about it. It resets in 30 minutes. Should I buy anything?
It'll come back eventually. Okay. Well, whatever. So that's my shirt. Is there pants or anything?
Okay. Weapons. Clothing. Shoes. Special power up. Oops. Hides your super jump landing point.
That seems good. That seems good. Damage taken. That seems good. I think it's this one. Stealth
jump is S tier. I feel like it's this one. Yeah. Anything else I can buy before I get back in?
General? You're tacky. General? Hey, welcome to Atlantis. I don't really work here but you can
shop around and I'll sell you stuff. Put it in your locker I guess. It's all pretty random.
Your locker's in the locker room. Duh. You can go look at it later. Anything in there? I guess
it's yours by default. Okay. What are these like stickers? All right. Oh, you can customize your
banner. All right. Sure. Should I get a sports comic? What should I buy? What do I do with this?
That's kind of a cool mechanic. Customize your locker. All right. Let's go to the locker.
Is it in the lobby? Cool. Okay. Edit splash tag. It's to your right. Oh, there it is. Okay.
Welcome to the locker room. Cool. Okay. That one's yours. These are other players' lockers? Okay.
I don't know. What do I do? What should I do? Does it mean this? Edit? Okay. Wow. What is this?
This is the fucking worst locker. Oh, whoa. Cool. Look at all this cool stuff. A shovel.
Oh, man. Just hanging up my hats. Chairs. Oh, now this is a cool music one. You have no idea
what's in those boxes. All right. I want to play a game. I'm playing now. I'm going to try my new
loadout. Regular battle. I got to try it with the motion control. I'm going to be really pissed off.
So just wait. Just wait for me to complain about the motion controls. It's going to happen. How
should I be sitting? All right. So should I calibrate it with the controller kind of facing
up? Where should my resting point be? What do you think? Should it be facing kind of down
and then up? So I face down. Where do you think it should be? Where should I rest it?
Let it rest on your lap. All right. You look goofy. Go. It's fucking weird to get. I can't get used
to this in a game scenario. It's like, no, I feel like I know I have to go back. I can't like,
no, no, it's going to make me puke. I can't do it. God. I can't use it. I can't do it. I
got to go back. No, no fucking way. Not a chance in hell. Not a chance in hell. I don't think I
don't think I've done one damage to a single other person. Let me drive my car over there.
All right. Don't get mad. All right. This is actually not that bad. It's actually not that
bad. Motion controls suck. Somebody wrote that in all caps. Let me try it without the motion
controls again. You know what my problem is? It's not just the fact that it's motion controls,
right? It's the fact that I still have to press B to jump and left trigger and rotate with the
right stick. It's just, it's not all motion controls. You're right. Right. For me, it's got
to go all in and nothing at all. Right. I got to go all in with most controls or not at all.
Like I need to make sure that I don't press any buttons besides maybe one. Okay. In my mind,
most controls are right. I got the sword and shield in both hands and there's one or two buttons
here that I can press needing to move. I don't know. I can't do the move left and right with
stick and motion controls. That's VR. Did you see how fucking weird VR is?
VR is not a good example. How many times have you walked into your wall playing VR?
How many times have you gone like this, take the headset off and go like,
and then put it? No, it doesn't work that way. Less than you. Story mode. I will. I just like,
I like playing this game. You're going to love the salmon run. I promise I'll try it.
All right. Let's pull it together here. Get off. What do you, what did I just do?
I just went back to the fountain. I forgot to buy boots. Let's go. How do I move? I don't even,
I don't know how the thing even works in invader and there was an invader. All right. Oh, you're
too fast. No motion controls. Andy, we're going to win. We're doing fine. What did you do? You
stink wicked badly. I can see the green stink lines. I should be able to check a box.
That is Cue me only with, with people that are not using motion controls.
All the motion control Morty's can play with each other. That's fine. All right. This is actually,
I promise this is the last one. Then I'm going to do story mode. Um, maybe I should hold on.
Nah, it's too late. I was a sniper on the enemy team. It's bad. Did you just,
did the person just teleport over here? I don't even know where the person came from.
Does that go through walls? I can keyboard world of Warcraft turning. Wait, is that an enemy? No,
the yellow freaks me out. What the hell? What does that thing do? Yeah. Don't let them get
away with that. I think we win. We got a lot of, uh, I think we're good. Oh yeah. We're good.
They had a disconnect. LOL. Try competitive. I'm not going to try. Why would I do that?
Yeah. I just learned. Um, I just learned how to play the game. I'm going to do ranked.
What? No way. What? All right. One more. Yeah. Well, I learned the controls,
a time to queue up against people that probably have been playing the game for like 500 hours.
All right. This is the one. Oh, I was going to dodge it. Shit. How come? Wait, where's our rollers?
Sorry. Covered a lot of ground. Where are you? Where are you? I don't even know where they are.
What the fuck? Whoa. Oh shit. Sorry. Come on. I was sitting there waiting for you.
That was a good one. How come nobody told me this game was this fun? We did. I mean,
some people did. And the recommended channel was like, Hey dude, you should really try Splatoon 3
or any Splatoon. It would be all right. And they weren't that many like thumbs up on it.
Like 15 to 25,000. So, I mean, I mean, a lot of people thought it was maybe some people did.
Oh, listen up. It's going down. Repping Anarchy Splatcast. We're live. Let's see the current
battle stages. Oh, are they changing stages? Go outside. You mean in real life? Go outside.
Why do I feel like there's a surprise birthday party waiting for me out here?
All right. What am I? What do you want me to do out here? Go to the grate.
The frame rate is so weird out here. I feel like I have 3D glasses on without a 3D movie.
Kind of hurts. All right. What do you want me to do? ZL. I've just pressed it. ZL. ZL. I'm pressing
it. Oh my God. I just have just ZL. What is the? Why can't we just call buttons the same? They're
all the same fucking controller. They have the same amount of buttons and they're in the exact
same place. Why do we have to? Why do we have to call them different things? ZLZRL. L is for left.
I know. But what is Z? I know Z is supposed to be the old N64 controller. Left bumper. Left trigger.
L1. L2. ZL. No, you don't. Flip it. ZL. It should be LZ. So why did I come down here?
Great Zapfish has gone missing. Okay. Go get the Zapfish. The pay is zero. Okay. Watch out.
Watch out. That thing does curse damage. Watch out. That does curse damage. You'll instantly get
killed. Octo-chirks. All right. So cool. Let's look for a way into the Ocarian base. If your
ears open for my nuggets of wisdom. This way. All right. Let's go. Okay. Don't touch the fuzzy ooze.
All right. That's cool. Let's go play the game. How do I get out of here? Tabletop mode? Pop that.
The whole thing would move. Disappear. That didn't do anything. Do we have anything with more oom?
Oh. Play the first level. All right. Okay. Let's go. Sick. This is pretty good burp core. Burp core.
Ooh. This is actually, this is pretty good. Rugrats core. You're right. That's a cool move.
Splat switch. Does this tell me how to aim at the center of my screen? Is it crate? Where? Far away
crate. Nice job. I got a toaster. Oh, come on. How do I get up there? Uh-oh. Watch out. An Octo-trooper.
This is LittleBigPlanet2 custom game. God. That's actually true. This is really what it feels like
that. That's a Zapfish. How do I get it? Bring it home? How do I pick it up? Oh, it's gonna be stuck
in my head all day. That's, that's fun. That's cool that you can do that. Single player is pretty
cool. Let's go back to be, uh, let's do some multiplayer. That was cool. How do I get out of
here? How do I get out of here? Menu then. Yeah. I have to go to, I have to go to the crate. Okay.
All right. There we go. Do salmon run. Let me do some more multiplayer. That's my favorite.
I'll do salmon run in another 30 minutes. All right. In 30 minutes, I will do salmon run. I
promise. I feel like I'm just starting to get good. Put on a 30 minute timer. Yeah. Mods. You can do
it. You need motion controls to improve. I think I'm doing okay. Salmon run is co-op. Well, let's,
let's do it. Cue up for it. Well, not right now, but you know, later. I like these a lot. You can
do Zelda. Yep. After I'm done playing split two and three, I will get booted from the servers.
Apparently I might have to restart the game. We'll find out. I like the, the actual just
play the game against players is probably my favorite part. I don't think this is going to
work. Only salmon run servers are up right now. No, you're a liar. All right. Let's go for it.
You got banned for being over 16. What? This is a new map. Oh, caught a few off guard.
I ran into a fucking pole. That shit out of here. I don't know this map. What the fuck? What? I
don't even know what just happened. I can't see. I thought I killed that person. Apparently they
went under. I don't know what is going on, man. All right. We're going to pull this back right now.
Wipe the whole team. All right. Come on, come on, come on, come on. Spread it, spread it, spread it.
Ink, ink, ink, ink, ink, ink, ink, ink, ink, ink, ink, ink, ink, ink, ink. Oh, I think we are.
We're good. Oh, yeah, we got it. Oh, for sure. Salmon run salmon run servers are up. Oh,
are they really level five? Stop bullying this new clothes. I'll check. I got last place. I didn't
get last place. Let's be honest. We're all within a hundred points of each other. We all contributed
very well. Your catalog leveled up. I'll check it after this. You're getting carried by viewers.
That's all right. What does this do? What the hell was that? I, you know what? I just still don't.
Yeah, I don't understand how to use that fucking thing. I'm just not going to use that fucking
old. It fucks me up. I don't know. Why am I even getting into the mechanical object?
I think we're OK. Nice nerd voice. That was kind of a George. All right. Let me go check out the
gear. I was come on. Look at I did. I I may have done a couple of I screwed up a little.
I think we did all right. All right. Let me go to the shop. Some new stuff, right?
Ooh, your catalog level went up. Cool. Growing rookie detergent. Expensive. That's not funny
to waste all my money. Oh, wow. There is new stuff. All right. What does this do? Special weapon
increases damage dealt to all non-player targets. Squid rolls and squid surge is easier to easier
to do. I can't. I feel like that's pretty good. Ink tank refill rate. That seems really good.
What do we got? Special saver is the same thing. That's good. That's good, too. Should I do double
ink tank? That seems kind of good. There's diminishing returns. OK, maybe I should just
keep the thing I have on movement speed. Oh, I think I want that. I feel like I'm too slow
by that yellow shirt. All right, let's go. You look really struggle scrunchily. What's that mean?
Oh, there's a is that a sword? Hold on. What is that umbrella? We're going to test some shit up.
Whoa, this defense. I like this. Everyone stands behind you or you could just like
them. OK, sprinkler. And you only have one of those active at a time. Yeah.
Oh, you lose it. I'm assuming it has a respawn. All right. That's cool. What about the special?
Special whisper time. I like it. Maybe I'll try it. That's what that is. What about what we got?
Umbrella. This new sword. That's a windshield wiper. All right. This thing seems amazing.
Am I invisible? Am I visible when I do this? A stealth or something? Oh, it's just the camera.
OK. Is that a homing missile? All right. I'm definitely going to try this. I mean,
you can just like whack, whack, whack, whack, charge it up and bang. This seems amazing.
OK, what about the this is what everybody was doing? OK, this team. This is broken.
Very cool. All right. So what else? A Nintendo blaster. Cool. I imagine this is just a lot.
Very high damage, short range and great ink coverage. It does, doesn't it? All right.
What's the special tuna healing station? I imagine. Or is it an ink station?
It's a speed bump. Cool. All right. What's the difference between this one and this one?
There are so many weapons in this game. This one faster carbon roller is faster,
but weaker. Actually, I would like this way more. You can actually get some coverage.
Well, Tune 2 had over 300 weapons. What? In my brain, it was just this thing,
the regular gun in the sniper rifle. I didn't think it was this detailed. I really didn't.
All right. What's the special look like? I don't know. What the hell? That's weird.
All right. Well, I'm going to do I'm going to do I'm going to do the sword and umbrella.
Is it a flamethrower cleanup? What is this? Oh, I get it. So you can be like, all right,
throw that shit and you know what I mean? Like this pop. Oh, that's really cool. I like that.
I like it. Wait, Jesus. I still think I'm going with the I'm going with the sword sword and I'll
try I'll get this thing. I'll try this thing. Are you going to be mad if I have to pee again?
Right back. Okie dokie. His aim is awful. I don't think I can't see what you're writing.
Don't act like I can't see what you just wrote. OK, so I got my new weapon. I'm ready to go.
We heard you dodge roll while you peed. Can you imagine that? It's just a stream of piss.
And then like, I don't think you would. Well, you wouldn't think I dodge rolled.
You think I like fell down. You just hear the fat rolling sound with a bunch of gear on.
All right, let's play. I want to see the funny platoon messages.
Well, you're going to have to wait until you play. Turn on post. I'm not doing it.
I'm not doing it. I'm not doing it. The plaza is full of drawings.
All right. Can you confirm or deny that? What if I maybe I'll check it out?
Maybe if you're good on your birthday. All right, let's go check it out.
I didn't I got so mad right there. We got it. We got it. We got it. We got it. We got it.
Sorry, I thought you were an enemy. Get that shit away from me. What was that little dog?
What was that little dog? Let's go. I got no ink. All right, man, I was I was going nuts there.
I'm impressed you didn't fall into the water. Can you actually does it kill you?
I'll try salmon run on your birthday. I didn't let's get off that screen because
I didn't really do that. I did a lot of kill stealing, I think. No, I didn't.
I got a lot of secured kills. You saw it was like pop, pop, pop, pop, pop, pop, pop, pop, pop, pop, pop.
I did pretty good. It's my birthday today. Well, happy. All right. Happy birthday.
We'll play salmon run. I didn't know it was your birthday today. Happy birthday.
I miss I was doing pretty good, too. That's unfortunate. It's the same spot in the same
spot, dude. Are you kidding me? I died in the same place. Pixel perfect. We got them all.
Let's go. One minute left. All right, we can pull this together right now.
There was somebody behind me. I'm going to install it. We all right. We're doing good.
I think we actually pulled it back. Look at that. Look what we did in that last 10 seconds.
We had to have gotten it. Yep. Throw your switch in the trash. That's so funny because the switch is
the only console that is big enough to throw away in the trash like it's a crumpled up piece
of paper. You can actually just drop it into the trash. You can't do that with a PS5 or Xbox.
It's too big. All right. This is the last one. I still want to play Breath of the Wild, too.
I like this weapon. It doesn't do very much damage, but it secures kills.
I don't do a whole lot of painting, but I've secured a lot of kills. You know it.
Don't tell me I haven't. You know it. You've seen it. Let me try. Might as well put the other
weapon on then, right? This is the new one I got. Oh, this one you shake, shake, shake, shake,
shake, shake, bro. This got a lot of spread on it. This is actually pretty damn good.
All right. How does this one work? Yeah. All right. We'll try this.
Please beatbox the Splatoon 3 theme. I, I don't
I don't think I can do it. All right. I'm actually going to get to play or what?
I don't like the water levels. You die instantly. This is GTA 3.
So yeah, I didn't get anybody. How did that not get one person? That's
un possible. That's impossible. What? I didn't get one person. I hit everybody.
You got a person. Okay. This game is fun. Damn. That was like three else at the same time.
What's that bubble launcher? I want that. Did you see what happened? Cause I don't.
Where were you? I think we lost. Oh my God. That's a wipe out. Over did that. You're an absolute pro
got that coverage. I was, I was only looking for coverage. I wasn't looking for kills.
I was looking for coverage, not kills. And we got it. It's been 30 minutes.
All right. I'm going to play one more and then that's it. And I'll do, um, salmon run.
If this is not the last one before salmon run, I will take a bite out of my switch.
I, okay. But I don't have to play that for a while. I can come right back to this,
but I will try salmon run after this. We need more coverage guys. What's going on here?
Guys, where's the coverage? Am I good? I have to take care of everything here.
Where's the coverage? There we go. Good coverage. Good coverage. How do you jump?
Just zone, zone, zone, zone them, zone them, zone them. That's going to be one of the best of the
night. You just made my seven year old nephew cry, dude. What the fuck? I want it. Can I see the,
let's get a screenshot of that one. Just saying. All right. Where's the salmon run thing?
Same place, right? But where do I do it? Okay. I guess I'll just do this one, right? Whatever
this is on fishing hydro plant map. Wait, what do you want me to do? Riz Co. Happy birthday, by the
way. Don't skip this. I'm ready. Tutorial. The tutorial is mega important. All right. Okay.
Listen up. Salmon is, will approach from the water. Get rid of them. They drop power eggs.
Okay. Is he enough? Why are the graphics better? Okay. More power eggs. Cool.
Sounds good. Harvest golden eggs. Only boss salmonids have those. Boss salmonid
alert. I like the colors. All right. There's a boss salmonid somewhere. You have to walk into
these. Okay. You have to get golden eggs. Take them back to the egg basket and only hold one
at a time. Okay. Okay. So they can steal them and take them back, right? How many people play in
a game? Okay. I think I get it. Okay. Communicating with your coworkers is an essential part of egg
collection. What just happened? Oh, okay. Okay. So if everybody dies, it's over. Up is asked for
help. Okay. Okay. I get it. It's like zombies. I actually never really played zombies at all.
Cool. We have 100 seconds. Okay. Got it. Grow your golden egg. Oh, so you can toss it to
people. I got it. All right. So you have to stay alive till the end. Do you get points for doing
extra golden eggs or no? Or oh, you do, I think. Okay. Literally on screen. You only get two uses
of your special. Who has this move? Because that's amazing. That's so much fun. Whose move is this?
Somebody have this in the actual game? They do the tri slasher. All right. I want to try. I want to
play with that. But first, another round of training. All right. This is an important one.
All right. I'll pay attention. Okay. The not basics. There are 11 kinds of bosses.
Which one do you want? Does it matter? This one?
Do all of them. Just do all of them. Um, okay. Place a bomb. What's up? What do you mean place a
bomb? Does that count? All right. Steelhead. It lobs giant smelly. Um, what does it say?
Shoot the bomb on his head. Hey, how do you, I don't have the range to hit that. I can't reach
that far. It happens so fast. What the fuck? All right. So that's that one. Launches missiles,
toss a bomb into both of its missile launchers. I was going to say that did not go in there.
Okay. This is much easier with four players. Yeah. All right. Scrapper
covers its frail body and shields made of cookware and putters forward. Okay. Get behind it.
Cool. All right. We're like almost halfway there. Don't let it touch you.
The slimy pilot is sitting in the tail end. So I hit it in the tail.
We do really have to do all these. I feel like I could just be in voice chat and somebody will
just peek, blow out their microphones, screaming at me for what I need to do.
And then call me a bunch of names because I didn't do it right. And then I'll figure it out. I'll
learn. We're almost done. I might as well do more. Stinger sits on top of a tower. Okay.
Did that one. All right. Drizzler. Our torpedoes that create clouds that rain ink. When it's under
its umbrella, your attacks can't hurt it. So he peeks. You can also hit its rockets to knock
them back. All right. All right. Fish stick. They plant a pillar in the ground and flying
circles around the top and spray ink all over. The pillar will stick around once they're gone.
So put it to good use. All right. You have to climb the pillar. I get it.
Flipper throws out an ink ring, then dives into it. Do not get caught inside the ring.
Cover the ring in your own ink before it can dive. Then it'll be a little bump.
All right. Cool. I'm a salmon runner and it gets much harder than this. I would imagine it does.
I'm gonna get some more. Big shot launcher. Jump over the shock waves from the cannon balls.
Cool. Use the cannon. All right. This is a UFO. Walk under it and it'll try to squash you.
If it tries to squash you and you dodge, you can climb on top and take it out. All right.
Let's go. That wraps up the training. All right. Let's do it. Thanks for sticking with the tutorial.
One last thing. It's all random. Okay. Okay. Okay. Okay. Let's do it.
Relance team of randoms. I mean, I just, there's no way. I'm not going to put like a code in the chat
and we're going to a hundred million people are going to try to join. I'm just going random.
How far can you actually throw this? Does it depend on your ink? Let's do it. Let's get it.
Hey, as we say, let's get it. All right. Wave one. Oh, boss salmon alert. It's umbrella. Nice
work. Nice work crew. Nice work. All right. That's good. Let's, uh, let's go back to the other game
now. Oops. I didn't mean to press that. I ended up working out with grenades. We do have grenades.
Okay. All right. I didn't know if you had to buy them. Boss incoming. What is it? It's a frying pan.
Oh shit. We did it. All right. Wave two. What's wrong with us? What's wrong with us?
What the fuck just happened? Who's coming? Who is it? What is it? Oh, it's a tower.
Chow crash can. This is cool. He hates this night. What? No, I don't. You've been loaned
the Octo brush by a final wave. All right. This is pretty tight.
Nine, eight, seven, six, five, four, three, two, one. Knock out. Knock out. Piece of cake.
Okay. So that was fun. So we get currency for this. Do you buy weapons? Okay. You got a raise.
Oh, I got an egg to open. Is that a surprise egg? So you get a rank up and it gets harder. All
right. I think I understand. Oh, this. I want this thing so bad. Splatoon is just cool. Look
at your awesome new Mega Man weapon that you just got. The video game. I love it. I want to use this
now. When do I get to kill cut man? When's electricity man die? So I get his electricity
bubbles. Oh, it's, um, no, I guess we got them. Okay. What is the grenade for this?
Actually, I don't know what it does. I think it's regular. Just regular. We're good, right?
Best of all, this music is bumping. It is pretty bumping. You're right. Splasher. Oh, medic. All
right. Where are they coming from? Which side are they often? Do I get credit for helping? Oh,
do I have to actually score it? Am I messing points up for myself? Oh, look out. Where is it?
Down here. Oh, thank you. Holy shit. Okay. I think we just lost. Revive me quick so I get experience.
Okay. Yeah. Now we're talking. Now I'm going to be doing some big, big damage. What's that mean?
Stop idling. Who cares? Just put it in. All right. Now to survive. All right. We're good. 14
things. Oh my goodness. Whereas the teammate don't have to just shoot at it. We did really good in
the last wave. Stay with your team at all times. Okay. Go get another, uh, hat. All right. Somebody
said that the, on the shelf is my stuff. Where is it? Oh, it can't be in queue. Okay. So when does
this start becoming really, really hard right now? Umbrella down here. Watch that side. Where's this
boss? Six out of six. I feel like we missed out on something. Did we miss out on something? Or was
it not on the right side? 96 gal? This does not seem like the greatest thing to spread out paint.
Do a taunt. Crashcan. Where's everybody? Oh, come here. Come here. Come here. I got you. I got you.
Oh, we're good, right? Oh my God. We just got absolutely detonated. I think we're good. Yeah,
we're good. Final wave. I guess I fell in the water. What happens?
Help me. Oh yeah. Oh yeah. What does this do? Holy shit. So this is the gentleman's cod zombies.
This webcam going to like two FPS. Do one more because it's going to be so hard now. Okay.
All right. Now I'm at part timer. Now the surprise egg. Uh, let's do it again. It's going to be a bit
harder. I'm so happy you're playing this. This is my favorite mode. I did not know there was this
much content in Splatoon. I saw Splatoon as like a side game. I don't know why. Oh yeah. It's just
an extra game mode for this other. It's like an extra game. It's like portal in the orange box,
but portal was awesome. I don't know why I was like, yeah, it's just like a game. It's not really
a game. I didn't, I didn't know there was this much to do. All I ever knew Splatoon was as the
Wii U big brick side game. That's all I know. Monster. That's what you call an A minus move.
Yo, we need that. Throw it in. Oh, sorry. The game is going to get content updates for two more
years for free. Really? I just thought this was the Wii U brick side game. I didn't know.
Help, help, help, help, help. Sorry. It's okay. Sorry. I got one in. It's all right. Come on,
man. I got to get over there. Did I go win? All right. Good. Uh, he's weird behind a wall.
Good. Got it. I'll take left side. We have the left side. They can't hear you.
Best weapon in the game. Oh shit. Okay. I can get it from over here. Looking good, right?
There's a couple more. What's raining on us? Something's raining on us. What is firing? Oh,
oh shit. It's that. Oh my God. Get up there. Pick one of these up. What's happening to my body?
What the hell was that? I couldn't pick one up. Why couldn't I pick one up? I had one.
I didn't know I had one. This is as fun as the regular game. This is really cool. I like this a
lot. All right. I'm going to get to the next rank and we'll see. I do want to play Breath of the
Wild for at least an hour or two. Or do I just play Splatoon and the Breath of the Wild fans
are going to be very mad about this? I don't know. What should I do? Breath of the Wild has a lot of
fans. I'm not sure they would like that. I do a poll. Do you want me to continue playing Splatoon
for the rest of the stream and whatever? More Splatoon or Breath of the Wild in another 30
minutes? Breath of the Wild in 30 minutes or Splatoon for the rest of the stream? It's going
to get hard. Oh, I need to be the one that hits that. This is my job. I'm going to get up top.
I got it. Oh, you got it. You're good. Oh my god. Oh, OK. We're good. All right. What are we
doing? Splatoon one by a lot. Oh, man. That was close. That was so close. That's so close.
Is that too close to call? No, it's not. It's over. Chainsaw. Another trash can. Trash can.
Thank you. Why won't this thing fucking die? All right. We could do another poll. That's not how
it works, man. Two thousand people voted out of fifteen thousand. Watch out for the dog. Roger
that. Umbrella. Giant. Giant. We're good. Who are you talking to? You should delay the switch
break. What else is there to play? What else is there to play? Not much, right? So what do I? I
got to leave, right? So I want to get my shit. So where do I do that? I have to be out of the lobby?
Front desk. Where's that? You can do Mario Odyssey. I already played Mario Odyssey.
I already beat it on my own time. It's in this room. Oh, here we go.
Let's open them. Oh, what did I get? Swap for chunks. I don't get it. Keep new gear. I mean,
that one's better, right? I'll keep the new one. Slop suit. A green slop suit. I don't know.
I'm almost at a part timer. Can you play grounded? I actually wanted to play it.
I actually wanted to try it. Okay. I'm trying to give us some, uh, some avenues here.
Shit. There's a perfect throw too. Thank you. We need it. Quester time. I didn't, did I not throw
it? We're good. We're good. We're good. We're fine. Don't hit me off. Oh my God. I hate water so
much. I'm never drinking it ever again. Only Gatorade from now on. Only Gatorade. Why is it
getting so dark? A giant tornado is approaching. What's that mean? Where's my teammates? Where'd
they go? Where'd the team go? Uh oh. Oh, we're good. Okay. That was fun. What happens if you
get them all? We got every single one. There's a big golden chest over here. Holy shit. What?
All right. I have an idea. I'm going to throw them over here and you guys get them and throw
them that way. We're good. That was a lot. All right. Final wave over here. We got at least five
or six. Oh my God. I'm never drinking water. I'm never going to go swimming. I'm never going to
drink water. I'm only going to... Oh my God. It's me. Where's head? We all died instantly. That was
instantaneous. Holy shit. That was just... We all popped in five seconds. Jerma, you're 70% water.
Get it out of me. Get off me. That one doesn't count. That one doesn't count. Why is my camera
frame ratey right now? Is it? Kind of is. Why is it frame ratey? That one doesn't count.
When are you going to play Breath of the Wild? Okay. So it was 53% to 47%. What does my vote
count for? How many percentage points does my vote count for? 5%? I would say, I would probably say
at least 10%. How many shares of my own company do I own? Right? That's got to be a lot.
Do streamers play this game? Deadass. I'm going to leave the stream if you don't. What? It's rare?
Vinny does? Vinny plays? Hmm. Shit. Watch out. Streamers are surprised that Nintendo games are
fun. We have some mods. We have some mod opinions here. I have a senior investor. I have a good
chunk of stock. Well, all right. Leather jacket. What's your share vote? It's typing. Get out of
the fucking way. You're so annoying. Leather jacket is deferring choice to streamers choice.
Okay. I'm just sitting around. I'm the CEO. God damn it. VR Josh has deferred his vote to the CEO.
Okay. Grump said that seems like you're enjoying Splatoon. I defer my voice to
streamers choice, which is Splatoon 3. Why can't I talk? I'm speech jamming myself.
What's this? What do we have to do with this? ZL. What do I do about what's this? What do we do with
that? Bro, what's happening? What? I don't even understand this game mode. Why are there big giant
marbles everywhere? This fucking orbital strike fly fish. Well, somebody explained to me what those
those bait giant bait balls were. They didn't even know what they were. I didn't even know what they
were. ZL, look at this huge ball. This is a weird game mode. What was that? I thought we had to move
those. I would have been in there with the team. They're turrets. I thought I had to roll those down
into the basket. They look just like this. They're the same exact color, the same sheen, everything.
They're the same color, same sheen, same metal. Art time, Perry. All right. So we have three
mods that have deferred their shares. I mean, I've got to see what Burger Boy has to say.
He's one of the biggest shareholders. Hey, dude, need your opinion on I need a share vote on a game.
Hold on. Is he watching? Let's see. Breath of the Wild for Splatoon. Need opinion. Need votes for
your shares. You have 20,000. He's typing. Bro, your stream sucks now. I sold all my shares a year
and a half ago. Do it again. What's this weird golden one? Dude, what the fuck is this little
weirdo? Why are you using your special in wave one? I've never even seen that guy before. Oh,
wait. I have three shares left. Forgot about them. I put my three shares to Splatoon. I put what?
You lose rank? That's not good. All right. Kind of pay attention. No more fucking around. Just unlock.
You don't need the team. These players, man, swear to God, don't need the team playing like
fucking bronze players. Dr. Clay, throw my shares in the air wherever they land is where they will
go. Oh, what the fuck, dude? 12345678910. They all landed on Splatoon. That's weird. Heads. Heads.
Whoa. That one landed on its edge, which I'll put that to Breath of the Wild. That's fair.
All right. Pay fucking attention to the game. You moron. What am I doing? I'm like,
I'm away from the entire team. Oh, my. Get this thing away from. Why is it attacking me
of all the people? There's four of us here. Why is it attacking me?
Why do I have all the aggro of every single enemy in the whole entire map?
We all did it. I wasn't the only one. I wasn't the only one. I wasn't the only one.
We're good. This is we're doing it. I actually really don't like this weapon.
But that was a little snail thing. Oh, activate. Oh, shit. We did 20 out of eight. We kind of
cleaned up there. We lost a player. Mandatory overtime is an egg cannon. Get to work.
Somebody else use that. I don't know what that does. That was stupid. What he took. He blew up
the entire map. We all die instantly. He kills everybody and you can't get away.
What are you supposed to do? What are you supposed to do? We lost a player.
I'm going to do Breath of the Wild. Is Breath of the Wild canceled? I just want to know because
it's late here and I want to leave. Shit. People want to see Breath of the Wild. All right. All
right. All right. All right. I'm going to extend the switch in on Sunday. Here's what's going to
happen. Are you ready? Listen to me. I want to all the shareholders need to listen. I was going
to do like a half Breath of the Wild stream, half Splatoon stream today, and I didn't do that.
But I'm doing Splatoon right now. But you know what that means? Listen to me shareholders.
That means that it will be an entire stream of Breath of the Wild on Sunday.
I was going to leave the switch on Sunday. Are we OK with that compromise? What the hell is this?
Why? Can I get a vote? Can we get a shareholders vote, please? Are you OK with Sunday being an
entire day of Breath of the Wild? Not a thing. Splatoon on Sunday too. No. We're kind of going
fracked out here. 23. OK. What are these new enemies? Shoot it in the mouth? Booyah, booyah,
booyah. Oh my goodness. That's a lot. I don't understand this one. How does this one work?
Breath of the Wild 82 percent. What? Only 1400 shareholders. What's going on?
This was for all. This was for Sunday. OK. How's that? Not hitting you. Oh, we're way far away.
Oh, I'm bad. We're good. Will you land already? Dude, why wouldn't that thing land? Yeah,
we'll do a full Breath of the Wild stream on Sunday. That makes more sense to me.
I may have been going for four hours, four and a half hours or so. Am I going to go to
Breath of the Wild for like an hour and 45 minutes, two hours? We'll do a full six to
seven hour stream on Sunday. Breath of the Wild. Oh, all right. Frank up. Are you going to complete
Breath of the Wild? I don't know. I'm going to play it until it's no longer fun for me,
which maybe I'll beat the whole thing. You postpone Breath of the Wild twice. You're doing
it a third time. Breath of the Wild is the last thing I streamed before this. Who remembers
the Omega Weekend? Hey, Omega Weekend. I streamed for 14 hours in a row. That's the longest stream
I've ever done. I am going to say on the record that that was an Omega Weekend. That was literally
a 14 hour stream. I don't do those. I will never do one of those ever again. That was an Omega
Weekend. Hey, you went to sleep and woke up and I was still streaming. I didn't do that. I stayed
up. That's an Omega Weekend. It was an Omega Friday. It was Omega Friday night and then we
were at Omega Saturday morning. Friday, Saturday and then I streamed on Sunday. I streamed on Sunday.
You don't remember that. You're remembering Omega Weekend wrong.
How are we all trying to do the same fucking thing? What's raining? Get the shit out of here.
Sorry. The oil game took up 80% of your Omega Weekend. So? No, it didn't. I was streaming for
like eight or nine hours before I did that. Holy shit. That would have just wiped us all out.
Someone's talking shit. Hey, come on. It's Groggy Gary. You guys don't mean that. Come on. It's
Groggy Gary here. What are you? Hey, shit. This is bad. Oh, fuck. That's going to kill us all.
No, I want to rescue you. How do I rescue this person? Oh, that's not the final round. Shit.
I thought that was, I don't know why my brain thought that was the last one. That's all right.
Where is he? Got it. Where is everybody? Oh, oh my God. Who's alive? I don't even know where they
are. We get it. Ah, thank God. He's still playing Splatoon. I thought he was going to play Breath
of the Wild. Oh, my Breath of the Wild got a virus. It was tragic. Yeah. Yeah. I was downloading
funny mods and I, I don't know. I crashed it. It sucks, dude. I don't know what I did, but every
time I opened Breath of the Wild, it starts playing the music and maybe somebody can help.
It starts going like, and I have to like hold the power, but I have to unplug this quick.
All right. I got to pay attention. We're in the big leagues now.
Thank you. Where's the boss? Oh my God. That thing's lasered. All right. It's over here.
I get it. I got it. No, I didn't. Where is it? Have I not picked it up? What drugs is this guy
character on? I, I couldn't pick it up. I was trying to pick it up. What did I think? Actually,
I think I just did that drill. Let's work low end UFO. Oh my goodness. What a fucking play.
That was all right. This is it. This is the, I got to really be in the front lines because this
weapon is seriously like, I can't, I cannot mess around. What is it? Oh, drill. We all right.
Somebody disconnect. Oh my God. What's happening over here? Oh my God, dude. We, well, we lost a
player. I can't. What was I doing? Oh my God. I kept on falling down. I was hovering and falling,
hovering and falling. We still won. Oh, look at whatever. 51 eggs. That's a lot. We lost a player.
That wasn't fair. Almost there. Another hat. You lost viewers. No, sorry. Those viewers are just,
they now know they have a day or two to prepare. So they're going to order the like 10 foot long
subway sandwich and have a party when I do the Breath of the Wild stream on Sunday. They're
just preparing. They just got to go and figure out what they're going to do. I want one of those
right now. I could probably eat the whole thing. I don't know. I don't think I would stop eating it.
If you got me like a cheese steak, like a six foot long cheese steak, and it was just like, oh hey,
by the way, like no, no one else is going to eat this. Like you can have it. I'd be like,
really? I'd probably eat the whole thing. My goodness. You take care of it. You got it.
Oh, shit. All right. We're good. Just stay alive. We're good. We're good. We don't have to get
anything more than the quarter. That's fine. Yeah. Nice cheese steak. Oh, play Stardew Valley. Um,
I played that a long time ago. Ice cream. That was like one of my first things I did on Twitch.
Mom, yeah. Oh, come to me. Walk to me. Walk to me. Get up. Get up. Get up. Get up.
That's 20. You've been more than 20. We're good. You're throwing on purpose. We just got 23
globs. You strike me as a Disney mom. Open, open, open, open, open, open. Good start. Good start.
Need some help over here. Good start. Oh, shit. Thank you. There's so much over here. Dude,
who even hit me? You don't even fucking lagging. I lagged out. Lag. I just lagged out.
Fuck it. I'm doing it. Somebody put these in. Somebody put these in. Somebody put them in.
All right. We got 22. All right. How do I not die from this thing? How do I not die from this?
Just get the fuck out of the way. I'm out of the way. I'm getting out of the way.
I'm out of the way. Where is he? This is hitting. I'm going to be a grenade, Andy. Where's the person
that's died? I got you. I got you. I got you. I got you. Come here. Come here. Come here.
Keep on the lookout for other monsters.
You throw the golden eggs at it and oh, I didn't know that. So close. So close. You throw the eggs
at 60 eggs. I hold on. Excuse me. I ate your sub order last week. It was mid. Sorry. What's my
sub order? It was mid. What's my sub order? It was mid. It was mid. A C? Like a C plus? That's
fucking fine. Mid I guess. It's like a medium. It's like mid. That means it's okay. That means
it's good. That means you didn't dislike it. You thought it was okay. So what? It was a meatball
sub? You're a fucking boomer. Mid means bad. To me, mid means like middle of the road. That was
mid. That was middle. That was like a C. It does mean that. But what are we complaining about?
You said that my sub order was like a medium on the scale of how good something was?
That's all right. You could have said it sucked. You could have said, hey dude, your sub order is
dog shit. I know. I understand that. Medium. Okay. That's all right. All right. I don't even know
what the order is though. That was a good grenade. Holy shit. Nice work. Thank you.
Oh, that's a shitty place for that to be. We got to get at least the two zero, right?
Yeah. But what was the order? Was it the meatball sub? I mean a meatball sub is not my order. It's
one of a handful of a lot of sandwiches I like to eat. It's a griller. I got you. I got you. I got
you. Come to me. And one of the mods tell me what sandwich it was. Two grillers. God damn it. It
was the meatball sub. Oh my God. Who cares? We did it. Okay. First of all,
a meatball sub is by very definition a mid sandwich. That's not a bad thing.
Final wave. Okay. We'll get it. Hold on. Got it. Oh my God. All right. He's my ultimate, ultimate,
ultimate, ultimate. Anybody alive? Dude, I just saved us all. Holy shit. 30. Are you kidding me?
That was a lot. Okay. So what I was saying is a meatball sub is a very basic kind of
generic sandwich. It is mid by it's on its own. It is mid by default. I like meatball subs. I think
they're great. A little bit provolone. That's it. I asked you in the slime rancher stream. That's
what you answered. It depends on the day. Let me get to the next rank and then I'll do the other
game mode. Meatball subs are good. Yeah, I know. What's the problem? If you want to know what my,
one of my favorite sub sandwiches is. Okay. A cheesesteak, like a Philly cheesesteak
with grilled onions on it and a shitload of mayo. Ew. Quiet. That's up there pretty high.
A chicken cutlet sandwich, chicken cutlet, lettuce, tomato, fresh chicken cutlet. Holy shit.
Not much is better than that. Mayo, mayo. Gross. If you do not understand that mayo can seriously
bring out a bunch of delicious flavors and everything else, I just, I don't know what to
tell you. A chicken cutlet sandwich with lettuce, tomato, mayo. I need, I detailed answer of how
that doesn't taste fantastic. It's, I don't get, I don't get you. All right. I'm just shooting in
the air. I gotta play. Oh my God. I thought I actually got that. That would be amazing.
Deliver. Sorry. Let me get that last one. Sorry. Um, give it a try. Japanese mayo. Yes. It's
incredible. But you know what beats everything? I can't get these out here. I mean, I can,
I kinda can. I don't even want to talk about it. I seriously don't. Don't touch those. Oh my God. I
look like I just installed the game five minutes ago. Oh my God. I didn't, I promise I didn't just
just use this button thing. How did that not kill it? How did that not kill it? How did that not
kill it? No, that doesn't count. Let's talk about fucking like cream cheese and mayonnaise on a
sandwich. What's your Starbucks order? A venti cold brew with a little bit of oat milk or almond milk
and then three pumps of toffee nut. Get on my level. Oh, the sandwich I was talking about. Okay.
Have you guys ever had a buffalo chicken sub? Oh my God. Yeah. Yeah, man. I'm so pissed. I've,
they don't really like exist out here. You, they kind of do, but not like it is on the East coast.
Oh my goodness. There's so much better. Thanks. You got it. I have good.
Crispy chicken, not grilled chicken, crispy chicken, buffalo sub, blue cheese on it. Oh my God.
And I'm talking, I'm talking a joke worth of blue cheese. Whatever you think I'm talking about.
It's like a joke. Add more like you're doing a joke. Nice job. Nice job. Somebody's hurt,
but that's going to hurt. Oh shit. What happened here? That acted like mold and blue cheese is
disgusting. Yet would happily eat something like yogurt, which is live cultured bacteria.
It don't drink alcohol anymore. You don't, don't drink alcohol. Don't have kombucha. Don't have
kimchi. Don't eat that. I don't want any hypocrite Andes in here. Start. I can't see you.
Oh my God. What just happened? I think that guy. Thank you. Oh my God. What is happening? What's
this? The whole map just turned green. I'm going to play too. I did pretty bad that run.
Really bad that run. Um, but anyways, yeah. You know what else is awesome? A nice just
Turkey sandwich, Turkey lettuce. You know what else is awesome? Just a bunch of wilted up spinach
in a pan. This garlic sauteed lemon juice, a little bit of a little bit of salt. Oh my God.
Eat it. So insane. Saturday coming in for that cloud. Oh, I thought the helicopter was a fucking
bad guy. I'm staying up here. Yep. Come over. Come on. Eat that. Why can we not kill this thing?
Just leave it. Leave it. Leave it. This is bad. Did I get you? Oh my God. I threw it in the ocean.
I don't. Do you know what else is really good? This might actually be the thing I want to do
tonight. Pasta. Spaghetti. Angel hair. Get that shit al dente. Like eight, nine minutes. Maybe
like a little bit. I thought I could deseed. Something in my eye. Get it al dente. Shit load
of like a good, a good high quality olive oil. Dump, like dump the cup smothered in olive oil.
Salt. Done. Did I get it in? Angel hair sucks. Thank you. I'm going to quit the game.
I got it. You weren't dead. I wasn't. I thought I was dead. All right. This is it. Final wave.
Over here. I'll do the turning. I'll do the turning. I'll do the turning. I'll do the turning.
What's happening? What's happening? Oh, what do you mean low ink? It's full. It's actually full.
You knocked me out. I swear to God. I, I couldn't throw the, I just fucking throw the goddamn thing.
We win. Oh, all right. Let's actually do it this time. I understand how it works.
Give me some boost me, boost me, boost me, boost me, boost me, boost me, boost me, boost me.
What happened? What happened? Get the fuck out of my way. Oh my God. This is so frustrating.
We have so many things to throw. Where's this big bird? Dude, I can't, man. It's just, there's,
I can't, you can't even see what's happening. Throw the eggs. Dude, I can't throw the eggs
when I'm being puked on by 5,000 different enemies. They're all like,
stun lock, stun, stun, stun lock, stun lock. I can't even see. Dude, that's one of those
encounters that you have to be in a fucking vent call. You're going to be in a discord call to
even do that. It's going to be like, corner, corner, corner. Go, go, go, go. Yep. Like we
have to be all be yelling at each other. You're going to be in vent yelling at each other.
It's the only way that works. You'd get on vent. I'm going in, going in, going in. Okay.
I'm there, I'm there, I'm there. Remember that? My voice is just gone too. What happened today?
You have so many hats. Do I have way too many hats? Should I go look at them?
30 hats. What about Breath of the Wild? I'm borrowing my friend's Switch today.
We decided because he wanted to play Breath of the Wild for this weekend.
I want to play Splatoon and he had Splatoon and I had Breath of the Wild so we traded
switches for a weekend. I'll get it back. It's so fucking annoying though. His Switch is wicked
greasy. It's like stains all over the shoulder, fingers. Get me up here. I can't even play the
game. This is just shitty place. Okay. What happened? It's already explained what happened
right here. What did we all just get such shit on? Thank you. Dude, I can't, I have to leave.
Oh, time to join vent. Left square bracket, right square bracket, left square bracket, right square
bracket, left square bracket, right square bracket, left square bracket, right square bracket, left
square bracket, right square bracket, left square bracket, live have left the channel. Oh, come on.
You're so bad at this game. I'm currently in the overachiever level and I'm not invent and
it's my first time, first day ever playing Splatoon and I've got my friend's greasy ass
Switch in my hand. It's got a huge crack down the middle. You can clearly tell that it was next to
his bed. He got wicked tired and put it down over there in the middle of a Diablo 2 remastered
session and he got up in the morning and he didn't know it was there and he stepped on it with his
heel and cracked the screen. I actually did that to my iPad, except replace Diablo 2 remastered
with a cookie run kingdom or something. I don't know. Over here. I'm a team player.
You just got to get in the way. Don't even run into me. Oh, yeah. Don't even run into me. You
puke stain. Don't die. Fuck. We're going to get demoted again. I think we got really far.
We're all hitting gamer fatigue. We're hitting gamer fatigue and that's what's going on.
I've been playing with the same players for like an hour. It's gamer fatigue. It's all right.
We'll be fine. I'll go back to turf war. What's that? So I should swap for chunks. What about
this? Which one's better? Up to you. What am I looking at here? Keep it. Is it better? Run
speed up. But I don't know. Keep this. That's a triple. That's a triple right there. Where's
the triple? Didn't I just get a triple? Are you telling me that's all I got? We're playing that
game mode for two hours. I got 18 cents. I got 18 copper. All right. Let's do some other regular
game mode. Do I want to stay with this loadout? I think I'm okay with this. I don't think I
unlocked anything though. Yeah, I'll stay with this. This works. How much longer are you going
to stream for it? I don't know. Maybe like another 45 minutes hour. I'll get to like six plus hours
or so and then we'll be back on Sunday with a breath of the wild. Play the card game. I wonder
how much better I'll be at this mode now that I played that much. New map though. Where you at?
What are your thoughts on the game? It is a 9.9. Oh, at least I got it. That's going to be huge.
It's a 9.9, 9.8, 8.7, 7.5, 8.5. Sorry. I got a little weird. I might need to recalibrate.
Oh, you're in the enemy base. Let's go. It's all right. I think we still win. They're not going to
take this all the way back, are they? No. All right. Read my lips. What am I saying?
Yeah, let's go. Do the gumball machine. I probably can't be in a lobby. There's no way this isn't a
bit. What? Top fragging in Splatoon 3 and being the best player on the team. What's happening?
Where is everybody? Where is everybody? Where's their team? Can we get up there? Oh, that sucks.
I got it actually up in their spawn. I'm confused. Where is everybody? Got to wrap around real quick.
Number one turf anchor, number one super jump spot and number one ground traveler. Play the
card game. I feel like I'm just getting good at this. All right. Three more rounds with this
weapon and then I'm going to change weapons. You ever going to play this again? It's really fun.
I don't see why not. I just didn't get it. It's kind of like how I felt about Dark Souls before
I actually understood what it was. Try ranked. I don't know if I'm going to do ranked today.
This is a huge map. Don't you dare. Don't you dare. I hit every single button. I hit every
single button, but the right one. I didn't know how to detonate it. I forgot. Oh,
did I do that? That shit out of here. Come on down. Come on down. Come on down. First time
I've had the whole game. There we go. That's a win. There's no way I fell asleep and you're
still playing Splatoon. Have you even seen Sam and Run yet? Like Sam and the Food? What's that
person talking about? Sam and the Food? I like it. How do you do that? Let's go. I'm going to do
weapon change after this. This is the third one. See if I can unlock anything new. Bro, don't make
me get up there. Secure the kill. God damn it. Secure the kill. I thought there was somebody
next to me. There is. Oh, I walked into it. Surprise. We just doubled. Hell yeah. Oh, okay.
Nice cheating. See you. That's a win. Oh, no, it's not. It's not. What happened? They had their
mecha thing. All right, we're going to do a different weapon. New weapon. That was a good
fight. That was actually a good match. Sword Andy, what do you think? Would you recommend this game?
Yes, a hundred percent. In my mind, this was a six, but in reality, it's at least an eight.
I fucked up. I fucked up. My fingers got locked up with the gamer fatigue for like six hours.
Gamer fatigue. I got locked up. Shit, I got a direct hit too. Oh my God, we're getting destroyed.
This is a domination. I switch weapons. Look what happens. I switch weapons. Look what happens.
This thing's junk. I don't know where anybody is. Is it weird that the orange and purple
fucked with my head? It makes it hard for me to play. I feel like it's hard for me to see
what's going on. Anybody else like that? You're going to join the Valorant scene? No, dude, never.
No way. I want to buy a new weapon. Thanks, junk. You look unhinged today. God, I want a Buffalo
chicken sub so bad. All right, so what do we got? This is the better roller. Should I try the umbrella?
No, you know what? Let's try this. This thing seems pretty cool. It seems to have pretty good
spread. All right, so what's this do? Press R? Wait, what's going on? What is this? It slows
down. Oh, that's kind of good. Oh, that's who does that move. All right. Okay, let's try it.
Make some blues ink. Wrong button. Get some outfits so you don't look like a lame librarian.
It's a new outfit. I've had it for like an hour. So this thing, the target rises up. Kind of weird.
While you hold the button down, your cursor goes up. Where's that weapon? That thing looks cool.
A chainsaw? I don't know about this. I don't know about this. It takes too long. This thing
sucks ass. This is the worst weapon in the whole game. I'm fucking glad I used a Willy Wonka
ticket on this piece of shit. F here. This is what I'm talking about. This is a real weapon.
All right, let's do it. So are they ink or are they squids? What are they? We just came
out of a box. That was a good start. Use the vending machine. All right. After this match,
I'm going to go spend some money. Can you do a dab, please? It's a 2017. What do you want
me to do a dab? There's two people there. I would have won. They're grouping. They're grouping.
They're on a vent call. They're in a vent call. They're all in a vent call. They queued up his
party. Land. Come on, land. I really don't like that super. I think it's terrible. Oh,
you're so dead, man. I think we're getting kind of killed here. Oh, come on. Dude, where? I
can't see. Gamer fatigue. It's over. It's over. We lose. It's over. It's over. It was over when
it began. It was over. They were all in a fucking vent call. All right, one more and then I'm going
to go buy stuff. You almost lost a 4v3. The word you're looking for there is almost. All right,
I'm going to put my pants on for this one. I'm just not comfortable. You know what I mean?
Oh, I thought I was going to sneak behind and get everybody. That would have been insane.
Sometimes he says something that bypasses his brain. What do you mean? Stay alive. Stay alive.
Stay alive. Stay alive. Stay alive. Oh, this is bad. Come on. Come on. To me. To me. To me. To me.
Hey, did I explode in the mech? Oh, where'd you even come from? Hacker. I'm sorry. I keep
screaming into the mic. Come here, you little shit. Hacker. Oh, no, it wasn't
a hacker. I'm just kidding. I'm just got angry at the video game and I decided to call.
Just yell out something. Oh, I got a license. OK. All right. I'm going to buy clothes. Let's
head back to the clothing shop. I want to see what's here and then I'm going to do one more game.
I'll do the gumball machine. I'll do this. I'll do one more game. Then I'm going to end the stream.
It's a good time. Same clothes as before. The shoes different. No. Cool. How do I get to my locker
in the lobby? Right. How does this work? Five thousand. It's a cool 30,000. What are you
kidding me? Where's my where's my locker in here? There's a locker room over here.
What the fuck happened? It cancels literally everything if you press B. Minimalist style.
All right. Last one is the last one and then I'm done. I'll see you guys on Sunday.
Yeah, we'll do. I know I'm supposed to play Breath of the Wild today, but I didn't.
We'll do a full Breath of the Wild stream on Sunday. But when you have fun, you don't want
to get up. Have a good time. Just keep playing. Oh, this is a lot of water.
Oh, this is a lot of water. I forgot to hit the jump button. No, I hit a big oh. Holy shit.
Boom. Kid got this game for their birthday, dude. What the fuck? So did I. All right. That's
a good one to go out on. That's a good one to go out on. They weren't. Look, the teams weren't that
bad. Six hundred five seventy two. Oh, this game's great. This is a I highly recommend it. Very fun.
Very fun. And that's it. I'll see you later. See you on Sunday. I'll see you later, guys.
Sunday, we're going to do Breath of the Wild and we might finish it out with some split two and three.
It's possible. You never know. I'm very surprised. I will tell you for real. I did not think I was
going to like this game at all. I thought it was going to be kind of fun, but then it was really
fun. Breath of the Wild should be fun, too. I'm looking forward to it. These Nintendo games have
been been on point. I haven't had a complaint so far. If I do that salmon run thing again,
I definitely want to do with other people. Those later levels, you 100 percent need communication.
Somebody's got eyes on something at some point during the entire game. You need that skill issue.
Yeah. Well, if I play with three other people or two or three other people,
then there won't be a skill issue. We'll have communication. That's a skill.
I'll see you later, guys. Have a good rest of your night. Have a good weekend. See you on Sunday.
Call your mother. See you later.