I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. Guide me. Direct me. You have to jump across to your right. This is a game about going to the right.
Are you serious right now? Not always. Not always. I wonder what Star is going to do. Is he going to jump on me? He's funny. Don't you guys think Star is the funniest guy?
Thanks. Thanks you killed us both because you have zero patience. You don't want Star to play with you. Even though you're like, hey, you want to play this with me? I'll buy it for you.
I didn't buy it for you. There's windies there. Maybe you have to jump towards them? You just need to calibrate yourself for the windies.
Windies? Not windies. I'm not advertising windies.
Big McDouble? Big Buckdouble? Shut up. I love Wendy's. Big Buck McDouble McDuckbubble. I had it. I had it. You have to go towards it. You have to move towards it. Just like this baby. Fuck.
You probably have to hold back so you don't go as far. What do you want? Wendy's Buckduck McDouble Mcbuckbuck fuckdouble? Oh my god. No.
It's because you're the host. You have host advantage. You have host advantage. Don't even try to talk shit. We live right next to each other. What are you talking about? You have host.
I have host. So Boston connecting to Boston. No, that's a huge problem. I keep forgetting that you have to. Let me be the champion. Let me do it. No. I'm going to do it this turn.
Alright. What happens if you don't do it this turn? I just got a hundred dollars. Everyone comment about a hundred dollars. You lost it already. Yeah. Well, this is for a hundred bucks again. If you don't do this, then I get two hundred bucks.
Thanks. No. Thanks for the two hundred bucks. Thanks for the two hundred bucks. Alright. You want to make it? Alright. Double nothing. Six hundred. This one if I don't make it, you owe me a thousand.
No, no, no. You're going to make it. No. No, you had it. You seriously just had it right there. You owe me a thousand dollars. I didn't make it. For a dumb fucking joke. We could have been out of this level. We've been here for like 20 minutes trying to beat this level.
Can you move or are you just? Thank you. Thanks for moving. These cats could really learn from being able to go down platforms. Oh, oh my, my God. That part really just messes with my brain. I need to eat like a bowl of Wheaties before I can do that part because I don't have enough like niacin or like vitamin F.
I got it. I got it. Don't worry. Well, if I get down there again, I'm going to do this. You have to just move faster. This is no up. You got to move quick. If you don't move quick during the only way you can really beat this is if you move really fast like this. Here we go. Yeah. Yeah. Are you going to cut out those three other times? You know, I just say that motherfucker. Patience. Patience, please have to go through the middle. Gonna have to go. You have to go through the middle.
Why did I do that? That was so dumb. Okay, easy. Here we go. Got it.
Fuck that cannon. Fuck that cannon. Fuck that cannon. Fuck that cannon. Rip it off the wall and send it back to fucking Amazon where I bought the damn thing. Cannon, no. Cannon, no. Cannon, no. Okay, I'm here. I got it. You're going to have to go through the middle. This is where we were like 38 minutes ago.
And I made the dumb joke. I should not have made that stupid joke. Why did I make the joke? You don't beat this fucking scream. You don't beat this. If you don't beat this level after all that.
How do you get through the middle? What did you do? I'm scared. Very, very gently jump through the middle. Don't go over the top. You have to wait till you're at like the very bottom.
And then jump? And then jump through. Make sure you land on the platform.
No! Why is this giving us this much trouble?
No, it's already, you already fucked us. Yeah, you already screwed us. You have to go through the first one quick. And the second one like bang, bang, duck. Yes. Do you see what I'm doing?
No, that's not how you do it. You have to do that. You don't have to. I've done it without doing that. Bang, bang, quick. Yeah, that's what she said. Oh, you're doing bang, bang. I did it. Fucked us.
No, I good. No, I good. Please. Please get us out of this. We had to make stupid jokes. We made stupid fucking jokes this whole time. And we can't get out of here.
We can. Why do we have to make dumb jokes?
Kill yourself as a joke again. No, no, we're done.