My name is Jean De Baer, one of the Order of the Night's Temples.
And this is the bitter winter of 1198. It has been eight years.
It will be long before overrun.
Ten of them have already breached the crossroads. This is the most important thing to penetrate.
Wait, is this us?
I think that this is supposed to be both of us.
Alright, let's fucking play this dumb game.
What?
Their story didn't just begin?
Fucking God!
As for Dems, his is about to begin.
But as fate would have it, there is another hero who would be impossible to forget.
There's too many people in this game.
A priest with pretty tunics. I bet he wields that sword no better than a farmer.
Wait, we get to play!
Oh my God!
I'm scoffed in my ass right now!
The Nutella is out of play in this game!
I wasn't this good.
I was not doing this good.
What?
Is that you?
I don't know.
Why is there a Mortal Kombat character here?
Different universes?
Where am I?
What is happening?
I died.
He's going to kill me.
Why are we in separate games?
No! No, skip me! Get us out of here!
I hit space, you have to hit skip.
Okay, you have to do the onscreen prompts.
He's going to kill me.
Dems is a talented swordsman.
Direct D, perform a normal attack, C, counter, co-op, star.
Why does it say that?
Why is it D, C, why wouldn't it be like A, B, C?
Why is it star?
No, because you're playing co-op with me.
I'm playing co-op with you.
Yeah.
A lot of weird shit going on.
That's performed when I grab an enemy.
Gee, that's HML. The low isn't star.
That's another character.
Do we need a third person?
He missed every arrow.
Did you see how many arrows he just shot?
He missed every one.
They didn't even get close.
They were all in unison.
They landed right in front of these guys.
Time to earn your pay, dogs.
They just missed him.
Come on, you're going to do some more work.
I'm doing all the work here on the left.
Are you dead?
Now's our chance.
Let's go.
I got it right in the mouth.
I can't.
Did you?
I got it right in the face.
He just put his hand up and wiped his face.
Do you feel like we're these guys on the right?
Which characters are we right now?
All of your audio is on the left.
Mine's all on the right or something.
I just ran away.
I just got...
He just took off.
Oh shit, this guy died.
I'm out of here.
Those guys on the left are dead.
That guy got shot with a machine gun.
So I can...
You step out and...
It's inverted.
Mine's inverted.
Shoot him.
What the fuck?
That was a bad guy.
It could probably fit us both on the same screen.
Not really.
It could probably just...
We probably could be on one screen right now.
Is that an enemy?
This is really going to be a headache.
This is where we came from.
Oh shit.
We're going the wrong way.
Is this a boss?
I guess.
Alright, first boss fight.
You ready?
What's the strategy?
Oh, good hit.
Alright, just co-op him.
You ready?
Yeah, just co-op him.
Co-op him.
Just co-op this guy.
Right into the fire.
Oh, they got me.
Good god, we co-opted.
You know how to wield a blade.
Yeah, you guys know how to do that.
Let's see if you can wield fire half as well.
Oh shit, he's a demon.
You ready to co-op this guy?
Yeah.
What a fucking useless enemy.
At the behest of his holiness, Pope Innocent III.
Pope Innocent.
Garin fucking T, that guy's a demon.
You don't have a name like Pope Innocent III if you're not the bad guy of the whole game.
It's funny because this is all historically accurate.
That's probably a real guy.
Here's the typical bored king.
Eventually, somebody hopes somebody makes me come from my sleep and see these two gentlemen.
Oh, look.
Do you see how good they did?
I'll speak to them now.
This game sucks.
Uh-oh.
Reign is back.
Hope he doesn't do a brutality.
He's dead.
Me too.
I'm dead.
Let's try the sacred flames.
He's dead.
No, we have to do the sacred flames.
One of us creates a diversion.
The other burns him down.
No, he's dead.
He's gone.
We won.
What?
There was a whole plan.
We couldn't even hear the whole plan.
We co-opted him too fast.
We couldn't even hear the plan.
This is not normal.
The way they were talking, that wasn't even supposed to happen.
It was like, you create a diversion and we'll do a purifying flame.
No, he's just dead.
I pressed X.