Let's go ahead and type in Grand Theft Auto into the App Store search bar.
Okay. Looks pretty legit, right? Looks pretty- San Andreas, you got Vice City, and you got all this.
What is all this? Grab the Auto 5. Please accidentally download me.
Okay, let's go ahead and uh... Thumbstick is right on an ad, so we're off to a great start here.
Do I have a mission to do? Or is this just pop in the game?
This engine, whatever it is, can't even load 15 feet in front of me.
I'm not even sure there's anything I can do here. Besides just drive around in the city and just walk around.
Alright! Let's get out and walk.
Does this actually have a radio like GTA as well? I want that bike.
Give me that bike. Yes, thank you. Thank you for getting off of your bike and dying.
Except he didn't.
Oh my god, I have to unlock- everything has to be unlocked. Money and diamonds and shit.
Let's just get back in my burger car, one of the only cars I can fucking drive.
Hold on.
They take a very long time to load.
This one has graphics. This music is so annoying.
Is anyone driving this car?
No, there's not. Nobody's driving the car.
How do I shut this music off?
Fucking music. I can't get over this music.
Shooting at it? Oh boy.
Am I still in their car?
Watch out for the cop car.
God, this camera. What are you doing, camera?
Why is it just singing to me?
Is that a police car or is that a bird, like a chickadee?
Cops found you. Get rid of them.
So they're just surrounding me.
Holy shit.
What am I supposed to- how do you beat that?
See, the greatest part about this is these two guys that don't care at all.
This is pretty normal to them, apparently.
It's just a normal day in Shitsville.
Two guys shooting at each other through a bunch of fucking bricks.
What is it with those guns?
There's like silly bullets in those guns.
No way.
We know this guy really likes this song. That's good to know.
At least he's got a favorite song.
This one's real bare bones.
There was no loading screen. There was no menu. It's just one.
Okay, um, I wish I could explain how hard this was to move, but I can't.
Oh, holy shit. That's a lot of money.
That guy was holding a bank vault worth of money.
Go get it. 20 bucks.
Where are you going?
I'm a psycho.
I can follow that guy.
Get out of the- pull him out of the window. Just rip him out of the windshield.
What is going on with- that guy just turned into a bunch of luggage.
There's a Mack truck. This guy's-
Oh. Pull him over.
God. Same game. Same engine. Same music.
The only difference is this time they decided to make you a robot Spiderman.
I guess this one's a slot machine.
No.
I'm gonna give it 15 seconds before I get run over.
Is somebody behind me?
Somebody's just throwing punches at me. Get out of here.
Are you serious? Is he still behind me?
He died.
This is another goal-less game.
Where the goal is-
Get away from me.
You fucking idiots.
Where are all these people coming from? Why are they fighting?
Why?
Is this dude just gonna stop fighting them?
Why would you start fighting this guy?
I don't know. I don't understand.
Is there a reason why these people are all doing this?
I can sit here and watch. It's a conga line of people punching each other in the back.
And then flying.
Oh, I'm gonna need a minute after this one.
It's never gonna stop. This is never gonna stop.
I'm gonna die.
I'm seriously gonna die.
I don't think I'm gonna live through this one.
This is the best thing I've ever seen in any game.
There's no reason for this to be happening.
I don't ever want this to end.
I don't want to hit pause. I don't want to hit replay. I don't want to stop it.
But you know what? I gotta get out of here. I have to stop this madness.
Because I'm seriously gonna throw up if I stay here any longer.
As amazing as this is.
So, I'll talk-