Today, we're going to find out something really important. Real important to me, real important to you, real important to the social studies of your school.
Ask your professor, ask your teacher, this or a guardian. What happened to the dinosaurs? Anyways, you know? Did they get extinct? I mean, did they get extinct?
Use your hammer to crack open the shells.
Use my hammer to crack open the shells.
This is the kind of power that I don't want to have. You want me to smash up these eggs?
They're okay.
This is one of the rarest things I've ever come across as an archaeologist.
Here we're playing spot the dinosaur. You need to really look and find them. They're hidden all over the place.
Check it out over there to the right. You might be able to find one.
Juniper, I've got a little snack for you. Come look, it's a snack. You're hungry, aren't you? Come on, come on, come get it. I know how much you let me in mine.
She's really nervous. Try gently waving the plant to make her come closer and keep you nice and quiet.
We'll never know.
Didn't think I'd be taking a quiz.
Bullfrog. Bullfrog. Bullfrog, final answer. Bullfrog, final answer.
No, I did once. Of course, Tiger. No. Bullfrog.
It is a bullfrog. It is a bullfrog. Bullfrog is the loudest animal on Earth. How could you not know that? How do you make that mistake not knowing that?
What is it, a fucking blue whale? Oh yeah, yeah, in your fucking made-up history books.
You looking at me? Are you looking at me? Hey, hey, whoa, whoa. You want to fight? Is this some kind of threat? Is this some kind of threat, bird?
It's that easy.
You'll need to turn the Wonder Book the right way up. Flip the Wonder Book over to the front cover. Turn the Wonder Book over to the front cover.
What the fuck do you think I'm doing?
Flip the Wonder Book over so you can see the front cover. Now turn the Wonder Book over to the front cover.
What the hell are you talking about?
Flip the Wonder Book over so you can see the front cover.
That's what I'm doing.
That's the front cover.
Flip the Wonder Book over so you can see the front cover.
Is this not the front cover?
You'll need to turn the Wonder Book the right way up. You'll need to turn the Wonder Book the right way up. You'll need to turn the Wonder Book the right way up.
Sounds like trouble.
Are they going to fight? Are we going to get to see a fight?
All right. Let's take a look.
Front row seat. Front row seat for the fight.
Here we go.
So which one of these are we on the side of?
I'm just like a dickhead in the bush.
What are they doing over there?
They could have put a little bit more interaction in this.
Why do I have to be the bush creep every single time?
It's like, why can't I be riding on the back of the Triceratops?
You know what I mean?
I should be riding on his back and throwing bricks with some other extremely heavy object.
But no, I sit here and give fucking Wiimote commands.
Wow, that was some ass.
What do I have to do here?
I have to weigh this?
How do I weigh him?
Drop it onto the scales and let's see what happens.
Oh, he weighs more than a bicycle.
Oh, two bicycles.
Does he weigh more than three bicycles?
He could weigh more.
Wow.
Laugh it up.
It's so funny.
Yeah, it's so funny.
Dinosaur droppings.
Laugh it up, guys.
Here's your opportunity to laugh it up.
Okay, is that suggesting that I just got dinosaur shit on my face?
Is that what they're suggesting?
That has to be what they're suggesting.
That you just got shit in your face.
Like when it splashes and hits the screen.
Rated E for everyone.
Bullshit.
Select a plant using the motion controller.
I gotta stop fighting.
All right, easy.
Easy.
Hey, hey, hey.
This goes to your brother first.
Not for you first.
He eats first.
He did his homework before you.
Sneeze.
What's going on?
No, I already.
Spinova.
You have any idea how much this Wonder Book cost me?
This one.
You know how much?
You have any idea how much it costs for a Wonder Book?
Five bucks.