Hold on, so you're telling me that I have to use dive and or kick to be able to navigate the menu. I can't hit up or down.
No, there is no up, there is no down. There is only dive and there is only kick.
This is so dumb.
It's pretty hard at first. I think I'm used to it now.
Where's my, like, can I change the settings?
Yeah, you have to hit them both at the same time to select something or hold the one button to go back.
What? Why? Why is this?
I don't know, are you not good enough to play this?
Dude, I can't even navigate the fucking menu.
I like the, okay, can we have a best out of three? This is winner takes all. The loser has to buy the winner new curtains.
Okay, new curtains?
New curtains.
That sounds like a plan to me. Let's go. I can't wait to get the new curtains in the mail.
You didn't even kick me.
He doesn't, he doesn't have to kick you.
He doesn't, what do you mean? This is dive, kick. This is not electrocute move, kick.
But it's still pretty much a dive, kick.
Okay, all right, whatever. I'm getting those curtains.
Are you really going to get the curtains?
Yeah, I am.
You want these curtains?
I'm getting the curtains. I'm getting all kinds of, uh.
Is that all you got?
Those fucking curtains of mine.
You're going down.
I picked like the slowest character in the world.
He's really good.
No, he's slow.
You can flip him over to change the type of his kick.
Yeah, cool.
It's good.
I can't get frauded out right here.
Yes.
I hate that character so much. Who would ever play that character?
Me.
Oh, nice.
Okay, okay.
Slowly coming back here. I want those curtains.
No, see, when curtains are on the line, you don't even stand a chance.
Really? Really?
Kurt, I thought it was who's higher.
Who's higher? No.
I was higher than you.
My foot hitbox was in your body. There's a difference.
I punched your foot.
You didn't punch my foot. I punched your kneecap foot ankle.
Idiot.
Here we go. No holds barred.
Fight.
Oh, die of a kick.
Yeah, about those curtains.
I want insulated honeycomb.
I got some really nice ones.
It ain't over yet.
Oh, my God.
Is he cheating?
My control is broken.
That's the only reason why it just broke.
I believe you. I believe you completely.
My control, the buttons are all broken on it.
I'm lucky to be even playing right now.
Your little moves there.
Yeah, good job getting lucky, nerd.
Take that to the bank and cash it.
And make sure to cash this one too.
Make sure to cash this one too.
Oh, he's getting in his head a little bit here.
Oh, you see me grabbing my head.
He's getting in his head a little bit here.
That's okay. That's okay now that I'm not concussioned.
Oh, take that to the kneecap and all the way back.
Hey, don't worry.
He's getting in his head a little bit.
Hey, what's this?
What's this? You want me to go like super kick mode?
What? It didn't activate on you.
You were like right there.
You cheated. You basically cheated.
That's one to one.
That's one to one right there.
It's eight to eight.
You know, let me tell you.
The drapes on my walls could really go good with light blue curtains.
Probably satin.
It could look really, really good.
You don't know what else would look really good?
Yeah, what?
Your blood on my walls.
All right, let's see it.
This is the game.
This is the deciding game.
Damn it.
That wasn't your head either?
Okay, it's like you don't even have one.
Round two, dive kick.
Here we go.
Stupid ass character.
Kick you right in the stomach.
Get that out of here.
What? It locks on to you?
I didn't know it locked on to you.
It locks on to you.
Oh, my God.
All right, let's make this quick.
Wow, okay.
Somebody got baited.
My God, no.
Come on, fill it up.
Oh, here we go.
Well, I've got to start picking out some curtains for Jerma.
Hit him.
Oh, my God.
You seriously act like you know what was happening.
Where are those curtains?
Here's my chance.
I need one more.
Get him.
You know what's best out of five, right?
You heard about that?
Did you hear about that?
Like it was on the news last night.
I was watching the news and it was like best out of five.
It was like what?
No way.
It was crazy.
Like everyone was tweeting about it.
It was trending.