So I'm thinking about a new intro screen that starts to play a loud like fallout boy song,
and it gets progressively louder and louder, starting at like 60 seconds until it is unbearably
loud. And every time like another number counts down on the screen starts at 60. Once we get to
like 15, the numbers start to fucking get huge. And like a big bass just explosion happens on
every countdown. It's like 15, boom, boom, and fallout boy gets louder and louder and louder
until it gets to zero. And then I come in, I'm like, Hey, everybody, welcome to the stream.
You guys like that? Should I put that one in a box and never open it again? I was thinking
about it sounds like pretty good, right? And there's like this fucking crumbs all over my chest
and like all of my mouth. I don't know why that would be there, but it is. I get that
one in the box. Hey, how you doing guys? You know, okay, I'm gonna give you guys a
tutorial on how to do the YouTuber and streamer yell. So you start normally like this,
right? And then almost almost pretend like you're yelling into a wall or like you've
ever yelled into a pillow. You pretend like the inside of your mouth is a pillow
that you're yelling into. So instead of being like, welcome to the stream. That's a fucking
yell. I just yelled. It's welcome to the stream. You almost like you use your teeth
as like a pretend muffler. So I used to do it. I think I got how do you think I made
fucking 50 trillion views on YouTube by doing the yell into the fucking teeth and
YouTube yell. Do you even know how to cook? This is cooking simulator. Just taking a sip
of my coffee hanging out here while I just made a tweet. I'm pretty much ready to go.
Came out today. Yes, it actually did release today. We don't have to pretend like I'm
going to stream this yesterday like I thought I was going to. It is now out. It's installed.
I actually have it up on the screen right now, but I'm not going to show you yet.
Show it. Not yet. It's not ready. It's not time. Not Hearthstone. That was still fun,
though. I had a good time. Well, here I'll have this ready. We already got right off the bat.
I've been waiting for this game for a long time. We've got some great music.
This is such unbelievably perfect in between announcements at the wedding music.
I'll give you an example. So for instance, okay, ladies and gentlemen, that that was it
for the first dance and your server will be coming around with the first course of dinner.
Enjoy it. We'll see you soon for the son and mother dance. It's every single one.
And for some weird reason, this stays on the whole time. Even when you're eating. I don't know why
they do that. Put on some like fucking Beethoven or something. That'd be more appropriate, right?
Anyway, we've wasted enough time. So I'm going to spend a little bit of time on this one guys
because I've been waiting for this for fucking ever. Cooking Simulator is the game that I've
been waiting for. This is my most anticipated game of 2019. No, it's not fucking Anthem 2
or whatever the hell is coming out. It's not like it's not destiny. Put a line through the two
and put it back on steam. No, it's this. So what should I do? Cooking School? Let me turn it up
a little bit. It's a little it's a little soft. There we go. Let's do cooking school.
Seasoning using if you have no idea what this game is. It's a cooking simulator. That's it.
There's nothing else. No shit. Wow. Okay, now it's really loud. Today's lesson is short,
but the skill you learn with it will determine whether you get tips or have to wrestle the
guests for money. Let's learn the basics how to season food. We need to wrestle the guests
for money. They're gonna steal? Target the salt container. Notice the number under the label.
Shows how much spice is left in the container. It's 500 gold in here. Okay,
now sprinkle the salmon and use the container to enter sprinkle mode.
All right, so this is sprinkle mode. Now for the actual seasoning. Aim for the fillet and use the
container until you season the fish with three grams of salt. Three. That was easy, wasn't it?
It gets a lot harder when the product is cut into pieces. Better practice your aim then.
What? That's that's not that's that's not too much salt. All right, so let's make a dish.
I am so fucking excited. You have no idea. Why is everything blue?
Think it's time you've served your first dish. Don't worry, I'll be here to guide you through
the whole process. This isn't a test, but if you run into trouble performing any task,
try one of the earlier lessons. All right, like seasoning the fish.
Steak with a side of french fries. Simple yet nuanced. There's no actual guest waiting,
so you can take your time. Simple yet nuanced. Look behind you. That's the checkout window.
Once we're done, you'll need to place the order on the shelf and use the tablet to
confirm. Simple yet nuanced. I don't think there's anything nuanced about getting a frozen
food section bag of french fries and a steak. I don't think that's very nuanced.
Look, someone ordered a dish. Every time a client orders something, you'll be notified
in the upper left corner of the screen. Notifications will also appear when you have
only a minute left to complete a dish. You're slightly late or when a client gives up waiting
and goes home. Imagine it takes that long for someone to make you food that you go home.
That's it. That's your order. Walk up to the display and press on the
steak with french fries. Take a good look at the screen. To the left,
you've got a list of ingredients. And to the right, what do you have to do with them?
Don't worry, we'll do it step by step. First, take the steak out of the refrigerator.
Imagine you order like steak and french fries from a place that like two hours go by.
You just leave. Why would you wait that long? I have a very strict policy on if the food is
not out in fucking 30 minutes or less, goodbye. If fucking Pizza Hut 20 years ago can come up with
that idea. 30 minutes or it's free. You can't make a fucking steak in 30 to 40 minutes.
I don't think so. Pizza Hut fucking made that a reality. All right, let's get a steak.
What we only have two. What does C mean? Is this the quality of the meat?
Try not to go bankrupt. Almost everything in the kitchen costs money. Plates, products,
and especially repairs. Don't take more than you need and keep an eye on your balance.
Once you're out of money, you're out of business. What is C?
Take, okay, take the steak out of the fridge. What is C? Does it sense?
All right, put down on the cutting board. Now pick up a salt and use it on the steak. 4G.
Hey, why don't I, never mind. All right, gotta get this right.
Pretty good. Now let's have some black pepper. Again, we'll need four grams on the steak. Okay,
so black pepper. All right, put this down. Pepper, four grams. Still on the save spot.
Okay, I did it. Time to heat things up. Turn on the griddle. It's right next to the fridge.
All right, put that down. Here's the griddle. Okay, turn it on. Put the steak on the
griddle. Target the steak to view its state. That green bar indicates that the food is cooked.
The little pan icon informs you that it's been fried. Look up. There's a spatula hanging above
the griddle. Take it. Precise handling of cooking the spatula. Ow, my hand.
Precise handling of tools in the kitchen is crucial. Holding down shift will open up new
ways. All right, I don't think I can take the fucking interlude wedding music. It's the same
loop. Holding down shift will open up new ways to manipulate whatever you are currently holding
in your hand. Oh, shift is like a context menu. We want to fry both sides of the steak so we need
to flip it. Target the steak. Use the spatula. Once the steak is on the spatula, target the
griddle and enter context. Hold the key to flip. All right, hold on. The steak is done.
It's done. Go and find some plate and paint that should be one on the storage shelf.
Do I take this off? Is it cooked? Shit. All right, I got it. We need a plate. Okay,
plate. Just put this down for a second. Move, move, move. I'm moving. How do I put this down?
Okay, back we go. Target the steak and plate it. Okay, put it down.
Put it down. Put down. Put container down. I just want to put it down. All right, pick up product.
Why can I pick it up? I need the spatula to pick this up. Where's the spatula?
I think I broke the tutorial. Target the steak and use the plate. Wait, I'm too tall.
All right, turn the fucking oven off. All right, now what? Oh, you want to put it
over here. Now take the cutting board. All right, I got the cutting board. Go to the pantry and buy
two potatoes. Potato one. Potato two. All right, now take them back to the countertop. We'll need
to cut them. I feel like I'm like my body is fucking so far away. Do I have the FOV too high?
Okay, here we go. You want me to just cut them? Okay, cut. Holy shit, this is unbelievable.
We don't want me. What? How many pieces? 10? 1, 2, 3, 4, 5, 6, 7, 8. How do I? Hold on,
rotate that around. 9, 10. Walk up to the deep fryer. Press the button to. All right,
the tutorial is kind of just like launch up at the top of the screen. Turn on the deep fryer.
What did that even just say? Okay, to the left is a fryer basket.
Pick up all the potato pieces. Put them into the basket and just target them and use the basket.
What? Why are they going through? Am I insane? Why did that fall? Okay, expand pickup range.
Expand pickup range. Oh, okay. I don't want this other whole potato though.
Target deep fryer. Place the basket inside. Now let's wait for the fries to cook. They're
supposed to be french fries. Oh, get the plate with steak. Are these done? How do I do it?
Rotate. This is so funny. I love this. Okay, you guess would be long gone by now.
Yeah, well, I'm just, I gotta learn the tools. Now to finish the dish, go to the herb
shelves in the pantry and add two rosemary twigs. This looks fucking terrible. I have two
gigantic potato pieces. It's supposed to be fries. Whatever. All right, what do you want? Two twigs?
Done. I was, I don't know why I was making potato chips. All right, here we go.
Order up. Take a photo of your dish. I can fix this. Context, guys. All right, click.
Look at how good that looks. Save that one. All right, order up. Steak with fries. You need
to place the dish on the checkout counter left of the exit. Yeah, okay. Look at that. They didn't
even know that half of that shit touched the ground. How many fame points were given for
this dish? The better the restaurant, the higher the quality of dishes you need to prepare to
earn any fame. Poorly made meals will lower your fame rating. Taste, determined by the
technical and thermal quality of the dish. I cooked it to perfection almost. Cooking points,
how many points do you need to learn new dishes? The better you cook, the quicker
you can unlock new recipes. Nine cooking points. Some paid for the dish by the client. 45 cents.
Tip, a sign that the client liked the dish. Any complaints? Guest complaints. French fries
where there weren't enough salt on the french fries and there were some heating mistakes.
The temperature was perfect, but how does it make any sense? You want five-star quality food.
Go to fucking Burger King. How does it feel? Ready to take on the challenge of the kitchen
in your own? If not, you can always come back for a lesson or two. Cool. Okay. So I think I'm
understanding it. Advanced buying. All right, there's only a couple more. Buying items through
the shop UI. I've shown you previously how to buy products from shelves. However, not everything
can be found just lying around. This guy looks mean. Today you'll learn how to buy everything
you'll need and more. See that cardboard box? I need you to walk up to it. Now target box,
okay. That's a shop. This is the shop. Ooh, look at this. Look at all this fresh ingredients.
This is the shop screen. Items split into four categories and by default have sorted alphabetically.
Spices and liquids can only be bought here and they come only in larger amounts. So be prepared
to pay a handsome fee. If you have trouble keeping track of your tools and pots, you can
buy additional ones from the utensils tab. Be aware that quality doesn't come cheap. Now go
to the liquids tab. Avocado oil. The tabs at the bottom of the menu determine the sorting
order. I want you to select the right most sorting tab. Okay. Product should not be sorted
according to their price. Descending. If you haven't noticed, prices are denoted to the far
right in green or red if you don't have sufficient funds. I want you to get avocado
oil from this list. Buy it. Bottle of avocado oil. Leave the shop view. You can buy only
one item at a time. No tricks with a container this time. Okay. Don't forget this lesson. Many
items can only be bought this way. I was gonna drink it. All right, now what I want
you to do is I want you to chug the avocado oil. And when you do it, look right into the camera.
And I want you to say it. Never mind. Last one. Today I'll give you a quick tour of the kitchen.
Stay focused. You need to memorize all of this. Great. We can't have you wandering about
searching stuff while the guests are waiting. I'm gonna fucking ruin everything. Go to the
marker. Here you find mostly vegetables, some fruit, bread, and buns. Some of the products
you will need to unlock by learning new recipes. Look at that fucking pantry. That's
an envious pantry. Remember that you'll need to pay for the products and be sure to bring a
container if you want to carry more than one piece. Here you will find plate stacks. And
again, you have to pay for every single one. Once the dish is served, the price of the plate
will be added back to your account. Fucking expenses. You can also use plates to carry
things around the kitchen, but be careful these things break easy. Even more important
are the cardboard boxes. Trouble finding something, you can buy one from a box.
These shelves are used for storing herbs. Just as with everything else,
the herbs have to be purchased. You pay for every twig or leaf you take.
Go to the next marker. Okay. Let me, let me, I need to get reading comprehension here.
Fruits and vegetables are here. I can grab them. They cost money. Oils, seasonings,
spices, all right here. Herbs, right here. Plates. If I can't find like a fucking
tomato in here, if I can't see the tomato, then I go here and I can just, it's a big list.
Okay. In case there's a fire, break out the fire. This is the refrigerator. Here you can buy
fish, meat, cheese and fruits. Some of the products are hidden in the drawers at the
bottom of the fridge. Okay. So all the meats and cheeses and stuff are in the fridge.
The griddle is used for searing and frying. As long as the recipe doesn't call for any
fat such as oil, most meat needs to be fried on both sides. So don't forget to flip it.
The stove is your best friend here. You can boil, fry, grill with the right pan, of course.
Under the stove, there's even a backup oven. Remember that pots and pans come in different
shapes and sizes just because there are six burners doesn't mean you'll fit six containers
on the stove at the same time. This is really, really detailed. There's so much in this
game. I like already love it. If you wish you can cut on any flat surface, just grab a
knife. However, what did that say? However, pans are up below that. What did that say?
There are pots stored on another shelf on the floor. All right, what did that say?
Use the cutting board. But I said, however, the ground is preferred.
They can't, you know, if you need to use the ground, if you don't feel the need to
prepare before the workday or you're done for the day, you can use the clock to skip
the preparation phases at the beginning and end of each day. Okay. You'll use the faucet
mainly to fill pots. Most recipes assume that you will use cold water. So stay away from
the red handle unless you're told to use it. The oven is for baking. Be sure to use
baking trays. You can find them to the right. Remember, you can bake multiple different dishes
at the same time. Oh my god, the upper switch turns the oven on and off the lower controls
the heat. Baking times correspond to the first setting. So be careful not to burn your dish.
Okay, okay. I feel like somebody's taking me a tour of the spaceship. And they're telling
like, you know, like, hey, come and come and see the cockpit, son. And it looks like a
fucking HAL from 2001 Space Odyssey. That's what that's what it feels like.
These are deep fryers. They're empty. You need to push the left button to fill them with oil.
The right button drains the tank. Oh, and don't forget to use fryer baskets unless you want
third degree burns. I don't think I want that. Well, this one's pretty obvious. The grill is
for grilling. Just don't forget to flip whatever you're cooking. Most recipes require
that. Go to the next marker. Darts? This is the dart board. The food processor. Throw the
ingredients inside and push the button. Presto. You've got yourself a liquid blend. You can
always taste it if you forget what's inside. And it's a microwave. I don't know what this
thing is doing in a respectable kitchen. Best you forget it's here. And this, this shows why
this place nearly closed down. The last cook didn't even bother to bring darts. He threw
knives instead. Pathetic. Go to the next marker. You can use any of the screens in
the kitchen to view your current orders. Time left and recipe details. They're really useful.
Okay, any screen will show that stuff. What's this? This is your desk. The radio looks old,
but don't be fooled. You can set it to play your own mp3s and even interact
internet radio stations. The laptop won't cook for you, but it will help you run this place.
I'm sure the manager will explain everything in detail. The phone will come in handy when
something breaks down. Just pick up and walk up to whatever needs maintenance.
Pick it up so if it breaks, okay. Choose the service company wisely. Fast and cheap
might be a warning sign. Stuff might break before they even leave.
Holy shit, this is... I'm getting gaver overwhelmed. I'm getting gamer-whelmed.
And there's the checkup. Put your dish on the shelf and choose the tablet which
order you're about to serve. Just don't mix things up. Once it's out, it's out.
Alright, I have no idea what's going on.
And the final station, the garbage bin. If it's not good enough for you,
it's not good enough for your guests. Keep that in mind.
Alright, this was just a tour, but I hope you learned something. A true chef needs to
know his kitchen inside out. I'm... alright. We're gonna take this slow.
Here we go. Tutorials done. Wait a minute. Oh, fuck. I skipped two tutorials. I just...
it started here. No wonder I didn't know how to do this. Hold on.
Hello, the manager asked me to teach you a thing or two.
I thought I could watch the third tutorial. I'll teach you how to buy...
without wasting... Alright, this is important. I want you to walk up to the wooden racks
in the pantry. See? See those tomatoes? Buy a tomato.
Okay, take that tomato to the countertop and set it aside.
Time to buy a plate. It works the same as with buying products.
Do you see what I'm talking about? How I feel like I'm like 30 feet away from this?
I feel like... yeah, it's the FOV. I think I gotta turn the FOV down.
Right? This site... this feels a little better. We'll see how that goes.
Yeah, okay. This... this is context really, because look. Ready? See how far away I am
right now? Like... this is not right. I am... I'm fucking clearly very far away.
That's what's causing me all these problems. We'll do 75.
Yeah, that feels much better. Much better. I'm not gonna do the low...
Walk up to the tomatoes with the plate in hand and... okay, with...
Walk up to the tomatoes with the plate in hand and get three.
Yeah, I actually feel like I'm in the space now. Three tomatoes.
Okay, cool. So you have to like, carry stuff to plates.
All right. Cutting. This is where I fucked up last time, because I didn't know what to do.
Pay attention. I will. Easy to learn, but hard to master.
Put in the extra hours to practice once we're done. Grab the knife.
I have very clear posted streamer hours, okay? Why are you calling me during my streaming hours?
What did the tutorial just say? Okay, grab the knife.
All right, so... now I want you to cut the tomato into at least four pieces.
Just follow the instructions in the bottom right of the screen. Four pieces.
So like, one, two, three, four. Fuck. This is hard.
Can I like, get in closer? The chef's like, lean in and don't...
Okay, I know what I'm doing. Here we go. New game.
Most people skip tutorials. Don't do it.
Welcome to Cooking Simulator. As you've already noticed,
the restaurant you're now employed in does not have the greatest rating.
Your task is to restore it to its former glory and reach the highest level of prestige.
The last chef left the kitchen covered in sticky notes.
Maybe they'll come to use to you, good luck. All right, here we go.
Do you want to follow tutorial during first day? Yes.
Hi, I'm the manager of this place. Since it's your first day, I'll show you the ropes.
Wait, I didn't... I already did it. Did I need to be told twice?
I would get fired. In case you get lost.
Keybinding hints are always displayed in the bottom right corner, yeah?
During the tutorial, you can view your tasks in the bottom left corner of the screen, yeah?
Three, this tutorial will auto-save between stages.
If you get lost or stuck, you can always go back. Why didn't I just do this first?
All right, if you have to hold my hand the whole way through,
left this place in a sorry state. Get on the phone, we need to call some professionals.
Oh no, he turned the stove into aluminum foil. This looks like aluminum foil.
This is horrible. What do you mean he left in a bad state?
Did he have a fucking sledgehammer with him?
Was he... we had a baseball bat and was swinging it around?
All right, so we get a call. We need to get...
We need to get that gas cooker running as soon as possible.
So we have to go over here and say, get the gas cooker.
It'll take ages to repair that thing. We better hire someone that's fast
while hovering over the cooker press to select a company.
NiceCorp, Bakerson, Handyman at your service, Home Repair, fast and smooth,
Fast Service. I would never use a service that was called Fast Service.
To me, that... this is like a weird knockoff website of like this place.
They even got like a similar logo. I'm gonna go with NiceCorp.
Okay, so that takes... that's the time. So we gotta repair everything.
How much money do I have? We'll have NiceCorp do everything.
Gotta get a good reputation with one company. What else is just right?
Wait, do I have to do both of these? Does this count as one?
Lower Oven Left Fryer. I didn't do this one.
Lower Oven. Okay.
Put the phone away. We won't be needing it anytime soon.
So then you just wait till they're all fixed?
Okay, no time to take a breather. This place is empty and we're gonna do something about it.
You get some utensils. We gotta fill the restaurant.
Okay, I just left utensils. I don't have any utensils at all.
We need to get a blender. I'm running out of money.
Put the blender away. You can carry only one thing at a time.
I mean, very clearly the button says throw.
I can't... no. No, this is the first mission.
Put the blender away. Put the blender away.
I'm not going to throw it. Don't throw anything.
Hover over it and press E to pick up the box.
Put it down on the countertop.
Everything. You can throw everything.
I'm not going to do that right now.
Guys, this is going to be like a nice long stream.
You want me to automatically start spawning easy pizza?
I don't think you want that. I don't want that.
Okay, we need to buy a cooking tool. We need a bake tray.
So we need all this stuff. Use the shop to buy.
All right, so we can buy a knife.
Oh, you got to individually put everything down.
You have a power meter.
Holy shit.
All right, no more throwing.
I need to put the knife in the knife tray.
There. I'm doing this.
I'm going to play nice.
Pan. What does a pan go?
Underneath here, right?
Fuck. Just put it down.
Put it down. Pan.
Big pot. Big pot goes under here.
Barely. Fits under there.
Cutting board.
Wait, how many do I need? Two big pots?
Okay. Baking tray.
Oh, let's get that.
I need to remember where this shit is.
I'm going to put it in places that I know where it's going to be.
All right, last one.
A spatula.
I need to remember where this is going to be.
I'm going to put it over here.
Yeah, hang it right there.
This too. Can I put it up here?
Okay. Don't it go to the laptop?
We need to get a recipe.
Click on the recipe manager on the left side menu.
Click on the not owned tab to open the recipe.
Not owned.
Buy a recipe for baked trout.
Look at all this.
How many are there?
Oh man, that's fucking cool.
Oh, this is awesome.
All right. Baked trout.
So here's the recipe.
Take trout. Season with black pepper, thyme, dried, and dill.
I need black pepper.
Place on a baking tray.
Bake for 90 seconds.
Season with horseradish.
All right, buy it.
Unlock salmon steak and boiled potatoes.
Okay. I'm ready.
So we need to get fish.
How do we do this?
Where's my recipe?
Oh, okay. Owned.
Seven minutes?
What do I need to...
Hold on. Not owned.
Oh, I get it for free.
Tomato soup. Classic.
That should do for now.
We'll improve our menu once the business gets rolling.
All right.
Exit the laptop.
It's time to go.
Let's see. Repairs, utensils, recipes.
Yes, we need some spices.
Let's visit the shop.
We need salt.
All right. I gotta put this somewhere.
Somewhere where I know it's gonna be.
Somewhere I always know it's gonna be.
Right here. We're not open yet.
There's going to be much time for shopping.
Not gonna be much time.
Best we buy all that we need now.
Get everything. Dried dill.
All right. I need to know what this is gonna...
Over here.
Oh, no. That's fresh dill.
I'm gonna say this is the spice rack.
Should I do it alphabetical?
Yeah. D, dill.
B, black.
C, A, B, C.
All right. Hold on.
I'm doing it alphabetical.
Then we need horseradish dried.
QRS.
Powdered cayenne pepper.
All right. Here we go.
A, B. Wait.
All right. So we got dill.
A, B, C.
B, C, D.
E, F, G, H.
Okay. They're alphabetical now.
I just know if it's like black pepper.
B, liquids tab.
Chicken broth.
All the liquids are gonna go in the bottom.
B, sunflower oil.
S. Wait. Does it fit in there?
Why not?
What? It's too tall?
No. That's too high.
I want it in here.
Oh, right. It's made out of glass.
Wait. Can I use this?
How do I actually use this?
There we go. Move vertically.
How do I rotate it?
They didn't teach me how to use this yet.
Where's the trash?
Can I scoop this all up?
I have to do it one by one.
No. There has to be something.
Look. People break shit all the time in a restaurant.
If you guys ever worked in a kitchen like I have,
you understand how many bottles broke a day?
You don't understand how much food was just like dropped on the ground
and the bottle shattered and broken and wine bottles and stuff.
Happens like every 10 seconds.
I need...
Wait. I don't have any oil now.
I need to buy sunflower oil again because I...
Wait, wait, wait.
I need to bake me a baked trout.
Hold on. I miss an oil.
I need this. I need the oil.
Sunflower oil, right?
Don't worry. You have some help.
I need oil.
All right. Fuck it.
I'm just putting it up there.
Oh, God. Okay. Here we go.
Seven minutes.
What broke?
What?
What happened?
I don't understand.
I put it...
I did...
Open the refrigerator.
All right. Let's go.
Each product costs money.
So we need one.
You don't have to worry about supplies, but still you need...
Okay. One trout.
Got one.
Okay. Black pepper.
Five grams.
Black pepper.
Where's the pepper?
That's salt.
Black pepper.
B.
Dill.
D.
Time.
T.
Okay. Here we go.
Five grams each.
Spin this around a little bit.
Rotate it like this.
I want to rotate it around.
I want it sideways.
Whatever.
Five grams.
Okay. Here we go.
Got it.
Dried dill.
Pretty good evening seasoning.
Five. Okay.
What am I...
Dill?
This dill needs dill?
How much is on there?
That's okay.
I missed.
Okay.
Baking tray.
Under here.
Oven.
Turn on the oven.
What's the degrees?
We need a lemon.
How long does it take?
Do I have a timer?
Four pieces.
Damn it!
Come on!
That's fine.
Hey, put this down.
What do I do with the lemons?
Is this done?
This is scary.
Imagine you go into a restaurant in the back
and the chef could be doing anything else.
And he's just fucking staring, just waiting.
How long does it take?
How do I know when it's done?
It's not burnt.
Fridge is still open.
It's wasting it.
All right.
Don't blow up the propane tank.
That was very violent mopping.
Is it done?
I need to check.
It's done!
My hands!
Ow!
All right.
Is it done?
No, it's not done.
Oh, fuck!
I can't feel my hands anymore.
Okay, it's done.
I need a plate.
Okay.
Transfer the product.
Five grams of horseradish.
My hands are probably so inflamed.
I probably have huge, huge Mickey Mouse glove hands right now
because it's swelling up.
All right.
Five grams.
Now pick up the lemon quarters and target them and expand.
Wait.
Okay.
So here we go.
That looks horrible.
That's just a joke.
Just serve it with one lemon.
Parsley leaves.
One, two, three.
Serve it.
Put it on the counter.
Wait, can I like move it around a little?
Well, okay.
Enter the...
Like that looks bad.
Okay, hold on.
Looks good.
Midnight.
Okay.
Okay, hide the UI.
Take the picture.
Save it.
Looks fucking pretty good, actually.
Put it on grandma's Facebook.
Ding.
Taste?
Almost five stars.
Pretty good.
What are the complaints?
It was perfect.
The lemon quarters were not cut perfectly.
Yeah, whatever.
You're gonna come back.
That's it for today.
Tomorrow we'll be open for business, so do your best.
All right.
After each day, you'll be presented with a summary of progress the restaurant made.
Our goal is to reach full five-star fame rating.
As you can see, there's still a lot ahead of us.
Yes, there is.
Total income, negative $1,400.
How much money do I have?
All right.
This is where it begins.
Experience points come primarily from serving dishes and doing daily quests.
Once you gain enough experience, you will automatically level up.
We get to choose a perk.
There are perks.
Okay.
Perks are very powerful unique abilities.
Once every few levels, you'll be given an option to choose one.
This choice can't be postponed or undone,
so take your time and pick what you think will be the most useful.
Can you view perks?
You're already using your perk browser app.
Okay, hold on.
Long reach.
Long arms.
Longer reach from picking up and putting down items.
Have really long fucking arms.
Fast feet.
Get at three skill points that are unlocking a perk.
Steady hands.
Hold down shift to freeze items in place while cutting.
That's what's going on here.
I want this one.
Lower score requirements.
Pass the food critics.
Learn the temperature of ingredients in a closed oven.
Oh, that's good.
Time slows down while cutting.
Once per day, reset the timer of an active order.
Reroll order grants a magic wand that removes all stains and shards.
I mean steady hands.
That's...
I have to use that.
Skill points are used to unlock and upgrade skills.
With each level, you gain a certain amount of SPs.
You can spend them...
Okay.
What do I have for points?
I got three.
Oh my god.
All right, so income.
Pay 10% more for their orders without affecting the score.
10% more cooking points.
Kitchen decorations are cheaper.
You earn 50 more experience points for dish stars.
Chain four star dishes to earn more fame.
Liquids cost less.
Products cost less.
Spices are less.
Gifts, guest tip, more.
I think I'm gonna go with they pay more money.
Yeah, I want 30% more money.
All right, the joke's over.
It's time to fucking actually play.
This is the real game now.
All right, here we go.
Remember, everything you serve today will affect your reputation.
Let's do this.
Let's make the best restaurant in the city.
By throwing the propane tank into the microwave and turning it off for five minutes.
The name should tell the story.
No orders yet, but you can use anything in the kitchen to prepare for the day.
Make sure to prepare the ingredients you'll be using.
Getting a head start on some of the dishes is also a good idea.
As long as you know what you're doing.
There's fucking rumors in this game.
I just had a flash of...
Okay, hold on.
I feel bad right now.
Okay.
Let's pick what we left off.
Open the skill manager app.
That's bright.
Mm-hmm.
If you didn't spend your skill points, you can do so now.
I did.
You can choose to save up points and use the app later.
Okay.
You can get decorations.
Reset all of your points, but that's going to cost you money.
Makes sense.
Perk browser.
You can actually select perks.
It's like Call of Duty.
All right.
Okay, hold down shift to freeze items while cutting.
All right, let's go.
Yikes, look at the time.
We need to open right away.
Let's get cooking.
What?
It's time to...
I'm not ready.
I thought you might still need me today, so I'm here.
But only for today.
Don't get too attached.
Dish salmon.
Oh, I actually have a timer now.
Find a big pot.
We'll need to boil the potatoes.
Fill it with one cup of water.
How do I know how much water I'm going to get?
How do I turn it on?
How do I turn the faucet on?
No, is this cold or hot?
That's hot water.
All right.
Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait.
Cold water.
E.
How much water?
I feel like I'm at a gas station.
Okay, got it.
20 grams of salt?
That's too much salt.
Ugh.
We need two potatoes.
Potatoes.
Two of them.
How do I buy two?
Can I buy more than one?
All right.
Boil potatoes.
Cook for 120 seconds.
Is this the right one?
Okay, that's the right one.
120 seconds.
Count.
One.
Two.
Where were we at?
10?
Okay, so 10...
120 seconds is two minutes.
So when this gets to 10, twice.
Okay, go.
Okay, boil potato.
Boil...
Where's my cutting board?
Okay, got salmon.
I just got...
I already have one.
I have one.
All right.
Fish on the cutting board.
Got it.
We need salt and black pepper.
How much do we need?
5 grams?
Okay, black pepper.
10?
Okay.
Where's the pepper?
Where's black pepper?
Give me it.
Frying in oil.
Oh my god.
Put it back in.
How do I put it back in?
Okay.
I need sunflower oil.
Well, don't step on the glass.
Watch out for your bare feet.
How much oil do I need in the pan?
10 milliliters.
Tilt the bottle.
Oh!
Get the salmon in there.
That looks fucking amazing.
I have bugs on it.
Why are there ants on this?
Fry the steak for 60 seconds.
10?
Are they done?
Wait, are these done?
Oh, that's not real time.
Hold.
Okay.
What do I do with this?
Pick up the potato straight from the pot into the plate.
What plate?
Plate.
I need plate.
Basic plate.
Deep plate.
Okay.
Just put this down.
How about the salmon?
Is the salmon doing all right?
Why is it not cooking?
Okay, hold on.
Do I have to cut these?
Oh, god damn it.
It's not on.
Okay, hold on.
Spatula.
When do I flip it?
Don't you not flip salmon?
I know how to cook salmon.
You don't flip it.
You cover it.
Where's the coven?
Where's the coven for the oven?
Where are the vampire ladies that are gonna eat me?
These are gonna get cold.
How much time do I have?
Three minutes.
Can I turn the heat up?
Come on, come on, come on, come on.
Let's go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go.
Wait, now it's...
Now I can't.
I have to do it again.
Flip it again.
Okay, we're good.
60 seconds.
Timer.
All right, 50 seconds.
Is it almost done?
What do I do in the meantime?
I got two minutes.
I'm fine.
I think I'm gonna have to cut up the potatoes though.
Are they still hot?
Yeah, they are.
Let me test.
Give me this.
I just heard a rumor.
All right.
Come on.
How much time?
I still got a little bit of time.
Perfectly calculated.
Put it down.
Just put the salmon down.
That's not cooked on the bottom.
Stop it!
Leave me a...
Pick up the plate with the salmon.
Put the plate on the serving shell.
This is not ready to serve.
You just want two fucking baked potatoes?
This is not even food.
What?
This looks like a dessert.
This looks like a cake.
No, that's a cake.
Imagine being served salmon like this.
Sitting up on its side.
You'd be like...
The chef is fucking drunk.
Not bad, actually.
I got a seven cent tip.
What were the complaints?
Heating mistakes.
Too much oil on the steak.
Yeah.
Well, he still ate it.
No time for slacking off.
Next order is here.
Tomato soup.
Wait, what do I have to do?
We need a big pot.
Find one.
Make sure it's empty.
Oh, fuck.
This is still boiling.
I'm trying to get it in the sink.
I'm gonna get myself a headache.
You just throw that into the ground.
How do I open this?
Open the chicken broth.
How much do we need?
700 milliliters?
All right.
Get it in there.
Stop pouring it.
All right.
Season the broth.
I need cayenne pepper to the pot.
12 grams.
1, 2, 3, 4, 5, 6, 7, 8, 9, 10, 11, 12.
And we need some cayenne pepper.
Where's cayenne?
Horseradish.
Cayenne?
Time.
I need cayenne.
Now.
I need it right now.
Six grams.
Good.
Okay.
I need tomatoes.
Add fucking salt.
God damn it.
Where is it?
Okay.
Done.
Take the pot into the pantry and put eight tomatoes in here.
Eight tomatoes.
We need an onion.
What?
This isn't how you make tomato soup.
Why do I get gas?
Oh.
Okay.
Boil the soup.
How much time do I got?
Five minutes.
I got plenty of time.
What was in here?
What?
I guess you can throw that away.
Hold on.
This is dirty.
I need to throw it away.
Fucking dogshit restaurant.
This is so fun.
How do I clean the top?
How do I clean in there?
Is it boiling yet?
Can I buy a sponge?
All right.
This is...
They're almost done.
Turn off the heat and blend the contents.
What?
Okay.
Turn it on.
I'm trying to draw.
It's a mouse scroll?
Oh my god.
All right.
Done.
Okay.
What do I need now?
Pour sour cream?
Pour sour cream.
Whisk sour cream.
I already have it.
It's already over here.
Okay.
This is not...
You have to easily till.
How much?
150.
No.
Deep plate.
Okay.
Take the pot and target the deep plate.
And press to hold down while pouring this...
Wait.
You don't...
I have to pour the soup?
Nobody doesn't use...
You lay...
It was a ladle.
This is not what I'm supposed to do, right?
That was the whole pot.
This is a huge serving.
Imagine being served a full pot of tomato soup.
That's a full five right there.
Any complaints?
Technique was perfect.
Wrong amount of product.
What do you mean wrong amount of product?
Are they done with 149?
Whatever.
I'm still going.
One baked trout.
I remember this one.
I can do this one quick.
Okay.
Jess, this one...
I can do it on my own.
Okay.
Baked trout.
Remember, on my own.
I need a tray.
Where's the tray?
Where's the baking sheet?
Bingo.
Okay.
I need...
What do I need here?
Let me...
I need a...
How do I...
What?
Let me see.
How do I determine what I need?
I need salt and pepper, right?
Where's the thing to look at?
The salt...
Hold on.
Right here.
Pepper, thyme, dill.
Two, three, four, five.
Get it on there.
Five.
Okay.
Come on.
Thyme.
Pepper.
Where's that black pepper?
That salt?
Oh, come on.
Where is it?
Right there.
One, two, three, four, five.
What's next?
Okay.
Baking tray.
Bake for 90 seconds.
Season with horseradish.
After?
After.
Okay.
90 seconds.
Get it in there.
Get it in.
This is still on.
I just burnt.
I just singed my fucking eyebrows.
Nice clown laugh, by the way.
All right.
Now I need lemon cut into quarters.
This is where I get a hold down shift.
Freeze.
Freeze product into quarters.
So here we go.
Let's get it nice and neat here.
Bang.
Done.
90 seconds.
I need to see in there.
How long has it been?
Okay, it's almost done.
And then we need dried horseradish.
And then...
So get it on a plate.
Garnish with parsley leaves.
Six grams.
I need a plate.
Basic plate.
Is it done?
I'm burning my fucking hands.
No.
Hold on.
Just put it back in.
Just put it on the fucking table.
Jesus.
Horseradish first.
Five grams.
Get it on the plate.
Six grams of parsley.
Two, four, six.
Get those lemons on there.
Wait, I need to like...
Okay, that looks a little better.
Done.
Bingo.
What do you think?
I didn't have any help on that one.
Got them all perfect.
You got to hold the basics pretty quickly.
So what's the master plan, you might ask.
Well, I want this place to go from snow stars to five stars.
Not in the red today.
Each dish you serve affects our fame score.
Do well and the score goes up.
Mess up and we're going down.
I made 108 cents.
We need attractive food critic.
To do that, we have to meet a fame score quota at the end of the day.
And I did it.
I got to 30.
I got 34.
There's a food critic coming in at the end of today.
Already?
We just opened.
Going over the quota to have some breathing space just in case.
Yeah, I did.
A food critic wants to try your cooking tomorrow.
Impress him and we're guaranteed a fame star.
Once the critic is here, focus on his order.
Score at least four stars to pass his exam.
Tomorrow, we're getting inspected.
It's a great chance to raise our fame.
Be ready.
Well, I need to clean the kitchen.
Level up.
Skill point.
What do you think?
More money?
Yeah, I want 50% more money.
I think we should expand our menu.
Look at the dishes below and pick your favorite.
Pork chops with baked potatoes or simple Ukrainian borscht.
This takes nine minutes.
This takes seven.
Borscht?
Chicken broth, salt, black pepper, beetroot, onion, carrot, parsley.
Boil for 120 seconds.
I can handle this.
Yeah, let's get it.
Beetroot is our new ingredient.
You'll find it in the shop and the larder.
Carrot is a new ingredient.
You find it in the shop and the larder.
Parsley.
It can be found both in the shop and the larder.
Yeah, I got new ingredients.
All right, good.
Okay, I got time.
I got three minutes.
Someone's coming to investigate this place.
We got to clean this up now.
Within an hour.
There's no faster.
I can't drag this over here.
Food critic's going to be here in three hours.
Just mop.
We're getting health inspected.
Anything else?
The fridge has been open all night.
That's great.
Okay, I got to...
How do I clean up that?
I don't think I can reach this.
Move vertically.
Rotate.
I can't get it in there.
Advanced controls.
Move vertically.
They can't do anything about it.
Rotate.
Move vertically.
Sponge.
Utensils?
Oh my goodness.
Spatula.
Bucket.
Sponge.
How do I use it?
Rotate.
Throw.
Advanced controls.
Rotate.
Drop.
I didn't even know you could crouch in the game.
Good.
Clean that up.
Anything else?
What else?
There's shit all over here too.
It's the Mr. Clean Magic Eraser.
All right.
I had fucking three sponges already.
Great.
Fantastic.
Okay.
Time to open.
44 seconds.
What else?
We got anything else?
I got to make things a little nicer in here.
Just get it ready for the day.
What about...
This oven's been on.
I can clean the oven.
Turn the oven off.
Clean.
What?
I can't clean it?
Clean.
What the fuck is going on?
Why am I wiping the tile?
How do I zoom out?
What the hell is happening?
Okay.
I can...
New order.
Chicken broth.
Salt.
Pour the liquid...
Okay.
So I just need a...
I just need a big pot.
A thousand milliliters of chicken broth.
Pot.
Big one.
Is this clean?
It's clean.
It's clean, right?
That looks pretty clean.
All right.
Get it on here.
Here we go.
Chicken broth.
What?
Oh shit.
It's empty.
Buy one.
What's a...
What's a thousand minus 164?
Three.
Okay.
Oh fucking perfect!
It was perfect!
Okay.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
Salt.
20 grams.
Pepper.
Salt.
20 grams.
Pepper.
Let's go.
Salt right here, right?
20 grams.
What's next?
I need beetroot.
600 grams.
Onion.
Beetroot.
I need beetroot.
Where's beet?
Beetroot.
600 grams.
Oh shit.
I need a plate.
Hold on.
Just bring...
600 grams.
Put that beet in here.
Come on.
Give me the beet.
All right.
600 grams.
How many are in there right now?
120.
That's 240.
That's...
How many are in there now?
One...
Two.
40.
Three.
One more.
Done.
And onion too.
How many onions?
120.
And then 70 carat.
70 carat.
One carat.
And then onion.
Beautiful.
Parsley.
What was it?
What was the parsley?
80.
Wait.
80?
Am I insane?
That's a lot.
Is there a dried parsley?
There's no dried parsley.
What is it?
How many?
Was this 80?
What is this one?
80.
Okay.
Boil for 120 seconds.
That's it.
Let's go.
Timer.
Where's the timer?
Q.
A.
It's got to be more like...
All right.
How much time do I have?
Oh, it's gonna be close.
That's kind of weird to do like Q-A-S-E-D.
All right.
Let's cool it down.
No.
Wait.
What?
Did that just cost money?
I can't put it back.
All right.
I have it for emergency situations.
Put it under here.
All right.
Hold on.
What about D plate?
The onions are almost done
and then I have to turn the heat off, right?
Do I have to grind this up?
Do I turn the heat off?
All right.
We're good.
I think I might have fucked it up.
It's cooking for like three times the length.
Take it off the heat.
No.
It's not done.
Where's my plate?
Double heat.
Hurry up.
I'm trying.
All right.
And done.
I need to...
No.
This way.
How much soup is soup?
How much soup do I need?
How much is it?
How much soup do you need?
300 milliliters.
How much time do I have?
20...
Okay.
I gotta dump this a little bit in the sink,
into the trash.
Oh my fucking god.
The whole thing came out.
300.
What?
Oh my god.
I don't have time.
Go.
Too much carrot.
Too much parsley.
Too much onion.
What?
I mean too much.
It was the same.
It was the right amount.
Dude, that's hard to pour.
All right.
The food critic's gonna be here.
Okay.
Food critic is here.
The food critic wants tomato soup.
Let's get this right.
Okay.
We need that pot.
Just watering down the soup.
Is there any water?
You want water?
This is how we save money in the restaurant business.
Okay.
What do I need?
700 milliliters chicken broth.
Salt.
12 grams.
12.
I need...
I just gotta clean.
Okay.
Clean chicken broth.
How much is in here?
Not enough.
Throw it away.
700.
What was it?
750?
700.
12.
6.
And 6 of cayenne pepper.
6 and then tomatoes and onions.
6 cayenne pepper.
All right.
We need tomatoes.
How many tomatoes?
Don't fucking run into the wall.
We need 960 grams of tomatoes and then one onion.
Let's get the onion in there.
Onion.
Did I just put a potato?
Okay.
Tomatoes.
So I need...
How many tomatoes?
Done.
Get it over here.
That's it.
Boil for 60 seconds and blend it.
And add sour cream.
Boil.
60 second blend.
60 second time.
Get the blender ready.
Sour cream.
150.
Not enough in there.
Dump it.
150.
Get ready to blend.
And then after the sour cream, we pour it in a deep plate.
300 milliliters.
Got it.
Come on.
Hurry up.
Fuck up.
Boil for 60 seconds and then blend and then turn off the heat.
Right?
Go.
Then turn the heat off.
Okay.
Heat off.
Sour cream.
150.
Is it good?
What's dumping?
Deep plate.
Done.
This doesn't look cooked.
Is it sure it's cooked?
Okay.
That's fine.
Done.
Water up.
He loved it.
He just absolutely couldn't get enough.
No complaints.
New fame level.
New...
Oh, we're about done.
The day's still going on.
Oh, okay.
We need salmon filet.
Last chance.
This customer leaves disappointed.
We're going to lose a star.
What?
It's salmon.
You know, I need to like...
Okay.
Salmon.
Salt, pepper.
Come on.
Salt and pepper.
Right here.
Five gram.
One, two, three, four, five.
Oil in the pan.
Oh my God.
Add the pan.
Sunflower oil and salmon filet.
60 seconds on each side.
Okay.
Oil in the pan.
Where's the pan?
I threw the pan in the fucking trash.
Oh my God.
I'm panicking.
Pan?
Pan.
Get a pan.
Sunflower oil.
What was it?
Ten?
Sunflower oil.
Ten milliliters.
60 seconds on each side.
Okay.
Timer.
Go.
Okay.
Next.
I need boiled potatoes.
Water.
A thousand.
A thousand water.
All right.
I did the thing.
Everybody could laugh.
Fucking feels good when you do a perfect water.
A thousand.
Don't even look at it.
Let's go.
Salt.
20.
Potato 300.
Salt 20.
I don't have time to do that.
Where's the salt?
Where's the...
Where's the flipper?
Where's the spatula?
I have to do with my hand.
Where's the fucking spatula?
Where is the spatula?
Oh my fucking God.
I do it every time.
What happened to the pan?
What?
Where's the pan?
Stop ringing at me.
Come on.
No.
Where's the pan?
That's bullshit.
Everything was going all right.
Why is the pan gone?
Come on.
This is so much money.
That's fucking ridiculous.
Honest to God.
I can't even use this burner anymore.
I can't restart?
Oh my fucking God.
No.
Pick up the salmon.
What are you doing?
People are fucking beeping at me.
It's fucking ruined.
I'm so upset right now.
What was that?
What else?
Add potato salt to the water.
I just got screwed.
All right.
Salt in the water.
Get the potatoes in there.
How many do I need?
Potato.
300.
Two potatoes.
Get it on there.
Boil.
How's this doing?
Spatula.
Plate.
Where's the plate?
Do I not have any money to buy a plate?
What the fuck am I supposed to do about this?
Um, all right.
But that wasn't even my fault.
The thing fucking disappeared.
I lost my pan and now I can't get another one.
There's another order.
Yeah, but I can't even get it.
I can't even buy a plate.
Just serve it in the pan.
Can I even do that?
They do that at hipster restaurants.
That's true.
Let's see if this works.
Why are people taking the plates home?
Yeah, that's weird.
No, I can't even.
Like, I need, I don't even have four cents.
What the fuck?
I have to redo today.
This is not fair.
Can I like redo the day?
Yeah, I'll give you a fucking restaurant.
How does this sound?
Quit fucking beeping at me.
It's too hot to pick up.
All right.
When was this saved?
23 minutes ago.
All right.
This time I hope the stove doesn't eat my...
Oh my god.
I have to do the whole day again.
Why did it eat my pan though?
It just deleted my fucking pan.
All right.
I'm upset about that.
I'm gonna get this shit ready now.
So I don't have to not have enough money to buy.
All right.
Here we go.
Prep day.
I did so good on that first fish too.
All right.
Let's get the spices in the right place.
Spatula.
Hang it up.
Blender.
We'll just put it right there.
That's fine.
We need fresh chicken broth.
We need fresh sour cream.
We need fresh tomatoes.
I got the plates.
Is there any dirt?
Let's go with chicken broth.
Let's get it over here.
What if you fool?
What?
This is why I don't have any money.
Well, I can, I...
Well, it's a new day.
Just relax.
That looks good.
Anything else?
Any of those things I need to clean up?
I got plenty of time.
Just use the spilled oil.
Oh my god.
That's fucking revolting.
All right.
No spills today.
I'm gonna be ready completely.
Is the oven still on?
This looks like shit.
And oven's on.
Turn it off.
I think I broke the oven by leaving it on all day.
So how much time I got?
45 seconds to get the pot.
Let's get the pot right here.
My spices.
Get them on the right spot.
This is gonna be clean today.
Salt.
Where's the...
There's the bowls.
There's plates.
Cutting board.
Nice spot.
All right.
Get it on the right area.
Use the radio.
All right.
Hold on.
There's no time for the radio right now.
I got my seasonings.
I got my spices.
I got my knife.
I got 11 seconds to turn the radio on.
Now playing on cheesy FM.
Cooking satay.
All right.
That...
I told you to get classical music.
That's fine.
New order.
Here we go.
Thousand chicken broth.
Salt.
Pepper.
Into the pot.
One.
Two.
Three.
Almost.
Come on, come on.
Clean it up.
Come on.
A little bit more.
Clean it up.
That's good.
Perfect.
Good, good, good, good, good, good, good, good.
Salt, pepper, right?
There's my salt.
There's my pepper.
One, two, three, four, five, six, seven, eight, nine, ten, eleven, twelve, thirteen, fourteen, fifteen, sixteen, seventeen, eighteen, nineteen, twenty.
In the hall of the mountain king?
This is the Lord of the Rings?
I think it was already content ID claimed because I don't hear it.
Yeah.
Okay.
What was next?
Next is beetroot, onion, carrot, parsley.
Beetroot.
Onion.
Carrot.
Let me get the onion.
Beetroot.
What was it?
Five.
It was five of these, right?
What about parsley?
It was one parsley.
Five of these.
And was there a carrot, too?
Beetroot, onion, it was one carrot.
No, yeah, it was one carrot.
Okay, here we go.
Boil it up.
Boil for 120 seconds.
I need to blend it, too, don't I?
It doesn't say to blend.
I mean, it doesn't say blend.
So just boil it for 120 seconds.
And then deep, deep plate.
And I'm good.
I haven't been counting any time.
How many seconds has it been?
Okay, let's clean up.
Clean up.
Clean up as we go.
Chicken broth, there's nothing in there.
I think I need another one of these, right?
Every chef will tell you clean as you go.
Onions are cooked.
That was less than one milliliter in there.
I didn't waste money.
Okay, the onions are cooked.
The parsley, everything else needs to cook.
And then just pour it into here.
Onions are getting a little crunchy.
Okay, that's it.
Get it in the bowl.
It was 300, right?
Only like 40 something more.
Just a little bit.
That's close enough.
I don't think I can get 10 from this.
Oh, whatever.
You get extra.
Happy fucking birthday.
That's all right.
Not bad.
Complaints were it was too much pepper.
Too much salt.
Wasn't it?
It's too much.
It was 20 and 20, right?
All right, quiet.
Here comes the critic, right?
I got everything I need.
I got the plate.
Here comes the fish.
Pepper, thyme, dill, trout.
No, wait, no.
Get in one of the trays.
Get in there.
In case somebody orders this again, just leave it on here.
Pepper, thyme, dill, trout.
Pepper, thyme, dill.
Pepper, thyme, dill, dill.
I need one more.
Got it.
Pepper, thyme, pepper, dill.
Pepper, thyme, dill.
Come on.
Pepper, thyme, dill, trout.
Pepper, thyme.
All right.
That's it.
Baking tray.
Put it in baking.
90 seconds.
God damn it.
I fucking can't believe it.
You can't run every fucking time.
90 seconds.
Let's do 80.
Let's do like just that.
I can come back and look.
Okay, they got the plate.
Now we got the potatoes.
No, the lemon.
It's not potatoes, it's lemon.
Lemon, lemon.
One lemon quartered.
Here we go.
Freeze time.
Pretty good technique.
All right.
Good.
Wait for the fish.
Need a plate.
And then we need fresh parsley.
Six grams.
How you doing in there?
Pretty good.
Just get the parsley on it now.
Because who cares?
I swear to God.
Fucking Burger King.
I don't want to run.
There's a perk to run faster.
Why the fuck would I want that?
Oh, right, right, right, right.
Is done?
Not yet.
That was horseradish.
Where is it?
It's the yellow one.
Five.
Is this five on there?
I didn't see it.
Was it five?
Tell me quick.
Was it four?
Good.
Fucking parsley's on the ground.
All right, here you go.
Yummy.
I can't wait for you to try this.
I've dropped everything.
You can't tell the difference though.
Forty-eight.
That's better than yesterday.
No complaints at all.
All right.
I still have that.
Easy.
New order, huh?
Done.
I'm gonna be shocked to how fucking quick this one comes out.
Take it.
It was still hot.
Too much salt.
Did we...
Did I put...
No, I had exactly a thousand chicken broth in there.
Two col...
How many orders do I have to do here?
Tomato soup.
Fuck.
Okay, tomato soup is...
Seven hundred.
Twelve, twelve.
Seven hundred, twelve, twelve.
Seven hundred.
Chicken broth.
Where's my chicken broth?
Is it still any in there?
No.
Seven hundred.
Come on.
Okay, twelve, twelve.
Pepper.
Salt.
Twelve.
Black pepper.
All right.
Here we go.
And we need six cayenne.
Tomatoes.
Eight tomatoes and one onion.
Three, four, five, six, seven, eight.
And then one onion, right?
Was it an onion?
It was an onion, right?
It was one onion?
It was an onion.
C.
What do you mean C?
What?
What's the matter?
Is it just too big on the screen?
What do I do?
Bun?
Boil for sixty seconds and then blend.
Sixty seconds.
Timer.
Fifty seconds.
Then blend it.
Add sour cream.
Sour cream.
I'm ready.
We did it.
Hello?
All right.
I'm on a new station.
We'll keep the jazz.
This sounds like a song being played in reverse.
All right.
Here we go.
Turn this off.
Blend it up.
Done.
Turn off the heat.
Okay, done.
Add sour cream.
How much sour cream was it?
I just got fucking completely blanked.
How much sour cream?
One fifty.
How much is in there now?
That's enough.
Where's my bowl?
It's so hard to pour that.
I'm buying a ladle.
It's impossible.
Sixty-four to thirty.
I'm doing better than I was.
Not enough sour cream.
I thought it's too much.
We good?
Does anybody think that I'm like stuck in an infinite loop here?
Isn't this day two?
Salmon fillet.
Salt and pepper.
Save the game.
All right.
Salmon.
So salt and pepper.
Yeah.
I need that pan.
Okay.
This is where I fucked up last time.
I threw...
I fucked up everything from the very beginning.
Throwing away the pan in the very beginning was the worst thing ever.
Okay.
Pan.
Oil.
We have salmon fillet and five for both salt and pepper.
These are so expensive.
Salt.
Pepper.
Okay.
Get in there.
Three.
Four.
Five.
Salt.
Pepper.
And then we need to oil the pan.
Sunflower oil.
Salmon fillet.
Ten milliliters only.
All right.
Hold on.
Let's get the other thing going.
We need boiled potatoes.
Don't get rid of that.
There's still soup in there.
How did that not go in the fucking sink?
Fuck you, sink.
All right.
Boiled potatoes.
Thousand water, right?
Okay.
Twenty.
I have salt and then potatoes.
Let's get the salt in there.
One.
Two.
Three.
Four.
Five.
Six.
Seven.
Eight.
Nine.
Ten.
Eleven.
Twelve.
Thirty.
Forty.
Fifty.
Six.
Seven.
Eight.
Nine.
Twenty.
All right.
Potatoes.
How many potatoes?
Two.
That's a lemon.
That's not a potato.
Boiled.
Here we go.
One.
Two.
Three.
Four.
Ten.
Eleven.
120 seconds.
Boiled for 120 seconds.
Okay.
Looking good.
Flip it with my spatula.
I hung it up, right?
I did.
Good.
Smart boy.
I'm gonna go for a flip.
Don't!
Every time I fuck this up.
I'm not gonna fuck it up.
I do it every single time.
Not this time though.
This is the time where I actually get it back in the pan.
Got it.
He got it.
Do it again.
All right.
Need a plate.
Here we go.
Serve hot.
That's it.
Just get a plate.
Do I have one?
Is a broken one over there.
Basic plate.
Okay.
I'm almost ready.
Potatoes come out.
This is gonna be 100.
It's gonna be like 120 seconds.
All right.
Here we go.
Almost done.
This is gonna be perfect.
It's gonna be right on time.
Okay.
One.
Two.
Three.
Take it out.
Don't drop it.
Oh no.
Is it over the...
Come on.
How do you do this?
All right.
Give her the plate.
Stop ringing.
I wish it didn't ring this much.
Done.
What did I do wrong?
Potatoes with too much salt.
Why does the recipe say 20 grams if it's too much?
Okay.
I'm done.
So.
Did I do at least four stars?
Okay.
Let's clean up.
I got...
Okay.
This is perfect.
This is amazing.
I got plenty of time.
I gotta clean this stove.
Clean this shit up.
Into the sink.
No.
Dump it in the sink.
All right.
I'm not gonna do that anymore.
Just get it in the sink.
There we go.
Finally.
I just poured it into the oven.
Come on.
Get out of the fucking way.
Why?
Why is it playing like the Godfather music?
Is somebody gonna come here and whack me?
Can I not clean this?
I don't think I can clean in here.
All right.
Pots are ready.
Hang the spatula up.
Sour cream.
There's not very much left in there.
There is a little bit.
Okay.
Let's get the spices back to normal.
Turn off the heat.
That would be nice.
Blend.
All right.
That's fine.
Look at how fucking dirty it is in here.
All right.
Give me the...
What?
I can't clean that?
Do I need to buy a new stove?
How much time do I got?
A couple minutes.
Let's get the cutting board in a good spot.
Get the knife on over here.
Salt and pepper.
Put them together.
The other spices can just hang out over here.
Everything that needs salt always needs pepper,
so I'm just gonna keep them right next to each other.
The rest of these can just hang out over here.
All right.
I'm gonna get a new recipe.
I'm gonna use it eventually, so just keep it over here.
Here's the reverse jazz...
Don't break.
The reverse jazz song.
I can clean that.
I can't clean this.
None of this is even dirty.
Okay.
I'm good.
Anything else that I need to do?
Besides mop?
I'll write this.
Yeah.
The broken plate on the ground.
There's no broom or something.
I can definitely sweep, right?
You have to be able to sweep.
Yeah.
I'll get a stove cleaning company.
Here.
I got a better idea.
No, I'm not gonna throw it in the...
I'm just doing this so I don't have to run around.
Don't waste.
What do you...
Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait.
You want me to use already old cooked ingredients for tomorrow?
Is that gonna work?
That's how stock is made.
Yeah.
I don't think that people are gonna want to eat like an old cooked tomato.
All right.
Heat proof gloves.
Long reach.
Thermal division.
Connections.
Time slows when cutting ingredients.
I think I'm gonna do long arms or heat proof gloves.
Yeah.
All right.
So I can just pick shit up and move it around.
Or long hands.
Let's do long arms.
So I gave them a lot of money.
This is not as important.
Hold on.
Is there one I can increase the time?
Experience points.
More fame.
Products cost less.
I mean, this is important.
Liquids stuff costs less.
I'm doing it twice.
Demonstrate your skills.
All right.
I cleaned up a little bit so I should be good to go.
Repair company.
Quickly.
Hurry up.
13 seconds.
Quickly.
Come on, come on, come on.
How long is it gonna take?
15 seconds?
This is expensive.
Okay.
Fine.
We're good.
All right.
I got two minutes until I'm ready to go.
I'm getting my ingredients out.
I'm getting a couple of chicken broths.
Can I buy a recipe?
Not owned.
Okay.
Pork chops with baked potatoes.
I can do that.
Do more soups?
I don't have, I don't think I can do soups.
Duck broth.
I'm not famous enough for duck broth.
I can do pork chop and baked potatoes.
Yeah.
Pork chops.
I can't buy soups.
Perks.
Skills.
Everything's good to go.
All right.
So I'm gonna pre-make the soup.
I need to pre-make soup.
So let's get it out.
Let's get the ingredients out.
Just pre-make everything and then put it in the microwave.
All right.
Here's the soup.
I already got it right here.
What do I need?
No, this is all...
I need one more beet, right?
One more beet?
No, that's not gonna work.
Is this gonna work?
And then an onion, right?
This is not gonna work, guys.
No, I'm throwing this shit away.
Which one is the one that I just bought?
I'm not gonna serve customers old food.
That's not how it works.
This is the new one.
Gordon Ramsay would come in this restaurant
and start fucking trashing the place.
Five and then I need an onion.
No, what is it?
Carrot and then parsley, right?
Parsley and then what is it?
One onion, right?
And then it's chicken broth or is it water?
Let's get like two or three chicken broths out here.
And sour cream.
Well, not yet, not yet.
Don't overbuy everything.
All right, I got my spices.
I got my pre-made soup.
Wait, what's the other one?
The other one's tomato, right?
Let's get over here.
How many tomatoes is it?
It's one, two, eight tomatoes.
Eight and then it's one onion, right?
Eight and then an onion, I think.
Okay, that's good to go.
Now that's also chicken broth, right?
Here we go.
This is why you prep.
New order.
Fish.
I know this one by heart almost.
Where's my tray?
Where's the fucking tray?
Come on, man.
Really?
I prepped and everything and the tray's just not here anymore.
I don't own a tray anymore.
Are you kidding me?
I'm wasting fucking time already.
Okay, it's pepper time, dill.
Three, four, five.
Get it.
Pepper is right next to it, right here.
And then bake 90 seconds.
Get it in there.
90 seconds and then hoist.
Yep.
Don't run like you usually do.
What the fuck are you doing?
Get it in the oven.
91, two, four, five, six, seven, eight, nine, ten.
I just did way too much time.
Okay, now we got the lemon quarter.
Just get it ready.
Freeze time.
Excellent.
Right down the middle.
Right down the center.
Perfect.
Not perfect, but it's okay.
Could be worse.
Plate.
Do I already have a plate?
No, I do not, Jeremy.
Focus, god damn it.
You're gonna lose everything.
When that shit comes out, we got horseradish five.
Get it on the plate.
Parsley.
Come on.
You done?
Oh, come on.
Hurry up and be done.
You're killing me.
One, two, three.
Horseradish.
One, two, three, four, five.
Easy.
Parsley.
Six.
Okay, done.
Enjoy.
Bon appetit.
Dick.
Don't be that mad.
And here you go, you dick.
All right, I'm prepped.
New order.
The Bostromish, whatever this is called.
All right, everything's ready.
Chicken broth.
Salt.
Chicken broth, salt.
Pepper.
Everything's already in there.
Chicken broth, salt, pepper.
Fucking close enough.
Salt and pepper.
20 of each.
20.
Did that actually get in there?
Am I crazy?
Did that say 10?
Did that not all go in?
Did it not all go in?
That was fucking weird.
It said 12.
All right, where's my pepper?
This is why I fucking prepped.
Give me my pepper, god damn it.
20.
Okay.
1, 2, 3, 4, 5, 6, 7, 8, 9, 10, 11, 12, 13, 14, 15, 16, 17, 18, 19, 20.
I'm understanding what's happening here.
I have salted.
I put like 20 grams of salt on one beat.
Oh my fucking god, whatever.
Okay, boil the time.
Just boil, go.
I don't have time for this.
120 seconds.
Put it on.
On 10.
All right, here we go.
Now we just fucking hang out.
Who cares?
I didn't mix it into the broth somehow.
You don't stir this up.
I want to pick it up by the sides and just like shake it around.
I'm gonna blow this place up.
Put propane in the oven.
I'm not doing that yet.
Give me another order so I can start prepping.
Add 40 seconds to the timer.
I want to just like start breaking stuff.
No.
The onions are overcooked.
Not yet.
They will be very soon.
Almost done?
Almost done, almost done, almost done, almost done, almost done, almost done,
one, two, three, four, five.
Why are the onions so overcooked?
You put everything in the pot and you boil it at the same time.
I don't understand.
Take the onion out.
All right, off, out, into a bowl.
And then sayonara.
Just pick up the onion with your hand.
Am I ever gonna buy a ladle for this shit?
Order up.
Italian borscht.
Pretty good.
Not enough pepper.
Yeah, I understand what's happening now.
All right, here comes the food critic.
Save the fucking game.
Here we go.
Oh no, I've never made this before.
I don't know how to do this.
Of course he orders the new thing.
I don't know how to make pork chops.
Okay, pork chops.
How many do I need?
Two?
Just one.
All right, and then salt the pork chop with black pepper and salt.
And then thyme.
So thyme, six grams.
One, six.
And then salt and pepper, four.
Evenly season it.
Four, nice.
For Minecraft food.
Somebody says, okay, pan.
Don't forget about the food critic.
What do you mean time's running out?
What the fuck are you talking about?
Sunflower oil, pork chops.
Okay, 30 milliliters of sunflower oil.
Sunflower oil.
30 milliliters of sunflower oil.
What do you mean mixture?
Is the oil already in here?
There's like dirty fish oil in here.
Hope you're not allergic.
All right, so we got fry for 90 seconds each side.
Okay, fry for, what else do we need to do?
And then bake potatoes.
And then you bake.
Okay, cut potato into chunks.
Cut potato, 300 grams of potatoes into chunks.
Okay, I need to say, pause it.
I just took my hand, picked it up with my fucking hand.
And forcibly tried to stick it to the table.
Like, like I was making a, oh.
Oh my God.
All right, I need to focus.
300 grams of potatoes.
How many potatoes is that?
I do need a plate eventually here.
So 300 grams of potatoes.
It's two potatoes.
Transfer them over to here.
So I got to cut these into chunks of 50 grams.
So I need six chunks.
So cut them into threes.
Oh, chunks of 50.
And that's, that's, yeah, that's six.
I didn't do anything wrong.
Baking tray, bake for 80 seconds.
Where's the baking tray?
Already in there.
Okay, turn the oven on.
80 seconds.
Here we go.
Now let's just fry, fry, fry, fry, fry, fry, fry.
I put tomato soup in there.
All right, fry for 90 seconds a side.
Okay, good.
I think.
Okay, now anything else?
Anything else?
Just transfer them onto the plate.
Hot.
Where's my spatula?
I'm ready for this shit.
I'm a flipping master at this point.
Potatoes?
What do you mean potatoes?
These are fine.
They're fine, they're fine, they're fine.
Don't fucking freak me out like that.
Like another five seconds.
This was on a perfect timer.
They're done.
No, put this down.
Put it down.
Put the tray down.
Oh, where's my, where's my flipper?
What the?
Got it.
What?
I didn't do anything.
It's not fair.
90 seconds.
50, 60, 70, 80.
I don't know.
Oh, I'm, I'm cooking on there.
I can't fucking believe it.
Why did that happen?
Motherfucker.
Just went through the bottom of the pan.
Unbelievable.
At least these are done.
Let me clean up while I go here.
It exploded on me.
That's bullshit.
Get it on a plate and hopefully I get four stars.
Hopefully it doesn't taste the glass.
I'm gonna be crunching on it.
Oh, this is good.
I taste a heavy iron.
That's a really strong iron taste.
It stings too.
Is this spices on?
Is this hot sauce on here?
My mouth is, my mouth hurts.
All right, let's go.
I see this, I don't like,
why can't I just like put it down?
I need to get the gloves.
Oh my fucking god.
I just can't put it down.
Why can't I just place it?
Oh my god.
I just, good enough.
Hope you like it.
Come on.
Not enough.
I lost a bunch of fame.
Well blame the salmon filet.
I'm gonna scum this.
Here we go.
How do you clean it?
Is it clean?
It's clean.
Nothing in here, right?
Here we go.
Now I'll get this,
I'll get the pan.
It's empty.
Okay, what do I do now?
What do I do?
Okay, pork chops.
Salt, black pepper, thyme.
Yep.
Two, three, four.
It's the thyme.
Wait, it was six thyme.
Six, okay.
Then we need pepper salt.
Oh fuck.
Turn it off, turn it off.
One, two, three, four.
Got it.
All right.
Three, four.
All right, got like the dinosaur dropping zone there.
That's it.
Now we add oil to the pan and pork chop.
Let's get the potatoes ready as well.
I got plenty of time.
It's two potatoes.
Stop.
Okay, I'm like panicking for no reason.
Plate, potatoes.
It's two.
Two, sunflower oil, pork chop.
Potato into chunks of 50 grams.
And then I didn't salt them.
Okay, they're all getting cooked anyways.
Don't relax.
Chunks of three.
Don't do it like that.
Don't be a fucking idiot.
Oh shit.
How many did I cut?
It's okay.
I can cook them and it doesn't matter.
Salt them.
Six grams of salt.
One, two, four, five, six.
Come on, six.
Get them on the tray.
Is there a reason why this doesn't work half the time?
Get in the fucking oven.
What are you doing?
Go.
Heat the oil.
30 milliliters.
Heat.
Heat the oil.
Here we go.
I'm ready.
Not fucking this up again.
Here we go.
One, two, three.
Wait till the oil is heated.
90 seconds.
All right, whew.
We're good.
We're almost done.
I don't know what to do with my hands right now.
All right, I gotta get ready.
I need a place to put this shit.
Move this out of the way.
Okay, perfect.
Clean that up.
Put the tray here onto this.
Yep.
Okay, timer.
Looking good.
Spatula.
Where is it?
The oil is burning.
Oh fuck.
I thought I had to wait till oil to heat up.
The oil is like on fire.
Fuck the potatoes.
No.
I only need a few.
I only need six.
Okay, what about this?
This is almost done, right?
Flip.
Where's my splipper?
Okay, slow down.
Slow down.
Oh yeah.
Okay, good.
Shut up.
Good.
All right.
Potatoes.
I need six.
Which ones didn't fall on the ground?
One, two, three, four.
Five, six.
Good.
Then put the pork chop on top and we're done.
90 seconds aside.
Where's my spatula?
Come on.
It's going to go to the red in a minute.
No, catch it before it falls.
Catch it.
Thank god.
It's almost done.
That's getting evenly cooked, right?
It better be.
10 seconds.
Nine, eight, seven, six.
Done.
That is very haphazard.
You don't get points for presentation, right?
Like this doesn't matter.
Just eat it.
We got our fame points.
Critic is pleased.
There's too much salt in the potatoes.
Well, cry me a river.
Timeline has been saved.
Thank god.
All right.
Closing down for the night.
No more orders.
Let's clean up.
Um, can I just save this?
I have an idea.
Hold on.
Can I do this?
I can't like store this in the fridge.
Well, here.
Just, I fucking hate this.
I swear to god.
I can't like keep leftovers in the...
I just wasted money now.
I wanted to keep leftovers in the fridge.
Leftovers somewhere.
Now I have to clean all this shit up.
Yeah, this is my Academy Award.
Why is there a timer up here?
Uh, all right.
I need to do song.
Nothing on the counter needs to be cleaned, right?
In the mop.
Why can't I rotate the mop?
It says rotate, but you can't rotate.
This is how I usually clean the floor.
I go like this.
I just kind of run back and forth from side to side
and just hold it in a new angle.
Usually does a pretty good job.
I need to pick up the glass.
I wanted to prepare.
This is not prepping for tomorrow.
This is bullshit.
This is needing to pick up glass
because I'm trying to put a bowl of soup in the fucking oven.
I'm very upset about this.
All right.
We good?
I think we're good.
Let me just move this stuff out of the way.
Come here.
Clean the pans.
This is dirty.
Let's get hot water.
How do I just dump it?
All right, that should be clean, right?
Yep, clean pan.
Still have plenty of oil.
Get the oil up here.
This is like only one milliliter thrown away.
I got plenty of chicken broth.
I got plenty of sour cream.
That's just still out.
Can I put this in the fridge?
Is this rot?
I don't think it does, guys.
I think we're fine.
52 bucks.
Reached level four.
Okay.
Request reward.
Cheaper liquid, I think.
Yeah.
Cheaper liquid.
Cheaper spices.
Probably cheap.
No, cheaper liquid twice.
What better tips?
Dish taste tolerance.
Yeah, more tips.
And taste tolerance.
That sounds good to me.
Choose a recipe.
Here we go.
I already have this.
I already own it.
Pork chops with bacon.
I already did it.
I did it already.
130.
Expand menu.
Am I actually soft-locked right now?
No.
I have to reload before I bought this.
No, don't make me do that again.
That's like an hour and a half ago.
Oh, no.
What?
Open the console?
There is no developer console.
I physically can't even get out of here.
I have to alt F4 the game.
No.
Why?
Oh, come on.
This sucks.
There's really no way for me to get out of here,
is there?
No.
I'm stuck.
Well, I can just do sandbox.
Fuck.
I was having a lot of fun.
Yeah, I was going to go into sandbox.
Damn it.
That's frustrating.
Oh, well.
Because I bought the recipe already.
Just do it again.
What's going on now?
I bought the baked potato,
and I was going to say,
what the hell is happening?
Sandbox mode.
Let's try Sam.
What about the auto save?
And we have to do that whole day again.
What's the difference between these two?
Is there a difference?
I don't think you get recipes here.
I don't think you get orders.
Yeah, this is just...
There's nothing here.
You just destroy the kitchen.
You just have infinite meats.
There's no order.
I'm so sad right now.
I'm trying to cook the propane.
There we go.
Is this going to work?
Let the propane simmer.
Why is this not exploded?
Yeah, hold on here.
Just get a little bit of rice vinegar on here.
All right, looks good.
How about some of this oregano?
Sounds good.
How do I get this to blow up?
What the fuck?
No, get it in the oven.
Get a blow torch.
All right, give me utensils.
Knife.
Spatula.
Sponge.
Just knife and just start stabbing it?
Blow torch.
Okay, now let's...
Like, Jesus Christ.
Let's get the fuck out of me.
I didn't think it was going to happen.
This shit was on the stove for like five minutes and it didn't blow up.
All right, I need to...
I'm going to go play the game.
I have to reload this stupid soft lock.
Throw the pizzas out the window.
Yeah, I'm just going to microwave a bunch of fruits.
Microwave a pumpkin.
Does this happen if you put a pumpkin in the microwave?
Oh, it's making noises I don't like.
Microwave some metal.
All right, that's half it.
This is like going to like irradiate the room.
If you touch that right now, you would like turn to stone.
Can I pick it up?
Oh, I can.
There we go.
Why is it still working?
Steam is coming out of the top but...
Holy shit, it actually makes a fire.
Does the fire spread?
Is it like the Sims?
Pumpkin is black.
All right, what would it take for you to eat this?
That shouldn't be able to...
I need more fire.
I need more explosive shit.
No, come here.
Drop it right here.
All right, burn.
Fire.
Here we go.
All right, we got a fire.
Oh, come on.
Stop.
Come on.
Why can you not blow these up?
Can I fry-a-late it?
I'm gonna deep fry a propane tank.
That's perfectly safe.
There's no oil in there.
Oh, I'll get oil.
What's the worst oil in the world?
Huh?
It's got like a bomb dropped on me.
Lime juice, soy sauce, which what has a high olive oil?
Yeah.
Okay, everything's fine.
We're good to go.
Turn every oven on.
Is this what the last guy did?
It's still cooking.
Torch the place.
Let's go.
Come on, blow up.
What's with this fire?
I'm trying to like burn my eyes.
Turn it around this way.
My face in here.
Why is it...
Wait, that just exploded.
Why is it gas coming in?
I threw a cucumber and it exploded.
It's a grenade?
All right, that was fun.
I need to like go play the fucking game now.
Is that enough for me to forget what happened?
Where was...
Where did I buy the recipe?
The lore was just getting good.
Okay, I have here and here.
Do I not have...
Is quicksave broken?
Do I not have a save before?
This is the...
Is the autosave dead?
Let me check.
Are both dead?
They're not.
I don't think they are.
They're not both dead.
We just have to do the day before again.
All right, let me like go get...
Let me get a glass of water.
I'll be right back.
We're just gonna pretend we didn't do...
And make a bug report.
Dad, don't worry.
I'll mute the music for you.
We'll fix it.
All right, I'll be right back.
Let's get a glass of water.
Hopefully we can get through this quickly.
I'll be right back.
Hey.
All right, let's try this again.
As severely disappointed as I am that we have to do this third time.
Because this is number three.
This is three strikes, you're up.
This will be strike three coming up.
The first time it went through the floor, my pan, and I had to restart.
Second time, I got softlocked.
Third time, let's see.
All right, we're good.
This is prep.
Oh, what do I need to do?
For a second, I thought all the...
This place was exploded.
It's not.
All right, repair.
I've been waiting years for this game.
Yeah, well, I was waiting like at least a few months.
It's fine, 28 seconds.
Kitchen Nightmares OST.
No, okay, I will put on the Kitchen Nightmares American OST.
When we get to a new level.
By the way, the Kitchen Nightmares OST is just every American reality show OST.
Run, run, run, run, run, run, run, run, run, run, run, run, run, run.
I hate watching those shows.
Five community subs just came in from Anonymous, thank you.
Whoever you are.
Oh, I gotta play.
Okay, what would...
I only got a minute, fuck.
Is this clean?
No, there's a blend in here.
All right, giving this another shot.
We keep doing Groundhog Day.
What did I...
Oh, fuck, this is before the...
I had all the stuff ready to go to.
Why game?
why have you done this to me two three four five carrot and onion all right set it up chicken
stock how much is in here 300 i need a cup i need two more by the way uh might as well
just start talking about this now so people know what's going on um not monday sunday
i will be doing uh a microsoft conference that's what i'm gonna start my i'm gonna pause it
because i'm just wasting time i'm doing the microsoft conference and the one that's after it
i'm gonna do e3 coverage we're gonna do an e3 stream okay cool just want to make sure you
know all right lightning around this right now please to get the salmon and the potatoes two
potatoes give me the pot good thing i didn't love this up with tomato soup potatoes ready
one two water boil it's water give me the water no water am i doing normie e3 coverage if
you saw my coverage last uh last year i uh had a lot to say a lot you don't like salt the water
right fuck you do salt the water don't do that yet yeah i had a lot to say six seventeen eighteen
nineteen come on come on twenty what the fuck just boil it for christ's sake all right
salmon five and five pepper five sit her down salt one two three four five not strike three
that's not straight through yet and then we need uh sunflower oil and then salmon in the pan
let's go sunflower oil ten make sure i don't have fish fishy oil next on the next one
heat it up let's go no not the whole tray just the salmon all right 60 seconds right
60 seconds each side i don't even need it i can just look at it like this no i need it i need
it i need i need the timer i need the timer potatoes are almost done get a plate just put
it on the plate from here this seems to be a hearthstone stream i mean it was a hearthstone
stream for but that's a mask i'm gonna run out of time spatula you are correct it was a
hearthstone stream once uh oh they're gonna be right all right flip it good all right this
is good this is nice and clean that was a good flip burnt it no i didn't i did i burn it a little
that's extra crispy crusty crust that's fine you guys don't like crispy skin my favorite
kind of salmon is crispy skin salmon i'm cooking it the way that i like it yeah that's
the skin what did you guys think that was i like my salmon i have a good crunch yeah it's
really good why does it sound like it's burning done there you go here's a nice
crispy crunchy skin how could i have made that any better explain that to me too much salt on
the boiled potatoes and i made a heating mistake what heating mistake i'm gonna be a defensive chef
here okay all right i got this is almost ready so yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah boil for 60 seconds
just blend it and add sour cream it's all right it's right here ready to go just need
the chicken stock that's fine chicken stock uh they're fucking way too much in there it
doesn't matter just cook it boil it i thought it was a thousand all right cook it and then
oh shit this is tomato soup this is tomato it's the same color it looks this exact same
no don't have a meltdown here just fucking do it right all right that's clean right
get it on here chicken stock chicken stock i got a fresh one this is not a fresh one
i'm fucked right now there's only 300 in here but those this is empty oh my god
come on i need four close enough 700 all right now i need the tomatoes i need chicken broth salt
salt it salt it salt this salt it up 12 okay done and then uh pepper i wasn't prepared for
this and then that's just i need the eight uh tomatoes and an onion get it on here and then
you uh boil the 60 seconds blend it sour cream why is it playing this song
this makes me want to stop breaking stuff what if i get cayenne got it 60 seconds and then
blend i am counting i gotta blend it and then add sour cream all right turn this shit off
get the doom ost on here i will eventually turn it off blend it up sour cream what is it 150
don't care this is what you get how did only 80 get in here how did only 34 get in there
what are you talking about how much is in there now okay bowl sir ladle just get one
there are no ladles how do you play what you're actually supposed to dump it out
i'm surprised you are supposed to do this i'll clean it later oh my fucking god i can't
believe it whatever why would you not have a ladle why do you have to dump it from the pot
that's no there's no way i definitely unlock a ladle oh my god that's so fucking hard to
do this here extra soup who cares that's so hard to pour the soup it goes from like one
milliliter every second to like 500 in a tenth of a centimeter moving your hand
there has to be a ladle all right another trout let's go all right pepper time deal
all the same right five where do you think i'm doing this why is it all okay deal i clearly
clicked it five damn times all right pepper why isn't vr they probably would update it to vr
eventually i think all right get it in the oven baking sheets i think still in there
i'm not gonna make the same mistake i make every time you know what that is it's called
turning too quickly and the fish falls on the ground one two three 90 seconds what's the timer
10 seconds had already gone by guys all right fish is in the oven quarter the lemon
one and not perfect but it's fine we're ready to go and we just need you to horse radish and then
six grams of parsley good to go plate horse radishes horse horse radish horse radish i'm
saying it right horse radish how do you say horse uh rin the cutest thanks for the five
community subs rin sub drop coming in right now while we wait for our food to be ready
which it is about five seconds and just a second thank you for the five steps one two three done
all right horse radish five grams right yes i actually love horse radish can i tell you
i use too much i love that nasally feeling you get parsley a hot mustard does the same
thing to me there is nothing better in my opinion than spicy hot mustard and i'm not
talking like i'm talking um like chinese mustard like hot chinese mustard is my
favorite thing on earth i would put it on everything all right i already got this pretty
much ready to go so this is thousand chicken broth 20 salt 20 pepper everything else is already
in there oh fuck it's already here how much is in here chicken broth no it's fine i just need
salt and pepper in here 20 don't get it in the middle here oh god damn it is this gonna
it's gonna touch isn't it in the mixture right that's not hitting the beetroot it fucking
is whatever i just need four stars that's it right just 20 grams of pepper that seems like a
lot does this dish actually have that much pepper and that much salt in it i'd send it back i can't
even get it in the mixture what the fuck am i gonna do about it we're just trying to get
to where we were before boil done just let it cook the worst is disgusting i don't think
i've ever even seen it before let's just use this opportunity to start cleaning all right you
can hear that one was real yeah i know you hear the fake one right now but that one was real
that was not a uh that's stupid i think the sink is clean almost here we go any of the spills
not that i can see how do you do this without overcooking the onion you put the onion in it
later you must have to just throw the onion later over the floor what did i miss the spill
oh fuck it is you're right this tomato soup i'm leaving it out i'm serving this tomorrow
i could care less deep bowl and done dump it rotate left rotate right there's got to be
a better way to do this that i'm just stupid 300 that's all right by two milliliters i don't
give a shit all right is it time take the finished okay this is strike three coming up
this is the day again that we have not been able to get through because of various issues
i'm leaving these both out because if they're served tomorrow i'm going to just keep them in
the microwave try me you think it's a joke it's not we got a few minutes to clean up
and prepare those two are done they can stay out get this over this way i don't even you
now this is done i need at least three chicken broths that are ready this is full brand new
how's this one this is all right too set them up in the right places get the oil back where
it belongs up top here this is uh i can still use this blender set it right here salt and
pepper can stay over there i'll put these in the right spots the oven's still on it is
am i ready i think i'm ready let me get some plates for the next day too
why would you have a honk this much this is not i could clean this here comes the panic music
cars yeah if you beep do you know who beeps that much this is like we just graduated high
school and we're on the line of cars waiting to turn out of the high school
everybody does it i think i'm ready bring it on they had cars when you graduated high school
yeah i'm not 140 years old how old do you think i am what did we pick last time liquids
cheaper liquids and tips right better tips and the tolerance level okay let's not get soft
locked i'm saving it right here preparation phase so we got these two already got two
we already got tomato soup and our borscht watch well i don't even know what it is let's get it uh
i'm hurry all right i'm gonna get fish out what do you think should i flip roll the dice and
just prepare them both what do you think salmon or trout both let's get it ready it's dill five
dill five uh what is it five pepper or is it four pepper five sponge i think it's four of each
fuck it whatever give me an order it's salt pepper i chose wrong give me the salt
i can't wait to serve the critic uh one full day on the counter sitting out bunch bunch
whatever the fuck it is he's gonna love it and why is it so cold and why does it smell
like ammonia ah it's just extra fucking seasoning there dude all right what do i
i think a bug just flew in my mouth and i ate it yeah it happened i'm not gonna freak out
sunflower oil well you need potatoes too right yeah two potatoes give me that pot
fuck i need a pot all right do not order the tomato soup don't order the tomato soup
he better not order the soup i'm not buying another pot don't buy that he's he better not
come in and order the tomato soup filled with water two potatoes that's fucking lemon
it's already ruined hey look this goddamn same here i need the lemon later anyways
no i want to cut them just don't touch the fillet fuck who cares it doesn't matter we just
need to please the critic nobody else matters 20 grams of salt gonna have a heart attack boil
these fucking things up 10 milliliters get the fillet in there this ain't even the critic who
cares get that shit on that's all right not every piece of salmon is perfect guys we're
good to go that's all done yes all right i'm spectacular if it's not a critic then who cares
well on critic day it doesn't matter what if the critic is undercover you can always start
with critic you can always tell the critic guys they come in for the first thing they
do is they look at like the drapes they look left and right like they're crossing the street
when they come in they come in and they look left they look right flip nice got it okay
potatoes are almost done let's get the plate i've got the salmon down to a science
whoa whoa whoa what's why is it burning what was it too long it was not too long
it's i think it's done the water is burning yeah pretty funny all right that's it
serve it this ain't the critic who cares and it was still perfect i really love what you did
here my favorite part is when it was cold and smelly and unedible in the middle
that's how i used to make it what did i already put on that
did stick that's gonna stink all right what did i already put on it where is it
what's already on this there's already black pepper and dill black i need one more black
pepper and then time where's the time five right get it in the fucking oven this is already done
lemons we're ready i can just relax in the meantime let's clean this out clean it nice
this is ready for whatever he throws at me if it's a stupid tomato soup and i'll be very
upset about it you'll see me scream i'll ask what about if it's tomato soup i'm going
to scream as loud as i can into the mic and break my fucking microphone i promise
i will scream until my throat hurts into the mic as loud as i fucking can
this is a nice expensive microphone i will ruin it i will break it this is not going to happen
by the way i'm a liar okay is this ready almost just staring at the wall dried horse radish
when it comes out get a plate and i'm saving the game so i don't have to do this another
time how are we doing by the time i get back over here this will be ready three two one
didn't time it one two three fucking asshole god damn it
hey perfect timing put it down put the plate down it's the same shit out of my hands
one two three four five lemons delish parsley order up so much blood yeah but that if that
exploded in my hands like that by what's wrong with the taste bad cutting technique
i don't want to sound like a fucking idiot here or an asshole but if you're going to take a
full star off of the taste portion of your food because it wasn't nice looking enough how does
that affect what it tastes like if somebody was like well the taste was four out of five
because the lemons weren't cut well for me i would tell that guy you're you're dumb very dumb
and then i would ban him for life from the restaurant all right food critics about to
order not tomato soup it's tomato soup i screamed for so long you have no idea
oh god oh tomato soup i'll take a tomato soup one large tomato soup please fucking asshole you
can hear me what about i gotta get this right okay i need to pause it so no turn this fucking
music off i don't want to pause it because the music plays and i can't is there a way to stop
the clock all right i'm gonna try to talk and do this can you imagine if you went to a
restaurant as a critic and you heard that the guy was gonna make you a day old of borscht and
he was gonna serve it to you it was cold he was gonna serve it to you and you came in and
you knew he was going to do that so you ordered tomato soup and you hear him in the kitchen so
angry whipping a fucking pot against the wall screaming as loud as he can because he can't
serve that to you don't you think you'd give it a zero or you just leave you wouldn't even
stay for him to make this he would just give him a zero and leave i i need tomatoes what
do i need stock water chicken broth salt pepper unbelievable i can't serve this guy
old food 700 it's got to be right for the critic oh my fucking god i hate myself
okay done eight tomatoes salt pepper salt pepper salt but so so so so so so so so so so so so
what's going on in the chat right now why do i see like a trillion timeouts what's going on
eight tomatoes onion good okay get it on there and uh that's all good cayenne i forget
the cayenne every time shit what do you do what's going on why is it why is this i fucked it up
god damn it i have to dump the whole thing out aren't i get in the mixture please
one two three four five six seven eight all right go cook 60 seconds and then blend it
you're gonna save me i am i don't even know what's going on in here you guys get me all
twisted right now it's the letter s too many times oh well stop doing that what do you guys
out of your mind blend heat off 150 milliliters of sour cream sir look at this look at this chat
room dump the whole thing slowly so i can make sure i get it all 150 no one done into a bowl
okay can we finally get out of this hell of doing the same damn thing over and over again
300 i can do it come on easy how much is in there how much is in the bowl almost perfect
299 you fucker take it i finally passed and we're not soft-locked too much cayenne pepper
and i'm famous wait there's a new order i think that's fine there you go
delicious threw this shit against the wall you don't want to be the person after that uh
wrong amount of product it was a little too cold uh we're good any other food new order
fine that doesn't matter though right i've already done everything okay it was uh pepper
thyme dill horseradish uh was there a dill pepper thyme pepper no hey congratulations
graduated high school congratulations you graduated high school nice work it was a knife
baked microwave for like 20 seconds that person is getting sick
47 dollars
i'm just gonna do it for everything why cook anything all right fine you want
is there any more is there any more in here hold on there's still residue in here
hot water all right that's good save the game this is like making me fucking laugh
there's still residue from the other one we're gonna add some color though
no they don't what are they gonna know fucking ordering this
you're gonna give it two stars on one i didn't want water not enough chicken broth not enough
salt dude the technique though i mean was on par was that the best i've ever had
there we're done the result okay i mean we're gonna keep the tomato soup
let's clean up uh you order a soup and the person pours water into a bowl
serves it to you sir this doesn't look like the picture uh well you know times are tough
oh you thought that was a borscht no no it was a borscht tea oh oh okay i'm sorry for my
misunderstanding okay it's clean let's clean this up these last a long time salt and pepper
right next to each other i really don't like the panic music because seriously it's
fucking with my head i'm not doing it to the beat it just looks like that
i feel like people actually do that shit i don't know why that's making me laugh so much but i
feel like people do that at like restaurants what's wrong with people when they're like
the guy standing in the lettuce in burger king or something you we you we laugh and you think
that's a joke but people are fucked that's why like eating at restaurants sometimes is scary
because you don't know if the person's like kind of just like piss in the tomato soup
for no reason how do you know that somebody didn't just like dehydrated like bright orange
piss into the tomato soup you don't know there's no way for you to know that you just hope
all right let's go i'm just gonna save the vegetables everything's clean is the oven on
still turn it off let's repair stuff while i have a minute come on quick quick quick quick quick
pick up the phone all right we're good is it a little burn mark there okay excellent 223 bucks
if there's just no way to know i don't know you guys have ever like
gone to like yelp and this is what's the scariest thing because anybody could just
write anything they want sometimes like what if you went to like a yelp review and the person
gave him one star and they said that there were rats everywhere what if that's right what
if that's not even real just like astroturfing and like gas lighting and no there are no rats
in my restaurant there were rats everywhere and then the that like the owner like hires
30 people to write like 29 reviews that are all five stars and then they got like the guy
that like didn't like his soup so he says that there were rats and cockroaches and stuff
who do you fucking who yeah i was supposed to believe you can't believe anybody you have to
go into the restaurant and walk around the kitchen and meet all the chefs and then sit
there and watch them make the food for you to get the real whatever you could possibly do
they won't let you do that yeah but if you i know you yeah that's what i mean you just
you're putting like complete trust fast no i don't want fast unbreakable bottles no
heat proof gloves let's get some better tips uh equipment repairs are faster
overtime for dishes and extended longer prep yeah i want some more prep and then now we don't
get soft locked thank god it worked thank god oh i'm so happy we can actually continue
no no no no no
this fucking place is haunted man okay i've only got how much time i got four i got some time
what did that what did they even tell me to do i gotta prep prep prep tomato soup prep the
tomato soup that's prepped make borsch make make borsch where's my where's the other pot
there it is okay there's uh this shit's gotta go i'm gonna i'm gonna make it fresh you know you
know just like wendy's fresh never frozen all beef patties they come in and they're freshly
cooked they're still cooked in a microwave but i mean they come in fresh every day
don't call me a sellout you hear what i just said okay um what am i doing i need okay i
need um i keep picking up and putting down the same pot focus it's a thousand of chicken
broth didn't wendy's stop um cooking on the flat top they used to cook on the flat top every time
right they don't do that anymore do they i need another one of these back like in the
80s and 90s they used to cook on the flat top they don't cook on the flat top still do they
they don't cook anything do they still i gotta look this up does wendy's still grill
their burgers fairly confident normally plus their butt what he uses flash cooking method
that utilizes a timed clamshell grill you place the patties down in two rows saw them and close
the grill which heats the internal temperature proper safety levels for a certain time holy shit
they still do it that's mcdonald's not wendy's oh fuck wow i thought i thought they all did it
now i thought they all fucking didn't grill anymore they still grill well fuck yeah wendy's
keep it up get some of the best chicken sandwiches i've ever had junior bacon cheeseburg
meal i've ever had was that reverse fucking reverse sponsored reverse like i fucking flipped
it on you thought i was talking shit and then i correct i got like corrected on stream and
it's like whoa fuck i'm not sponsored by wendy's by the way at all let me make that
really clear not even a fucking centimeter i've never they don't even know my name i've just
eaten their hamburgers once sponsored by burger king no one will ever i will never have a
sponsorship because they watch this stream and then they go no i'm not different i'm not
sponsored this guy he's fucking freaking me out i got an email one time about somebody looking
for a sponsorship and they watched a stream and then they ghosted me for the rest they'd never
return my call they were like yeah well check out your stream man sounds fun i'm like yeah
check it out and the person uh literally i think they every time every time i call that
person now it goes right to voicemail every time that means i'm blocked right he's still
i still call every you know every few months all right focus i've wasted so much time how much
is in here i need much i need a mother chicken to lay some chicken broth into that fucking pot
parsley get in there carrot and then and then uh beats five right and then one onion we've
already talked about the fast food chains in this channel did i gain time what is happening
no it's just all right now everything's it i didn't salt the fucking water just get everything
up now when wendy's burger king and mcdonald's are really the only three for burgers that you
really put in one list together i know everyone's like well what about arby's and what about uh
this place and carl's no no no no it's wendy's burger king mcdonald's this is the best one
those are the three fighters that are competing it's not like oh in and out no no no no no no
fucking prep the damn salmon all right so it's sam fillet we got uh salt and black pepper
no the other ones like aren't shouldn't be on the list there's like a bunch of different categories
mcdonald's burger king and wendy's have like 10 like thousands and thousands of stores and it
really bothers me people start to talk about how they think they know about fast food and
they really get involved and they start to talk to me about fast food and how you're wrong
jeremy and everything you fucking say is wrong and it gets me really livid people start to
tell me that oh yeah that you put lettuce on your hamburger of course i do i put lettuce
on my hamburger it's the fucking best kind of put on your hamburger and a little bit of mayonnaise
and people get really fucking mad at me and it's the music turn it off uh new station new
station uh sorry i'm really sorry i don't know what the hell came over me there uh well there
we go i feel better that's good sunflower oil and put it in the pan i started making this
stupid fucking soup i swear to god i'm buying another pan make the soup in real life is it
actually this easy to do this it can't be right salt and a bunch of salt and then the two potatoes
it's fine i almost i almost just put the salmon into the pot boil them up let's go oil in the
pan same time 10 milliliters nine is enough no it's not get it right it's too much
what was i doing with these oh right for that okay uh salmon okay let me crack my knuckles here
can you hear that everybody oh uh let me oh let me continue to prep this what do i need to
put in there salt and pepper right 12 and 12 correct me if i'm wrong here 12 and 12 right
it's 12 salt 12 pepper right wrong there was a fucking grenade in here why
why i fucking can't they're done they're done they're done you know what they're just done
and that's what there is that's all there is to it no flip it that's no water in here flip
the salmon who cares this isn't cooking what is going on cook cook what do you jesus
little crispy i don't know what happened there you yeah you can do like a little drizzle
what's wrong with a little drizzle if i do salmon i do like a little drizzle of olive oil at the end
different colors it's fine is that a potato now these are yams almost done come on that's
just doesn't matter fresh meat crunchy not enough salt whatever being a critic who cares
so let's there we go tomato soup i got that ready to go right now perfect not too much
we go order up this is the best tomato soup i've ever had what's that flavor i'm getting
what is what's that what's that what's that smell what's next okay i was right in the middle
of making this so what was it it's 20 grams of salt 20 grams of pepper and then i'm ready to
go nice where's the pepper one two three four five six seven eight nine ten eleven twelve
thirty forty fifty sixty eighteen nineteen twenty all right get it all in there done
okay 120 seconds get a bowl i'm going to keep this as long as i can don't break it i don't
care if a week goes by i'm going to still serve it there's parsley in there the onion
every time the onion everything should be on time now no not quite take the onion out
all right that's whatever smash a plate and put it in the soup um no i'm not gonna smash
this fucking onion i swear to god you keep sticking your hands in nothing else right
that's it pour the liquid into a deep plate and serve it hot yum done a little more that's good
what's that plate sick can't wait to serve this for the next six straight days
in fact yeah i'm gonna be conservative on our servings now now i really wanted more soup i
get to serve more too much pepper too much salt whatever it's a lie anymore salmon just in case
something bad happens i'm lying to the customer oh this cutting board is really dirty where's my
pepper and salt there it is five and five surface sponge instead of salmon it looks the same
how they know okay let's clean this out i got two orders to do the same time oh shit
i can't fuck around here oil okay we need uh water boiling potatoes potato potato salt salt salt
potato potato salt flip it flip it flip it flip it flip it flip it now good potatoes salt the
water boil 20 grams of salt right i feel like this song has been playing for like three hours
okay on go boil how we doing on the salmon not bad not bad not bad what's uh what's next
that's that's all done all that's done i need the other one pork chops salt black pepper time
black pepper wrong i want the other one no give me the other one give me a different one
i got how do i get out four four four four six is this not done potatoes done
not quite okay i need uh i need salt and then six time you have a plate i don't have a plate
okay i need uh salt one two three four and then time six and that then goes into the pan
uh 30 milliliters of oil 90 seconds aside whoops no that's the right one okay i thought i
clicked on the fucking pork chop all right so that's uh sunflower oil pork chops potato
and then we bake the potatoes i gotta do the two potatoes and then six chunks
this still just need hold on i gotta rinse this i think 30 milliliters of oil get some potato
water in there i don't know if i want to do that i'm gonna save the potato water though
okay so salt black pepper time sunflower oil 30 pork chops 90 seconds aside
30 fucking god damn it man i tried too hard get it in there in 90 seconds aside one two six
seven six nine 31 34 three 44
four 65 66 seven 68 69 70 what 71 72 i gotta flip it now all right we're good nice i'm getting
pretty good in the kitchen let's clean up i need to uh the clean clean up the area over here
what is happening come here are you stuck there's like old beet juice over here i forgot about
this stuff the pork chop get it off not yet put the potatoes almost done plate perfect they
fucking fall on the ground all the time oh my god it's like a little cluster grenade just
went off why just get the pork chop on here dude i can't it's like looking for a contact
lens i can't control where they go they just go the customer can see you no they can't it's
a closed kitchen that was the last for today clean up all right save the game i've made it
we're good to go so what do i got i got the let me put the stuff that's already done over
here we still have like three servings of both of these let's put the timer over here
put the tools in the right spot here feet potatoes let's clean up a little though
i'm gonna have to repair some stuff get in there we're gonna we need a new radio station
yeah i'll change it okay looks that's dirty but i can get rid of that i need to clean this
clean this too rinse it okay that's clean how is there water on this same deal we got
put the all the ingredients over here how do i there's still a lot in here i'm gonna clean that
up i wish i have three minutes nothing else okay that's clean i need the sponge again
no i'm not gonna use it that's like somebody that knows like my address and they just do
this every day we gotta get out of here i'm just trying to cook all right any more spills
on the ground no oil no spills over here is a little bit okay thanks uh eight cents 30 seconds
six cents six let me that's cheap nice and fixed everything's good to go a few more
seconds i got water in here it's not necessary not a big deal cook the phone clean pan oops i
don't care i need to clean the stove with my sponge let me just get rid of the germs real
quick on this need a good clean workstation otherwise what the hell are you doing how fast
are you gonna do this in a circle not really that fast are you high no more tips what about
down here products lose their temperature slower yeah give me all of these that means
i can have the tomato soup sit out there for like five days this is important grilled
tuna steak grilled beef chuck with baked potatoes or duck broth i'm going for the duck
broth it's it's more soup i could have three of these ready to go yeah i'm just turning into
a soup shop all right get some good prep we're serving pork chops with baked potatoes as our
dish of the day so i gotta prepare all right let's get a couple pork chops out here at
least one two pork chops the dish of the day that means it's gonna happen at least once
or twice i don't stack them why are you stacking these all right so if i remember it is
times six right salt and pepper four and then salt and pepper four one two three four
looks like bird shit is that really what food looks like before it's cooked i've never seen what
it looks like before i've only eaten it okay then uh it's the cut potatoes baked potatoes
right so i'm gonna need give me a give me a bowl give me this i need four potatoes
i'm gonna cut these up try to get them in a nice spot okay i mean the knife these need to be cut
into threes how the hell am i gonna do that no i gotta take these off i gotta take like two of
them off okay that's better there we go all right get those on here i'm gonna do i'm doing
cook them all the same damn time why don't restaurants just do this just cook like 30
potatoes at the same exact time no i don't want that on here get this shit off that is what
they do not wendy's money's fresh never frozen every time all right we're good to go we got
two here i need to load up the salt wait a minute it's how much salt is it it's five right so we
need like 10 four five six seven eight nine ten that's ready pork chops are ready we need oil
in the pan all right let's go 30 milliliters right give me one easiest thing i've done all
day one tomato soup coming up is this fresh every day because you know i've been to wendy's before
and it's fresh never frozen yeah we're just like wendy's i can't put it in the microwave
hey four out of five on yelp is pretty damn good guys what's next perfect give it go i'll
get this in real quick oil in the pan 30 milliliters let's go let's kick it up a notch
done bake i'm gonna wait no no don't get it they're gonna be fresh on the first flip 90
seconds it's been like it's been like 10 seconds on the flip turn on the fryer later it was six
grams of soft potatoes well they you don't want that much salt 10 is enough dude i've got this
secret technique i'm gonna make like three or four tomato soups and like three or four of
these and just have all of it done and i oh no no the order came in shit it's tomato soup
it's already it's already great in fact let's just start doing it now now i got like three
more i got some legs left in this one new radio yeah yeah yeah yeah spatula go for a nice flip
turn on the other let's get perfect timing here three two one bang nailed it i fucking nailed
it find somebody on earth that's better than me at this game and that time's up you can't
i'm fucking best in the in the world this game don't you hate when people do that
the like times up i hate that so much did i break it don't don't don't explode catch it it's done
one two three four five six i hope that was funny it's never mind it's perfect
i think green ass food hey it's fine i'm gonna leave it in there so it stays warm no just
keep it here new water another one got it same deal we need uh oil 30 milliliters almost
perfect get it in there 90 seconds everything else is done can i get a soup order that coming
up let's get a soup order come on give me with the uh double time here come on i'll take one
borsch please sir it's ready i'm gonna drive by honk unless you cook the sponge yeah all right
i will serve the next person that orders food a sponge on a plate with olive oil on it
i wasn't timing this that's fine look at how much time i got let's just start preparing it's
just delicious food fry the sponge i don't think you can i don't think i can or yeah a
broken plate soup just okay put take a plate break a plate put the broken plate in the plate
and serve it how do i get like get out of this okay this is almost ready serve a blowtorch
serve just a thing of chicken broth not even put it in a plate i'm talking just put this
on top of a serving tray and put it in the window it's like did you order this or did you
go to the grocery store boiled sponge soup with a straw
this takes too long i like just going to the restaurant and ordering and then talking about
like politics while you drink wine and then finally comes to you and then when the waiter
comes over with the food you have a two second panic attack where you're like oh yeah let me
move some stuff out of the way for you uh is that enough room you got to move everything
move just fucking take everything and just take your hand and just slide it across so do you
have enough room to put this here oh yeah that's me that's fine and the waiter says
oh why watch out why that plate is hot that plate hot plate oh okay i won't touch it you
don't listen at all you wait till he's out of the like earshot and out of view and you
immediately just start grabbing it and eating it and you have this weird internal panic where
you think that he's gonna come look at you he's gonna see that you didn't listen to him
he's gonna be like fucking idiot i told him not to do that he's like sneaking the food
before you're supposed to be eating it no complaints at all heating mistake you gave me
almost five stars across the board and you got i made a mistake let's get some soup in here
thank you i didn't have to spend any money that's the best part i'm not spending money
i'm just gaining income fish i wasn't prepared for this the flavor was perfect you licked the plate
and sensed that there was fish on there temperature oh let me tell you i just wish
that there was a fish on there the plate was nice and warm and i licked i tasted the fish
flavoring from the fish being on there but i just wish there was a fish on there god damn
i don't want to make another i want to make that duck soup okay i can't lose fame
can i put this back in the fridge yes i can oh shit no no no i'm not ready for this
i wasn't prepared give me soup order okay wait wait slow down slow down okay
hold on it is uh salt and pepper no i'm not going to give any more sponges not right now
guys just give me i don't i can't lose all my fame points i just served a guy an empty
fucking plate and told him it was trout and potatoes all right oil get it in there 10
turn the heat off for a second get the oil in the pan 10 oil 10 oil liters okay this is ready
to start going flip it halfway through and then we got to boil the potatoes too right
yep just get it in there don't turn it on yet potatoes water i need more i need a couple
more potatoes need salt in here i should have prepped this i'm only gonna make soups
i need uh 20 grams of salt okay i need potatoes i need one two three four okay
don't freak out trust me i'm gonna put look while this is cooking i gotta prep the potatoes
for the uh pork chops what do you think i'm stupid go all right now i need cut this up
soft it up quickly quickly where's the salt oh fuck flip it which way am i going with this
this way perfect got it they're boiling up all right salt six one two three four five six
okay pork chop get it ready and this is um four four six time how we doing getting close why is
this not cooking anymore hurry up plate potatoes done what are you doing give me the potato cooked
it's not raw it's fine continue this next part okay so i got that get that oil in the you know
i just need a little bit more oil 20 get that in here what are you doing fish no oh no no it's
the fish sauce they won't tell it was only in there for a second get this bottle okay we're
good oh the potatoes done oh shit they're done it's okay i just need a plate
did you order an extra crispy you had to have an extra crispy
no don't fuck around not yet i need a plate one two three four five six this takes too long
flip it and give it to them clean the piss clean the piss
damn boiling piss that's yeah that's a lot of piss i've been peeing in there for five or
six straight days what i'm gonna make a stock out of pee that's enough cooking this is one
day worth of piss no how many what is that how many thousand milliliters is what
how many cups of pee is that very dehydrated where's that plate where's my plate with the
potatoes on it tasty fame points we've leveled up complaints there's too much salt on that
hooray closing up for the day let's clean the pans um i have an idea i have an idea
we'll see how it works tomorrow keep my piss when somebody orders a tomato soup or a bourse
i'm gonna put it back on the burner for like 10 seconds right day old soup it's way more than
a day old that's about four days old these are ready i'm going to clean the stove that's how you
get maggots how much time do i got three minutes we're good uh i got plenty of time so
seven cents and that's easy five cents it's nothing don't need a new sink or anything wait
maybe do i need to sink i don't think i needed no i don't need to put the phone down can i get
it from here the phone goes out the window the phone go out the window
no it's right there oh it is a ghost phone there he is next mode empty folder internet
radio well let's play it turn it on is he doing it okay i don't hear anything
all right uh i need the mop where's the mop there's so much broken glass
pick it up
all right let's go to the fucking people beeping they're driving me crazy
this is a weapon okay i need more glass we're good give me my trophy let's go
remember 257 dollars tomorrow we're getting inspected it's a great way to water
the water is still on oh no it's been on for a full day
am i going to come into like a flooded kitchen oh god that's not that much it's okay both
faucets were on today's special is this got plenty of it the special is this i need to fucking
relax the special is the soup i have enough i definitely have enough to do three servings
i'm gonna get it on the burner because i'm gonna heat it up when somebody orders it
do i need to do any prep maybe some fish i'm gonna just get what should i prep the special
is the soup but it's i can't take one of these out who knows what it's gonna be
but yeah i'm gonna do a bunch of potatoes let's get potatoes let's get like just let's boil two
potatoes let's boil let's boil four potatoes salt that water up with 20 20 ounces of salt
21 just for a little bit of extra kick let's do this with four i feel like it's gonna be a
salmon day i really do all right boil those let's get uh let's get four more potatoes onto
the tray let's cut them up for the pork chops that inevitably will be coming out here
let's get them right there let's cut them up good enough good enough salt the fuck out of
them like a hilarious amount that is unedible like 200 grams one two three four five six
that looks good it's six on each get them on the tray get them into the oven and i'll turn
the oven on prepped how are these doing nice and prepped let's start the day three two one
action what do you got soup here we go done nice and hot let's be scarce on this one let's
do like that's enough nice and piping hot i'm a little too cold still this is fruit punch
no it's not fruit pun oh all right sure thing is it done how much do i have left in here i'm
getting really i'm getting scarce here i can really only do this one more time just start
diluting the soup i don't think it works like that food critic is here i'm ready throw something
at me fuck shit hold on save it is it what am i going to do about this i don't want to
make a whole nother soup i should have given the last person fucking way less he's gonna
i gotta i don't have time for this that's perfect soup i'm not throwing that away
i sound like the people on kitchen nightmares that's perfect soup it's not it's not it's not
perfect what's wrong with it dump it until you get that through your fucking thick skull wait
any water in here one two three four five carrot i was can i make a triple batch how
much chicken broth thousand thousand i don't have a thousand where the hell is this going
that's enough what a perfect number 20 20 and 20 done boil not very not much longer i want to
soak up some of those fucking tomatoes why is the onion cooking why is it carrot not cooking
why is the carrot fucking not cooking oh now i gotta play whack-a-mole oh my god god damn it
no just put now the parsley is not cooking is it that's fucking carrot all right we're good
wash your hands in the soup take the parsley up whack-a-mole what's coming up next that's
gonna start burning onion all right get the onion out of there pull up under the beets okay
okay okay okay okay off bowl can't believe how to make a fresh fucking soup for this guy
why why why am i doing this why the hell would i waste this i've already got half of it
um it's already done what do you mean didn't save yeah it didn't right here it's fine we're
good this should work see you guys were so concerned about that not enough pepper
yeah it's because it was diluted in its own juices new order tomato soup i got that right
here i'm gonna put my other trophy it's my trophy storage unit tomato soup give me a bowl i already
have a bowl it's already done that's four and a half stars or 4.3 4. like 4.33 i still have
these potatoes in here let me move this out of the way um you guys think i'm thinking crazy
but i have an idea i'm gonna save all right hear me out i'm gonna make like two or three
pots of each of these soups and i'm gonna pour them in like 10 bowls and store them
like over here just in the corner and then i'll have the the pot the pots will be completely and
totally ready to be used i'll have like 10 five of each soup ready to go yeah that's what i'm
doing it at when uh i close that's a pretty good idea i think all right what am i what the
hell am i doing uh the trout right trout i already have i got a trout that i was going
to use before there it is we need uh pepper thyme dill five of each what's the dill and
i'll do that with potatoes too how am i gonna make all this food and only make it once and just
serve it just cut up like a hundred potatoes and boil like a ton of potatoes so they're always
ready black what did i just do dill pepper and thyme get this baked oh fuck this person who
cares it's done done what's wrong uh it was only 10 seconds sorry this is broken tomato
soup coming up oh shit um bright okay it's all right i still have hey one oh no all right coming
back got those fame points back i'm fine i gotta make oh no wait wait wait wait i still have
another order oh no i don't okay duck broth i've never done this before duck soup what
this is green not even that bad that's like three and a half stars that's fine i'm good
okay this is the important one duck broth water 1300 salt pepper duck breast put it all in a pot
got that you're fucking kidding yourself if you don't think i'm gonna make like
30 of these before the day's over i'm gonna make like two or three pots at the same time
all right i did duck water salt black pepper so i need take the duck breast from the
you're not gonna get that i'm sorry take the duck breast from the broth cut it into slices
so i need water salt black pepper duck breast everything just throw it all in a pot 1300 of
water all right get it on there and then i need salt pepper and then duck breast let's get the
duck salt pepper salt salt pepper salt one two three four five six seven eight nine ten
ten of each where's my salt one two three four five six seven eight nine ten put it down
no put it down duck breast 560 carrots and an onion where's the duck breast
need two duck breasts all right and then a carrot and an onion boil for 80 seconds
okay take the duck breast from the broth and cut it into slices
35 grams each i don't know what the fuck that looks like in one two three five slices
pour the liquid into a deep plate this carrot's not cooking fast enough all right give me deep
plate the person wants salmon right say i can do the same right now salmon just where's the
oil don't matter i got the potatoes already i can just cut it up i can get that done it's not
gonna be perfect but who cares i can at least get to serve it and not lose points
give me the two potatoes they're right here all right this is done fucking onion all right then
get the breasts out cut them into into five slices kill heat five slices right holy shit no
no do that again do exactly what i just did again what did you want who cares i don't care
just put the potatoes on this that's good enough that's fine it was terrible but that's fine
i'm not gonna lose points so then you got how many did i just did i make too much fuck you
take the duck breast from the broth cutting the slices pour the liquid into a deep plate add
duck breast pour the liquid into a plate and add the breast on top how much how much was it 300
how much is supposed to go in here how much is supposed to go in here
am i putting too much in 173 grams i said yeah why did i do two duck breasts it asks for
two right just don't waste it save it that looks fucking gross well it's all right you
don't have to eat it all right i'm gonna pork chops baked potatoes wash your hands no i refuse
yeah hey i'll wash my hands i wash my hands when i'm dead you know what i mean
okay we need oil how much what do i need on that salt black pepper time what no here pepper
all right oil oil are these burning almost no oil i i broke the oil the oil shattered
into the ground bingo okay i'm gonna start making okay now i'm gonna start making my
signature move here you ready turn this off okay signature move this is burning yet
no it's good no i'm fine so far all right let me keep let me keep this going in my brain
so i need um more i need i need this pot back there's all this cooked already i need
to throw this shit in the trash borscht flourished i'm gonna serve this one there's
one second left so i have all the time in the world to make like three different soups
and the thing is this these can exponentially increase i'll eventually have food cooked for
like a week two weeks i don't even have to do anything can you select that please thank you
how's it look almost done get a plate good all right hold that off i have four minutes
to keep to keep this going what i wanted to do all right here we go so when i thought
thousand i'm just gonna eyeball it like grandma used to do thousand milliliters of water
grandma didn't use a recipe she fucking just threw a bunch of stuff in a pot and just
hoped it was going to taste good and that's how you got spaghetti how do you think the
lasagna was invented it's 20 right 20 and 20 now it's chicken broth it's chicken it's
chicken broth it's a thousand chicken broth isn't it right is it chicken broth is it water
it's a thousand chicken broth how much time do i got three minutes i need a little bit
more chicken broth and then i can use this for it's gonna be perfect how much is in there 938 a
little bit more what okay yeah there's no okay that's fine all right now i got the chicken
broth in there 20 and 20 salt and pepper okay now we get the uh ingredients it's uh five one
two three four five it is a piece of parsley it's a carrot and it's an onion don't step
on that food onion shake it up a little bit fucking fantastic i'm glad that's wonderful i love it i'm
very happy about what just happened everything's everything's great nothing's wrong nothing's
wrong at all it's going under the beats it's in it's out there we're good boil go okay how
much time do i have 120 a minute 20 let's get the other let's get tomato going these baked
these are these are already cooked i'm gonna remember that they're up here don't let me
forget that these are too cooked in case of the salmon now it's 750 for a tomato and then we need
how much salt is it 12 and 12 30 seconds 12 and 12 right 16 seconds we're fine okay i got it i
got it i got it i got it don't forget this is up here because it's cooked and it's ready to eat
okay how are we doing perfect all right look at that again look at i got two two minutes
soup is done everything's cooked beautiful all right i got two minutes here i know i need to
um let me tell you it's tomatoes right one two three four five let me tell you something larry
oh i think that you you're not very nice to my wife you understand god damn it onion and that's
it right and then cook and then you add and then you mash it up 60 seconds right is this
right is it eight tomatoes eight eight fucking tomatoes all right get it on the burner go
turn this off 60 seconds and then we start mashing all right oh wait wait wait okay
bulls bulls bulls i need bulls no no idiot where's it you fucking dumbass i'm so pissed
off right now i'm so angry oh i'm so i'm uncontrollably fucking i'm so oh my god no
oh
i need to pause it because i'm laughing i gotta fucking stop
oh this is the perfect plan too i just am like adhd psycho man slow down it's okay all right
okay f4 oh shit oh no it's still on it's still off but it's gonna be on fire oh no
oh why would they just like shove you out it's not like a fucking dance club where at like 2 a.m
they like turn the lights on it's like everybody get the fuck out of here out out out it's it's
i can spend an extra two minutes there check dishes score before serving it to a guest
no learn the temperature we need some taste uh the one that tastes tolerance right here
duration of the cleaning phase is extended yep new recipe you bet your ass would do
in a soup gazpacho and that's a cold soup so french fries though steak and french fries
but this is elaborate and it's gonna ruin my soup stuff it's done okay now i need to add
um sour cream sour cream 150 good enough heat it up a little more heat it up needs
to cook a little more good okay i need plates i gotta get this situated how much time do i have
i have a lot of time okay just slow down i'm fine let me get this correct tomato soup is
over here it's the first one i'm not going to screw this up that should be able to get me
like four maybe i think i'm putting you feeding the rats i'm putting out these plates to like
whatever i'm gonna like feed a bunch of fucking cats oh you see by my restaurant i feed like
200 neighborhood fucking stray cats come on kiddies all right i got five over here i should
be able to spread this spread this thin enough just gonna be gentle yes you like
the tomato soup don't you sweetheart too much less than 200 in each one that's a little more
okay good okay are you fucking kidding me i can do even more i think i can do one more yeah i can
do one more maybe even two more those of you that are wondering what the hell i'm doing just
it's plays we call we call these big plays oops why because no matter what happens i am
guaranteed because this game is strange and even if this is here for three months
i will always get at least four stars so i will never have to make tomato soup probably ever
again perfect let's get started on that the guy gazpacho well this is i'm gonna hold on
i can spread this out a little all right i have four this is a carrot on the ground
okay now i got time to i got a couple minutes here what kind of summoning ritual is this
is stop don't make me laugh i'm trying to summon chef boy id all right what's in here oh wait
this is um that's broth for the hold on that's broth the duck the game cannot handle this many
things on the ground this is duck broth don't let me forget that i can do this like probably
three or four times we are preparing for the rest of the game you all think i'm crazy
everybody's like what the fuck is wrong with this dude i'm gaming the game i have found the
meta of cooking simulator it's only pick soups make them all and have like 50 of them lying
around and just get to the end of the game in less than four hours should we really get
one more out of this i can do another one give me another bowl and then i'm gonna start
making gazpacho this is making me uncomfortable well i'm sorry to hear that all right tomato
duck broth borscht let's clean up a little bit so this isn't disgusting
we're open okay we're open open open i'm ready i just i just gonna make
and i'm crazy tomatoes the next one right
i'm going too fast the game can't keep up with me it's okay it's still like it's still
good enough oh wait i don't have that ready how do i make that cucumber add to the food
processor cucumber tomato red bell pepper garlic and bread what add to the food give me the food
processor cucumber tomato cucumber tomato how many cucumber how much how many i don't know i
wasn't counting how many tomatoes 360 what i need one more and then red bell pepper gar why
does it have to be in grams red bell pepper garlic and bread red 480 red bell pepper
why can't it just be two garlic and then bread that bread looks horrible i wouldn't want to eat
that with garlic are you sure this is how you do this okay bread blend add to the mixture olive
oil wine vinegar salt and pepper 10 grams of olive oil i need olive oil how much this one you
put in there 30 milliliter 30 i can't even tell where i am it's close enough 30 milliliter
and then 30 milliliter white wine no wine vinegar what do i get oh over here wine vinegar
oops it's okay okay and then salt and pepper how much was it is a 10 okay and then pepper
where's my pepper 10 of this i thought for i don't know why i just thought this had food
poisoning container i was like okay i didn't say it all right then pour the liquid into
a deep and then i'd garnish with eight grams of chives so you got it a new soup
i think i can get like four or five out of this let's try to get five so 300 right into a deep
plate and then garnish with chives it's a weird bowl it's weird it's weird to pour this am i
ashamed of myself why would i be ashamed of myself now that is a little more all right
then garnish with eight grams of what was it chives all right gazpacho you got another
gazpacho for me i'll do it again hey look at that gazpacho huh here take your like
green bean soup take your fruit punch and green beans got anything else for me i should probably
make another one of these work faster on that order our guest is in a hurry he came to the
right place hey how does eight seconds sound did okay i guess that way to be annoying new
order of it's the fish okay do i have do i have one of those already i just need a lemon
no i got duck in fact i think i'm gonna cut this duck in half and then store it over here
okay why not i need the fish one trout fucking broken i gotta get that fixed remind me to do
that i could actually use the damn oven all right it's five five five of time pepper and dill
time pepper and dill over here uh-huh yeah why would you order fish here if you knew that
they were storing soup on the ground where the fuck do you think they would be putting
their fish that's a no order what does it do not order you store the potatoes over here
get that in the oven all right good here it goes then we need the lemon cut into squares
let me see if i can get away with this i'm just curious i'm just curious guys that's pretty
beautiful let me do it this way it's gonna be like lemon sprinkles diced lemon with the
skin on the game doesn't like me sorry i tried lemon wedge lemon wedge um i need all the lemon
here don't i yeah i do all right let me get the horseradish on here the horseradish new order
coming in and then i need actually that was a lot that looks better than the other one
on the left at least looks like pineapple slices all right i got i think i got one of those
ready what was the matter i didn't like your cutting technique lemons i'm gonna sneeze okay
i'm good so we got um this is already cooked right are you supposed to remind me this is
cooked and i have the potatoes already done too where are those potatoes right there done
this food is so old it would be like stale bread at this point you wouldn't be able to eat this
i told you i figured it out i figured it all out you spot you hey how are you
save you for later there we are nice fresh you're gonna complain no i don't worry it's
in the sun it's in the sun it'll be fine okay uh duck breast 42 seconds to make duck people love
this food what am i gonna say that you're wrong for loving this food well what do you want to
do tell you i know i was wrong it's not good what's that oh i got that right here i'm making
so much money all right i gotta make i have to cook i have to cook food though unfortunately
i know right dumb where did that go all right can you not no no more orders
if it's expatio then i'm gonna i'm gonna improvise where's that pork chop it's fucking
because that's expatio not good not good not good um that's not one of my pre-made soups
all right what was it i have to all right all right get this all right hold on i'm i'm
gonna make the i gotta make the soup first let's just get this settled that's fine okay
soup first that is we need cucumber tomato cube of uh where's the where's it i'm just gonna
i'm gonna guess i don't care it's two cucumbers three tomatoes it's a loaf of bread some bell
peppers and then garlic it doesn't matter how many bell peppers have we got yep yep yep yep
get it off 30 of each 10 salt 10 pepper i just tried to hold down shift to sprint
over here where's the fucking pepper what do they do with the pepper it's right here right
yep okay why does this look wrong this looks light the color is off why it's fine all right
i'm just gonna you know what i'm gonna do i'm just gonna leave this here i don't want
to play it all over the ground oh god damn it what the fuck have i done fucking ding i turned
to pick it up this thing's so sloppy it's like the slug where's the pork chop i don't
care it can be that's fine salmon all right there we go it's cooking why don't i have
two pans give me he really did forget about the doom ost after i'm addicted to soups okay
once i'm not addicted to soups anymore let me clean this up okay anymore uh dirt is some over
here okay that's fine why is this not cooking cook what the fuck are you doing all right uh
i need potatoes potatoes i don't have any potatoes cut these up put them in the oven
wow wow oh wozrs settle down what is this doing finally it's sizzling i can hear it
all right i need oh shit oh shit oh shit oh shit shit shit shit shit i don't have time
plate just cut up raw potatoes what an insult what a fucking insult this is just an insult
it's salty i didn't lose points a net zero that's fine i what it's it cooks when i take it out
listen to this what how does it cook when it's not in the pan that makes no sense
there's nothing cooking what's the sizzle oh my fucking god it's the sizzle guys the sizzle the
sizzle do you hear the sizzle i'm losing my mind here the sizzle's the pan on the left
fucking damn it i'm so flustered right now just no no no no just put the plate
what are you adding potatoes to right potatoes potatoes fuck off i can do that
we're going downhill we're going downhill boys i did beat the system i just went nuts
for five seconds and ruined it we're no longer taking orders finish what we start
okay that's seven minutes that's plenty of time why can't i make my own menu just make
a gazpacho right now i'm already here salt i'm turning sounds off in the game because of this
it's fucking my head look at how much better this looks why does it look so much better
okay these are done just at that when the order comes in add the garnish
i have a ton of gazpacho how much time do i have four minutes that's enough time to do
uh how much tomato soup do i have plenty of tomato soup plenty of broth i need to make
another one of those one of these one of these things one of those one of those things
one of these i forget what uh hold on it's what i'm scratching my face um what is it one of these
that's okay i know i know i know i know all right it's um it's beets five beets and then
it's um no it's not a loaf of bread parsley carrot onion go salt salt and pepper get it both
over there it's uh 20 right i got two minutes and 40 seconds to get some bowls out
we're spreading this really really really thin i'm talking like 140 per bowl one now it's gonna
be like 150 per bowl now let me uh clean up a little bit i gotta repair some stuff
i got lots of money i don't know what now turn the microwave off the microwave's not even
broken what was i doing where's the phone oh my god hurry up come on thor pull it 21 seconds
i need something quick 10 seconds when this is done do this one first okay that's good
is there a parade out so i was already playing a tuba one minute okay get the phone out of here
this soup is done done how much time time behind what's up behind got it okay one of these is two
full this one i'm gonna put a little bit in here just a little these both look exactly the
same i'm gonna fuck that up it's okay how much time okay behind okay clean up no i'm good
i ordered my soup like an hour ago yeah i'm sorry about that let's see how do i do my
complete and total soup let's see is there's like a bonus to soup percentage is like a 30
more soup from soups no the xp boost maybe or probably the taste did i do that all the way
i thought it was the diapers no the tolerance is all the way up duration of clean i need
more prep and i need like more after time and before time there we go you lose less fame
place that's good none of these are soups which one of these is the easiest salmon with
asparagus okay i know how to do salmon already grilled beef chuck with baked potato or tuna
i'm gonna collect that one because that's the one i would probably eat the most salmon is easy
but like i saw tuna all right i got six minutes here we go more soup okay got one two how much
more do i got simple borscht that's soup of the day you got it i need what do i need what
do i need come on think use your brain stock the whole thing goes in here okay done
then we need uh salt and pepper 20 and 20 what's wrong what's going on what's empty
i thought the game was broken okay here we go parsley uh carrot five beats and an onion good
to go kick that shit on overdrive let's go and over here i'm gonna prepare a couple things
here we go let's get these both these pans clean and i need to these both these potatoes
both cooked good how much is left in here that's plenty um what do i need to prepare i need to
prepare some some meats i got plenty of spatula plenty of tomato i didn't get some meat prepared
let's get the tuna out here i don't know how to make tuna though not yet i potatoes
there's another i need a pot no there's those are lemons i keep doing that okay now i'm
gonna split this up i need a give me like a bowl i mean like a big plate i need my knife
with my knife i'm running low on duck soup that's for sure this is almost done do i get bowls not
yet that was close all right you're done you're done you're done blend it no you don't blend this
i never had before oops a little too much all right good oh frame rate frame rate hurts good
all right how much time two minutes of the restaurant opens i need i got my potatoes right
here i've got already cooked buns i gotta fill this with uh water get these boiled up i need
some salt you got it good to go okay these are already done um is this cooked it will be clean
up a little before it's time to open the stains have been here for like a year it's permanent at
this point okay uh clean that anything else on the counter it needs i'm just cleaning counters
no anything else no counters bills is that over there almost time 45 seconds that's enough time
for me to get these potatoes out they still need a little bit more time get these in the
oven get these ready to go they need to be chopped up into thirds try to get them as
close as i can i'm gonna have to eyeball it with my knife i just bought a new one somebody puked
hold on okay now i should be able to take um my knife where's my knife restaurant's now open
of course it's the duck and then what was the other one uh the ukraine we're good very stingy
with the servings but it's all right we'll get a good serving here here comes pork chops
this is fresh so i know it's good all right pork chops i got the potatoes are right there
here these ones these are done these are done uh okay here i got i need a trash can all cooked
potatoes are going on the left side of the sink that's the only um i'm not gonna be able
to remember it any other way dude i don't think i can take these out i can't physically
get those out so no i'm just gonna leave them in them no um i'm not using this yet
they can just go in here see these are these are completely cooked potatoes boiled remember
any cooked potatoes i'm gonna stop storming here all right these gonna be chopped i got
okay with my knife dude i want to just dump this out the window i can't just open the window
where's the knife i just bought it there it is here we go i can't cut them on here oh fuck
off don't throw the plate how do i stop the plate from being thrown how do i stop i can't i
have to let go somewhere safe but i know it's gonna be safe it's like holding a grenade i'm
like i gotta get okay that's why i perfect pieces all right into threes i gotta try to
do this quickly three bang bang this one got that one one two three all right good get them
on the tray soften what was that what was that how what happened over here why did these break
what happened why did that happen i am fucking confused i'm okay i have no idea i've come up
all right i get uh oil 30 i've i don't know why that happened the wind from the open window
is the only thing i think of pork chop uh let's get the seasoning right on this so i don't blow
it completely yeah salt pepper and thyme pepper is behind me go cook it up that is so annoying
now don't do that this is gonna take a million years i have no other orders right no that's
two orders fucking ruined i'm pissed because of what like a gust of wind blew in here
and knocked a plate over gather the pieces onto a plate does that work no it doesn't
work well i need that plate anyways it's okay can i delete the sticky notes why can i even
click those i've been in the game for like seven hours why can i click sticky notes still okay
potatoes are there potatoes shit spatula anybody see it i don't see it i need plate six potatoes
one two three six at least it's cooking smash all the soup as a joke and blow the last
hour of time no i don't think i'm gonna do that save and do it not yet i'm in the
zone right now that's raw enjoy i guess you like it a little underdone hour long joke
no i'm not gonna do that i need to make more duck broth it's about portion size really
i need more portion size i gotta make double spatula eight they don't like the fact that
it's old moldy and potentially a week old they just want more of it see plus 12 nice
you gotta have at least like 180 milliliters this is all my duck i don't have any more
hey hey like seriously uh fish i don't know where it is
what okay this is fucking broken oh my god this thing is fucked this thing is beyond repair
it's haunted i'm not using it no put it i don't care what do you want salmon steak and boil i
can do that salt and pepper all three all three burners are just on by the way get in there
nice okay cook it up the potato was in there my trout okay two boiled potatoes what else uh trout
i need a lemon i need a how how close is this almost done i need a lemon cut it into quarters
plate salmon i need a spatula i need a spatula i need a spatula oh no um horse rider order up
enjoy leave me a good review pretty good nice perfect okay uh what do i go to this one
i'm not screwing this one up again i know that they want portion size they want bigger
portions two of these in a row well after all you didn't mess that up what uh that's a key lime
pie what's it what is that a cake okay that's good uh one of these is a gazpacho right good
get it on there tomato not okay put it back it's already done just pick that one up after
tomato is back here good they want portion size remember that's important that's too much
spread it out what a perfect 300 milliliters almost that faint level three what's up what's
the next one five dollar tip for a fucking soup what's the c that's an i don't understand c
i lost uh lost a green bean hold on give me the green beans i'm killing it right now
i'm i'm killing it i'm doing like this is the best i think i've done in the game in like a
week two tunas what is i've never done it before and a fuck oh no hold on this is
important uh slow down i'm gonna cheat take tuna salt and pepper 80 seconds aside lemon slice
uh so it's one can you grill it for 80 seconds aside so let me get two out
tuna okay salt and pepper right salt and pepper get it on the grill any sides just a lemon
into into the little platies okay grill 80 seconds aside what time uh i need uh let
anything else no lemon i need to cut a lemon 80 gram into 20 gram i need to cut a lemon
into fours any style yeah yeah yeah you're gonna give me a style to do come on all right that's
done and then transfer them onto the plate and garnish with uh eight grams of oregano
i swear to fucking god guys this is spring loaded that was spring loaded out of my hand
okay 80 more seconds i need to find the other wedges that's a potato one lemon there's one
more hanging out writer why where the fuck is this other lemon that i just some of
they're getting free lemon it's only fair wait hold on almost done kill the heat uh
oregano twig eight god damn it it's scaring me that's apparently the best i could have possibly
done i just leveled up stop plate i got one more thing to do right oh that pork chop is
gonna be so old i'm gonna have to brush it time to wake up for school pork chop uh
yeah okay we gotta go uh i don't have time to season yes i do i got i got time i got time
i need uh salt and pepper and then uh time time time time time six come on come on that's it
start cleaning are these cooked these are cooked right what are these yeah they're cooked they go
in the cooked pile uh get the pot back up here this is what what is this timer this is
sour cream still here that's all right salt pepper still some that's still all right i
can use it still i need a spatula before i do the stupid thing again that i just did
slip it trash all right i'm gonna start to make make trash i still have i need duck breast
yeah i gotta make more duck soup speaking of trash i can't believe it give me a spatula
give me a nice spatula is there a better one don't move don't move don't
this has been on the whole time i just flipped it and i wanted to put a little sear on it
oh that's unbelievable all right i need to clean the stove clean the stove is this done all right
i got my i just my like stomach fucking hurts six potatoes listen you heard when i said the
thing when i said tuba everyone looked at me like i was crazy you didn't hear it
all right yeah the radio is supposed to be on yeah the radio is on this isn't working
all right seven minutes okay i gotta make more duck broth and gazpacho duck broth gazpacho and
how am i doing on tomato i'm gonna get three pots going at the same time here and make them
all at the same time forget about cleaning this stuff i didn't need to be clean big pot get
all three pots up here so i can look and i can get a good picture of it in my brain
okay well how to make the duck these are all been cleaned down thank god i thought about
that beforehand let's get a trio going at the same time so i need to make gazpacho
one more of these and duck broth and no i didn't make tomato soup i gotta make tomato um okay
gazpacho first this is the only one i have memorized for no reason this is arguably the
most complicated one come on get it in there come on i have this i don't have any of the
other ones memorized this is like two steps and a ton of ingredients why can i not get
those other ones to memory ten got it lined it up okay i'm gonna fill those two bowls and get
three more is it possible to double the recipe i'm not sure at all it would fit in there
i don't think it would all fit two two over over 200 it's fine two like 20 to 250 way too
fucking much but it's okay anymore yeah a little bit good all right now i can spread
these out this one can go over here just a hint just a hint okay up top a hint and then
over here just a hint okay yeah okay that's just gazpacho done now i got four minutes to do
uh another uh dog food soup whatever it is and that is i need a bunch of chicken broth and i
make tomato soup too but tomato soup tomato soup tomato soup tomato but i need to um
a bunch of chicken broth they need a bunch of chicken broth way more than this oh get it one
two uh get three of them just i'm gonna need it probably later all right this is a thousand
then 750 come on hurry up what's that a little bit more good stuff the rest goes in here
trash 750 what's the duck one anyone remember the duck come on i i'm gonna need my germa
bites to come out and come through here 715 was it a thousand a thousand water or a thousand
it's it's a thousand water okay what what else was in it i don't remember at all
you put the duck what do you have what is okay hold on let's get this
and then i need parsley carrot onion go oh my god what happened we're good uh okay now this
is um tomato soup is eight tomatoes and an onion go 60 seconds mash it up and then the
duck is what is in the duck broth i think it's a carrot or an onion it's a carrot it's 1300
water why is it not going up oh your mother fucker how we doing how we looking all right it's been
60 seconds it's time to mash almost now what the fuck goes in here um what goes in here
what goes one carrot one onion one carrot one onion and then the duck breasts also go in here
let's make a few of them time there behind okay uh good go this is almost done oh fuck oh
my god oh my god oh my god oh my god oh my god oh my god oh my god oh my god
um okay um sorry put this down no i think everything i think it's gonna be fine i want
more tips no i don't pull that back what am i i'm stupid i want more time pork tenderloin with
caramelized vegetables let's do this let's do the french fries please don't be on fire
please don't be on fire please everything just be cooked i turned off the burners
i turned the burners off so we're good people really like our grilled tuna steak so it's a
soup of the day oh please who gives a shit i'm done it's done this is done this is done as well
right done i'm good to go how much time do i have plenty of time let's get to some bowls
oh none of these have been seasoned um sorry people get enough sodium in their damn life
all right i'm overfilling here two more three more possibly this should take us for
another couple days yeah i can i can spread this out too i fucking spilled it like a dumb
ass do like 140 all right that's good don't breathe thank you for not breathing just saving
right there all right this doesn't have anything in it this has this has the spill in it all
right let's dump i'm gonna put tomato in here tomato's done tomato goes over here i'm gonna
bring i need to okay get rid of these i'm gonna clean this up yeah you guys can breathe
yes yes yes yes yes yes yes yes yes yes i meant for like that one like two seconds
yeah tell it to my lawyer yeah i represent myself by the way i come with a clown suit on
i make the jury laugh and then they're on my side sorry that's kind of how it works all right so
i should be able to do three or four more tomatoes here don't crash i bet you i can get
one more plate here holy shit save the game wow that would have been a disaster i've been
playing for seven hours when did that happen when did that happen okay well whatever sometimes
you play a game let's fill these up tomato soup is precious it's like gold i don't want to waste
it here it's annoying to make i just realized my posture was so bad i just holy shit i'm like
sitting crooked at least this is gonna be hot i could probably do another one yeah i can do
another plate i mean actually let's make this one a little let's top them off anyone look
low all right those are good in fact hold on okay that's better spread this one down here
better okay these are all perfect i would classify this as perfect now duck we have
to cut the duck up how much time i still have i'm still all right same thing that i did the
last time in fact i'm gonna cut it up really thin this will last a fucking month yeah this
will last a long time did it not cut through the other one no it did okay give me uh give
me a plate can i fit it all on here i can easy slow slow slow slow slow slow down it's not that
that that don't fall off maca s that's cooked all right um now i get the broth i'm gonna keep
the duck broth over no i'll step on it um same place over here too many bowls the game's gonna
crash it's all right how much time oh all right all right okay that's everything's fine
here comes another one here comes an order coming in soon exactly what i was looking
for and i can take my time with this i just made it oh no i've never made steak and french
fries before all i've done is floor soup and tuna cakes um all right hold on i need to duck
rough 220 200 is fine too much it's okay i can transfer it all right i'll just transfer out
holy shit you idiot it's okay i don't need the onions in there whatever uh-oh no okay we're
good just gonna have to deal with the way it is put this plate in the trash no right here yeah
spinning up preparing all right no no no no no no duck broth so i need to grab the plate
my duck is over here nice and sizzling and smoky and it's 140 grams three six nine twelve
one more that's good right that's not raw i mean it's gross but it's not raw all right
the next thing was the this which i never made before what is it steak season with salt and
pepper i need to steak steak and then salt and pepper four four and fry for 35 seconds aside
that's it okay salt and pepper you know this is this is a joke i gotta somebody clean this
i got lots of time i've got tons of money lots of time i'm good to go
clean this up i mean this is just filthy it's just this this looks this is a bad look on my
stream i'm serving all you guys all this delicious food i don't want you to come in here and look at
the stove and be like what is this this is disgusting jeremy you're gonna call me by my
first name we're on a first name basis at this point okay so steak salt and pepper i didn't
really prepare that i got six minutes though that's a million years um where this it's up
here salt uh let's get it over there and pepper four right four in each good my game is
really starting to lag and then fry this for 45 seconds aside fry it like on here or which one
or in the flat top or on the in a pan 45 seconds is not a lot of time so what's next potato cut
into sticks put potato into frying basket oh man that's a whole nother potato season the
other side too i think there are already potatoes in the fryer i gotta transfer those out
i gotta transfer this what do you what okay this spatula sucks can i just say the spatula
is terrible all right that's going all right we're almost done with that let me get a plate
french fries french fries french fries french fries it is cut two potatoes into sticks
and then put them in the frying basket sticks pick up the steak i i got it i got it steak is
fucked what the steak is perfect except like the oil stain all right cut it into sticks
this and then it's gonna be flat so that's fucking good enough all right fry basket
um i gotta move these out give me a plate okay fry basket where the hell is a fry basket
i have to buy one fryer basket okay so put the fries in here the fuck was that somebody
just walked up behind me and i didn't see them come in the room and they grabbed me by the
shoulders and went thing in there how do what do i need for oil i need oil what kind of oil
put potato in five and deep fry what oil do i need how long does this take oh shit i have
like 10 not even 10 seconds i need to season them with salt and pepper salt just salt salt
and then rosemary twig salt get it ready how much time 30 seconds
oh
my stomach hurts i mean you imagine you go through all that
just serve the person a fucking potato a whole fried potato what's next
no i don't think that was the critic was it
no it wasn't don't say that i don't think it was all right i got that ready
it's like this person went to the dentist before they came to work and got like their
wisdom teeth pulled and then decided to come to work bro how much do i need this right
it's all right i got it all back just wait till i have to serve somebody a steak and then
i could this game is gonna kill me new order work fast you got it done i know how to make
a mean bowl of soup that's true new order uh okay i don't have that ready but i can do it
right now this is not the critic right so fuck it okay now i need a lemon food critic is here
i hope it's not a steak please tell me it's a fucking bowl of soup is it a bowl of soup
be a bowl of soup people it's okay it's i can make that fresh i can make it nice and fresh
i have most of it done already still that's for any sense i'm gonna lose my mind
okay oh my god just take it i i'm sorry what do you want me to do critic oh the credit
critic critic okay pork chop with baked potatoes pork chop i can do that clean pan oil season it
nicely in the pan cauliflower oil pork chops season nicely salt some fresh cayenne pepper
where's the pepper this kitchen is a fucking mess that was gordon ramsey watch his regular
show his real show he used to do that that was that was a good gordon ramsey i don't give a
shit did that just buy another pepper and then uh time time six i gotta make this perfect for
him into the fucking pan go nice and perfect we got i already have the potatoes done
where are they over here it's six potatoes what's going on cook is it not oh my god
he's gonna be angry with me all right and then i need to i got the potatoes done just gotta get
this has to just cook that's it is there another order of this tuna hurry hurry i like i gotta i
gotta get the tuna going how much tuna how much tuna does this person want all right it's just
salt and pepper right salt pepper and then onto the grill was it five i'm gonna say four and
if it's wrong it don't matter they'll still eat it onto the grill go ready to flip almost
ready to flip this is very quick come on hurry up come on come on come on come on come on i hate
this so much i i swear to god i swear to god like why why does it have to be able to do that
the tuna okay plate plate plate i need the potatoes okay which i need i need the best ones
i need some good ones they're all bad whatever i say i say good time go go go go go go go go
good here you go eat up guaranteed four stars got it come on four four four that's so bad that's
130 fucking god damn it not enough salt on the potatoes not enough salt on the fucking potatoes
you serious dude i was like two tenths of a point off i'm so upset right now all right
lemon and i need to i can't believe i just lost everything that was bullshit all right i just
tried i swear to god i just tried to cut that and the game's like broken i'm getting such frame
frame rate issues right now it's fine everything's gonna be fine i'm gonna knock it out of the
park tomorrow and reagan o twig i can't fucking believe it we have to make our way all the
way back up there all right well i know i know what i have ready to serve right now
that's my bread and butter and it does really well and everybody loves it
don't have some critic asshole coming in or you didn't put some salt in all those potatoes
and one more tuna i get two of these so two tuna steaks get them on the grill salt and pepper
is it five or four it's five don't get the pepper come on i gotta get some fame points back
this is gonna be perfect all right get these on the grill nice all right and that's 45
seconds 80 seconds aside right okay and then we need the lemons so many two lemons and
cut them into into cubes hey hey hey hey hey nothing else right no other orders
seven hours of potato abuse i'm like losing my voice do you hear this have i been screaming
what have i been doing i've been like smoking crack like what's going on
okay plate and then we need uh reagan on two plates so let's get this on here little lemon
wedges both plates ready right here
i love this game the first the first like hour or two we ran into all those
fucked up bugs it was really annoying but it's it's kind of fun all right i need the other uh
all right put the steaks on kill that heat in a second they need to be perfect i need my
points back kill the heat kill the heat kill the heat kill the heat kill the heat
no i don't know what that white stuff is i didn't put it on it's probably like
fucking maggots it's just squished bugs okay now it is uh oregano first one going up give me nice
points for this one five stars i'll get five in the next one i needed this bad i'm only
getting five points for this credit can walk in and drop my score by like 70 like i was an
asshole and just an absolute dick it was 130 points what a joke look at how long this i was
level three i was a three star restaurant all right no more orders i gotta clean this
shit up like actually clean let's repair clean i've got plenty of soup i got plenty of food
i'm ready for the next day i'm doing this i'm getting this shit together i get the phone
back in here all right how we doing give me the mop not yet get the stuff off the ground
get a cleaner area i'm not making any i'm not prepping any food i'm getting a clean area
for this stream i mean for this like i'm streaming tomorrow in the game the hell am i
talking about okay is it clean i gotta pick up i need a plate these can still be used
these potatoes can still be used they really can i can serve this to somebody i can't and
i will that's just ready to go it's done i didn't do anything i just placed the plate
down on the on the counter and it's made out of ectoplasm that looks good place thank you
now i got even more cleaning to do with this bullshit all right i'm gonna move these
to a better spot right next to the radiator you know put them on the windowsill right
no i don't think i get no i'm not risking that okay these this way tempers i can get
the mop in here you i i didn't even move it i need that stuff i need that it's like so sloppy
pain in the ass oh my god it's like a it's like a rubber band this thing's made out of
fucking jello this is the floatiest mop i've ever used in my life i really am on drugs
using this thing can i stack the plates stack them no i gotta move all these i can't believe
i have to remake the caspachio i'm so annoyed by that i had two good caspachios that are now
wasted how old is the floor soup some of them are at least six days probably five to six days
for some of them that's a little bit better these can just kind of hang out here until
i figure out what i want to do with them that's fine to sit there i gotta mop that up
i have tomorrow in the morning too all right what about let's get this way mop up over here
all right can i i'm gonna can i make a suggestion to the to the development team
well i only have one suggestion patch out the guy driving by and holding the horn down
it doesn't need to be in here it happens like every 20 to 30 seconds that's my only complaint
is the guy driving by one minute broken ass plates everywhere my kitchen's in disarray
everything's just a mess i used to be a fucking three star chef and then larry came in
and this place i don't like that food he didn't salt the potatoes and he've ruined my reputation
how do i clean the oil there we go what is that is it a burnt potato shut up it's gonna
drive me crazy this is really look at how dirty this is i think i need a new counter
is this a super caked on dirt oh whatever yeah that's fine all right let's choose a perk
unbreakable plates yep you've seen it happen a million times now i want to do direction of
cleaning is really important i can now no longer break plates which is that's very very good
you should get unspillable plates duck broth i got plenty of it you're not breaking any
i can't so don't you worry about that okay speaking of i still can't believe i that this
happened i'm just gonna throw it away it's perfectly good fish try to blit break a plate
we're good all right i gotta pick this up all right i have plenty of duck already made
not too concerned about this i just want to clean up the area plastic bowl bucket why in
the name of god did i not do this before i'm picking up individual pieces can i throw the
whole thing in the trash um never mind thank you again i'm getting i'm getting tired i'm telling
you all right i'm i'm too addicted to this game i have to pull the plug here in a little bit
not yet not yet once i go through my whole soup inventory then yes i'm still i'm not done just
know that it's coming soon all right what was it soup of the day what was it soup of the
day was what clean this up duck right all right i got plenty of the duck i'm residual
i'm laughing residually over something that happened like an hour and 25 minutes ago
psycho wasting food else is dead all right i am ready to begin i've got some prep i've got
plenty of stuff i got my spatula i've got my workstation cleaned everything is all set
i still have a couple i still have a few minutes maybe it's worth it to me to get
some prep here maybe some tuna steaks some salmon a steak i don't actually yeah i don't
need more than one duck i'm gonna i'm gonna pre-make french fries now i already have no i'll
be fine i'm probably gonna need some more duck broth which is very easy to make and i can do
that in like less than a minute i don't need you know let's just make it just so in case
customers want to have like an extra little uh a little bit here they can get some extra
chicken duck whatever the hell it is okay so water 1.3 liters of water i got something in my
eye okay then i need a carrot a onion and that's it right carrot and onion and then salt
is it 10 carrot onion salt and then put the ducks in there and that should be good pepper
too oh there is pepper in there you're right let's get a broth going i'm ready clean the
sink i thought somebody was just lying and just like baiting me to look in the sink
but that is bad that's very it's really bad so that's how that works when it works it's great
isn't it get this in there i can't get in there and clean pretty satisfying i'm not gonna lie
clean this thing i'm cleaning i'm clean i'm doing it why is everybody spamming clean the
sink fuck it you want to make like a like a prison wine soup all right i'll make some
prison wine and i need uh can i even buy it i don't think i've unlocked it do i have like grapes
no i have beets some more wine uh vinegar in there okay all right that's good that's not
nice and beat it up so now we sit this over here in the sun for like six weeks what's first
all right steak with french fries oh look at that i made this like three weeks ago
this would hurt somebody that has been sitting there out for at least it has to be like five days
still good what's next oh you guys made you guys told me to make toilet wine and i forgot
oh whatever it's still good no it's not added to the toilet wine what am i doing
i spot you you know what that's turning into that's every six year old's experiment
what are you doing over there science oh okay what are you making over there
flour soup oh i'm pretending to eat this delicious okay good i think i need one more
piece yeah my the customers are just people pretending to eat the food because i'm six years
old what's wrong here not enough pepper not enough salt wrong amount of product wrong
amount of am i giving too much or too little got that right here yeah if you think about
how fucked up of a situation this is this is just i'm we're playing pretend right now
this is what goes through the head this is what when you're six this is what you see i'm in a
restaurant right now but i'm not i'm not i'm six and i'm serving flour soup to people
and they're pretending to like it this is what it's like i'm in kind of a crisis right
now all right a grilled steak uh all right uh salmon and the potatoes let's do sam i have
that ready salmon and broiled potatoes it's just salt and pepper that's easy save the sponge
no you would if this was real i gotta pull this full circle okay sorry welcome you you want you
want grilled tuna steak come in right up
would that be all for you today i we have to mash up the tomatoes make them really yummy
mm-hmm yeah yeah okay who ready to eat i am
what else do you want okay i do that too yes i'll take a cheeseburger with extra peppers
and onions and i'll also take it with a side of french fries okay
hmm
okay here come in come in right up
oh is it a bird a bird just flew by it's a robin oh okay your food here you it's ready to eat
ding order up
whoa you made this yes you this is delicious i know it's the best food i think i've ever had
in my life all right i'm gonna get back to playing the game i'll think back puke
what's the okay i need to make i have the potatoes i think it's time to turn the stream off
i'm realizing what i'm turning into and i actually am turning into like the experiment
pretend to have a restaurant five-year-old thing and it's it's been freaking me out
for like 25 straight minutes all right let me let me finish this day pork chops
i don't hear any more honking cars in the game yeah i don't either this is freaking me out i'm
gonna get to the end of the day why no soups we have not there's been nothing one soup this
whole time salt pepper it's salt pepper and um whatever time lag lag oh by the way i also
forgot about one very important thing all right it's time to make more food no uh
it's not we're not making more food yes no no uh jacob jacob you it's time for bed
no it's not you want another salmon no no no no jacob jacob jacob jacob it's ready jacob
you have to go to bed now no jacob jacob it's time to go to bed no jacob jacob get to bed
right now i'm right that's it you're grounded no i make more food jacob
it actually goes out the window somebody scream at me i just caused a car accident my chest
you get oh now everyone's going to jail everyone's going to jail all right thanks
everybody for watching that's going to the end of the stream people are talking
nothing no i think what's done oh my chest oh this game's actually killing me all right
anybody want some free soup yes i'll take one did they get out who wants one all right i'm
treating these like pies like i'm a clown i gotta save don't worry oh all right uh it's
all right it's been eight hours it's time to go i can't break them okay get the mop yeah once
i start like pretending to be a child it's time to this really is a kid it's like you're gonna
have a party you have like 30 relatives coming over you're gonna make a bunch of food i can't
i gotta get out of here guys i've gone fucking absolutely out of my mind it's over
serve the bread out the window oh my god all right that's it oh i gotta kill that audio
oh my god that was too that was too much so i think i'm gonna play this again i i'm not done
with my floor soup empire but we're gonna take a break from it because we actually might be able
to play it again very soon because of e3 because as of uh the microsoft conference is the next
time you'll see me live which is sunday sunday at uh 4 p.m eastern so 1 p.m pacific
so i'll be live at one o'clock maybe like 12 30 just like to but the reason why i might be able
to play this is because isn't there a there's like a two or three hour break between
microsoft and bethesda right so during that break i'll just play this and then we'll do
the bethesda conference that makes sense right i don't know how long it is in between
uh why didn't i why did i not light the kitchen on fire i did earlier
oh my goodness it's a four hour break that's that's perfect so the next time you'll see me
you'll see me uh for the microsoft conference i'm gonna go grab some food after pretending
to make it poorly for eight hours but this is uh this is great i want to get the i want to
get at least another solid stream or two out of this because i feel like some of the
later recipes might be fun to make thank you everybody for watching uh i'm gonna just
take a quick break and go pee i'll come back we'll do the bits in the subs uh i'll see you on the
at the microsoft conference i'll be restreaming it if you feel like stopping by please do
i'll see you very soon and for those of you that are sticking around see you in about two
three minutes all right guys let's uh let's dial it back a little bit here go over here
hey look at that let's go back a long time ago eight hours ago to be exact we had four
dollars and 15 cents from spicy skeletor thank you spicy skeletor no message just
four dollars and 15 cents five dollars from shkal thank you shkal they say doritos chip
doritos sometimes i'm a fan of doritos other times i'm not depends on what kind
i'm a nacho cheese guy not a cool ranch guy i will tell you but thank you the five dollars
doritos hack it fast thanks for five dollars buy an egg and microwave it until it explodes
that's a mess too messy too messy but thank you thank you hack it fast with five dollars
thank you trust no one for the 250 decided to come back with a video
of you in some peculiar state
peculiar state the germ of the vr madman and why am i in a peculiar state though
we're gonna have to investigate this one hold on let's get the uh
let's get it on the screen so we can decide for ourselves okay yeah what do i become in
virtual reality
what oh that is so good what good night freeze to make you drop the heaviest tear
that was a real dick move oh come on i'm just a normie boomer that's me that was really
really funny thank you here's the link for those of you if you want to watch it on your own time
there it is that's trust no one uh resident funny video maker makes all kinds of funny
shit all the time thank you so much for that and thanks to 250 thank you burly man bob for
the 15 dollars thank you 15 bucks dropped on the floor five star meal something isn't adding
up right yeah but they don't know that if you drop food on the floor and it tastes the same
the customer isn't going to know if they do find out and they do know
the whole place shuts off forever so that's why and the customer doesn't have a window
that's why i like open kitchen concepts in restaurants because you can see if the
guy blows his nose into your food you know if you hear like a big cough and you look up
who the fuck is that is that chef no okay just making sure if that wasn't the chef
they're great concepts thank you burly man bob for the 15 dollars talks ray thanks for 11 dollars
as mlc stealth once said these rats have burnt they are crisp
anyways love you streams as always germa hart thank you mlc stealth was always a always
contributing really funny things and interesting lines during the old videos and you see i
think he's doing pretty well too got like family and stuff he's like he's a good kid
he's a good kid but thank you to the 11 dollars appreciate it uh oh muffin thank you for the
seven dollars they say germa please let me go i just want to see my wife again please
what and then they say pride 100 pride 100 pride 100 pride 100 pride 100
this one's for my fellow lgbt thank you oh muffin appreciate it thank you for the seven
dollars thank you afro ninja for the five dollars no message just five dollars thank you so much
parodian weapon 250 no message just two dollars and fifty cents thank you so much
much love to you espada escar is it the fucking chef doing that no it's just this
normie boomer streamer that's good i can sit back down uh thank you espada for the two
dollars and fifty cents have you ever had hers cheddar horseradish chips i've not are they good
i'll buy them the next time at the grocery store are they available because that sounds
pretty good i love horseradish i like it on sushi because that's what you're putting on
your sushi essentially most of the wasabi that you put on sushi is actually just
green horseradish i just ruined i blew you mind right there didn't i
yeah not really no it is real wasabi is yeah it's pretty rare they have it in some places
if you eat sushi at 7-eleven no what that's a thing but i didn't serve sushi at 7-eleven
that's against the law at this point you can't legally have sushi at 7-eleven they still do
no no they don't has anyone ever bought sushi from 7-eleven and if you have why
there had to have been a reason you were dared by it you got it you lost a bet
everyone that buys sushi from 7-eleven lost a bet previously that's how they make all their money
is on lost bets i have i was hungry i was still hungry after puking oh that's too bad i'm i'm
of the opinion though i might sound a little elitist here but unless i see the person making
the sushi unless i order the sushi and they do it right now right there i'm not gonna eat it who
knows somebody could have like stuck another tag on it add like the grocery store there's a
grocery store sushi all right maybe but if it's just sitting in a box hey here's some salmon
sushi how long has it been there for has it been on the fucking ground in a bowl for more
than four days i know somebody that's done that personally very much so i know them very well
who knows how long they could have been in there yes they have standards
but i want to see the person i want to order it and have it done and given to me in like less than
an hour raw food i don't mess around with raw food i eat sushi i like i really like sushi
but i don't mess around with raw food steak tartar i will don't i won't even touch it i
won't even be in the same room if you have steak tartar in a room and you invite me over
it's i'm gonna be like a vampire i'm not gonna be able to go in the room it's gonna
be like a satan going into a church like i like skin will start to burn but yeah sushi's great
i wonder what my favorite sushi roll is anybody know can somebody guess have i ever said it on
stream i don't think i have it's not california roll no you got it somebody got it i have two
or three favorite rolls philadelphia roll is in my top three spicy tuna is probably number one
and number three is uh debatable it's out there somewhere but spicy tuna is my favorite
especially if they do spicy tuna with like avocado on it it's so good but yeah with flakes
tempura flakes now you just make me want to get a spicy tuna roll uh there's a sushi
called philadelphia roll yes philadelphia roll is raw salmon and cream cheese rolled up with
um but usually what cucumber in it too now people that are going whoa that's gross um
you know bagel locks you never had like cream cheese locks and bagels before
it's kind of the same idea you never had a bagel with locks and cream cheese on it
that's fantastic too if you have never had it smoked salmon cream cheese yeah that's
it's the same idea it's just the it's a sushi roll and the salmon is raw
in other words the fish in spicy tuna isn't regulated quality and cut tuna doesn't have to
fall into an fda quality control because it's a minced meat mixed in sauce uh what yeah but when
i go to like nice sushi places that you can kind of you can like see them making it they don't
do they don't like scoop it up like an ice cream scoop usually i usually eat it it's a
sham i've actually been to a place before that had sushi and they the spicy tuna was
scooped up with an ice cream scoop and i immediately was like i'm gonna eat that but
i'm not gonna come back i still ate it and it was fine now you think now that you say that i
yeah they do a lot of ice cream scoop spicy tuna interesting i'm not even like ever again
except from the places that i know do it right i do like like uh simply this tuna sashimi
the nice dark almost purple fatty tuna it's really good with wasabi on it and that stuff's
real because i mean it is that doesn't come out of an ice cream scoop you see the guy like
two sword with two fucking big blades in his hands
and he picks up the thing and he starts sliding carving
carve and he puts on eat it that shit's real they don't make that up that's not a
stuffed animal what if it is but let's move on i think we've got them from cheddar horse radish
horse radish chips i will definitely try them hey podcast listener thanks for four bucks
happy birthday it's not my birthday my birthday is not for a long time remind me in like
another an undetermined and determined amount of time but happy birthday to you if it's
your birthday wouldn't mean if it's maybe it's your birthday today happy birthday to
anybody whose birthday it is thank you podcast listener for four dollars thank you
for two dollars and fifty cents honestly i don't know who's worse at this point the honkers or
the vroomers just be happy there are no actual honkers i would have to like stream in a cement
basement if that were the case thank you waffle monster for the 10 bucks thank you
waffle monster uh use me like you thank you for the 10 dollars i appreciate the 10 bucks
that's uh and then they said something about the sponges and they called me dad
thanks for the 10 dollars uh thank you shalash ashka for the two dollars and 50 cents you're pretty
good just what i'd expect from the man with the same house as italics it's been a long time
since i had a good stream but you're just getting warmed up ouch what my 250 bits what's
going on here jerma lied about taco bell thank you for the seven dollars and 50 cents
750 may say hey jerma i had the weirdest dream and you were in it you keep having
dreams about me it's the same this you didn't you have like two dreams about me already
this is this is like i think this is dream at least number two is three
you were a pirate captain and i was a member of your crew we were looking for the infinity
stones and we had followed a map to this one specific island i immediately found all six under
a rock brought them to you and asked you to put me in the rumble you got super mad and
then i woke up thanks for the infinity stones can i be in the rumble the hardest decisions
takes the strongest of all decisions and then i fucking push you also seriously wendy's
mcdonald's and burger king aren't you forgetting one taco themed restaurant taco
bet has good hamburgers is it not up that no if you're talking about hamburgers burgers
actual burgers we're talking about mcdonald's wendy's and burger king all these other places
don't exist in the burger vast 10 000 restaurants by the way if you're wondering why i'm like
stopping and stuttering i just like reached behind myself and like scratched my back
and it's like there's like a scab back here why is there a scab back here i didn't i didn't
get like what that's weird examine that in the mirror later was it like a fucking leech on me
earlier that's weird it's confusing anyways a taco bell is not a burger restaurant it is a taco
restaurant therefore it is compared with other taco restaurants which there are not very many
fast food taco places there are some but i digress and they say put me in the rumble
against the other germa lied memes there are too many there are too many germa lied user
names to fit on the screen and no this is just you trying to get in the rumble from no you're
just trying to get in the rumble let's see c4g thanks for the 250 hey germa i set up a bot to
count your plus twos and minus twos on this stream interesting i'm probably going to fall
asleep before the stream ends so you should be able to check your final score with chat
if you do hold on really what's the total does it work i think it broke i must have been too
funny that must have been so funny that i was too many classes and it broke uh they say if not
then i've fucked up my code terribly anyway good cooking good looking have fun with you soups
well so i'm sorry that it may have gotten a little messed up somewhere along the road
it said 264 so i'm uh i'm um that we're talking about like an starting at zero right
so minusing two so that's that's pretty good must have been fun i mean yeah it's zero
keep an eye on that one that's an interesting bot that's really interesting i like that keep
that but that was c4g thank you uh lethargic ferret thanks for the four dollars this stream
hit close to home i keep so much of my stuff on the floor and people think i'm disgusting
because of it thanks for letting me know i'm not alone i keep so much of my stuff on the
floor i don't keep really anything on the floor as much as i keep it on the desk
i always have a really cluttered desk and a really clean floor but thank you lethargic
ferret for the four dollars zyte's thank you for the five bucks i can now understand why
your family brought extra food to thanksgiving and how you served them campbell's soup
omega lull campbell's soup is good plus it lasts like 500 years you'll be laughing now
but you won't be laughing at the guy that has a hundred cans of campbell's tomato soup in his
closet he's ready for the zombie apocalypse and you're not hey mad thanks for the mad 47 for the
five dollars and here's some of the money i got from graduating it's not much but it's
as much as i have now i'll be happy to donate more as soon as i can get more have a great
night congratulations on graduating college i mean um high school i don't know it's not
specified i got from graduating whatever what it was was high school if it was college
congratulations high school all right high school house congratulations time to turn the page start
the next chapter of your life take care of yourself wish you the best thank you for five
dollars as well uh our kin thanks for three dollars no idea hey hey no idea if you remember
me at all but i'm the guy who went on exchange from fitland to australia you want to
know why i went oh okay a bit of an underwhelming answer but it's run by my school and i figured
it'd be a worthwhile experience considering i've never been overseas before anyway i also want
to let you know that you're one of the funniest people i know and an inspiration to
myself and many others keep it up man appreciate you that's still cool you don't have to have
some elaborate reason why you go and do things right that's just a good experience to do
that's awesome you don't need to have some long story right it's it's cool either way but i'm
i am floored that somebody sees me as an inspiration i hope it's a good inspiration
and not a bad one but thank you so much for the three bucks and cool fucking trip you must
not know very many people ban that guy for five seconds no no no double that you're
gonna double ban 10 seconds that's a double ban i've never double life sentence anybody
before but thank you for real thank you potato chief for the five bucks jerma this is this
chief of potatoes and i have to admit i'm super disappointed by how you handled by sole namesake
so i sent a rogue potato to destroy your soup either one that crashed onto the plates when
i wasn't looking i'll smell you i could smell you i'll see you next time hey bingo sunshine
thanks for the 10 bucks patented no spatula tuna flip gonna see if this works out first
though god mode first try double thank you for the ten dollars bingo sunshine hey uncle joe thanks
for two dollars and 50 cents been having pretty bad anxiety from finals lately your streams always
help me relax and laugh my ass off when i need it been a fan since 2013 and i know
i can always count on you for a laugh thank you so much for the 250 and yeah finals that
everyone's pretty much done uh over the next week or two right there's usually but between
may like 15th and like june 20th june 30th good luck to all of you hopefully you guys did
all right on them don't stress out too much just do what you can and you know try your
best once it's over you're gonna feel great let's get the credits on the screen as always
thank you for the subs the resubs the new subs the community subs i appreciate every single
one of them it's good shit thank you guys yeah good luck to everybody that still has them if
you still have a final study a little bit take a break grab some snacks study a little bit
more get some good sleep because your brain has to comprehend that information school in june
yeah there's there are still a lot of people that are not done for like another week or at
least this week right how'd the colonoscopy go oh for those of you that didn't hear about it
it went well i the doctor doesn't have any major concerns they took a few biopsies which
is why i spent an extra day or so away from the stream and just kind of wanted to reassure
myself a few things so the biopsies will come back in a couple weeks and again he doesn't
have any major concerns but it's always nice to know the results of those but yeah it went
well where was i the youngest person in the clinic um not not not that i don't really remember i
wasn't really paying that much attention to other people i was kind of just remember i hadn't really
eaten solid food in almost two days so i didn't really care who was in the clinic i was just
wanted to get it over with it was more about just focus and get in there and let me get out
of here and be done but no it went well uh a couple more bits are came in here a little
bit earlier we had uh ragarnoi for the two dollars and i fucked that up you cook your
cooking is like watching someone give birth directly to a woodchipper all right that was
worth reading that was good thank you for the bits there uh short stack thanks for five
dollars been too busy to watch the streams lately but cooking sim was such a fun game to come back
to thanks for the laughs king i i mean i gotta address the fact that you just called me the
king i mean king hey i mean hopefully i'm good to the people here i appreciate it though thank
you for the five dollars uh unicorn butt crumbs thanks for two dollars and fifty cents hey
jeremy been watching you for about seven years now since the early days of youtube you never
fail to put a smile on my face buddy i've been struggling a lot with uh ssri withdrawals
and your streams are a nice escape from my crazily imbalanced brain love all your content
creating and passion for what you do got a question for you okay which fictional character
has had the biggest impact on your life fictional character that has had the biggest
impact in my life um honestly probably probably ren and stimpy if i'm completely and totally
honest because that like shaped everything about like the way that i wanted to think was funny
and the way that i was and imitation and ran and stimpy both those two would just characters
that you only get to pick one ren is ren is definitely not stimpy it's ren always ran
stimpy is cool but ren was the clear clear anchor of the whole show uh ren was the little
chihuahua i mean i guess a better i mean you say fictional character but billy west is not
a fictional character that's the person that did all the voices for ren stimpy doug he did
almost every voice on futurama billy west is probably like the reason why i'm the kind of
person that i am billy west jim carrey um a couple other probably cartoon actors probably
but yeah billy west was doing all a majority of those characters when i was growing up
and he was so good and he was he was so interesting the way that he would put stuff
together in the way that he would talk and how we would roll sentences together it was
it was fascinating and probably uh charlie adler too if you want to know who charlie
adler is um ed big head uh the satan from cow and chicken uh ikus from ah real monsters
just so talented just could do anything with his voice it was just he could go up he could go
down he was so good yeah like the ass devil guy yeah yeah i think he had an actual name
was he just devil but there you go i did a kind of a wordy answer there but i'm really
sorry to hear about your having withdrawals here and if i can be something fun or something
interesting that you can relax to or have fun with i say it a lot but it's that's great
for me that's great for this community that means a lot to me that's like that's great
for me to hear that because i would never want somebody to come and watch this channel and then
say that's this is not good this was that i didn't like that this made me like
uncomfortable this made me feel like shit i don't want you to like feel like shit after
the stream i don't want you to leave this stream like mad or upset or angry or not having fun you
know what i'm saying i don't want you to feel bad so knowing that if you feel people tell
me that they feel good that's a win for me like i feel great hearing that it wins not really
the right word but i mean maybe it is floor soup was uncomfortable yeah and i know like
honestly like we fuck around a lot on these streams but it's to a point where we're
it you know what i mean that i can't really put it into words the floor soup made me
uneasy yeah but you didn't leave you still here floor soup was pissing me off it was
hey it's just soup on the floor it's a clean floor it doesn't where else was i going to put
it i almost screwed hey i'm having a moment here okay i'm having a little moment here i'm
trying to like tell you and i care about you sport anyways that's gonna be it i will see you guys
for the microsoft conference i'll probably be live 20-ish minutes before the conference so i can
get set up and we can hang out and remember last time i did this i was like 10 minutes late and
i was like in a bathrobe with wet hair from the shower i'm gonna try to avoid that this
time that is sunday let's see e3 microsoft so that it's at 4 p.m eastern so let me let me
get a good look here i'm not doing the ea play live i feel like that's not gonna be anything
worth covering microsoft is sunday at 4 p.m eastern so 1 p.m pacific so like 12 30 pacific
on sunday is when the stream is probably i'd say between like 12 and 1 p.m pacific and stream
will turn on and then bethesda is four hours later so depending how long the microsoft
conference goes we'll play uh kitchen flipper for a couple hours or so and then there's also
i probably probably won't do devolver because i probably at that point would have been
streaming for almost 10 hours so i'll probably take off after the bethesda conference four five
six seven eight nine ten no actually never mind i'm reading this wrong it'd be like
maybe not we'll see how it goes because that would only be six hours or so so yeah we'll
just play it by your sunday between 12 and 1 pacific the stream will turn on we'll do
the conferences and we'll hang out and that's pretty much the next time you're gonna see me
have a great rest of your night take care guys thanks for hanging out hope you enjoyed
it that game was fun and i had a lot of fun hope you did too take care everybody have
a great rest of your night and have a good weekend too because i won't see you until sunday
or yes sunday good night