Good afternoon. Hello. Hi. Hope everyone's having a good day. I know I saw you last night and the
night before, but you know, just checking in on you. Today we have a very special stream,
one of hopefully many of these. You probably saw the title change earlier, like an hour ago.
We're going to do the Community Content Night. I've been talking about these for a long time,
and the first one's going to be tonight, or today, depending on where you are. These streams
will be once every month or two. I am going to monitor because there was a lot of submissions.
So I'm going to try to monitor how long this stream was, right? And then count how many,
I guess I'm going to keep track of how many tabs I had and how many length of the videos and all
that stuff. So I have no idea. This stream might be long, it might be kind of short,
but I want this is the first one. This is an experiment. He's got a stream monitor open.
You know, when you have too many tabs, when Google Chrome no longer puts the new tabs on top of the
screen. When I was clicking new tabs, it's like a ruler. Each increment of where a centimeter
is a new tab. It's a ruler up here. A giant ruler, a yardstick with centimeters on it.
Those are hard to find. Not using Firefox. Well, I use Chrome on stream. I use Firefox
for me. That's me. Chrome? Stream. Firefox? Me. Why do I do that? Well, that's because I do all of my
things on Firefox. I do all of my banking on Firefox. I do all of my all of my passwords
going to Firefox. So Chrome is a completely separated, totally separate entity that is
only for streams. Banking. All his Reddit accounts are on Firefox. Why do you have that many stream
tabs open? What do you mean stream tabs? Not using Internet Explorer? Here's the thing about Edge.
Isn't Edge kind of good? No. I've, I've heard that it's sort of good now. No, it's not. No.
I've heard it. It's okay. They've been slowly building that browser to make it a little bit
better for everybody, I think. But I like Firefox. Chrome was all right, but I don't know. When you
do Ctrl Alt Delete when you have one browser of Chrome open. I don't know why browsers do this.
Some of them do. Why are there like 12 processes when you have a Chrome browser open? Why? What does
it do? Why can it be one? It's one per tab. That's because Chrome sucks. Each process is a tab. No.
How my number is doing? Oh, shit. I forgot to open it. I forgot to keep it open. I turned off my
computer. I was gonna have it going for like 16 hours. Oh, well. I'm never playing it again now.
That's the nail in the coffin right there. Not playing it again. Once you make a mistake like
that, you cannot do that again. Now I have to go. What am I gonna open it again? Wow, that's too much
work. And speaking of work, I would like to change. We're gonna move on here. We're gonna start.
There are a lot of videos. There are a lot of pieces of artwork. This is Community Content
Knight number one. You were here for this one. You were here for the first one ever.
So let's start with the artwork. Here it is. This is artwork number one. Now one thing I do have to say
for the future. In the future, it's probably a good idea for you guys to watermark these with
your name because there are so many submissions that it's kind of, you know, it's hard to keep
track of every single person. So for the future, if you have something you want to put forward here,
throw a watermark on it if you want. If you, you know, want people to know that it was you.
It's mine now. Now let's go. Should I do cam for this? I don't want to do cam. Should I? I'm like,
all right, I'll just be down here at the bottom. All right. So how do you, I don't use Chrome.
How do you zoom in on Chrome? Is it control and scroll? What is it? This is, I don't use
Chrome. This is my streaming computer. There we go. All right. So this looks like a rumble.
This is, isn't, this is, uh, Gloo Man, Demon Lord Zaraxos, and a bunch of other fucking crazy
characters. So we got, this isn't good. Demon Lord Zaraxos is too strong, but if I fail,
the Jerma Rumble is doomed. You think you can beat me, you Gloo Man, the original shit character?
And then a big laugh. I'm the lord of all hells. You haven't got a chance. I may be the original
shit character, but I won't give up. Not when all of my friends are counting on me. You can do it.
All the beers agree on it. Beer. I make all the rules, kid, and I rule number one is don't lose
to this asshole. Gloo Man, win this for all the shit characters. This is all, that's all I get.
This is all the shitty characters. Like, well, that's, that's not a shit character. Do the voices.
You know, I need to sip my fucking cold classic before I can do that. Read, I'm reading them.
I am reading them. No, you can do it. All the beers agree on it. Beer. I make all the rules,
kid, and number one is don't lose to this guy. That boy didn't have a voice. Gloo Man,
win this for the shit characters. We believe in you. That's not what his voice is. That's
a placeholder. It's a template. Uh, Gloo Man can beat him. I bet all of my goat eggs on it.
And you can never have too many eggs. That's true. Hey, I think you fucking jump seed my grandson.
The little shit fuckhead is late for the stream. That's the best character. It is. I'm not late.
It's not even two o'clock. It's not even two o'clock. What are you on about?
That was great. And look at how quickly we can just go like this. Here's another fair
enough for the egg. Did someone ask for an egg? Balancing eggs. Very good. I'm early. I'm not
early. I'm in the exact window. Good stuff. I did say this in the rumble video, but the egg has
only been in two videos ever. He just, he has, that's the test of time. If you don't want a
character is, is just, is a great character when they've been on camera and on screen
for a collective, maybe seven minutes in 10 years of me doing this. And this fireman,
observe this individual, this handsome fireman. That's terrifying. That's horrifying, but still
cool at the same time. Am I going to play cube world? Are you going to play cube world?
Did I just get asked if I'm going to play cube world? No, I'm not. I'm not going to play cube
world. Uh, this is this, uh, person said that this is drawn in the, uh, style of, uh, I'm going to,
I'm going to butcher this name and it's a very popular, very, very talented artist,
Gendi Tartovsky, Gendi Tartovsky, Turovsky. What am I so phonetically spelled out for me, please.
The book is just almost flew out of my nose and we're not even five minutes into the stream.
He practiced that line for three hours. What? Gendi? Whatever. It's, that's, that's the guy
made Samurai Jack. Very cool. I love the line work. You're going to get, uh, by the way, you're,
I don't know anything about art. Uh, like you're going to get weird, uh, positive things here. I'm
going to be like, Oh, I really love the, uh, I really love the, the, the color scheme. And
if you're going to be like, fuck you talking about, you don't know anything about color schemes,
idiot. And I'm going to be like, I don't know. I just like it. So I don't know anything.
This is actually my ideal outfit. If I could wear this every day, I would, like, I mean, I do
besides, I mean, it's, it's blue, but this is, oh, I didn't show you this. This is, I, I got,
let me tell you something. I got a quick story for you. Take a look at this shit. I like this
shirt a lot and now I can never probably wear it again. Unless I get something like Oxy clean
or something to fix it. Take a look at this shit. I have coffee all over me. Can you guys see that?
It's literally all over the whole shirt. Um, coffee shops do this thing sometimes where they
fill your coffee so high to the brim that when the lid goes on, it creates this fucking vacuum
that sucks up the coffee and pushes it out of the top. Cause there's a bunch of ice in it. And I
don't know if it's like a cooling to heat rises. I have no idea, but they make, they fill it to
the brim so high that it's just obnoxiously high. And then they go, and when you grab it and you
go over it and you put your straw in, you get sprayed by coffee because there's pressure in
there somehow. Well, I got coffee sprayed. Like it was like, if you work at a coffee shop, you gotta
go like three or four centimeters under the line. Come on. And I'm just sitting there going like,
now what do I do? Now what do I do? Right? It wouldn't spray all over your shirt. Well, it was
like, and I'm like, oh shit. And it started dripping down, down, drip, drip, drip, drip,
drip. And I'm like, oh, it was very, very fast. You can't react fast like that.
Sorry for giving you more coffee. I guess that's not customer error. That's called the coffee was
filled too high to the top and it sprayed me customer error. You got extra coffee. No, I got
extra ice because what they do with a lot of these coffee shops is they dump a fucking whole
cooler worth of ice in your drink. And then they pour like three shots of fucking liquid in there.
And then over the course of a day or of a few hours or whatever, or an hour, your ice melts
and fills the rest of the drink up. It's just ice. You drink an ice. That's why you say no ice or
you say light ice, please. If you don't say light ice, you get a, you get like a tailgating party
worth the fucking ice in your drink. Light ice. Then they go, you know, normal. Anyways, that's
a great outfit. That's the outfit that I wear every day. Oh, this is during the, the, the Werma.
There we go. See, there we go. Dragon breath. There it is. Those of you that remember this stream,
this is from the dreams stream, which I took, took the defeat there that I, I couldn't really do it.
Why did you create me, Jeremy? I think this is based on the Garfield stuff, right? You know,
that's Werma. It's, it's horrifying. This is exactly what it looked like. This is not, I mean,
this is, this is an artist representation of Werma, but it's 100% accurate. And just in the
case you felt like sleeping tonight, here's the German scorpion. You can't stop me, Jeremy.
That's fucked up. Yeah, it is. Those of you that have played a certain video game, this is Ludwig.
That's what I see. It's great. That's from dragon breath. Thank you. These are great.
Very well done. This is my, they said this is my fursona. Frog. Yeah, that's right. I don't know,
I don't know, I don't know who that is. Is that, that's supposed to be me with the star wars shirt
on. Frogs don't have fur. I don't give shit. That's my frog soda. Fireman, take a look.
This is Clown Fireman. I mean, that's perfect. Timely, timely as well. Look at this dude.
He's so cute. I know. Fireman is, is the most adorable character, I think, that exists.
You could make a whole franchise around Fireman. You could have like, you could have like a
children's tv show. You could have a platformer that they could teach like safety and shit.
Fireman walks into like rooms and like lights shit on fire and then tells you like, this is
what you have to do. You're monetizing memes. Look out for this dude. Sell out the character,
will till we hate it. No, why would I do that? Fire Marshall Bill. And there's another one here
too. Look at that. It's just beautiful. But why is he so sad? What happened? Why is he so, why,
what happened? Just crying because he's sad. This is a meme. Oh, because I sold him out. No,
I didn't. Now this one in particular, for one second I was like, oh shit, there's somebody
naked here, but it's all right. This was, this is a banner that was made for the whole Jerma Rumble
pretty much over the years, I guess. It's awesome. We got Batboy up here, the egg.
Now let's see if I know, let's see if I know my own character universe.
His uh, wall dad, super green screen, Charlie uh, cheese nips, Pac-Man, 30s, Milkman, the egg, me,
Batboy, Demon Bloods, Raxos, Sonic the Pencil, uh, Captain Cheez-It, right? Oh fuck, who's that?
Salad Fingers? No, what, did I put Salad Fingers in a rumble? Oh, Frogman from Dark Souls,
Frogman from Dark Souls, right? Frogman, this super Jax. Uh, there's the VR guy, a little bit
of background here. VR guy is my, probably like top three favorite characters I've ever made in a
video game. That whole thing, that the whole thing just was perfect for me. I loved every second of
it. That's VR guy. Uh, Garfield, Miserable Mikey, uh, Dr. Roker, Dr. Roker's pizza, haven't eaten one.
VR, why, why VR guy? Because he was on a wireless VR headset and just was playing a VR game and
didn't know he was in a wrestling event. That's my favorite character. Are you making fun of my
favorite character? Uh, there's grandpa, obviously, there's me again. Look at how deep, I love, I love
the, all right, here we go. I don't know shit about art, but here we go. I like the smoothness. I like
the, the almost, um, I love the smoothness of the palette. What am I trying to say? I love the,
it's like sanded almost. It's like sanded wood. I love the sanded wood look here. Take a look at
us, you know what I mean? It looks great. So we got Blue Man, uh, Mr. Sneak Man. Everybody has a man.
Everyone's man or boy. I'm coming to that realization right now. Uh, this is Bia, Bia, Bia 38,
by the way, I don't think I know my own characters. That's Bia 38. Uh, Dick Dastlely Richard.
Oh fuck, I don't know his name. Chuck, Chuck Schnauz, right? Chuck Schnauzwell, that's the one.
And that's the bottom half of the two person horse. I got it. And we had 10 community subs
just come in from Soft33. Thank you. Soft33, appreciate that. 10 subs. Congratulations to
those who got them. And thank you for the giant sub drop. Really. Thanks a lot. Forgot Frogman.
Well, I don't, I just, it's been a while. This is fantastic, Bill. It was awesome. And then
there's another one right after this one. I remember this one. I did, I've shown a couple
of these already on stream, but Jesus, some of these are so fucking good. You have to just look
at them again. You nailed it. It's a police sketch. That's the best damn police sketch
I've ever seen in my life. Uh, no, this is great. I love the, it almost looks like it was,
you know what I'm saying? You did the whole thing and then it was like,
whatever that's called. I love the smoothness of it. It's dope. I mean, you know what I'm saying? I
love, I love the tapping of it. I love the tapped smeared tapped on the cheeks. You know what I'm
saying? Like see here, it's like a, I can, I know exactly how your hand moved when you did this,
by the way. You went like this, like here's the paper. You went like, like, no, what are you
talking about? This is pencil. I know. But after the pencil was done, you went there with like a,
like a cloth and you went like, it's fucking fantastic. It seriously is. Thank you for this.
And that's me as Spider-Man. The Simpsons. What the fuck? It's like Peter Parker.
My brain is fucking fried apparently. I don't know why that was instantly, that was instantly
Peter Parker. They both start with an S. That's the problem. Spider-Man Simpsons. Peter Parker.
Thanks for drawing me as Peter Parker. No, this is great too. I have no idea why that came out.
Seriously. By the way, this outfit, I love it. I love the gray. Gray? Here's, I'm going to give
you, look, those are guys that are like, oh, I need some fashion sense. How do I, help me.
Well, I don't care. I can't help you up here because this is obviously like a joke, right?
But for here, gray, gray, black, blue, gray, black, blue, gray top, black jeans, blue sneakers,
black top, gray jeans, blue sneakers, blue top, black jeans, gray sneakers. Boom. I just did
your entire wardrobe for the rest of your life. Gray, black, blue, different shades. You could
have like a navy blue shirt, black pants, black shirt, black pants, black shoes, navy blue shirt,
navy blue shoes, gray pants, gray shows sweat. They all do. Okay. We're all humans. That's boring.
No, it's stylish and it's classic. Guys, it's classic. If, if you have the timeless for a reason.
This is called, this is called when chat is bored. I think too many jupes. There it comes. Can we get
one? I want one completed one. I want a real completed one or I'm not moving on. I will sit
here until we go. Somebody got it. They got it. Good. You got, wow. Holy shit. You guys did it
very easily. That's, I'm surprised you did it that quickly. It's too many jupes, too many jupes. That's
what we're seeing right now in chat. Stream will be bopping. Remember that one. This is great.
This one's really good. Yeah. They're all really good, but yeah, this is fantastic. Yeah. This is
from the game that I don't, I can't even, I can't even tell you the title. I don't know what it is.
It's something about like existence is, existence is futile or whatever. Resistance is futile.
That's the Borg from Star Trek. It's something like that. You'll find it. Type in the word like
existence into the steam bar and like it'll probably pop up. This is weed game, whatever
you want to call it. But this is great. This is the very beginning of the game. That's the best
part of the whole game. What's bopping? What's bopping, gamer? Yeah, that's true. What else we
got here? But that's great. Thank you. Oh shit. We're zoomed in, but this one is, this one's got
our, one of our favorite characters. That's an iced coffee. That's fireman enjoying an iced coffee
while the rat cooks a marshmallow on his head. I mean, this is like, come on, this is genius.
And I think they're in the desert. So this is probably somewhere in Las Vegas. Hot chocolate.
Oh, it is a hot chocolate. I thought it was an iced coffee. All right. That's my head cannon.
That's an iced coffee because he's like fireman. He's got to like cool down with an iced coffee.
I thought that was ice, like ice coffee. Whatever. But this is, I love it. I love the rat. I love
the marshmallow. He needs to heat it up. He would die if he drank this. No, he wouldn't. Why would
he die if he drank this? This is not going to kill him. Why would this kill him? Because it's cold.
It's too cold. Guys, if there's a fire blazing, like if you have a fire blazing and you pour a
water on it, you're not going to put the fire out. You're going to, it's going to be like,
and then just come back. It's not, you're not going to put the whole thing out.
If you have a big fucking fire in front of you and you take a cup of water this big and you go like
this, it's going to go and it's not going to put it out. You need a bucket of, if this was a bucket
of iced coffee, then maybe I would be concerned. Do it. Especially, you know, he, he might be made
out of grease. So that would just make it worse. If this was a cup of like powder, how do you get
rid of a grease fire? It's powder, right? Yeah. This was a cup of like talcum powder. Get it away
from him. Sand. Yeah. Yep. Cover it. Don't go near him. Don't cover him with anything.
You use milk. Now this is great though. Thank you. This also is a strangely, strangely in like the
same spot somehow. This says, it's so the curio had cheated death in the cemetery outside Good
Springs, cheated death once again. And the Mojave wasteland was forever changed. That was odd.
Michael's trip to Vegas. This is pretty good. Is this a spoiler? Spoiler for what? Wait, is this
not, is it, is this the end of the, of the game? This is the, this is the game's intro. No, it's
not. Is this the outro? Is this the game's outro? Uh oh. The game's been up for 15 years. If you
didn't play it yet, you're not going to play it. And by the way, why have you, why have you not
played it? It's the best one. It's the first portion of the outro. Let's skip that one then.
This is a odd, we'll stay on the odd. Odd Michael theme. You know what I really like on this one?
I like the pixelated graphics. Each beard is a pixel line. I like it. It's, you got the edges
here. Very pixelated. Nice teeth. I like the beard. It's the, the beard really draws you in.
When you look at this, what's the first thing you look at? You look bang right at that beard.
This right here. I haven't shaved, so this still works. Looking good. Thank you for the, uh,
and we've got the pretzel here too. That's what I like the most. Same artist, I believe, but this
is Jex. I don't have that much hair though. No, I did. I did have this much hair. I forgot. Do you
guys remember like two or three years ago how fucking long this was? It came down, it came down
to like here. It was crazy, but it wasn't nice long. It was just gross long. It was ugly. It was
just long and to here. I didn't have it layered, so it was just weird looking. Now my hair is a
mustache. That's fine. I'd probably rather have mustache hair, but this is great. It's got the
glasses too. What the heck are you talking about? Old man, even bald for 30 years. I hadn't even
been alive for 30 years, but that's Jex and this was Odd Michael. Good shit. This is me. I did,
I did this one. Oh, right. This is, this is a part, okay, this is a part two. I have no idea
what I was doing here. I can't, I don't know. This was supposed to be what? This was Twitch,
right? And then this is a streamer. Oh, right. This is from, from a couple weeks ago. So I,
this is me drawing a streamer. This is, Jeremy is my favorite finger YouTuber. What do you do?
Just go like this. Hey, what's going on guys? Welcome back. Uh, welcome back to, uh, hands
episode of 415. Yep. That's the one. I'm going to go like this today. Okay. What would that even
mean? Hand, just, uh, this time a finger. I'm a YouTuber that just finger hand YouTuber.
He's still got it. He's still got it. Yeah, guys, I don't know. I'm really like trying to think
about a change here. I've been a, I've been a finger YouTuber for like the last six years
and I kind of want to move on. I want to move forward. I want to keep the content going.
So I'm thinking of transitioning into elbow, you know, I know, I know I'm looking at the
comments right now. No, it used to be so much fucking cooler when you were a hand YouTuber,
but no, I don't want to elbow is different. I don't know. I don't want that guy. I'm just
trying to do something different now. You know what I mean? You got, you like, you guys cool.
I know people can take a while. Maybe just give it like 10 or 12 episodes. Look, I'll do here.
How about this? Once a week, I'll do a hand and a finger YouTube video, but like I'm going to,
I'm really into this right now. Uh, anyways, the next image is a continuation of this. I believe
they drew this. They like interpreted that. Oh, is this supposed to be me? No. Why am, why am I
being like obeyed? It's me watching your stream vessel. Right. Right. Right. Right. Let's take a
look. See how accurate it is. Pretty, pretty accurate. This is the fucking thing you hang up
on the fridge that your three-year-old drew. This is not streamer. This is how is your first day
of the first grade? Well, this, this, this Mr. Stevenson is really nice and we got to go to
computers and he turned on all the computers for us. And then I prayed. I played Minecraft.
Oh, wow. Wait, wait, your T your teachers letting you play video games in school.
Yeah. I played Minecraft for 10, 20 minutes. I'm going to be writing a letter to that
fucking superintendent, but I was just great. Thank you. Pull them out of that school.
Now they, they, they should, they should be teaching children about what should they be teaching kids
now? What do they teach? What are the, what's in school now? I haven't been in school in a long
time. What's the, what's like the, what's the first class you take in like middle school?
Stocks. No, they don't. There's no, I would have signed up for that class in like high school.
Science taxes. They don't teach you how to do taxes. You want to talk about how fucking
strange the American educational system is. We have this thing that everybody has to fucking do
when they get older. When you get to be 15, 14, 15, 16, 17 years old, why are they not teaching
us how the tax system works? Because you just get a job afterwards and then you just are supposed
to know who fucking supposed to tell you these things. It would have been really nice to know
how the credit system worked. But Christopher Columbus drove his boat and found this.
Okay. How do, what does credit mean? And please help me. I didn't know what credit fucking was
until I was like, I didn't understand how the system worked until I was like 26. And I would
imagine that a lot of you guys still don't fucking know. Exactly. That's what I'm saying.
Why is this not like a subject to teach us skills? Give us like skills that we need. Give us life
skills. Roll the TV in and show the Christopher Columbus shit on the TV. We'll be way more
involved in that one. There's got to be like a, an old like magic school bus episode about
Christopher Columbus. That's 22 minutes long. That's not like eight days worth of reading
textbooks. Teach me how to do my taxes. Teach me how to live. Does a magic school bus have like a
taxes episode? That'd be pretty fucking funny if they did. Anyways, sorry. I mean, I just,
I just want our education. I want, I want people to be, I want our education system to be working.
German 95 in Cox Cowboy, the slowest upload in the West. What is this? What is that? Is that a brum?
Am I holding like a brim up? Okay. At Hot Topic, they sell those lamps that are like that, right?
Is that a lamp? It's a horse. Where's, where's the horse? And who like shaved it? Because there's a
large chunk missing here. Is this the tail? Is this the horse's tail? And like the horse is like out
here. This is the horse's mane. Well, what, what is this? Is this like the, that's it looks like a bar.
Sometimes it's too easy. This is great. This is Glooman. Got you. Please stop. People are
going to actually think that you're dumb. This is why if only they fucking taught us in school
zoology, I would have been able to know immediately what the fuck that was.
Don't blame me. Blame the educational system that I was taught, which was algebra two part two.
I don't remember a goddamn thing from algebra two part two. Not a thing. I don't even know. I,
I'm going to close my eyes. I'm going to try to think of one word that came out in that class.
I can't. Imaginary numbers. And I don't look, math is important, right? But I don't buy
the whole thing that they used to sell us in those classes. You don't think you're going to use it,
but you will event. You're going to use it. You don't know you will, but you will. Yeah. When?
When have I ever done like X parentheses, two plus three brackets? No, we have Excel for that.
Mrs. Stevenson. This is great. Glooman, by the way, like this is, this is perfect.
I don't know why I thought that said style Seinfeld. It's like, wow, he fucking nailed it.
I didn't, there's a Seinfeld style in, uh, uh, soul caliber. That's pretty cool. What does it do?
And I mean, like this could be like a Seinfeld thing. That's like a Kramer move or something.
I don't know. Oh, here we go. We've seen these before. I just, uh, that was like, so that was
such a stretch. Oh yeah, Kramer, when he walked in and he goes like, he does that though. That's,
okay, that's not a stretch. That's not a stretch. He does that shit. He like opened the doors and
he like, he would like fucking move his hands around and be like, oh, Jerry. But this is from
Yan Wen. This is, uh, some great stuff from Yan Wen. Look at me, Jerry, look at me. This, I think
this is the first one that, uh, Yan Wen ever, uh, thank you, at least on stream. So I can't even,
man. Uh, but yes, it's fucking fantastic. Yan Wen is incredibly talented as you'll see here.
This is one of my favorites. This is the, uh, Seagull one. It's so good. It's so detailed.
It looks first. It looks nice. It's so, yeah, I'll tell you up here. See up here, the effect
that the wings are flapping is done. It's achieved by like, you take your, you take the palette and
you take a little bit of a cloth and you like dip it in some water and you go to blur it out. The
blurred image is representing movement because if you take a photo, if you would take a picture of
this happening, the frame rate would not be fast enough. Your ISO would need to be, um, closed
or opened, you know, depending on your, your shutter speed has to, it has to do with it too.
So if you, you see, this is like a great family photo. Of course stocks are crashing. Like,
wait, like in real, like in real life. All right. Let's imagine like the Dow drops like 10,000
points. Someone just comes into Twitch chat and just goes, all right, what happened? Oh, well,
time to buy gold. This is also from Yan Wen. This is, uh, before the carnival happened. Get
yourself, get, hey, unfortunately, I was not the clown in that string. That's no, it's, that is,
that is not a penis. That's a dog or it's a cat. That's, I, that's, I don't know how to make a dog.
So that's pretty accurate. This is me trying to make a dog. Look at that intense face though.
I could paint it on eyebrows. I should ask Polly polite, see if she can help me here.
But they're all, I picked out a few of my favorites there. So they're all, ah,
damn it. You ever, that ever happened? You ever get like stuck and you have to like,
that's been happening a lot lately. What's wrong with me? It's me with the rats.
It happens. Sometimes you just get like a little kink. Uh, it's just me hanging out with my rat
friends. Go see a chiropractor. I've actually been told that before, but chiropractors are weird
because 50% of all people say chiropractors are horse shit and they're fake and it's like going
and getting a psychic reading. And then 50% of people will tell you, I went to a chiropractor
and it changed my life. So who, what the, who do I fucking believe? I guess if you go to like,
some people can go to like a psychic reading and that can change your life too. Cause they're like,
oh, you have money coming in the future and you're like, holy shit, that was awesome.
I guess that could, that makes sense. I don't know. It scares the shit out of me too. I don't
know. I feel like, okay, like lie down here and just put your back that way. Okay. Now I'm going
to turn your body like this and I'm going to put my knee into your back and pull as hard as I can
this way and snap the other way with my knee and like break your back. Right. And then they like,
I've seen like, I've seen videos of people that they put them like in this like device,
they like lock their head like this. And then the guy takes like a thing and like puts it around
their head and like pulls it up. Like, and every time I see one of those videos, I just go, I don't
want to fucking do that. But then somebody will tell me, man, you got to go. You got to go. I'm
telling you, like, I feel like my, my spine's got like fluid in it now. I'm not going to go.
I don't want to have like that thing put around my head. It's going to be like medieval torture
device, but this is great. Me and the rat friends. That's a fireman. He's got underwear on. Relax.
This is a super fireman, as you can see, powered up in or in mid powering, possibly. Good Lord.
Yeah. I wonder how many ice coffees it would take to put this one out.
Right guys. God. And then from the same artist, this is Dick Dastley Richard. I like this a lot.
I like the, the bag. I like the, the eye slots. It looks, it makes it look more like a mask.
It's a hand tuber. Yep. Contemplating getting into the hand tuber scene. Did you, did you paint,
did you do that? That looks, this is really cool. Did you take the media from the game
and just kind of layer it on here and then go over like around it? That's pretty cool.
Cause this is, this looks like the game media. That's exactly what I did. Nice. That's awesome.
And if not, then you came really, really, really almost scarily close to what it actually looks
like. Very, very cool. This is from the computer doctor stream. So it reminds me of like a Sunday
morning cartoon panel. Gold plated. Yep. I feel like this should be like a bubble here.
This is like panel three or something. You gotta make a statement. You do have,
you gotta make a statement with your computers. Looking for Garfield. Looks like Kramer.
And I'm doing a Kramer right here. That, this is, that's Kramer. Do I look like Kramer? Maybe.
Maybe a little. No, I don't think so. Kind of. No, I don't think so. A little. Not really.
Oh, this is an animation. This person said that they were working on an animation. It's the first
time they've ever animated anything. And they have a little template that they were working on
for. This is a pre carnival stuff. And this is just a little bit of a teaser for what might come
later. And we have a little bit of a look here. They were going to do what I, what I assumed was
going to be a carnival cartoon with all these little ideas. Does it look real? It just looked
cool. So I wanted to look at it. I wanted to show it. What's that called? So you guys gotta help me
out here because I don't know anything about art. What is the thing called when you draw,
let's say you're going to draw something. And then the first thing you draw is like all the lines,
like lines, lines, lines, lines, lines, lines, lines, lines, lines, and then over what's,
what is that like called when you do that on line work, rough sketch? Does it have anything? Does
it called anything like a rough sketch? Because then you do, you go over it, right? Will we drop
in frames? No, we're okay. Cause then you go over that and then you delete, you delete the
layer behind it. Construction lines, early access art. There's like six different terms for it.
Structured lines. Okay. Yeah. I always found that interesting because it's almost like you,
you're like building out a skeleton and then you go over the skeleton and then you delete the
skeleton and you keep adding and then you maybe delete that too. It's a DLC sketch. This is cool
though. Really cool stuff. That's just me, you know, just, that's just me just looking great.
Try it. I can't do it. Delete your skeleton. Yeah. I think you got it pretty good. I think
you got it pretty close. I said my hair is a little longer now, but maybe not before.
This is Jerma Chad. That's just, that's just Jerma Jerma. Nice work. Here's some donkey donuts
because you're epic. I don't, I don't know. I still don't understand this.
Did this, did this come from this channel? It gets blurry. No. Okay. So this is not,
but the Dunkin Donuts thing. Here's some donkey donut because you're epic.
The little rat is great. And I got the Twitch logo on it. I feel like this is something you would do
out of Starbucks. If you were like really, really pretentious about your stream.
And what's the name? Twitch.tv slash Jerma985. Okay. And they have to write it on there. And
then you can walk around with it and like you just, people can just see it. I don't know.
People probably do that. Phylactery, let's just say 5,000 bits, 50 bucks from Phylactery. Phylactery,
a lot of money. They're the money king at this point. And they say this,
Hey Jerma, quick question. Do you find it weird that right now your bones are wet?
No, not at all. Because the bones are just the thing to protect the meat inside.
That's fine. That the bones are the shield for the marrow that's inside of them.
I don't care. Do you care when your car gets wet?
No, the car is the shell protecting the meat inside, which is you.
I just saw somebody just wrote, he's insane. No, your bones. What do you mean wet? How are they
wet? Okay. You've got skin, muscle, bone, but what the, is muscle wet? I mean, it's maybe,
it's maybe damp, like moist, damp. Muscles are not like, they're damp. They're like liquidy, I guess.
But who cares? Because if we weren't, if we weren't like 76% water, then that's fine. That's a,
that's the actual question is, is it weird that you are 76% water? I guess, probably.
But guess what, guys? You want to talk about some weird, fucked up,
next level meta shit? So is the earth. Weird. This is from the hit and run streams. Bogdanoff's are
calling. It's from the hit and run, the Simpson stream. This is from the Spider-Man stream.
If you remember when we played Spider-Man, I did. It was very, very good. It's an interesting
depiction. It was, you know, Doc Octopus. That was two years ago. Was it? No, it was not. That
was in, no, that was in Vegas. I've only been in Vegas for a year. That was like five, that was
like six or seven months ago. That was like three or four months ago. That was not that long ago.
It was two years ago. Oh, this is great. I think this actually was the thumbnail for that second
Derma video that was made, I think. It was in December. Right. Trying to figure out his own
lore. Right, but to be fair, I have an encyclopedia this thick of stuff that I've ever said or done
on camera. And sometimes you gotta cycle to like the S for Simpsons. Okay, there it is. Thick. Okay.
This is Glooman and me. This is great. I love this. Okay, much taller than Glooman, as you see.
We have seen this before, but it's worth showing again. This is the old Derma. New Derma shrunk and
became... I'm still all right. I'm not going to give you guys any gasoline to dump on that fire.
Uh, yeah. But this is, we've seen this one before. It's really good shit. I think this is all made
by the same artist, these two, this one as well. I believe so. Very, very good work. I like the
background here. It makes the foreground pop. Did you guys know that I was... I swear to God,
this is not a lie. This is 100% true. I promise you. I fucking 100% promise. I was an art minor
in college with my degree. My degree is an art minor. Yes, that's true. It is. I need to show
you. I don't even know where my degree is. I don't think it's even in this house.
I don't... I don't have my degree. If I ever needed to prove... This is the funniest part.
If I ever like applied for a job somewhere and they were like, oh, can we like see a copy of your
degree? I don't fucking have it. Can I like call the... Can you call the college? Is it like sending
you medical documents? Hey, I need you to fax my medical degree, my documents over. You can do
that, right? Is there... Is it like a timeline where you can't do that anymore? What if I graduated
20 years ago? Do they still have it? What if the college... Okay, what if the college
goes under and doesn't exist anymore? Where can I get it? I should get it now then. I'm going to
get like five copies of it. Hey, can you send over five copies of my degree just in case you're
screwed? No, I'll be fine. Back to college I go. The state government should have it too. They have...
The state government has everybody's degrees? What was your major? Engineering. Oh, look at this
one. This is a cute picture of me and Kim. You know, Kim is my girlfriend. Those of you that
might be new, you might not know. And that's me. It's adorable. I'm gonna... I'm gonna hang this
one up. I'm gonna hang them all up. I'm gonna get them as bumper stickers on my car. No, this is
great. What I really like here... I'm not gonna say it. No, this is good shit. We've seen this on
stream before too. What do you mean egomaniac? Hold on. I'm an egomaniac because some...
What if you... What if somebody took a photo of you and your girlfriend
and they showed it to you and then you're looking at it? Would somebody come over and say that
you're an egomaniac? Holy shit, dude. Wait, you took like three... Wait, hold on a minute.
You went on vacation and you have like 10, 20 photos of you on vacation? You fucking egomaniac.
Who are those for? I don't know. Why doesn't everybody take pictures? Why doesn't everybody
do anything? They're for me. If they were insane and had no concept of social standards.
So me wanting to frame a photo like this and like put it in like, like the fridge or in the
bedroom or something. This is like a nice moment. No, egomaniac would be if I told you to edit this
photo and up here write top fucking 500 streamer, wicked sick stream, really talented guy with an
arrow pointing over here. Like I have you edit it and do that and put that in or I won't put it up.
That's how you make the difference. Please OP. Edit that, please OP. OP? Oh, original poster, right?
Now this is good stuff though. Thank you. Let's keep going.
I just played this. I was over on my other monitor and the video portion's coming up.
You didn't hear it. I just played that accidentally but the audio was muted.
There's a video portion coming up here in a little bit and that is the first one.
Anyways, this is a artist depiction of what that image looks like down here.
Frame this one. Now this is a Halloween mask. This is two steps away from BF Bugleberry.
It's October. Make 3D print this as a mask. How much would that cost? How much would it cost to
have a company actually make me like a silicone like 3D printed like actual mask of this?
Like $150,000? I don't think so. What is it made out of? Is it made out of like silk?
300 bucks? We'll see. Maybe. This is great though. Thank you. It's good shit. This is from
the Dragon Lair stream. Please save me. This is, I think it's called German Daphne.
The cage is locked with the key. The dragon keeps it around his neck to slay. The dragon
used the magic sword. We saw this I think 150 times. Dragon's Lair.
That was close to a meltdown stream by the way. That was very close. Like I would say like another
10% more frustration in that game. I may have lost my mind. It was close. It was a lot of fun
though. It was. But thank you for this. It's great. That's supposed to be me in the glass tube
thing. Now this is Jex and I believe this is who made it. This is my Namco light gun. I missed that.
I should have signed it. I should have signed that and like cut the cord off, signed it,
and put it up in my entryway. Just to like have like look at that piece of like history.
Fucking egomaniac. This is Vinnie, right? It's a little gif. It'd be padding. That's Vdub.
Oh okay. I'm sorry. I'm sorry. I'm sorry. One of these days maybe they'll team up. I don't know
though. I can't determine when he's going to come out. Sometimes he just does. Now that's cute. Very
cool. And then the next one is, I don't know. I don't know the context on these. Learn the
difference. It could save your life one day. Vinnie the Jerma. But I'm like sweaty and he's
cool. He's really cool and I'm like sweaty and weird. And then this is Vdub and Jex. Eats veggies
is cool and has a has a gun. Taller than Jerma. Jex. Totally better than Vinnie at video games.
So this is Vdub is better than Vinnie. Vdub vapes and just very epic. So wait. So Jex is
better than Jerma? Is that what we're coming to the conclusion of here? No. No, no, no, no, no,
no. This is like it's like Vegeta and Goku. You need both of them. Otherwise you're not going to
be able to take down Frieza. Give me a break. This is not better or this is the this is the version
of I have to be that. No, no, no, no, no. Need them both. There was what what was the movie?
What the fuck was the movie or TV show where the person's all their like alter egos came out. They
had to like um no it's uh the um no not face off what face off is two guys faces switched um
there's a Zelda game where this happens split no no no no no different Zelda Zelda and the four
links right like there's like sleepy link and then there's like comedy link and then this like angry
link right and they like split up does that happen no there's something else too it's not
snow white the seven dwarfs did not combine into like a mecha dwarf no jimmy neutron
why would that be so that's too specific i didn't watch jimmy neutron enough to know that
it's the movie called identity the power rangers identity okay you take that's from teen titans
no okay every major cartoon has probably done this every major syndicated cartoon television show
has probably done the you through some weird scientific experiment had like six personalities
come out of you it just depends on which one you want to name this happens in the muppets
no it doesn't danny phantom to i'm going to be to me danny phantom episode one and episode 100 of
the same episode what what happened in danny phantom was how do you what was this what was
the overarching story arc of danny phantom because i saw like five or six episodes of
danny phantom and they were all the same episode i could i could not take it tell them apart
i do remember the theme song because it was lit let me do it for you right now if i remember
he's he's gonna catch up on cuz he's danny phantom gonna catch up on cuz he's danny phantom
that's that i've been fucking hearing that and just being like
yeah just pump me the fuck up every time somebody gets 50 dollars uh it was by lactory lich again
5 000 more bits from uh i just said danny phantom thank you danny phantom for the 5 000
my brain is fucked up today can i just be very clear uh they say this is basically jix i cannot
click it right now we'll watch it in a minute because that's in my stream labs here and i have
like a weird setup to try to capture everything so we'll we'll get we'll watch it but not right
this second cutting in line cutting in line with a video no no that's not how it works
don't worry it's all right cutting in line no no this no there ain't no disney fast pass on this
stream all right but anyways uh let's keep going we i'll don't it's gonna don't worry we'll get it
so that's fair enough yeah let's keep going this is uh the ringleader here at germa from the
carnival stream cotton candy the most terrifying aspect of that whole stream was the cotton candy
machine i think i talked about it before but the thing was dangerous and of all the things that
were there they were machines that were shooting uh softballs at me and the thing that was the
closest thing to me actually getting severely injured was the cotton candy machine we watched
the footage afterwards and we like that's dangerous frog what about the frog the frog is all right the
umbrella yeah still have a i still have a scar on this finger that'll be my next uh uh finger
youtuber video hey i got like a cut the other day that'll be in all capitals big cut on finger
healing really well no i didn't but it didn't cut me it pinched me and it hurt a lot but this is
great this is uh i really wish i looked that good because but here's the thing about costumes
when you buy a costume there's an 80 chance that it's going to be made out of a material
that's closer to paper than actual clothing so that hat and that robe were they were barely
caught it was that hat was barely a hat i don't know why it's just cheap cheap cheap shit material
paper is actually clothing i don't know why this can't make it normal clothes germa venus oh yeah
it wasn't a top hat it was a brimmed sack perfect description it was it was it was a brimmed sack
and no matter what i did i put my hand in there and i folded around like i was frosting a cake i
was trying to just make it so it was not so weird looking and so smushed looking it just looked like
it ran off by a fucking car but this is fantastic thank you oh this is one of the things that didn't
make it into the uh into the activity stream carnival at castle griffin steed find the hidden
images all right hold on i don't have my pen available i don't have my pen i gotta mark it
somehow i gotta mark it with the um all right i'm gonna mark this with what how do i mark this
i could do this here we go hold on can i do it like this i think i still have it no i can't
just write on the monitor you won't see that i think i can do this yeah i'll do it like this
i'm gonna add a circle here that was another 5 000 bits those 5 000 bits from ab joe ab joe
thank you for the huge amount of money they say ola germo piqueno here is the agreed upon amount
for the services rendered we will contact you in 36 days for your next assignment p.s hope you
write off all those costs on your taxes keep being you my man what are you talking about
uh thanks with 5 000 bits i appreciate it drugs drugs in the whale lord
piqueno meat i all right i know what it means all right we're gonna do this
i'm gonna very easily here i can do this yes i can all right so let's see if we can find some stuff
because i should be able to go like this yeah i can do like a line like that we'll make the line
like red what the fuck is it there we go all right let's try to find something so what am
i looking for here i'm looking for giant rat giant rat got it right there germa chomp germa chomp is
see if i can find it whatever germa chomp bald coin use click maps shit hold on i don't think i
can no i my setup is completely different today because i have like three or four different
captured windows let's see hold on maybe i can what if i do this is this even possible no no
wait wait wait wait this is not gonna work is it no no no no no well you're gone you'll be back
in a second hold on all right i think make sure yeah i can do it all right here we go you guys
ready to click help me find them click maps is cheating find it yourself you guys didn't get
to do any of them when we did that last time let's go give me a hand right there what's that
what's this one burger oh that's germa chomp right there good work oops germa chomp is right there
that's bald coin nice up here is germa raptor a wizard this is it's just a wizard all right
over here we've got uh germa moon germa pluto where's the clown car hold on my turn my turn
my turn my turn there's the two-person horse right there there's the j there's spiderman
there's pac-man shito frog treasure where's the clown car is the wario belt wine clown car
my turn my turn all right it's your turn go ahead find some ah there it is right there good work
chat you guys did it i'm proud of you there's glue carnival at castle griffinstein this is great
and then uh egg i think we already got egg down here right oh no that's not an egg it's a speaker
okay he's proud of us yeah you guys did a great job you did a fantastic job of course i'm proud
of you there's bat boy demon lord i think we got all wait not yet hold on where's where's um
there's a comet sparrows wheel where's an egg find the egg i don't see an egg egg egg ah there
we go right here nice nice work guys then there's the banana trophy right there and there's that nice
good work very cool this is great i wish i could do this one uh before i don't know how i missed
it maybe i did i was it not done or did i just miss it somehow i don't know but that's the banana
trophy nice all right let's keep going this is uh somebody's asshole not the picture like the photo
not this i'm talking about like you know what i'm saying what did i just delete this is uh the yep
the red line i got it i got it i got it it's from the video the photos are in
somebody was asking yesterday what's the first video i should show somebody that doesn't know
who you are the photos are in yeah i think that's a pretty good start hey welcome to las vegas and
the carnival this is a cute little photo that's a that's a nice image of my perfect three day
five o'clock shadow timed stubble of course fireman's there the rat what's it why is the
rat so concerned why is the rat is the rat annoyed that fireman's on my shoulder looks very irritated
and there's the tent we didn't have a tent but maybe we should have because of the wind but
you know you work with what you can and then uh leave a las vegas good shit very very very nice
and then of course real actual photograph of the uh of the frog in the face pretty accurate
representation the somebody i'm sure is putting the clip in i would assume if he hadn't seen it
uh if you didn't see that stream chat did a wonderful job not winning that game but
hitting me directly in the face there it is i was there i was there no not the slap
uh that was awesome though that was an amazing time thank you for everybody for punching me in
the face now you can say you did that you can say i hit germa in the face and it would not be a lie
it would be true you won this is from my stardew valley streams this is the duck person from
stardew valley it was a long time ago what was this what was this character's name yeah this is
a full probably three or four years ago stardew valley i think is some of the first streams i
ever did it was greg every character is greg greg is my go-to when i don't have anything to think of
it's just greg back to bed i do remember that though what a great game what just what a lovely
experience that was i miss it i kind of did everything though and then kim played it again
a couple years ago and she 100 percent of the game and i was watching almost the whole time so
i can't really play it again unfortunately and then after that we have a germa heart
except this is a little more uh this is a little more morbid this is a germa stab heart
but it's uh it's really cool nonetheless what monka s why i think it's great i look very angry
though and this is not even supposed to be me this is supposed to be the person living up here
if i'm jeremy and jex is jex jerk this is germa the same they all share an apartment up here like in
my nose like through my nose into my brain this is the front door this is the two hey we got a
two-car garage here that's expensive oh jesus christ um okay this is this is a i believe this
is a where's waldo garfield edition is my am i in this somewhere this like hurts to look at
uh i have no idea anybody see it no that's john but that's not john it's that i'm looking for me
right oh i don't know what i'm looking for am i looking for me it's just so much orange all right
i see what is this there's a garfield wheel got it right there that was good that was a pretty good
one garfield mario is garfield reaching shrek levels right you know exactly what i mean by that
not yet maybe already already surpassed already was there okay i'm sometimes curious because i'm
seeing some shrek levels of manipulation here like it's shrek but shrek looks like this now
it's shrek but mar it's he's got a mario overalls on i mean i put shrek's face on a lasagna
it's just nests from earthbound but it's it's shrek's face we have reached that point play
earthbound what are you talking about those are shrek levels of mean creations somebody knows
what i'm talking about here and that person gets it you know sometimes you just get it
making the same face that's my shit eating grin i do it all the time free me
free me that's germa greed then there's a seal and i didn't even know what that was until very
recently i have no idea what that seal is that seal is on some kind of other completely different
journey completely new adventure i did not save that seal that seal is doing this has been
released into our wherever they're going to be they have they're on their own with a new life
the seal spy no that's just a regular seal but yeah that's from the carnival inside the money
machine it was a lot of fun and this is great i've seen a few of these this is uh the giant rat
it's a fair not a giant rat almost as a kingpin i do like the double cigar that's a nice touch
one for now one for later and this one is the later one as you can see because this one is
being uh dragged down quite a little bit dual welding cigars how about both for now
now you'll puke i gotta give you some advice here cigars are horrible because unlike a cigarette
if you smoke a cigar you are going to throw up because it has so much more concentrated
power in it it will you will puke if you smoke if you if you like i'm gonna smoke a full cigar
to my just to my face you'll throw up don't inhale a cigar don't smoke a cigar if you're
going to smoke a cigar don't breathe it in and don't do enough where you puke just don't smoke
that's easy you taste it and then spit it out just don't smoke don't smoke cigars don't be like this
guy he's got two you don't want to do one somebody just wrote something so so incorrect that it's
making me upset it's a good image though and then a birthday rat it was my birthday recently
happy birthday right thank you tell us what it is they said no because i don't want to be
i don't know i don't want to bad i don't want to be the person that is gets attributed this
shit they said something about it makes you stronger because it makes your lungs work harder to let
you like no no no no that's what it was that's what it was uh happy birthday rat thank you
very very very cute everybody loves rats let's get right in here close very nice tail
you got the nice earthworm looking tail that's correct very nice it's just a really really
nice image nice fucking job uh happy birthday little man little man how come it can't be big
man actually big man would be i think more of a tongue in cheek more it's like more of an insult
right right it is why can't it be happy birthday dude you know what i'm saying with the fireman
shirt on and the microphone from the carnival dermal wild two emote it's invaded you it's all
right you're too small i'm not all right i gotta i gotta like i gotta get you guys out of here
like in here like go to sleep at night i just hear like i just see like the images
like the edited fucking images and i like roll around like sweating this is great too i don't
even know what i don't know what this is referenced to but it's cool this is me versus chat when you
guys controlled that bot and i i just i destroyed you it wasn't even contest you know you got like
two hits on me nice try though he doesn't know it's a jojo thing i'm never gonna watch that
show i don't think i don't think it's ever gonna happen i gotta be real with everybody in the in
the office here i don't think i'm ever gonna do it i keep thinking of like times where like i might
do this and it just never becomes a thing just read it read it stream it i can't stream tv shows
i can't stream that germa can't read this is great though i love it regardless of where this is a
reference from or two it's it's still a great image now this one this is fucking amazing this
is a very recent stream the fmv night when i was stuck in the rocket wheelchair for 25 minutes
it's probably the hardest i've laughed in a long time at least in the last few weeks last month or
two my game was ridiculous that was from fox hunt i believe that's the game right fox hunt
that hurt to watch that hurt to watch imagine how much it hurt to play who's but somebody
eating your pizza what it was hilarious to watch it was it was just an absolute mess but this is a
this is a fantastic just encompasses the entire stream because it was an absolute joke put a
clip of me stuck in the chair if nobody saw that then that's a good opportunity for you to see it
because it was insane nobody has any clips of it oh too bad it's all right and then this is um
what i don't know why i included this i i this was just there it's i don't know it's like me
saying i don't know what this is what a perfect image to go after that that it was okay it's
supposed to be a me doing monkey s as me new emotes no i can't no no no these images in
succession they tell a story this is me back in my coal mining days you kind of have to double
take this one because it looks like a real image for a second and then you realize no it's not
it's not at all actually that was from my vibe stream when the stuff that weird charcoal stuff
was melting onto my face he hasn't aged a day look at that hair that hair is disgusting
i have such fine hair though that's the thing i have really fine baby fine hair that even the
slightest variable turns it to shit i will go out like this okay and i will look like this i'll take
a step outside and they will be like a six mile per hour wind gust six like maybe five miles per
hour and it just it turns in a second into just madness like this and i'm constantly like fuck
god damn it and i don't wear uh gel i don't do like gel or um hair spray i can't because
when i do hair spray this is the one thing that you need to remember about when you put products
in your hair you got to get it out because if you sleep in that shit it goes stays in here and goes
down and just gives you this greasy gross fucking hairline and i just break out all around my whole
hairline so you have to if you go out and you put product in your hair when you come back you have
to shower and sometimes that's a pain in the ass because you're tired and how many times have you
just been like all right it's like it's like 10 11 12 whatever i don't know one two three who knows
how late it is and then you have to go take a shower when you'd rather just go lie down and go
to bed i don't i don't put product in my hair at all use the water-based pomade i it doesn't work
it makes me just look like a sicko not shampoo yeah i shampoo in condition don't go all the way
to the roots so wait you won't no don't go all the way to the roots so you want to put like
like hair gel like here and then when the gust of wind comes through this happens are you ready
if i would do just right here the gust when the gust of wind happens this happens and that's what
i end up with and it's unfixable his hair is fucked no it's just fine it's really fine and
it can't i just let it do whatever it's gonna do but i like it like this i like the way it looks
like this i don't want to like shave it off am i sweating probably i liked it shorter i like it
short but i like it like this this is this is how i'm gonna wear it and i'm gonna cut it again
soon i'm a red dead redemption 2 npc oh here is what you mean because i'm curious i don't
understand how how me are you talking about here okay whoa we're in close but this is uh
this is one guy whoever you are doing a little dance gif image very cute i do uh and yes for
the future when we do these again make sure you watermark it just throw a little thing just like
just even if it's a copy of the image if you don't want to do anything to like the original
copy the image put a little thing on it just so we know who it is i said i said gif i didn't say
gif it's a it's a gif it's even i know it's pronounced gif whatever but this is very cute
this is the fireman gif fireman gif that was glue man and uh me apparently everybody loves fireman
i love fireman i'm noticing a lot of fireman content it's really cool go back to the gloom
fine here you go you know how my twitter banner is just this so change it to just this
it's good stuff though fireman and then we have the rat knight uh is that shovel knight
that's shovel knight armor it's good shit though it's just it's just a rat it's just it's rat
it's rat knight or it's rat man that's rocket knight no okay every knight is shovel knight
yeah just like how every game is dark souls i love it though i love these shoes i love the
the boots he's ratting us out good shit uh this is the one of the most recent ones this is from
the numbers going upstream last night um and the joe there's a joke here i'm sure you can figure
it out uh the actual one of the people that worked on the game made this we showed it last
night but i want to show it again uh viewers going down yeah don't matter dev in chat no actually
actually yes but yeah that's good shit thank you for that this also happened last night this
actually hurts i can't look this hurts my head birthday shito i forgot we did this shit weird
stream no emotion this is like the vacuum cleaners like oh okay the shito birthday shito
you know i need to make like i need to have like one of these be like an actual emote
and that is it that's the last of the artwork or the the drawn or written content good stuff
there were a lot of them they were very very good and we have a lot more to see if you put
something this is by the way this is as of last night so this is as of like yesterday so anything
that was put in there yesterday after i essentially went to bed is not in this stream whatever we
stop at at that point going forward is where i pull from so uh nerd neck give me one second
uh that took about two hours all right that's good to know that's good it took about like an
hour and 45 minutes or so where do you do this in the discord there is a public community discord
there is a channel called community content nights you put it there this could be there
are rules there you got to follow those rules it could be a video content it could be um
photoshopped content it could be original artwork as long as it's put there i will i will go through
that and that's where i pull it through so we're going to move on to the video portion of the
stream it should be probably another couple hours or so i would assume uh and there's deep fakes
in there well you could but that's fine just this rule just as long as you follow the rules
you're going to be fine so give me one second as i switch to the video portion let me just do this
real quick i want to make sure i can actually get it on here and maybe because this is probably
like this is probably just about halfway point maybe just take a little pee break what do you
think yeah because we're gonna be here for a little while longer yeah let's go pee well let
let i mean like just go pee i'll be back i'll be back in like fucking two minutes three minutes
hello i'm back so we have oh boy we have like we got a lot of videos so we gotta get this started
we're gonna open it with something not that with that take a look at those tabs up there
there's a lot actually let me go like this make this look a little cleaner like this a little
bigger all right using chrome this is chrome i'm glad you picked up on that all right this one's
called germa jam is it the same shirt no it's a nice gray shirt though i approve he's not using
edge it's all right all right we're gonna have to play with the audio on this one because i don't
know how loud it's gonna be but we'll see here we go let's go germa jam germa jam why was i in the
car oh that was the sound wait is that that's me turning the wheel oh that's fucking that's
banging seven hundred seven hundred and fifty people are now subscribing to the channel
i have nothing to say besides thank you so much germa here for the two thousand subscriber
extraordinary thank you all so so much for subscribing to the channel you playing the
piano i really do appreciate the four thousand let's keep rolling everybody the view to the
big number
huge thank you so much for 20 000 subscribers i'm saying that but thank you this is good shit
oh you actually got the qrs let me know if you want to help in ml studio if you happen to help
hell yeah that was fucking awesome all right uh i want i want to hit the qrs one more time that
was a that was awesome the best part about that is you can hear you can hear me very clearly
hitting the wall where i'm actually capable it's like when you get to a certain point when you
when you sing and you hit the absolute i cannot do this but i'm going to try anyways that's how
you get like the like now i know my a you can't like go any higher there's no going over that
but you still try and it ends up sounding like a horn that is too much air coming out of
i got a fear yeah exactly uh you're not here here's the link those of you that are looking
for the link it's control c right control c is copy there it is all right so uh that was that that
was uh germa jam it's really good shit good job are you serious i don't i don't i do but i i just
told you it was control c anyway let's keep going there's more to do here we go ready actually
hold on let me do this make this a little bigger that means i can hold on hold on hold on hold on
i don't want to screw this up hold on hold on hold on that's better way better way better all
right uh the next one is called uh this is called blend j okay five two five one three
a huge door bullshit it's worth blend below average
five eight is male height an average male i'm average
that was very very smooth five for ten is average in the u.s sorry jeremy you're
no
hey you guys don't know what it's like to be sure i take a shower and i'm out of the
shower and i'm looking at myself squeezing my like butt cheeks together i don't
what the fuck is happening
oh by the way i'm not like five eight i'm not i'm five feet tall you're fucking tiny germa
coffee chicken right here of course i do i'm like five two that stack is taller than me
her was fucking tiny
oh yeah i'm not that short i brought it i'm
oh no i'm like five feet tall
i was crouching down
down her was fucking tiny i'm freaking dull
i was fucking insane i'm not five feet i'm five feet tall oh that was fucking insanity
i'm one more one more time what the fuck happened that was too much stimulation at once
huge door bullshit it's worth blend below average
coffee
five eight is male height an average male i'm an average yeah i'm intact that was very very
smooth five foot ten is average in the u.s sorry jeremy you're no i'm not that short i draw this
cheese i'm like five two i wasn't talking about the u.s i was talking about it's worth blend
you guys don't know what it's like to be sure i take a shower and i'm out of the shower i'm looking
at myself squeezing my like butt cheeks together i go you're fucking tiny
oh by the way i'm not like five eight i'm not tiny i'm five feet tall you're a fucking tiny
of course i do i'm like five two
is
i wasn't talking about
i was like crouching down
Herb is fucking tiny.
She wants me chicken.
I'm three feet tall.
The cor- the correcting.
The correcting.
Somebody wrote in the chat, you've said too many things.
Yeah, that's what I'm talking about.
That is exactly what I'm talking about.
I've said too many words.
Correcting, like how fucking neurotic.
Correcting yourself over and over again.
I'm not five, I'm five feet tall.
I'm fi- I'm not five eight.
I'm five two.
Like how many times have I said these words?
Just fighting internally, like panicking, correcting myself over and over again.
That was fucking hysterical.
Jesus.
What a- what a show.
See we got a link.
Somebody already linked it.
That was called Blend J.
Yeah, it's in the chat right now.
There it is.
Jesus.
Alright, we gotta move on.
The next one is called...
I don't know, we'll find out in a second.
It's called Jerma vs Mika.
Jerma Fighter V.
V.
Here we go.
Ow, my butthole.
Life is pain.
I can't.
Turn your lights in your house off too.
No.
Oh, I'm just gonna fi- I'm gonna face this way.
I'm gonna watch it on the big screen over here.
So that I can watch it with you guys and not like over here.
God, that's fucking hysterical.
I've said too many words.
Alright, coming up next is...
This is gonna be interesting.
This is Get Out Of Town Shot For Shot Remake.
Side by side comparison video.
I don't know how you make this video.
Okay, here we go.
Get Out Of Town.
You didn't actually do this whole thing.
Wait, don't I like strip?
Do you have to do all the movement?
Please don't.
I can't.
This is supposed to have taken you a long time to do this.
It's all my fault.
Neck breaking.
Why would you make this?
It is the same.
The same.
It is actually the same video.
Even the looking back and forth.
He's like...
Oh, he's autoplaying.
SNL.
I can watch this part here.
The most unbelievable part to me is...
Watch the comparison video.
Watch the actual video.
The left and right look right here.
Here it comes.
You had to have studied this for like 12 hours to do that.
That was fucking insane.
Good acting all around.
A 12 hour stream.
Holy shit.
That was called Get Out Of Town Side By Side Comparison.
Yeah, I've got to link these.
Oh no, we already got it, right?
Somebody just spam them.
Just link them when they're done.
Just because I don't have to fucking...
I don't have to do it.
He's an egomaniac.
This is warm now.
That's not even a link.
Alright, I'm just going to do it.
Somebody got it.
My stomach hurts from laughing.
We're just getting started, by the way.
Give them a like.
I'm not even logged in.
This is my Chrome account.
I'm not logged in.
You do it.
Fucking unbelievable.
You guys just keep getting better.
That's the scary thing.
You know what I mean?
You guys just continue to get better at doing this shit.
Let's keep going.
This is called Leaked Trailer For Alien Compact Isolation 2.
If you're ready, let's kick it off
and to get an update from our friends
at one of the most celebrated development studios
in the world, Bethesda Game Studios.
Please welcome Studio Head
and my good friend, Todd Howard.
Are there any gamers in here?
Of course there is.
We've got quite a lineup this year.
Last year we saw some of the best games
highly reviewed that we've ever had as a company here.
And we have you all to thank.
Our average Metacritic score reached over 58.
And I find it completely necessary
to now show you, the fans,
a brand new experience
that you won't have anywhere else.
World Premiere.
Nobody fucking knew.
I need to pause it.
Wait, wait, wait.
I need to pause it for one second.
I think this is like the first or second time
anyone has ever used this footage.
Nobody used that
because it has no context for anything.
The socks, the white socks.
Now show you, the fans,
a brand new experience
that you won't have anywhere else.
World Premiere.
So I guess you need to explore in this game.
There was a crash. Oh no.
Investigate the mystery of the crash.
Which is what I plan on doing.
Let's go ahead and go...
Oh fuck.
That's him.
Can I get away without him seeing?
That's the main thing that's got to be...
No, no, he's right behind me.
Oh my god, oh my god, oh my god.
If I can make it up these stairs, please.
It's an alien.
It's a fucking alien.
Where is he? Where'd he go?
The doors are all locked.
I'm trapped in this spooky game.
What do I do?
Oh, I guess I could climb in here.
It's an old video.
Turn my flashlight on.
An achievement. Nice.
You know, I love getting achievements.
Especially when...
There he is. There he is again.
He's in the vent.
He's in the vent. He's in the vent.
Get out of the vent.
Out of the vent. Down the stairs.
Through the metal detectors.
Hopefully I don't have any weapons.
Okay, go, go, go, go, go, go, go.
Straight down, straight down, straight down the stairs.
Come on, come on, come on, come on.
I know you can hide.
Hide in here.
Open it.
Okay.
Shh, quiet in here.
I don't want to...
If I make any noise, I'm going to be in a lot of trouble.
God, there he is.
Please don't come in here and kill me.
What the fuck is he doing?
That's psycho.
What is it?
Do you eat ass?
Oh, that's the archive.
If you're ready, let's do the...
I was going to say this one more time.
Are there any gamers in here?
Of course there is.
That's my favorite part.
Oh.
That was a leaked trailer for Alien Compact Isolation 2.
It's just me.
Okay.
We need a link for that one.
All right.
I'll get you a link.
I'm going to be lightheaded by the end of this stream, I swear.
I don't want you to see how many videos are left, though.
You know what I mean?
I don't want you to see how many videos are left.
That spoils everything.
All right.
So this next one is...
This is German95GermAnimatedFanArt.
This is actually ridiculous.
You guys ready for this?
It's a very short video, but check this out.
That's like Slimer from Ghostbusters.
That's a real 3D shit.
It's really impressive.
I like the lighting inside the mouth.
Look at that.
Let's do it one more time.
The tongue coming out of the mouth.
What made the Simpsons writing...
I don't know.
What made the Simpsons writing so special?
Maybe you'll find out one day.
Here's a link to that one.
It's called the German95GermAnimatedFanArt.
Here it is.
Yeah, take a look at the top.
Actually, you can't even see the top.
Oh, fuck yeah.
There is it.
I'm not going to...
No, we have like 40 videos to watch.
I'm not watching a Simpsons breakdown
of why the writing degraded after season four.
You could put that on a playlist
and listen to it in your car.
All right.
Let's keep going.
Coming up next is Germa and the...
This is a Dreams level.
I think we've already seen this,
but I want to show it one more time
because it's crazy.
This is Germa and the Bee from Dreams.
A game that I abandoned
because I was not good at it.
Turned up.
Guide the bee to Germa's iced coffee
within 30 seconds.
Are you serious?
Holy shit, there's a bee in here.
Star Wars.
I didn't even pick up.
The Star Wars is just text floating in front of me.
That's so funny.
You can't get it on a shirt.
Bumping into stuff?
What's...
Who's up in smoke?
You see that?
Look at these pogchamps.
Oh, he's dead.
What?
Are you serious?
Holy shit, there's a bee in here.
Oh, fuck me.
Goodbye.
Something about a bee,
it's just...
It's always scary.
Always.
And I know, save the bees.
The bees are so important to us.
But they're terrifying
just because you know what they're capable of.
The running animation is just like...
Do you win?
Do you beat it?
Get in that iced coffee.
Let's go.
Nice.
What's in the trash can?
Wait, that's not...
Wait, that's the coffee cup.
Oh, that's the cup.
Right, okay.
Stupid.
Idiot.
Moron.
Dumb.
Pathetic.
Okay, let's keep going.
That was Germa and the Bee.
Let's get you a link.
Very, very good shit so far.
What do we got next?
This is Germamari Damacy.
Apparently it's from an old advertisement for Katamari.
Let's find out.
Where is it?
Where's my guy?
There he is, right there.
Get back!
Come here!
They dropped it!
Get out of the fucking way!
I'm in the middle of a check...
That's all I hear.
Shut up.
Get in your car.
What?
What is that?
I think I was going to catch it.
Hey, that's right.
Really?
Are you serious?
Shit, it worked.
Go fuck yourself.
What's up, man?
I'm in the middle of a cha-
That's all I hear.
Shut up.
Get in your car.
That's fucking funny.
Why am I so mean?
I'm not.
I'm just...
This is the Katamari guy.
That's not me.
That was fucking fantastic.
Here it is.
What's next?
Another one of these.
Suck a fart out of my ass.
Alright, that was that one.
It's called S stands for...
Suck a fart out of my ass.
Do you want me to even link this one?
There you go.
This is the Life and Times of German985.
Based on the DOS Alter Ego stream.
Oh, this is my entire life.
Is this me reaching out to my old self?
That's me.
I mean, that is me.
What happened in this stream?
What the fuck is this?
Was this part of the stream?
He forgot...
Oh, right, right.
It's me on the bench.
Why?
I had a heart attack on the baseball field and died.
I remember.
Thanks for watching.
That was the Life and Times of German985 from the DOS stream Alter Ego.
Sometimes I forget all this shit and it's instantly reminding me.
He got old real quick.
Yeah.
34.
I look like fucking 80.
What's next?
Alright, let's keep going.
This is Vine Wrestle, a German story.
Alright.
Welcome, ladies and gentlemen, to Vine Wrestle.
If this is your first Vine Wrestle, it is the sauciest wrestle event you'll ever see.
It's Joel.
Dookie Nookie, Dick Hickam.
It's time to chew ass, and I'm all out of ass.
It'll be real good.
It's been a long-awaited Vine Wrestle.
It's a sacred Vine Wrestle community event.
I invaded.
And you bet.
It's going to get real exciting.
Lots of new exciting things happening this year.
Before we do that.
Be a part of this wrestling event.
Because I'm Mr. Wrestling Event.
That's right.
German Rumble.
German Rumble 2.
German Rumble 3.
German Rumble Life.
German Rumble Rumble House.
The Sims one.
Nobody really liked that one.
I did.
But that's five.
I got six somewhere, too.
I do.
Somewhere.
Stop moving.
Stop the moves.
This is important stuff.
Boom.
I did everything possible.
I just wanted to come in and prove to the world that I had an enemy to do it.
I really didn't.
I really did not mean to do that.
Listen.
How do you think I'm going to get out too when you're gone?
Take me for everything.
Me out of my own.
It is time to hit the road.
Oh, the F.A.W.D.
The F.A.W.D.
Belt was fake.
Hang up on him.
Hold on.
Wait.
Hang up on him.
You can hear the Super Mario RPG music in the background.
Listen.
Yeah.
Those of you that don't know, on the Vine Wrestle, I invaded.
I was not supposed to.
I really didn't want to win.
I just kept winning.
I just kept winning no matter what they threw at me.
I won every single time with a fake belt, though.
I should have known.
It looked a little weird.
He told me it was official, but you know, crayon.
It was just red crayon on the belt.
I just thought that's what they did there.
I was like, oh, this is like a joke.
They do like, it's a funny joke belt.
Maybe we'll see it again.
Maybe we'll see you next time.
Maybe.
We'll find out.
But that was Vine Wrestle.
It was a great event.
I was absolutely thrilled to be a part of it.
And I fucking won.
This guy.
I won.
Let's get you the link to that one.
Look at me.
It actually was a true look at me moment without a single doubt in my mind.
Coming up next.
This is called, Jerma Gets Back in Shape.
I'm looking forward to this one.
I want to see how I do it.
Do two headphones in for this one.
Come on.
What am I thinking?
How long is this video?
Do you want to send a car song?
I don't either.
Let's get it started right here.
Preview.
This is really coffee?
Jesus.
That's so loud.
I almost just ripped my pants.
Me too.
I was supposed to rip it out.
Holy shit.
I thought you were in jeans.
To the gym.
Jerma saves the galaxy.
What the fuck is this?
The time has come.
Wait.
Hold on.
Have you ever seen any Marvel movies?
Don't watch.
I don't know what this is.
There is a Marvel movie in here.
Somebody gets injured.
Somebody might get hurt.
Somebody might die.
But I don't know.
Oh, wait.
This is like a Disney movie.
Let's just get to the part where I'm in it.
This is a spoiler.
If you don't want to see Marvel movie spoilers, close your eyes and block your ears for 30
seconds starting now.
Do it now.
Now.
I just ripped my pants.
We don't need to watch anymore at this point.
I can't do it anymore.
Hey.
It's.
Tim.
Oh my god.
It's good to see you.
Thanks, man.
Yeah.
It's great to see you again.
What are you doing?
Hey.
Somebody keep track of my hands.
Get out of this.
There's an extra one for you.
I don't know.
I'm not even going to link you on that one.
You'll find it somehow.
What I'm next is I think we've seen this is called Jerma and the Dark Guy.
I walk out the door and there's just the there's the dark guy and he's just lined up the shot
and you're like, OK, go ahead.
And he's just like, hold on.
By the way, this happens like two or three times a week.
After a year, you're going to like kick out of the dark.
Jesus Christ.
That was loud.
You're going to be like, don't fucking get.
Don't come in my house ever again.
He's going to look at you like, what?
Don't don't leave.
Don't ever come back.
Get the fuck out of my house.
And he'll just be like, well, this bag like his bag of fucking darts on his back.
OK.
Bye.
You'll never see me again.
And you're like, yeah, get the fuck out of here, dark asshole.
The door closes and he's gone.
By the way, two months later, a dart hits your like window and you look out, you're
like that motherfucker.
And he's just like.
And he fucking runs away.
What the hell was I talking about?
I don't know.
I can't I cannot tell you what that I can't bring anything out of that for you.
Just there was a guy that throws darts at you.
Just watch out.
Didn't get rid of him.
He's in your house.
I don't know why there's a guy throwing darts in your house or what that's alluding to.
But here's the link.
It was a metaphor for Cox.
Oh, I see.
OK.
That makes sense.
What does it?
Probably not.
All right, let's go.
This next one is, oh, we got a chair, chairs, bizarre adventure, golden stream streaming
gold.
I think this is like a season five opener or something.
This is like late season Jojo's Bizarre Adventure.
I think opening.
So if you've never just whatever, it's not what I don't at this point, I'm just going
to press play.
You know what's about to happen.
So do what you need to do.
One guy.
Looking out for you.
Really.
That fucking hat is so bad.
I've got to get in front of that square and get away from it.
One guy.
I don't usually when I see an image of myself, I know where it's from.
Sort of.
I don't know where that's from.
It was Jared Jared's Bizarre Adventure Golden Stream.
Here you go.
Why do you love watching yourself so much?
I don't.
I love watching other people create scenarios around things I've done.
It's fucking wonderful.
He's an egomaniac.
He's a narcissist.
Don't ever trust this guy.
Don't ever trust him.
All right, let's go.
This one's called the cool guy contest.
This is the cool guy contest.
Alien.
Contest.
Have you seen this?
One day, fast German alien were walking to get burgers.
What game is this taken from?
Cool guy.
That's insane.
Right there.
Can you see?
I can't even hear it.
Yeah.
Yes.
That's it.
Purple alien says he's going to win.
You got something to say?
Say it again.
I want to win.
He's gone.
Who do you think will win?
Enough fooling around.
The contest is starting.
Calculating.
Who the fuck are these two?
Fever.
Steve.
Fast German.
Purple alien.
Frosty.
Frosty wins the cool guy contest.
This is terrible.
Absolutely terrible.
It appears as though they have misunderstood the contest.
That was fucking wild.
That was a dream.
That was, that was perfect.
That should be a children's TV show.
Think about it.
Maybe.
We got a lot more to do.
You thought, yeah, this is a good indicator.
This is about three hours.
There's much more to see.
You guys have just absolutely knocked it out of the park.
That's why I want to do, I want to do the green screen again.
Because I feel like so much interesting shit comes out of these green screen videos.
And when we did the first one, it was like, oh, that was cool.
Do it again.
Yeah, I guess I was only going to do it that one time, but I guess we'll do it again.
And the encore happened recently and it was awesome.
And then people are still making these things.
So why not do like another seven hours in front of a green screen and put on more costumes and stuff and give you guys more material?
Just keep adding more material.
Maybe.
It seems like you guys have a lot of fun with this and they're really, really fun to watch on stream.
Maybe I'll get back in that studio and do it again.
Making an entire cinematic universe.
Yeah.
Something to think about.
But let's see.
Did I link that?
I did, I think.
Did I link it?
Just in case I didn't.
The JCU.
Just random clips of me puking, pretending to rip my pants and punching the air.
What a cinematic universe that is.
Let's go.
This is called Alex Jones spots a liberal.
What the fuck.
Here you go.
There it was.
Look at me.
Coming up next.
Next is Jerma Shortking. I'm going with that height theme on today's stream.
Shortking. Why does a scale say 5'1"? A scale does not tell you how tall you are, it tells
you how much you weigh. That's why it's called a scale.
I'm five foot something but my bills all pay. All my tippy toes from L.A. to the bay.
Going off the deep end, chill in the shallow. You don't need your heels girl, just bring
a towel. I'm five foot something and I'm royalty. Short King Mama A. I'm five foot something
and I'm royalty. Short King Mama A. They know my speed, it's all the ride. I'm a fun size
super nice guy. I'm five foot something and I'm royalty. Short King Mama A. Short A. I'm
five foot something. This is not a real picture. This is a real picture. That's a real picture.
Not a real picture. It was a real picture. Not a real picture. I'm not linking that one. That was
fun. I think that's 5,000 views. That's 5,000 views? How? Didn't, did you just, did you, you did,
how long has this video existed? Did you, was this like, submitted like today? Like 10, like a week
ago? That's like, that's pretty good for being live for, it's been a month, never mind. It was
uploaded a month ago, a month and a half ago. Optimization. That's not gonna have a million
views in a couple months. This is called Top Streamer. What did it say?
Jeremy eats ass? Tonight, Jeremy eat ass. And then the snort. I feel like this is what a lot of
people use for their I'm starting stream soon stuff. Like I'm going live. Here we go. Stream
starting soon. And then it like loops like four or five times. Tonight, Jeremy eats ass.
That fucking snort. Seriously. You do something on camera that you just, the second that you do it,
you know, uh, here's the link. Uh, this one's called, this streamer is bleeped. This streamer is
fucked. It's bleeped though. Here we go. Oh, you motherfucker. You motherfucker.
It's a lot of editing. Oh, this is the best part. The plus like, if you enjoyed the video with the
smiley face. Where is it? Where is the press like if you liked the video?
That's authentic. That's authentic old YouTuber. Where is it?
There it is. Plus like, if you enjoy the video. Oh, right. Like video, right?
That's on my first like 150 videos. This is crazy. All right. Let's get you linked to this one too.
Get away from that one now. Uh, this is called Jerma tells chat how to puke on a ride. Source
filmmaker. Okay. Let's hear it. Guys, if you're going to throw up on a ride, don't be the dick.
Like you're throwing up, right? So try to do just, you're going to, your day is going to be fucked
up after that. Anyways, grab your shirt, lift it up, tilt it. So it makes a big cup and just
puke into your shirt down. Don't ruin somebody else's vacation. Just, yeah, just underwear.
It's true. Just imagine seeing somebody go, oh no, like pulling their pants and just
puke. That would be the funniest thing I've ever seen in my life.
I would never get over it. Ever. That would be the only thing I could think of for the rest of my life.
I'm okay. I'm thinking right now as if I've seen this, I've never seen this, but I'm laughing
because of it. Now I'm laughing after that. This didn't happen. Guys, but it's true though.
That you see, if you puke forward, if you are on a roller coaster and you puke forward,
it's going to spray and hit everybody. Not just one person's vacation. How many people can go on
a ride on a roller coaster or a spinning ride? I don't know, like 25. You have, he's doing it again.
I'm doing it again. Did I do this already? If you're going to throw up on a ride, but if you
throw up on a ride, there's 25 different people. You don't want to fuck up somebody else's vacation,
especially you have to throw up into your shirt. There's a big cup that you can make and you can
puke into your shirt. Don't ruin somebody else's vacation. Don't be the dick that you are throwing
up. So grab your shirt, lift it up, tilt it so it makes a big cup, and then just puke into your
shirt. Down. Don't ruin somebody else's vacation. Just puke into your underwear.
Did I get it? That's really fucking good though. Nice work. He's got the same shirt on. I tell
you, I wear the same clothes every fucking day. Well, not the same ones, the same types of clothing.
Blue. Black pants. Navy sneakers. Black shirt. Jeans. Sneakers. Black socks. Shoes. I don't know.
Every day I wear clothes. This is called German 985 egg. YTPMV? YTPMV. Oh, it's the egg. Of course
it is. We all love eggs. I was trying to be healthy. What song is this? Wait. This is from Donkey Kong.
The egg. I can't take it anymore. I cracked an egg in his mouth. What's German walk? Yeah,
I like cracked an egg in his mouth and it like revived him. 2012 YouTube was weird.
What the fuck is happening? Was I making these noises? I don't remember doing that.
Loud. This is gonna be loud. Very loud. Play it. I don't want it to be loud. I made it like
lower the volume. Look at that Kramer. Look at that Kramer. That's a perfect Kramer impression
right there. This isn't even part of the playlist. Why is it so laggy? I'm not, I'm not pausing it.
No, we're not just gonna play other videos. I paused it once. All right, I'm unpaused. My hands
are in the air. I'll prove it. Just want to make sure. All right, there you go. That's not me doing
that. I paused. We've seen the video five times. All right, let's go. This is called We Got Him. We
Got Him. I'll let you, I won't move. It'll hit me right in the face. It'll hit me directly in the face.
I don't care. Do it. You want to make that joke so bad.
Nice job. Nice work. Take a look at that hat. This hat is not made out of a hat material.
Same thing with this vest. Direct hit him. It's a critical hit. Yeah, that's a crit.
Surprised I was still standing after that one. That's We Got Him. The hat's made out of skin.
Okay, here we go. Coming up next is Jerma Scream Simulator. This, this video,
I'm looking at it now, is two hours long. It's a two fucking hour long video. Well, we're not gonna,
we're not gonna watch the full two hours of this. This person made the, okay, so the context here
is, remember when I talked about if you were just screaming, you turned on a live stream and it was
just you screaming the full blast for like three or four hours and you just looped it and put it
and made it, you didn't have a start, you didn't have an end, it just started and ended. This
person did it. This is my me yelling. Why did I think it was gonna be different? Faster. Faster.
That didn't do anything. Slower. This is an electric razor. Adventure MF Dan just gave five
subs. I'm not laughing at that. I'm laughing at what somebody said. Don't laugh for two minutes.
We're not doing that shit again. I can't, I'm not gonna sit here and do that again. No, no, no, no.
What have I done? What's going on? Why is this about an hour and 42 minutes?
It's up and...
This is just a drunk guy. This is a drunk guy at a party like,
don't look at how much better I look with my glasses up.
Do you think I look better with them up or down?
Yeah, like I got glasses, but I don't need them. I'm gonna put them up there
just in case you need to read something.
What's that? Like your number and then...
Okay, we're gonna keep going. Oh god, my stomach. Now fix the speed.
This is a different guard. So, um, hey, I'm a fucking secret agent.
What about up here? Look at how much more attractive I am when they're up there.
Now this is, you're on drugs. You're not, now you're not drinking. You're just on drugs.
Something, what, something very quick. Something very too much.
What about up here? Look at how much more attractive I am when they're up there.
Yeah, like I got glasses, but I don't really need them. I'm just gonna put them up there
just in case you need to read something. Like your number.
All right, I'm fucking out of here. That was fucked.
This next one's called Germ of the Acrobat. Germ of the Acrobat.
And we're gonna put this back to, uh, to normal, which it is. Good.
Not a big deal.
I just want to hear that. Do you eat ass? Yes.
Deep fake. They're everywhere now. You can't escape them. I said no, by the way.
Okay, moving on. This one's called, uh, it's a trailer. Murder on Main Street.
I guess this was a movie. Was it? Wait, hold on. Was this a movie? It is now.
No. There's your tree. Merry Christmas. There it is.
Get bent. Speaking of getting bent, I got a two by four here. Why don't we have a little fun, huh?
Santa! With a fucking two by four? Is that what you want to see?
So hey, Merry fucking Christmas, everybody. Fuck out of here, Santa!
We went to Black Sea.
Ladies and gentlemen, we have a breaking story tonight. The UN implanted the were in Santa,
and is he still alive chip back in the late 80s? This is terrible, truly terrible. I hope they
throw the book at whoever it was that did this. The crime you see now, it's hard to even take.
Spoilers for a movie. It's major. It's not that I'm afraid of it. I always knew you had to be
willing to die to even do this job, but I don't want to push my- Spoilers for the noooo country
for old men. Chips forward and go out and meet something I don't understand. He'll have to put
his soul at hazard. Did you have to say okay? No country for old lambs. Because I killed Santa.
To count one and two. I look like Jerry Garcia.
What's the number one thing people do? The real court? Punch him, punch him, punch Santa.
What are these movies? How many movies do you have? I didn't do that. That was peaceful.
What is it?
Which would be worse? To live is a monster. To die is a good man.
There's a bunch of movies.
There was a spoiler for like 10 movies. Don't watch it. That was Murder on Main Street.
Vaught is now in pieces. No, you can watch. Can you not watch trailers on Twitch? Spoiler
for the OJ trial. You've never seen the OJ trial. Spoilers. This is called Bring Me to Germo.
You guys, you guys might be too young. Every single person learned how to do the
Dun Dun Dun Dun Dun. It's true. It's true. I just stopped playing like a fucking evidence.
Do you eat ass? Don't say yes. Do I eat ass? No. Do you eat ass? Of course I do! Eating
ass enough for that don't worry eating ass no bad idea that's like not even
funny if sans was in smash brothers but he was a hundred and fifty dollars
goodbye my eye doesn't look like that hold on I want to what what the fuck is
this from this what is this from no no no I'm talking about like me I don't
think that is that from the green screen it's oblivion when was I what was I like
a button-up shirt I don't remember being in these clothes why was I in a button-up
shirt that was at a dinner party oh I have no idea
no at the family dinner I was wearing blue I had a nice blue gray black look
it up trust me go look at it here's this one I will get into the last quadrant
here of submissions another five to ten give or take this is called reality
unfolds around man crying to farting and screaming no no no I'm fucking crying
god damn it you're killing me you can hear it you got you listen you can hear
it in the ears that's how loud this shit was listen closely I've seen this image
before this has been linked to me like a shitload of times this I've seen that a
lot please I don't want to listen anymore I'm sorry I'm sorry you I don't
even gonna link that one yeah I do I gotta link them all reality unfolds okay
now go here this is called German lied about ace attorney I've proven that I
have not lied about ace attorney I just didn't want to play let's see what this
I let's see what they had what they're gonna bring to court here
your clients stated on screen that he would play ace attorney trilogy soon
as of October 2019 this still has yet to happen
furthermore your client has known history of making promises he can't keep
and lying about them when pressed face it right
German lied about Minecraft VR German lied about Taco Bell German lied about
ace attorney oh this is bad is it possible to prove that
German is an honest man with polygraph take a look at this your honor what is
this these would be the results from the polygraph test my client took could you
read the results to the court your honor why he's incredibly honest somebody
can say he's the most transparent streamer on switch that wasn't even a
real doctor he was clearly a hired actor doesn't matter if the doctor was an
actor the polygraph machine was real the polygraph machine was a cheap laptop
from the right of the stuff in Best Buy one month in the electric
one full month guilty guilty here's the thing though I wasn't asked about ace
attorney on the polygraph so the polygraph would not be admissible in
court if you want to know if I eat ass or not maybe you could bring that to
court great here's a link we got four more videos actually six seven more
videos and then we have a couple songs to just chill out too let's go this is
2015 German versus 2019 German let's see who wins oh you oh you I saved the best
for you I kicked his ass I kicked the shit out of you oh you oh you I saved
the best for you didn't even need to try the problem is you what's that in the
bottom right so the problem is in 2015 that was a PSI camera which is like like
140p 2019 German was in front of a 1080p camera that's the issue if you ever if
you've been tracked correctly 2015 Jeremy may stood a chance but I guess not
why are they fighting and I have a confession to make these next few
videos I just I saw one and I had to get the other two that are like my
favorites in that same series these are not submitted this one was but the next
two were not they're just like my favorite videos in that same realm of
series okay let's let's show the one that was submitted recently I love these
so much Red Sox are winners!
Manny Ramirez with an absolute rocket into the Boston night and the Red Sox lead the series two games to none
that's it the Red Sox has looked for all night okay so that's that one so here's
another one there's a few of these and the I love them so we have to watch them
all I don't care
okay cool this one's my favorite I love this video so much this is like I came
on top of like my favorite videos on YouTube this is like in the top ten to
Lewicki a couple of doubles last night he's hit in ten straight
who is Alex Chapel let's check in right now Alex Corbin on the mound and they
will be facing Walker Buehler
a perfect run for baseball
Claus-Angelo's in the net
an average fastball velocity for him
two balls and two strikes here it comes
and he got him just as he said he would
with a pitch of the runners
on down
wait hold on what's playing in the background?
what's playing in the background?
stole 15 the Nats hoped he would be
second time we've seen Buehler spike one about 53 feet
why am I?
comes to the plate rounded softly to second
two up and two down
oh this is a baseball game playing
is this a baseball game?
by 21 games
I'd rather be in that position than be the team to home plate umpire
great
okay anyways I love the I catch it
first of all the shush
it's just I fuck I love it
to Lewicki a couple of doubles last night
you're in a baseball you're a pitcher in a baseball game
what are you talking about?
he's hitting 10 straight
look at me
this is the best part though
this is the only place that somebody used this
the only spot that somebody used this clip was right here
fucking fantastic
it's a fucking soaring home run
this would go into the ground
directly into the fucking ground
you guys are fucking hilarious
fucking hilarious
god damn
dark man too that's right
you know you better believe
when I do this in front of the screen again
you're gonna get so many more sports clips
I'm gonna do like an hour of sports clips
like throwing footballs
like tagging people out and shit
like I wanna be in a whole fucking goddamn
I wanna be the super bowl
so that's it for the video
well no no no that's not true
incorrect I just made an incorrect statement
anyways coming up we have
we have a twitter video
twitter video I couldn't figure out how to get to work
but I'm just gonna try
so here's the twitter video
it's from obviously google the gareth
and this thing has been auto playing
for the last three and a half hours
so here we go
let's see if I can get this to be full screened
I can
okay so this is called
I don't know what this is called
it's a wine thing
how upset I am right now
I've missed the wine convention
by two hours
and I bought this special red wine suit
to prove how much I love wine
and now what am I supposed to do
throw it in the trash
this is a monster from monster hunter
I can't even put it in words
how upset I am right now
I've missed the wine convention
by two hours
and I bought this special red wine suit
to prove how much I love wine
and now what am I supposed to do
throw it in the trash
you just
you just animate
no, that was awesome
awesome awesome stuff
I don't know how some of you guys do it
alright the next two
are
they're not, I had to put them on my computer
so
google the gareth makes great fucking animations
of course, let's move on
this one is
I don't know, it's going to be a surprise for all of us
because I have no idea
this is from the same two dates
oh it's kim
the best part about this
is sincerely
that's like a whole tv show
but
those clips are taken over the course of like
four hours
looks like you got cancelled after one episode
like a real tv show
we lost the fucking license
not anymore
alright coming up next, this is the final video
of the
this family guy of course
I don't get this one
somebody's going to have to
I don't get this
is this supposed to be me?
by the way this is called germa chin
is this a chin joke?
oh
oh right okay
because somebody made me in family guy
creator dot com whatever
alright
that was that
and that is
the end of the videos
there was like an hour and 30 minutes of them
so now we're going to move on to the music
there's a couple of tracks that somebody gave
what a dumb video to go out on
we're not going out yet
the stream's not over yet
there's still a few more things to see
do the blend s one one more time
okay
yeah I mean that was un fucking
that was ridiculous I have to say it again you're right
yeah you're right you're right
which one was it it was right here
okay this is the final this is the encore for this one
I'm going off cam we want a full
view of it
five foot ten is average in the U.S.
sorry Jeremy you're a dwarf
I'm not that short I draw this
I'm like five foot
I wasn't talking about the U.S.
I was talking about the dwarf land
you guys don't know what it's like to be short
I take a shower and I'm out of the shower and I'm looking at myself
squeezing my like butt cheeks together
I go you're fucking tiny
fact cheating
cheating
I'm not tiny
I'm five feet tall you're fucking tiny
yeah
wait did he say five feet
ass
no I was like crouching
down you're fucking tiny
I'm three feet tall
did I say five feet
ass
no no did I
oh
that was fucking awesome
oh alright let's get to
the songs there are a few things here let's put the
camera back on let's get
this in a spot where
it needs to be so that
was kind of it in a way
I thought I knew it was going to take
somewhere from like three to four hours
that's kind of what I was planning
the length of this one oh yeah I did it earlier
but gotta do it again
this is just fucking this is art right now
so you could
judging by how long this took
you can expect them to all
sort of be this sort of similar length like a three to four
probably this would be about four hours
I would assume
this I could make the camera bigger
and we'll listen to this couple of music
tracks to listen to
don't fucking do that
some of you did
alright let's get the music on here
there are two tracks this is called
the only good joke is
the beginning okay
what do you mean by that though
the only good joke is in the beginning
let's see here it comes
alright
I see where you're going
Michael's mom
fucking Michael's mom
is pissed
here's the link to that one
did I lose connection to Twitch
how come I can't see
I guess I'm still here
there's that one
I'm still here
I guess I'm still here
there's that one and there's another one
this is called I made this with a clip of the labo
so this is a Nintendo labo song
both of these by the way made by the same person
let's check this one out
okay we're ready
didn't make this
that's pretty good
what's my soundcloud I don't have one
I just listen to other talented soundcloud artists
and go like this
nice
you should do one
that was pretty good
that was a nice beat
no emotion for two minutes
we did that yesterday
and I lost fucking 1500 viewers
those people are never coming back
alright that's the end of that
I have zero viewers now
shit
I don't want to be here anymore
but before we move on
I'm going to just hang up for a little bit
I want to tell you
that thank you
first of all for everybody that submitted everything
you guys are immensely talented
I am shocked every day
when new videos new artwork everything comes in
and this was number one
so I think
I think it was a success I think this is a cool idea
I think this is a better idea
than just showing this stuff
at the very end of a livestream
when the wind down happens
I think this is a much better idea
tons of great videos tons of great artwork
my body hurts from laughing at a few of those
and I'm in awe
at the sheer amount of talent some of you artists
can put forth onto a piece of paper
it's fucking incredible
so the next community
content night
is probably going to be
whenever there is about
fourish hours of content
I think that's a good
clean community night
so it's
when I announced that channel
about what like a month ago
that was like just about what thirty
thirty five days ago something like that
I would say probably like once every once a month
it'll probably happen and if there's not enough
for like to fill because I see how many tabs
here I'm going to see I'm going to count
how many videos there were how many pictures there were
to see how long it took to go through it
so you'll see
hopefully once a month if not that then every other month
we'll do like a just a night like this
so should be good
after this stream it'll be full in a week
then we'll have plenty of stuff to go
through so that should be good
who are you talking to we're not real
zero so wait what is going on
what is going on with twitch right now if I go
to twitch.tv does nobody have any viewers
is it zero viewers across the whole website
or is it just me everybody
uh oh uh oh
everybody has zero
viewers it's all been a lie
from the very beginning
it's all it's been a sham you're all
not real wake up
wake up wake up wake up wake up
wake up didn't work it's real
I knew it no I think that's um
I think that's a good cap
I think that's a good cap for the night
I could what time is it five thirty
four hours yeah
I think that's a good cap for the night
so I will see you guys I'm trying
to sleep over here baldo
no I'll see you guys um I'm not
I have to do some stuff
so the next time you see me will probably be
Monday Monday I have
I actually have I'm doing my
ultrasound on Monday so
I'll still be live on Monday
Monday after I go to the doctor's
appointment they need to
they need to look and look at my
they look at my gallbladder is what they do
my mother had her gallbladder removed
uh and so
I'm having like abdominal
problems and they think that
I might have to it might be that
I don't know we'll see
but uh I will stream after that
that's gonna happen earlier in the day
uh I don't think
I might have to stream later
around like three or four
just because I'll be there at the appointment
earlier in the afternoon
is your gallbladder a boy or a girl
but thank you again
for watching pretty good turnout
I'm glad everybody thought it was fun I did
I thought it was fucking hilarious and
uh awe inspiring
so my fucking gallbladder
we are gonna move
out to here does it work
does it work does it work I think so
and
one no no
no it's still me
why is it still me it shouldn't
be still me I thought I fixed
it fucking ego maniac
I know seriously
god damn it I had mine removed
it feels better but you have to be careful
with those cheeseburgies yeah I'll
do what you gotta do you know we're not even
100% sure that's what's going on but they just wanna
check it uh so this is not
legit so we're gonna take those off
I thought I fixed this
but yeah I'll see you guys on Monday
have a fantastic weekend let's go through the bits
thank you so much for participating
those of you that did and those of you that
watched thank you as well
let's do let's go back a few hours ago
just about four hours ago
I gotta figure out what I'm gonna do on Monday
there's a few games that I think I'd like to try
I don't know I have to I gotta see
please watch your step on the way up
cube world
somebody said it in the beginning somebody says it right now
alright so earlier
we had
what did we have
why is my computer going so slow
what the hell is going on okay this is weird
alright now I can see them
that took a while Twitch why are you so
messed up right now
hey thank you Jerma Stinky Feet for the 250
250 bits so of course I get to see
yesterday's stream but I have to work for
a good stream hey
you know what I don't care what anybody says
yeah I thought yesterday's stream
I had a ton of fun on yesterday's stream
I had a lot of fun
so it don't matter
thanks for the 250
hey Siku thanks for the
thousand bits thank you for the ten
dollars they say the carnival was awesome
thanks thank you
really appreciate that I'm glad you liked it
then we had iPod
Matt gave 250 bits
they say
I love images I love Jerma
I love chat I love iPod
I love Britney Spears I love
funny images I love burgers I love Jupiter's
I love a lot of things there used to be
a time when I was cold and afraid to love but you
and this whole community have helped me get a more
positive outlook on life
and I can never thank you all enough it's really
great to hear stuff like this is
just it's why I wanted to do more of these
types of things it's fun to collectively
come together and look
at stuff feels pretty good
I also love iPods
thank you though
I can't see the top donators yeah I know something
I don't know why
that's here but it is
I need to like
Streamlabs OBS has this
thing where it says
the sessions right
so I have for a source
it's the sessions top
subgifter doesn't that mean the stream
session so why does this
not work half the time
it doesn't make any sense is it not
pulling it from Twitch's end somehow but it's
a Streamlabs thing I don't know
maybe it's from the stuff from today
but it didn't work a few days ago either
Twitch has had zero viewers right now
somebody's panicking in that office
at the Twitch office
papers are flying around probably
like three people got fired
or something it's just like who did it
the alarms are going off
zero views
but thank you iPod Matt appreciate it
SFC 100 thanks
for the 500 bits pledging bits to your channel
Germa I tell you the exact amount
but I skipped Algebra 2 episode 4
I thought it was a clip show
Algebra 2 episode 4
that's perfect I love that
thank you KXE
gave 2500
bits a couple hours ago
thank you there's no
message just 2500 bits 25
dollars thank you
thank you thank you
he gave 5000 bits and said
this is basically Jex I said I was going to watch it later
so that's what we're going to do
maybe get it on screen
hi guys I thought it was
going to be a web browser
turns out it's not it's just me
and my fucking just candid
face
now you should see something on the screen
this is basically Jex
this is real this is dumped
alright that was the coolest Jimmy Neutron ever
it's supposed to be
John Travolta
somebody just said what an awful show
it's not it's not
Jimmy Neutron was great
what's wrong with Jimmy Neutron
that was a good show wasn't it
wasn't it was that was that a good show
wasn't it was it
hey Tar
Alakran thanks for the 700
bits
and your 36th
straight month as a sub
they actually stayed right here
Jerma it's my 36 month sub anniversary
this month you're an amazing streamer
thanks for all the fantastic content
the community you built here is truly one of the best
on Twitch and that's right chat
I love you guys
PS can you please upload a new badge
for 3 year subs so I don't get confused
with these worthless 2 year
pleb bandwagon sub losers
well
thank you
for the
700 bits and 33
years I really appreciate
that I'm gonna have a bunch of new
stuff put on the channel you'll
see some more stuff soon it's gonna get
weird am I gonna have to do 3
4 5 6 years 7 years
holy shit can you imagine that
I never thought anyone would stay sub for more
than 6 months let alone 3 plus years
so thank you
but yes you can expect there to be more
sub badges
soon
thanks a lot appreciate that
hey it's Garfield the Monday killer
thanks Garfield
can see you again thanks for the 250
glad you liked my Garf
my Garf collage collage
Jerma even if Garf doesn't do
Garfographs anymore you can count on
fun Garf content every community night stream
I still gotta hook you
in to join my new animated
movie you said you might
join I know just how the
scales I couldn't get it done for this stream but next
time you'll get an exclusive trailer and a real Garfield
face reveal don't
I already know what Garfield's face looks like
he's everywhere how's that for a Garfograph
can you tell Garfield the next community night stream
is so I have the trailer ready
probably I would say somewhere between 30
and 40 days from right now once a month
here's the thing with projects
I am currently
working on
2 at the moment right now
remember I told you guys before the carnival happened
that
there were going to be more of those
very very quickly so you can
expect that
every couple months every 2 or 3
months there's going to be something like
that on this channel not
carnivals just bigger
streams that I want to plan and
spend a lot of time on 2 of them
are already being worked on right now
one very much in particular is already
in the pre-planning stages
and is hopefully about 2 months away
maybe a little bit more depending on time
potentially really
exciting stuff in the future
we'll see
I'm just keeping my mind open
but look for the next community night
somewhere in November
like the first week of November maybe
something like that
thanks a lot Garfield
hey Appleship thanks for the 250 bits
hey man I'm so insanely happy that you like my drawings
they were awesome
thank you so much for the kind words I've got many more on the way
I hope to see them during the next community stream
very talented so
thank you so much
I missed these from before but I am
whizbang
gave 20 community subs
I am whiz thank you
20 subs
and then AdventureMFDamn we got you but you gave 5 community subs as well
thank you thank you thank you
it's a shit load of subs
it is a lot
appreciate every single one
I'd ever agree
for the 300 bits
Jeremy just want to say what's up
I finally got an interview for my first job and I'm super nervous
but I'm finally becoming a big boy
finally becoming a big boy
there you go congratulations
get that job
go for it don't be nervous
you're going to do just fine
good luck whatever it is hope you get it
you don't got to be nervous
remember this is something that you want
this is something you want to do
so grab it good luck though
I want to get a goose cab for the 250 bits
hey Jeremy I'm so glad you like my two home run videos
so much
I didn't even expect you to show the Ortiz Grand Slam again
but I'm glad you did
thanks for showing my content on stream
and I hope you continue streaming for a long time
they were great
they were fucking hilarious
absolutely
something about just super imposed on top of
Red Sox World Series wins
and playoff victories
it's just hilarious to me
so thank you
my pleasure
thank you for the 500 bits
you didn't read the short story I submitted for the community night
short story
because I was just pulling images out of here
was there text in here?
oh there is like there is something right here
let's have text to speech read this right now
join the discord if you're not
that's how you can submit things
this is a short story
I believe this is
this looks like an
oh this is a spoiler I don't want to read that
alright let's see
I'll turn the music off for this one
hold on this is going to be faster
that's good right there
soothing reply of Dr.
Nelson resisting the urge
to roll her eyes
she was a professional and she had seen
far stranger than this she kept
telling herself
she wasn't going to let someone like this
break her composure
Dr. Horowitz Saturday
silently staring across his desk
Saturday
Nelson and the patient
Jeremy as he had been introduced
well geez gosh
I mean the voices
Jeremy laughed, eyes bugging slightly
they're just voices
you know, a couple of them
not that big a deal
Jeremy has apparently experienced
over 11,000 voices
speaking to him at once
Jeremy winced as the words
left drive, Nelson's mouth
but drive, Horowitz
D-I-D-N-T react at first
11,000
yes sir
no, that's crazy
that's the sort of thing a crazy
person would say
I'm not crazy
Jeremy sit down
Jeremy hyperventilating a little
Saturday back down in the folding chair
tell me
Mr. Elbertson
what do these voices say
Jeremy remained silent
and eventually drive
Nelson spoke up
it depends sir, but they seem malevolent
malevolent
they encourage dangerous behavior
they award him points for it
points
when he hurts people, breaks things
makes good jokes, they give him points
and they take them away
for wholesome behavior and bad jokes
I see
do they do anything else
they like to
all at once, Jeremy leapt to his feet
clutching his head and screaming
will you all shut up
talking about my feet
shut the fuck up
get off this topic
no more feet
before either doctor could attempt to pacify him
the door to the office slammed open
and security guards charged in
to restrain the screaming man
stop saying it
the big punch line got cut off
here's the big punch
right here
why did this get cut off
as he was hauled away, drive
I'm sorry sir
both SCP-985
and its host can be rather unpredictable
there you go
SCP-985
there's your punch line there
alright, we're gonna do the credits
the actual credits are gonna be probably right in front of my face
how do we get them here, let's see
well, we can go like this
are they gonna be in front of me, or behind me
we'll find out
chat's the true monster
eh, debatable, I think that's debatable
alright, am I
I think in front of me, or behind me
let's find out
thanks everybody for your support on these streams
they're in front of me
all these people subbed today
during the stream, whether it was from
a community sub or not
or you just decided to stay subbed for 36 months
in a row
thank you, all of you
here you all are
hell yeah, thanks a lot
we do have a few more bits to do though
here, I'll put them on a different screen
we had
that was Dr. Zutsu by the way
thanks for the story, sorry I missed it
when I was pulling stuff out, I was just gonna go in line by line
videos and pictures
I didn't see it
I just kind of squirreled by it apparently
it was very very very
very creepy
and it was a little twisted
but thank you, and thanks for your 500 bits too
GTX 1080 quad SLI
gave 250 bits
they say
why don't you do more things with italics
we just did something like last week
which is a twitch con
but to answer that
a greater question there
I don't do very much collaborations anyways
I think
it's just me
organically if you want to do a video or a stream together
I don't
typically do
co-streams or multiplayer streams
sometimes, but for the most part
if it makes sense
then yeah
but
I typically just do my own thing
typically
and yes I have seen the birthday card, it was fucking incredibly wholesome
and wonderful, thank you
we went over it
I'm completely floored
that there's that many people that want to say
that fucking nice things about me
so, I really appreciate it
words seriously
cannot describe the feeling
when I look at stuff like that
but, no, to answer the larger question
like I said
I get questions a lot about
hey, you should play with Star some more
what about Kraken and italics
you should play with Vinny or Joel
it has to just sort of happen
it's not like
I don't typically go out of my way
to do much
multiplayer content with people
and that's sort of just
I've been doing that for the last
five years or so
kind of, you should play with Ninja
why did I even read that out loud
why did I read that
Vinny said you peed your pants and he doesn't
need that kind of attention
I did not pee my pants
the song makes me sad
why does the song make you sad
it still hasn't streamed with Joel
it just
it just has to happen, you know what I mean
well that's not true
that's not true
we did the whole fine wrestle
that was a whole thing
yeah of course it does
but I typically just kind of do my own thing
that's kind of the shrug
you have to take the initiative
but I kind of just do my own thing
and I just bump you
bump you in the face
that's a big gamer shrug
to be honest you're much better as a solo act
I don't
I don't know if I necessarily agree with that
but
I'm like at my most comfortable
when I can kind of
just do whatever and kind of say whatever
and just kind of just be me
I've actually had this conversation before
about why won't you do this
or why you could play with that group or this group
it's because
maybe I am a little more comfortable
solo, maybe it is
maybe that is what it is
and obviously with all of you
I prefer solo less to comprehend from my tiny brain
my tiny brain
but I don't know sometimes stuff just randomly comes up
like for instance like Star
and Terraria it was just like
there was no plan there
it wasn't like oh we're going to do this
we should do this, we should do this more often
it was just like I want to fucking play Terraria
and you do too
let's do it, let's just play it, let's beat it
that's just kind of how it works
and that's how it will continue to work
what did he say?
Dermis Sauer
oh yeah I didn't put that, Dermis lied about it
no it's not
I have like four hours to put Dermis Sauer as an emote
but let's finish this up
let's get to the end
we are at the end
and that means we switch over to the real end
this one
we have 250 from Gnarly
at the end here, thank you
thanks for showing my Soul Calibur Glueman on stream
I don't know if I uploaded it right
but that was supposed to be a whole photo album of characters
regardless happen to have my shitty Glueman
next to some really high quality fan art
that was great
I don't think other ones popped up
but it was still awesome
it was still very very very good
good shit, I didn't even know that had that good of a character creator
until somebody told me about it
I was like damn, cool
but no it was great
Freudian Weapon thanks for the 250
this community content is a great idea
I'll definitely make some art for the next one
and good luck with the doctors, be well
I'm gonna try
I am gonna try
I'm not too concerned about it
but
there has been
just a random nagging issue
that has been around for a while
and it's not anything to do with my intestinal problems
at least not that I've been able to
because I had the colonoscopy, remember?
that was because of these symptoms
I wanted to check on a few things
keep going to see what the hell is going on
but I mean I feel fine
I'm okay, I'm fine, I'm not sick or anything
like I'm just
there's nothing going on internally there
that once I find out
what the hell it is
just do it, figure it out
I'm not concerned
do I have a FODMAP problem?
that's what they thought it was at first
but I'm not sure that's what it is
I get like this bad
abdominal pain that sits like under my rib cage
like on my right side
and it's kind of right in the center
so they want to do an ultrasound
on gallbladder and
check out the organs
just make sure they're all working properly
and it's peace of mind too, just to make sure you know
I want to stay on top of it
I guess, but thank you Frodeon
Bala Koala, thank you for the thousand bits
play more N-G-U
that's a great game but
I don't think you'll see that on stream anymore
we hit him too hard with the frog
could be irritable bowel syndrome
well I have irritable bowel disease
I was diagnosed with colitis
10 years ago
maybe a little bit more, like 12 years ago
the symptoms are different
they're not the ones that I'm typically used to
we'll figure it out
you won't see that on stream anymore
it's a great game but
I probably will move on from it
but thanks for the thousand bits, appreciate it
Bala Koala
also C4G, thanks for the 250, hey Jerma
I did the Ace Attorney video
I had a bit I wanted to include where the judge
gavel on the emote only button
but I was in a rush to finish it in time
and forgot to include it
I'm glad people seem to like the video
even if you won't admit to your crimes
that's fucking funny
but
it still was great regardless of any
finishing touches, so
thank you so much for that, it was fantastic
Superintendent Chalmers, thanks for the 250
hey Jerma, when you were talking about taxes and whatnot
I immediately thought of this
white suburban punk, just like me
what?
taxes?
repo man?
click on the album, click on the album
hold on
don't click on the album, why?
why why why why why
what's in it, what's in it, what's in it
what did you make me click on?
one fucking guy, it's just
a one guy
oh I see the album though, hold on we'll go through this in a second
let's get to the end of the bits, there's only two more
two more
and they are, that was from
Superintendent Chalmers
silent serenity thanks for the 250
silent serenity right now
Jerma, I'm not sure if I told this story before but I'm gonna
so I'm going to, since I was reminded
of it anyways, years ago when I
was still in high school I had to write
a play for English class
so what did I write about?
the egg of course
I adapted the original egg video
into my script, my teacher loved it
so I hope you don't mind that I plagiarized
what did you get for a grade?
did you get an A?
because that's only
okay if you got an A
if you got a C-
or worse, then that would
upset me a little because that means that
a teacher doesn't understand
true artwork
below average
because it's true art
is what that is
but Phylactery gave another
five thousand bits
may as well be
five thousand dollars at this point
total, thank you Phylactery
this is another video here
it's another Jimmy Neutron
video
how do you have all these Jimmy Neutron
clips just ready to go?
where are you getting the Jimmy Neutron
clips?
oh hi Jimmy
I have to do a report on snails or
napoleon, can you help me?
what's the point of doing homework
we do it and then what?
poof, we're gone
emptiness, we're all just dust in the wind
okay
I don't want to be dust in the wind
is that from the thing
we were talking about?
he got clipped into
five different Jimmy Neutrons?
oh okay right
like I said every cartoon has done that
thanks a lot Jimmy
well not Jimmy Neutron
Jimmy Neutron did not give me that clip
I misclicked, hold on
go back over here
but thank you Phylactery
and let's show the images
of, wait wait wait wait
somebody link me that image gallery
again of the
the characters from Soul Calibur
thank you
that is okay
that's one, that's one, that's one
alright, let's scroll through this
in the right spot though
go back to here
do a German Rumble special edition
special edition
they're all special, anytime
I'm still on Jimmy
that's on the stream dashboard
so, I mean that's incorrect
I don't know where it's pulling that from
password leaked
this is just like the stream bits
this is from the German Mustard site
it's way better
than stream labs
where
hold on
shouldn't it be this one right here
it is this one right here
so what the hell is this one
so this is this one
let's take a look at these, this is a glue man
pretty sick
I told you there was a lot of tabs
this looks like Super Jex
that's super blue screen
odd Michael
pretty good
that's deep
wow
that's pretty great actually
Socrates, the fifth turtle
is the clown joke
that's very accurate actually
what it really looked like
clown joke, bat boy
you've been busy
these are awesome, I don't know if this is
detailed
the pirate spy
this is ridiculous
jewel wizardry
you have the wizard from jewel
wizardry
this is a candy man
from
brutal lethal league
say it
I can't say it
say the thing
I can't do it
I have to have just had a coffee
I'm really excited
this is Jevil
these are awesome
Sekiro
this is easy Pete
I can't believe that these are so detailed
this is awesome
nice work
awesome job
that's a lot
somebody who makes characters
and spends time on them
I know how long these take
it's deceiving
please
I'm going to leave this open
and I'm going to put a blanket behind my computer's fan
because I feel like it
but that's it
I will see you guys
on Monday
Monday probably around 4
just because I have that appointment
I know we've been doing streams at around 1.30
1.00, 1.00, 2.00
that's where they're going to be permanently
but just because of the doctor's appointment
that's what it was a few weeks ago
around 4 o'clock
just to let you know and make sure you're aware
I will see you Monday
have a great weekend everybody
thank you for participating in that community night
I thought it was a fucking blast
much love to you all
see you Monday
good night guys