Hey, what is going on everybody? Jerma here with a Team Fortress 2 gameplay commentary and tonight
gonna be playing as the... So what I want to talk about today guys is a few things and uh
some things are really bad in this video some of the things we're gonna talk about are not cool
but you gotta deal with it you have to deal with these problems if you are going to have a computer
that is custom built that's just it's just things like this are going to happen so
let's start from the very beginning here you probably watched the video from like two or three
weeks ago where I was like building a supercomputer going to the micro center gonna get a bunch of
parts it's gonna be so sick and I did that and I had it built and the thing like shit the bed
last night like that I had a motherboard problem last night I don't know what's going on I think
the motherboard might be bad it might be a crappy I don't know I don't know all I know is that it
doesn't work and I'm currently recording this on my laptop so if this video is not 1080p I
sincerely apologize I'm gonna try to do it so it really could be 1080p it might not it might not
but it might be now if you've been following this whole me showing pictures of it me talking about
it then you you'll know that when you get when you run into a problem like this with a computer
when you have an issue if you custom build a computer if you have somebody build it for you
whatever whatever if you have a custom built pc when you run into a problem like this you want to
just pick the thing up and like spike it through a fucking window like that last night when this
was happening and it was like 12 hours were going by I was having so many problems I was trying to
figure out what the hell was going on doing everything I could possibly think of and nothing
was working I couldn't get anything to really work the way I wanted it to and it was just a
nightmare and if this thing had a tail if this computer had a tail I would have grabbed it spun
around a bunch of times and just let go and shut up into whatever it was gonna fucking run into
it was that close good thing I didn't install a tail on this pc and actually I just thought of
something what if you took what if you took a computer bear with me for a second what if
you took a computer and you put a little tail on it and then you gave it ears on the front
and put whiskers on the front too so it was like a giant like mouse that would be pretty funny
wouldn't it or am I this is just totally just inaccurate but that probably wouldn't be funny
at all all right forget it but the computer is currently being fixed it's going to be fine in
probably a day or so I just haven't really been able to do very much this last couple of days
which sucks because I got a whole lot of stuff going on there's a whole lot of videos I'm making
in the process of I was in the process of making them before the video dumped to the bed like
dumped its pants and shit its diaper in the bed like I there are at least a few videos and thank
god that I backed up all this stuff if you guys have never seen my video on backing up your hard
drive then go watch it well you don't really even have to go watch it just back up your hard drives
with information you don't want to lose because if I had lost a bunch of this stuff for videos
that I'm currently working on right now like I don't even know I can't even imagine my
infuriation if that would were to happen anyways we're gonna move on we're gonna talk about the
second thing I wanted to bring up in this video which is a little better and a little nicer and
a little more uplifting than the previous few minutes or a couple minutes and that's the tf2
mix-up tf2 mix-up number six I got to be a part of this year so it was really really cool really
awesome if you don't know what the tf2 mix-up is they get a bunch of youtubers and some gaming
developers a couple people from valve end up showing up and we play matches against each other
and it's all recorded it's all captured and it's all for charity so I was able to be a part of it
this year I was actually on captain sparkles team a link will be in the description if you want to
watch the videos that were recorded during this segment of time we were playing for the mix-up
there's going to be I think three or four different rounds that sparkles is going to
be uploading so if you want to check if you want to check out the perspective from our end our team
go to sparkles channel go to that video that's going to be in the description there'll be a
link there you can't miss it you're going to take a right on second street if you see the mcdonald's
you went too far and then take a left at those lights and you're going to be a captain sparkles
channel so that's where you want to go if you want to see that and we're going to move on to
talk about something else in this video is the fact that holiday crates are dropping now
holiday crates are dropping all over the place I just got some I don't even I might even have
gotten one in this video I don't even know if I show the death or not and I think they've been
dropping for a little over a week I think December 6th is when they were added so like a week and a
few days since they have been dropping but what this means the initial hypothesis that we are
going to be getting three updates in three months is actually potentially going to come true so we
are probably going to see the holiday christmas miss miss whatever you want to call it tf2 update
fairly soon here and everybody can cross their fingers and hope that we get some pretty cool
stuff because there really has never been a holiday themed tf2 update that didn't give us
something cool they've always introduced at least a couple of new weapons at least a couple of new
maps or new modes they have there but they've always released something cool for the christmas
and holiday season so here's hoping that these holiday crates coming around is a sign that the
update is sort of looming and with that that is going to wrap up the video thank you all so much
for watching I really do appreciate it stay tuned for the holiday animation video that I was talking
about that should be ready to roll here in the next week or so I think I touched upon this
once but I'll reiterate it one more time there's going to be an animation on the channel it's going
to be a grandpa video it's going to be grandpa animated that's all I'm going to say I'm not going
to say anything more about it you'll just see it in your sub box when you see it a lot of time has
gone into this the animator has been spending a ton of his time putting it together and I hope you
guys enjoy it you'll see it when you see it so that's it everybody thanks for watching everybody
just appreciate it and I'll see you guys all next time and of course take care everybody I did I
just did that because um I don't have any like the files the sound files or the photoshop files
they're probably not even a thumbnail on this video either and you know I because I don't have
the files okay well bye