He's on time. I am on time. I made it. I'm here. And I got the tweet out too. Seconds to spare.
Yeah, well, I started at 12.59. But it takes two, three minutes for it to process through the
internet and then go through your screen and then get to your computer. Why are my lights not on?
My lights aren't even turned on. Yeah, I have one of those, like, click click lights. Hey, there we
go. Now I can see. Is this title too too much? I think it is. I kind of have to change this title.
The title is hurting me. Well, there's a reason why that I made the title the way it is.
Today we're going to play. Well, first of all, let's go right to business. Let's talk about
what's going on. Hey, how have you been? It's been a few days. I don't want to get right to business.
We actually got a couple things to talk about. Maybe one thing. It's hard to talk remotely
seriously when this is on my screen. I'm sitting here like, hey, let's talk about some serious
stuff. There's like a pancake blueberry guy dancing on the screen. How can I be serious?
That's what I have to look at. The title of this game is sometimes to deal with the difficulty
of being alive. I need to believe there's a possibility that life isn't real. That's the
name of this game. I would have abbreviated this. I don't think this even fits on Steam.
Does this dot dot dot at the end on Steam? You thought this was a joke? No, no, this is real.
Those of you that don't know, typically maybe 30, 40 minutes before a stream starts, I get in the
chat and we just talk. We go over lottery numbers. We go over our favorite animals.
And then sometimes we're talking about the game that's going to be played in the next 30, 40
minutes. So I did a poll, a couple of polls. Usually I throw it up there if I have like
something I like to do or something that I want to do. And everyone thought that this was fake,
that I was just putting this up here to be like a weirdo. No, this is an existential game. There's
no end. There's no beginning. You just play it. I don't know if this could be fun. Somebody
requested this. And I tell you, I take requests dead seriously. That recommendation channel,
if you have a recommendation, put it there. I look at it all the damn time. I am absolutely serious.
If you don't think, oh no, I'm not going to recommend that. There's no way he'll fucking
play it, right? No, there's no way. If I put something in that channel, is it possible that
he might just like glaze over it and and not care? And no, I think I'm good. I don't think
he'll play that. I don't think he ever would. Don't worry. If you got something interesting,
put it in that channel. I'm all about the interesting things. Why is there no audio?
No, that's why. Because there's music here, isn't there? Yes, there is. Well, now that makes more
sense is why the sprinkle bread guy is dancing. How long do you think I can stay on this screen
for? This is a starting soon screen. It just is. Hold on. Like, oh, that's a gerba is starting soon.
I need to see. Okay, we're gonna make that. Let's do orange or something. All right, here we go,
guys. Hey, let's turn the stream on. Starting the stream right now. Okay. Okay. Oh, hey,
hey, what's going on, guys? Hope you had a good day today. Me, Jeremy. Nice to see you. Happy
birthday to all of you birthday people out there today. Got a special one for you tonight.
Have you been playing? Sometimes there's a possibility that life and death are the same
thing and it's not even real in the first place. There's a possibility that I've never
found it to begin with. That's the name of the game we're playing. Let's go. All right. How do I?
All right. Hey, buddy. I'm going on vacation tomorrow for my birthday. I told you happy birthday.
Awesome. Happy birthday. Awesome. All right. There is no beginning and no end to this game.
Who's gonna go? I don't. I'm not even gonna get told how to control the game.
I have a traffic light on my back. There's a punch. Uh, okay. Try to examine the things over here.
Oh, there's a sprint. All right. So if this is, if I was making a video right now,
okay, you ready? Those of you that are like, oh, man, remember, remember when he used to make
videos? What I would do here is after about a minute is like, what, what just happened right
there? Like, oh, how do I play this? Left click, right click. Oh, I don't know. There would be a
cut right here and it would cut to police sirens and wanted stars in the top right. And I'd be
running around like punching and screaming and stuff. That would be like the joke for this part.
That's what I would do. I'm not even 10 seconds into the game and I know that's what I would do.
Is this an NPC? I want to chat. Uh, okay. I thought he was grabbing me. I thought he was grabbing
me one star. Uh, I don't think I want to do this. I'm busy. Can't talk now. I don't like this. I
don't like what's going on here. Hey, you're so dumb. You think I'm a computer. Obviously I'm not.
Uh, who's running around with these people in the background? What? Okay. Wait, wait, wait, wait.
What's going on in the background? That's important. There's like a half house there.
Where are you from? Um, I'm not, I'm never gonna tell anybody where you from online.
What are you doing? I was gonna write like Ohio. Did you just converse with a human?
That was a machine. Lost one. Yes. Hold on. What? Oh, it's, it's people. There are people.
There are no people in this game. What do I have to do? What happened? Did it break? Uh,
oh, I just lost my HUD. Is this part of like the existential part of the game?
Sometimes to understand the actuality of the universe, you have to fucking combine two or
three atoms in the root of all square roots. I'm coming back. Hold on. Come on. I still think it's
funny. And that's all I care about. I think that's funny. Some of you comedy fucking scholars,
maybe a little bit. I think that's funny. All right. Single player. What the fuck's happening?
How do I get out of this place? I just want to play the game. Okay. That's clearly not a robot.
I don't think this is a robot. How do I talk to this person? Go away. I'm swimming. I want to talk
to you. Come here. Go away. This is not my head. Oh, go away. I'm picking up items. This is not,
we're even picking up items. Two. Did I get two items? Press E to interact. This is a guy from
Pee Wee Herman. An artist was secretly hired by the Bolsheviks when he was 14 to try and ruin
Western culture. He becomes an egomaniacal misogynist who hides gold bars under his bed.
Everyone loves him and admires him. Institutions teach children to be like him. Um, that's a little
too deep for Pee Wee Herman. Can you just say the word of the day? It's like sofa.
Ah! Would you like to play pizza in the woods? No. Wait, should I have said yes?
Somebody's just lying on the ground. Oh, I got something. Turning on radio.
Is this a real song? No, no, no. This is a real song. This is a, no, of course it is. No,
you just, okay, go away. I'm in a conversation. Holy shit. Is this music? Is this music?
What a sick computer set. Look at that. That person is all over the place. That's fucking
Bitcoin. That's fucking Ethereum. That's gold, silver, platinum. That's all.
Except if it was gold, it would be pretty high.
I just, I want to go near the song. A capitalist buys up all the aspirin to control the headache
market. He stores it in a giant warehouse just outside the city. One hot day, the aspirin melts
and forms the largest privately owned lake in the country. It costs 10 bucks for a swim.
I feel like this is, you put on headphones and you walk around and press the buttons at the museum.
Now stop playing music! The beginning of every fucking battle royale game.
All we need is the guy that crawls around, the three people that crawl around prone,
and then the one guy that punches everybody in the face like over and over again. All right,
I'm talking to you. Come here. I feel like I've done this move before. On camera. I have. I've
done that exact fucking move and you've seen it like a thousand times. All right, I'm going
to go play the pizza one. How do we do anything? I thought I was supposed to be only, okay, here we go.
Hey, where are you from? From Ohio. I hate my job.
I'm sorry. I'm sorry. That was a machine. All right, let's go play the pizza game.
What am I gaining here? I'm gaining some kind of weird currency. Pizza in the woods, a walking
simulator. Leave idle and pizza will walk and fly by himself or explore on your own with WASD in
the mouth. There are things to see in four corners of the forest and a lake to swim in. Hit escape
to return to Polly's pond. I feel like that's something nobody wants to do on his own.
All right, so my hand, I'm just watching this with you guys. We're watching the same thing.
There's nothing more hilarious than the urgent care waiting room. What the fuck is going on?
Fires on cocaine and the elephants have learned to use email. They're writing letters to giant
squid who are saving their ink for perfume that makes bats horny. The bats are making babies to
replace the supreme court justices. It's all been signed off on set of four. Annex is playing the
flute on top of it. This is what happens when you take a dose higher than you're supposed to
take of acid. First of all, just don't do it. I'm not going to condone any of that.
Don't take drugs, ever. Don't take too many of them because they end up writing a sentence.
I see that person in the corner with their eyes wide open saying all these things. Just don't do
drugs. They're not good for you. Take Tylenol. If you've got a headache, take Tylenol. Aspirin.
I did just say the thing that the museum button press thing just told you not to do.
It's documented evidence of why things like marijuana are beneficial to the human body
taken in the right way. It's good for pain relief and especially for irritable bowel disease as
well. Just want to make sure everyone's aware of that. Be careful when you do drugs. If you
don't do them, just don't do them. Can I have control again? I have no more control. A pizza
like Pizza Paul, whatever his name is. What am I throwing? Are those jacks?
If you can just do something different than your parents, it is a major accomplishment.
These are just acid fortune cookies. Oh, something's going on here. Why is this
getting so laggy? All right, what is laptop lap dance? Return to main level. How do I
teleport? Return to main level. Should I find something in here? There's probably something
in here to do. Hey, you want to ditch the stream and light up? No, I can't, man. I can't.
All right. I can't, man. What is this? Should I go to find the laptop? There's like two rockets
and stuff apparently out here. There's things to see in the corners. There we go. I found it.
I found the portal. I can't wait until the wild development team. I know I make a wild reference
every single stream, but I have to. That's the portal. That's the original portal in what was
the name of the zone for the Emerald Nightmare, the Emerald Dream. That was the Emerald Dream
portal. It was right behind a dragon. There were four dragons in the world. What was his name?
Duskwood, right? That portal that was behind. What was the dragon's name? It was in there for
eight years. I'm not telling a joke. I'm giving a wild reference. What is this? Toilet? All right.
How many more times am I going to do it? Is it naked? What? Holy shit. What is that?
Well, this looks different. Is that pencil? Whoa. Is it an actual pencil NPC?
How do you talk to the pencil? Holy shit, dude. Duskwood. Okay. This is somebody's house. I don't
like this. I want to go through this quickly. I don't like this tunnel. What am I doing? What's
going on? Why am I sitting? What do you mean you can't believe that? That sounds awesome.
That's not it. No, I get it. You guys thought this was going to be like a meme. You know,
this is like an existential fucking like serious game. Why is it dark? All right. I kind of want
to get away with getting from the pizza place. I want to get out of the pizza place. This gives
me like freaking me out. A fox and a cricket develop a deep friendship in the Buruburu forest,
but the humans are encroaching with their subdivisions and shopping malls.
The fox and the cricket organize all the animals in the forest and they commit group suicide.
All right. So, um, can I do the test again? Run. I'm going up here. Is there anywhere else I can go?
Bed? Painting? I can't like hold down and go like, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait. Something going on
over here. There's a guitar hero controller. Give me some music. I don't want to do it.
I don't want to do it. I don't want to do it. I have to. I can't help it.
I can't stop. I can't stop. I need to do it.
It's all I care about. I don't care about anything else. I'm losing my mind right now.
Wait, wait, just wait. Just wait, wait. Okay.
I'm sorry. I'm really sorry. People are probably fucking pissed. I can't help it. Okay. What else
can I do? That's the only thing I've been able to do in this game is just zoom in on people doing
that dance. I really should be paying attention to the message that the game is trying to convey,
right? Like the messages and the things that you should be thinking about. All right.
What the fuck was that? Somebody's driving by really fast in a car with windows down.
You know, I love, anytime that happens, I laugh my ass off. When you get this like,
oh, it's coming from over here. You know, like you're at a red light and the guy,
somebody pulls up next to you and you hear it. You're talking like your mother in the front seat.
Like, oh yeah, I really do think that it's, yeah, I think that the best part about,
um, uh, yeah, no, no, yeah, that will get milked too.
Look at that windows down. You got your windows down. Is anybody going to roll them up?
No, the person is going to be like, just get fucking rolling his windows up. You don't like
my music. Topical stand up. You know, you know, when you pull it up at a red light.
So I did say that this is going to be, I did say I've been, I've been very clear that we were
going to either play this for 30 minutes or two hours and it's been 30 in 30 minutes. What was
that? Is it stack city? Yeah. Okay. This is a lot. We got, try to read this. I'm not going to read
this. Should I read this whole thing? That's too many. That's too many words. I think picture a
dark room in your head. It's night. Maybe just a little bit of moonlight is creeping in through a
window so you can just make out some of the silhouettes of some objects. The pictures on
the wall are black. The couch is black. The table is black. The lamp over the couch is black. The
air is dark blue. Take out the ceiling. Look at the room from above. All you see is blue and black.
Now turn on a lamp in the room. It spreads over everything. The pictures are white. The couch and
rug are over saturated warm colors. Yellow is pouring out from the window. It's so bright. It
hurts your eyes and you have to squint, but you stay in the room anyway and bask in the glow.
You feel so nice. Now there's a light on your head. And let me tell you something, Larry. Get
the fuck out of here. Now there's a light in your head. That's one of the best shows of all time,
by the way. Kirby Enthusiasm is one of the best fucking comedic actors. Some of the best comedy.
Just true quick witted fucking real comedians. Not me.
Bart Simpson. No, no, no, no. Bart Simpson's not part of that group. I just saw that and had to say
it and I think that's Bart Simpson. Okay. What do I press? No, no, no, no. This is another one of
these. Oh, wait, wait, wait, wait. Here we go. I had somebody wash my face with rose water.
My bedroom window, but I don't think I could actually see it. Okay. Well, what else is going
on? Let's think about the private parts of my ancestors. How much they... I don't want to think
about that. I really don't want to think about that. I'm not sure I want to. I don't want to
look at it. I don't want to look at this one either. I'm not going to do it. I'm not going to do it.
I need to fix it. It's wrong. One of these times I'm going to do this and I'm actually just going
to get up and fucking leave for like five minutes. I will drop a thousand viewers, but like, I don't
know. It might be worth it. In the shower, my girlfriend art pieces is when a Russian cosmonaut
plugged a hole in the international space station with a thumb knife. But Billy Hilliard's space
was prevented from seeping into the astronaut's small living pot. Since the thumb around the same
time back on Earth, they're already receiving a real astronaut breakdown. He's advanced nothing
into space, aspiring with corrupt leadership to take a branch on Earth's improbable complexity.
That's like an emote. That's the emote I would expect to like have like react to this. We've got
some overlap here. Let's get to the frame. Let's get to the top. In the shower, my girlfriend
from a young age, William Blake, I don't... This is freaking me out. I don't like this. And maybe
it's... Maybe that's by design. Homo sapiens die off. Some of the computers we program to act like
us live on. What if a future homo sapien, homo species, is able to communicate with us through
our AI? Will they be convinced to click on links that claim to forgive their mortgages and have
pictures of large breasts over they have a conversation that inspires them and makes them
miss us? Holy shit. That's a good point. That's a great point. What will they do?
What the hell's gonna happen? I think the five-point narrative structure has ran its course,
homelining with the Sopranos. Lately, when I put on a movie or TV show, I get so bored and barely pay
attention. I browse the web and send messages. I just want bright, warm lights on all around me.
Things to glance at and be reminded I'm not alone in the universe. I don't know. Five-point structure
I mean, it's... The Sopranos is one of the best TV shows ever made. I mean, I want your... I want
your character creator because I definitely would make something like this in like the journal
record. I would love this creator. Give me one of these WWE. I love the idea of a tulpa, a spiritual
being you make with your focused mind that acts independently from them. I'm always having dreams
where I interact with people I've never seen in waking life. That's true. Happens to me too.
I've fallen in love and grown very angry with people that don't exist. I probably have a lot of
tulpas in me I could create if I ever really concentrate. A capacity for creating
analogical spaces could be the greatest thing about us or make us the shortest surviving of
all the species. Dude, I... I'm telling you, I've had dreams before where like I had this... It's
like me and my dad in our house, but it's just some bald guy with a mustache. My dad does not
have a mustache. I am of like Irish and Polish descent and like this guy in my dream
he's in like a few of them is like an Italian guy. He's like an Italian guy with a mustache.
He's not my dad. So I don't know. I have no idea why. Why does that happen? It's not Mario. Oh,
you guys, it's not fucking Mario. It's just... It's what it just is. I play too many video games
and fucking Mario has been burned in my brain as like dad. That's also kind of messed up
and maybe that's... What's going on? I want to keep... What's going on? Trees. Trees. Gathering.
Gathering. Humans. One human at Pala... Pawn. So? What the fuck? Oh, I forgot to tell you guys this
story. It's about sleeping. This is important. This has nothing to do with anything going on
the screen. Nothing at all. So, um, you know, every so often I tell you guys a story about like
Kim and I with some like weird shit happens when we're in the same... We're sleeping in the same
room sometimes. Like she'll have a dream or I'll have like a dream or something funny will happen.
So why are you rezzing sleeper? I don't even... This is fucking fun. This is a funny story and
I'm gonna tell it and I don't even care if you think it's a boring story. I thought it was funny
and that's what we do on this stream. We talk about funny things that happen in my... What a crazy
fucking life, right? What a wild life I have, right? Listen to me. All right. So Kim gets up
sometimes in the middle of the night and then goes to the bathroom. I do it too, but I was dead
asleep. I'm lying on my back and I'm dead asleep and I heard her start to move around and start to
stir, if you will, right? So she kind of turns and she sits on the edge of the bed and that's
when I started to wake up and I didn't know... I didn't see what she was doing. I'm looking at her
back, right? So her back and the back of her head. So she's sitting on the edge of the bed and she
leans forward and this is the first thing I remember. My eyes just open. I see this. I hear
and she leaned forward. I thought she shit diarrhea in her pants. Just like leaning forward,
just shitting her pants, but she was blowing her nose, but in my... I just barely got out of sleep
in my... I'm... I just am becoming conscious. I was just like, what are you doing? Are you okay?
He's like, why would anybody sit up on the edge of bed, lean forward and just
fucking... You know what? What? I really thought it happened. It was a huge nose blow.
That's a funny story. That's a funny like, be it my girlfriend, you know, like funny things.
Why is that a story? Because we're talking about sleep and dreams and stuff. What? You don't think
that that's like a humorous story? That's not even a boomer story. Was it a boomer story?
I thought it was really funny. Oh, we have something else.
A man is so anxious he can't stop grinding his teeth. He grinds them so hard they start to break.
This makes him even more nervous and he starts to grind the broken teeth into his gums as he
gurgles while his mouth is dripping blood. I don't want to listen to that. Can I light off?
Cut to power. Can I get up there? Would you like to play the founders now? Oh god, I don't know.
The central nervous gives you a version of reality that keeps it comfortable.
To exist is to have a body. To have a body is to have limited understanding.
Suddenly you find your consciousness far away from your flesh and your awareness drifting to
wherever and is very slowly blending with a universal laziness that shrouds all sentience.
Why did somebody say ASMR truck? It's not truck. That is not actual TOS. What? What are you talking
about? What do you mean? Turn it off. Turn it off. Turn it off. Turn it off. Turn it off. What? What's
going on? What's going on? A break dancer with ice cream zits. An alien reggae band using
dismembered chimeras as instruments. Everyone's listening to radio stations from across earth
trying to make sense of humanity. The more they try to make sense the less sense there is.
The founders of Daytona Beach also founded Dayton, Ohio. Stock trading through Vedic ritual.
Decapitated heads telling sci-fi stories to walls. A green cowboy stuck inside a wooden temple.
I don't understand. Is it like something at the end? If you want your body back you need to
pronounce a seven syllable word three times. It is a vibration key to a corporate figure out your
work and you will return to a body. Seven syllable word. Supercalifragilisticexpial. That's
like 12. Never mind. I need a seven syllable word. No. I'm not going to do it twice. Whoa.
Isn't that thing just... Everybody always makes these horror game things and these scary monsters
and oh my god look out it's the lady with the long hair and the coat on or whatever and they
know if this thing's sprinting full speed down like an alley screaming
this will be way scarier than like the guy from Outlast.
There's nobody dancing here. Is this a band song? All right if I do that joke again I want 100
people to unsubscribe. If I do that joke one more time I want 100 people to unsubscribe.
Ugh. Mouth? Oh it's an eye. Whatever it is. What did I just pick up?
Do I have to collect all the things? Is it going to bite me?
This is very strange. I guess this is weird. This is strange. Am I not tall enough to go over here?
What's that? R1. Do I have to press R1 on the controller? I like that. I like that little guy.
Now that's cool. I know what that feels like. You know when you just look at something I know it's
like a leather. It's like a nice smooth leathery feel. I know what that feels like. I want that.
I'm gonna feel that right now. I want to like raise my hand over that like soft like very smooth
leather. I'm losing 100 subs. Got my finger on the unsub button. Am I just talking to this thing?
Don't don't don't don't what do you mean don't don't don't don't don't don't don't don't don't
go upstairs don't go upstairs don't go up don't do it don't is this like something up here
it's fine chat you guys are freaking me the fuck out right now is it down his back
why is it so dark i don't fucking like this help him do you i don't like this
okay okay right that's all right that's
i don't i don't know that was i wasn't i don't i think that was his stomach it was his stomach
something come out of the stomach there's a like a monster coming out of somebody's stomach
what the fuck no oh my god damn it i can't i thought it was like done the the thing came out
of his stomach this is like it popped out of the stomach and it was it was out the eight uh eight
i'm gonna give you exactly what happens this guy up here helped me out my stomach hurts i
went to the fucking just like it was very two and a half stars on yelp and i went anyways i was
hungry it was like a uh a restaurant that was really lowly rated but it was like two stars on
yelp i was hungry only thing open i went there i got a fucking like triple bean and fish burrito
i don't know why i did that it was just it was a special was a dollar 40 i don't know what i
didn't realize why it was that less expensive but i ate it anyways and it was okay going down
and then like i fucking my stomach started hurting and like i had a ton of diarrhea problems
and then like oh like an alien bursted out of my stomach that's what just happened nothing else
happened how do i get out of here i don't want to have to do i wanted to like just press this
i know if somebody else has streamed this game that's fine but i run a pgr rated stream
all right it's gone no it's not it came out again it did it again oh jesus fucking christ
okay this is well you have no idea how fucked up this is okay i'm out of here i'm leaving i'm out
how do i end this i did all the things wait go in here oh low low low low low
t re t low t re t low what is this three t low can am i getting smaller oh seven syllables
t re t re t low can need two more okay t re t low can lick t re t low can lick is one
what the word is this gonna be where's this final word now get it no it's not in there not around
here seven syllables t re t low can lick one more i missed it somewhere here this this guy didn't do
anything mirror oh got it um triangle
all right i really don't i don't even know where i need to find here
here one of the sharks maybe i might i may have missed it way back
it's not really something you dance like this
move out of the way
no i i i i i looked at that already i was already up there
i'm missing i would think it would be something like over here but i already got that one
i already got that one i need to at least complete this i have to just get out of this computer
inside wait got it okay so i got t re aha say it t re t say it three times
t re t low say it again t re t low again t re t rolo can lick er
t re t low can lick er i did it oof am i cursed now forever no i don't have the forever curse
somebody look that up does that mean anything should i not have said that is that like
he just took my soul all right here comes that's a person total 25 is that a good number to leave
obviously i'm not gonna reply because i want you to think on the computer
i am fat and don't like the way i look um i exercise or change lifestyle change
no that was a human no i don't want to play that is there any other game to play
i feel like there's probably only a few more things to see do the multiplayer about no i'm
not gonna do multiplayer in this game if it even still works
multiplayer in a game like this is probably just like hey come on in anybody and fucking
destroy the stream in 1930s america a horse becomes president yeah i'm not even gonna say
that out loud all right well that was interesting we can play metal wolf panic now that was a nice
start wait what is this metal wolf wait did i say metal wolf chaos metal wolf panic
what is it called isn't that like that's like a
panic full metal panic i don't know metal panic full frog metal chaos all right let's play it
this was called i'm gonna try as hard as i can to say the name of this game
i can't i have no idea okay let's say i have 100 points and i get five points deducted for every
wrong placement of a word ready i'm gonna try to write it on screen okay i'm gonna try i'm
gonna try so i gotta start with 100 points um there is something about life no no hold on don't i'm
not gonna look at chat either there is something about life no there is something about life
to which is it even real or not something like that right there was something who's oh no no i
think it's like who who's to say who's to say there's uh something about life no no no hold on
i'm not done yet i'll get it who's to say who's to say there's something about life who's to say
there is something about life to which is it even real or not it's something like that right i'm
close all right i'm gonna go with this and we'll see how bad i did who is to say who is to who is
who's to see who what did i write who's to say here is something no no the here is not supposed
to be there who's to say i missed the whole feature of the game okay wait i press three
oh well that's i can be the other characters okay i can't do anything about this three
let's follow uh this person why are they all cutting down trees
do i need to collect this stuff and they're gonna go to bed yeah there's a ui i have mail now
all right so how close was i what's the name of the game uh greg 39 gathering gathering i can make
them do things this is like a weird idol game out here they can like build more town sometimes to
deal with the difficulty of being alive and to believe there's a possibility that life is not
real who's to say there is something about life to which is it even real or not all right that's
close enough i don't think i have to deduct very many points i get like a 75 visiting secret lair
i didn't do that all right i apparently am visiting the secret lair am i in their brains
what hey i wasn't done i actually wasn't done i don't get this thing going is this a person
or is this a person's clothes i think this is their clothes yeah that's like a sweatshirt right
i think so go away and pray all right i think that about sums it up no i'm not gonna do it
that's too late for that i already read over it i've already read over it i've read over it
i can't do it again see he stopped doing it no i can't do it all right let's play metal wolf chaos
that was a nice little beginning to the stream this is a request and it was pretty interesting
it was pretty weird it was all kind of out there you're forgetting the xd i know and whatever
that was called there is something to say about life and death to bring yourself to the
realization that it might not be real it's just type in there is something into steam and you'll
find it i think that's the only one that has that