Hey, what is going on, everybody? Jerma here with a Team Fortress 2 gameplay commentary.
And tonight, gonna be playing as a bunch of different people. I think it's the Demoman, the Soldier, and the Scout.
I believe I could be wrong. I don't know how I edited this together.
But it's okay, because I'm not really gonna be talking about the gameplay all that much.
I'm gonna be talking about Team Fortress 2, and specifically...
Well, first of all, this is a 100% crit gameplay, not meant to be taken all that seriously.
And that's the point of this whole video. TF2 is not a very serious game.
I mean, there are, of course, the competitive aspects of this game.
There are the very hunker-down focus, get a bunch of kills as whatever your favorite class is.
But this game is meant, at least for me, primarily for the humor and the hilarity of every single moment.
There's at least one or two moments per round that I laugh at the screen for.
Like, heavy, like eating a sandwich and then getting backstabbed while the Spy then goes onto the point and gets hit in the face by a frying pan.
Like, these things happen all the time in this game.
And I really do truly think that this is sort of where I'm taking this video.
If Team Fortress 2 did not have the humor, where would it be?
Would it just fall into forgotten memories, or would we ever play this game that much anymore?
If the Spy didn't have revenge kill lines, if there were no fully voice acted characters, there were no meet the team videos,
if this was just a first person shooter and nothing else in a phong shaded world, would we still be playing right now at this point?
I don't think so. I don't think I would still be playing.
If Team Fortress went with the original design for Team Fortress 2, which was a more serious guys in camo outfits with rifles and stuff,
if that really was what it was and there was no character, there was no humor, there was no ridiculous moments,
I probably would have played it for a couple years maybe and then I would have probably moved on to something else.
Now I'm not sure if that's because I really love cartoons, I love animation, I love the voice acting behind different characters,
I love when people are brought to life and they don't really exist anywhere else and there's a whole lot of comedy,
I love Cartoon Network, all the adult swim shows, I love that stuff.
So not having it really just go, it's like meh, this game was fun for a while, but you know, whatever, I'm done with it.
What else is it? What time is it? Can I like do something else?
I would say the same thing about the Grand Theft Auto series.
There is a reason why the GTA series does so well and performs so well and gets such high ratings and has such a huge replayability factor.
It's because the game is bat shit crazy, like you can do the most ridiculous things in that game.
It's not meant to be taken that seriously unless you're playing obviously the campaign, but even the campaign does not take itself seriously.
People blow across the screen in cars and the cops like fly off buildings and stuff.
It's insanity and that's the reason why I keep going back and playing that game.
But I want to hear what you guys have to say about this.
What do you think is your favorite crazy moments in quotes game? Is it something like Team Fortress?
What's the craziest most hilarious thing you've ever seen in Team Fortress 2?
We'll start with that.
So I guess I'll go first because obviously there's nobody else in this room, so I guess I'll go first.
So anyways, my favorite most hilarious Team Fortress 2 moment is something that I recorded and it unfortunately got deleted.
I was going to show it because I wanted to talk about this and I was going to show it right freaking now, but it is no longer in existence.
What happened was I was playing as the spy and I was completely tryharding.
I was trying to get I was trying to get a gameplay backstabbing people, pull out the rubber, bang, bang, bang, getting a couple kills.
Go after this guy, get behind him.
I was trying to get a gameplay and I ended up turning a corner.
This was on viaduct right where one of the buildings are on the enemy team side.
I was in the building and I walked around the corner and there was a sniper there.
The sniper saw me.
He knew I was a spy and we started dancing.
He started to try quick scoping me.
He tried to then come in with the melee back up like I was trying to shoot him with the revolver.
And then we just stopped and then he crouched and I crouched and we walked into each other while we were still crouching.
I kept on calling him a spy.
He kept on saying yes over and over again.
And for about 45 seconds to two minutes, I don't know what the exact time was, we were just sitting there doing that.
And the whole time this is on viaduct.
There were just there was shit going on all around us.
A pyro, an enemy pyro actually came over and looked at us and then walked away.
He didn't want to interfere with our like weird tea party moment we were having.
I was cracking up so hard and I'm so mad that I didn't have it recorded because I was going to put it right here.
It was hysterical.
Why did that happen?
You can't do that in Call of Duty.
You can't do that in Battlefield.
You can't do that in any other game besides the hilarious Team Fortress 2.
And with that, that's going to wrap up the video guys.
So in the comment section again, please, if you can remember, leave me what you think your funniest Team Fortress 2 moment has been thus far.
And thank you so much for watching everybody.
You really do appreciate it.
And I'll talk to you all next time.
And of course, take care everybody.