Hey, what is going on, everybody? Jerma here with 10 million, and before the video gets started really at all, I do have to preface this by saying, guys, this is probably my favorite game right now.
I would probably put this in the top three games that I'm playing right now. I just had to make a video of it. I didn't even know this game really existed, and to be completely honest, I was sort of overwhelmed by this game when I first saw it.
But now that I've played it for a little while, I cannot put it down. I cannot stop playing this game. It's got a hold of me, guys. It's got a hold of my balls, and it's just squeezing them, and that's kind of gross.
But anyways, so what this game is, this is an action RPG puzzle hybrid game. If that makes absolutely no sense, that's okay, because nothing is really like this out there.
There are a couple of things that come to mind when you think of these sort of RPG hybrid type puzzle games, but this one is unbelievable.
So here's the thing, right? So you're this little guy on the screen, and the whole purpose of this entire game is to get 10 million points. That is it. You are supposed to get 10 million points, and you get your freedom from this freaking dungeon, because essentially, it is a dungeon crawler.
So you got your little guy up there. He runs on the top of the screen, and he just goes forward into various encounters. This can be enemies, doors, chests, etc.
And it's your job as the player to get this guy through the dungeon by lining up the corresponding tiles to whatever tasks are at hand.
So let's say you go up against a monster. There's like a skeleton or a zombie or something. You want to line up the sword tiles or the wand tiles, because those are going to use your weapons.
If you see a chest or a door, you want to line up the key tiles, and you can only do this if there are three tiles lined up. It has to be at least three, and you can do four. You can line up as many as you want after three, which do more damage.
Sometimes you can get a double key if you do four keys lined up in the same row, but you get the idea. You have to peruse yourself through this dungeon only by using these tiles.
And if you look at the top left corner of the screen right now, you're going to see three spots where items can be. These can be things like an extra sword to do a little bit more damage to an enemy.
They can be a blueprint to add more key tiles or more sword or wand tiles or something like that. It's a fantastic little game, and that's really the basics of it all.
But if you think that's it and you just go to the end and try to get 10 million points, no. And the reason why I love this game so much, guys, is because every single thing in this game can be upgraded.
And that's everything from the amount of damage your sword tiles do, the critical strike chance you have, your wand damage, the different staffs and potions. There's so much stuff.
You can upgrade your armor. You can upgrade your armor, and it's insane. I can't even begin to tell you how much fun this game is just by going through and upgrading, because it takes gold and it takes resources to do all these upgrades.
And you have to play the game to get the money to do the upgrades. So you'll spend an eternity in this game, and it's really not a bad thing.
One of the things I wanted to talk about in this video is this game's just fun. If you find a game that's fun and you really like it, this will actually help your hand-eye coordination, too, and your thought process and your problem-solving skills, because of all the things you have to do at the same time.
It's like your brain goes into overdrive when you play 10 million. And it really is something insanely addicting about being able to chain together different tiles and chain together moves and seeing the wild card tile drop down, get a bunch of points, get a bunch of upgrades, and then do it all over again.
For $5, it's only $4.99 on Steam, guys. For $5, it's truly a steal. There's no reason why you should not own this game if you have Steam, let's put it that way.
So that's pretty much going to wrap up the video, guys. Just a quick little video showcasing my latest addiction, which is this game, 10 million.
And I have not beaten the game yet, and I'm actually considering livestreaming this game, because it's very livestream-friendly, me just kind of running through the dungeon over and over again, trying to find new things, trying to upgrade new things.
Let me know what you think about that. If you guys would like to see something like that, maybe I will try and do it at some point.
But yeah, that's going to wrap up the video. Thank you, everybody, so much for watching. I really do appreciate it. And go get 10 million. Go get this goddamn game right now, because holy hell, it's the most fun thing I've ever done in my life.
Well, not necessarily. That's an overstatement. But still, go get this game. It's a lot of fun, and I'll see you guys all soon. And of course, take care, everybody.