Hey, what is going on everybody Jerma here with face burnt Jerma sunburned fortress 2
No, this is face game fortress 2 Monday's edition
Playing as the demo night as you see here, but this is gonna be a very special
Demoman demo night video because it's going to be a live
Stipulation match now. What is a stipulation match? Oh, it's that it's where you're only allowed to do one
Very specific thing with a very weird loadout. Well, not really a weird loadout, but a weird set of guidelines and
This particular set of guidelines I'm using for this stipulation is shield only
So let's see if I can kill people with the shield in this live stipulation match
No
So I'm only allowed to kill people with the shield. That's it
If I try to use the sword I am eliminated even though I don't know why I would try to do that anyways
Unless it was on accident, but this could get very very interesting. It could be very bad, too
I could just totally lose this entire thing and never kill one person, but that's the beauty of stipulation
Splendid screen does 70% more damage. That's why I'm using it map is high tower and
I gotta I gotta wait till I have a little bit lower health get smashed. Oh
All right, there's one there's one I got one kill I'm happy with that
Come on who wants another who wants a shield in their face? Oh this sniper does this sniper does
No, no I get this guy too ready watch this
Come on. Give him again. Give him again. I got the assist. I got the assist
Where is he? Oh my god. That was scary. Come on. Come on. Oh
Scout oh you don't even know. Oh
I missed everybody. Oh my god. I'm a no man's land. Come on. Come on kill the scout kill the scout
Oh, no, oh
If he had had less health I would have killed him damn it
Oh, well, at least I've killed a couple people. It's not a total failure. Let's go again
And if you're wondering if you weren't at the live stream last night, you're wondering why I'm all burnt to a crisp
That's because I was at the beach the other day
And I wanted to I wanted to get some color in my face a little bit
Before I went to Seattle for Pax Prime and I stayed out a little too long in the Sun
So hopefully I'm not a peeling mess when it comes to Pax Prime and is anybody even
Nope, whatever. I'll get away
Hopefully I'm not appealing mess before Pax Prime is what I was going to say
I probably already said that but I just want to reiterate it again. This is actually pretty fun. This is not gonna lie
This is like fun. Some stipulations are really hard already watch this
Can I oh?
Man that would have been so epic if I'd hit somebody that ran around. It's alright. It's alright. I got my charge back
Who wants a shield planted in their skull? Oh this pyro does what is this guy doing?
Come on one more time one more time. He doesn't even know he doesn't even know he doesn't even know
Come on turn around. Come on one more time one more time. Let me get it. Oh
It's alright. I'll get this by oh
You went which were you going spy you don't even trying to stay a stabby is that what you think you're gonna do
Is that what you think?
Come on why don't you stay a stabby come on? What how did that not connect? I am gonna get this spy
I am gonna get him don't he's gonna he's trying to stay a stabby. That's this is his plan. No. He's gone damn it
He's gone. No. He's right there. He's right there. Oh, I could have had him right there. I had the chance
Where is he dead? Did I get him? I don't think I got him
I don't even know if he'd done wait. Why did it make the noise? It made like the run into you noise
All right, come on. Let's go. Let's go got like a 19 second respawn. Holy Toledo
It started out pretty well. I killed like two or three people in the beginning there
live stipulation
Dot-com dot edu dot org. Oh, no, the bomb is almost reached a final terminal. All right, we got here. No
Oh, I just clicked good thing that was not a kill because otherwise I would have been eliminated
And it by eliminated. I mean just I just I swing and I lose and here we go
I got this soldier right here. I got this soldier right here. He's probably needs health. Oh
Come on. That was she was so toast. He was so dead. I'll get him again
He's gonna come around the corner and I'm going to smash him and he's gonna die
Come on before he gets the century up. Oh, he the soldier got him soldier got him. I think you are a spy
Yeah, you are
Come on, come on. Shoot me. Come on. Come on. Shoot me. No, no what what?
How did he not die? Why didn't I run into him? I can't believe you didn't die from that. Oh
You've got to be kidding me. I think we're gonna win though. That's the good thing. Come on. Come on
Come on. Come on. Come on. Come on. Come on. Come on. Come on. Oh, yeah, this is a win. This is a win
Come on. Oh
So close yet so far this guy is like he doesn't even know all right is 85
Got to do it in the look the other tool to know man, man. I could have killed that guy for sure. Oh
Fine
Fine with me man. Oh, this guy is hurt. Yes. Yeah. Oh my god. There's nothing I could do
Oh, you got I got the assist I
Gotta try and knock somebody off the edge like I did that sniper before what the hell
Why did that guy just run off the edge that guy just literally walked off the edge and I would have oh my god
Well, that's one
What is going on? Everyone's just dying. I think we're gonna win this right now though. Yes. Yes
No, yeah. Yeah, we got it for sure. Hell. Yeah, nice
Stimulation match medic heal me, please heal me. Oh, I gotta get off the cliff gotta jump off the cliff
Come on. Oh, yeah. Well, that's gonna wrap it up for face gear fortress to live stipulation match number one
I'll probably be doing these a lot more often because they're just goofy and fun and ridiculous, but I'm gonna do one more life
So I feel like I can kill one person again. Here we go. Oh too many people over there
I gotta wait till somebody is injured Wow that guy just direct shot at me. You kidding me?
This guy right here like this guy right here. This guy's dead
Oh
Come on, I don't even care if I get hit. I just gotta get him. Yes
Mmm. All right. It's up still on the same life. Come on. Can I get I want to get up there we got
Oh my god, that's a century take out the century engineers going down. Oh
That was mine. That was mine. Oh this guy's toast. He doesn't have any idea I'm behind him. Oh
Come on, come on. Oh you
Son of a
Son of a bee that spy is not one of us that spy is an enemy that spy is not one of us
That's why is you I don't I just slid off of him like he was covered in butter. I was stupid
Yikes. Oh, this is my end right here. No
Oh, well, but that's gonna wrap it up here guys. Thank you so much for watching
Really do appreciate it and I'll see you guys all next time and of course take care everybody