Ugh, I'm not gonna lie. This coffee tastes like somebody flouted in my face.
I'm currently trying to get this guy to punch this lady in the face accidentally. He's trying to punch me in the face.
I'm trying to get him to hit this old lady, and he's going to eventually.
Oh, the germa laugh.
Come on, do it again. Do it again.
Knock the lady out again.
Hold on, this cop, this cop is shooting him.
I'm moving in.
There's the guy.
I'll see you later.
How did he get up here?
Here come more people.
Oh, there's stairs.
Here comes another one.
Come on, come on down.
You can make it.
Did you think you were gonna make that?
Suspect down there.
Don't worry, I'm going in boys.
Cover me. It's only like a 200 foot drop.
Where was it?
Come down here.
No, no, please. I don't want to get in here.
No, shoot like the fence down for me or something useful.
What the heck?
I'm gonna wait.
Again.
What was he accomplishing by doing that?
You called that guy to help protect you.
That guy just gave his life to save yours.
What happened?
You better be grateful.
I was still clueless.
Okay, let the headache pass for a second.
Okay, I was...
Oh my god, there's a whole bunch of...
Oh my god, here they come.
Oh my god, that's terrifying.
This is the scariest thing ever.
Let's go, let's go.
Where are they shooting at?
Are they shooting at me or you?
They're shooting at me probably.
Why are my bodyguards not helping me?
Oh, here we go.
They're probably shooting at me.
What are they doing?
Why are your bodyguards going crazy?
No, seriously, leave me alone.
Are they chasing me?
Jerma, you better run.
Because I'm coming for you.
No, I was on your side.
I can't go that way either.
I cannot go either way.
You guys are chasing me down.
I think they stopped.
No, they didn't, they're sprinting.
They stopped, Jerma.
There better be.
I don't trust the one in the back that's crouching.
Take a screenshot.
We're going to use this for my album cover.
This guy back here, I don't trust him.
The one that's sitting back here.
I don't see one.
He's crouched, he's permanently crouched.
One just fell.
Let's go.
I want to go make sure all these guys are dead.
We can't have any more Unsullied on the streets.
Get in, quick.
This is too much.
You went too fast, too quick.
I'm going to die.
You were just dragging around a magnet.
Hello bus driver.
How are you?
It's 7th and 24th street, please.
I would appreciate it if you were on the double, by the way.
I have a kid's birthday party I'm going to.
Thank you.
This looks good right here.
I think I'm going to get out right at this moment.
The second your character stepped out of the bus,
it was all a hell.
Everything was controlled until that moment.
Like the very tip?
Yes. Enjoy.
I'm going to be fine.
I'm going to land right in the water and be completely fine.
Wow, that was amazing.
You have to do that again.
That was unbelievable.
Hey, this is a good boat view.
Look at the birds up there.
I'm in the boat holder.
It's the perfect size to be a boat holder.
Let's put this up on the shelf, Ma.
I'm in the boat holder.
I'm going to take my boat out today, guys.
This guy's a fat fuck.
Is that the funniest thing you've ever seen?
I've never seen a guy in GTA that was this gross.