Here we go. Oh man, that was not a good idea.
Hey, this is gonna take me like five minutes to do this.
No, actually I'm... timer. Let's see how long it takes me to clear this room
because I kind of have to because look at all the stuff you get.
This is ridiculous. This is gonna take me like 15 minutes to do this,
isn't it? I don't know. Alright, so here we are guys.
You want to talk about value of an item early? Oh my god.
If you get card against humanity and you have a room that is this big,
a big room like this, and you go in and you use it,
I don't even know how much money is on the ground here and how many
like spirit hearts and evil hearts. Like, let's find out.
Ready? Look at the timer too. I only used two bombs.
This took me like seven and a half minutes. Let's see. Ready? Look at the
counter. There's like dimes in here and stuff.
Like, I'm gonna break the game. Can you go past 99?
Because I'm going to. Like, really. Hey, what is going on everybody?
Jirba here with the Binding of Isaac Rebirth.
This is the reimagining and redoing of the Binding of Isaac.
It's now on Steam. I'm sure you've probably heard of this game by now.
It's pretty popular. It's become a somewhat cult phenomenon.
This game has been over the last couple of years with good reason.
Because it's fun, it's really interesting, and it has a lot of replayability. I
think I put somewhere around a hundred hours or two
hundred hours or so into the last Binding of Isaac game.
And this is not a sequel. So this is just the read.
Ooh, already right off the bat. We got a robo baby.
So I really don't think I need to explain what this game is.
Because a majority of us all know what it is. It's just a better version of the
Binding of Isaac. With a ton of extra stuff and a bunch
more content. And I'm playing as Sampson, who is an unlockable character.
I don't know if this was a good idea for me to do this or not because I'm
not particularly great with the low damage characters, but he gets this thing
called rage where the more you hit people, the more you go
and you see, for instance I'm getting hit already.
Jerma just talks and then just gets hit by enemies that are incredibly easy to
dodge. It's time to happen again. I told you.
Told you! Alright, but I'm going for a mom killer, I'm going for a heart
kill. And let's hope we can get that in this live session, because that's what
this is. I'm just recording the game. Maybe I'll
make a bunch of- I'm- I'm- I'm- I'm- I'm- I'm- I'm- I'm- I'm- I'm- I'm- I'm- I'm- I'm- I'm- I'm- I'm- I'm- I'm- I'm- I'm- I'm- I'm- I'm- I'm- I'm- I'm- I'm- I'm- I'm- I'm- I'm- I'm- I'm- I'm- I'm- I'm- I'm- I'm- I'm- I'm- I'm- I'm- I'm- I'm- I'm- I'm- I'm- I'm- I'm- I'm- I'm- I'm- I'm- I'm- I'm- I'm- I'm- I'm- I'm- I'm- I'm- I'm- I'm- I'm- I'm- I'm- I'm- I'm- I'm- I'm- I'm- I'm
I'm- I'm- I'm- I'm- I'm- I'm- I'm- I'm- I'm- I'm- I'm- I'm- I'm- I'm- I'm- I'm- I'm- I'm- I'm- I'm- I'm- I'm- I'm- I'm- I'm- I'm- I'm- I'm- I'm- I'm- I'm- I'm- I'm- I'm- I'm- I'm- I'm- I'm- I'm- I'm- I'm- I'm- I'm- I'm- I'm- I'm- I'm- I'm- I'm- I'm- I'm- I'm- I'm- I'm- I'm- I'm- I'm- I'm- I'm- I'm- I'm- I'm- I'm- I'm- I'm- I'm- I'm- I'm- I'm- I'm- I'm- I'm- I'm- I'm
Actually, wait, hold on a second. Hold on. Just a second here
Just a second. I can't believe that fly was hitting me. I really can't believe it
Famine. All right, time to be quiet because Jerma can't talk and play games at the same time
This guy's not bad. He just spawns the flies and I've got technology, baby
So this should go fairly well and I have rage as you can see my character is getting even angrier at the situation at hand
So he does more damage
There we go. Okay things are back on track as they say and I got the bandage which if you remember from the last game
This is the super meat boy
Equivalent of it being bandage girl. So let's go. Mmm spiders spiders
Damn it when I play this game
I feel like I need to have a swear jar because when I'm not recording if that just happened right there
I would have been like fuck so I need to open up like a swear jar fund
Like donate it to charity or something. What's going on? What the fuck is happening right now? What is going on?
What the hell was that? He's so
All right, that was odd. Why did my game just speed up by like three times? Ooh, I will take that money
I really don't know what the hell was that. I'm gonna like watch that back and probably throw up
Don't get hit by the easiest enemy. Come on now secret room could be up there, but I'm not gonna do it
I don't want to see what else I potentially can do in these other rooms
Okay, I like how I can see how long this video is so far four minutes. All right, speed it up
Let's go. You gotta get to them. We gotta get a mom's heart in like ten minutes
It's not gonna happen
I do want to keep those guys locked in over on the right because I don't want to open that up
Because once that opens the other guy will run out and make my day very very bad. I don't want a bad day
I want a good day. Damn it. Can you can that go through rocks? No, I guess not. I
Guess not. Okay, you are now free. I have 99 bombs. What are you doing? Just blow them up
Did I like forget that I had 99 bombs and you know
I thought for a second because I was talking I thought that was
The blast damage one not the actual 99 bombs one, but that should get rid of all of them
It does. All right secret room hunt time. I'm gonna say it's right here. Nope. I was wrong. No, it must be down here
Oh, I don't know actually it's to happening again. What is going on?
Why is my cave doing that? Do I have like a some messed up item that's doing this? I have technology
I have the T or Samson rage the bombs and the
Bandage something's going on here. Something is aloof because I don't have an answer to that. Ah
I don't know how to stop this
I
Don't know what to do
You know what? I think is actually going on right now guys cuz I'm running the games running at 120 frames
It's now back down to 60
It is speeding my game up when my frames per second go up
What on earth that happening at random times during when I need to dodge some of these harder boss fights is
Is not gonna be good
It's not gonna be great
It actually might get me killed but whatever we're just going to let it just do that. I guess
We'll see if it happens again. I'm gonna assume it's gonna happen again. Cuz why wouldn't it? It's happened like four times now, damn it
I can't whistle fun fact guys. I don't know how to whistle
I've tried to learn many times and it just never has happened. What is this matchbook evil up? Okay
So from my understanding
The evil stat in this game is the more evil you have the more chance you're gonna spawn a devil room
I believe I think let me just take a sip of my iced coffee and then maybe that maybe I'll figure it out that way
Yeah, yeah, it's the more evil you have the devil rooms will spawn
More or something and I guess you can get evil points by doing evil things
Like if you blow up the beggar, I think that gives you evil points. These are just think I don't know
There's a whole lot of secrets in this game as all of us are aware and I don't know like
75,000 percent of them. I only know a few things. I don't have very much stuff unlocked
I have I think I've only beaten the game like three or four times and now we're in super fast super speed mode
And what do I want now? I'm gonna blow both these so I can get the key
I apologize if that's like off-putting maybe it's because I'm recording in 60 frames a second or something
Maybe you know what? I'm gonna hold on a second
I'm gonna try to like fix this 60 what happens if you record a 60 frames per second video on YouTube and then it goes
To 30 frames per second halfway through the video. Is that gonna like break? Is my like channel gonna explode? I have no idea
Hold on. I'll be right back. Okay, I think I figured it out. Yeah, I definitely figured it out
I think we're good now if it happens again, I'm not sure what to say about this. I hate spiders
I hate spiders. I don't want to waste this run though cuz these items aren't that bad having the bandage
And here's a little trick
Here's a little tip about the bandage that I haven't really been talking about I haven't really even been doing
It does a ton of damage if you touch people with it
I'm kind of been scared to do it in this run because I've been talking and trying to introduce the video and saying hello
And everything but if you can get close enough to somebody and touch them with the bandage
It is a ridiculous damage see if I can do it here without like instantly dying and now I'm not going that close to these
Guys forget that I'll do it on the next boss
Whatever the next boss is you will see the super bandage powers and I only have one bandage. It is very very good
What's in the chest? Oh?
Pills here great luck done. Here's another thing I've noticed about this game
I feel like pills I've gotten a lot of pills that are just awful and I know that cane from the last is anything
What is good? Come on hit somebody
Come on, you gotta do like the arcing of the bullets. There we go
But I feel like there's so many bad pills in the game
Maybe I'm just having bad luck, but I
Maybe like 40% of every pill I've taken has been even not has not been terrible
I'd say it's 60% has been bad. Oh, maybe even more than that double shot. I'm okay with that
I wish it worked for the familiar to be cool. How many coins do I have enough to justify opening the store?
Probably not but I have so many bombs that I'm not using I need to just blow up all the secret room potential areas
Okay, I got some keys so the video still should be in 60 FPS by the way
I'm pretty sure I figured out that problem. I figured it. I used my
Science and I figured it out. Come on. Come on. Come on. Oh, you're these enemies. I forgot open. No
And these guys don't stop shooting either which really stinks almost just got hit by that
That would have been embarrassing that would have been embarrassing wouldn't it have been so funny thing about 60 FPS
I like haven't even watched any 60 FPS videos cuz I have Firefox and it like doesn't work in Firefox yet
And I've just been like too lazy to open up like Internet Explorer talk about like a lazy bastard, huh?
Oh 60 FPS for you videos on YouTube. I bet that's cool looking but I just I don't know
I gotta reach my arm over and click on Internet Explorer or Chrome and that's just too much work for me
My hands gonna get tired, but I will look at it now. Is it on like iPad?
I've watched videos on the iPad like in my bed just chilling out and I don't know if I've noticed a difference
Maybe I've just been tired or is it's HD only right? Isn't that one of the stipulations of using it? It's only HD
Screw it. We're going in. I have eight keys who cares
We're gonna donate some we're gonna go to
Whatever I'm gonna go to 115 because I'm not gonna get the necessary coins to be able to get to that
Which is what I want and give me these pills. I don't even care. I fought it. Hooray
Let's go the dark one I don't think I've ever fought this no first time I think I've ever seen this guy
You know I do what he does
Actually, no, maybe I have seen this guy. We'll find out if I can know no absolutely
I definitely haven't seen this before because I can't see anything
This guy's this guy's new shit. Here comes the dark. I love this double shot
Hopefully I get something cool to add on to this because the different the amount of modifiers that they put in this game and look
At that stupid item that's in the store came over here. I don't want mom's coin purse
It's a bunch of like garbage pills that I don't need won't but whoa. Whoa. Whoa. I thought that was the same one
Thought that was the same pill. All right, come on. I've had all bad ones. Give me a good one. There we go. Okay. Hmm
Super secret room. I don't know. I
Forget the criteria of soup. It's been a long time since I played Isaac
Isn't the super secret room has to be connected to one room or something like that or one door?
We're just gonna go with regular secret rooms for now. I'm not gonna get that coin. It'll kill me
We'll just kill me. That's right. I'm done. What do we got the time? Oh 14 minutes
This video is gonna be like an hour and 15 minutes long. Fuck it. Let's just go in
Hmm
Well, I don't have a space bar item
So I'm gonna use one and just use it right there because it only takes one room to recharge anyways
Which is another thing I'm happy that they did and damn it. I got stuck on the thing up down there
The recharging of items is a lot more clear in this game. It's actually just the number of rooms you have to clear
So on the top left, I just have one bar there
that means one room needs to be cleared and of course depending on if you have any of the
Like the battery or like the 9 volts and stuff to be able to reduce your charge rate
I'm sure that affects it as well. This guy's giving me a real pain in the ass
Faith up Bible tract. I don't know what this does. I'm pretty sure this just is faith up
So that means I have a better chance at finding angel rooms. I still don't know the petrified poo is just lucky
It is more lucky
I don't know feel free to scream at me in the comments of what I just did was stupid and left out there
Oh dear. Oh boy. Oh boy
double mega tears
That's so cool. All right, let's continue. He's doing a lot of damage. I forgot to show you the bandage thing
Oh, I'll do that. This is what I do. I just forget things to the right
Secret room actually might be right here. I'm gonna assume it could be right. Hooray
Just a regular chest got the bomb back and a coin. Okay, sure thing
I'm gonna go in here too because that requires two keys to open. I don't want this. I don't want this
I'm pretty sure this is going. No, I don't want that the dice room that one dice. I
It every time I've done that it is randomized every item that I currently have
So I don't want to do it because I like this setup. This is actually pretty good right now. There's a lot of damage
And it could it can only get better from here if I get like tears up or something
So I'm gonna let it be
Let's go. I have enough bombs to get it might as well go get it, right? Let's let's be go-getters a heart
Yeah, was not worth it. I don't want to die from that open
These enemies are so annoying because you have to wait till they walk at you and open that guy
I wonder how much damage I'm actually doing actually the gurdy will be a really good showcase of the bandage
So so ready I'll show it to you once I can clear this stuff out. All right, watch this ready check out the bandage
Hold on. Hold on. Hold on. Hold on. I'll get it. I don't I get the hitbox
So this is kind of weird. I need to get to a place where like right look at that. See I didn't touch him
That's just the bandage doing that. All right
I took enough damage for you to see that so if you're like good at the game and you can't like you can avoid damage
That is a huge deal
I just took like seven points of damage to show that to you and a lot of you probably already knew that was a
Good thing. So whoops devil room. Did you just teleport me to the same room? Okay, good and two troll bombs
I got what I needed out of there anything else I could go down, you know, let's screw it. We're gonna go down
We're gonna be completionists. I'm not technically but sort of what's down there. What have I not seen could just be a regular room
I don't want to die cuz seriously Samson. I'm building up such a ridiculous damage. Holy shit. I'm one hitting every enemy
I don't know what this is. What is this? I'm scared to get don't you even think about it fire. I'm scared cursed
Guppies tail. I don't know what that does. I don't know. I could just go like Wikipedia this right now, but what's the fun in that?
I want to find out I want to have it be a surprise
Okay, let's go already wasted enough time in the first like two or three areas
Let's just keep going up up and away and into the next tier of dungeons
Where are we the depths level one? Welcome young Samson
Technology baby can shoot through those so we are perfect. Oh
Come on get him you weakling use your super techno powers and shoot his face off. Good. Good job missing page
Mmm, I don't know the thing with the trinkets is I can always forget what the trinkets do
What's gonna shit all the trinkets and relics and stuff? I just never remember what they are
I could have like the stupidest worst drink at that in the game and I would I don't even know it
There's somebody in the comments right now probably like and I can't even I can't hear you. I can't hear you
You have to scream louder. I can't hear you. There you go. Now I can hear you but this run looks like it's gonna be pretty good
Considering I want this I want Bob's rotten head so I can go like this now
I have to wait three rooms for the charge again. That was not worth it
I should just be dropping bombs everywhere. Really just put them all over the place. There's no reason not to I have a million of them
Getting confused by these skulls open you fucker
You
Okay, be I need to be careful cuz I have a tendency
I'm one of those people when I play Isaac to totally lose total control and it all falls apart
It happens to me quite frequently. I'll have a cool build. I'll have something going on
I'll be like, oh, she's going good
And then I'll take like a couple points of damage in the same room and then it all falls apart and I die like in
The next room and I don't want that to happen because I'm recording this and I don't want to get embarrassed
What do you think? Should I wait for the item? Actually? I know I already
Wait, it might be a better use of these. Holy shit. This room has a lot of people in it
There could be better use of that key and there is already good thing
I didn't do it because that would have been kind of a waste kind of excuse me
Don't step on the goo on the ground and you're done too. All right, let's get another item a lot of actives
I've been not getting anything to help this build out with the double huge super shot
But this is very good too. You put a coin in and it like it does all your damage pretty much
It shakes the screen hits everybody in the room for one coin like this ready point just did it. Okay. Yeah
If I lose there's no way I lose I can clear every room no matter what watch this. I'm gonna open this door
Oh, you're all dead. Bye. See ya. Thanks. Thanks for the coin
Okay, I wish I knew what this stuff does I need to play more Isaac
So I know what things do and there's something up here to now. I'm leaving that there. That's absolutely staying there
we're gonna leave these I am also not going to use the
Store room anymore because I want to keep these coins so I can clear whole rooms in one second
That would be good to do. I think I'll open it. Come on. Give me another give my key back
Nice and that's what we call value right there. That is total value. I want to save my keys
I'm not forget the item room. Hold on to my keys and let's just keep going
It's always those little turkey guys that screw me up
I know what this does this I believe if you take damage is a chance to turn you into Pac-Man
So you better believe I'm holding on to it. Okay, how bad it is. I mean you've got to mention Pac-Man
Keeping it dude. They're gonna trash this item never I will never trash it. I'll both secret room
Could be right here. It probably is right here. No, so where is it down here? Whoa. Whoa
Forget it. No, I need that secret room because the amount of coins I have is very very big deal very important
So I have to open it like a please tell me I'm gonna hit it if I open it right here
Shit, we'll have plenty of bombs. Maybe I let it if I do it like that shit
What if I do two bombs damn it fuck? All right, so it's obviously not right there
So that means it must be over here. So you should blow these up too because there's stuff in these
There's one right there. That is a
Evil heart which if you don't know what these things do when that heart is consumed
It's the same thing as a spirit heart. It will do damage to everything in the whole room. There it is
And it's two keys which means I'm probably gonna go
Open those chests or at least one of them because then I have an extra key or maybe I'll just open the door
I don't know as a beauty of Isaac you could it there's so many different options like which one do I do?
Which do I pick do I open? Yeah, we'll just open in this and we're gonna go in here
I'm gonna attack the boss lots of items. I wonder let's see what happens if I do this not worth it
It's not doing that much damage. I'm doing so much damage with these tears anyway
So not worth doing the active item in this room at least and spray jump down here
And do the spray again. No, you're gonna jump. Yeah, I think you only spray from to the side. Yeah, no, maybe probably
But it doesn't matter you did. What am I gonna get? What am I gonna get? Oh boy
Damage up and I've cute actually cue the fool. Let's do it
I was kind of hoping it was gonna teleport me into the item room
Just because I wouldn't have to spend a key to get in there and there might be something in there that I want
But nope
No, one of these times I'm gonna do that and I'm gonna walk over it and get hurt and you're gonna hear me scream
Okay, let's go in. This is the part at this point. This is where mom is
So I wonder if we're going to do goodbye whole room then I wasn't even gonna think to deal with that room
No way can forget that room 48-hour energy just gives you a battery. No, we're not dealing with this room either
All right, do I try to get some coins let's I'm gonna bring this down to ten, okay
Give me this coin. Come on. I need this you fuck and now we're just gonna take out the whole room
Didn't get my coins, but I will get probably one or two here. No, I didn't even mean to pick that up shit cuz I need
Well, that's not cool. I really didn't want to pick that up, but I did cuz I'm a klutz. Hey look another room
I don't want to deal with okay, so we won't deal with it. Do you see how awesome this item really is?
It's just you pay one coin to destroy everything
Don't think I need to do it here
And plus I'm gonna hold on to that for the womb because there are some really awful rooms in the room
So from now on conserve my financials
conserve actually still might be able to get the benefit from the heaven heart or the
Good heart would be want to call it smart fly revenge fly. I believe if I take damage this thing goes after
Enemies in the room. So pretty cool
Don't want to do that yet. We've got more stuff to explore like this room with the bone people get out of here
You bone people somebody bombs. I just don't know what to do with them all
I wish I could trade the technology baby for something because he's kind of I mean he's doing a little bit of work
But not even close to the amount of work that that massage machine is doing. You know, we're gonna hold the coins
No reason to do it. Mmm secret room. I wonder maybe down here. Maybe no, maybe down here
Another one of these trolley type rooms
Excuse me. This guy's still doing standing here. Come on. Give me a chance to shoot you not fair. Well
I'm not entirely sure maybe if I go in the item
No, I don't check this I already did check that didn't I yeah, and it wasn't there
So it must be somewhere down here. Watch out and I don't think so. No
mmm up here
Spending a lot of time trying to find this secret room when I should just I should just go to mom greed
This is amazing. By the way guys just realized how awesome it was for me to find greed right there
Cuz look at all these coins. I have no look at the amount of times. I'm gonna be able to you
Oh boy, I'm just gonna walk in and just totally roll rooms in the womb. No one's gonna even hurt me
Nobody will hurt me once in the womb. That's a bold statement to make but what is going on here?
These are the guys that disappear right they have stealth and another heart. I'm just gonna pick it up because it doesn't matter
I already gonna get a completed one. Okay time to go
I have a ton of confidence in this run a ton. Can you hear it in my voice?
I mean we're talking we're talking 60 frames per second. We're talking 60 FPS here guys. That's how much confidence I have
I'm uploading in 60 frames a second. Here's mom. Hello mother. Whoa, everything's like blue
Oh, I'm pac-man. Oh, yeah. Oh my god. Look at pac-man's doing so good
That run was just saved by pac-man. There it is. Please give me coins ace of spades
No, no, nobody's gonna give me coins. I'm gonna keep pac-man cuz this kind of is like an oh shit button
Even though I don't activate it. It's still it's just like oh shit. It's okay. You're pac-man. Here we go. Here we go
We are now entering the womb and I didn't pick up cue the fool again, which is dumb, but watch this guys
Oh, hey, haha. What? Oh, it's cuz they're not the heads are not okay. This is wasted two coins. That was really stupid
I didn't even need to use them. I just got scared
Hello room. Goodbye room. I said I wasn't gonna wasn't gonna take damage in this womb
Well, it almost just wasn't true. Goodbye
Hey, look look at me. Hi. Oh, wow. Those guys had a lot of help. Oh, look a room full of shit
No, not anymore. This is amazing. This item is so good
It's so good. Oh, why is my game lagging? I'm lagging. No, not at this time
This is I'm doing such a great run. I hope my computer doesn't crash man. Goodbye
Let's just let's just go screw it right? I mean, why not just screw it? Let's just go
We're gonna beat the game like in the next five minutes
I don't even have any tears up or anything, but I'm gonna just blow through this. Yeah
My only concern is when we get to the heart and there's a devil room. I wonder what's in there a couple of keys. Oh
Is that ah, I don't you know what?
I'm not gonna risk it cuz I forget I know this is a familiar
But I don't know what this is and frankly right now the familiars
I don't even care about the familiars because my tears do so much damage and I have the massage machine thing
So I don't think it matters. I'm not gonna waste a heart where it's not necessarily when it's not necessarily
Let's go speed run you what you guys want to talk about a speed run
I mean, come on speed run right now that got 32 minutes. We're talking about a speed run lust and you are gone
Don't know what this does. Are you a wizard? No, I'm not but this only lasts
I believe like a minute or so or a room or two. So I'm okay with this actually. I hope it wears off
You know what? I don't I don't I don't thank goodness you blocked that fly or maybe it was the bandage
Guys taking a lot of damage geez. Oh, that's cuz he's like a mini boss finally at war off right when we get to the boss
I'm going right in guys. I'm not wasting any time because I might be able to get this to
To
One of the harder places which would be cool. See you later. And we also another damage up. Holy shit
I'm I must be at man. I'm at max damage. There's no way I wouldn't be I love how you can just do that
Hey, you ever play like the game binding of Isaac before it just press the space bar with coins with the damage up items
You win the game. Whoa, that didn't happen instantly. I thought they were all gonna die got my coins up again, which is good
Don't even want to deal with you don't want to deal with you don't want to deal with this room either
So yeah, but I do want this chest. I would be singing a totally different tune guys if
Yeah, I don't want screw that I would be singing a completely different tune if I didn't have this item and look at all these
These coins they want me to win. They want me to win this
They I the binding of Isaac gods have determined that I'm going to win that's what they've decided today
We're just gonna go. Let's go mom's heart. Oh, hey, look guys like I'm playing the game
No, we don't have an opportunity to go to
one of the other places like heaven or
Or the chest or whatever or shull shale shull. How is it pronounced? Well, yeah, that that's uh, what is it? 35 minutes?
That's not that bad. I'm not bad for a beginner