Hey, what is going on everybody Jerma here with face cam fortress 2 and I'm here with a couple of other dudes
Of course should be 2142 and MLC stealth go and introduce yourselves dudes. So what's going on guys ships here?
Hey guys should be 2142 here. So, uh, yeah, we're playing some man-up mode
So that means we're spending tickets and we're doing this on cool town. Which one are doing the CPU slaughter or uh, this is I
Think this is CPU slaughter. It's not control. I'll delete. I don't think yeah, it is if you'll tab you can see so
So I was waiting for a German to ready up for me
Yeah, a little sniper action going on here playing as the scouts stealth. What are you the demo man? Mm-hmm? Yeah
Oh, look at that little thing you got and yeah, I guess my joke wasn't very funny about me saying I should be 21 for this
No, that's very insensitive
Sorry
Just kidding. I love you. Get rid of the tank. Get rid of the tank shoot it those heavies though. Oh
Leg
Yikes, I'm gonna go behind those guys
Try and take all those medics actually, yeah, I'm not doing a whole lot damn
Right. Oh, thanks down. Oh
That's not a good idea
Come on snipers
Should be so many look at how many people down there right now
What like I had some crazy hit detection going on here. Give me the money. Give me the money. Oh
There's a lot of money down here. It's so many kills
Yeah, it's a lot of money down by those heavies. I just picked up a lot. There's one more little piece of money
Uh, so the viewers know what uh, what uh, what are you guys rocking right now? I am using the cool
Sticky launcher and that's it
I'm using the force of nature the mad milk and the candy cane
To get that health from killing these robots
I'm using the heat maker. Oh, yeah, pretty interesting once you get the focus
All right. We got all the money watch out for the sniper. I
Didn't kill him right there. I have so many the sniper watch the wrong my god right side right side
There's a ton of people they're all just walking over there right now
They're all going up
I'm trying to pick up the buddy
I'm just like hiding back it trying to pick off. Oh my gosh. Yeah, I know there's a million people there
We got the way got all the money. What are we missing? We're missing. Oh for snipers. Oh
Where's this last piece of money? Where's the $13 got it? All right. Oh, yeah, there's just a bunch of snipers now
This guy right here
Another one up here. Don't kill me, please. Oh
My god, I got him he's dead
They don't drop money, right? Nope. Wait, who are the snipers now? The snipers don't so where's this $13?
I just killed a medic down there
Did I get it? Oh, did I not there's more money somewhere over here give me it. Oh, I didn't get it all
Sure, huh? Now there's nothing I could do go attack all those heavies Jerma. What do you think? Yeah, I'm gonna
Go like bye-bye something get myself smoked
Man, oh man with that money go let's Jerma. Did you say what you know? I got it. I got it
No, I didn't get it. What what?
Yeah, I said the force of nature. Oh
I'm covered in pee right now
I'm just trying to kill this stupid medic right here. So my back get it. This medic is dead medic is dead
These freakin heavies man. I swear to god. Well, I was still missing that 13. We're gonna miss it till the end. Oh, well
Sorry, but I bet you saw it on the ground. You just don't walk over to it cuz you don't want pick it up. I
I don't understand why I'm getting a pocket medic as sniper but
What else? Oh still you just died man. Who put that gravity in the server?
I pretty much all decked out in this
resistance and
Good go with super boobies being I'm not even touching this really at all
Just going for like super money collection, but time to beef this thing up a little bit
Cuz I got all my resistances all the way up bang bang. All right
Ready when you guys are with spy support is the worst spa sapping my bum. Oh
He's happy my bum
Is this video going up while we're at Pax term? It is tomorrow. It's gonna be going up on Friday
Okay, so happy Friday if you see in that happy TG IF
Thank Gavin. It's Friday. Well, wait a minute. I wouldn't are you are you putting this up on Friday as well? Yeah, I'll do it
All right. Well, then yeah, then hey, what what did I have scheduled for Friday? I think I had a daisy helicopter video
We could always say it's any of the days of the week watch the video. Yeah, it's probably up now
I wouldn't say go that far
Just like tapes
All right
What I didn't even see what we had this round two big heavies two big soldiers all I saw was spy support
I cried
Get the money get the money. Oh for those of you watching right now
There's something I did not even know and why I never wanted to play scout for a man versus machine you get
Overhealed for every single dollar you collect. I did not know I have like 500 health right now, right? Yeah
I get full of a 400 right now. It's just like are you serious? That's insanity. It's by support
Wow, oh that was a spy right there. I thought they spawned behind us. I do that guy just spawned right in my face
That guy legit was just right. They're smart, man. Yeah, they get a huge upper hand. Give me the money
They know I didn't yeah. No, I didn't it's up here. Well, there's still $22 missing. Where is it?
Oh, I couldn't have even gotten it. It was all the way back here behind the uh, oh no, we are really no
We got it. We got it. That was weird. I was like weird glitch
Oh, yeah, I have no health gosh. Oh, thanks for mad milk in those. I actually got health back because of them
That's what I'm here. This is margin Ford. There's no health. He's almost dead. Yeah, just get rid of him. Yeah
Hooray, it's more more spy. Okay, watch out money. They're like spawn on us
Oh, if you're watching this video, right and you're wondering why if you're wondering why I keep hitting tab to look at the like the scoreboard
I'm looking at the money collected see in the lower left collected and missed
That's so I can tell if I've missed the money. Oh, oh my god
I just went a thousand free there. Help me die
This guy's coming to milk you can stand while picking your nose up for a second. Hey Rockets money money money
Money, yeah, just try to pick those pick those medics off. Oh, there's a bunch of money back here. Oh
Oh
Bomb all right, these guys both have used their uber trying to kill the medic only I had more
Yes, run. All right. That guy does not have any more medics on the right neither
Does this so no this he just uber damn it. You're a spy right now. Wait, you're a spy
That's that was a spy for sure got all the money so far. Oh, no, you guys are right over there. No, yes
No
No, this medic this medic just ubered. I didn't get him. So we have a giant heavy
Alright, just focus on the soldier. He's gonna he still has a medic on him
Our bomb is about to be destroyed. Yeah, I got the money right? Yeah
That makes me happy that makes me real here a ton of scouts on the left. Holy crap
Oh, just don't let him in do not let these bastards in this is it. This is it. This is why this is why so
everywhere
One more last round. Oh, okay. I was I was spending money like it was last wave
Okay, what I got fully upgraded that yeah, this sniper's a little okay clip size
And ready up. We'll go with that. Ah, no spy sport. We're also gonna go with an uber canteen
Because I feel like it. All right, three tanks two deflectors. Oh
Really the tanks. I'm not that worried about it deflectors on the other hand
Yeah, I was a dude deflectors come with three or more medics usually. Um, well, there's 18 total medics
So I'm assuming that they're gonna be
Spread out six each nine each. Well, I mean they could be on the the heavies as well
Medics could be on tanks. They'll be so unfair. I'd be really easy because kill the medic
They're all
All 18 minutes. Oh, they're just but the tank you have to beat the way before the tank with the uber
Alright, this is sniper support though. This could be a real pain in the ass. So
Be careful facing snipers is so scary. There's like ten at a time and like nobody has like killed
Yeah, it is pretty terrifying like the wave gets pushed back so all the snipers like merge into one position and you just like
Walk to the front lines and just
And our heavy has invested in jump height. Wait, did he really wait? Hold on. Yeah. Oh
My god, well done like this just so what just so we can do like a what is it called a triple?
What's it called? What's the ice skating move? I'm just watching his robot. That's the best part
Triple let's let's what the hell
I thought it was like a wangu triple ax triple axle triple axle. There you go
I saw the puzzle someone told me if you shoot the tracks on the sides, it does more damage that person might say
Let's see. I don't think it's true. I don't know if it's true. I
Like that we can pretend it's true though
Well, no my god me you'll need to get that I'm gonna run right into the line of fire here
Yeah, actually money is is kind of important to sniper get out of he's gonna kill me with his stupid
Club. Yeah, go ahead. Try and hurt me. I got massive resistance, baby
Wait, what's this guy say about fake shibby? Oh fake shibby just added me to friends. Really nice. It's probably probably cool
Night where this guy's gonna try and club me again. Oh, these guys are all covered in milk have at it
It's a lot of rockets go from behind
Collect the money. Yeah
snipers everywhere
Yeah, Oh big heavy snipers, this is incredibly fun because I've I've such oh kill the max
I'm gonna take care of the snipers taking care of the snipers got him another one over here, huh?
Snipers are all gone. Just being heavy
Dead
Yeah, make sure you use your money cuz this is it. Oh my god snipers literally all over the place
You shouldn't have used that milk
Are you even playing on our team?
That Jerma is not one of us that Jerma is an enemy that
Lasers on Jerma. Yeah big heavy on the left and he's gonna be covered with milk. No, he's not not yet
Medic is not dead. Yes. He's dead get health heal off of that guy
Man, there are a lot of snipers in this round another tank another tank ton of soldiers, too. Oh
My goodness, I just like I just knocked that guy over the fence
No, are you serious?
What haven't you I got stuck in a corner Jerma a bunch of uh with a bunch of with a one sniper
So it's a bunch. Yeah, get rid of these scouts and Jerma is not all of us
He is not that Jerma is a piece of crap
Rockets. Oh my god frame rate. No, I mean that money. Give me that money. Give me that money. Oh, he's waving
Kill the stupid sniper
Are you guys getting leg spikes every now and then you're just I am I am I am getting them
I got spent some money Michael bag back in get rid of that sent for Buster. Go go go last tank
So I got any milk yet. No
No, I need to get some of that money is any money even like dropping I feel like it's not even like I'm dead
I'm so dead. I covered him with milk though. Yeah, I don't think people aren't even like dropping money
I think I'm going crazy
No, no one's dropping money man, we have all the money we have 700. Oh, hi. Yeah. Hi
I don't know what this game is. So it's only second
And oh my god, what'd you get for items?
It's great
Power of duty. Oh, somebody had a thing of duty
Surplus ticket. Thanks. It's a
Thanks H and G. Hell. Yeah. Thanks, dude. You got a frontier justice cuz it's good
Tommy's law. Yes
Dollars all time. We suck. Yeah, that was the very beginning very the waves go
Forgot to get $13 that one time. I take all the blame. But uh, yeah, thanks a lot
Gents, so uh, yeah guys that was CPU slaughter man up mode man up mode
Thank you guys for watching and yeah, hopefully we'll have some packs videos of whatnot and fun and that's pretty much it
So any last words boys? I don't know. Take care everybody. See you all soon