Alright, sorry I ruined the birthday. I walked back into the door, and I... I didn't forget that this was here, but I kind of... kind of did.
And I walked... I took down the... I walked into the thing that was hanging.
Okay, so now that was a ton of fun. I'm really surprised I had that much fun on Roblox.
I thought that was going to be like 20 minutes of just like, oh, whatever, let's just play something, or like an hour or something.
That was really fun. Yeah, I walked into the banner. I'll show you.
Um, let me turn my switch on. What about Five Nights at Freddy's?
I think Ster was just tired, and he just was like, taking off.
Because it's, uh, yeah, we're late night Andes over here.
That's it. We'll do it again. We'll do something else later. That's fine.
I want to play that game, uh, with Poke2, the scary one. Let me make sure I am capturing this correctly.
One, one sec.
They're making a new BNAF movie. Holy shit.
Yeah, actually, when I was VRV, Polly was like, I thought you were hot micing.
No, I'm just stupid and had my desktop audio muted.
Uh, why is my switch not working?
Um, is this not even plugged in? Oh, shit. Hold on.
Give me one more second. I got to plug. I unplugged the switch for something else.
Okay. Wait, did you not hear when I said I was going to leave? Wait, what?
I said I had to plug my switch in because it was unplugged.
You didn't hear that? Wait, what?
My audio is not delayed still, is it? It shouldn't be. That's weird. Okay.
Alright, let me just plug my headphones in. You should be able to see it now.
Or in a second.
Hey, there it is. Uh, let me just plug my actual headphones in.
Alright, it's time to play.
What was the last thing I did? What did I do last?
I do need to do this.
And if I'm going to have any face cam, I need to do this.
Like this. Hold on.
Oh, you want to see the, uh, yeah. Here, I'll show you.
Oh, hold on. I fucked it up. Did I fuck it up?
Uh, yeah, I accidentally walked into it. I tore it down.
I hit my fucking head on the birthday.
No, I ducked. I was ducking down. That would mean I was very small.
Well, it's okay. Let me fix this because I need to delay this camera.
That should do it.
Alright, I am officially ready to play Breath of the Wild.
Happy. And get...
Rip the decorations down when you fuck a puzzle up?
Alright, this is the last Divine Beast.
But I don't want to do that right now. I think I want to do...
What are some side... There's, like, the trials, right?
Should I do those? Go get your horse? Bottom right.
Am I going to play Minecraft again?
There's an island with a really cool side quest down here.
Check it out. Ignored? What happened?
What did I ignore? Ignore what?
Oh, the horse. That's right. I'm imagining it's probably over here.
Not the horse, but this... Is this the island down here you're talking about?
Ooh, there is an island down... Wait, I was here before.
Isn't there, like, a big troll here?
Is this a stupid thing I'm doing?
I think I'm going to make it. I think I'll be alright.
I have stamina drinks.
Can you finally sing Happy Birthday?
Yeah, I said I wasn't, but fine.
Happy birthday to you. Happy birthday to you.
Happy birthday to... Whoever you're watching.
Whoever's watching, right? And you distracted me.
And you just probably got me killed.
How do I get down there?
Do I just have to make it with stamina?
I need stamina potions.
I think I have some, don't I?
Nah, this is haste.
Is there any stamina food?
I need a boat. Stamina potions.
Maybe I can't do it yet. Stealth. Cook a durian.
Well, I definitely can't do it yet.
There's a boat to your left.
Ooh, wait a minute. Over there?
Yeah, I think I remember that.
Actually, I can make this too, right?
I can teleport to the shrine. What am I doing?
My mom said you made her day by playing Roblox.
It was fun. That was some of the most fun I've had on stream, I think, in...
I don't know. It's been, like, a month or two. That was awesome.
That was just super fun, super funny.
There we go. Ooh, wait.
I need a leaf or something, don't I?
Isn't there usually, like, a leaf? What was that?
Cut a tree down? Oh, there it is.
I'm going to drop. What should I drop?
I'm dropping this. I can get it later.
Drop the Master Sword? That would be awful.
I'm going to turn that thing back on.
This is to get one of those seeds.
Hurry up! Got it.
Yeah, I need way more of these.
All right, that's the destination, right?
What the hell am I doing?
Okay, turn it.
What a gamer.
All right, so what did I do wrong?
Oh, I thought...
He's throwing rocks at me.
Is there still an after party going on at the fashion contest?
That's the... I love it.
After party.
All right.
So, even tied up.
So, even tied island.
You who has traveled to this island,
I present you the challenge.
In your travels, you've relied on the equipment...
Oh, that's right. It takes all your equipment and shit.
Offer up the orbs to the three altars on the island,
only them you... Okay.
So, three orbs.
All right. Is it puzzle stuff in this?
Oh, it's going in E mode only? Oh, no.
Uh...
Yeah, it's a big puzzle, isn't it?
All right. We're good. We're good. We're good.
I got a stick.
Oh, I don't have a bow. Shit.
Bananas.
30 minutes?
This is not going to take 10 minutes?
You're saying 30 minutes?
There's an axe right there.
I didn't even fucking jump.
Okay. Woodcutter's axe.
All right. So, I'm going to cut down some trees.
Okay.
Wood. Okay.
I probably need a bunch of wood.
I got three wood.
I don't think I have any... I don't want to die.
Ooh. Okay. Good. I still have this.
Should I eat the bananas or should I cook the bananas?
Probably cook, right? Yeah. All right.
I'm going to cook. Wait. I need something to light it.
No. No, no, no. I need something to light it.
I could fight these guys.
Shit. That's a lot of
nose. You guys don't think I can do it?
That's a ton of...
That's way too many nose.
I got it. All right. Here's one.
Ooh. Bow. Good. Soldier's bow.
What?
Okay. I got one.
I need three. What do I bring
these? Wait. There's a fire right here.
All right. Should I cook individual
bananas? Roasted mighty
banana. It doesn't do anything. How is
that any better than a regular
banana? Okay. Let's do this.
A couple bananas.
This should be pretty good.
Wait. It's not a stove. Pick it
all up. Oh, shit.
It's not a stove.
Okay.
What do I take this?
Isn't it up? All right. I'm going to go up.
I think it's actually up. I'm
90% certain that it's on one of the mountains.
No, no, no. Wait. There's one
kind of on the beach, right?
Please don't wake up.
Why did you let
go of it? Why did I let go of it?
What? All right.
I need this. Right there.
I need to just despawn this guy.
All right. Get out of here. Get the fuck out of here.
Okay.
You can't run with this. How are they so
accurate? This is going to unlock
something, probably, right? I hope so.
Why are you laughing at me? It's not funny yet.
It's not funny yet.
Okay. Hold on.
Shit. I'm terrified
of this. Can I
golf it over there?
Am I going to lose it if I go in here with this?
I am, aren't I? No?
Wait. I'm not going to. I won't lose it.
This is very conflicting.
I don't know what to do.
I have an idea. All right.
I'm not supposed to do it like this. I'm just
going to go for it and whatever happens happens because I'm just
going to test and see if this is even possible.
Am I going to lose this shit?
No. This is bad. This is a bad idea.
Is there another spot on the map
where one of those is?
Don't even do that.
Rebranch?
I'm so paranoid just to walk over there
with it. I probably can just
walk over there. Whatever.
People are going to laugh at me. It's fine.
Okay. I didn't lose it though. I had the right
idea. I thought it was going to disappear.
Yeah. I was just paranoid that it wasn't going to go away.
Like it was just going to disappear.
Let's go. All right. There's
one. What does that do?
Okay. So I got
I just put free in there and I'm good.
What is happening? Thank God.
I just did that. That would have been a
disaster. Okay.
There are two more balls on the island.
Got to find them. That was almost
frame perfect. I'm going to have to kill
that thing, aren't I, eventually? I'm going up.
I know there's another one up there. I remember
seeing it. So the play is just don't
aggro the big guy, right?
That's what I would think.
Oh shit. There's another one.
Oh.
It'll get solid.
Do they notice this?
Ah! How do I move this?
Wait. Will that, does that actually work?
That's going to get struck by lightning, right?
Do I have to have it equipped? How do I get this
to strike? Come on.
I don't even know who I'm walking onto.
Go. Come on.
Where's the flurry? You got
to be fucking kidding me, dude. Can I
stand up here? There's a spot right there.
Come on. No!
Yes.
Oh, thank God. I'm so relieved. Thank goodness.
Don't get greedy. Just climb.
If I just do it normally, I'll be fine.
Just do it normally. Yes. All right.
Do I have any food? I do.
I'm just eating them. Okay. Can I
clear it with my lightning move?
I just killed everything else.
I wasn't even close. I just killed everything else
in the whole map. What?
Oh, I can cook here. All right.
Let me clear this.
All right. We're good.
Now I can take a good look and figure this out.
Arrows. Food.
Hell yeah. All right. I can cook now.
Ooh. Somebody said to find one of those. I just found one.
Happy birthday.
Take a picture and then kapow.
I gotta delete some of these pictures. What's this?
Pretty cool rock. Shit.
How do I break it? Smash. Kapow.
Smash. I did not even know
this was small, like big enough to do this with.
I thought it was too big.
All right. Nice. That's two.
There's only one more. Nice.
All right. One more. We're good.
So where's this last one?
Let me cook some food for us.
You got ten minutes left. Oh, I got...
I got ten minutes for each ball.
I'm gonna be close. All right. I'm gonna pay attention.
I need fire.
All right. Where's this last one?
It's on his neck. All right. Watch this.
I'm gonna drop this on this fucking guy's head.
Come on, Link. You can do it.
Come on. Push it. You can do it. I know you can.
Perfect.
Perfect. Crush his head.
Shit. I just killed a fucking
goat accidentally. All right.
I thought it was gonna roll.
I'm gonna walk this down. Wait, wait, wait.
I want to bring this too. Where is it?
I'm gonna be strategic. This is the last one.
I gotta be strategic. It respawned.
It wants me to do that, I think. I think it wants me to do that.
It wants me to crush him. Look.
It's back. It's back.
It's right here. It wants me to crush him.
That's not bad.
God damn it.
All right. It hit him.
At least it hit his ass.
How do I get him? I get it. Uh-oh.
It hit him right in the fucking head.
Why would I have this equipped?
Why did I have this equipped?
What the hell?
I'm alive.
I'm alive. I'm alive. I'm alive. I'm alive. I'm alive. I'm alive.
I need more arrows.
That's the problem.
There's a lizard here. Don't hit me. Please don't hit me.
Please get up.
Climb.
Holy shit. Look at this. Oh my god.
This is bad. Oh my god.
He's coming up. He's coming up. He's coming up. He's coming up.
Hold on. Do not blow those up, please.
I need those.
My lightning move isn't cooled down.
What's wrong with him?
What's he doing?
What is he doing?
Everybody fuck off for a second.
Just get out of the fucking way.
Oh.
That didn't even hurt him.
What am I doing?
I'm zooming in on his crotch.
Fine. I'm fine.
I am going to be just fine.
I just have to smear this all over his fucking head a few more times.
Get out of here.
You fuck off. Can I punch you?
Oh, let's go.
Oh.
I got him. Stop.
Stop moving. Stop moving. Stop moving.
So close.
Stop. You have what?
It's not over? What do you mean?
What time is it?
31 minutes.
I didn't know that lightning instantly killed him.
I didn't have it charged either.
It spawns one of these.
Now there's a shrine up there.
I'm going to enter the shrine.
You could have just walked up and taken his necklace while he was sleeping.
Oh.
That's good to know.
What's wrong with my face?
My face is kind of weird.
It was really close?
I should probably cook some food, but I'm not going to.
That was fun.
Is there an easy way to get up here?
It's fine.
Alright, so what's in here?
Your eyes are all messed up?
Something in my teeth?
Everyone's cyberbullying him.
Dude, Roblox was so fun.
We should definitely do it again.
300 rupees. Okay, I'll take it.
Oh, also, people started getting the grotto beasts.
We've seen a lot of people writing
like, hey, look what I got.
Look what I got. Look what I got.
I think a lot of the kits have gone out.
If you have ordered it, keep an eye out.
I would anticipate it very soon
if you ordered it in the first week or so of the presale.
Got mine yesterday.
Also, the FAQ
and the
quick start rules should be on
the site now.
They should be there on the bottom of the page.
It should be like a PDF or something.
So, a while back
I talked about the baby
being a digital version. So, over the last
I want to say a couple weeks, two or three weeks
we've been really trying to figure out what that
meant and what a digital
version was going to be. So,
I will tell you right now what we are
doing right now, what we're exploring right now, and it's
currently the thing that we are
doing. We're going to do a tabletop simulator
mod, a free mod
that, there's a person here,
is going to have all 200 cards available.
And the idea was to make it so
so the
actual experience is not going to be like
card pack pay openings
or anything. It's not like, oh yeah, let's
buy more card packs digitally.
We understand that there's a lot
of people that want to play with other people that just
don't really have any way to do that
because there is a game, right? There's a game on top
of it. So,
the game designer
and we're going to get some
other people like
the core art team and maybe
a 3D designer is going to come in and
we're going to make a whole experience in tabletop simulator.
Just tons of
little toys and it's going to be a whole
experience. It's not just going to be, here's a
wooden desk with all 200 cards. Good
luck. They're going to dev it out.
So, if you don't have tabletop
simulator, that's, I mean
I think that, it goes on sale
a lot, doesn't it? I think it's pretty cheap too.
I think it's only like, what, 10, 15 bucks?
20 bucks? Yeah, very often.
But it also gives an opportunity for the, so the
game designer is going to be
kind of curating that space
on top of the art team. So
it's just going to be free. You can
have fun, play with it, play with your friends.
That's kind of the idea.
I'm seeking adventure.
You and I have that in common. It is only from here
that I can probably hear the wind.
I want to live as the wind does, free and unrestricted
to bide here and listen to
its voice offers a taste of that freedom.
Don't you long to be like the wind
too? It didn't really occur to me.
We can read the messages ourselves.
These?
You don't want me to read them to you?
Okay. Is there anything else
to do with this bird? Have you returned a train
to become the wind?
Okay. 20 rupees
to set it, alright, let's go.
Wait here while I prepare the course. Obstacle course?
So I gotta fly through these?
Gotta go faster than this.
Daruk's protection is now ready to roll.
Goku? No.
All the way up. Oh, over here.
Whoops. Wait, go down.
Oh!
I gotta go.
Wait, what happened? Why do I have no stamina?
Am I gonna fall?
Wait, why did I run out of stamina?
Do I not have enough stamina to do it?
I need to eat stamina food.
23 rings.
He gave me my money back.
You know what, here, take it back.
Let's do it again.
Release the glider when you're descending.
Oh, that's true.
Alright, let's go.
Do I have an opportunity to release it though?
How did I not go through it?
Oh!
Shit, alright, I gotta...
That's a tricky one.
Let go in the middle and then press it again?
No, I wanna do it again.
You gonna beat the game tonight?
No, no, I'm just gonna do some side stuff.
Eat stamina food. I don't have any.
I'm gonna have to come back here when I do.
I went through it.
You saw me do that. I went right through the middle.
What the fuck just happened?
Whatever, I got 25.
Okay, I made money. I wanna do it again.
That's the end of the course, right?
Is that the end? Oh, it's not.
Did you actually play Roblox?
Yeah, me, poke, and stir.
It was a ton of fun. Poke is fucking hilarious too.
So stir.
The vibe of that group is really fun.
Let me go this way.
I'm gonna go for air this time.
Much better.
Where? Over here?
Get the fuck away from me.
What's going on?
Dude, get the lightning out of here.
The lightning is distracting as fuck.
Distracting as fuck.
Relax. That was better than before.
Nice.
I'm gonna try one more time. I beat it, but I wanna do one more.
31 is the biggest one?
That was risky, but I did it.
Don't even fucking think about it.
Don't strike me with lightning, please.
That was going so well too.
That was going so well.
That was like the best...
I probably wasn't gonna 100% that.
That was going so good too. Take off the armor?
Okay, I don't have any gear on anymore.
I shouldn't get struck by lightning.
Can I get a bunch of bananas or something?
Alright, let's go.
I think I screwed it up. I think I'm alright.
No. The first one was so much better.
What is happening with that shit?
Why do I go through, but it doesn't count?
What's going on?
I just went through three times.
I have to do it. Why do I keep doing this with my mouth?
Like this? I had it that time.
Did I get struck by lightning?
Alright, last try and that's it. No matter what.
Let's try to get too flashy with it.
No, just try again. I was being flashy.
I was trying to be so flashy.
That was stupid.
Alright, this is actually the last one no matter what.
Let's go.
Why are you talking? What happened?
I just won.
Just go. I need to get the money back.
I was going to say, I love how my knees can go through.
But if my head goes through it doesn't count.
Why am I losing so much momentum now?
Why can I not do it anymore?
I don't get it.
I've done this like ten times. These last three times I've just fallen on the ground.
Alright, this is the last one.
It's alright. I think I'm fine.
What part of your body has to go through the rings?
Because sometimes my knees go through and it doesn't work.
Sometimes my head goes through and it does.
The middle of my body has to go through.
Why does this keep screwing up?
I've done this like fifteen times now.
I'm doing it the exact way I did it before.
Oh my god.
Just go.
Dude, I can do that. I know I can.
I know I can do that.
I made all my money back. We're good. I can do it again.
I made it all back. We're good. Everything's fine.
Are you guys betting on these? I think I'm going too quick for you to bet.
Alright, this is actually going to be the one for real.
No more messing around.
What are you talking about?
Why is this so finicky?
What? Are you crazy?
What?
I'm making money but
What the hell?
How can I get the first one and not the second one?
I just got the first one. It's a fucking air vent.
Yes!
There it is. I got it.
What happened? Oh no, people are still betting.
Oh, I only get a hundred? I thought I was going to get something more.
Well, I left it with like three hundred extra dollars.
That's cool.
I missed one? No, don't tell me that.
I'm not going to do it anymore. Alright, where should I go from here?
That was cool. I can remove this.
It's thirty-five, not thirty-four.
Eh, it's alright. I want
Can I upgrade my gear?
Where was that? It's like over here, isn't it?
Upgrade the Master Sword. Fifty plus is the top reward.
How would you even do that?
Where's the, where's the
Kakariko? Whatever it is.
Salmon upgrade? Southeast.
Where is it? Hyrule Field.
East. Oh, it's right here. Isn't it?
Where is it? Right here. Where's the upgrade person?
I want to upgrade. It's marked with a leaf?
Isn't this where I have to, the big forest,
big bunch of trees and shit and I have to go
this way, right? Yeah. What was that?
Is that something cool? I don't even know if I have
any ingredients to do this. I don't.
I probably do. It's been like
six to ten in-game hours.
I can do this. I mean,
I might as well put your clothes back on.
Wait, can you not actually do it with my clothes on?
I don't, I think it just said I couldn't
really do anything. I don't think it's worth it.
Yeah, no,
it didn't have to be on.
Nah, I'm going to wear it. I want
this one. I like this stuff. Swim speed
is cool, but I think I already did that area.
I feel like I really need it. Although those horns,
I feel like I have a lot of those.
I don't know how rare those horns are.
Go find another fairy.
Four upgrades per piece.
Doesn't cost like nothing.
There's other fairy fountains. Oh, okay.
I'll just do it. Why not?
Set bonuses.
I have.
So it said follow the path behind
this area. Follow the
path and there's something to do.
I'll check it out. Cool.
Okay, follow the path.
Like the actual path path, like
the road. Or is there some like secret
over here I haven't seen? What is
your bedtime?
Maybe a little bit.
Northeast. Like over
here? Do I have to
climb out of here?
Am I going the right way? Path
does not mean climb. I mean, I feel like
I'm at the end of the
forest here in the northern section.
Just kind of stay. I mean,
you mean like over here? Yeah.
I think this is it. Birthday
raid song. I don't have any weapons
equipped. Not bad. Who's my horse?
Um, I don't know. I never seem to have
the horse. About a year ago I was walking along
the road here at night when I suddenly saw a
blinding light in the sky. When my eyes finally
just started looking at a shimmering object floating
overhead, I couldn't look away. I was bathed in light
when I came to. I woke up in bed covered in sweat.
What do you think about
that? That sounds like a dream.
Bed full of liquid in an empty room and
when I looked in the corner there was a weird glowing
device. When I touched the device
I was overwhelmed with a feeling of familiarity.
When I came to I was here.
What do you think about that? Does that sound familiar?
Hylian Champion.
Master Koga.
I ain't dying here. Got ya!
Ooh! Demon
Carver. Alright. What can I drop?
It's not what I wanted. Okay.
So left or right here? I'm going to say
right. Right looks kind of interesting.
Keep the leaf. Keep the leaf
please. Keep the leaf.
That's a lot of damage. In exchange for what?
I don't know what to drop. You don't need the leaf.
Oh, people are trolling. Okay.
Yeah, there's a million trees
in this world. I'll find another one.
Interesting. Okay.
You could beat Ganon
with a leaf. Um,
probably not. I highly
doubt that. How do you break these
without blowing them up? Do I have to blow these up
with the magnet? Just by smashing them?
Oh, okay. Cool. Nice.
I got a lot of money. I could probably
buy something nice. You need a big two-hander
to break them. I mean, this is effective. It doesn't really
do it a couple times.
That did not hit me. Master Sword.
Where's the Master Sword? I mean, it recharges
in time. Yeah, how come it's not on the menu though?
That's kind of freaking me out. Yes.
That's very good. Ooh.
Down here. Ah,
that's why everybody wanted me to get a leaf.
Now I understand. I can
swim this. That's not a problem. It's not
even deep. Where's the actual line?
Is it underwater?
Underwater. All right. Get up.
Get on the thing. What are you doing?
Hey. Nice. As long as I don't
dash, I think I can. Wait. What on my
swim? I just upgraded it. How come you're not listening
to us? Uh, I'm going
behind the waterfall, right? Swim upwards.
Swim upwards. Quick. I don't even know what just
happened. All right. What's wrong?
That's a very good idea. I think I'll do it.
How do I get under there though?
Climb it. Oh, shit. Yep.
What is in here? This looks pretty expensive.
Whatever it is. Soldier's
broadsword. Should I get rid of the
bat? This thing is 60 damage though.
That's ridiculous. Not worth it. It's
terrible. Got extra durability though.
Not worth it. Okay. So
now what's the deal here?
Should I just swim up? How do I
get down? Swim under?
I don't think there is like a dive,
right? Swim through. It's behind it.
Oh,
okay. So now what?
Uh, where am I?
Look up. I'm gonna fucking die. Hold on.
What? No. Dude, stop.
Just let- You killing me here.
You- I- I can't go down.
You said- Do you say it was underwater or is it
up above here? It's not
down. Oh, I thought people were telling me to dive down.
Chat- Chat is dumb. It's
behind the waterfall. What?
What the hell is up here?
Am I even moving? Okay.
I thought it was under- I thought it was down, like in the-
under the water or something. Okay,
this makes way more sense. I saw like
the reflection in the water. I thought it was like
down in the water. That shit
wouldn't even reflect that far. Unrealistic.
Alright, what is this?
Uh, I don't think we're doing any voting
or betting. Alright, chest.
Are you gonna turn any- emote only on though or are you gonna kill me?
You're gonna get me killed. Cause I can't
see the chat and they can't help me. Alright.
Big button. Big button
can't- ooh, okay, hold on.
What does this big button need?
Can I put like a chest on it?
Okay. I think it's just a weight thing.
Is it a weight thing? It's gotta be
it, right? Okay. That's enough
weight. Okay.
This goes over here. And then I climb
that. Wait, let me get the items first.
This is not gonna mess with the weight, is it?
Nope, not. Zora sword? If that's any
better than what I have. Zora sword
meh. 14 damage.
That's really not that much. How do I-
Oh, like this. Is it?
Well, I hit the wrong button. Do I have four?
I think like- I feel like I need way
more stamina. How many do I have? You can't
see it, but it's two. Very cool.
What else is down here? Anything else I should do?
Probably. Can you just do a shrine
normally? There's a memory
down here apparently. Okay. Hold on.
Let me get this. Ooh, wait. What's this?
Should I climb up here? I'm climbing up here.
Are you more like Zelda or Link?
What's that little- what's that little weird guy?
He like does confetti and like
flies around. Tingle. Yeah.
I wonder if I should just keep going that way.
But, I'm intrigued.
Vinny also said he's like Tingle.
Yeah, okay. Vinny's a smart
fucking guy. Get away from me.
I'm going across this bridge. I'm not going to fight
these. Why would I? You can't
both be Tingle.
Who can I be? Ganon? No.
No way. I'm
way too lazy to be Ganon. The prospect
of taking over the entire universe.
Like, oh yeah, alright. The whole fucking
universe. Let's- I kind of just want to
watch The Office on Netflix. Never mind.
That was a- eh. I don't care.
Check your iPad. Memories.
Found it. Oh, that's right. Okay.
Shh. Let's see.
One second, I felt like I was still
in Roblox.
After all, it's not like your last shot
was up there on Mount Mineru.
Anything could finally spark the power
to seal Ganon away. We just
have to keep looking for that
thing. That's kind of you.
Roblox
brain rot. If I may.
There is to say it,
but I was thinking about what I do
when I'm feeling. You know, what
usually goes through my mind.
It helps when I think- when I think
about it.
This is it, then.
Are you sure? Positive.
It's awake. Ganon.
Let's stop wasting
time. We're gonna need everything we got
to take that thing down.
Now champions,
who are your divine beasts?
Show that swirling swine who's boss.
Link will need to meet Ganon head-on
when we attack. This needs to be
a unified assault.
Little guy, you get to Hyrule Castle.
Count on
us for support. But it's up to you
to pound Ganon into oblivion.
Come. We should go.
We need to get you someplace safe.
I'm not a child anymore.
I didn't- I'm sorry. I may not be much use
on the battlefield. There must
be something I can do to help.
I dragged it over. Cause
I have to be on
a different input on my monitor.
And I can't see what's actually
on my desktop behind the screen.
That was cool. That was a dramatic
moment. It was fine.
There. We'll go facecam off.
Live tingle reaction.
Alright, cool. Let's do it.
Oh, it's one of these
guys. Alright.
Okay. Oops.
Where- Stop!
For one second! I can't-
What's going on? What are you doing?
Shit.
I don't even know what direction he is swinging at.
Is it vertical or
horizontal? I need a shield.
Oh, right. I unequipped my shield.
There's a stupid lightning
dogshit. And now I can't
parry this dogshit.
Okay.
Oh my god. You have a lot of health.
Don't!
I need a- Where-
Put a weapon on! What's going on?
Oh my goodness gracious.
What can I even eat?
I have to eat all this stuff. I have to.
Eat it all. Just eat everything. I don't-
Doesn't matter. Oh, you do that more than
a few times.
Oh, that wasn't a swing.
I think I'm dead here.
Oh, I'm in so much trouble.
Oh, missed it.
One more hit. Yeah!
Very nice. What do I get?
Sword.
Mighty. Lionel. Bow.
Well, I absolutely am getting rid of something.
Holy shit. Alright, awesome.
What should I get rid of? Golden bow?
I feel like this is the worst of all of them.
Golden bow. Another lionel shield.
I think.
What is better? A knight shield or a lionel shield?
Probably the knight shield, yeah.
The lionel shield does damage when you parry.
That one's about to break.
This one's new though, isn't it?
Drop the old lionel shield.
Actually good idea.
But how much have I used it?
I have used that a lot.
Sparkle means new.
Go back to Impa.
Is that all I can do here?
Copy. That was part of it, right?
Keep going up the mountain.
It's kind of chilly here.
Wait, even with the occurence?
I don't think I have anything, do I?
Flame sword? Is that enough?
No. I don't think I can do this.
I need special armor.
That's what I figured. Alright.
Sweet. Imagine there's something up here.
There is. Eventually.
Where's Impa?
Somebody said go talk to Impa now. Mark it.
I don't want to mark this spot right here
because I'll be confused how to get there.
How did I get up here?
It was through the waterfall.
I'll mark it just to...
Leap. Oh shit.
I don't know if that was a quest or not.
Let's turn it in. What do you got for me?
Impa uses a neti pot, do you?
I've used it before, but not in a while.
It kind of feels weird.
I'll hand this over to you now before I forget.
Champions tunic.
In ancient Hyrule, this garment could only be worn by one
and earn the respect of the royal family.
Equipment will reveal an enemy's life gauge.
Wait, don't I already have that?
Doesn't it already show people's health bars?
Exact values.
Wait, is it telling me to go kill the divine beasts?
I already got three down.
Let me see that thing. Five.
If I upgrade this, it's already going to be...
Alright, that's cool. Do I have enough materials to upgrade it?
I don't think I do.
Be careful.
You're dressed like a dork right now. I think I look pretty cool.
When it's fully upgraded, it's one of the strongest in the game.
Well, alright, I'll keep it for sure.
Alright, I think that's probably a good place to call it.
I think this is a good time.
11.15. Five hours and some change.
I gotta get some food too.
It was a really fun night though.
I had a great time.
I feel like the vibes were on tonight.
So, it was a good, good, good, good, good, good, good, good, good night.
Do the DLC?
Uh, yeah, I mean...
We're just gonna play it. I'll play it just to turn it on.
Then I got really nothing else going on.
I think the next thing I really want to do...
I did that.
I want to at least get this area uncovered.
Because I want the whole map sort of revealed at this point.
At least from here.
Baron is really cool.
When are you gonna do no-cam chill streams?
Yeah, I feel like they've been a little crazy recently, but...
There's been a lot going on.
We'll slow it down a little bit.
I said that last week, but I mean it this time.
We're gonna hold the, uh...
We're gonna put the brakes on.
Yeah, I mean, next stream, I don't know if I'm gonna play Breath of the Wild next.
Maybe I will.
Let's say, um... Friday?
Oh, also, uh...
Something else I really want to do.
I want to do another, like, 80s and 90s commercial watch stream.
I feel like people really enjoyed that.
I thought that was really fun.
I think we'll probably do that at some point, too.
People have been asking for that again.
And I've just kind of been like, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
Maybe we'll do that, I don't know, at some point this weekend.
Maybe a little bit after this weekend.
I'll get it set up.
Maybe it launches tomorrow.
Ooh, maybe we'll do that on Friday.
Yeah, I still have to watch Ster play Five Nights at Freddy's.
But I think we played Roblox for, like, three hours.
And I think, uh...
I don't know if we anticipated we were gonna do that.
But yeah, there's a couple games that me and Ster are gonna play at some point, too.
Next week, probably.
More of Roblox.
Roblox is, like, the kind of game that I kinda like.
It's just, you can just jump in a game and who cares?
It doesn't even matter.
Thirty minutes can go by and you can just leave.
Or you can play for, like, two hours.
There's no shame.
No, that was great. Thanks again.
Big thanks to Poke and obviously Ster.
Vibes were immaculate tonight.
It was really fun, really funny.
And I'll see you guys on Friday.
I don't know exactly what we'll do on Friday.
Anticipate either Resident Evil 4 Mercenaries, maybe Breath of the Wild,
maybe, you know, maybe I might just turn on something random.
Just play it. We'll see.
Friday's stream is gonna be slowed down.
We're gonna chill out.
And then at some point, maybe this weekend, we'll do the 80s and 90s ads.
See if I can get it set up.
I'll let you know.
Yeah, Hilux 2.
Can we submit videos?
Um, no, I have a lot of compilations that we didn't even see.
So if I ever get to a point where
I need more,
which, I don't know how often I do this kind of stuff,
so I don't know if I do it at the frequency to need to have
a bunch of submissions or something.
Because it's still a lot that we have not even looked at.
There's the music?
Oh shit, sorry.
Oh well, we're at the end anyways.
Vinnie might have some good playlists, especially for terrible video game ads.
Yeah, I'll be talking to him soon anyways.
Maybe I'll see if he's got any good ones.
But yeah, thanks for watching.
Good night, good stream.
Fun freaking times.
I'll see you guys on Friday.
Take care of yourselves. Have a great evening.
See you this weekend.
Same time, 6 o'clock Pacific.
Is it standard time?
Or is it day...
Is it Pacific standard or Pacific daylight time right now?
And I can never keep track, I have no idea.
Is it PST or PDT right now?
Pacific standard time?
Yeah, it's PDT.
Whatever it is.
Alright, I'll see you guys later.
Take care of yourselves. Good night.