Hello, how you doing? Welcome. The next big thing on Twitch. What's up everybody, how you doing?
Lagging? Sometimes when I, I don't know why, sometimes when I start my stream, I, it like
crashes. I'm gonna figure out why it's doing that. Hmm. Why did I crash? Yeah, that happened, this
happened last time. I'm live, right? Yeah, the stream crashes. That's really weird. I don't know
why that happens. Well, I think I'm back. I've got to like, reinstall something. All right. I
can't see the chat though. Hold on. Let me see if I can refresh it. That was a little bizarre.
I gotta pop out a new chat now. But anyways, hi. Welcome everybody. That's weird. Uh, gonna be
playing Battleship. The new Twitch meta. Lagging Larry here. That's me, Lagging Larry. We're gonna
play with, uh, Ludwig. I hope he doesn't even know who that is. Let me see. Huh, let me, I gotta pop
my chat back out. Why does my shit crash? What happened? I got a new computer. Maybe that's why.
I gotta pop out this chat. Hold on. Sorry. Technical difficulties already.
Barely are. Okay. Millionaire PC. I don't, I don't know what it is. I don't know why it keeps doing
it. You know, it's only for the first like five seconds that I'm like flooding my computer's DNS,
right? I don't even know what that means. Millionaire Barry. No, I hope you guys are doing
well. Uh, I'm very excited for today. I think this is going to be the best stream of the year.
Fuck, I shouldn't have said that. But like, you know what I mean? I'm just fucking around. But you
know, uh, let's go ahead. Let's see. Let's see if he's ready. Hey, hey, you there. Go ahead. My
stream crashed. I don't know. I don't know if you saw that. Yeah. Stream crashed, but I got it back.
We're back. We're good. Oh, you're back. Everyone's there. Everyone's happy.
Dude, my stream just crashes. I don't know why. Like I turn on OBS and my computer freezes.
Oh, wait. Is it, are you adjusting OBS when that happens? Um, no, I like, I'll just, I hit go live
and like my, I drop a ton of frames. Oh shit. Did my computer crash? I think you might have,
um, what is it called? Why is C cleaner running? I think of S C D bro. Why is C cleaner running?
You got shitty computer disorder over there. You need a better, I need to get you hooked up with
like a better computer. Your computer should not do that. I have a great computer though. I just
got like a new awesome computer with an extremely overpriced paid, like 30% premium 30 90 in it.
You have a 30 90? Yeah, dude. I paid like, it was, I paid for battleship.
Yeah. But I played other stuff besides, but you know what? This was not a fucking good
spending of money of me at my part. Not at all. Yeah. I played resonable eight is the only game
I've played that has 3d graphics. You should like be mining Bitcoin while you're live or something
with that card. You're wasting that. Uh, are you ready for battleship? You ready to do this?
I am ready for battleship. I have a bit of mutiny on my side already. Everyone's on team
German, my chat, which is concerning. Really? Are we in the same game? Did my internet crash?
No, it crashed. You're gone. Oh, okay. Yeah. I'll make a new room. That's all right though.
Yeah. I don't know what's going on. 30 90 for battleship. Well, it's not like you'll
play battleship a lot at least. I mean, you tell me this is like potentially a pretty big deal
from what I hear. What? What? Sorry. What? What's a big deal? The battleship is,
it could be really fun to play with people on stream, like with friends. Yeah. It'd be fun
for a bit for sure. Yeah, of course. That's what we're doing right now. That's like why we're
hanging out and playing it. It's yeah. Battleship is definitely fun for a little bit. Yeah. I agree
with you. It'd be good. It's like we'll have a good hour for it. Hour. Oh, or two. Yeah. Maybe
I was assuming like six. All right. I got a friend code for you, but I'm just going to say it.
I don't want. Should I just type it? I'll type it to you. You could say it really fast and then I
could try to join. No, I don't think I want to do that. I'm typing it to you in discord. Perfect.
There you are. All right. So does it show the room code anywhere or can I go over to the actual
stream? I don't see it anywhere, but I don't think there's another way for someone to join battleship.
I don't think so. All right. I think we're good. Just do all right. So those who don't understand
how battleship is played very, very complicated game you do is you get five ships. You place them
around and then each turn back and forth. Ludwig and I are going to try to kill each other. Sink
our ships. I'm sorry. Are you explaining battleship? Yeah. That makes sense. No, no bets already.
Oh, are you a bit of a gambling man? Let me just snap the camera on. Uh, yeah. All right. But now
we haven't even played one game though. You want to do this already. You want to bet all. What do
you want to bet? Well, we'll start. Let's just start off like casually, just like with a casual,
you know, let's just say five gifted, you know, just a casual breezy. I've gifted subs to the
other person's channel, just to the other person's channel or, or, or better yet. I thought you were
going to say like 500 bucks. I was like, Holy shit. We're like already going. No, we'll start.
I mean, it's the first match, you know, how about this? I imagine you're not tier three sub to me.
Is that right? That's that's incorrect. I I'm not, I'm not tier sub to tier three. Okay. I'm not
tier three sub to you. The loser tier three subs to the winner for just a month. All right. That
works. Game one. Let's go. Do you have any experience playing this? Well, let me tell you,
I'm using, uh, Fredrick Poitier, which try, try to click on him right now on your stream.
You bought this guy. Yeah. I spent money on this. Why did you buy this? It was three dollars.
It just changes. You're never gonna, you're never gonna open this game ever again.
Yeah. This is no, no, no. Yes, you are. Cause this is, yeah, this is a big deal coming on
Twitch soon. What, what, what? I'm sorry. What do you mean? It's a big deal coming on Twitch.
Like this, you're going to be playing this all the time. I think like battleship. Yeah.
Why are people spamming new meta in my chat? All right. You ready?
Here's three sub to the other person. Tier three sub to the other person.
Let's go. I was just press cancel. All right. So we don't tell each other where we're going,
right? Well, no, you're supposed to say the smallest ship where you put it.
You suppose you have to say the smallest ship where you put it. Yeah. You have to tell me where
you put your smallest ship. Okay. Small ships going bottom, right? Yeah. Mine's also going
the bottom, right? Okay. Can we rotate? Oh, okay. Yeah. Good luck. Oh, don't cheat. Don't look at
anybody's screens. No, of course not. Of course not. I'm not looking at any screens and I have my chat
just, just firmly out of my, out of my grip. I'm ready. You ready? I'm prepared. Yeah. Who goes
first? I don't even know who that is. I called heads in the air. All right, here we go. Okay.
You lied. You lied. Wait, did you say bottom right? I did say bottom right. Welcome to war.
So did I. Oh, you lied to me. It's more hurtful when you do it. Hey, here's, here's how I know
that this is going to be correct. He went up one square. Fuck with me. No, he didn't. Whatever.
Ah, maybe you're saying he went up one square because that's what you did.
A mirror match. He went up three squares. No, he didn't. You're, you're trying to fool me here.
You did not go up a square at all. You went left a square. So how do you win by sinking everything,
right? You got to, you got to sink my destroyer, my battleship, my star command. You got to sink
everything. All right. This is, this is for a tier three sub, right? I don't want to fuck around
anymore. This is a tier three. This is $25. Yeah. Come on. You don't do this like, you don't do this
like a puzzle where you do the edges first and then you go in the middle when you're like ready.
German, it's a, it's a children's game. You just click a random square and then occasionally you
hit. I mean, honestly, you'll probably do as well if you just don't even know what you're doing.
If you do it blind, if you get like a monkey to do it, you probably have more success.
I mean, you thought, you thought I was in like the edges there. You know, I thought you were
a corner Karen. Yeah. Oh, what do you think? I'm crazy. The way you do the thing where you
put all your ships in one corner. That's how you instantly lose this game. I know that at least
you got, well, you got one for the corner. Apparently you're a bit of a corner Karen,
but you get to go twice. What's this bullshit? You go until you miss. What?
There's no way I hated that shit. When I used to play basketball with people one on one,
it would be like, Oh, you go until you don't. And if whoever scored gets the ball back and I never
got the ball back, they just scored like 20 times in a row. Yeah. Winter winter stays is kind of
hard. Uh, but fortunately for you, it's not like shooting a jump shot here. I'm still shooting in
the dark. You're working your way up towards E 10. I'm a little nervous about my E 10 strategy.
E 10 eating this stick. What? It sounds like eating. Well, it's all right. You get one.
Oh yeah. You thought I was, you thought I was doing the thing. Yep. That's it. It was, it was
worth it. Yeah. I think you're in the same place. No thing about me is I'll never click where I am.
You're such a corner care. No, no, no, no, no, no. You just have to get the one,
you have to get the one that's over there. Oh God. This is your destroyer. Oh no. All right.
Wait, German. No, no, you didn't. It's a tier three. Oh, it's hard. You got one more. We're
sneaking with it. You're not going to fight. Yeah. Yeah. Maybe that last chip will save your day.
I have a feeling you put every ship in the bottom left except for your small one, which you put in
the top right. Yeah. But that would be a stupid strategy that you'd lose every time.
All right. I got it. It's a bit of a stupid strategy. I wouldn't recommend that.
Yeah. Well, it was, at least it wasn't for $2,500. It was for 25.
We get in there. We'll get there. Oh no. Oh, oh no. Excuse me. Somebody's right here in the middle.
Yeah. I went for a little, you know, a little middle play. Okay. All right. That's good for me.
This bottom left strategy. Would you have been so foolish? Everyone's calling you a middle Manny.
Yeah. Cause you got, you got stuff in the middle. I got a couple of things in the middle. I wouldn't
focus on it too much, which what is down here? Oh, that was your four. That was your four ship.
Yeah. It was my French four. I don't know what, I don't know the names of the ships. I just know
how many numbers there are. Okay. So I think you did. I think you, are you not as dumb as I am?
Did you not put anything right next to each other? No, I played this smart. I played this by the book.
I made a thing about me is, you know, I come up with strategies. I know you're a chess player,
right? Yeah. I'm a, I'm a chess player by trade. So, Oh, found you. Which way are you? I think this
is your little guy. Thank you. Nope. Phenomenal guess. Where did you hide this last one? This
is a bit devious. It's a, it's a four, right? Yeah. There's a bit of strategy involved here.
All I need to go is from this point diagonally upwards and then I'll eliminate every single
place. Oh, close. Very close. I don't trust you. I got up. It's a war of attrition right now. You
know what I mean? Like I just got to, you got to spend a million years finding this last one.
Well, I have my, my, my tugboat hidden pretty well. I only need to get one ship. Oh, all right.
Let's eliminate this. Everyone's screaming. Why? What do you mean? Why? They can only, there's
two ways it can go up or down. Oh, this is where, this is where your big guy is right here.
I did find my big guy. That's the easiest one to find though. Mathematically.
That's true. You won't find another ship for years.
Well, you did put them right next to you. You did the same thing I did. Didn't you?
Well, I had a gap. Yeah. But you saying there's a gap means that there's definitely another ship
right here. Yeah. You did the same thing I did. We have the same board. What?
What? This is really bad. This is really bad. No, it's not. This is really bad.
This is really bad. What do you, what do you wait? Did you do this?
What? How do you have two ships that are this big? You have two destroyers?
No. I'm so confused. I was just. You just got to keep shooting your shots captain.
Oh, wait a minute. Oh, they're all connected. Oh boy. You're in deep shit. Oh no.
Well, actually I have one last trick up my sleeve. Yeah. And I think I know where it is
because it's probably exactly where I put mine. You did the same thing, man. That's so funny.
Which way? How many are left? There's a one or two. There's only one three ship left and it's
either left or right here. And I don't know. Did you, did you, are you as compulsive enough?
Oh, that voice. I'm getting low. Were you as compulsive enough to make sure you created the
full Tetris line? Right? Like it has to be perfect. Or did you have? That's a good point.
It is. Of course it is. That's such a good point. Where was yours? That's it. Oh, you're devious.
You won. I won the game. Yeah. The greatest comeback of all time.
But you did the same thing that I did and I just, I thought that you were so much smarter than me.
That was what I was hoping. That's what I coast off of in my life is that people think I'm smarter
than I am and then I'm not. I was hoping I would get there. All right. Well, uh, tier three, tier
three sub. It's a tier three sub. It's a tier three sub to you. I'm sending it over. There goes my
tier two. Here's where I, where, where I am kind of concerned about this. So I'm assuming we're
probably exponentially going to increase this number. Oh, did I really just blow it in the
first round? Like, Oh, I won. I won the first round. Yeah. You won the lowest stakes game.
Yeah. So when we get to like, Oh yeah, we're going to do this for $5,000, which I hope we
don't do that because I don't know if I have that, but you know, I don't win that one. I'm,
I leave the battleship casino with $4,995 in the hole, whatever it is.
That's exactly what's going to happen. Yeah. To a T. All right. You ready for the next one?
That was a good warmup. I I'm trying to subscribe. I I've found out that I can't now. I think,
I think someone gifted me a tier three, but that's been paid. I'm going to gift a tier three back
gift to tier three. Yeah. Cause I've been tier. Someone got there before I could get there.
That's so funny. All right. Let me make sure that the room codes are not here.
I imagine if we just hit rematch, it should be, okay. This was somebody, somebody just invited
me to a game. I've never heard of this name. Uh, is this a dumb question? Do you only have
one scene on your Twitch OBS? Well, I've, this is why I have multiple scenes, but what, who the,
who the fuck is Cleven? Are you, that's me. That's you. We just played a game together.
I'm Cleven. What? I thought this was like a steam user. Like, like, no, Cleven's my real name.
Wait, what? Cleven's my, it's, well, it's actually my middle name, but I went by it for a while.
I thought that was the name of your, your, your, like your guy. How did you know that?
I was hoping you wouldn't know that. Yeah. Cleven. I don't know where Cleven,
Cleven's a random name I made for a rust server eight months ago on my steam. And I've kept it
there ever since. Wait, what the fuck? I was like, who is Cleven? I'm Cleven Ballsworth.
Is that actually what you went by? Cleven Ballsworth? Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. I thought it
was somebody like was spammed Kevin really quickly. And they were like, I got to get in this game.
Like, Cleven. He's just trying to, they just got really like, just hastily fucked up the name
Kevin. What is, uh, hold on. I'm buying a, I'm buying a new one. You've, okay. Hold on. Wait,
wait, wait. You've spent, have you spent more money on the game than you have giving me a tier
three sub? I gifted you a tier three. Ah, you just got just buying shit. All right. I'm sticking
with, um, this guy. I don't know. Here's the thing. I was playing a Frenchman, which is just
brain dead in war. Oh, by the way, soda pop or tonic. Which one are you? Soda pop or tonic.
Soda. 100%. Okay. Yeah. Good. Good. I'd imagine where you're, so I'm from New Hampshire. Oh yeah.
All right. So I imagine we have similar. All right. Let's, let's do this. How do you say the area
where you, uh, like a, in a house, like a sectioned off area, R O O M. How do you say that?
It's a living room. And then just without the living part. Room. Me too. Yeah. I get a little
trash for that for not going room. Yeah. I don't know. But people always give me shit for saying
other stuff too. What are the, what are the other stuff? Room. Oh, okay. Wait, wait, wait. Um,
what do you put your clothes in? Dryer. Okay. You take them out of the, okay. Take them out. Okay.
You wash your clothes. You dry them. You take them out of the dryer and you put them in a.
I feel like this is a trivia test now in a, in a, are you looking for the word hamper? No, no, no.
That's what happens when your clothes are dirty. You've washed them. You've dried them. I've washed
them. I dried them. I put them away. Now you put them away in your. Well, usually in my, in my,
in my closet. Okay. But like, uh, how do I, what's the thing that you, what's the thing that you pull?
Oh, now you fucked it up. You say draw, draw, draw. It's a draw. You're not saying the full thing.
You're giving up halfway through. Oh, I gotta go to my draw. Open up, open up that draw.
But you're not, you're not, you know, you're not finishing the sentence.
Whatever. You're just saying draw. Draw. Yeah. My, my draw. How do you, do you say underwear like that?
Underwear. You don't go my drawers. Underwear. Underwear. Just underwear. Okay. Yeah. Underwear.
But it's not, but the thing though, it's not underwear. It's underwear. Right. Are we saying
it underwear? Underwear. Underwear. Am I saying it weird? Am I saying it weird too? You're making me
self-conscious about how I'm saying that now. Anyways, dude, New Hampshire, New Hampshire,
that's my fucking backyard. That's my backyard. Yeah. I, uh, I'm one of those New Hampshireites
that, you know, I'll just associate myself with Boston, even though I got no business.
Yeah. But New England, that's New England, New England, man. Red Sox nation. Yeah. That's what
I go for. I go for, I try to take all the teams, all the pride because we don't have much in New
Hampshire. So we take what we can get. I like New Hampshire. I think New Hampshire is nice.
It's good. You ever go up to pheasant lane mall and no sales tax to buy something?
I live in Vegas, man. We don't gotta worry about that here. I guess that's true. I guess that is
true. No sales tax. Yes, but the income tax. No. Yeah. I think there's no income tax in New Hampshire
as well. Oh, there's not. Yeah. Yeah. But you have to live in New Hampshire, which means you
probably develop a heroin addiction. Oh God. What's the mountains? Oh, by the way, I was just like
absentmindedly placing stuff. I think this is okay. I've placed, I feel like it's fine. All right. So
what is this for? Are we upping the stakes or are we lowering the stakes? Let's, let's do it. So
last time was a tier three. Let's, let's, let's, I feel warm right now. I'm ready for a,
you know, just like a, like a casual hundred gifted, a hundred gifted subs for this one. Oh God.
What's that? Okay. It's 500, but honestly with the, with the write-offs, you get it all back.
Vegas taxes, New Hampshire taxes. We can't go from, we can't go from $25 to 500. Okay. All right.
Well, then you give a suggestion. What's a, what's a better escalation and a better escalation would
be two X. So let's, let's do, let's do 50, 50, 50 bucks, which is what? All right. $50. What do
you mean? What is it? It's $50. How are we doing subs? Oh yeah. We can do like 10 subs. Okay. 10
subs. Wait. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Okay. Yeah. That works. I have a new strategy. You do. Oh, okay.
I, are you, okay. There's psychology here. Like, did you do the exact same layout? No. Oh, smart.
I thought you were going to do the exact same thing. That's it. There's no reason why I even
ever would aim down here. I'm going, I'm going to tell you right now from J one to a 10, just in a
diagonal line. It's going to take me too long to find that coordinate. So I'm just going to click
here. I'm, I'm marching up diagonally. All right. Like Petco stock prices in 2000. And you just have
to find me before I get to your ship. Cause I'm guaranteed to hit one on this path.
Fuck. All right. You found that quick. What do you, what is G three? What are you thinking?
I don't know. I G three was speaking to me. All right. All right. Well,
I'm sure you don't finish this off. You're going to go the wrong direction here. You think so?
Yeah. Why would you have her? I don't know. Cause I thought maybe you put them next to,
I was going to freak you out. I was going to freak out you and like you're insane.
It would have been insane, but it was just so, so bold. Oh, I found your super five, whatever
they're called. Destroyer. I think, or maybe it's, yeah, it's a destroyer. Look at that. Look at that
art. Very cool. So if, if I were you, I would be going right here. Nope. Okay. We're, we're,
you know, similar areas, but, oh, that's, but that strategy is unfair. Cause you're guaranteed
to hit something. Wait, what are you doing? I tried to be like you. I tried to be like you.
You get bold. Sometimes I thought I'd throw a little spice in it. You know, that was pretty
spicy. Oh, that was really close. That was, that means it wasn't close at all. Oh, he went the
wrong way. I hate going the wrong way. You got to wait for soda. Oh my God. That was actually
really close. Yeah, but that could all be really close. It's a 10 by 10 grid heads. I go right
tails. I go left. I'm going to get, I'm going to let you know, just fun, just for the sake of the
broadcast content quality. It didn't matter which way you went. And I literally told you,
I just actually told you, why did I do that? For some reason, I thought I got the control of the,
I thought I got control back. Why did I just tell you? I don't know. I would have kept going
left. Yeah. All right. Well, I feel good about that. I'm continuing my, my line. What are you
giggling at? I can't tell. I can't tell if you're trying to. No, dude, don't keep doing that. That's
like a dumb strategy. Don't do that. That's like stupid. Don't keep doing that. You're double
getting me. You don't like being an idiot. That's like not like, don't do it. They double get me.
All right. You'll never get the direction. Yeah. Well, obviously. Uh, here. No, I thought you were
laughing at something. You, you've really rattled me here. I think I've got you rattled. Oh, all
right. You went down with it. That's good. Yeah. I went down. I want, I want a little nuts of that.
My, if my strategy nets me one ship, this is the biggest waste of time ever. I was going to say
that's like a, that's a one for how many moves is it? Like 15. Yeah. All right. But how big is
this one? Oh, she's a big one. Keep clicking. Keep going. Oh man. Those are your two biggest ones.
Those are the easiest to find. This is good for me because where I have hid my tugboat, it will
take you years. Damn it. I thought it was that one. That would have been hard. All right. Last one.
And then I've done my line. Okay. Yeah. Well, you know what? Just go the other way. Do the other
diagonal. You'll probably get something. I'm sure. I feel like you've word played me a bit here.
Maybe you told me right. Cause there's something to the left. No, I think your strategy would work
if you did it the other way. Wait, like a one to J 10. You'd probably hit like five. Oh,
see too. Shit. Okay. Okay. You'll, you're going to fuck up the direction a couple of times here.
Ooh. Ooh. This is the lying better. I mean, yeah, kind of. I'll tell you right now. It's B2.
I'll tell you right now. It's B2. I don't think it is. You gotta go up. You gotta go up. Trust me.
I'm going to, I'm going to do it. I'm going to trust him. Oh, you got it down left, right.
Never eat soggy waffles. It wasn't even go B2. Trust me there. B2. All right. If it's not B2,
then I'm going to be. Oh my God. What the hell? Why did it work? It worked. Honesty. All right.
We'll go B seven. All right. Fuck you. All these information I've given for what feel like a bot
and spy lie lying warfare. All right. So where are your little, where's your little one? My little
one. I will. Do you want me to tell it to you? Cause I can't tell it to you. I can tell you the
row. I will not tell you the exact number. All right. Give me the, give me the row. It's G.
It's G. It has to be with this one. Wait, wait. But if it was two, it would have to be in the middle.
I played pick girls. I could go up down. It could go up down. They span because they got it. You
gotta have up down, you know, cause it could be G and F or G and H, you know, or I think you're
right here. You like, you like pairing things. I do. I like having things together. I like having
things paired up. I just realized I didn't shoot this ship last turn. No, you didn't. I feel like
you would do something like this. Oh, good call. But nope. So it looks like you, okay. You, you
actually made a pretty significant map here. You moved around, you have them all scattered out,
like, like, like an actual strategy. I did that too. And it is, it is not be fruited me much.
Well, I mean, we're still, I'm one ship ahead of you. That's, this can change in a second.
That is true. That is true. And I did get one of your threes. I feel good about that. It's
whoever's tugboat lasts the longest. This is going to keep escalate. It's going to keep,
doesn't dude, it doesn't matter who wins any of these right now, because whoever wins like the
$500 one, like just wins everything. Anyways, like that. Oh yeah. No, you're a hundred percent
right. I just went to Vegas. We were, I was doing like craps, you know, it's the game I like to play
with like a big group of people. And I was betting modestly the entire weekend. And then Sunday
rolled around and I was like, fuck it. I'm, I'm up a couple thousand. So I started betting just
nonsensically. I just started betting like 500. I lost everything. Nothing I did mattered because
I knew I was just going to escalate to a point where it was make or break and I broke everything.
It was gone. So, so wait, hold on. You were up with thousands of dollars. I was up $4,000.
Come on that you got to do. Come on. And then Sunday rolled around and I wanted to be up more
money. So I just put it, you know, the you play craps ever I've dabbled a few times. I just put
everything on the field, just $4,000, you know, just trying to run it up to a 25 grand. What are
you trying to do? Well, no, I have a, I have a goal because I think if you don't have a goal,
it's not stupid. Wait, you go, wait, hold on. You're going into Vegas gambling with a goal
of how much money you want of how much money, of what I want to win. Oh my God. That's, that's not,
that's, that's don't do that. I go in with a thousand and I want to leave with a really
nice watch. Oh my God. No, that's good. That's a good thing to do. I mean, if you, if you, if
you're going to give it to you for free because you like hit a jackpot and they go, how about this
watch instead of the 40 grand? I would be like, sign me up. Can I get two? Wait, you would take
the watch over 40 grand? Well, I, well, I get like a really nice roll. I'd get a $40,000 watch.
I don't know. Expensive watches always didn't do it for me. It was always just like somebody come
take this from me. I'm not a watch guy by any means. I just think that getting it for this
occasion would be, would be cool. Cause it'd be like my Vegas watch. And then people would be
like, where'd you get that watch? And I'll be like, do I got a story for you? I'd walk them
through every blackjack and craps table hand. The expensive watch on your wrist is like,
you remember in GTA online when somebody became like the bounty and they just showed up on the
mini map. Yeah. It's just like, you're just like showing up on everybody's mini map with this
gigantic, expensive, like $500,000 thing on your hand. Yeah. If I were to leave my house, sure. But
you know, it's probably not found. Look at all these empty spaces, these gaps. How have I not
found you? Oh, I miss clicked that. I don't understand where you could even be right here.
I'm eliminating all these one spaces. Yeah. I'm actually wasting my time up here because he's so
many places where you kind of hit your tugboat. It's almost frustrating. Yeah. You, you focus so
much on the top here. I'm clearing out the top completely because you could have hit it there.
And I'm going to be so sad. Like, look at this. Do you see a five and six? Yeah. If your tugboat
was there, I would lose my life going for the bottom. So I have to guess there. Is it possible
to fill the whole board and not, what happened? Okay. What happens if you miss everything and
like this still boats on like spaces? Does every bolt just lose? Wait, there's no way to, it's not
like you run out of bullets. Do you run out of bullets actually? I don't know. Do you run out
of the bullets? No, I, I imagine not. That would be shocking. All right. Now I'm going for the five
strap. Cause I know you're destroyers out there. I'm just, I'm just looking for a place where there
are two and I got it. Oh, no, no. Okay. Now I'm in trouble. I mean, do you mean I'm in trouble now?
That's, that's my battle. Look how nicely it was tucked in. You painted around it. Yeah. That it
was an actual, uh, like in a Looney Tunes cartoon where they fire the machine out of the person and
it just does like the lines around them. And then like the wall breaks behind them and they'd run
away. Yeah. Yeah. It just falls behind them and there's just that, that faint outline,
but then you still shot Bugs Bunny at the end, which was fucked up for a children's cartoon.
Yeah. You somebody say I'm used to like shoot at people to like dance. Like then that's kind
of fucked up, isn't it? It is fucked up, but also in a way art. Yeah. What did he'd be like,
well, wait, was it just an awful shot? No, I think it was like abusive. There was,
he was firing at them to like at their left, but why wouldn't he just shoot Bugs Bunny in the,
in the stomach? I don't understand. Why not simply murder Bugs Bunny? Because he was always like,
like, all right, you're right. You're right. Right. Right. Right. Right. Right. Right. Right. Right.
Right. He would do that. And then he would fire like 400 rounds at him. Yeah. I don't know. Like
missing almost all of them. I think he just fits the stereotype. Like the, like I get off my lawn.
I'm down. I'm never going to find this. That was a family guy joke. Whatever. You get that
problem. Family guy had good jokes. Oh, there it is. That's your destroyer. No, it's not.
That's your destroyer. No, it's not. It's not even a destroyer. You're going too,
it's too much. You're going to miss this last one. Heads I go right, tails I go left.
God damn it. The coin. God in his head. That was me. That was all me. Don't think
German is even good. You're just really bad. Okay. Look, can you be bad at like throwing a
handful of popcorn in the air and just like looking at the ground and picking up one or two
random pieces? Can you be bad at that? Not really. I mean, let's be real. I did stack all of my ship
into the bottom left last round. I think that's a bad strat. Oh, I did the same thing though.
Yeah. But even you had the, the, you know, the redundancies of throwing a tugboat in the top
right as a security measure. All right. All right. All right. Well, this is fine though,
because what I'm doing is hustling you. Cause if I lose a couple, you start to get a little confident.
That's true. You could be just pulling the hustle on me and then I strike.
So where, where, what? That was one tier one sub and then one 10 subs,
one tier three sub 10 subs. You won $75. All right. How much did you go into the casino with?
What do you mean? Walked like last and Vegas. How much did you, how much did you go in with?
I went in with $900. Okay. I'm going to try to get $900 from you.
Well, you're trying to fuck me like the casino did. Yeah. I'll give some back sometimes.
You should think about me. We'll do another game where it's like, oh, this one's for $200.
And you'll, I'll just lose on purpose and I'll just give you $200. And then you'll keep playing
and I'll make it way harder. I have a really good strategy where if I lose like, let's say
$500, I'll chase my losses and bet another 500 to win it back. And then if I lose that,
I'll bet like a thousand to chase those losses and win that back. Um, wait, what is this? Hold on.
Alone in the dark. Is this like a, is this an alone in the dark game? What, what are you looking
at? Is this named dev? Why don't I'm confused? Like in the, in the, is that, no, that's my way.
Is that, it's my profile picture. I think. Are you looking at your own profile picture getting
confused? Yeah. I thought, I thought this was like an alone in the dark dev made this or something.
It was like an ad for alone in the dark. Now I understand that. I remember I made it alone
in the dark because it's such like an unassuming profile picture. I used to hide when I played TF
two. So people wouldn't know it was me. So I could just play a game and like hide and like make my
name like fucking like vacuum cleaner and like make my profile picture, something just completely
unassuming. So that's what that is. It's been that long since you've changed your profile picture?
Probably. Yeah. It's probably been like two or three years. That's insane. It's like, when you
hold tab, it's like, I didn't have, oh, German, like German, NA five, the germ, the logo. Like
I didn't do that. Like if you saw alone in the dark, you'd be like, oh, I don't fucking know
anything about that guy. I don't care. Right. Cause then if someone saw a German, they might,
they might just chase you the whole time. Yeah. Cause I wouldn't, I wanted to like be able to play
without having like any like, oh, there's like the guy, let's go get him or like, let's help him. I
wanted to be like completely a natural environment. All right. That commander was not working out for
me. It's time to buy a new one. I'm going complete free to play. I'm purchasing Sir Philip Wade. Look
at my ships. They're beautiful. Yeah. They actually, the art does change. That's true.
That's the only thing I'm paying. It's $3 every time I've spent $9 on changing the art of my
ships. I think you just woke up like one of the devs of this game from like Hasbro because they
just got like a text on their phone because that probably happens so infrequently that they have a
tied to notifications on their, on their cell phone. They have, it's like a wolf blast. They
get a text, an email, a Twitter notification. All right. So what do we, what do we got going
here for this one? What's going on here? So look, we've, we've, we've escalated. You've,
you've won, uh, two of the money ones. How about we, how about we remove the money for this one?
I have, I have a bit of a fun idea. Okay. The loser gets to buy a shirt for the winner that
they have to wear on stream camera on, of course. Okay. So wait, but I buy a t-shirt that you have
to wear on stream. You buy a t-shirt and I'll wear it on stream. Yeah, exactly. Okay. All right.
T-shirt the loser wants. Now I will say it must follow TOS. No, but yeah, it's, it's any t-shirt
the loser wants. Oh, this is way more. This is way more than like $20. This is worth a lot more to
me. This actually is more about, we could go back to money and save this one because we can do this
at any point. No, I, I, I, I'm into it. Someone said to look at the battleship category.
No, come on. What is this? What, what, what, what is it? Look at the battleship category.
Look at the battleship category. Yeah. On Twitch. Look at the fucking battleship category on Twitch.
All right. Hold on. I'm like a joke. I'm a slow boomer. It takes me a while.
No, take your time. Take your time. I'm sure it'll stay there for a while. Okay. Back to Twitch.
Battleship category. I'm so slow. You did this in two seconds. I'm like category dashboard.
Okay. Battleship. Where is it? Fuck. I'm too old for this. I didn't need help.
I'm going to link it to you. You just click open my link. They changed it. Did you? Oh, there we go.
Browse. Okay. And then you just got to show it to your chat. Okay. Battleship. What the fuck is it?
I linked it to you on discord. You can click it. Oh, thank you, son. Appreciate it. No, no problem.
Respect. Oh, it's the directory. Right. Oh, thank you, son. Person losing. German one, Ludwig zero.
Person watching who's losing. Person who's watching. I want to screenshot this. Oh, it's
unnecessary to screenshot. This is amazing. This is terrible. No, this is incredible. It's slightly
defamatory. I took a screenshot. I need that later. It's just my stupid face. And then someone who's
pointing to me losing and then someone watching me losing. Oh, we do. Should we encourage this or not?
I feel like we shouldn't because now someone said refresh. Oh, okay. Yeah. All right. Did it get
worse? Yeah, it did get worse. It's person who's watching the person who's watching who's losing.
Oh, my God. You guys, you are blowing up the Hasbro guy's phone. Another person went live
playing Hasbro's battleship. Oh, my goodness. I can't wait to see what they're doing. We need to
make a sequel to Battleship. All right. We'll let that be for a little while. Yeah, let that
fester and we'll come back to 18 people watching me lose. I need to win is what I'm noticing. I need
to make a little bit of a comeback story. I can't look. I can't go on forever. I don't think I can
win free in a row. You saying that is so stressful for me. Okay, I've gone one less ship. There's too
many. I've gone for a stratagem. This might be stupid. This is so stupid. What a stupid thing
I'm doing. Hold on. Let me see if this works. There we go. For people watching my chat like,
I mean, all right. All right. I've I've developed the stratagem tails. Come on. First and get it
goes first has a huge advantage. Just inherently as if you land, then you want you pretty much can get
one. You don't know what direction is though. You're from East Coast. Why did you do that?
Why did you do that? I clicked wrong. I just actually misclicked. What the fuck?
Wait, what did I just stumble upon? Jerma? What have you? The game is bugging for me.
The game is the game bugging for you. Oh, yeah. Is it bugging? I specifically remember a phrase
that would watch what I'm doing here. Come on, give me that might have been the greatest
misclick of all time. All right. You went northbound on both of these then.
Oh, that's huge. You went northbound. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Parallel. Look at this.
That was a misclick of this entry. No, this is bad. This is bad. I don't know. I don't finish.
Oh, you forgot about the ship. I think I see what you're doing. You're trying to see if I went that
way. They did the same thing. I'm not that much of an idiot. I just don't buy the mega milk shirt.
That just that's my one request. Don't say that one more time. Don't buy the mega milk shirt.
That's like my one request. Just don't do that for you. When I win this,
don't buy you the mega milk shirt. Yes. So please don't do that. Could you tell me why
I should show you mercy here? Well, first of all, you got to win. Oh my what?
You're looking at my screen. You're cheating. I want to win this one. Everyone gets one cheat.
Come on. It's Twitch. You know, you're allowed to cheat on one game show on one on one battleship
game. Oh, no. But the thing is, though, I have something very hidden. He's not going to understand
where it is. Okay. You know, be wicked funny if you got me in the t shirt for the band that I
fucking hate more than anything. What is that? I don't know. I don't think I want to tell you
because if you buy it, then it's really embarrassing. I have a like it almost feels
the way you're posturing. This is that you like you love this band. No, I have a thing with my
chat where we talk a ton of shit about the gorillas. Like I just hate them. They're like the worst
really in the history. Yeah. It's just like me going. I would hate if you got me a signed Tom
Brady jersey like that would suck so much. Please don't do that. Where are your ships? They don't
exist. You're doing the the old the old rabbit you're shooting around. Yeah, I really am. I
have no rhyme or reason to this. Oh, I think you put a ship in G3. You don't think about the
letters of the numbers, do you? No, I just my brain just goes fired there. There's no point.
I don't think the numbers mean much. No, you're probably right. I think I'm putting too much
weight into them. So what is this mega milk shirt? I'm going to look this up right now.
Don't don't don't look it up. No, I'm serious. I'm actually serious. Like you probably shouldn't
look it up on stream. That's I would look it up off stream. Well, no, don't. No, no, no, no, no.
Don't look it up off stream either. Don't even look. There's no reason to look it. What the
hell is this? It's not like, oh, hey, off stream. Go look at this. No, people are freaking out.
It's it's just it's like I don't know. I don't know. I can't even explain it. Just
don't look it up ever. OK, I looked it up on Amazon and what I saw was this shirt that said
mega milk. They're very tame. But then one of the shirts has an anime character. Yeah, don't look
it up. Really? OK, yeah. Yeah, I'm sorry. Be careful. You're not talking about that, right?
Like, obviously, that's not related. It's just a separate. No, somebody like that. Yeah,
that's unrelated. And it's not. Yeah, that's a bet. It's not even worth looking at. OK,
yeah, it's not even worth looking up. That makes sense. I wore that shirt, by the way.
The on stream. No, no, I have this shirt that's like a blue, like a Toronto Blue Jays
S baseball tee. It's the blue sleeves and the white on the front. And every time I wear it,
people say I'm wearing the mega milk shirt. And I'm just like, leave me alone. I like this shirt.
I like the colors. Who is Blue Jays S like the same color? Yeah, it's like it's like that blue
and white baseball. It's just a color. OK, all right. Yeah, I see that. So like the sleeves
are different color from the body and it looks like the mega milk shirt just without the text
on it. The more you talk about this, I have to tell you, the funnier it is, the more I want to
do this. Would I get suspended if I wore the mega milk shirt? Oh, I mean, look, Twitch is I am I
don't know which one you're talking about. You'd have to link it to me for me to know because I've
worn a slew of bad things slew. It's it's numerous because I do an Amazon stream. I let chat buy
anything and I'll wear it. So, you know, I've worn shirts that say like come in me. I'm here for the
bukkake. I have a set of keycaps that are just gatchy keycaps, just abhorrent things. I have a
six hundred dollar statue of Nami from one piece. OK, the first one has got you got you got me a
little twisted on that one that you wore that on stream. The come in me shirt. Yeah. Oh, yeah. I
wore that. I wore that out. I were away. We wear this frequently. I wore it like because I don't
leave my house often. So I wore it like, you know, a pretty good amount in my home because I thought
it was funny. But unlike, you know, without thinking much, I went to Vegas one time and I was
wearing that and I and I didn't realize until someone pointed at my shirt and went that that's
insane. It's just like, oh, shit. And I was like, oh, shit. And I put it inside out. I was embarrassed.
And so it said Mucknee M for the rest of the day. That's the kind of shirt you have to make sure
is not available if you have to do laundry or something like it's the only shirt left. Yeah.
Yeah. Finally, I fucking land on you. I do feel in a in a great spot right now because I only have
your destroyer, which is a five X ship. Yeah. It can only be in so many locations. I'm in trouble.
Let's see. This should be it. Oh, I get to live another day. What? Oh, you're up. Once you see my
strategy, it's going to change the battleship meta. You think so? I genuinely think so. I went
for a Jack and the Beanstalk method. Wait, does that mean that you went just in a straight line
the whole way? No, no, no, no. Although that's a great strategy, I'm sure. And I almost get the
feeling that you're throwing on purpose because you want to wear this mega milk shirt. I want to.
I don't even know why you would have bought something like I have no idea why I said that.
Yeah, I would have never. There's no universe where I would have gotten. You know what? I'm
going to get you a mega milk shirt. It's a you brought it up like, oh, please don't do this to
me. I don't know why I get the feeling you know, maybe party wants to try it. Oh, no,
I might not get the opportunity. But I don't know what kind of shirt would I get you if I absolutely
probably know I'm not going to win. Let's let's not worry about that. I still I only need one.
You only need one. But if you happen to get it, OK, you're covering my Jack and the Beanstalk.
I am whiffing a lot, though. Mm hmm. Mm hmm. On a five ship. Oh, come on. Painting around it.
OK, it's a five X. It can be here. It can be up here. All right. There's a two,
a two and a four and a three and three. I'll give you a hint. I'll make it spicy.
What? It's not. You said Jack and the Beanstalk. That would be straight up.
I'll give you a hint right now. You might need to refresh your browser on Twitter,
like the channel. I'm watching your channel right now that you refresh your channel.
It's F5. It's a it's like a technical joke. You're right here. No, you're not.
Joe, I told you were. Oh, you were telling me where you were.
I was telling you. Oh, it's F5. I thought you were doing like a hit F5.
You're watching my stream. I know you're cheating. Ha ha.
No, I was trying to give you information. Oh, but I think that was the only place
it could have been there. Well, congratulations. I feel good. I don't know if you threw that on
purpose, but my strategy was pretty impeccable. No, I thought you were going up up. Well,
we don't know if he's going to buy the Mega Milk shirt or not. You know what I mean? Nobody knows
that he could find a favor might have something really funnier to do. If you could just link me
the Mega Milk shirt you're referencing, what happens if I look up Mega Milk Jerma? Oh,
I do not think you should do that. And I'm serious about that one. I'm dead serious.
I don't know if you should write that. This is fine. It's just that the text can't be there's
nothing wrong with the text, right? Does Mega Milk mean something I'm unaware of? I don't know. I
don't know what it means. I just know it's something that's like TOS. Look up Mega Milk on a wiki.
That's a website I can't pull up. I don't know. I just know that it's like a thing. It's like a,
I got some kind of potentially sexual thing. I don't know. Okay. I'm looking this up. You
said the shirt you like it, but you're you're just wearing it here. I mean, in broad daylight,
you are wearing. No, that's somebody photoshopped that. That's not real. No,
how would they Photoshop with the lanyard? No, I know that image. Yeah. No, that's a Photoshop
shirt that they like. You're telling me that's not real. It's not real. No, I didn't wear it in
public. I don't know if I buy that. It seems like an innocent enough shirt. It's just look,
how about this? You'll just you'll think of something really funny to make me wear. And it's
definitely not going to be that one. All right. All right. I'm going to just link you an option
and you just look at it. And then I want you to react to it and tell me what you think. Okay. So
I did you give it to me as an image, by the way, because I'm so stupid. I don't, I don't,
I don't want to wear that. You're not a fan of this one. Okay. This is like, I don't, I,
can I even wear this? How did you, how did you not get in trouble for this?
Wearing your shirt that says, come in me. Hold on. I have to show it.
JPG. What is this? Why is this saved? Can I show this? I don't want to show this. I have to wear
this. This is what you're deciding on. Okay. We saw it. I don't want that on this camera.
Oh, I just muted and deafened at the same time. Sorry. You've been deafened for like probably
two minutes. I'm sorry. I hit the wrong button. That's all right. Are we going to have more of
these? Okay. I'm just sending you a few shirts that I think this one's pretty good too. You look
soft. Are you showing your chat yet? Yeah. Each one that comes in, they're getting, they're getting
a view of it. All right. All right. This is one I wore, uh, quite a lot actually. My, my girlfriend
took it. She, she likes wearing it now because it's a pretty comfy shirt, but, but affirmed,
they have been worn on stream. Oh my God. You said your girlfriend, you said your girlfriend,
where's this now? Regularly. I mean, all right. People are going to screen cap this. I have to
go like, no, no, no, I am. That's not me. No. Yeah. You have to have your, uh, uh, what about
this one? I do not look forward to wearing these. Okay. What do you got? What do you got for me?
What's the one? All right. And this is, this is one that I think is great. Which one? Here's
the final one I have. All right. There it is. This is a fun one. Hold on. I'm saving them.
Oh, I am. I'm a hundred percent American, 75% Irish, 60% water, 50 cents, biggest fan, 40 pounds
overweight, seven years from retirement and five minutes from having to shit at this lows.
This shirt sucks. Yeah, it does suck. This looks like an old like webpage from 1995.
Yeah. Yeah. It'd be like the, like the banner for like some shitty ass, you know,
blog form or whatever. What is this one? So this, this is what you've narrowed it down to.
Oh, I mean, I'll, I'll mull over a bit. Uh, you know, maybe chat can inspire me some more.
A lot of people want you to have this one. I'll, I'll send it to you, but I, I wouldn't do this to
you. Cause I think this one's abhorrent. I think just even owning this is a bit of an atrocity.
What am I owning? If you like owned this, cause you'd wear it. Obviously you'd have to, I don't
want that one. I don't want this one. I know. That's why I'm saying I don't want, I don't want
this one. No, I know. Please spare me. Please spare me. I'll wear the cum shirt. I'll wear the
cum shirt. Okay. I'm serious. I'm not wearing this one. Where is it? I, I, I, no, no, no. Okay. All
right. I'll know. I would, anyone, but this one, if chat was to decide, that's what they would do.
They would put that one on your body, but I wouldn't do that to you. Cause I understand there's,
you know, there's lines, but I'll, I'll mull it over. I'll have to look at this mega milk a bit
more. I got, I got, I got $70 and you got to humiliate me in front of everybody. Yeah. It does
seem a bit imbalanced. Doesn't it? What's a monetary equivalent to how much you wear that
shirt on stream for 70 bucks. I've worn that shirt for free. I paid for it. Yeah. You've worn the
pizza, pizza one with the, yeah. So I do an Amazon stream and I, and I let them buy anything
and I only get three vetoes. So I could veto that shirt or I could veto like a $10,000 engagement
ring. So I, you know, I have to pick my battles. Hold on people. That's so funny, dude. They just
link whatever they want. And let me tell you that you buy cars on Amazon. You can, yes you can. You
can buy a Chevy, a Ford. That's so funny, dude. All right. That's amazing. The category of
battleship has blown up. Checking the battleship category. Let's see it. Oh, it's, it's, it's gone
off the deep end. It's there's, there's just someone with a mega milk shirt. You want to play
among us. These people, you're all going to get banned. You remember Bukaki 4k webcam.
You guys are all going to get your like channels banned. Look at this guy. It's a big Jerma
supporter. Go Jerma go. This dog's pretty cute. One of these guys has like a hundred viewers.
Yeah. The losing 50, 50. Yeah. The person playing among us says it's doing, doing well actually.
Yeah. They're, I think they're just playing among us. This one's just trying to get you to add an
emote. Jerma Sag. This person is jerking off on stream. Can you define zirking for me? It's from
that streamer simulator game where everything, everything had a Z replaced at the front of the
word. Right. That is a good game. It is pretty good. This is an auto emote. I can't keep track.
Chicken McNugget. I'm looking at you kissing, uh, Chuck E. Cheese. Did you ever hear the story of
that? Of you kissing Chuck E. Cheese? Yeah. Oh yeah. I'm not familiar with that. No. Chuck E.
Cheese raided the channel like last year. Oh, like the corporation. Like actually like Chuck E.
Cheese was streaming Fall Guys or something and he like raided a host of the channel and somebody
said, put this on stream. And I said, what is it? And I, and I, I didn't like really want to put it
on stream, but like, I just did it anyways. And like, I think I, I think I fucked up and put it
on twice. Um, it was me kissing Chuck E. Cheese, like on the lips and they had already had it made.
It was already, it was already ready. They had me kissing Chuck E. Cheese. But the funniest part
about it is the Chuck E. Cheese stock price tanked when the image showed up on stream.
Like actually like in real, like actually the real stock went down. Like when Cristiano Ronaldo said,
I don't drink Coke and the stock plummeted, you have the same effect on Chuck E. Cheese.
But like, I don't think that's what happened. I think they had like some kind of announcement
or some kind of news or somebody like sold for some reason. And like, it just happened to line
up to like the 10 minute window of me showing it on stream. I like to imagine the largest Chuck E.
Cheese shareholder just watches you, you know, for entertainment and then happened to see that
and thought, you know what, it's, it's time to pull out. It's time. I don't think it was related
at all though. It was like just some weird, hilarious coincidence. I think what is this?
So what, all right. So what are the stakes of the next one? If we're going to keep upping the stakes
here and then now what, how do we go from, how do we, how do we add to, to the stakes?
How do we add to the stakes? So look, we, we flipped off money. We can, we can go back to money.
You want to go, you want to go back to cash? We could do like, uh, I think it's time.
We could do the a hundred gifted match. Okay. Cause I think the, if we're escalating shirts,
that then it goes outfits. Then, then one of us is going to become a cat made for a day.
Have you worn a cat girl costume before? No, I haven't. You haven't?
Bugleberry, right? That's, that's my answer. If I looked up for instance, like cat boy,
you would find plenty of material. That's for sure. That is a lot of it. That's more fan art
than times you've worn it. Surely. Oh yeah. Probably by a hundred times. That's crazy.
Fan fiction goes a long way. Uh, are you, are you getting the rematch? Oh yeah. Sorry. I, uh,
Oh, there he is clubbing, but I'm happy to do a 100 gifted match. You want to do a hundred gifted
subs? I think that's a, that's a strategy. All right. All right. A hundred gifted subs. Let's do
it. Okay. Sir Philip Wade. He's never lost. This is really important. This is, this is for a lot
of money. Do this. I'm ready. I'm not ready. I'm not ready. Hold on. This is a bad strat.
Is that good everybody? That's weird, right? That's like a weird one that he won't ever figure it
out. No, you're throwing. No, I'm not. I don't think he's going to get this. I think this is
the winner right here. I really do. That's the winner. God. Are you happy with yours?
I am as happy as I think I could be. I think my chap bullied me out of my strategy, which was a
straight line up the middle. I, you probably would have won. That was a mistake. I I'm, I'm kind of
like a frog brain. I probably wouldn't have done it. Uh, I think you've gone back to being a corner
Karen. See what if you went, what if you did this though? What if you went right in the middle?
If you get this, okay. All right. Save. All right. I got this. I know where you are
living another day. I have a fine amount of time before you hit. I gotta make this count. Oh no.
Oh God. All right. All right. So here's your destroyer right here. Oh no, you went down. Yep.
Yep. I think, I think you try. I think you're avoiding all the edges. Corner Karen is this a
waste of my time. I feel like I'm wasting this. You're not a corner. Karen, maybe you avoid it.
Not in those corners, not in those corners. Oh, you're trying to get me to click the last
corner, but I'm, I'm too smart. I'm never going to click the last corner. Well, then I guess
you're never going to win the game. You've swayed me. You're a villain. What if I told you something
was right next to my destroyer? It probably is. I'll get there eventually. Don't worry. I'm just,
I'm just saying what if I told you not that I'm not telling you that. Okay. Oh, all right. All
right. But I mean, it could be anywhere. It would have been so bad ass if I had hit another ship.
Oh, you're just trying to be like, throw the, throw the ball behind your back and swish. Yeah.
I wanted to try to, that's, that was someone who has never seen basketball before. Try to explain
that. What? You said throw the ball behind the back and swish. It sounded like you'd never seen
the sport of basketball before. Oh no. I'm talking about like you, you like turn around and like face
away from the hoop and just throw it backwards and try and get a swish. Oh yeah. Just behind the
back. Yeah. Yeah. And absolute. It was a, it was a YOLO attempt. Oh, you thought I meant like,
oh yeah, the guy that like throws the ball around it back and goes into the hoop, that thing.
Like an announcer's first day on the job. Oh shit. Oh, all right. All right. I'll make a wager with
you. Oh wait, right now? No, no, no, no. I was going to say if you got the right direction,
I'd give you five subs. Oh shit. You, you got it. You got it. I feel good about that. I think,
if you land this next one right here, that just this next hit, it just has to be the next hit.
I'll wear the mega milk shirt tomorrow. Oh my God. Oh my God. I have a feeling your strategy
was having your ships go from the edge towards the center. So only one piece of it touches the edge.
I don't, I don't know. I don't think so right now by like my heart is like, oh, like kind of,
this is a bit stressful. Well, cause I, well, I didn't want to wear the mega milk shirt tomorrow.
Yeah. That would have been bad for you. It would have been. Oh, okay. Okay. Here, here, here.
All right. I will wager you five gifted. You don't know which direction I'm going here.
So if I hit, it's wrong. That's right. But if you miss, thank you. I'll get that. Yeah. I'll
get that right away. I do have to open your stream to give that though. Why don't we keep a tally so
that we can just remember later? Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Cause it is kind of like a, you have to like
this and then you're going to accept and then process and then I was saying, cause I would
see where you are. Oh, right. Yeah. Hey, don't do that. Hey, don't do that. Oh no. Are you
shitting me? Oh no. And it's right here. Are you shitting me? Oh no. You're in a lot of trouble.
I am in a lot of trouble. I think you've discovered my stratagem. Oh, you get another
one here. If you get at one right here, you're doing, you're doing like the, like the everybody's
facing in. No, no. I found you out. I was doing, it was a cross is, you know, like a,
like a Christian cross. Well, it's you're in a lot of trouble now. Well, you'll never get my two
boat. Imagine it's just in the center, linking everything that you were drawing. Uh, okay.
There we go. Oh, left, right. I'm actually, but oh no, maybe it's a tugboat going down.
So this, this might take me a while because it's just your two boat. That's the only thing.
It's just my two boat and it should realistically take you about 10 shots
to get here. Realistically. But it's too bad that it's right here. It's too bad that it's right
here. I thought you were going to do a thing where it's like up. That was a dangerous shot.
Oh, cause now you've left the corner open. Can you do it? Can you do it? Can you do it?
Toy boat, toy boat, toy boat, toy boat, toy boat, toy boat, toy boat, toy boat, toy boat. Toy boat,
toy boat, toy boat, toy boat, toy boat, toy boat. That's another time gift it's up.
You practice you're embarrassing me now. I
Have actually have I do that all the time. They have a lot of practice that was actually really good for a first-timer
I'll tell you
Yeah, you guys are like meet meetings you do meetups. Oh some people people can't even get past the second one
That was pretty good. That really was I'm serious. I appreciate that. I used to do when I was younger
There's some French tongue twisters. You could try
It's so it's um the the English translations if your uncle shaves your uncle
Uncle be shaved but in French it sounds like it's very literal
The French one is sit on m
Oh, say it again. Yeah, I want to hear that again.
On your pizzeria.
Say it again?
It's, so it's
that's yours.
That's how you say uncle.
Tom, which is shave
Tongue your
Tom Tom
will be shaved.
I feel like the Charlie Brown parents talking...
...don't you.
We are now just the adults.
We can't communicate with the children anymore.
Uhhh...
Did you still have a destroyer somewhere?
There we go.
That wasn't a Family Guy joke.
That was literally...
He just said a thing in French.
They're calling my joke a Family Guy joke?
It just said Family Guy joke.
I know.
It's unbelievable.
I can't believe them.
Every...
Everything we try to do on this platform,
Peter fucking Griffin is already done.
I can't believe he's not in Fortnite.
I was so sad when he didn't get in.
Oh, you got him.
Wait, that's huge for me.
That actually...
That's very big.
This could be a comeback of epic proportions.
I'm actually kind of nervous because,
like you said,
I have to find just your little two guy.
Yeah.
And that could be anywhere.
I...
I do think you have a strategy that might be in my favor here.
Oh, it could be anywhere.
It's gonna take me forever to find this.
Alright, I just have to...
I have to rein it in.
Just focus.
It's gonna be, like, in a weird place, like...
I'm trying to clear every 5x area.
Why is everybody saying Aaron?
I'm not gonna do that.
Aaron?
No, I'm not gonna...
I'm not gonna embarrass myself in front of Ludwig.
No.
Wait, what's Aaron?
It's just...
It's this thing that people like that I say.
Do what?
Say it.
Okay, have you ever watched Attack on Titan?
Yeah, of course.
Okay, have you watched...
The dub of Attack on Titan or the sub?
I think I've watched both, but mostly the sub.
But I think my first season was dubbed.
So you've seen, like, the dubbed actors in the show?
Yes, yeah.
So if I were to go like this...
Aaron! Aaron! Aaron!
You would know what that was?
Yeah.
Okay.
I would imagine that's the blonde twerp.
You're...
What the fuck?
You just hit two.
What the hell's going on here?
Am I right?
Yes, that would be Armin Arlott.
Yeah, that's him.
I like that show.
Do you like that show?
I do.
Do you watch a lot of anime?
Do you consider yourself...?
Once a year.
I get myself one anime a year.
That's what I'm allowed to do.
That's just so you don't become a weeb or...?
It's just because at time and, you know, there's a million animes.
You get sucked in, you watch like a hundred of them.
You're right.
I get myself one anime a year.
I only watch...
No! No, he's got it.
He's got it.
Just one more and he's got it.
Oh, thank the Lord.
Now I have to find it.
Everything's on to this.
Right.
It would be the greatest comeback of all time if you get this.
There are two places where it could be.
Because I don't think that you would put it this close.
I don't.
You're either right here, right here, or here.
You want a hint?
Uh...
No, I don't trust your hints.
I think you're one of these two.
Give you a hint.
Because this would be like a perfect map if it was like one of these two.
I'll give you a simple hint and this is honest.
Dude, that little tugboat, it was right next to my destroyers to the left of it.
Oh, no!
Oh, now I have to give you a hundred subs?
Let me tell you, you were right.
You called it.
You were like, oh, I've won these petty games for $75.
And I have to wear the fucking cum t-shirt and pay you $500.
This is exactly what happened.
Taking you for all your worth, your pride, your dignity, and your wallet.
I won the two games.
This is like the pool shark.
You know what I mean?
Like, oh, hey, how about the first game for 20 bucks?
And it's like, oh, man, I missed.
I suck at pool.
And then you just clean me out before I leave.
That's exactly the plan.
All right, well, draw it down.
I'll get it to you at the end of the stream.
Yeah, yeah, no rush.
No rush.
All right.
So how much higher can we go with this one?
So we could, we're going to reach a point of power creep where we've gone too high.
Yes.
And here's the thing about me.
I live my life by the gambler's philosophy.
So once I start to lose a little money, I'll dump my net worth till I get it back.
I don't think I'm the right guy to guide this ship.
I'll let you make the next bet.
Well, that was a money one.
Yeah, that was.
So what if we up the stakes into a non-money one?
What would it look like?
I'll throw out a couple of things that work.
One is a tweet.
A tweet of the of the of the person's choosing.
Uh-huh.
Yeah.
That's pretty good.
I would get a tweet on your Twitter.
Oh, those are rare.
Those are rare.
But it's it's it's pretty equal value.
I would say because you rarely tweet.
That's true.
And I tweet pretty much all the time with my sponsored shit.
Yeah, you probably have like five times the followers that I have.
But I have a few more followers.
Exactly.
So it's about even because the rarity versus the just the followers.
Okay, I like this one.
Yeah, we get to you get to craft a tweet.
Wait, is this like a so like it would be as if it was me tweeting, but you wrote the tweet.
Exactly.
Yeah, you would never be able to explain because you know, we have a good amount of viewers here.
But you know, we have hundreds of thousands of followers.
You'd never be able to explain to those followers why that was tweeted or be like,
oh, I had to tweet this because of some dumb bet.
Oh, yeah, it has to be like you just this is you talking.
I'm going to show you an example of a tweet.
I had to do because I lost a bet against, you know, disguised toast.
Yes, I had lost a wager to him.
And maybe this isn't the best to pull up on stream.
But but here's the tweet regardless.
I'm not a picture or video.
Yes, but I would say I won't go as harsh as as as toasted.
Do you see the tweet?
Oh, let me see.
I saw the pizza thing.
What is this underwear?
Is this you?
This is my ass.
It's a picture of me in briefs with the caption.
Anyone want to sniff what the fuck?
Toast was not he was not exactly gracious and victory.
He was quite merciless.
Anyone want a sniff?
Yeah, and it's a picture of my butt in briefs.
Okay, because I was going to say I was going to like just have you take a picture of like
an apple core and just have the like the text over B.
What the fuck, dude?
And I mean, like something that like, yeah, that's what I was going to have you do.
No, that's that's what I would go for.
I would I would this this is, you know, toast went all out.
I'm showing you this is like this is a high end.
You know, it's probably like this is where it caps out.
I'm not expecting this or going to do this if I won.
And I don't I would hope, you know, you wouldn't do this to me if you won.
It's more so an example of a tweet in the past.
Okay.
Hold on.
I got to show this because it's important.
I didn't even show it yet.
There's maybe no eyebrows, but don't look at that one yet.
That's a great thing to have right there.
Just pull up your shoe.
That's a bit of a zoom.
Actually, that's going on.
This is your ass.
What what are you doing?
I'm staring at a portrait of myself.
By the way, I think that you have been the first person
to ever have me show the word of become on my screen, by the way.
Just want to make sure we're clear on that one.
Should I be ashamed or proud?
Probably probably both.
It's a mixture.
All right.
So I think that's it.
That's a fair wager.
Oh, that's fair.
Did you just purchase Sir Philip Wade?
No, I didn't buy anything.
It shows on my screen that you're playing a Sir Philip Wade.
Wait, what?
Yeah, what's going on?
What's this?
This is you?
Yeah, I think this is we're in the same game.
But for whatever reason, all right, I have a genius strategy
to line my ships here.
Can you give me a number between one and ten, please?
Three.
Now, are you under the impression that Battleship is somewhat
of a skilled game?
Yes, I think it's very I think this is going to be huge.
Okay.
Yeah.
Do you not think so?
No, it's not just asking questions.
Yeah, like we are.
This is like a this is a pre-show how everybody is going to
be playing this.
This is a huge deal, right?
Like everyone's going to love this game.
Everyone's going to get into it.
Roof to you that this is a game made for children that that,
you know, actual just trained monkeys would do better in.
I've randomly placed my ships and I'm using a random picker
to shoot your ships down randomized shot randomized placements
against your strategies.
So it will see if I was able to win with pure randomness that
I proved to you.
This is a game for little baby boy children.
My strategy is not good.
The best way to go about this is to do it twice, which is
there's no way.
I mean, no, there is no way you know where you can get it.
It's that yeah, that's one space.
That was another another bat behind the back swish attempt.
I'm random number generating every single hit you are.
Yeah, what?
Yes.
So every time I hit so you'd randomly generating the number
and the letter.
Yeah, I'm just basically doing to one through tens and then
just cow first down and then over well shit.
That's a huge advantage for me.
We'll see.
I have a feeling that this is an impeccable strategy and actually
might be very good in 95% of every game.
Are you committing to this the whole game?
I think I might follow up on some of the reds because random
number generators don't do well after a hit.
Mm-hmm.
Oh, no.
All right.
You're right here.
You always put one here.
Oh, no.
What?
That's your poker face.
You always discovered me.
Yeah.
All right.
Or North South East West.
That doesn't matter how many pairs of hoods and sunglasses
you put on.
I can see right through this.
I know you have one here every time.
All right.
North South East or West North North South East or West
North again.
There we go.
Oh, all right.
All right.
Let me do one more random and then I'm going to try following
up.
Yeah.
The longer this goes the worse.
I feel like my strategy is.
Okay, there goes your destroyer, but that's the easiest one.
I want to find you.
This one.
Oh, I still think you did something like that.
I'm bad at counting.
It turns out.
Hmm.
I think I think you did something like this.
I really do.
Well, you have to understand I'm not lying to you.
I randomized it.
Oh, okay.
All right for this one.
Oh wait, you didn't.
Oh, I see what you mean.
And the ships were randomly placed.
Oh, all right.
So that actually is an advantage for me.
Although you coincidentally did get my destroyer.
Oh my gosh.
Yeah, if you go to the right here, this is brutal.
I'm thinking somebody faces into my face cam like every time
like I click I turn I go like I'm just such a good fucking
YouTube face.
All right, whatever you got you good reactions destroyer.
Okay.
Yeah.
Yeah, whatever.
All right.
Seven six.
Well, whatever you got that one where we're even now.
It's perfectly even unless you happened to hit something
here.
Oh, you don't.
Oh, this would be a funny one funny one.
Why funny is there a Jason?
Yeah, that would be actually very funny humorous in a way.
That would be very funny.
I get it was randomly generated ships and it would be
it would freak me out if you actually did that that'd be
so funny.
Okay.
All right.
I might abandon my strategy here.
I'm realizing this this guy I might swing over to your
side.
This could be a game of skill.
It's incredibly frivolous what you're up to.
How are you not down there?
I don't know.
Okay.
You hate the edges.
You love the center fail again and for what right I left
the right you're right.
Yeah, this is it right here.
Oh, come on.
I tried to sway you with the left or right.
Yeah, I would I would say you're flailing right now.
If it were me what is on the line here a tweet a tweet what
I would love to tweet on your Twitter account for sure.
Finally, it's my turn.
I think the computer went that way.
You think the computer has rhyme or reason.
Oh fuck a phenomenal hit that was randomly generated.
Oh, did you did you t-bone yourself t-bone?
What does that mean?
Like did you put a ship going into your ship so that it
would be a collision that would be very unwise.
Oh, you connected it to you actually t-boned yourself.
There's no confirmation that that's what happened.
Well, if there's a what do you think the ship pulls a
last-second left turn?
It's an L-shaped ship.
All right.
I'm gonna have to freeze Ludwig.
I have a feeling did you grow up Catholic at all?
Yeah, okay.
I thought per chance there was a there was a cross of
David or that doesn't make any sense of Christ.
Come on.
How are you not there?
Okay, back to my strat.
What a oh, I already done it.
Then I'll just do my own.
What's your favorite animal favorite animal?
What's your favorite animal is a zebra zebra finds a frog.
Why I kind of just like word you the the reason it's your
favorite is because of the word.
I've enjoyed the word especially the letters.
I love that green frog.
Are you hinting at something could it be?
Does he need more tweets?
What did your computer do?
That was a terrible shot by the computer.
No, I'm all right.
It's right here.
How is it possible?
They all have probably up top.
I would never say you definitely there's no way you're
not up here somewhere.
This thing is statistically impossible.
I promise you that northbound will be in your your undoing
you think so.
There's no way you're here.
With these apps could a strategy be so simple that he's
trying to get me to go in the effort where nothing is.
Oh my God.
What are you up to over there?
Jerma nothing nothing.
I could really take this home, but I'm going in everything
that every place that you're not is impossible.
That's a re redo.
Is that random or was that you?
I had it had already been on that spot the one that it
selected.
So I went it's kind of my rule.
It's random unless it already had picked it picked one
that's already been shot.
All right.
You have just have little ones left right here.
I got a couple little ones.
Yeah, that's right.
I mean you have just a lot left.
I do have quite a bit ones currently.
You have right on this one.
Maybe you have a four somewhere.
All right.
This is this is me going here.
I could cover that was such a bad shot.
It was just a bad shot.
Oh, oh, come on.
There's no more.
How many more places can you be?
Three two.
I think well, you've you've left entire sections open.
Yeah, maybe a little bit or three.
What a terrible what a terrible follow-up.
There's this is the worst randomly generated shot of all
time.
It only hits a tugboat that just happens to be adjacent.
Maybe you are like right here.
No one three.
They're actually screwing me.
Look, you see I've done like a row.
I'm just cleaning out entire row.
I'm suddenly thinking the strategy is not impeccable.
I think that's we've already done that.
Yeah, we have.
Okay.
It's me again.
Do you let's let's let's clear out.
Let's clear out this one here covers up and down for three.
Hmm.
I have to assume that you're because you have a two, you know
what I like, but you have to understand this was not me.
This was not you.
That's right.
It doesn't matter if I'm a middle man in go in go.
All right.
There we go and eight.
We've already done that.
What are you laughing at?
Nothing just I mean, there's a bit of laughter.
It was a little bit of laughter, but it was kind of humorous
what just happened.
Me shooting was kind of humorous back back in this bullshit
again.
We're where your two is.
I mean, I guess you aren't random got one.
Is that the letter F was no what a terrible round to do
randomly generated shots on.
I know it's not over.
It's not even close to being over.
No, especially considering I found your two.
Well, good for me.
You did what?
No, it's not my two seven ten going in Shirley.
It has to be a three or two.
No, it's going up.
Damn it should have I shouldn't have talked myself out shit.
Okay, that you too.
No, no, this is a three.
It's up or down here.
Okay.
All right.
I got I got I got a nail this right now.
Okay, this you have struggled on twos before there are 3000
places.
This one could be there are but all right, you're going in.
I painted around this.
I've genuinely painted around this one the Lords.
All right.
You got a good shot here.
Okay.
And by good shot.
I mean it could be anywhere it could this could be B 10 C 10.
All right.
I'm going down now and that means the only ship left is a
three-man boat.
I don't think a randomly generated thing functions as well
anymore.
Cause there's there's three where is there a three is could
be this here doesn't places.
Yeah, that was a weird choice.
It was because you could have gotten left one and covered
more.
Okay, I'm a bit stressed out right now.
I am too.
This this covers a lot.
No, I have to think about this is no longer random surely
you didn't do anything to muddy the letter F.
So this must have been a displaced boat to have somewhat
of a coverage in case I found the F it could be like a J 3.
No, we should have done one more to the right.
It could be a really tall F.
I mean that would be interesting if I were to do something
like that, wouldn't it?
I can't tell if you're trying to convince me not to do it.
I guess I I thought the F was over but it could have just
been beginning.
I mean that was very interesting.
If I were you I would maybe take a shot.
Wait, you did do that.
Yeah, why don't you tell me that I was doing the psychology
thing where you're like, oh, why would you tell me?
I thought you're telling no, no have to tweet something.
What a tall F I was going to do the whole thing, but I figured
of course it was right there.
Yeah, the randomly generated was terrible.
I mean you didn't have the best stratagem for sure.
But I lost the last three in a row.
I won the first like two or three in a row.
You know what it is.
It's whoever gets the tugboat first almost just assuredly
wins.
Yeah, cuz finding the tugboat as the last thing is it's miserable.
It's the worst.
So I have a I have a I have a tweet now.
Yeah, you get to have a tweet.
This is this is valuable.
I mean, this is this is I tweet something maybe once every
like four months.
Yeah, you're not a the most avid Twitter user is a reason
for that.
Yeah, it's kind of you know, just don't care.
Yeah, sure.
You know, I think it is because I can never think of anything
to say I have somebody drafted tweets that is right and then
I just delete right.
See what I'll do is I'll send it and then I'll and I'll delete
it which I think is harder to do because sometimes after you
already said to you don't want to delete it which which makes
me tweet more often.
Exactly.
I'll read you my last two drafts.
Yeah, please.
Fortnite is starting to look a lot like those old Smash Brothers
character leak screens the ones with Heathcliff Pepper Anne
and Al Bundy on them in the other one if almonds are available
I'll eat them till I throw up.
All right.
Can you speak on that one?
I just I don't know if a bag of almonds is there.
I'm just going to keep eating him till somebody tells me
to stop eating them, but I didn't know those I did though
those I'm like, yeah, do you do you have the ability to
to protrude your stomach?
Yes, like in a pretty severe way that people would think,
you know, you're working on a baby.
Wait, you want you want a jokey stomach protruding like
in the okay, not just in a mirror like in the oven reflection
that you see and you go holy shit.
Is that me?
Yeah, is that something you're capable of doing?
Do you want a stomach protrusion picture?
Okay, how waste up full body?
I think a stomach protrusion picture with with your second
drafted tweet is you want that to be honest use you tweet
so rarely that anything is great here.
So you want if almonds are available.
I will eat them till I throw up and do the like I got a
big stomach picture.
Yeah, like, you know, kind of like how Twitter would be
used in like 2013.
God.
Okay, I'll do it.
Just I could eat almonds till I throw up and then you know,
your stomach so full because you've eaten so many almonds.
It's it's comical in a way.
All right.
This sounds good to me.
What do you want?
What do you want my hands?
Am I like like holding it like like underneath like it's
a big globe or like a big bug juggly or what am I doing?
I think you create creatively can can take this any direction
you want because I think you know what my sentiment what
my what my desire is here and you can you can get it done.
Somebody said this is literally fetish art.
It does feel like any time you even like any part of you
that you give out to your stream is just is just taken
and they just run with it.
There's going to be fan art for years on pregnant.
Germa.
I'll do my I'll do my best.
All right.
Can I go pee?
Yeah.
Yeah, please.
Please enjoy.
I'll be right back.
I'm going to go pee.
I'm looking forward to this.
Yeah, of course.
Of course.
All right.
I'm back.
It was one of those times where you pee.
It just doesn't stop.
You know what I mean?
Oh, did he just go afk?
All right.
Well, whatever we can wait.
We can have why you guys not playing the advanced game
mode.
I mean you play classic is an advanced game mode.
It will do that in a minute.
When we talked about doing the stream was just like,
oh, maybe we'll play this like 45 minutes.
Maybe do something else.
I'm very invested.
I have to try to at least make some what I may I got $70
the first like two or three games.
So let's let me get let's let's break this down a little bit.
So I won the first few games and I got 70 bucks.
He won the last few games and gets $500 a tweet on my Twitch
and gets to make me wear a cum t-shirt.
This is fierce.
That's a little skewed.
I have to win one of the big ones.
I got to win a big one.
I actually got pool shark.
You get a free shirt though.
That's right.
Five gifted.
Why do you have such a hard time saying the word penis?
Please explain like that time.
You thought your zipper was down.
You almost said the word penis five times but stopped.
I don't know.
I said it there.
Hello.
How are you?
Good.
Just just pissed.
Yes.
Why?
Oh, you went to the bathroom.
You went pee.
I thought you meant that I'm just sitting here pissed like I took
too long or something.
No, no.
I had to go, you know, I had to go to the bathroom.
Do you pee sitting down by the way?
No.
Have you ever used a bidet?
No, I find them to be revolting.
What?
Yes.
Are you a bidet user?
This is going to fracture us in a way.
Are you sure?
I need to be enlightened.
Explain to me.
So let me let me tell you what I think when I think of a bidet.
So when you after you're done with the bathroom, if you go to
the bathroom, you finish just over.
Turning a water jet into your asshole.
Wouldn't you get shit and poop water all over your legs and
butt and stuff and have to make more work for yourself?
I don't understand.
Explain it to me.
I need it.
I need to know.
Right.
Okay.
All right.
That first of all, I'm not going to come at you.
You just seem to be a little bit ignorant on on all the
positives.
So I don't want to shame you.
Second of all, it's it's the greatest thing I've ever used
has changed my life.
I'm a bidet, not just a user.
I'm like a I'm like a salesman for bidets.
Okay, tell me so you can get you can get like a rinky-dink
one on Amazon.
It's like $30.
It blasts cold water at Mach 5 in your asshole.
And it's not comfortable.
I use a fancier bidet.
I use right now the Toto SW 2034.
Is that okay?
Is that like a AMD chip?
What was that?
This is about as expensive as a 3090.
All right, let's just put it that way.
Okay.
This has five different types of oscillating sprays 10
different pressure gauges.
All right, warm heated water also an air drying capability.
So you don't even need to use, you know, toilet paper if
you didn't want to comes with a deodorizer comes with white
noise maker.
So if you're if you're pooping and you don't want people
to know you're pooping they make it doesn't work.
That shit doesn't work about how loud your TV is.
Everyone's going to hear the like you've never you've never
used the Toto look it's it's just more hygienic.
You're you're cleaning a rug that has dirt on it with with
like, you know, sandpaper.
What kind of toilet paper are people using?
I'm just saying even you're using three-ply.
It's it's cleaning a rug with bounty.
That's not going to take it out of water.
What about the wet wipes, right?
What about like the wet wipes you they do not as they're
good, but they're not they're not as great for the environment
also need to keep re upping them.
You know that they're not always flushable.
Look, I understand it.
I will say it's it's a it's a concentrated spray.
It's not going to get on your legs.
That's absurd.
But isn't confined isn't your asshole wet?
How do you how do you go from like spraying your butt and
butthole with water to like now I'm putting my underwear
back on that always confused me.
So you use the bidet and then it's a it's a one wipe.
Here's my sales.
No way.
So I'm sorry.
I don't feel I that doesn't make me feel clean.
Let me tell you what if every poop for the rest of your
life was a one wiper.
It's impossible.
That's what a bidet does because I'm not normal though.
I have like colitis.
Like I don't think that would work for me.
It would be like messy.
No, it'll it will work for you.
Trust me.
Look, how about this?
How about this?
I'm going to get you bidet.
All right, you're going to buy me a bidet.
I'm going to buy you bidet.
I'll help.
I'll help you set it up.
You can try it.
If you don't like it, I'll take it out of your sight.
I'll burn it.
I'll destroy it.
We'll have you know, that scene in the office space where
they destroy the fax machine.
Yeah, we can do that with the bidet.
If you don't like it, it already did.
I already make this joke on my stream that like me having
a bidet, I would do the like laugh out loud Will Ferrell
skit where he like needs to take a drink out of water
and he like takes a drink out of the bidet fountain, right?
Like that's a Will Ferrell thing.
I already make that joke.
You haven't made that joke yet.
Okay, it's up for grabs.
I just made it.
Oh, sorry.
We can redo it.
All right.
Do you think that was funny?
Yeah, it was great.
Well, it's actually too close at home.
I've drank out of a bidet for $40 a couple years ago and
it was a big it was a big meme.
And then I did it again last month for $50.
Why are you drinking out of a bidet for $50?
Because 50 bucks is 50 bucks.
I mean you put that on a craft table.
You could walk out with a Rolex.
Why do I imagine you with like crooked sunglasses on like
eight drinks in?
Just like, yeah, man, I'll drink out of the bidet.
Fuck it.
You're gonna give me 60 bucks.
I'm just sitting in the bathroom and people are coming
in.
I'm just harassing them.
Oh, you think I won't you think I won't and they're like,
can we get can we get a little bit out of the bathroom?
He's just drinking out of the bidet.
He's annoying.
He said eight drinks get a load of this guy.
He thinks I won't like no, and I don't want you to I keep
lowering the amount of money that I'll do it for 40.
You think I won't pay you to drink out of this bidet right
now.
You think I won't do that.
You just don't you put your hands on it.
You do a headstand and like keg stand the bidet.
I'm way too adept at it.
I'm too skilled at drinking out of it.
People are weirded out.
Yeah, that's that's that's me.
No, they're amazing.
I'm gonna I'm going to do that.
I've done this before for a different friend of mine.
You've purchased bidets for multiple people.
Eventually, I'm not lying to you.
Eventually.
My goal is to create my own bidets and sell them.
Jesus, did you really want me to play World of Warcraft?
That's like the I need to get my friend to play World of
Warcraft.
Hey, I'll buy for the first month, man.
I'll push you up.
You need items.
Oh, let me tell you the lore of this place.
This gets me no there's no this is a selfless endeavor.
Oh well until I sell them then that's a selfish endeavor.
But for now, it's a selfless endeavor because I just think
it's such a great product.
You know, it's World of Warcraft because I'm trying to play
with you this.
I don't know what happens when you shit germ.
I've never I've never thought about it till today.
You just want me to have a much better experience.
Yeah, I want you to feel about shitting how I do which is
it's like a it's like a good experience pleasurable not well,
that's not it's not pleasure, but it's a good experience.
It's like a it's a good experience.
It feels good experience.
It's a positive experience is what I was looking for.
Okay, is it before we move on one final question does the
water hit you in the bag of you know what I'm saying?
I imagine I imagine like really cold water hitting me right
in the balls and it's like, oh, okay.
All right.
Well, look there there is much like a car seat when you get
in for the first time maybe you're a little too far up and
you need to crank it back.
But after you've done it, you should be fine unless you sit
in obtuse ways every time you get on the toilet, I said like
you get your mode.
You're good.
I said this is how I sit on the toilet.
You should have like a phone is usually like this.
I'm watching.
Yeah, that's that's fine.
That seems standard.
It seems like a standard.
Okay, that's oddly 45 degree.
It's still fine.
It's just you know, yeah, it's fine.
That's that's fine.
Do you have long balls or something?
Yes, I was okay.
Sorry.
Look, I'll tell you this.
It's it's not cold water as well as heated water.
Yeah, but you saw this different kinds.
Are you going to buy me like the all right?
Are you going to get me the Cadillac or are you going to
get me like the the used car?
I like I'm getting you the Ferrari.
Okay, walk into your bathroom.
You're going to think you walked into a SpaceX ship.
It's going to make noises.
It's gonna have like blue light emanating from it.
It's going to be amazing.
Sign me up.
I'll dumb.
I'm down.
Yeah, I'll get it for you.
All right.
Do you want like a like a like a live reaction like after
I come out of the bathroom like let me tell you about it.
Like is that what you want to like tell you exactly like
right after I use it.
I don't need to be gratified immediately.
I think I'm so confident in a bidet as a as a as a thing
as a product as an invention that I know long-term.
You'll love it.
Okay, I'm game.
All right next time you're in Vegas.
Give me a shot.
We'll go buy a bidet next time.
I'll I'm going to fly with it.
I'm going to travel with a bidet.
I'm going to travel.
I've done this before you laughing.
I've done this.
I went to Texas to deliver to deliver to deliver my friend
J slot a bidet and I set it up for him.
Do you have to check that is that like are you carry like
in a backpack and put it?
I had to check that.
Yeah, I had to check that they were had to hide the whole
conversation.
They waited they put it in put the little ticker on it.
Why am I imagining you setting the bidet up in the airplane
bathroom because you like it and you want one in there.
Yeah, I just have like an extra everywhere.
I go.
That's just like a quick place just in case.
Yeah, you got you got to set it up and you have to use it
there.
Do you do you know the movie Pursuit of Happiness with
Will Ferrell?
Well, you did well.
Wait, did Will Ferrell did this in a movie?
That's what will Smith will Smith.
Oh shit.
I thought you guys tell me Will Ferrell put a bidet in an
airplane bathroom and had a drink.
No, no, no.
I'm talking about Pursuit of Happiness with Will Smith,
you know where he buys all these medical equipment and
he has to he has to like sell them.
You know that movie I think I've heard of it.
Basically he goes into debt because he buys all these
medical equipment and he has to go door to door to every
hospital to sell them.
That's me with bidets.
Like I put my net worth into this product and now I'm just
desperately trying to sell them just going door to door
trying to get people.
People got to buy these bidets.
Yeah.
It's got so many of them bidets.
Yeah, just it's it's like floor to ceiling.
My girlfriend's pissed.
She can barely walk into the bedroom because there's so
many bidets.
Hey, I just have a long-term strategy long-term strategy.
You'll make 10% on each one.
We're going to make 10x if you just wait.
All right.
Yeah.
For now.
We have bidets everywhere around the house, but soon we'll
just have millions in an entire country adapted to the world
of bidets.
Put them on every sink instead of a brita.
It's just a bidet that you can drink from that's fucking
gross, but it's not even it's just like a piece of metal
that shoots water like you can shoot in your mouth.
It's not gross at all.
Whatever.
It's 0% gross because it doesn't you know, I mean the first
you can drinking out of a bidet on the first spray.
That's that's anything.
It's more hygienic, you know, 50 sprays in we got some problems.
I'm telling you.
I'm telling you after day one.
I ain't not drinking out of a bidet.
Not doing that.
That's fair.
But day zero you'd be like, yeah, it's just you know, okay.
I don't want to stay on bidet for a million years, but I
have another question.
Yeah, please.
Oh fuck.
All right.
Where is the nozzle?
Do you like shit on the nozzle?
Like where is it not?
Where's the point?
How is it pointed angle to not get like pissed and pooped on?
There are two nozzles and they retract.
I mean they were like like landing gear in a plane.
Yeah, exactly like a landing gear in a plane.
You can literally see it retract.
What yeah, it goes into itself and then to clean itself.
It will spray where it retracts to think of it as like an
enclosure and it'll just ricochet off of like its enclosure
to clean itself.
What this is I'm telling you the technology exists.
You just don't know about it yet.
I don't know man.
This is I know this is freaking me out, but I'll try it.
I'll do it.
You'll do it.
It'll be great.
I'm looking forward to it.
Let's do it.
Day bidet stream.
Well, no, no, no, like a bidet like we build it.
No forget everything.
I just said bidet blog.
Sure.
Yeah, definitely a pre-recorded.
Yeah, definitely need some editing.
All right.
What what's what's the wager here?
What's the wager here?
I don't know.
All right.
How about okay, whoever the how are you?
How are you feeling by the way?
You good?
You are you still having fun with Battleship?
I'm feeling phenomenal.
I'm happy to switch gears at any time.
I'm so easy.
I'm easy.
Okay, there apparently is like an advanced super mode.
We're playing want to try that right now.
You want to try the advanced mode?
I'm happy to try the advanced mode.
I did see that.
I didn't know what it meant.
I don't know things.
I'm scared of them.
How about we speed run this one?
Let's do one speed run round.
Well, you cannot you cannot take more than two seconds to
click on a space.
All right.
How about how about also every ship has to connect in some
manner?
Sure.
All right.
Every ship has to connect and you have to take you can
now take more than two seconds to click.
Corner connecting is fine.
Okay, that should be good.
Shit.
I don't know.
This is like way more complicated than I thought it was.
Yeah, I find myself struggling a bit here.
It's actually a pretty good lineup.
No, I'm not going to do F again.
Why would I do that?
I think this is I think I think you might be mind-tricking
me here.
No, I was I was just doing it.
I was just moving ships around to make it enough.
What a terrible design.
But the design was so much better than this.
Why does it look so fucking wrong?
Is this supposed to look wrong?
It's just it's not bad.
How does it can't look wrong?
You can't do battleship wrong.
No, but I'm trying to be I'm connecting them wrong.
Adam already.
Oh, two seconds.
Oh shit.
Shit.
Oh my God.
What how are you not going down?
Oh, we didn't even bet anything.
We didn't bet anything.
Oh, yeah, we just said speed around so we could get to
the other thing.
That's right.
Let's just do a very casual very breezy one gifted sub.
Okay left.
Oh song.
All right.
So it has to connect in some way which that makes this game
somewhat easy.
Corners can connect to right?
Yeah.
Corners connects is nothing on the line.
You're going to win this miss clicked.
I literally miss clicked.
I don't actually think I win this one.
I think you do.
Give me that's all about sub.
How it's connected.
I actually would feel bad for you if you won this because
you just be winning all the low stakes matches for $80.
At least I got to participate.
It was fun.
Yeah.
Oh, you went corner.
You did.
I did go corner.
Well, I want a bit corner.
You went adjacent.
You did.
Oh, no, this is your destroyer.
Okay.
All right.
How would you have connected this?
I think a corner.
There we are.
Oh, you just made it like the letter I.
Hey, I think you might have made a perfect letter.
I what did you do though?
I went for a more refined strategy.
This is this seems pretty refined.
I wasn't thinking the letter L or anything.
Oh shit.
You didn't do that.
Okay, so must be here for now.
The question is you have a what?
Oh, no.
Wait, okay.
Is it continued down here?
It is it's a letter.
I it's the letter.
I you just made the letter letter J.
I just did it wrong.
Wait, you didn't do the letter J.
If you that's supposed to be the letter J.
Right.
All right for Jerma.
Mm-hmm.
Now we're going to refine that is I went for at first.
I just did a really like a cross and I was like, no, I've done this.
All right.
Well, it was it was low stakes.
It was it was just a gifted.
So that's fine.
It's just a gifted.
It's all right.
And on top of the hundred hundred and one gifted subs actually 96.
I owe you five from our side bet.
Oh, that's right.
Okay, I'm going to create one.
It says commanders.
Whoa.
Yeah, this is I can hold this another game mode.
He there's like different maps.
Let's do one of the wacky ones.
Yeah, we're going to play at.
Oh, I can I can purchase this we can play at going to buy it.
Yeah, I'm going to buy I can buy the White Cliffs of Dover or the
Colossus Bay Colossus Bay.
Yeah, that's I think sounds somebody keeps saying don't bet on Jerma.
He sucks.
Well, I mean, look, you sometimes get into a streak and I was on
a winning streak in the beginning and now he's on a winning streak.
You were hot for a minute, but it can come back.
Okay.
All right.
You got a code sending you the code.
So I opened up our discord.
This is your ass.
Yeah.
Might be we didn't clear that.
It's just it's just written on your ass.
So here's the thing.
The boats are not all shaped like boats in this one.
Wait, what are you seeing this?
Yeah, this is weird.
I think you can show now.
But yeah, they're not all like well, this is weird.
This is different.
This is like a different arena too.
Do you think there are advantages for different commanders?
Should we do a Clone War here or torpedo airstrike bombardment
projectiles surgical strike?
So what does this mean?
I don't know what salvo means.
I've never even heard of that.
Salvo is like a four or five like six like kind of spread out
shooting a missile, huh?
I'm going to try this.
I think we have nearly the same shifts.
We'll have to remember the shapes here.
Yours seems really bad though.
I'm not going to lie.
Are you happy with that?
He's oh, maybe not.
Look at the far right.
It's just a giant for yeah, this is I'm happier with this guy,
but he's got but maybe he has a better I'm going to go with
this guy because he got torpedo.
All right.
I'm going to go with Sir Philip Wade.
He's doing well pay to win.
This is pay to win now.
Shit.
Do I have to buy these abilities mine sonar bomb torpedo?
What I'm seeing is that it's almost like set up to make me
put these really beautifully in the corners to get that urge.
I do have this urge to kind of Tetris this.
Yeah, and it's the worst idea possible.
I'm happy with that.
I almost think it's what if I do something like this would
be a little silly, huh?
I'm happy with this.
I feel good about where I'm at.
So when do we what decides if we get to use our abilities?
I have no idea how any of it works, but I guess we'll see
I'm starting us off.
Well, what's our bet?
What's our wager?
Another tweet.
Okay.
Oh, whoa.
Is this a double or nothing in the sense that your your
other tweets like gone or how do you know just just just
for another one?
Just a second tweet.
Okay.
All right.
Interesting interesting.
This is this is weird.
All right.
I have a single shot.
I got two lightning bolts.
You got two lightning bolts.
What is going on?
I don't know.
There's like a there's like abilities.
I don't know what's going on here.
It gave me two lightning when I what did I do just
dropped a mine.
What does that do?
I don't know.
Maybe if I click on it, it hurts me.
Do you know where my mind is?
No, I have no idea.
Okay.
I was going to shoot it.
That would have been a giveaway.
I thought that was a mine.
Okay.
No, no, no.
I put my mind somewhere.
I guess you get like ability points per turn.
Oh, all right.
I get it.
Oh, it shows you the pieces.
Oh, I get it.
Okay.
Yeah.
And I play some mine, but I can also just not do anything
and I think I save.
Oh, did you tuck it in?
Wait, that gave me a lightning bolt.
By the way, if you can still afford some abilities, you
can choose to save him.
I'm going to save my mind.
Wait, I should mine where my ship is, right?
Presumably.
You know what?
Oh, whoa.
What you bombs away and I didn't do anything.
This you don't have anything in the side.
It was a whiff.
No, not to say I have nothing over there.
You should you should keep your forces.
Keep your forces on the left.
You just missed you're close.
All right.
I reverse psychology you.
So where is it?
Where is this fucking scumbag?
Okay.
So I have so many points.
What does this do?
Oh, you used five point.
I'm going to save up for my my maximum surely you went to
the right here.
Like you do know damn it.
All right.
So I have to be careful because now you have like a super bomb
now, don't you?
Whatever your like ultimate ability is.
Yeah, I don't know what it is.
It's my salvo or whatever.
What are you feeding me right now?
I have a few.
Okay.
You have this still.
Oh my God.
How did you know?
I just figured it would be.
Oh wait, that's not even that one.
Which one is this?
No, it's not.
It's it's the other one.
What?
Oh, all right.
All right.
That's that's big for me.
Okay.
So you're you're just presumably wait, what does this do?
Does it just shoot?
Hold up.
Let me let me do this.
Oh, nothing you have goes.
This should probably be down here.
No.
Oh, what is this?
Is it a square one?
Oh, it is.
So where does this go?
Maybe here.
It's actually a lot harder because there could be so many
places where the tails can be.
All right.
Let's let's try this.
Oh, oh wait, somebody said use your cue.
I'm actually kind of scared.
Are you going to draw like a nuke on here?
Oh, what the fuck you actually got it.
Yeah.
Well, because it can only it could have only been there,
right?
Because if you flip it, it'll be the other direction and I
can also do this.
Oh my God.
What is that?
What did you do?
What does that do?
I just I sonar checked and I think there are two there's
two ships in that area.
Zero color zero zero torpedo fired across a row or a
column.
It stops when it hits a ship.
What what?
Oh shit.
That's awesome.
What is that's the best ability I've ever seen.
I wish I would I do with this.
Well, now, you know that there's a ship there.
No, I just put a mine down.
Oh, you put a mine down.
I put a mine down as well.
I don't know what happens.
I assume on when you hit it, it just ends your turn.
All right.
So there's two ships.
This is kind of cool area.
This is amazing.
Yeah, I think it has to be here.
Yeah, and then probably down.
No, no to the to the right.
It must have been you.
I know you got points.
Let me do one of I think I might.
Oh, you can't do that.
Okay.
I thought you okay.
What if I put something?
Okay.
You know what?
I was talking a lot of shit.
Jerma this this could be meta.
You think it is.
Oh nice.
It's your little one.
There's going to be like a character tier list.
You have two small ones.
You have two twos or what?
I have two twos.
Yeah, I don't know if that's like because I paid for this
character and I'm paying to win.
Oh fuck.
All right.
You must have some points built up.
No.
Oh, I got four.
Presumably it's here.
Yeah.
All right.
I suck your little guy.
That's a little guy.
That's big.
You also have another little guy.
Oh, I do.
You're right.
Yeah.
This is fair.
Let's let's let's scan this is a big area.
Oh, someone's in here.
But on the just on the outskirts of it.
So probably here and there's a comeback mechanic because
every time you get shot you just get a point and go.
Oh no.
All right.
What do you got twos?
I have a I've got quite a few.
All right.
So that what do you got left?
You get this one could go this one can continue.
I think it's this one.
No, I already got that one.
No, I didn't.
Yeah.
Oh fuck.
I did already get that one.
Oops.
What's funny is you just gave up on another ship.
I thought I was the three one, but I already got the three
one.
I'm an idiot.
Yeah.
Okay.
No, that wasn't the three one.
Oops.
Not yet.
Okay.
No, wait, I can just do I can do this.
No, Trevor.
Where is this ship?
Yes, there's only one inside my sonar area.
I'm painting a picture around this ship.
Aren't I?
Maybe wait, I think that might be one of the greatest.
Is it this?
Oh, yeah, it's it's my weird.
I don't even know what to call that.
All right.
I got to be careful there.
I don't I keep using my big one.
I don't want to use the big one again.
So you got another two.
It's probably here.
I'm saving points.
Okay.
All right.
I think that's a good strategy.
So you either have your two jutting out to the right my
God.
This is it.
There's only one spot 10 points now.
Don't you?
I have I have four now.
I've been using my sonar.
That's why I know that's right here.
I also have a couple of mines just lingering.
What where is this one going straight?
Okay.
All right.
I'm saving up my points here.
This is a hit.
There we go.
Finally.
It must be down snow there and to the left.
Wait, how does this work?
If it flips, it's the same.
So this can only go to the left.
You got it.
Okay.
This this other ship it's able to sneak in weird areas.
Let me let me try the barrage.
You have a barrage.
You have enough points for that.
Oh, I let me tell you I got barrage points over here.
You think we're not barrage and you're out of your mind.
Oh, come on.
That one's good.
It must be and then it has to go up.
I'm going to be able to like you feel I'm at so many points
now.
All right.
I need to win quick.
I'm a little nervous.
You only have a two bitch.
All right.
Let's just clear this.
This is I got I got to make something happen here.
Your torpedo is just such a weapon.
Well, you got to you got to clean up your food first.
Thank you.
Oh, no.
Okay.
Oh, it's not it's not worth using this.
Um, can I not move?
Where can I?
Oh, I get it.
Okay.
Oh, no.
What we need one one only one only one doesn't make any
sense.
One it's a lot of sense.
If you think about it, no way not too hard though.
Well, they go come on.
I have a two left.
Oh, I thought it was counting that one as the one.
No, no, no, no sonar.
There was a little crazy because you knew is connected.
Yeah, but I thought there would be something over here too.
Right.
That makes sense.
I like that.
You can only sonar where you shoot.
Whoa, that's not the what are you talking about?
I don't get I thought it was the one that was up in
the left.
Oh, oh, fuck.
You know, you're you have a one fatal flaw right now and
it's that you have started to ships and then just quit
on them.
But I don't want to give you the points.
I know where the I know where those are.
Oh, if I hit I get you get a point.
Oh, yeah, you're absolutely right.
I do.
Oh, I only shot that cut so I could sonar it.
Let's just want to I want to metal with your let's see
what happens here.
Why should I put this I can win this right now if I
actually do this, correct.
So you've got you've got a two left.
You've got a three which is either home and cancel this
it's either here or here.
Wait, no, it'd have to be I flipped out.
It has to be here.
I have to write this shit.
I'm stupid who tweets we talking about two tweets.
No, I'm gonna win right now.
I just think it's gonna take me a minute.
Wait, why does it say that?
Hold on.
What is this one?
Then is this one?
There's still a two hanging out somewhere.
It's this three one or this for one one, two, three, four.
I got it.
One, two, three, four.
That's the only thing it could be.
It couldn't be anything else.
It has to be here has to be it has to be here.
Fuck.
What's the end of your turn?
You got three choices here.
I don't think I have that few.
No, what do you mean?
How does that work?
I dropped a bomb.
Do I I hit your mind?
Is that fine?
Oh, it's fine.
I think it just ends your turn automatically.
Oh, oh, it went that way.
I thought it was.
Oh my god.
This I think this is a great game mode.
Jerma, I've thought of the tweet.
I'm actually very confident on this one.
I have to fucking win a game here.
You want to hear my idea?
What's what's the idea?
Let's hear it.
It's a combination.
I had that one one two.
I just went to I just you actually got every ship tagged.
It is just the wrong direction.
Yeah.
All right.
What's the idea?
Let's hear it.
Well, right now I have to I get one tweet and I also get a
shirt.
Yeah, you get a shirt so we could combine the two feasibly
where you wear a shirt and you have to tweet it out.
God and when I went to the bathroom earlier actually did
a bit of research and I'm really fond of this new merch
company.
I found called Mega Milk.
Yeah, I thought it'd be apt to get you a Mega Milk shirt
and then have you tweet it out.
Am I do I have to is this part of the almond thing?
Oh, it's just that because it's two tweets now the almond
thing totally separate.
Yeah, he just wanted a second wasn't even a just a second
tweet like a sex Twitter.
Yeah, you're gonna have to change it to 18 plus.
Let's go.
I'm I'm trying as hard as I can for this one.
I am gonna pull out all the stops for this one.
What I'm gonna I'm gonna try someone new.
I think because I like the the different strategies.
I'm gonna try we did a gamble is always lose.
He's a gambler too.
And he's winning over and over gamblers lose as long as
I keep sitting here.
I'll lose eventually but he's he's just has the special
awareness that I don't have.
I'm gonna try William Cars Lake.
All right, what are we doing for this one?
Yeah, we got a I'm open.
Look, you're the one who's down the most right now.
So I think it's it's only fair that you set the wager
where you want to about if I win I get to remove the
Mega Milk shirt tweet and hand it over to you.
You want me to tweet Mega Milk and you would have to
tweet the Mega Milk shirt.
I think that's reasonable.
But you understand that you're gambling here that this
is a more than a double or nothing.
What happens if I win?
What do you say you're getting rid of the tweet?
Do you are you getting rid of the shirt as well?
No, I still I will still wear that shirt.
All right, but that's not we don't know that we don't
we're not positive yet, you know, right?
Okay, I would agree with you that if if I didn't have
the tweet, I probably pick a different shirt.
I don't want to flood your Twitter like five tweets in
a row of like different weird things.
I'm doing.
Yeah, it would just be just insanely.
All right.
No.
Okay, so you reverse it.
You're just bent.
You're saying no you but if I win because I've already
earned the shirt and the tweet, give me just a moment.
I have to think this is this is difficult in the way.
I don't like these shapes.
I think what would be equivalent to that in my mind because
this is a full reversal is I would need for you to get
a full catboy costume.
Yeah tweet a picture in this cat made costume something
to the effect of I'm having a good time right meow.
So I'm removing the last tweet and giving you the
Mega Milk tweet.
But if I lose I have to let's just make sure I get this
correct.
I have to tweet a picture of me holding my stomach talking
about almonds.
I love eating almonds.
So I throw up and then I have to tweet a picture of me
in a Mega Milk shirt in the bathroom.
I was using the bidet or something.
Sure.
Yeah, and then I have to tweet a picture of me in a
catboy made outfit saying I'm having a good time right
meow.
That's what I stand to lose.
Yeah, because you have to understand this when you say
you're getting rid of yours and reflecting on me.
That's it's like twofold, right?
It's true.
It's almost like right now you owe me a hundred dollars
will just translate it to money and then I'm going to
owe you a hundred.
It's a $200 swing.
I would rather pay you thousand dollars right now.
Well money money has no no effect here.
I mean you're in wait.
No, no, no, not in a hole.
I want to make sure this is a good placement.
Yeah, I'm in you're sure about this.
Yes.
Wait, wait.
I sorry you need to you need to I I pulled up your
stream instinctively to see how your chat felt about
that and I just saw one of your ships placements on
the bottom.
You need you should change your ships.
I just accidentally cheated.
Okay, I'm sorry.
You might have been happy.
I close it out.
I just wanted to see what they thought about the Catboy.
But what if that was the game winner?
What if that was the one?
What was that?
That was the game winner.
Don't think of it.
It's it's battleship.
It could have been the game winner.
That was the game winner.
That could have been the game.
It was not the game winner.
I think I deserve you eating an almond for a tweet.
I'll eat an almond for a tweet on the house.
Yeah, that's fair.
Because you got the game winner.
I should have left it and you never would have clicked on
those faces.
You can still do all of that.
I don't know.
I'm not ready.
Oh my god.
I feel like I'm doing my hair in the mirror and it's just
not it does.
I don't like it.
I actually love my ships placement right now.
All right, let's go.
All right.
You still have torpedo man.
I choose a different person.
I chose airsprite.
You did.
Oh wait, we have the same man.
Oh, this is a mirror.
This is perfect.
Okay.
Oh, it's a nine.
Was it nine for the torpedo?
No, it was like six.
Okay, off rip.
Let's make this play.
No should say my money.
Oh my god.
It must be going up, right?
Oh, I thought you would have.
Okay.
All right.
Oh, oh, brutal.
Oh, that is really bad for me.
What a randomly place ship too, right?
It's it's, you know, as isolated as they could have made
it.
Unfortunately, that's that's oh no.
My Lord, no, please.
Please.
I know you're down bad, but cheating really.
Oh, no, no, you're in trouble.
Oh, no.
Well, I'm getting points.
I'm getting really rich.
There's a thing.
My brain has to take a second to think about where this is.
It's that way.
It's either or it could be anywhere, right?
I think you're a cheeky fuck.
Nope.
There's so many places it could be.
It's it's shocking.
Okay.
I am rich in points though.
Let's let's let's just do let's just chill.
Let's just do this is if it is anything, it could be the L
shape, but more realistically, I think this could be I could
secure the bag.
What's oh, yeah, yeah, let's do this because it's the L
shape.
It would be no, it doesn't.
Yeah.
Okay.
It is the L shape.
What?
Yeah.
Why fuck you fucking got it?
You got you.
What did I get?
You got you had you hit the wrong one.
I went for the bottom of the L so I could sonar.
Do I save my money for an airstrike?
Okay.
Yeah, let me do this though.
I've made a devious plot.
So it had if it's this then it has to be this way, right?
It has to be that way has to be it has to be this way
with this way.
If it's that which I don't know if it's that or not.
Well, this could be the big L.
I'm going to do something here.
You might think this is insane.
My God don't do it.
Come on.
Okay.
All right.
I have deduced what it is.
What is it?
I don't know.
I think it's the L.
It's the L.
Oh, it is the L.
Oh, which way?
He lives another day.
All right, let's go.
Okay.
I have I have an airstrike now fire at all cells.
What does it do?
Oh, it's it's it's like the torpedo.
Oh, that is the most OP thing I've ever seen in my life.
I gotta get one of those quick.
I gotta get one of those right now.
Damn it.
First of all,
Catboy Jerma.
What it's not the L.
It's not the L.
What are you talking about?
What the hell is it then?
It's this little guy.
No, it's not.
What the fuck is happening?
It's this way.
The airstrike is so OP.
Like a baby having a tantrum.
All right.
Let's let's just keep it simple here.
So I this to right here.
Does it go down or does it go most likely here?
Right?
Yeah.
Which means this has to go and then that's I'm giving you
so many points.
That's right.
I think I've tagged every ship.
So I just need to I need to finish it out.
Now.
What is this one to the left down up?
I don't know.
Best odds are here, but it could be this one or this one.
Oh, so that must be this one.
What?
Wait, what?
Thank God.
It's down there.
You don't know where it is.
You have no idea.
It could be anywhere.
I do know though.
I do I do get it.
I shouldn't I shouldn't I should do this.
Are you you must be flush with points right now.
I am I got it.
I got to get the most amount of surface area here.
Oh, I got one.
That was your two.
You just suck it.
You literally just sunk it.
Oh no.
Oh God.
Okay.
All right.
This is bad.
This is now bad for me.
Okay.
Oh, I you're in trouble here, but so am I.
In a deep crock of shit.
This could be literally any one of these though.
I only have two ships left.
It can't be anything.
I mean, it's either it's either it's either this way or that way.
That is true.
And I got it.
Well, no, you didn't get it because there's a lot.
There's a lot that it could be.
That's right.
There is a lot that it could be.
Oh, wait, that's that's physically not possible for it to be that way.
What do you mean?
All right.
Okay.
So this this this has to be here.
We know that you do know that.
Oh, and so that that leaves me with a wait.
Am I am I still missing a ship?
I still haven't tagged one ship.
This is so nerve-wracking.
It's too nerve-wracking.
This has to be left or right.
I could put like my poker face.
I don't know what to do.
I just been hiding from the camera.
I don't I think an airstrike.
Here's a waste at this stage of the game.
The airstrike kind of you son of a bitch, you son of a bitch little bomb and it
just ends what happened when you get two counter shots.
What about that?
What just happened?
I don't know.
I have no idea what just happened.
I think since I hit it you get two counter shots or something.
I got two counter shots.
Yeah, I wouldn't even pay attention.
This tells me if it's a three or two ship.
Oh, it's a three ship.
You have some dastardly to somewhere.
No, you did not.
No way.
You got that this impossible.
It's not possible.
It's impossible.
Oh my God, why did you get that?
That was like a 4% chance to hit that one.
What I do is I flick my mouse and I click.
Oh my God.
That was the most stressful game.
What the fuck?
That was insane.
Oh my God.
How do I even get anything shaved off of this?
Look at you.
Look at your guy's face.
He's so sullen.
Oh, that's this is okay.
At this point.
I almost own your Twitter account.
Even know what to do about this.
I want to keep playing to try to like get some of this back.
Yeah, but I can't like I can't even win a game.
No.
Okay, you know what?
You know what you could do.
We could make a what I owe you what it's it's three tweets three
tweets and like I feel I don't I feel like a shit in a bag
or whatever it was.
But what was it where shirt?
We have to wear a shirt.
It's three tweets.
It's 96 subs.
You know at this point I got a stream key $70.
Okay.
That's like the okay.
This is what happens to the person that gets last place in
Mario Party.
You know what I mean?
Oh, but you least we gave you fucking 10 coins.
Yeah, thanks in the final five turns.
They throw you a couple.
What is it?
What do you feel in your heart?
You want to win this back?
I can't imagine what to use the worst thing that you owe.
It's it's surely not the money.
No, it's it's it's it's definitely the last one.
You just said it's the cat made one.
That one's tough.
Probably the last two last two tweets are rough but Twix the
cat in the milk.
Which one is worse both equal equally bad.
Equally well, I would have to get in and out going to outfit
it.
Okay.
Yeah, no, it's it's it's it's something it's it's surely
something but how do we how do we even give you an incentive
anymore?
You have ones.
Okay, you just won.
You sat at the blackjack table like 200 bucks and you have
like $15,000 in chips.
Like what do you care?
You know, I have I have my watch now.
Yeah, you have the watch or you don't even need to play.
You're like you're good.
This is I know I feel great.
I feel great about this, but I am I'm still a sucker.
For monetary investments.
Okay, so I'm willing to make you a wager you making me a
wager.
Okay.
What's the wager you right now?
Oh me a just a little under $500.
Sure.
Would you say that $500 is about how much one of those tweets
is milk boys worth?
Yeah, I would say so I would say $500 is probably what the
word that would be worth for me.
I think okay.
Here's what I'm going to do and you can decline this offer.
Because I think I'm more I'm willing to give up the Mega
Milk shirt tweet and stream.
I'm willing to give that up.
Wow.
Okay in exchange you already owe me $500.
Let's just say if you win, we'll just cut those.
All right.
They're just eliminated.
What so the two tweets with the costumes?
No, just well, let's not get in over our heads.
I'm trying to rewrite the contract here.
Yes, the milk boy tweet stream are gone.
Okay, in exchange if you win.
Okay.
All right.
If I win you still owe me all that but I need you because
you live in Vegas to take $1,000 go to the casino and put
it on black.
Oh my God.
And if I win that bet you have to give me $2,000.
It's a pretty good bet.
That's a thousand bucks though.
Well, you already owe me 500.
It's more like oh I know it's a $500 bet.
Basically, is this worth $500 to potentially erase now?
I will say if you lose you owe three tweets one stream
with a shirt on cat made outfit pregnant almond milk
boy.
You have to give me $1,000 to go to the casino with
it.
Put it on a roulette table on black.
It's a lot.
We we would you be willing to remove the cat made outfit
if we made this 1500.
Wow, that's how bad the cat made outfit is honestly like
tweeting in general.
It's like so like it's the tweets themselves.
Yeah, I could only dress up in any costume, but I have
to tweet like fuck the tweet is look I would almost be
creating enemies if I got rid of that for how just you
I mean look at your chat.
They're fervorish about this.
If I got rid of this they I mean they would be there
would be riots if they know what they're if they don't
let them fool you.
They already got something because you owe me 500.
You're saying it's basically a thousand dollars on this
game and I will literally I will literally like livecast
it to you.
I can't do that.
I can like I can I can take a picture before and after
and it's either gonna be like a picture of an audio
experience just do like your phone recording and you
can just audit auditorily bring me through it.
You know what look I I love catboy, but I would never
give I would never take away a man's opportunity to win
back his dignity.
So all right.
So hold on.
So if if so, this is all of if you lose this if I lose
this so we are just rid of the we are just going over
what happens at the end of this game.
So if if you win this game, yes, I have to do all of
that and I have to do the 1500 on black.
It's a lot you have to do a lot.
This is like an astronomical amount of stuff to do.
It's an insane list of errands.
It'll take you literally like weeks to accomplish
everything.
But if you win and you wipe out the two tweets, you
got to wipe you got to wipe out all three tweets all
three.
No, actually even though the almond one can stay really
there's so many terms of this contract.
We have to like write this down.
Oh, just to clarify you win.
You only have to go post the almond boy tweet.
Everything else is gone.
Yes, if I win, it's three tweets and hey, hold on.
I'll sweeten the deal.
I'll sweeten the deal for you.
If even if I win, I'll sweeten the deal you take you
get rid of those two tweets that the cat made out
for one and the mega milk tweet and I'll tell you
right now you delete those.
I'll do I'll do I'll do 250 on black with $250.
I'll do 250 on black.
That's that's lower than that's not sweeter.
Oh, that sweetens the deal because otherwise it
would have been wiped out.
I wouldn't have to do it.
Oh, you'll still do still do 250 for me.
Yeah, that's sweetening for you.
I'm in.
Oh, all right.
Let's go.
This is the final this is that we can't go past this
though because after this it's it's it's I mean,
it's it's it's like the deed to your home.
Yeah, I'm gonna start giving you like titles to cars
and stuff.
This is the last one.
Okay.
All right.
Oh gosh, I'm already nervous.
I can feel a lump forming in my throat.
All right.
I think I'm gonna keep it with William Cars Lake.
The airstrike seems pretty good.
I agree.
All right.
All right for everything really for everything here.
All these positions matter so much somebody said Fox
only from a lose lose lose.
I know you guys want me to lose cuz then I have that's
like two weeks of things that I have to do.
I have to win this.
I have to put on all the stops.
I've got to win.
What a difficult this is.
This is me taking like back shit that I have to do.
Honestly, even if I win I still lose.
I just don't lose as much.
Yeah, there's because there's there's zero risk for me,
right?
It's zero risk for you.
I'm clawing back.
You're you're getting more you're gonna lose now.
I like this.
Are you placing things?
I've placed everything.
Yeah.
Oh, I'm still on the waiting screen.
Oh, yeah, it does say waiting.
Do we do we need a real we may need a redo?
Okay.
All right.
Oh, yeah, I'm my games like frozen.
Let's let's reconnect.
I'll just try to remember this.
I'll just create a new one.
I'll send you the code again.
God is telling you not to do this.
Well, if God were telling me not to do this, he's got a weird
way of saying it because I have to literally dress up in three
different costumes and God wants you to dress up as a God.
I want me God wants this God is here with us on this battleship
board.
I've sent you the code Colossus Bay.
I am now in.
All right, should be good to go.
And here we go.
All right.
This is for all the marvels here.
I'm gonna have to do this.
There's swaths of people invested on my victory.
I almost have to turn my monitors off.
They're gonna like DM me on discord monitors off.
This is like an episode of schooled.
All right, I placed this one before it was here.
Remember you have to think I so I don't know what to do.
There's so many ways that this could go so wrong.
Okay, I'm done.
I'm done.
Oh my God.
Are you prepared?
Almost.
This is this is a preposterous amount of gambling on battleship.
I think it's you that's that must be you, right?
Yeah.
Okay, first shot is everything.
Oh no, it's two.
I thought it was the three.
I thought you put up I thought you put the three in a weird
place.
I'm not that cheeky.
Let's let's play this strategically.
All right.
Now, whatever.
Don't remind at the very beginning.
This isn't a three.
It could I mean my best bet.
No, it's only one.
I should go here.
Yes.
Okay.
That's fucking phenomenal.
I mean, that's just oh my God.
Oh my God is doing this.
What the fuck Loki put the mask back.
What the fuck is this bullshit?
This is ridiculous.
There's no way no fucking way.
This is possible.
If I get the third one, I'm cheating.
No fuck that fuck that Poseidon throwing a goddamn trident
at me.
This is insanity.
Okay.
Oh my God.
If you hit my if you hit my thing to me, let's just fucking
let's go.
Oh God, I love a God.
I'm a bomb fucking everywhere.
Over here too.
Let's go.
Okay.
My God, you just had so much money.
I didn't realize I just gave you the fucking Northrop gumption
supply.
I can't believe you just did like six in a row.
God.
Hey, is he going like this?
Is he like looking down like an iPhone that has like this
frame up?
I just have it.
All right.
I gotta think about this.
These are bigger than two.
So which means this could be the top one's hard because it
could be any of those four.
It could it's it's this one's gonna I bottom ones easier bottom
ones for the easiest one because it's literally you can go
one way or the other.
All right.
You know, it's good.
Well now it's hard.
Phenomenal guess.
All right.
That's good.
That was good.
But wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait.
Not not quite as this could be this could be the Tetris
piece or the elf.
Yeah, that's fair.
Well, I know what it is now.
You do know what it is now.
Okay, I can't fucking believe what I'm looking at right here.
Oh, yeah, I just got three ships in a row.
I do.
All right.
The problem is you only have the good shit left.
That's true.
You son of a bitch.
That's huge.
That's actually huge.
Oh my god, you son of a bitch.
That's actually actually ignored the god.
This is this is bad.
This is really bad.
That's huge.
But can I capitalize on this?
I want a phenomenal start for that to happen.
Just a missed airstrike.
At the bottom.
All right.
Now I'm confused though, cuz is this the L go?
No.
Yeah, could the L go this way?
Can the L go that way?
I think it can to go like boom.
Boom.
I think the L could go that way as it goes boom.
But that could also be the three.
I'm going for it.
All right.
I think I got you now.
I got you.
Wait, what?
Oh, no, you do not got me.
Okay.
What's what happened?
Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait.
Oh shit.
It's this way.
Oh, yeah.
Okay.
So it's just either up or down, right?
Simple enough.
Are you serious?
That's terrible.
I'm oh, I think I know where that is.
I think I know what you just did.
Oh, yeah.
I think so.
Take a try.
Take a gander.
I don't think you know.
I have abilities.
I'm saving the points.
It's gonna come in handy.
It's all right.
He's missing.
We're good.
All right.
Well, now at least I know what this is, right?
This is I'm not freaking myself out for no reason, right?
No.
All right.
I got you here now.
I think I'm gonna sonar this one here.
Why did I do that?
All right.
Two?
How could it be two?
I'm so confused.
What's going on?
This has to be the three.
But what the heck?
Why would it say there are two?
It's either this way or this way.
Wait a minute.
You got a motherfucker right here somewhere.
Yes.
Oh God.
The mines are terrifying.
What are you doing?
Are you placing a mine?
Fuck!
I'm freaking out.
All right.
I was placing a mine.
That's right.
That's a given.
It's pretty big.
A two and a three.
What's he up to now?
Another goddamn mine.
I'll just wait.
Patience.
Well, wait.
Yeah, it has to be here.
No, but is that certain?
It is.
That's certain.
It's like Minesweeper.
This is it has to be here.
It is certain.
It's either here or here.
It's not certain.
I'll tell you that much.
So wait, does the sonar mean two ships?
Or does it mean two spaces where there are things?
I will I will grant you this.
It means there are two things in that area which includes mines.
A bunch of people in chat were saying it means there's two ships.
You fucked with me.
Oh, this could be anywhere.
Fuck.
Yes.
Come on.
Give me something good.
Something good.
Yes.
Dude, mines are the worst.
This is heating up.
All right.
So now so it has to be right here.
Right.
Of course.
Okay.
Now I just got two of your little shit ships.
My little shitters.
It's either on one side or the other.
So here's what I'm going to do.
I'm going to go like this.
Oh, what they'll get four shots for free.
Come on.
Come on, baby.
Get me there.
Yes.
Oh my God.
My mind strategy worked.
Wait a minute.
It's not over.
I flooded my field with mines.
Oh, I'm sweating.
Yes.
Oh no.
Oh, this is bad.
Oh, this is this is actually kind of bad.
I can't be so haphazard.
It ain't over here.
I think I think I got him right here.
I think I got him right here.
It's either right here or it's right here.
Can I can I do it?
Did he do that?
Did he do it right in the middle?
You got it.
But but but this could hit me.
This could hit me.
Oh, come on.
No, so it's here.
Here.
That's it, right?
All right.
So we're going to do one more.
We're going to do one more at this point.
Last one is more about.
Offer a man who has it all.
All right, so shit.
What do I even owe you?
I owe you like you won the showcase on the price is right.
There's nothing more I could even offer you.
I won the free trip to Hawaii from United Airlines.
I won the house in Malibu.
I won the entire Lexus car.
You got both showcases.
They don't even do that on the show.
I think I got I feel like James Holtz hour right now.
The most winning game show contestant of all time.
Well, that was that was a blast.
I'm glad I owe three weeks of content.
It's so much.
It's almost too much.
I will say does this make it easier?
We can space it out, you know, a payment plan.
So to speak a monthly payment plan.
Yeah, you know, we can't just do three tweets in a week or something.
That's a that's absurd.
I'm the ball by almonds.
You do need a ball.
That's that's the least of your concerns.
Almonds are easy to come by.
All right.
Can I can I consolidate this this internet?
Can I just consolidate this?
Yeah.
Okay.
Here's my offer.
Please one tweet in a catboy outfit with almonds in front of me looking
into the mirror of an oven with the stomach sticking out stomach.
Big big glow.
I eat too many almonds, whatever.
And like I have like a mega milk photo behind me.
I will I will allow you to consolidate two of the tweets into one.
Three is a bit.
It's a bit what the almond tweets your tweet, right?
Technically that technically.
Yeah.
Yep.
So I feel fine.
What if we just consolidate cat in milk into one?
I did not think I was going to be having this conversation.
Oh, let's combine cat and milk into one.
I'm just sitting there like we were going to play Battleship a mega milk
made if you will like you at some like a doorstep like an old with an
old-timey bag of milk, you know, like like a tree like you got all of
your six.
Okay.
Could I just have a huge thing of milk?
That's a that's a mega milk.
You know what I mean?
That's a lot of milk.
How much milk a huge amount?
It would need to be minimum like five gallons.
I don't know if I even get that much.
Well, that's what I'm saying.
Like how big is this?
Because a gallon of milk is like that's normal two gallons even somewhat
feasible, but standard what how about we consolidate it easily, right?
You so it's you, right?
Hey, it's me, Jerma and you're wearing a cat boy costume, but it's a
cat made outfit, right?
Okay.
And you're and you have like the milk delivery cartons and it's just
like like a perspective of someone opening their door to greet you.
And then the caption is mega milk made and you know, I feel like
that's a good consolidation there.
Oh, that's somehow worse.
So it's way worse it for that.
I I would almost be willing to just, you know, throw out the almond
tweet, you know, we for mega milk made.
That's just one big juicy tweet.
It needs to be almond milk.
Yeah.
Yeah, it's mega milk made.
You're not wearing a cat made outfit and and you have almond milk
that you're delivering with the caption mega milk made.
Can we play one more for what for me to look at me?
Look at me.
Do you see me?
Three hours and 20 minutes has changed you.
You do look concerned in a way.
Like I would be concerned if I walked by you.
All right.
His art is we're gonna do we're gonna do we're gonna do one more.
One more.
How do I even?
All right.
We're gonna fuck.
Okay.
So this is how it's uh-huh.
So I will accept your omega milk made.
Okay.
I accept that offer.
Right.
So this next one is to I don't even know how I even all right.
This is to do a fuck.
Okay.
This next game because we already know the tweets happening, right?
Like I'm not going to be like, well, check that out.
But okay, sure.
This next game and this is the final game.
This is it.
This is the final game is it is by the way, it's been a blast.
It's been a pleasure.
I've had a great time today.
It's been absolutely fun.
Fantastically fun.
This is to solely if I win is to remove remove the cat costume.
So you would be delivering milk as a mega milk made but without
the cat costume in this picture.
Now, are you wearing the mega milk shirt?
Um, it's really nailed down the T's in the eyes here.
I think I'd probably rather just be the cat.
Well, let's pick a poison here because look you you're down bad.
But hey, I want to help you refinance restructure.
That laugh was just like that was such like a perfect evil laugh.
I would love to help you restructure this now.
Let's let's just talk brass tacks.
Are we more scared of the cat or the milk because we're going
to have to pick a poison here.
We got to go down a road Robert Frost style.
We got to pick one now, you know is is a the lesser of two
evils or the evil or I think it's the evil or you do you see
my my vision of this image of this tweet.
It's delivering milk as a mega milk made with a cat costume.
It's it's it's got to it's got to be up there.
I mean this thing's going to be downloaded, you know, let me
just say that this is how this is going to be downloaded.
So I mean the amount of fan art that will come from this will
teach artists for years.
It's just like this is going to be the modern-day scream.
It's going to be recreated so many times I am down to just
let's just remove the cat in this next wager.
Let's just get rid of the cat and you are now just you just
wear a shirt that happens to say mega milk which which could
mean anything.
All right delivering almond milk.
All right.
What if I lose this something else that you can add?
I you're just giving me like oats which I very much appreciate
by the way.
That's that's what happens if you want if you lose unfortunately
the cat.
How about this cat if I lose if I lose this no more like oh
double down remember if I lose it's over.
That's it.
It's locked in.
How about yeah, I am down.
That's what I win.
If I win this is that it just it's almost like I'm able to
walk away from the table and it has to be done.
It's like we'll we'll just nod at each other in passing knowing
that the deal has been done and it's it's been written in
ink.
Okay, it's over.
Yeah.
So it you you pressed and fake prices.
So what wait what what was the next part?
I said if if I win the deals over call it done.
That's it.
We're going to be you know, nodding as we pass and fake
breasts.
No, I'll walk away from the table right now.
I'm kidding.
Come on.
We we can joke around.
You know, this this these keep getting we're getting more
and more and more things added.
Eventually.
What are you going to?
I'm going to have to put like something on my head like a
crown or something.
What what's next?
SpaceX ship about to launch.
All right with your adding creative character shit bald
head.
No, no, I actually am happy to wager cat for for deal being
done.
And that and then just and that's good for me.
And that's it.
And then that's it's over.
Yeah, this is just this is more of a give really giving me
it out.
It's kind of giving you it out.
It's also like ball.
Don't lie.
You know what I mean?
You know, I'm shooting the extra shot.
We're contesting it ball.
Don't lie.
If I win this one, then I mean, it's true.
It's there's nothing else.
You're just giving me an extra life here to basically go back
one of the layers of onions, but I but also if I win it's
like it's so reaffirmed that you couldn't argue it, which
is which is this is no argument.
It's like this is yeah.
All right.
Let's do it.
There's almost a meta that's formed right now.
Yeah, I don't I don't know what to do here.
I have no idea how to place my ships.
Everything looks so wrong to me.
I mean everything just looks so wrong.
This is crazy.
But I think I'm happy with this now.
I am.
No, now I am.
I'm happy with this.
Go I am.
I am panicking over here.
Not ready.
So hard to avoid.
Fuck it.
Whatever.
All right.
Fuck it.
Let's go.
Oh God.
All right.
Come on, baby.
Come on.
Give me tails.
That's both of us, isn't it?
Yeah, but I'm silver.
You're bronze, right?
What I found to be one of the best strategies is this.
Not as good of a start for sure.
I did have a godlike start and it was a close game too.
Oof.
Bit of a mind war we have here.
This is more mind sweeper than battleship.
It is.
He's more man than machine.
Damn it.
Come on.
Do that.
Just a couple of mines.
All right.
So you go in mind strategy here.
Well, it gives you two hits.
So anytime you do an airfield sweep, it's just like game over.
More mines.
You're really going with the mines here.
Mm-hmm.
Hmm.
It also fucks up your sonar.
I mean, yeah, it does.
It truly does.
There's so much meta.
What are you thinking of doing?
Where did you put that?
You son of a bitch.
This is the most tense.
Somebody you're looking over with a stack of $100 bills.
I've got like 50 cents on the table and I want I just want you
wiped out and you're just like, oh boy.
That was tricky.
Wow, tricky for that one.
And I'm just like, yeah, it was really tricky.
I got 50 cents.
Well, well, well, well, what do we have here?
Not there.
I'm just copying him.
He's once five straight games in a row.
Why would I not want to do what he's doing?
Okay.
All right.
Where are you going now?
You put a bomb over here.
I did.
Did there it is God my God.
That is so huge.
That's blessed thinking about putting a mine over there.
I knew it.
Devious devious.
Okay.
All right.
Let's do this.
Let's let's sweep this here.
What did you do up here?
Nothing.
So that that's either your L or more realistically some
hug boat.
That's just been did I just find your L?
Oh, I just found it.
How are we?
Oh my God, I just found your L perfectly.
I thought that was a minefield for sure.
Okay.
All right.
You're rich now though.
That's concerning my best bet, right?
I still don't have anything of yours even uncovered.
Well, you have a sweep over there.
Yeah, but why just airstrike right down the middle or just
airstrike over here because I'll know those eventually.
I think that's the play.
That's the play.
Oh, that is that was one of your twos.
That was one of my twos.
Oh, why does that?
Why is that even a thing that can happen?
What is this?
What happened?
My my random missile.
My spot which triggered you hitting me which could just
be a forever chain.
Oh, that's funny.
All right.
Well, I you have the two you didn't put two twos up here.
Did you damn it?
It's really hoping you'd go for row three.
I think you did you didn't I thought you did like a one
two just trying to be a weirdo like I like I would have
like you would have freaked me out or something.
No, no, none of that none of that shenanigans are you
you must be here just have to be are you serious?
No, man.
All right.
Let's do this.
Oh, okay.
All right.
I'm narrowing it down bit by bit inch by inch.
Oh you all right.
There you are.
Did find me.
Here's the real question though.
Is this your L or is this your your three your three?
Oh, this is a tight war right now.
Now here you are.
Here you are.
Say like such a villain.
Okay.
They are this could be your Tetris shape in the top left.
No, it can't be bottom, right?
Thank you.
Fuck fuck.
I've wasted eight turns on this one.
Damn it.
Let's do one of these though.
I'm on a sonar meta right now.
Oh, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah,
re re nice.
Nice.
Come on.
Give me something.
I know where you are now.
This is this is guaranteed all but lovely.
It's a good one to take down.
Now we have four over here.
So you placed a bomb up here did place a bomb up here.
But if we have three before that then it couldn't be here.
It would most likely have to have been four piece.
So this is guaranteed either way.
All right.
That happened to one of these.
Well, it's one of these two spaces because you just put a
bomb over here.
What could this even be?
That was stupid of me.
There's literally only one place I could have put the bomb.
But wait, hold on.
Could this just be it here?
I wonder.
Okay.
Fuck.
I gave it away.
I think I got you.
I think I got you here.
Hold on.
No, this could be anything.
This could be anything.
This could be your three.
This could be your two.
This could be anything.
Okay.
Is it the two?
Nope.
Now here's the tricky part though.
This could be your Tetris piece or could it not?
Is that I think this is your three.
Did you go this way or this way?
Mm-hmm.
The amount of stress I have right now is so unparalleled.
You went this way.
Okay.
Wait.
No, hold on.
I think this is your Tetris piece.
It's right here.
Isn't it?
You can tell me.
My hair is crazy.
It is.
All right.
I got you.
Get me.
You did get me.
I'm now quite stressed.
You are in a good position though.
You've only you've got your two is.
Magically somewhere over here.
So let's see if I can do this.
Okay.
Shit really only one put your two right here.
That was the bomb.
There was three before.
There's a four piece remaining.
How are there three terrible?
Why people call me terrible one.
How are there three in here?
Did I I must have found two boats.
I must have pinged two boats because that's a two must
unless you put a bomb.
There was not a sound mind and Ludwig is taking advantage
of him.
What do you mean?
I thought that was stupid.
You just that was a lot of points.
Yeah, I think it's too late for the airstrike.
Where is this this?
Okay, this should have to be like over here.
I wonder if I wonder I wonder if it's down here.
On our and this is not maybe also not this one.
No, your two could just be anywhere.
That's the problem.
It could be anywhere.
Yeah, but the problem is if I'm gonna this I already hit
these two.
So I would realistically only be hitting like these three.
I'm going to sonar this one.
No, that's so no sonar this one.
Sonar this one.
No, I think I'm going to sonar this one.
I'm going for it bucket.
Oh bingo.
Okay.
So interestingly enough it ain't any of these ones.
Thank you down here.
All right.
Now is this the two or is this the Tetris piece?
What I do I fucked up.
How do I fuck up?
I thought there was a see you see he still has a two.
He still had a two.
If I think this through I might have it one.
Right here.
Is it right here?
Right because it has to be oh, this is a bomb.
This is either a bomb or it's right fucking here.
Well have it once bold you're so missing.
This is the sonar picks up bombs, right?
This is a bomb.
I fucking knew it was a bomb and I still clicked it.
Oh, no.
Oh, come on, please.
That's fucking huge.
Yeah, how unlucky can you get?
Oh, that is so bad for me.
Oh, this is this is this is this is all down to this turn.
I think this is all just here we go.
Hmm.
Okay.
All right.
I need I need a win.
I need to win right now.
Now that this this this this has to be down.
It has to be oh, oh, I think there's only two possible locations.
No, I think there's only one.
I think it has to be here.
Jerma.
Oh, I will give you one last attempt.
What do we play another game?
No, that's not what I mean.
Wait, you're throwing on purpose.
I'm giving you one turn one turn one turn to save everything.
You cherish what a good luck.
What a good guy.
It's not going to be easy.
You have to guess right on which ship is where in what coordination
is it right here?
I'm going I'm going to the bottom right because if it's if it's
this is the I'll get good info, right?
This is info.
There's no info.
It's your last turn.
I know but this is info.
There's no oh unless you're doing like a major shot.
Yeah, that's this is info.
Oh, no, but you hit my thing.
What I got you.
I got you.
This is it.
I did it because you get me know because now all all the all
that's left is this is your Tetris piece, but which way is
it going?
Yeah, how do you know where it's going?
I don't know.
I have to sonar something.
I have to sonar this one here.
No, wait, take your time.
I don't want to mess with the cat.
So no this one or sonar this one.
I got a sonar the top right one.
This would be one two.
This would be three right or this one this one, right?
But this one because it was going down then it'd be one two.
It would be one if it was going this way if it was one two
bang bang.
That means this would just be one right.
That's that's this.
All right.
Here we go.
I'm going for it.
But could you flip it some weird way?
Oh, yeah, you can flip horizontally for what do you mean
for you have a bomb in every spot here.
It's one.
It's okay.
It's either one, two, three, four, one, two, three, four.
Oh my god bullet, but it has to be this one here has to has
to be guaranteed one below has to be this has to be it at
least this one.
It has to be.
At least it can't be a bomb here.
There's no way this would connect to anything but shit.
But what if it's these two as it could be this one in this
one, couldn't it?
Oh, no.
What would you have done?
I want you to trust yourself.
Maybe flip a coin, but you might have bombs here.
It could be one.
It could be bang bang or it could be just bang bang or or
it was rise.
Take a breath.
Take the shot.
I have a sonar here.
Zero, zero, zero, zero, zero.
I got you.
I did it.
It's your zero IQ.
Gerber figured it out.
You're like God, right?
I'm so I don't know one, two, hold on zero, zero, zero,
zero, zero, zero, zero, zero.
So it has to be this one.
Thank you dad for letting me play the game.
Hey, look, I can't take $1,500 a catboy three tweets for
exclamation point seven houses on our first time hanging out.
That's that's too much.
All right.
We got to got to draw the line somewhere.
So what do I actually have to do now?
You owe one tweet, huh?
Where you are delivering almond milk in a mega milk costume.
Oh fuck.
That sucks.
And you also have to wear that on stream.
Oh, that sucks too.
And then you have to put I think $1,500 on a black at a
roulette table.
Oh my God.
That sucks.
I yeah.
Yeah.
So, you know today, what happened here?
So I don't I don't feel to the alternative would have just
the only thing you've won.
There is the removal of cat which which I feel I feel okay
with that.
Excuse me.
And like 70 bucks, 80 bucks, whatever it was.
That's true.
You did also win 80 bucks that you didn't wait.
What was how many subs of it?
Well, no, the subs are removed.
The subs are replaced with that with that with the with the
with the wager for the roulette.
So zero subs.
Wait, I thought I got no, no, it wasn't subs.
It was dollars, right?
$50 it was 96 subs and then it's been translated to the
casino bet.
Oh, okay.
So just give me a list of things.
I have to do I'll do I'll just I'll send you the list of
errands.
Look Ludwig.
What a hero.
What a streamer hero for me.
Yeah, let me tell you I've made enemies in both of our chats
from that.
Hey, but here's the thing though.
I could have really I could have fucked that up big time.
You could have easily fucked that up easily.
I think that that that explosion explosion you place in
the bottom right was that was a good explosion.
Because you could have decided to have placed that in the
top and that would have that would have been much tougher.
Well, that was fucking a lot of fun.
Yeah, I had a blast.
I had a blast.
Thanks for playing games.
I did not think we were going to do this for four hours,
but we did know.
Yeah, we were like we should get a list of games because
we're probably going to get a little bored.
No, absolutely not.
That was yeah, that was a pleasure and I'm glad you had
fun because even though I feel like we're leaving on a
note as if you had won you lost so much.
I very much lost a shitload.
Yeah, but I won the first like three games got really
overconfident and then lost five or six in a row.
It did feel for some reason like it was easier for me.
I don't know.
I think you just psych yourself out because even at the
end like it was mathematically proven with the sonar.
Yeah, I think just the stress your brain just melted.
Yeah, it does that but that was great.
That was a pleasure and I'll see you again Tuesday.
That's right.
I didn't even tell anybody I had nobody even knows what's
happening on Tuesday.
It is the first time I've streamed since last week.
Oh really?
Yeah, they don't know I've told my chat.
I don't think you've told your chat.
Would you like to go ahead and tell them what's going
to happen on Tuesday?
Oh, yeah, you want my words not your I can do my words.
Yeah, but if you do your event.
Yeah, this this Tuesday, I put $5,000 on the line for
a 12 streamer Mario Kart tournament.
It's going to be about two hours starting at 6 p.m.
Pacific and it features myself.
Jerma cutie Connor simply ms.
Kiff Clint mango XQC Northern Lion moist critical and in
a mystery guest meaning.
I just I haven't filled a slot yet, but but that's it.
That's that's this Tuesday.
It's a mar the switch Mario Kart.
It is the switch Mario Kart.
So you'll need a you'll need that game and to capture it
which I think you you got that already, right?
Yeah.
Yeah, I got it.
But yeah, that's that's that's Tuesday at 6.
It should be like a about a two hour session and then
then there'll be winners.
Yeah, I'm I'm ready to go.
I'm actually not very I'm not bad at that game.
I am pretty bad.
So I don't expect myself to place well, but I think the
the favorites going in are definitely Clint and Northern
Lion because all that man does is just win shit just wins.
He just he just wins things.
That's what he does.
He's a winner.
He's a winner in a in a bald man's body.
Hey, what was we talking about like, you know, just he's
a winner, but he took one out.
He just thought that you I mean your hair is looking great.
Like you're not on your I'm kidding.
I'm gonna know man.
It's good.
I'm it's happening.
I'll be balded for you.
Do you think if it if you feel like it's coming you take
Propecia?
No, I'll just drink some extra green tea and I eat somebody
have some fish oil and shit.
You'll be fine.
Yeah, me.
I would have a existential crisis when it's coming because
both my grandparents are bald.
It is coming.
I know me too.
It's gonna happen in like the next probably three or four
years.
I'm gonna be 40.
I'll be 40 in like less than five years guys.
What are you talking about?
Yeah, five years is a long time.
All right.
And look, you know, this is 40 40 year old Virgin.
It's that's a hot year.
People like that year.
Excuse me.
What do you wrote?
Yeah.
Yes 40.
You just call me a virgin.
No, I'm saying that like it's a popular like, you know,
how like when you turn 22, you're like, oh Taylor
I'm feeling 22 40.
It has so many exciting things that come along with it.
Like the movie the 40 year old Virgin is it omen to 40
year olds or who are virgins with the movies about it's
a footnote.
It's a footnote.
It's more so I think Virgin comes up 2000 times in the
script.
It's mostly just a vehicle for talking about the beauty
of aging more so than about virginity, which is which
is a beautiful thing.
And it's in its own, right?
For virginity.
All right, man.
It's been a fucking pleasure.
This is the first time we ever like hung out on stream.
Yeah, it's a blast.
And and now we've definitely set up one more hangout
and at some point I'm going to knock on your door
with far too expensive bidet for your asshole.
I can't wait to spray water into my ass.
It'll be clipped.
Not live though.
Oh God.
Yeah, I'll see you on Tuesday.
But all right.
Yeah, I'll see you.
I'll see you.
Have a good rest of your day.
Yeah, take care man.
Thanks for playing.
All right.
Bye.
That was a lot of fun.
Yeah, when we first turned the stream on we were like,
oh yeah, maybe we'll play like Battleship for like,
I don't know.
We like 40 minutes.
We like 30 minutes maybe a tops.
That was a lot of fun.
Have to do a bunch of stuff.
Why does it always end up like this?
Anytime this competition I always like end up like
dressing up in a costume that happens every time I'll
figure out what the what how those tweets are going
to happen.
I have to like he's got to get this shirt.
If that's the shirt you want we got we got some
stuff to do but that's a perfect opportunity for me
to stop.
That was Ludwig if you don't know.
I mean, how could you not know Ludwig at this point?
He's hilarious fucking top 10 streamer.
He's probably probably in my top five at least of all
streamers will follow him if you don't which I don't
know how you don't but yeah, well, I'll see you guys
on Tuesday.
I'll be streaming on Tuesday.
I'll probably be streaming my perspective from the
Mario Kart Tournament.
I have some practicing to do so I'm going to be
streaming because I haven't I don't never streamed
Mario Kart.
So we'll see how that goes.
I need practice but is Ludwig still going to stream
or is he ending I think we're ending right?
That was a lot of fun.
Yeah, it was.
Thank you for the subs by the way.
I didn't really pay I would kind of locked in my
brain was kind of locked in to you know, everything
that going on on the screen.
Yeah, I will see you guys later on Tuesday 6 p.m.
Pacific by the way 6 p.m.
that's going to be a late start 9 p.m.
Eastern for a lot of you guys and let's um, let's
go raid Joel.
He's playing Noita.
Oh, we all know how that's that's a no.
That's a notorious stream here.
Go say hello to Joel.
Barg Skelethor if you don't know he's a very very
very very very good streamer very funny guy and I
will see you guys Tuesday.
Good night.
Goodbye.
Have a great rest of your afternoons battleship game
tag on Twitch.
Yeah, what the fuck is going on there?
I feel like we gave that just enough attention to
be confused.
Let's get the raid going.
Goodbye.
Good night.
Take care.
Bye stinking man.
Music really should not still be on.
There we go.
It's off.
All right.
Good night.
See you guys later.