I didn't realize this was still playing.
One more time, all right.
All right, I'll- all right, it's off. I'm turning it off. Hold on.
Oh, you're set, makers.
I'm not doing it one more time.
The next game we're gonna play for an hour or two. Although, who knows?
This might be one of the ones that I don't stop for a while.
It's a classic one, my favorite that I ever owned in my whole life, and favorite SNES games ever.
Vegas Steaks.
Those of you know what that is. It's not Team Fortress, it's not Super Nintendo. It's a casino game. That's right.
This game, you gotta get to a million dollars, and if you don't get to a million dollars, then you lose.
This game actually is very, very, very good. Let me change the title. Another casino game.
It's- it's gonna- I'm telling you, you guys are gonna like this.
Random NPCs come up to you in this game, and they like try to take money from you and shit. You're getting, like, fights.
Yeah, I'm telling you, you guys are gonna like this. You know, Inc. Never Again? Well, I already did it.
I already did Casino Inc. Let me get this right. All right, what should I title it? Road to a Million Dollars?
Road- I'm- it's gonna be Road to a Million. That works for me.
Make it E. Why would I make it just E?
It's not gonna happen.
All right, you guys ready? Las Vegas.
Vegas States. Vegas Adventure. When are we going to get there? I'm so tired of riding in this car.
Oh, quit complaining. We'll be there soon enough. Well, it'll be nice to stretch my legs and walk around.
I'm not complaining, just anxious to get there. Blackjack, sloth, roulette, craps, and poker. Which game should I play first?
Well, I'm heading right to the poker table. That's where I'll make my riches.
I don't know how to play poker, so I'm not gonna be doing that.
Hope I don't lose my shirt like I did the last time I went to Las Vegas.
We're here. Good luck and remember to go out in pairs. It'll be more fun. I don't know how to play poker.
I really don't. Like, I know like the basics of poker, but I don't know how to like look at a guy and be like,
Nah, fuck you. I bluffed you and then I lose a hundred thousand dollars. I don't know how to play.
You- all I know about poker is you wear sunglasses and just like- you're like the guy sleeping in the back of class.
That's how you be a good poker player. It's just emulate every college student that's sitting in the back.
Welcome to Golden Paradise Hotel. Checking in, please write your name.
Mr.
Mr. 23-D-C-T-3-4-5-F-G
Go back. How do I delete characters?
How do I delete this?
Mr. How about Mr. Space? Space? Like a ton of spaces.
Mr. L
Yes, Mr. L, we certainly have your reservation. I'll show you to your room. Please follow me.
Let's see if anyone wants to come to the casino with me.
How about
Cliff, Maria, Isabelle, or Richard? Who wants to go with me to the casino? Richard? How about Richard? Yeah.
I have to call him? We're not staying in the same room? Wait, wait, wait, wait. You guys didn't get a fucking suite?
Separate rooms?
What are you talking about? No, get like a- get like an executive suite. Everybody pull their money together and you get like fucking three bedrooms.
Hello, Richard. How about going to the casino with me?
Richard, wait for me in the lobby. I'll be right there.
All right, here we go. Select game.
What do you think we should do first? How about slots? Yeah.
All right, $50 slot. How much money do I have? I have $1,000.
Okay, that's just $250.
I just got something.
That's it?
$250, let's go. Give me another seven.
All right, I'm out. I'm out. Give me up. I'm out. How do I leave?
I didn't want to play again. I wanted to know.
No, I wanted to get out. I wanted to leave.
How do you get out? No, stop putting money into the machine and leave.
How can I help you? You got any advice?
There's only one way to win a slot machine. Insert a coin, pull a lever. With luck, you'll be a millionaire.
I'll be a- I'll be a millionaire?
Thanks for the advice.
What's that? Oops, all berries.
Go on, another orange.
That's fucking nothing.
Stop, Jeremy. This is my college money. There it is. All right, that's got to be something big.
All right, give me up.
Uh, I'm done with this one. I lost $400. It's okay. Let's go. We're gonna go. We're doing
Blackjack.
I actually kind of know how to play craps a little bit. Not really that much, but I know a little bit.
Max bet $250 to Blackjack.
At the start of this, I'll be a fucking idiot. At least you bet. I want to bet
$50.
Give me a hand. What do we got?
20.
Stay.
13, 20. This push gets the fuck out of here.
No, I'm staying on a 20. Why would he? Why would you? I'm not gonna hit it. I don't care. That's 20.
Just can't stay on 20. Why would you? I'm not hitting it. Why would I hit with the- No, what are you crazy?
You stand here too.
Uh, I've come to the realization the chat does not understand Blackjack. People don't know how to play this game, but don't worry.
Um, this is actually how you play Blackjack and you'll get corrected if you ever play.
Uh, this is basic strategy Blackjack. That's what it's called.
And uh, if the dealer has a four-five or a six,
is it- I'm talking to zoomers. Uh, sorry.
No, I'm not.
Why did you say that? I think I'm not talking to zoom. See, right? Just stand. Just take it. See, that's-
That's a 67% chance that he's gonna lose.
It's like probably 20 zoomers in this chat. Maybe. The rest of you are fucking doctors and shit.
You should know what I'm talking about. $250. Let's go. Big one.
It's horrible. All right. Should I split the twos? I guess the 10?
What do you think?
Split twos against the 10? That would be the worst thing ever.
Okay, we're gonna hit.
Give me 18.
All right, stay on. I have to- I should have hit on that one.
Okay, uh, I don't know what happened. 20 fucking one. Give me a break.
See, what I did right there is you never do that.
Uh, that was the dumbest thing ever. I was doing it for a stream joke and I ended up losing all my money. Big one.
Let's go.
13 against a five. Don't do anything.
If you have a 12 or over, don't do anything.
As you see, again, people don't get this. People don't understand.
If the deal is showing a five or a six, especially a six,
if you have a 12 or more, do not do anything. Stand. Don't hit. Don't be like,
well, I would have hit and then you bust and you lose.
No, you don't. No, no, you- that- you- this is how you- that's how you play blackjack.
Not if your cards count. Well, that person's gonna get thrown out of the casino. Let's fucking split.
I have- wait, how much money do I have?
I can't- how could I split this? I only had 250. Doesn't make any sense.
Let's take a card here.
Nope!
So, I lost 250.
You just did what you said not to do. No, a four, five, or a six.
All right, I'm gonna get it all back.
Here it is. This is bad. Insurance. No, it's fucking- that is my- that's the blackjack, right?
Okay, here we go. Come back. Just count cards. And now I know you guys don't- don't play blackjack.
You guys know that most decks have like eight decks.
Like between like six and eight decks is what people like to play. Good luck counting fucking like 500 cards.
By the way, get out. Kicked out of that- kicked that fucking person out of the casino.
All right. So, uh, where's the uh-
Where's the ATM? Why did I hit against a 10?
Yeah, that's a joke. Okay. That's a funny joke.
Uh, Gerber, we've been here for
10 minutes and you are- we- you know, we have like, uh, the hotel booked for four days, right?
Yeah, I'll just take a walk. I'll just- I'll just take a walk every day.
I gotta get that million, man. I think you actually like level up and shit. All right, just don't- no huge bets.
Need a new name here.
Mr.
Not Mr. L. This is- no, Mr. L is- is- Mr. Loss is more like it. No, no, no, no, no. Green. That's me. Greg Green.
Mr. Greg Green. God.
Let's see if anyone- okay. Richard was a bad- Richard was bad luck. We're gonna bring, uh-
Let's go with Maria.
Maria- no.
Yeah. Greg Green is the greedy Grinner's alter ego.
That's me in the lobby. All right. Here we go.
Select game. We're gonna do- gonna go to roulette.
Okay, no monster bets. Just play it well. What numbers? What am I choosing, guys?
All right. Always- always double zero.
Double zero. A hundred- no.
Twenty dollars on double zero.
And then we're gonna do, uh-
We're gonna do- can I do like corner bets in this?
Can you kind of go right? Okay. And then 13, 14, 16, 17.
Hundred bucks on the line. Let's go.
How do I say yes go? How do I say yes?
Ready. How do I say yes? Okay. Mr. Green, have you finished your bet? Yes, I have.
Let's go. Is that four?
Four black?
Anyway, all right. It's all right. You go- you go with the same strategy.
Same strategy right here. 13, 14, 16, 17. Hundred bucks. Get it on there.
Double zero. Zero and double zero.
Twenty bucks on each one.
Go for it. Let's go.
Mr. Green? I'm ready. 13, 14, 16, 17. Let's go.
The corner somewhere. Right here. 26. All right.
Just put one in every spot.
Dude, just put like a dollar on every number.
And then just sit there and stare while you don't win or lose anything.
You just are annoying.
No, you have to-
If you did this at the casino, it would be like, sir, sir, sir, sir, sir, sir. Stop, stop, stop.
What? I just want to make sure I win.
All right. Mr. Green?
Are you finished betting?
Yep. I'm ready. Spin that wheel.
Did I?
What? Okay. I was gonna say no way.
It cost $20.
Give me that all back. Thank you.
Now, here's the real fucking play. Mr. Green knows how to play roulette.
$40
on half the number.
And there's a 50-50 chance for you to make it back.
Now, don't call me Mr. Green for nothing. Spin it. Don't ever doubt Mr. Green.
And then I do a full cigar in one drag.
I won $720.
How's your luck, Fred? Mr. Green? Mine's been awful. Mind if I hang out with you for a while?
Get out of here, you fucking loser.
Well, that's okay. I think I'll just try someone else.
Copy the green strategy. Not on my watch.
Skip every number. Every other number.
See, right now there's like a group of like maybe 10 people have uh congregated behind me.
And like
I mean, they might be taking pictures of me and shit like like this is this guy's a fucking psycho. You know what I mean?
All right.
Hey, and just good luck.
All right, spin it. And the smoke comes out of my ears.
Mr. Green, you've won $640.
Thank you.
Oh, I can't put it all on red.
Sorry about that. It's Mr. Green sometimes. I'm out of your drink.
You know what?
Take my money somewhere else.
Let's take this to the slots. No. Blackjack.
$50 just came in 5,000 bits from Lesbian Bigfoot.
Thanks for the $50.
And they say, Jerma, today was my payday, so I thought I'd toss a couple bucks of your way.
You can use it on a couple more Funkos for your gamer room. Also, I know how much you hate playing Nancy Drew.
But I've had one request in the world. It would be that you play Ghost Dogs of Moon Lake from the series.
My sisters and I used to play those games all the time, and watching you play the games you did reminded me
of the fun we all used to have.
Thanks as always to the great content, Drew Crew Forever.
I'm such a w- I'm such a klutz. I sprained my ankle. I hate to ask, but Mr. Green,
would you please take me to the emergency room?
Who is the- why? Why me?
Can you imagine if I'm like a big high roller and I got a big crowd around me?
Like, wow, Mr. Green, that's another $100. Whoa.
All right, and like you push through this crowd. Mr. Green, Mr. Green, what is it? Yeah, what do you need?
Can you take me to the ER?
Can you sub- how many people did you push through?
And I'll tell you, you got gumption. You got gumption. No one's ever done that before. Get in the car. Let's go.
No one's ever fucking dressed me that way. Mr. Green took that person to the emergency room.
What?
That's it?
Let's go. 13 versus- yeah, I gotta hit, hit, hit, hit, hit.
Oh, I gotta hit again.
Okay, now you stay. He's gonna flip over 10. It don't matter. I lose anyways.
Oh, yeah. Mr. Green, you're so kind. Accept this gift I won at the slot machine.
Give me a thousand dollars?
Let's go. Uh, just spend her money.
Blackjack. Oh!
There it is. Blackjack.
Yeah, 3,500 bucks. Going pretty well. Do it again.
Nine, give me- oh, come on.
No, why would I double this?
Against a nine, that's stupid. Just hit. Take the card. Give me 10.
All right, I stay.
Flip over- oh, you motherfucker. Poor shit.
Remember, this is- we're spending her money right now. Blackjack again.
13 versus Jack. That sucks. Uh, I'm probably gonna lose.
Oh, that's even more annoying.
That's even more annoying that I probably have to take another card, but I can't.
I can't after three.
If I take- if you got three small cards like that, what the fuck, man?
Like eventually, I'm gonna get a monster card.
How's your luck been, Mr. Green? Mine's been awful. Mind if I hang out with you?
Yeah, sure. B.F. Bugleberry.
You can sit right here. You are always welcome.
Hope I can pick up some pointers.
You want to bet this? Yes.
11.
Ah, versus 10. That's so stupid.
This is dumb. This would be like a gasp at the table if I doubled down right here. Jesus Christ.
Well, I hope-
I hope some of your luck rubbed off on me. See you later.
I felt a bump when the loser walked past you. Check your pocket. Everything was okay.
Why is he a loser?
I didn't call him a loser. The game's calling him a loser.
Blackjack.
Ah! Not 20, anyway.
Mr. Green.
Your luck didn't rub off. I won $15,000 on that slot machine. I can't forget my lucky charm. I want you to have this
$5,000.
Holy shit.
Some voice. What are you talking about?
This isn't right. This is wrong. This really isn't my voice. This is my voice.
All right, dude, I got $8,000 right now. Fuck you. I have to hit again. Oh, that's how you get it done at the table.
All right, get up. Let's go. Out.
What do I got? I got fucking 8,500 bucks. Out.
Game's really loud.
I can exit the casino.
Should I go? Well, I'm gonna return to the room.
Just hang out in the room for a little bit. Go gambling with another friend. Save your scores and
let's go with another friend.
Get room service?
All right, Cliff. Let's go. Let's go, Cliff.
Keep your 8.5k.
This is road to a million. Not road to 8.5k.
Select game. Let's go. All right. Let's do. All right. How do you play poker? Does somebody help me?
$200 minimum. Maximum. It's easy.
Everyone's got 10 grand. Anti. 20. Minimum is 20. Maximum is 20.
Press A button to anti up.
All right. Anti up.
So do we all get five cards? This is gonna take forever.
I got a seven. I got a two. I got hearts.
At 20. All right. This is what I don't understand about poker.
This shit here.
Like bet. Raise. Call. Check. I don't know what that stuff means.
Um, what does call mean? It's an awful hand.
Call means like I don't want to raise.
Hold.
It means call your mother. It means
the call means you put the same amount that they did.
Oh wait, the bugleberry's over there. He's using some of that money.
It's equal to current bet. Okay.
Call. Call. Call. Call. Call. So what does check mean?
No bet. Do nothing.
Don't bet anything.
I want to play. I want to participate.
What's the pot worth?
This dude's got two fours.
Hey, we got we got a pair over there.
Call. Call. Can I? Can I?
Can I hurry up?
Wait a minute. I thought you weren't supposed to
like
show emotions.
That's that guy's got like a royal flush.
This is getting to be five hundred dollars.
Why don't you guys make me fold? That that that was a chance.
Is anybody gonna they keep doing this?
Get a straight straight. Uh, yeah, of course.
What did he just win?
He just won 4100 bucks. Ha ha ha. I won. I won. Look at this pot.
All right. I lost 20 bucks. Let's do it again.
Anyhow, this game's not even played anymore.
Yeah, Texas Hold'em is the one that's this at every casino now.
But this also sucks.
I'm staying in. I'm just gonna bluff the fuck out of everybody.
Raise a thousand dollars.
Raise 200.
Okay, go ahead and spin it around.
Yeah.
All right. What you don't know is I have pocket aces.
Call. Okay.
All right. Leave that queen. Oh fuck. That guy's got
Uh-oh.
Raise it again.
Maybe next time I fold.
Call.
Look at this dog shit hand.
I'm I just tried to scare everybody.
No, he's got I no no no no no that guy probably has like a three of a kind. I'm out.
This dude's got a three of a kind. He's probably has three jacks.
Yeah, who knows that guy could have a a flush.
No, I can't like just pretend. I mean look at he's look at how happy he is again. He's probably got like a
No, he's back to normal.
I want to see one of them get excited.
Raise 100.
Call.
All right. What do you got?
I got 100. This looks like I want this money.
He only had two pair. Whatever. Two pair. Two pair. Two pair.
This is bullshit. I won. Look at this pile of chips and they're mine. Whatever.
Let's do it again.
I had shit. Yeah, I keep getting why am I the only person who gets bad cards? Not fair.
Leave the table. No, no, no, no, no, no, not yet. All right, come on.
I'm not gonna fold this time.
Yeah, see you later. Get out.
Give me another. Give me a jack. That's I could get a flush here.
Check. What? Yeah, zero. Uh, wait. Hold on. What did I do?
Call. 50 dollars. Should I call that? Raise 20.
All right. Call. Call.
Can you just go around the table and just keep saying call, call, call, call until the cards come out?
Holy shit.
Get out. Good.
My secret is to know when to hold them and when to fold them. What about you?
I can't keep it. I can't keep up now. You can't because they all that's so they all saw the fucking they saw the royal flush.
That's a 900 dollar.
Wait, oh.
All right. Last one.
900 by the way. Yeah, well they had to take taxes out.
Got an ace.
I do have an ace.
Fold with an ace? No, no. I'm gonna get another ace.
Raise.
50 bucks.
Lower the game audio? I will. After this pan.
Ace.
All right, I'm leaving.
All right. Now we're gonna take this to the slot.
Well, should I play a crap? I know I have a very very basic understanding of crap.
How about just leave the table?
Sit on the toilet.
Fuck. Leave this casino. Go to a different casino.
Go to a different casino. All right. I I don't want to see how happy they are that they're winning.
I want to go.
Why is it? It's because John he wins every time. Oh, no.
Carol wasn't all that difficult. Maybe next time I beat you. I'm so sorry to ask you for a favor, but I desperately need some cash.
Would you like to buy this diamond? I guarantee it is worth quite a bit. It's been appraised for five thousand dollars.
How much will you give me for it?
All right, I'll make him an offer.
Five thousand you say, huh?
Give you ten dollars to get the fuck away from me and stop talking to me and my friends.
About four thousand. Ten dollars.
Maybe you give me a little more. How about thirty six hundred?
Ten.
Dollars.
How about thirty two hundred?
Ten.
Fucking.
Dollars.
Can you give me a little more? How about twenty eight hundred?
Ten.
Dollars.
Can you give me a little more? How about twenty five hundred?
You're going to only get
ten fucking dollars.
Ah, what a pain.
God, some people. Let's get out of here. All right, I'm gonna pee. I'll be right back.
I'm full of piss today. Sorry.
Oh, mute. Oh.
See this.
It is. It is. The music's kind of annoying.
I'm gonna drop it. Here we go. I don't know if that's any better.
Better? Is it better?
I'll be right back.
Screen is back.
Uh, exit casino.
Can you go to different casinos? Is that how this works?
Exit casino.
Can I go to a different one?
Oh shit.
Which casino should we visit? Whoa, the 2020.
We have to go to the 2020. It's the current year.
Oh, check it out. This one has a sci-fi atmosphere.
Yeah, let's go.
2020. The 2020.
That's so weird.
Holy, this music is gonna drive me nuts.
Oh, no, there's a higher minimum. There's a higher max. Oh, no.
Five, ten, fifteen, twenty, twenty, five hundred dollars for a spin.
Come on.
Oh.
One more. That's it. I'm done.
Come on.
Okay. Yeah, I'm fine. Everything's fine.
All right.
Oh shit. What was that?
All right. Let's play craps. I know very little of them.
All right. I'm gonna do a thousand dollar craps. Here we go.
I'm gonna fucking destroy this.
So I'm gonna put...
If I remember how craps works, I'm gonna...
The whole thing with craps is you don't want to roll a seven.
I'm gonna put a thousand dollars on the pass line.
Let's go.
And then I'm gonna put...
And these are bets that if this shows up, if you get double sixes, right?
Then you just get this payout.
Pass is the best out. Yeah, I know.
And these are sucker bets. This is 30 to one for snake eyes.
Can I do a thousand dollar sucker bet and make fucking 30 grand?
All right. How about 50 dollar sucker bet?
Looking for two ones.
All right. I'm good.
I'm done.
No seven.
Six.
Yeah, there we go.
Too bad I didn't pay that.
Yeah, because of the fucking bet over there.
Okay. Now, if a six shows up...
Wait, hold on.
I'm trying to remember how this works.
All right. Now I want to...
Now I'm...
Okay. You're gonna land on a fucking four.
I can't bet here. Why not?
Yeah. Okay. I want to...
500 bucks and you're gonna fucking be hitting fours all day.
If a six shows before a seven, you win.
Right.
Okay. Good.
I'm gonna throw a four right now.
Nine.
Nobody wins. Nobody...
He's gonna...
Come on.
Let's see a four.
Stay.
The sucker bet.
I was gonna put a hundred dollars on that.
Do that four.
Six.
There we go.
That's it. I win.
Bingo.
Thousand bucks.
Keep going.
The thing about craps is you can just keep going.
Thousand bucks on the pass line.
God damn it. I was gonna do that too.
I was gonna do one of these moron bets.
How's your luck been, Mr. Green?
Mr. Green, how's your luck been?
Oh, mine's been awful.
I have $15,000 I want.
Can I hang out with you again?
Sure.
Thank you. I hope I can pick up some more pointers from you.
I blew it out.
Hey, sit down.
No.
Give me a fucking break.
Okay.
Thank God.
Well, I hope some of your luck rubbed off on me.
I'll see you later.
Oof.
Bugleberry bumps into you as they walk by.
You check your pockets and everything is fine.
Go on, Bugleberry.
Go hit a fucking hundred million dollars.
Again.
Yes.
Don't hit a seven.
No sevens, no sevens, no sevens.
Oh, Mr. Green, you'll never believe it.
Your luck rubbed off on me again.
I want another $15,000 on a smart machine.
I can't forget you again.
I gotta give you five grand again.
It's $10,000 in two days.
Hey, thanks for the $5,000.
And guess what?
Now I'm back up, oh boy, before I even walked in the fucking door.
Back to roulette.
$1,000.
We're going...
Okay, this is where we...
You're gonna think I'm fucking nuts.
You're gonna think I'm nuts.
I'm saying $1920, $22, $23, right in the middle.
$1,000.
Let it ride, go.
That was Bugleberry money.
Who cares?
That's all right.
I'm doing it one more time.
This is Bugleberry money.
Again, $1920, $22, $23.
$1920, $22, $23.
Oh.
Ah.
Ah, it was right there.
Right next to $19.
Oh.
$1920, $22, $23.
$18, you motherfucker.
You gotta be kidding me.
$1920, $22, $23.
If I don't hit, I'm out.
Back to the slot.
Right, it lands on the one right next to it.
Put every cent that I have on $9, $8, and $5.
Ah, fuck.
Shit.
Mr. Green.
Mr. Green, are you all right?
Yeah, I'm doing fine.
Let it roll again.
And listen, don't ask me how I'm doing after this.
Just leave me alone.
And another drink.
If I could get one, it'd be really good.
Mr. Green.
Yep.
That's a three.
Yeah, I can read.
Place your bets.
I'm telling you, I love this guy.
There's a guy I watch.
He's a live streamer.
He's really, really lucky.
It has to hit it at some point
because this guy just makes noises on the internet
and he's the master fortune.
He's got to be the luckiest person in the fucking world.
Mr. Green knows all.
Fortune.
What?
That's four times in a row?
An alien who's just in here
and just speared through my chest.
Fuck, that hurts.
This is an alien from Aliens Vibes.
Just boom, bam, through my chest.
Let's go, 985.
Oh my god, ace right there.
God damn it.
Well, here's my last.
Hey, Bugleberry.
Do you need any more luck?
Where's Bugleberry?
Can I have some more money?
He's losing his two.
All right, everything on four.
Everything on four.
Fucking piece of shit.
Mr. Green, thank you for your stay at the 2020.
Yep.
How'd you do?
Oh.
Yeah.
Jerma sucks at this game.
Jerma sucks at gambling.
No, I have to, I have to get, I want to be,
I want to get transferred to the executive suite.
They're just kept playing half the numbers.
Mr. Green, you're back.
I'm back.
How about Mr. Green's?
I changed my name to make sure I, yeah, Mr. Green's.
Stop wasting your money on gambling.
Tax fraud.
See, I changed my name every two or three years.
Just add a couple of letters.
It makes me able to, hold on, wait, we need,
why am I talking like this?
All right, safe plays only.
We're going to make it.
I'm going to get, I got across the $10,000 threshold after.
Different casino.
You just ruined three people's lives.
What's another bankrupt person?
Okay, let's go to the Buffalo Head.
Let's make a killing in the Old West.
Easy Godina Crunch is the worst item ever.
You're just trying to get me to be angry with you?
Sound weird.
All right, here we go.
Face your bets.
Hey, Mr. Green's, do you remember me?
Uh, yeah, from poker.
Your face seems a little familiar.
I bet you thought you'd never see me again.
Thank, thanks for being so nice to me.
I appreciate it so much.
I'd like to give you that.
What I've won here tonight is here's $2,000.
Oh, wait, no, this is the emergency room.
Oh, nice.
She knows your identity.
All right, this is Stephanie money.
This isn't even mine.
Bye, Jack.
Fuck.
Damn it.
I had to do it.
This is Stephanie money.
14.
Fuck you.
Stay on.
It's just a six.
It's gonna, you're gonna bust it.
Boink.
Oh, you got fucking 21.
There's like a 10% chance that you would get 21 with a six.
Unbelievable.
That's bullshit.
This is Stephanie money.
Who cares?
19.
There we go.
All right.
Good, good.
All right, do it again.
Mr. Greens, I'm down on my luck.
Would you like to purchase my lottery ticket?
The payoff is $10,000.
It cost $1,000, but I will sell it to you for $500.
Yeah, sure.
This is Stephanie money.
Who cares?
Thanks a lot.
I'm sure that ticket's a winner.
Good luck.
What if it is?
No.
The winning lottery number is 98985?
98955.
You checked your ticket.
I just won $10,000.
This is Stephanie money.
Who cares?
Yes, finally.
Four versus.
Oh, no, no, no.
21 again.
You can't be fucking serious.
I'm so sorry to ask you for a favor, but I desperately need some cash.
Would you like to buy this diamond?
I guarantee it's worth quite a bit.
How much were you willing to pay for it?
You know, there was another guy that used to come around here.
And talk about his diamond.
I'll give you 100, 100, 100.
This is fucking Stephanie money.
Who gives a shit?
Seven.
Eighteen.
Stand.
I don't do it.
Fifteen versus six.
Just fucking stay with this.
That's fucking unbelievable.
I hate this.
The coward play.
Whatever.
What the fuck is happening?
That's 212121212121.
Fuck you.
I have to do it.
What do you got under there?
Yeah, of course.
This table's fucked.
I'm out.
This casino I'm out out.
I'm out of here.
Maria, let's get the fuck out of here.
I let's go to another place.
This place fucking stacks their decks.
Let's go to the golden parrot.
No, let's go to the hideaway.
Hideaway club.
This place looks pretty run down.
We should make it our last resort.
You sure you want to go here?
Golden paradise, isn't that where I was?
This one seems okay. Which is the one that I started at?
Golden Corral? Go to Pasta Italiano.
All right, here we go. Let's see what I got. Slots.
What do we got? 50. All right. Now I can't get- I can't damage myself here. Even if I want to do something insane, like for instance.
Five dollar spins. Look at this.
How do I increase the bet?
It's 50 dollars? How do I do it? I want to do- I want to do 50 dollar bet.
Go back. Did I have to pick it? I had to pick it.
I need to go to a different machine. Oh.
Staff are asking for a raise.
All right, here we go. Let's do it.
250 a spin. Get a big hit.
And then I'll- I'll get a million dollars.
That's a- that's a pretty big hit. That's a million dollars, I think.
Nice.
Ah, your staff has died.
Oh, that game is so fucked up.
No, I gotta get a good lineup with the 250 dollar bet. It's a terrible payout.
It's 50 dollars a line.
And this is the junkie payout? This is a junk payout you're gonna give me for this shit?
Oh, look at this junk.
Junkie payout.
What's that? Relax. This is just Stephanie money.
Uh,
not anymore.
This is Mr. Green money now.
Come on.
Say, Mr. Greens, do you remember me?
Yes.
I bet you thought you'd never see me again. Thanks for being so nice to me. I appreciate it. So here, here's two thousand dollars. People
just come up to me and give me money.
And uh, apparently because I-
I remember what they look like.
Hey, Mr. Greens. Yeah, that's me. Remember me? We sat at the same blackjack table for 20 minutes.
Oh, yeah, I guess we did.
Yeah, thanks for letting me play blackjack with you, even though that's just what you do at the casino.
Here's two thousand dollars because you sat next to me and know that- remember what I look like. Yeah.
This is realistic.
Casino plants.
Wait, I just- whoa, whoa. Oh, no, right, right, right, right.
Give me a big hit.
How are these coward bets?
This is 50 dollars a line and you're calling this a- these a coward bets?
Orange. Now that's gonna be big.
Now that's gonna be good.
That's not good at all. Can I see the- um, let me see, please.
Holy shit, this really is the worst machine ever. Um, okay.
Seven. I'm taking it down to- if I go under ten thousand, I'm fucking out of here. Watermelon. Oh.
Ten dollars for a bag of cheetos.
Watermelon. Shit.
Go big or go jump king. It's an interesting one to hear.
Go big or go jump king.
Ah, shit.
All right, this is it. This is it. Nine, nine, nine, nine.
Let's go win it. Can I give you a lottery ticket? No, I don't want anybody's lottery tickets.
Under- okay, now I'm under ten thousand.
Hey. Hey, say Mr. Greens.
Do you remember me?
Yes. Um, you just walked over here, but at half an hour-
You're the girl who gave me two thousand dollars for remembering what you looked like. Yeah, I remember you.
I bet you thought you'd never see me again. Thanks for being so nice to me.
I appreciate it. So I want to give back. Here's another two thousand dollars.
Thanks.
I know who you are. Remember that. I know what you look like if you ever want to give any money to people.
I know who you are.
You're the two thousand dollar girl. Come on back if- I don't know. I remember.
Nobody else will though. Nobody else. Come to me.
People have shit memories nowadays. Come to me.
This feels like a weird-
Uh, like-
It's a- it's a- it's a simp?
Watermelon.
But no-
Come on.
German, no. Shut up. I- what do you want me to say?
I'm just reading.
That's a big one. Give me a monster hit.
I mean an absolute fucking
monster of a hit.
You're the screamer.
Oh.
There it is. Monster fucking hit.
Monster hit.
You all didn't believe in me.
You didn't believe in my monstrous ability.
That's probably 20 grand.
Look at this. Oh, it's not 20 grand. It's a lot though.
All right, that's it.
Far. Now stop. Not yet.
Just- I- I- if I go under 16, how do you give yourself a new ceiling?
16 is the ceiling.
If I go under 16, we're out.
Okay, now we make it- we're gonna make a new ceiling?
Okay.
Under 16, 5, we're out.
Bingo.
Under 17, we're out.
Okay.
Same plan.
I'm gonna stop right now. This is not real. It's not my money. It's not real money.
Under 17, we're up.
What if it was?
We fucked up.
All right. This is it.
I got one more after this potentially.
Okay.
If I don't hit, we're up. Because we're under 17, fuck.
See?
8,500 fucking bucks.
Stop. You're gambling your net worth.
All right. Now let's go to the- let's go to the nice casino.
I want to go to the one that has like $5,000 bets.
All right. Uh, Richard, come on with us.
Go to the shitty one. I'm not- you- why- are you kidding me?
You want me to bring
$17,000
into a casino that's supposed to be like a bad casino?
Oh, this looks really really bad. This is pretty shady. We shouldn't go here. Oh, no, no, no, excuse me.
All right, don't worry. Let me just take $17,000 in cash with me in here.
I'm Mr. Greens.
It's only 17k.
All right, let's go to- I don't want to go there with that much money.
Let's- we got to go to the big casino.
I can't go to Laurel Palace yet. 2020 is the one that is
big bets.
I'm ready.
Here we go. 2020, baby.
All right.
Here we go.
Back to Blackjack.
Thousand dollars a hand. Let's go.
Let's go. I'm fucking- I'm bringing this down to ten. I got a $7,500 bankroll.
Shit. Bad start. That's a bad start.
Fuck you.
Fuck. Mr. Greens, I found this wallet with a thousand dollars in it.
You fucking idiot. That's just the money I put on the table. I was about to place it and I dropped it.
What are you, dub? I'm sorry. I don't mean that.
Uh, turn it in. It's a thousand dollars. It means fuck. That's nothing to Mr. Greens.
Turn it in.
I'm so glad you found it. That's mine.
Stay.
Wow, you found a wallet. I've been looking for that. Thanks.
Double the bet? You can't double-
Why would you do that?
Mr. Greens, the hotel office said you turned in my wallet. Thanks.
I played roulette and put all the money on my favorite number and won. I would like to reward your honesty.
If you weren't so honest, I wouldn't have won. So I'm giving you half of my winnings.
Wait.
Is that just how- that's- that's just my money.
You gave me 17.5? I had 17.5.
Oh my god.
Okay, I got 34,000 dollars.
That's a 20 versus six. Why can't I split them?
I wish I could split these. Why? I can't- I got- because it's not the same damn thing. Whatever.
Look at how well I did.
You know, it's bad when you're playing a game, a casino game,
and the amount of, you know, your net winnings so far are probably
maybe like positive four or five hundred dollars at this point.
But the amount of charitable donations to my bankroll has been upwards of 50,000 dollars.
That's kind of a strange casino game. My profit is just donations.
Come on.
Something- why? Two aces.
This is so dumb.
Ah!
Just like in real life.
He's a streamer at heart. These are all bits.
There's a blackjack finally.
Life imitates art.
Another blackjack. Two in a row. I got 30 grand. When do I- oh, why?
When do I unlock the- the expensive casino? I have 35,000 dollars. Do I need to go- it's six figures?
The only way that's gonna happen is if somebody loses another wallet.
Ah!
That's so bad. The link? Link, link. Hold on. Wait, wait, wait. I just clicked a stay.
Holy fuck. I didn't even mean to do that. I can't believe that just happened.
All right, click the link. Click the link. Hold on.
Where's this link? Is it on screen?
I don't- who-
What is this?
Who is that?
Is that a- is that a- wait, is that a per- is that- that's a person. Mr. Green and Bugleberry?
I don't- but that's like a per- that's a real person.
Bugleberry.
Do it again. Give me a blackjack. Four, five, six, man.
Howard.
Howard is not how you win in a casino game. I mean this- that is how you win. What am I talking about? Yes.
Even.
Okay, sure. Could you put
$20,000 on the table right now and hit blackjack and have like 80 grand in your pocket? Sure.
Um, or you just don't win that hand and then the re- all your money's gone.
Rather than just bleeding 500 to a thousand dollars like I'm doing here over the course of like seven hours.
I'm not doing this because that ends everything now.
I'll do this
over the course of a few hours.
And then look, you lost 30 grand. I only lost 100.
Insurance? No.
Turd grand.
It's just virtual. I- look, are you kidding me?
Do you really think the guy with no self-control
if- if I was able to like legally at this table that I wouldn't do this three times? Are you kidding me?
You know, you- you're on- what channel you're on, right?
There you go. This is blackjack. I want to be able to bet $10,000 a hand. That's what you don't understand. That's double blackjack.
All right. Oh, we've crossed.
17 versus a nine. I hate this but I'm gonna do it.
Don't let him. He could have just won so much. Yeah, but I- it's not allowed. The max bet is 10- is a thousand.
I'm max betting right now.
Go all in. I would if I could. You know, I would. I would do a
$35,499 bet now.
See if I can break 40. Give me blackjack again. All right, let's split him up.
Here we go. This is it. Split him.
18 and 20. Stay on both of them. Stay on both.
Get the hell out of here. Yep. That's a double.
2,000 fucking bucks.
Okay. Now-
Mr. Greens, my little girl is very sick and needs an operation. We're too poor.
I know we just met but could you please lend me a hundred dollars?
Absolutely. Thank you so much. I'll come back in about two or three hands with 50 grand.
Bye!
Do you- do you wish to come back?
Remember me? I know your face.
Mr. Greens, you've saved the life of my baby. Here's two hundred dollars.
Oh. Two hundred?
I-
Uh, not more than that. Uh, I mean,
I had a guy sit next to me
and he sat behind me for a few hands and gave me five grand.
And then a lady came up and asked me if I remembered what she looked like twice and I got four grand.
Okay, I just saved your daughter's life and I only got a hundred dollars.
What is this?
Are you fucking serious?
And then just a huge- another huge inhale and I'm holding it in.
Where is it? Where is it? Where's that- where's the smoke? He has to breathe the smoke out eventually.
And then like a little trail of smoke is coming up from behind me.
And then I just stare and I go, you know where that's coming from. And then everybody's like what the- this guy's- fuck!
I can't wait till you get old. What? You think I'm gonna be like this?
You know what? I'm gonna get insurance because fuck it.
God damn it. And one time I do-
The one time I- oh my god, whatever. Grymer's teeth are gonna be brown.
Wait, why do I have brown teeth?
Damn it. All right. I'm getting up. I'm going.
Too much CBT oil?
I'm getting up. Okay, quick quick quick quick.
Okay.
I'm doing poker. I need your help here.
I'm doing a thousand dollars on poker.
I need you guys help. The ante's a hundred bucks. Let's go. Seven- seven cards start his ass.
Did I just combine two messages in a row?
Stefan, you got- all right. I'm ready. Double Stefan. We're ready to go.
Go all in. A hundred- a thousand dollars.
Raise 500. Sure. I'll do that too.
Hey, I'm gonna raise it a thousand dollars.
Who's this guy?
Wait.
Who's the guy with like the- the cyborg face?
This is a fifty one hundred dollar pot right now.
Paul.
Give me another seven.
Shit. Oh no. All right.
Okay, let's keep going. He doesn't get shit over there. We got a pair of fours. Dickhead.
Paul. Paul. Paul. Yeah, you got a pair of fours.
Dickhead.
Seven, eight, nine.
He's from the future. The year 2020.
He folded. That was the guy I was worried about. Wait. You got two aces.
Oh shit. You have two aces.
What an idiot. Holy shit. Did it work? He's got twos.
Fuck.
Call bluff. Call bluff. Get out. Oh shit. You just- oh my god. That's too much.
Call. Give me a se-
What's that? Two pair?
I got two pair though.
Holy shit. I'm gonna win ten thousand more dollars. All right. Raise it all in.
This is seven. I got a pair of threes and sevens.
Let's scare the shit out of him. Are you still- are you still at the table?
Are you still at the table? Okay. You still want to go, huh? You want to go?
You got any more money? You got a thousand more dollars to put on this?
Okay. All right. You want to play games?
That's one of- that's a scenario where you- you're like at the table
and you just like sit up. You stand up and you like
point like once just at the sky and you go, ah,
ah, um, good luck.
Good luck everybody. Good luck everybody.
I wish everybody good luck.
And then you fucking just walk away and you walk with your hands in your pockets and you're just like one, two, three, four, five, six, count my steps.
Okay, I gotta take a piss. Let's pee.
Okay, then you're fine. Just go
It's all right. Say fuck. Fuck. Let's hope. Ah, it's okay. All right. Let's go. Let's go to the buffet.
Oh my god, what's happening? Thirty one thousand five hundred dollars on one?
Okay. Wait, what just happened? I can't do that. Stop doing that. I'm trying to-
Why is it doing this?
Oh, I have to- minimum bet is a hundred. Oh shit.
Okay, we're gonna do one, two, three, four, five.
Six, seven, eight, nine. I'm ready. This song.
Is that a color? I thought I was a coward. Just bet one through twelve, but you don't get the same payback.
It's thirty five and one. I said the word thirty five and it landed on it. Great.
I'm pro- how am I- I'm this- I'm pro- look, this is not even my money. Somebody gave this to me.
And I'll bet my age. One, two, three, four, five, six, seven, eight, nine.
Thirty four. Why didn't I just do my fake age that I said that I am? I'm thirty three.
Now, how old are you? Ah, thirty three. All right, now thirty five.
I'm just on a fake age. God damn it. Do your real age. I'm not actually thirty five, but okay.
Let's see if it works. God damn it. I should have done how old people say that I look.
It's not about the age that you actually are. The age that you pre- it's the how- it's how you feel.
People think I'm twenty five, twenty four. Fuck. All right, now I'm gonna- it's now- it's gonna be
the age that I wish that I was. The age that I wish that I just still was. Twenty eight's great.
You know, it's like twenty eight. You're older, but you're not old. That's the age I wish I could
stay for. All right, fuck the whole twenties. Twenty- we'll start at twenty one. The twenties
are gone, guys. I don't have them anymore. I'm now in my thirties. Well, dude, we'll do my entire
demographic. Wait, how many is that? Okay, now this is like how old- I'm wrong. All right,
all right. I'll do the range. Fine, fine, fine, fine, fine. You're not gonna complain. You're not
twenty one. You're not even that same range, old boomer. I'm gonna say shut up. I'm gonna say shut up.
Okay, there you go. Twenty six. Twenty six to thirty five is like my age kind of range.
God damn it. I should have bet on the fucking median age of the audience. Not about how old I
am. I keep getting this wrong. The age that we act. There's the thing. Here's the thing. All right,
well, let's be- okay, here we go. Here's my- how I act. Not how you act. How I act. Okay,
I think that's pretty good. Let's go. All in on eleven.
The gods wanted my real age again. I act thirty-four apparently. It's how thirty-four
year olds act. Okay, uh, a thousand dollars on one. All right, if you come over to a table
and- hold on, this is important. Let me- how do I- let me get out with this. Where's my camera?
I'm gonna show you what you do. Here's- here's how this plays out. If you ever come up to a table,
okay, and you put a thousand- here's how you're gonna- it's how you're gonna act. Wait a minute,
hold on. Dougalberry again. I'm such a klutz. I- I'm such a klutz. I sprained my ankle,
and I hate to ask, but Mr. Green, would you please take me to the emergency room?
Yeah, let's go. Hey, thanks for the free money. Mr. Green's took that person to the emergency room.
Okay, here we go. We're gonna put a thousand dollars on, uh, twenty. This is what- if you put
that much money on a number, you're gonna go up to the table, and you're gonna go like this.
Hey, who's back? Let's go. Thousand dollars on 13, 14 in the corner. 13, 14, 15, 7. What was it?
It's gonna be impossible. The numbers are too close together. Okay, literally how this is going to
work is I- the first- the first number that I see in chat is again a thousand dollars on it.
There's 10. Got it wrong. Boring number. Omega lol. What? Ban that person. Okay, yeah. Time that
person up. Time that person up for fucking five minutes. Okay, um, okay. I'm gonna pick a number,
and I'm gonna say your name. Uh, jbumbum. jbumbum. Twenty-three thousand dollars on it. If this
doesn't hit, ban that person for ten minutes. Uh, gun gun guy said 36. Gun gun guy. Hold on.
Blown all of my money. I even spent my return fare home. Can you spare two hundred dollars
for this watch? Yeah, sure. Thank you for saving. Well, all right, what was that guy's name? Uh,
gun gun? Gun guy, whatever his name was. Okay, thousand dollars here. What's wrong? Time amount.
It left. Time amount anyways. Well, you ran because you knew that it was- it was not gonna
hit. You just said number. Uh, skeletoxin says 14. That's a nice watch. You want to sell it for
a thousand dollars? Yeah. Thirteen? Wait, what is it? Fourteen? What was their name? I don't even
remember. Wait, I didn't put a bet down. If this is actually 14, don't even. I don't think. Thank
God. I didn't put the bet down, but they were wrong. Ban them anyways. All right, what are we
doing? 26. All right, the true Mechi. 26. Ban them for 10 minutes if this is wrong. Oh, 27 to 26.
So close, but it's still a 10 minute time up. Goodbye. Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait,
wait. What did they say? Double zero, stinky. Okay, fine. Psycho. Psycho. What was it? Psycho what?
I don't even know what the psycho in their name. Double zero. Ban them. Ban. What is it? Ban me 12.
Ban me- who said that? I said ban me 12. Ban me 12. Okay, ban them first. I'm gonna do 12. Do 20
minutes if this is wrong. 35 keeps popping up. Let's just put- I'm gonna- okay, I'm gonna put
a hundred bucks on 35 every time. Uh, MaxPowey31. You know the deal? 21. Okay. Somebody said get the-
get the range and ban everybody writing the numbers. 11 to 35. Ban everyone.
I have a kind heart. I can't believe this. All right. 16 or ban me. 16 read or ban me.
I will mute for five- I'll mute for five minutes. Ah! That's fucking ridiculous. I know I'm banned.
Ban me again. Fucking whatever. I'm saying my piece. That's ridiculous. I didn't get the
last two. Whatever. It's been five minutes. Whatever. Fuck it. Here's what do you got.
Uh, it's one- 10 grand. Somebody said move on. What do you mean move on? I got 22 grand still.
This is not even my money. Six or mod me. Okay. Who said that? Wait, this- this is or mod me? What
do you mean? Six means if you- lands on six then you get mod. Yeah, you were wrong. No, no, it was
if they got- no, it's not mod me. No, they- if they have it hit, yeah, then you deserved it.
Game's muted. Oh, fuck. Seven or I eat eggs. Whoever said that. Seven or they- oh, they eat eggs.
Well, yeah, and you're gonna get timed out for 10 minutes. Ooh, that was close. That was close.
That was pretty close. All right, let's go burn the rest of this. Let's go. Ready? You know what
I'm going- you know what I'm doing here. This is what we're doing. Let's go. Let's do it. Let's
fucking go. Let's go. We're going super mode. $2,500 a spin. Let's go. Go broke.
Come on. It's gotta get one fucking monster hit. Oh, come on. I gotta do it. Come on. Where's the
monster hits? Derma sucks thanks for five community subs. God damn it. Seven. Seven.
I just won. That's like a hundred thousand dollars I win. Get the fuck out of here.
None of you believed in me. None of you believed in Mr. Green.
Is there anything even left on this? I just put it in my mouth and breathe it in just to make you feel
less than me. You see? This cigar cost $2,500. I got $110,000 fucking dollars. Yeah. Did I beat the
game? Mr. Greens, I've got great news for you. Due to your great success, you have been awarded
a high roller status and with it a complimentary room at the Laurel Palace. The Laurel Palace?
We could never go there before. Good going, Mr. Greens. Go pack your bags. Our limo is waiting
to take you to Laurel Palace. Oh, that's right. Where I belong with all the other rich people.
A high roller. I'll miss this old room, but not too much.
Well, I hope my limo is ready. Now it's off to the Laurel Palace.
That's my internal monologue. My internal monologue, I still think I'm a good person
and I talk normally, but I'm actually horrible. But I like to pretend I am in my head.
Welcome to the Laurel Palace. Wow. Check it out. A great room and free to boot. Well,
time to go back. Get back to the casino floor. And there'll be no stopping me till I reach $10
million. That's, uh, if you, if you go to the casino, going there with the goal to
come up with $10 million, um, what you should be trying to do is to be able to still afford to go
to Taco Bell when it's all over. So I think you're going in with weird expectations here.
Holy shit. Look at this place. Wow. Like games. Let's do, how, what's the slot like? Oh, that's
a $5,000 bid. Oh, that's a lot of money. Oh no. I'm about to lose. I'm about to lose a comma.
Come on, keep it up. Okay. Is it weird that I feel like if you're sitting at a,
if you're here doing a $5,000 a spin slot machine, you are like this amorphous blob thing that your
body is just folding over the sides of the seat and you're just like leaning back and
you have like two drinks attached to like a helmet on your head. And there's like people,
you're getting a manicure and a pedicure on all of your hands and feet at the same time.
And when you blink, somebody else presses the button for you. That's $5,000 a spin.
If I get a big hit here. Oh my God. That would have been, I would have won. That would have been
the whole game. Okay. All right. I don't want to lose all my riches. Don't get cocky. I just,
I've got to give myself a limit down to $90,000. $90,000 is the limit. $80,000. That's a good call.
$80,000 is the limit. All right. I can, I'm still here. What about $70,000? No, that's pushing it.
Damn it. That watermelon would have been sick. You know what? $80,000. Come on. What the
fuck are you doing in here? I'm so sorry to ask you for a favor. I desperately need some cash.
Would you like to buy this diamond? I guarantee it is worth a bit. It's been appraised for $5,000.
How much will you give me for it? A lot of money. How about $500? I'll give you $500. Come on.
$500. $3,600. No. $500. No. $500. $2,800. You got yourself a deal. $2,800 bucks. I mean,
I was $5,000. All right. Guys, I spent $5,000 a spin. Big one. All right.
Mr. Greens, that's a very good imitation diamond. I'll give you $100 for it.
I don't need that. You were conned. How would you know?
How would you know? If I had a ring on and you came over, like, hey, you got a fake ring on.
Okay. I know. What if I knew that? Game sucks. $777,000. I got all $777. That's why I got out
like game Blackjack. We'll be doing monster fucking hands here. No.
I can't. I can't. I can't do it. I can't do it. It took me so long to get this.
I can't do it. I'll do it. I'll do it. Oh, shit. I have to stand here. This is handy.
He's going to bust on. He's going to bust on it. Oh my God. Oh no.
Do it again. Do it again. Come on. $14 versus $8. Fuck. Oh shit. Don't turn over a $10.
yeah I am invincible I am untouchable no one can fuck with mr. green that's a 19
baby stand on 19 yeah what do you got you ain't got nothing and I know for a
fact that the next colony is gonna be blackjack at 50 grand fuck you
stand I'm not good for it get the fuck out of here you know you're talking to
how's your luck been mr. green mine's been awful can I hang out with you for
a while hey I remember you I know your face maybe you'll come back with today I
learned you some stuff let me show you how it's done I'd say you get it done
stand oh mr. green a push mr. green quick question do you feel anything
you know not really $50,000 a hand I mean hope some of your luck rubbed off
on me see you later yeah whatever get out of here oh it is bumpy everything's
fine everything's good to go one more $50,000 hand and I'll be out of here
blackjack that's how we win that freak out that's how we get out of the fucking
table here where you got nothing but hey you startled me mr. green your luck did rub
off I won $15,000 and just shut up and give me my cut there we have 10 grand
you fucking idiot yeah I don't want to hear your story I uh let me show you
how it's done oh look at me hundred fucking thousand dollar
blackjack and what do you want to do you want to get a 20 here
oh
the greedy Grinner never has insurance
hey and just because I feel bad for you no oh I win two of these
shit I have to double this that's a winning hand that's a that's a winning hand give me a 10
oh Jesus Christ
oh
mr. green you can't just throw up on the table
yeah mr. green you can't take your shirt off just give me a second I'm just
throw them all over my shirt I got five of these in a backpack that one of my
associates has Steve yes mr. green give me another t-shirt oh my god oh thank
you Steve and by the way Steve I'm a good tipper here's two dollars Wow God I
caught it thanks mr. greens no problem by the way you're my favorite I'm your
favorite yep mr. green you okay yeah I think of my
arms I think I might have something exploded in there I felt that I could
feel it if I heard it mr. green do you want to hit hold on a second this would
be the third heart attack in the last probably three days oh hold on let it
run fast mr. green oh hold on I just need to grab my hand on the table he
hit no I'm just grabbing a table for God's sake oh mr. green oh I do it what
was it a four okay it looks like it worked out all right oh hold on a second
I gotta stand up I gotta stand up you'd like to stand no I don't want mr.
green you've won Wow $200,000 Steve Steve I hate you yes mr. green can you
help can you clean that part up over there let's see what I do it all the
lunch came on already mr. green $400,000 bet please mr. green do I I would like
to do a strange I'm like but I'm sorry to say I can't my home I've fallen mr.
green you all right it's green I mean that counts as a hit mr. green he said
mr. green mr. green mr. green get up what what what is it what we'd like to
do would you like to stay at 18 yes okay mr. green is staying that's a push
what how much did I bet now that was a $400,000 bet oh do it again okay mr.
green's about $400,000 13 Dave what do you think I should do Steve come here
yes mr. green what do I do what would you do by the way your life is on the
line here mr. green this is a really tough to hand to have I would probably
say that I mean 13 versus potential 13 it's very very tricky I would probably
stay on this hand it's very hard to I'm not sure it's up to anybody's
discretion I would tell you to stand Eve I trust you Steve yes mr. green that
all you have on you what do you mean all I have on me is that all of the
equipment you have just your shirt you could be a bag in it yes hit the fucking
road well am I being am I being fired you're being fired I'm blackjack right
at the fucking I had before Steve Dave I'm just kidding come on back Steve it
was a joke Steve you're not fired I got fucking 10 million in the bank are you
kidding me get back over here oh my god hopefully shit I thought I was fired no
of course not what do you think I am a fucking psycho Steve sit over here you're
good luck what would you do here Steve oh I'm just fucking ready I'm gonna
fucking stay I can't split cuz I don't have any more money Steve do you have
any gas in your car fuck oh that was nightmarish damn you had four hundred
thousand dollars welcome to Las Vegas now now look the rest I can't play this
this is gonna be nothing now nothing will ever match the rush that we just
had I'm gonna be doing hundred dollar bets I was doing four hundred thousand
dollar hands I can't go back to doing fifty dollar bets well that was gonna be
the end anyway yeah that we can wrap it up here that was fun end of the stream
voice yeah yeah yeah I will try one more attempt at only max bet mr. Steve go to
the yeah yeah I want to do that I want to go to the to the the conceit did like
the shady casino me and Maria Steve inherited Mr. Green's life savings
after he died and it's a thousand dollars 1k inheritance student has become
the master all right let's go to the hideaway this place looks pretty run
down are you sure you want to go here I'm sure let's lose our money here and
then I'll call it okay yes okay yes okay yes okay yes
monkey ass what is it multiple links turbo for fuck's sake multiple links
there is this mr. green here here's a sketch of mr. green just wet he's just
a sludge why is there a gas pedal there's another one this one too that's
fucking funny all right so what are the what are the table minimums here but
damn uh let's do slots what is it 50 cents dollar slots just play you know
just hit her five dollars is good let's go you I need a bigger rush yeah that's
what I'm saying you can't I can't do 100 200 300 thousand dollar bet oh I did it
I won $15 no it's not enough it's not enough what the fuck just happened it's
gonna be a huge jackpot it's not enough hundred and ten dollars that's what a
huge that's like what that's like 25x that's a huge extreme jackpot it's not
enough no I'm going I'm leaving it's not enough active roulette dude if I if I
get another like $50,000 I'm doing $50,000 out of one number the max wave
in it and I what's the what's the bets here and I do like one dollar on every
number and I do that imagine somebody doing this shit like sir sir what are
you doing I'm trying to make a picture why oh my name this would be so
obnoxious this is obnoxious oh oh something's going on with the chips oh
Steve Steve stop all right spin it spin it roll it all right roll it yes I'm
done I don't even know what the numbers are all right just on every single solid
number I want to get a win big hit stop doing that oh I can't look at it I can't
look at it that's hurt by it hurts my fucking head this is what the red and
black space is before I know I'm just fucking psycho okay let's leave this
place going to the 2020 I'm gonna put a thousand dollars I'm just gonna bet
here's what's gonna happen I'm gonna max out spend money that's gonna be a
thousand dollars a hand in blackjack and maybe somebody will come by and give
me three five thousand dollars and then I'm gonna I can't believe I had four
hundred thousand dollars damn it by Lactory Lich gave fifty dollars five
thousand bits my by Lactory they say so far I'm really enjoying the CBD on
drugs arc of German I hate deal it 18 he doesn't have a tent under there let's
get kicked off the table could have saved the game $66 nice job Steve I told
you that's enough for up that's enough for at least four or five like monster
meals from Taco Bell that's like 50 that's like 25 cheese ago D to crunches
well I'll just sit in the hotel room and speak five or six each all right that's
it we're gonna hang out for a little bit and do the bits and everything but that
was the sort of the length I thought it would be about four hours sad end though
I will see you guys on let's see on Monday see you guys on Monday we have a
very very interesting week coming up Monday and obviously the later on the
week 14th 15th and 16th they're gonna be very interesting does this coming
weekend after this weekend here next weekend we have easy bake oven and green
screen DLC immunity content night will also be on the 14th so we're gonna do
probably Monday probably Monday let's I don't know we'll see Monday Tuesday and
then Thursday Friday Saturday or Monday and then Thursday Friday Saturday we'll
see it's gonna be an interesting end of the week I will see you guys on Monday
thanks for joining me for the week carry yourselves I'll see you guys on
Monday oh my god he just confirmed Rue crew on I didn't say that I do appreciate
enthusiasm Rue crew thanks for hanging out he's played Doki Doki on July 30th I
don't think I'm gonna do that I can't even give you a July 30th fake promise
there let us rewind the clock heavy is spy thanks to the 300 bits three dollars
thank you heaviest by no message Wembley TTV thanks to 250 mr. green is a real
betting website Europe and it was founded in 2007 sad to say someone stole
your idea well his name is what was Greg Green that's mr. Greg Green it's all
right excuse me mr. Greg greens he changed his name mr. Greg greens
yesterday's bits yeah I know I will these we're gonna go through these really
quickly because there's only a there's not a whole lot so we'll be able to get
through these easy but mr. green is mr. Greg Mr. Greg green eg golden boy
thanks for the $15 derma you inspire me so I wanted to give back for all the joy
you've brought me thanks for the 15 bucks it's a lot of money just to give
somebody thank you in flux thanks for the $5 derma a long time watcher first
time donor a big admirer of your work ever heard of the GameCube game amazing
island it's a pretty brainless minigame collection but the main feature of it is
that you get to draw your own monster and you use that to compete even if you
don't play it on stream I think you'd be right up your alley and it didn't even
have legs he just slides around but thank you appreciate it and I'll check
it out what's what's it called amazing island feel like I passed by that one at
one point don't know when why remember that name is familiar it's familiar a
bean drop thanks for five dollars my friend's birthday is coming up who's a
fan and I'm making him a custom birthday card that plays the rats birthday song
is there any chance to get you to say his name Nick like you say in the Michael
rat song so I can edit it instead Nick Nicholas happy birthday to Nick happy
birthday have a great one drysies the great thanks for the five dollars thanks
for reminding me how annoying my customers are Jeremy casino security
guard here I'm sorry sorry you Nick I did it without sound I got it what yeah
sorry to remind you of the bullshit hey will God thanks it's free a hundred bits
greeting streamer why did you push the streams so that is European peons can't
enjoy them in the evening leave mr. Funko pop collector please I have to
give you a hard truth here is a hard truth for all these people that are in
Europe I know you don't want to hear this I live I streaming between 2 and 4 p.m.
my time is is my time and we live across the world from each other I live across
the world from you this is the time that I'm active and I'm awake and I'm the
most alert and ready to go is around somewhere in their afternoon Pacific
time that's just the way it is that's the way it always will be is the way it's
always gonna be we live across the world from each other he lives in an
NA society yes just say it say you hate us no why do you want to say it what
are you talking about I live in America and I stream on American time we're
going to say just move to the EU I'm not I don't want to move to the EU just say
that you hate them I'm not gonna say that I hate anybody back up you're
getting too close to mr. green well what am I ten hours behind like that eight
to ten hours behind you're and it's a long time that's like that's a huge
amount of time it's not like it's not like I'm a few hours behind you I'm like
a whole day behind you it's eight hours you're asleep for fucking eight or nine
hours yeah at eight hours is a day that's it that's a day they move on to
the night time you sleep you wake up you're not alert for those extra six to
eight hours you're sleeping a long story short I can't I've never been
somebody that can have a bunch of energy in the morning that's when I
would have to stream for me to I would have to stream around 10 or 11 o'clock
in the morning to be able to have it be like what 8 p.m. 7 p.m. EU time I'm not
at high energy I'm not at high it's not gonna happen I've never had in my whole
life this is the time it's gonna be this time it always will be that's pretty
much it sometimes I'll stream before then because like maybe I'm just I
happen to want to do it sometimes I do it but it's not the norm it's not
supposed to be that's not normal it's not normal what do you mean 11 in the
morning omega la lazy wait so started starting at 4 versus starting at 11 is
lazy it's just a different time than the day some people are morning people some
people the graveyard shift people I'm one of those people I'm at my absolute
most active between like 3 p.m. and like 2 a.m. some people are incredibly active
in the morning and that's just the type of personality type of person that they
are we're all different people why don't you start when I want you to I think
you pretty much nailed it on the head there this is fucking good this is
really good mr. greens but there's not enough sludge coming off it's pretty
good it's pretty good did you do this in one fucking sitting here in like the
last three hours holy shit that's awesome but I know that was a little
long-winded but I do get asked all the time
German pull you streams back German start at 12 German start at 10 yeah I'm
gonna stream when I want to stream that's the way it is that's the way it's
always gonna be sorry that we live across the world from each other I can't
this I don't have a time thing they make us closer if I could if I could press a
button there I'd be at the 4 o'clock everywhere at the same time baby can't
do that though this is a flat earth yeah maybe if the if the earth was no
that wouldn't make any sense it would still work no wait what would that work
flat earth anyways thank you neuro wolf for the five dollars mr. Jeremy do you
remember me you do thanks for being so nice here's five smackaroos hey thanks I
appreciate that extra five dollars person that I remember does dis thanks
to the five dollars remember me mr. greens yeah of course I do you gave me
gnarly thanks to the 250 it's a shame German lost so much money on gambling
that he couldn't afford to hire the real bugleberry and had to get a text-to-speech
synthesizer that sounded like him German Pluto maybe these bits will help you get
back on your feet I'll be good there's a real person thank you to not for the five
dollars mr. green do you feel anything my sides that's the best character I'm
glad you think that these I don't think we'll ever see him again I think that's
the one and only time that mr. greens will ever show up ever I guess he has no
more money hey and on tins thanks for the five dollars Reaper thanks for the
250 remember when it comes to blackjack 17 is the magic number always hit if
below 17 and stay when above it it's not true the dealer is showing a four or five
or six and you have 12 or higher the correct play if you're playing basic
strategy is to do nothing especially versus five and a six that that is actual
basic strategy it's a term that's been used to bring the most returns over the
over that more than a dozen hands in blackjack this guy just lost a shit this
guy lost a shitload of money why would you believe him I didn't it was mr.
green that's not me it wasn't me it was is mr. Hyde I am the casino Steve
Steve Steve I turn myself into a casino Steve I look Steve of a casino somebody
that's fucking funny you guys are fucking funny I love it control X thanks to the
250 I want Jerma hearts in chat now I'm handing just be thanks for the five
dollars Jerma thank you so much for being a part of our Xbox gamer coalition
for national Xbox day if you tell us three reasons why you're so proud to be
an Xbox gamer and none of this is real this is fake this is a joke this is a
bit I'm not on that coalition but I'll tell you anyways hey they they're very
good at stopping doors after you open them if you don't want the door to close
hard behind you what else hey somebody breaks into your house and they're
brandishing a weapon you'd be used as a defense mechanism very heavy third one
game pass I get to stay on the coalition let's do a 360 and roll walk away thanks
for the five dollars Microsoft is a good company though that they're gonna come
back real strong I think that this next console a generation I think so hey post
thanks for five dollars Jeremy I also recently started doing THC and CBD vapor
pen for my panic attacks talked about it last week at the recommendation of my
doctor it's so much more effective than taking a benzodiazepine orally it takes
30 minutes to actually take effect when the panic is already over also I'm not
substituting your e-clown shenanigans for professional help like you said last
time I donated fucking egomaniac all right yeah I have been doing small doses
of CBD THC combined three milligrams taking it because there's been studies
and data at THC and CBD have an effect potentially on kind of shutting up the
nerve response if you have potential nerve damage or nerve pain so giving it
a try to see if it kind of calms it down see what happens small dose not very
what's the term it's not very psychoactive just put it that way with
like a one to three milligram dose smoke wise ganja he's fucking stoned let's
click it already will you guys relax oh wow yeah there he is this is what you
guys have been spamming me the last three gosh darn minutes it's pretty good
actually all right we are at the end we have two more three more from today
stream beyond thanks for the five dollars germa I want to say thanks for
the streams and also when I posted a juke the other day you called it a pleb
juke my reputation has never recovered and my girlfriend won't return my calls
I needed to repeal this statement at once please a four-year-long relationship
gone because I forgot to renew my sub if you don't what I'm forced to do
Bella Lugosi is this a Bella Lugosi is died thing oh anyways no the it still
stands my pleb juke but I don't know what that means what is a pleb Jupiter
is that just a regular Jupiter just just connected with all sides what's a pleb
juke what is it does it show it to me it's just a regular one no like weird
crazy other stuff in the middle oh it's it's somebody doing it that's not subbed
okay there it is I see it that's a pleb juke okay I get it and now I know my
terms for my own community anyways thank you and yeah fine it's been repealed hey
mr. jazz oh thanks for the five dollars your mom was more interested I was more
invested in mr. green and Steve than I was in Resident Evil 3 also did you not
realize that bugleberry was a robot the whole time no I had no idea so you just
said hey Mikasa thanks for the three bucks I'm mr. German I've been trying to
reach you concerning your vehicles extended warranty you should have
received a notice in the mail about your cars extended warranty eligibility so
you're not gotten we haven't gotten a response I'm gonna give you final
courtesy call before we close out your file press 2 to be removed in place on a
do-not-call list to speak to someone about possibly extending and reinstating
your vehicles warranty press 1 for warranty specialist I still connected
pressed 1 hey post thanks for the 500 bits baked streamer oh mega low good hey
ex whimsical moose thanks for 250 germ I love this train wreck I was wondering
when the next channel points thing will happen also our IP Bella Lugosi the
next channel points thing that's a good question we might have that we might
talk about something like that soon we'll see we'll see but we're gonna move
on to yesterday and I'm gonna go through these bang bang bang bang bang
bang bang and then we'll catch the ones that came in now yeah this is from
yesterday you ready for the lightning round
Hamrick five dollars thanks a lot for real dough 250 us Delgado president evil
three I don't know what that is I don't know what that is
Kier thank you car for the five dollars I hope this works the first time I've
ever donated to twitch German please try to enjoy this game it's way better
than people say I did think it was good I did give it a 74 though it's the amount
of save files that were available clammy Bob thanks for the $10 read all the
lore and make up voices for the dialogue nah somebody else will do it Adrian
thanks for the three bucks agent dark booty thanks for the $50 and I
not catch these how don't listen to the haters this game is as this game is fun
just not as good as Resident Evil 2 I think I caught these there was a fart
there I didn't know there was not I would I was I one of the haters at the
end of the last night stream 74 is not a hater like 62 is a hater I think like
58 is a hater 74 is now I'm not a hater silence serenity thanks for 250
grandma love you big fellow why don't you have a channel points icon it
shouldn't it be like bald coin and points will come back soon agent dark
booty thanks for the $5 Jill sandwich princess kitty thanks for $15 hello e
clown will you please say hello to wolf song it's her birthday and she thinks
you're neat a wolf song happy birthday fucking yesterday I've had a great one
hope you had plenty of fucking cake in them and toys and stuff I birthday
yesterday missed it I missed it happy birthday yesterday elated all right
that's what they say clammy Bob thanks for the $5 ignore earlier bit messages
forget it I forgot it wouldn't be read until post stream lol and you were
actually correct but wrong at the same time because this actually ended up
being now we had $15 from tag that guy tag thanks a lot tag for $15 hello again
germ stuttering chat was seeing at the start of the stream is due to some new
dumb Windows settings and newer games games use a hundred percent of your GPU
leaving none for OBS the game will look fine to you it will lose frames and OBS
no matter what encoding process you use if it happens limit the frame rate of
the game or lower its video settings I've had this problem I have an RTX 2080
it's really silly I so I had it right I put my I capped it at 60 right I kept it
on there right with I capped it right that is a fucking silly RTX 2080 is it
good I should I get one things a beast isn't it I get a 2080 the hell are they
cheap they've been up like a year right that means that like they drop by like
80% in value after like three days I'm what is it how much is worth just wait
for next-gen okay aren't graphics cards like used cars or so you drive off the
lot it drops like 20% but thanks the tip tag good to hear from you good to see
you thanks $15 hey Mick Muscles thanks for 10 bucks German it's me and my
girlfriends one year and I can't spend it with her because you know what thanks
for making quarantine a lot more fun sorry to hear that but I'm more than
happy to hang out everybody here we're all dealing with this shit also that we
all have to fucking just ride out and see what happens and hope it goes away
and hope they can be medicine and hope they can be shit they can be taken care
of and people go back to work and can be brought back to work I mean you see the
numbers it's fucking it's terrible I really hope we can get back to some kind
of normalcy if you're affected by it I'm really sorry to hear that I really am
because that's fucked up because you didn't do anything wrong that's the
worst thing about all this is if you if you're dropped from a company because of
this that's just that's just fucking horrible because you didn't do anything
wrong thank you an anonymous cheerer gave ten dollars no message just ten
bucks thank you whoever you are mr. fish pudding gave 300 bits German it's my
brother's birthday a lot of birthdays you guys have a ton of birthdays your
brother's birthday on Friday I think he's already expecting me to play the
birthday rat song for him I was wondering if you could say his name so I
could edit it in no I think wait hold on his name is Griffin same person I want
to edit it's like hold on his name thanks and thank you for all you do this
is pretty good this is weird the other person was Nick compare the messages
hold on that's like very weirdly it's like worded right and a lot of birthdays
is this if it's the same person if they're different hold on where is it
where's this message why is it gone oh here we go
it's my brother's birthday on Friday my friend's birthday is coming up who's a
fan I'm making him a custom birthday card it's basically the last birthday but
I was wondering can you say his name so I can edit it in please raspberry the
song is there since like I get you say his name like you Michael and song so I
can edit it in thank you no that this is right after this this is interesting
it's crazy well Griffin happy birthday this is two different people then you
guys got really you guys got the same great idea happy birthday to Griffin
Peter Griffin somebody said that and I've read it all right thank you that's
mr. fish pudding and then bean dupe thank you really appreciate three bucks
hey graven brace thanks to 250 German looks like Jill Valentine well drunk
Scotsman thanks for the $14 take these in hopes that the zombies don't get you
gamer what happens when money is useless and the zombies come after us I'm gonna
what am I gonna do with paper start fire with that shit thanks for the 14 bucks
dragon pixies thanks to three dollars German looks like he electrics from the
Incredibles 2 which I'm trying to get this image on the screen Google images
sucks it really is the worst if you want to try to like pull a photo from Google
images good luck you get like redirected five times I just want to get the image
even me to work I know I want to show this on stream because it's fucking
crazy this actually looks very much like me oh yeah I just tried I had to save it
like three times yeah that's there I can see it thanks for the thanks for the
three dollars dragon pixies hey bop beep thanks for 250 sending my oh wait this
is the okay this is the guy it was a guy that okay alright they say sending
sending my suicide note to germa only for him to be on CBD and skip the lore
and speed read it it's talking about in Resident Evil 3 talk about resident for
the guy that I just I didn't read this note that's what he was okay all right
for a second I was like what the fuck is this the guy that was sitting on the
ground and I didn't I didn't read it okay yeah I get it I got you you can't
be freaking me out yeah I got freaked out for a second I was like what ha what's
going on what did I have what had it what did I do what did it happen thanks
to the 250 though hey illu SSB thanks for the thousand bits your my friend of
mine showed me your 700,000 games video last year and I've been a big fan ever
thank you for making me laugh and I hope you're doing well in these tough times
thank you hey I don't know if you don't know did a 700,000 game stream part 2
edition I did that last year some things that may not have shown up in that video
showed up on that live stream thanks for the thousand bits don't promo yourself
it's my it's my own damn stream what do you mean if I served you food that I
cooked what am I wait what do you say huh here's here's a steak I made it's
probably disgusting don't eat it you know I my steaks are terrible all my
food is bad eat up no you're gonna be like oh look I got the best rub on it
you're gonna love it cook perfectly to your loving to you how you like it how
would I do that no steak ems call me false thanks for five dollars actual
grenade throwing streamer I do throw grenades in these games and I do very
well rock writing thanks for five dollars
your hair is looking very picture of Dorian Gray esque unpack that as you
wish I trying to and while we're on the topic of Victorian things it's probably
time you pay a little respect to your ancestors I don't understand that's not
me okay this is like an old an old timey clown or something what is it is your
real ancestor it's you it's him the one-man band one-man clown they're all
what hey shower beer thanks for three dollars German you should host the
tonight show fog Jim hey zero giblets thanks for the five dollars hi German
thank you for all you do I hope you and Kim are staying well remember you once
said that the only thing that prevents blood-borne from being a perfect ten was
the game ran at 30 FPS it's a fair point check it out though someone patched the
game to run at 60 it's very nice to watch I actually did see this I did see
this if there is a PS 5 here we go if there is a PS 5 sort of remastering of
blood-borne and they pump it up to 60 tweak a little bit of things maybe I'm
not asking for it I'm just I am I'm asking for it maybe maybe like another
maybe like a DLC it's all that's asking a lot but if there was like a PS 5 like
re like classic edition of re just paint it over and bring it over to like PS 5
or even PC add a little bit of content to make a couple items it would be a
tenth it will do that on July 30th maybe remember tell the banana with the olive
oil story one time I dipped a banana in olive oil thinking it was gonna taste
good and it was just gross but it was gonna add like some saltiness to the
sweetness and it was just didn't work out and I bleh I spit it out and it was
gross I spit it into the trash yuck hey goo berry juice thanks for 250
good and tug Dharma I was just wondering why do you wear wooden wigs sad face
whatever a job to bone thanks for 250 what do I do if I forget my clothes in
the washer for a week and a half easy what you do is you just close the lid
what detergent in and wash him again and then change him over hey snoozing
copter thanks for the 250 hey it's me snoozing copter by now you probably
know me better by the guy that won't stop talking about God hand that's yep
I will now though really and long enough okay but I have one last request could
you play it on August 10th that's my birthday we now return to our usual
programming stay tuned I'm playing it on July 30th I already said that July 30th
that's what is happening fabled July it's happening on July 30th don't worry
you'll see it sooner than your birthday in early birthday present see key of the
dead thanks with a thousand bits and no message just thousand bits and some
emotes with a grave thing with a month zombie coming out of the grave thanks
for the thousand dollars it's not how much that is thanks for the thousand
thanks for ten dollars that's a nonchalantly saying thanks for the
thousand dollars thanks for the ten dollars it's ten dollars is still a
really good amount of money to give anybody but reading it like thanks for
thousand dollars fuck me white Fox thanks for the 300 bits
Dermot would you please play a resistance fall of man sometimes it was
a launch title for the PlayStation 3 about an alternate history of World War
2 the series kind of died out when the third game sucked one or two are amazing
don't listen to the two haters they're both great I actually remember that game
I do remember it I remember it was the big selling point was they look at how
many enemies we can put on the screen right and that a big thing about it it
was we can handle like 50 enemies on screen at the same time it was a big
deal that was that's cool the online was terrible yeah I forget that yes three
and Xbox three sick they had a online was huge and on the 316 ps3 sometimes I
forget it existed you know it doesn't feel like Wi-Fi like even the Wii right
oh the Wii yeah we have like Wi-Fi built into it like holy shit it's been that
long since that technologies existed which is not even that long if you think
about it's been like 15 years but the Wii had a Wii had a fucking Wi-Fi chip
in it it's crazy to think about that why hey the dash you thanks for the nine
dollars and 27 cents what's up j-man today's my last day of college and I
want to say I couldn't have done it without you I don't believe that I don't
believe that at all I think I think you had it in you the whole time I had
nothing to do with it it was you man I streams it made me laugh and cheer me up
when nothing else could I'm about to graduate with a 4.0 thank you in the
bottom of my heart well thank you and good job you doing that I didn't do it
you did it I had nothing to do with it you did it give yourself some credit nice
work that's fucking huge that's huge thanks for the nine dollars and 27 cents
rave embrace thanks for 250 cut him into germa sized pieces oh yeah I did say
that yeah well that was because that's the way you get rid of nemesis just
have to I can't say it again because I think we're out of context now and
people are gonna fucking just flip it and only a serial killer like a psycho
or something you know what I said yesterday well just watch the entire
eight-hour stream and you'll find it eventually you have time nothing who
cares hey amber thanks for the five dollars germa I've never been able to
tell you but you've been such an important person in my life you made me
smile and laugh when I had no joy in life anymore
you've helped me out helped me have a lot of dark times only now the courage
and possibility to say this and I had to tell you you saved my life more than
once thanks for being who you are and making my life a brighter place where
there's hope thank you on the bottom of my heart if I have that kind of effect
on somebody it's it's sometimes it's hard to respond be honest because I can't
even believe it like I can't even it's hard for me to even give you anything
an answer or even a comment is it this this shit floors me I can't believe that
people think this and say this it's unbelievable to me all I can say is
thanks for watching and I really hope that you take the steps necessary to take
care of yourself and move forward thank you so much for the insanely kind message
slap yourself see if you're dreaming no thank you they carry self a flug a boy
thanks for the five dollars Jeremy long time no don't know deep fakes are you of
you are honestly starting to scare me maybe I'm a boomer too also since I'm
basically smack dab in the center of New York City quarantine has been my 24-7 so
I started playing Diablo I've been sucked in save me why would I want to
save you from the greatest thing on earth why would I want to rescue you in
your utmost perfect place that you're in stay in Diablo stayed in it stay in hell
you want to be there it's awesome you're gonna love it I'm so glad you're in
hell so glad you're here with me in hell go to hell it's a great game but thanks
to the five dolls have fun with it it's a fucking great franchise just stop at
three just play three play three like you would play an iPad game just pretend
three was an iPad game it was like oh it's the threat it's the iPad version
don't know I mean like play it's like fun but it's like iPad fun it could be
completely honest with everybody here Diablo 3 is iPad game fun it's not
Diablo 2 fun it's still fun that's not fun no iPad games are fun they're just a
different kind of fun a s Haluco thanks for the 250 got a head out early early
morning tomorrow thanks for the laughs and the Lego here people happy thank
you we did go late last night it's a huge insult is it that's not meant to be
I guess maybe it is that's not I'm just saying it's like it's not that major
insult yeah that's a really name one fun iPad game there are a ton there are
there actually are a lot there's a lot there's a lot sorcery was on the iPad
okay excuse me at the brakes for a second
sorcery was not on Steam sorcery was an iOS exclusive experience for the first
three or four years it was out that's a port to PC and that's one of the
greatest games ever so I think they get some points to the iPad side there hello
neighbor tooth surgery we were gonna do another iPad night where I just download
a bunch of junk and it freaks me the fuck out sometimes when I'm looking at
iPad games that is crazy cuz yeah there's just is these games that with
people with their mouths open it's just like rotten teeth and like holes in
their teeth and shit it's like every single cartoon character every single
Marvel character every single thing every they all have these like teeth
rotten teeth games but why that why why like teeth why like teeth surgery I see
it everywhere every time I'm like I'm looking for like a cool I'm gonna do a
crazy iPad night teeth surgery surgery teeth surgery to the mouth dentist
dentist dentist dentist dentist and rotten teeth teeth teeth like green
teeth green teeth teeth teeth teeth because it's blood and surgery is that
I I'm not gonna I don't I'm not gonna play those games on stream a grave
embrace thanks for 250 do you eat your milk with or without the skin I don't
drink milk it upsets my stomach at this point I drink almond milk I don't drink
any other milk I don't drink soy milk I don't drink oat milk I don't drink rice
milk I almond milk is the only dairy substitute that I take in my stomach I
have intestinal issues milk doesn't really sit well with me I can eat a
piece of cheese or two but I can't I don't I get I've been trying to get rid
of dairy forever SILAC thanks for the thousand bits just $10 no message just
a $10 bill I'll take it thank you P flavor thanks for the $5 this stream was
super good everything about it was great you suck and get the game chat was funny
the tuber faces I haven't laughed that hard in a while thanks to the $5 talking
about Resident Evil 3 thanks a lot and we have been caught up let's run the
credits while we chill for another few minutes there's another few bits have
come in on the credits change this over to here image Steve we've had addition
there's been an addition I'm gonna disgust everybody here there is there
has been a hair in my throat a hair just all the way in the back for 20 minutes
and I don't know what to do about it I don't know what to do about it I think I
swallowed it oh I hate that I hate that shit oh I hate
swallowing my hair it's just a hair in me now there's Steve Steve oh yes mr.
greens ah ah credits right right right right right right right right credits
credits credits credits credits roll credits roll them roll them roll them
roll and thanks for all the subs everybody all of you there's been a lot
even on a stream that's less than four plus hours long it's still a shit load
of people sub to this channel thanks for doing it thank you let us conclude the
bits we had three dollars from Jude minecraft by the way this is we've
bored down with yesterday we're back onto today the last five ten minutes or
so just got her at the end because my five bros been weird hope you're healing
okay I'm working on it too I believe you're speaking about is it fibromyalgia
it's one of those illnesses that is just it's a fucking mystery to everybody for
some reason it's just a thing that happens that's been one of the things
that some of the doctors have talked about people throw just random ideas
costochondritis fibromyalgia nerve damage intercostal neuralgia there's a lot of
random things that the thing I have could be I'm still just trying to RA
might have arthritis rheumatoid arthritis it's just seems like a never
ending game of musical chairs when it comes to this shit I'm really sorry to
hear about your fibromyalgia I hope you're doing good hope you're doing good
too thank you many clips for the $5 I'm a little late on the stream but I have a
question what was that stick figure game that you voice acted in a long time ago
I can't find it it feels like a fever dream I don't I think that might be a
dream I think that could that could be a dream
apotheon maybe the one with the Greek gods and everything it was apotheon
stick figure though yes that's the one yeah apotheon I was the horse lord all I
did was just make I got killed noises and I said what did I say I'm like yeah
how dare you across this bridge it's like I just die it's like a mini boss
yeah and maybe that's the one you're talking about maybe thanks the five
dolls hey hey sugar shanks thanks for the 250 hello again Jerm bombo back at
again with another game request if you liked Mario Galaxy in sunshine I
recommend a little game called a hat in time it's a cute 3d platformer that
think you make for a cozy stream you know I've had that game installed for
like three years but I just never did it yeah hypo worked on that game one of
the mods here I feel actually worked on that game so I mean I remember talking
to hypo a long time ago like oh shit yeah you were like worked on this it's
good right yeah it's good oh maybe I'll play it and then you know you know
hypo you got July 30th three years ago maybe I'll play it on July 30th we'll
see they also say I don't skip Pikmin 1 if you get around to that series I'm
going to I'm sorry I'm going to be flat I'm gonna play Pikmin 2 sorry I'm gonna
skip Pikmin 1 has been unanimously told to me that Pikmin 1 is the one to skip
Pikmin 2 is Pikmin 1 but just better I've been told that's gonna ask I'm
sorry I have to do it that's so wrong but I but it was like an 80% vote I have
to trust the people because I don't think I'd play more than one Pikmin game
I don't think I will I gotta tell you honesty I do I don't think I'm
gonna play more than one Pikmin game it's like four of them I have to pick
the one that I think people think is the best
Pikmin 2 is gonna be a crack cocaine stream maybe it will hey spooky future
thanks for the three dolls hey Jeremy it's my sister's birthday Friday I'm
making her a birthday card her name is Mona lot and you say her name so I can
edit it in happy birthday happy birthday happy birthday Mona thank you BS 88
five dollars thanks for your kind words drama I've been stood down from work
due to kovat they're working on videos in the downtime to keep me sane
encouragement like yours is appreciated yeah I mean tons of people just got
furloughed or laid off for nothing no they didn't do anything wrong it's not
like oh we have to get rid of you because of this because of that virus
fucking swept into the goddamn world and into the states I don't know where
you are and into Europe and to every Asia everywhere these these employees
didn't do anything wrong it's just really heartbreaking to fucking hear
about it I hope that a majority of if you're working right now or you're not
working I mean I really hope a majority of you go back to where you were before
or maybe if you don't want to go back maybe you'll have a different career
path that you can go forward with cuz that that sucks that just sucks and it
breaks my fucking heart to hear about it I wish you the best thank you omni cash
for the five dollars play the newer bubsy games I don't think so they one of
them try almost I threw up almost I threw up into my mother's bed after
playing bubsy 3d so don't want to do that again
phantom tech thanks for three dollars Germany the best man thanks for being
such an awesome and creative streamer your vids are the best keep up the good
work just an insanely nice encouraging thing to hear I'm gonna try I'll do my
best thank you Hanvo breaker thanks for the three to 250
dear Jeremiah when I said Xenoblade Chronicles 1 was the Chrono trigger of
our decade I didn't think it should be a stream game at all it should be
something that you enjoy on your own taking the time to soak in the world the
same goes for chat the game is great as long as you don't mind talking to all
the NPCs all of them they're interesting don't worry higher however is a great
stream game it's basically NBA Jam the choose your own adventure game also has
a mustached airbud that true higher is the NBA Jam of choose your own adventure
games I'm trying to break that apart I'm trying to figure out how that what that
means the NBA Jam it's basically NBA Jam the choose your own adventure game higher
is good but it makes no sense lol yes I don't lie in donations okay all
right I'll look it up higher EYRE yeah I'll check it out
Lapster thanks for five dollars believe it or not you actually managed to keep
me sane in some weird situations especially in the past few weeks I'm
planning on going to university part-time next year while working full
time as a developer you being here as a moral support is for real don't
underestimate your influence you e-clown yeah but I I also I also want you I want
people I want you to get better I want people to get better I want you to move
forward in your life I want you to take care of yourself and sometimes you know
when you hear stuff like oh Jerma you're the reason why you're the only reason
why I've been able to I I wish it wasn't just me I really want you to get better
and if that's the case then I don't know that's not this exact comment but I want
you guys to take care of yourselves and I think it would be selfish of me to sit
here and be like yep yep it's me it's me yep stay only watch me I feel like
that's selfish for me to ever have that cross my mind so I really really
implore anybody that is feeling bad or terrible and this dream is an outlet for
them to be a part of I really hope you take the necessary steps to try to move
forward and get better because I don't want to be I don't want to be that if
that makes any sense because I feel like that's like I said I feel like that's
selfish for me to think like that and not say something about it but thank you
so much I really hope you move forward whatever those situations are whatever
the last few weeks have done I really hope you got through it good luck at
University thanks for the five dollars hey raindrop thanks of 250 Jeremy wanted
to let you know that mashing buttons fast is seriously called jacking just so
you know you're like a self-proclaimed number one jacker if you don't want to
say that out loud that's cool just know that you fucking rock thanks for
everything been watching since 2014 when I searched TF2 diaper on YouTube
and found stirs tell it diaper teleporter video question why did you
type in TF2 diaper into a search what were you what were you trying to gain
from TF2 diaper as a Google search and even more awful what a video that I'm a
part of comes up still one of stars videos comes up TF2 diaper German 985
and stir the two diaper wearing TF2 players oh no I don't know the brand and
what do we do that's fucking that's fucking funny thanks to the 250 boy key
thanks for five dollars hey guys turn up to selling at 439 one airhead bar per
entry also mr. green you're banned for trying to sell one of the nooklings to
pay off your loan shark Omni cash thanks for five dollars do a
staring contest stream I would know I would sit there for five minutes and
be like I'm done I would have to move Omni cash again thanks for the five
dollars do a yodeling stream I could do it not now it's been too long
remind me to do yodels I could probably do it I could probably actually do it if
I if you catch me on like an hour one of the stream I guarantee you I could be
able to yodel really well fuck I just punched you you all right all right I'm
sorry my me hey Ike turtle thanks to 250 when is the fortnight stream we can play
duos and get the dub I thought I'll never play I'm not gonna play for life
it's not gonna happen dinosaurs Rex thanks for 250 I found your IMDB links
the German 985 T's TV series and Jeremy had that's not even you gotta use my
real name Jeremy Albertson check out the filmography on the second one is this
actor 20 credits Ant-Man and the Wasp the Slim Jim guy uncredited love live
sunshine as shiitake stardew Valley as grandpa's bed minecraft story mode as
mr. sneak man you guys understand like this is just absolute just gibberish
Jeremy Harrington is an actor and known for rat movie mystery with the Mayan
treasure fateful findings and too many cooks it's all just fake I clicked on
biography height five four and a half good now you understand why IMDB is no
reason to oh my god it says Jim Carrey is gonna be the next Iron Man in 2024
they're filming Iron Man 5 no no that's not happening but it says there no it's
not I'm telling you that's not happening oh that appreciate it thanks for the
thanks for editing giving me fake shit on making my life hey I appreciate the
fake life you've given me appreciate that thank you hey Joe Joe 360 thanks
for a thousand bits hopefully this works it's my first time to try donating but a
sub on the YouTube channel both the dead one and the second one for a couple of
years but with being stuck inside all I forget I go actually try to watch a
stream but I stream was definitely a favorite and I probably owe you more
there's a college kid it's easier said than done thanks for helping me and
everyone else through these times now you never don't ever have don't give me
any money ten dollars is that's that's you paid for a subscription to a ton of
these fucking places they have tons of shit and tons of value I appreciate I
really appreciate people give me money tend to want to tell it fifty dollars
thousand dollars five hundred dollars ten dollars one dollar two dollars five
dollars five five five but I really hope that you're doing that because you feel
like doing that and you want to do that you don't have to ever I would actually
implore a lot of you that don't have a lot of money to not and to save it and
take care of yourself first absolutely I sound like a broken record when I say
this but I really I hit it I hammer it because I want to make sure it's real
clear they carry self save your money you don't got to give it to me thank you
so much for the ten bucks finally the end here to the end the actual end of
the stream the German subscription takes precedence over everything if you feel
like that sure but you don't have to do that if you have to choose between give
German nine eight five ten dollars and buy ten dollars worth of cheesy go to
the crunches I hope you make the right choice I'd hope you make the right
choice there a post thanks for five dollars I'm going to keep bugging you to
check out receiver two until you do receiver two is this VR yeah this is a
VR game it's not this is on the list no it's not it's not in this this way this
isn't VR what is this what game did I what game do I have that's this game
it's not VR this actually looks pretty fucking good I thought don't I own this
or something there's a VR game that looks exactly like this all right put it
on the list we'll play this soon that's pretty cool all right yeah I will see
you guys we have one more we have slug brain thanks for three bucks oops too
late sent you money thank you thank you thank you thank you thank you thank you
thank you all of you have a great weekend I will see you guys back on
Monday I have actually no idea what we're gonna do on Monday I plan on
figuring that out on Sunday night we'll see take care have a great weekend see
you Monday