Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait. What the fuck is this? I have predict- people can predict stuff?
What is this? What- I didn't- when did this get activated? Did this just get activated like a
minute ago? I didn't even know I had this. What? Don't spend all your channel points on coin tosses.
When did this come through? 1.8 million. Who- you guys doing millions of dollars?
You've been betting for an hour. Wait, stop. Hold on. Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait.
I- I- I don't- but I don't- the thing is I don't understand. How much are you gonna lose on a coin
toss? I don't know. I- I- I turned the stream on. I pressed start streaming and I saw that.
1.8 versus 2.3. Well, what the fuck is it gonna be? I- hold on. I go to my details. Introducing
channel points. Watch Terma 985. Wait a minute. I gotta go in my settings for a second. Holy shit.
You guys saying tails? I got- it's just gonna be coin tosses all day.
Prediction results is heads. Oh, but you guys- half you guys lost like two million dollars.
Holy shit. Hold on a minute. I- wait, give me a second while I figure this out.
What? Panel points. Hold on. Manage rewards. Smart costs for- no. Where is it?
Community challenges. Where's predictions? How do I do this? 4.1 million goes to sticky brick.
Wait, what? Why did one person win? Why- is this like Mario Party? Did he get it first? Did he come
in first place and when you come in fourth place or over you get like two coins? I don't understand.
All right, I don't even know how to turn this on or off. It's just gonna- it's just gonna have
to be like this, I think, for a while. Turn it off. I don't even know how to turn it on.
Okay, community challenges. Default rewards. Keep it on. Hold on. Wait, wait, wait. How to play.
Details. Point toss. Predictions. Manage rewards. Here we go. Okay, enable channel points.
I don't- there's no way to do anything. I can't- I don't think I can even turn it off. Manage
rewards and challenges. Customize points. Enable channel points. I don't have like a predictions
tab. Custom rewards. Default rewards. Community challenge. I can't even turn this off. Okay,
anyways. Hi guys, how you doing? It's tails and heads forever. That's the- welcome to the stream.
I lost 120k thousand channel- don't stop gambling until I- don't use this until I get something in
here. I want to- this is the oh shit game. This is oh shit game 2. Dermasucks just gave 20 community
subs. This took me way off guard. I was not prepared for this. Is there a place I can change this
stuff? I don't think I can. What about if I go here? Review recent raids. No, what? I can like
see who raided me? I didn't know you could do that. It's slash predictions. Slash predictions.
Flash predictions. Unrecognized command. That didn't do anything.
Why do people keep looking at so many subs right now? That was 20 community subs from
Dermasucks and then 10 from Zurkda. Right in the browser. Oh, hold on. Good call. Sorry,
this is throwing off the whole beginning of the stream, but like I- I did not even know I had this
until- I didn't even know what it was. I'm looking at heads and tails. I'm like,
what the fuck are they doing? Okay, let me see if I can do it in the browser.
It's brand new. Yeah. How do I- I don't have a pro- prediction result is heads.
Wait, hold on. What the fuck, dude? I didn't even- don't lose all your money already.
Once- open a setup menu to create and manage predictions. Thank you. All right, let's go.
Okay. Manage predictions. Coin toss. Okay, start a prediction. Oh shit. All right, here we go.
Boys and girls, here we go. Um, how about this one? Possible outcome. I- I wish I knew I had this.
This is- uh, all right. This is gonna take me a little while. I have to set some stuff up for
this. Who wins? Derma Mars or Derma Merc? It's five minute period. What do you mean who wins?
Who wins? Okay, I'm gonna do who wins. Derma Mars or Derma Merc. Start prediction.
You or a mod will need to confirm the outcome within 24 hours at the end of the prediction
submissions. Once you start a prediction, you cannot change it except to delete it or close
submissions. If an outcome isn't selected or the prediction is deleted, all channel points will be
returned to participating viewers. Okay. Um, who wins? Derma Merc or Derma Mars? I don't even know
what that means. Who wins? But wins what? Do I have to decide who wins? Holy shit, Derma Mars is-
apparently you guys think Derma Mars is gonna win. But what are they- are they fighting? I have to
pick. What? No, I can't pick this. 6.4 million versus 2.1 million. Do I actually have this in
time to set this up for the rumble on New Year's Eve? Oh my god. All right, don't blow all your money.
Turn this off. Don't you- don't- nobody do this. All right, I'm gonna send channel points back. How
do I do that? It's too late? Oh, it's not too late. Cancel it. How do I cancel it? Cancel. Cancel. How
do I cancel this one? Did I do it? Did I cancel? How do I cancel it? You got rid of it?
Oh, all right. Good, good, good, good. Okay. So, wait, who is starting predictions then?
Is it mods? Are the mods just trying to get you guys to lose money? Wait, did everyone get scammed?
You should have got it back. Okay, so the mo- all right, so for a second I thought that you guys
were activating the coin toss. All right, you got it back. Good. All right, hold off on this.
We'll- I want to get some stuff done for this because now that I know I have it, I can't wait
to use it. I want- I've wanted a system like this for a long goddamn time and now it's here.
Just some normal guy, thanks to the five subs. Thanks to the five community subs.
What about all the coin tosses I lost? Yeah, sorry. You can't go into- you can't go into
a Vegas casino. Go play roulette for an hour. Lose a bunch of money and say, hey, I want a refund.
I didn't have- I want my money back. That wasn't fun. They don't give you a receipt
every time you make a bet at a Vegas table. Yes, I'll take five dollars on Blackjack, please. And
they're like- like print you out a big CVS receipt. Sir, you've busted. Oh, I didn't like
the outcome of that. I'd like to have Red Jack return that hand. Okay, yeah, hold on. Let's
process that. They have to take it to the back and somebody says a manager has to sign it and you
get a five dollar bill back. No, no, that would be impossible to play. All right, let's go. Today
we're gonna play Fear 2 and I've got some things to tell you. I've got a little thing to talk about.
Let's talk about some things. All right, listen. Listen up. So, I am going to- here we go. Take a
break, Andy. Here he comes. He's gonna say it. Going on break, Andy. Here he comes. Delay, Andy.
Delay stream, Andy. Okay, so we're gonna play Fear tonight. I'm gonna try to stream very early
tomorrow. I'm gonna try to get a good stream in tomorrow as well. I have a lot of things to take
care of. I've got a lot of things to do. I've got a lot of holiday stuff to do. I am going to be
disappearing for a week. I'm not gonna be around. Well, I'm gonna be working on stuff and doing
things and doing holiday things and- because the New Year's Eve stream is both a rumble and
the award show and I want to make sure I get that situated too. So, I'll be on break. Break, Andy.
Here he comes. Talking about going on like an eight or nine day break after tomorrow. So, with
that being said, I'm going to- tonight's gonna be a meaty one. Okay, we're gonna- I'm gonna be here
for- I'm not- this is not gonna be a four hour stream. I'll be- I can say- I'll be here for a
longer than that. I'll be here for- I'm not gonna be here for four hours. This is gonna be a little
longer. It's gonna be five hours. Fucking pug jam. You hear that one? That's right. Five hour stream
tonight. Can you believe it? But I will be back to get the festivities going for the end of the
year. But yeah, let's go. I- sorry that it's been 10 minutes to get started here. Year two is coming
up. I'm so glad I have that channel points thing though. It makes things so much more interesting.
It's not just like spend 1200 channel points to give an emote a mustache. Like this is- this is
real stakes now. Okay, let me- let me get started. Good link. They added a billion to the debt
counter. Why? For the impossible quiz and that's incorrect. I love how we have debt auditors that
are on the case. No, no, no. Excuse me. I've been- I've been an auditor. I've been looking at this.
All right, let me get the game open. Fear 2. Never played this before.
Let's get started. New deal. Hold on. Okay, Otto's Adventure is outdated. Let's put this on stream.
Let's find out what you guys want. Let me see here. Okay, Otto's Adventure is outdated. Yeah?
Otto's Big Adventure, A Dog's Day Out, full movie.
Eight years ago, okay. Remake it for 2.5 billion off the debt. Otto's Pogtastic Adventure,
A Dog's Day Out, remastered. Okay, deal. I agree. Deal. You got a deal. I will do a remastered
Otto's Pog Adventure. You ever gonna continue Hades? You quit at like the beginning of the game.
It'd be like quitting Binding of Isaac after four floors.
All right. Listen, I know. I've got a lot of things going on at the moment. It's a- I love
that game. It's a game of the year. Yes, I got four floors down in Binding of Isaac and said it was
the game of the year. Yes, but it's true. You know that. I know it. Everybody knows it. It has to go
on the main channel. Oh, you're gonna have to sweeten the deal there. No, no, I don't think
you can. I don't know about that. I don't know about that. That's gonna have to be much more.
To put that- to have that be the last upload on my main channel. You know how many people are gonna
just forget that I existed? That's gonna show up in their sub box and they're gonna think that I'm
on drugs and like I've gone like just over the edge. Like, oh, it's been like- it's been like
four and a half years since a German 95 upload. Oh, I remember this guy. It's Otto's Pogtastic
Adventure. I don't know about that. I feel like this is five billion- no, it's gotta be higher
than that. Higher than that. Ten- what is- okay, what's the debt at right now? Three billion if
you use that thumbnail. Is it at fifty? Did you- no, I thought I thought I got- we need some
auditors to take a look at this. Oh, yes, I'm interested. I'll do it. We gotta get the right
price though. Let's play Fear. Fear 2, actually. Sorry about that. Let me get that correct.
You guys will figure it out. You guys will figure it out. It'll- you guys- I have confidence you
guys will know what you're doing. Camera's not on, right? Okay, just making sure. Is this Fear? No,
don't do any coin tosses. Don't- do not humor them. Okay, so, all right, give me one- give me one
second. I just want to grab- I want to grab- hold on. I gotta grab something. I gotta- hold on. I'll be
right back. I'm gonna sprint. Right back. And make sure you get in your- no, just getting nominations
are closed. Sorry. You had your chance. Uh, the voting for the New Year's Eve Awards, by the way,
will be up pretty soon. So, you're- the actual voting will be available probably by the end of
this weekend or by Monday, I would say. Somewhere around Monday. You need to do a face cam. I don't
have any clothes on. Okay, I promise if I get jump scared once, I will turn on a face cam. It's not
gonna happen. This is not a scary game. I'm not gonna get scared by this game because this game
came out back when Little Girl is Scary was huge. And holy shit, if a little girl is, like, on camera
and she's standing at the end of a hallway, she's fucking terrifying. That doesn't scare
me anymore. I've seen it a hundred times. Back in, like, 2008, 2007, whatever it was.
Why are you naked? I'm not naked. I just don't have clothes on. You can be- you can- you can have
clothes on and be naked. And you can have- not have clothes on and not be naked. I don't even know
what I'm saying. I put my headphones in and music started playing and I just- I got speech jammed.
All right, let's go. I got so sorry. I got speech jammed when I put on the headphones.
Let's-
Okay, let's go. Single player online play doesn't exist anymore. There's no way it does.
All right, campaign. Fear 2. Reborn. I don't know. It's doing normal difficulty. What's hard
or easy? It's three. This is halfway there. God almighty, he's so high. I'm not high. I'm on hard.
I'm not putting on hard. I don't do hard anymore. Back in, like, 2012, I would have put it on hard.
Not now. 35-year-old Jeremy does not play games on hard. He plays games for the story and for,
the comedic material. I don't play games to look cool and be good. I play games to laugh at people
like getting hit by a car. I don't care anymore. I'm playing on normal. You've been diverted from
an assignment to assist- I'm still good at games, by the way. You've seen me play recently. I'm still
cool. And I know that any time you have to say that you're still cool, it means you're not cool
anymore, but I know I still am. All right, Svod- Svod D. Mission in the Auburn Industrial District.
Your new orders are to proceed to the private residence of Genevieve Orestide of Aracham
Technology Corporation and take her into protective custody. She will instruct you
where to escort her. Is this a 90 FOV? I hope so. I didn't download any community mod patches
or anything. Is this a 90 FOV? Why is this so low? Volume? It's 65? No, it's not. I remember
optimizing my fear 2 experience. Uh oh. You need to optimize it? All right, fear 2.
What? What the heck, man? Scared. Oh my god. Little girl with a teddy bear. She must be scary.
Little girl with a teddy bear. There may have been some blood on the teddy bear. That
might be scary to me. This is dark. Hold on. Right off the bat, I already see a problem. Just
give me a second. Yeah, that's got to go down. All right, how about FOV? Video settings. You
know you're in trouble when the only video settings in game are brightness and a resolution. Okay,
what about um whatever. You should invert the aim. I want to name scary. Mac in 2012. That
was terrifying. That's still too high though. Hold on. It's got to go to like zero. Okay,
that scared me. Where did I go? All right, let's go. How does this still feel like too high of a
mouse sensitivity? Go in and not only that, but there's like scary music box music.
Got me. It got me. I gotta turn the cam on.
No, that didn't even get me. That didn't get me. It wasn't even that that got me. It was the fact
that I was looking at the music box and I sat down weird on my chair. There was a glass on it and it
hurt my bump. I don't have clothes on. Hold on. I can't. Hold on. It's gonna have to be in a minute.
Our job is to secure this. Where are we driving? Are we driving off road? I don't want any breakage
even if she resists. We're bumping around like we're like the tower of terror. She's directly
linked to the bloodbath at Armicam headquarters. It's like a Universal Studios ride. It's like
the back to the future ride. She's a high value target and we've been tasked to bring her in.
So that's what we're going to do. Put on a seatbelt. Lighten up, Tom. She's a suit. What
she gonna do? Send a nasty text message? She's not the problem. Okay, for a second I thought
that was my finger over there pointing at them like yes, no, you talk. Now what do you have to say?
Fox, you're with Stokes. Keegan, you're with me. Beckett, Red,
Manny will drop you off in front of the building. It's a lot of people. That's us.
Shit. Why do I get into a bucket? Let's move. These guns. Okay, the guns. They're kind of
pointing them and I don't like how they're pointing the guns at each other.
Some people trigger discipline. Our mission is to find Aristine, not Cabaret.
This pop is bullshit, man. What's so important about this chick that the cops can't pick her up?
Yeah, I don't know. Dude, do you want to start taking hits at that fire extinguisher? Like,
fuck it. What's just us here? That situation is getting out of control.
Nah, dude. Not at all. All right. I'm just kidding. All right, here we go. PDA,
gun. Okay, I can't even shoot at him. Really? Okay. Access PDA. Place Genevieve
Aristide in protective custody. Rendezvous with your team in the building lobby.
Facecam. Why a shift? Aim down sights. That's not going to happen. Let's go back here for a sec.
Wait a minute. I got to brush my teeth. I got to brush my teeth. All right,
I'll put a face cam on, but I got to brush my teeth first and I got to put clothes on.
God fucking dammit. I didn't want to put a face cam on today. All right,
I'm going to brush my teeth and I'm going to put clothes on.
Just wait a minute. I'll be right back. Hold on. Just hear some cool art for a little while.
Let me just brush my teeth, put some clothes on. I'll be right back.
All right, guys. The lawn needed a little work too, so I wasn't prepared for the stream yet.
I haven't cut it in like six months. I'll be live in actually a few minutes. I'll be live soon.
All right. Am I ready? I'm going to get this ready.
Fucking face cam, man. God, scary games. I lost like a thousand viewers. What am I going to do now?
No one's even going to watch me anymore. All right, relax. You'll be fine.
Ooh, I'm the giant rat that makes all the rules. Of course you are.
All right, what do we look like? Let's see. How are we doing today? I told you I had to put
clothes on. I had to get like a shirt. I had to get like, I had to brush my fucking teeth.
I had to like go like this with my hair. I had to go like, how many boogers on my hands? No,
we're good. Nice v-neck. I own a lot of v-necks actually, so. Okay, wait a second.
Wait a second. Nice villain hair today. The thing is, I think every day is villain hair,
if I'm honest, at this point. Okay, so this is where I'm going to be sitting, like this.
Am I going like this in my mind frame? How does that look? Do I look evil? How does it look with
the game up? Am I blocking like ammo and shit? I probably am. You want to get a real close look?
I didn't frame my nose hairs yet, never mind. I ain't getting a close look today.
Okay, I think we're good. Face cam is in the wrong spot. There, now we're good. Okay, I'm ready.
Do it blue again. I can't just turn it, okay, let's go. What would I have to do? Can't shoot him.
All right, right, right, right, right. I told you this is gonna be a long one. Key bindings.
Where's my chapstick? Where's my chapstick? I can't, I cannot stream without, I cannot stream
without my chapstick. I gotta have my chapstick. I don't, I don't have my, I don't have my chapstick.
I'm actually furious about that. Okay, movement. It's uh, interaction. Shift. Mouse button two is
already assigned to melee. What kind of drugs make it, no. What? This needs to be sprint.
Or sprint. Is alt? Excuse me, it's not. Sprint, shift. Shift is already assigned to zoom. Yes,
that's, no. What are you doing? I don't want it to be alt. What are you doing? All right, zoom is
mouse two. Okay, let's go. Much better. Much better. Okay, I'm ready to play the game. No melee.
Don't get too close. They'll see your nose hairs. Hey, and by the way, I just shaved too.
What do you guys think of that? This is, this is like, I just literally shaved. Shaved my face.
Clean shaven. What do you think? I'm supposed to be playing a game. Like, who cares? Who cares
if I just shaved? What am I looking for? A reload? What did I do? I already forget it. What we were
just doing? Melee. Okay. Interaction. Melee is this button. What should I do? V? Mouse button? No,
no, no. I want mouse button four. All right, the game doesn't even know you have mouse buttons.
Middle mouse? V. V is assigned to thermal vision. Oh my fucking god. I don't know. I'd like,
what the fuck do you put it? Alt? Alt is already assigned to sprint. No, it's not. Who has alt for
a melee? Wait, what did, what did I just do that for? Why am I, why am I sliding? Is that a slide
tackle? Whatever, let's go. Okay, so we gotta go, where are we gonna go? Place? Yeah, yeah, rendezvous.
All right, so we can't go in the front door. The sensitivity is still too high. I don't even know
how that's possible. It's at fucking zero. This is zero sensitivity, by the way. It's zero. Go through
the coffee shop? All right, well, I'm trying to figure out how to get to the coffee shop, dude.
Turn it up all the way. It's not gonna even do anything. All right, we're going that way.
Eat the chapstick. Hold on, I'm too busy trying to not have my brain explode out of my front
of my eyes because I can't turn the sensitivity down. DPI is up. Yeah, I can't even change it.
Cool. No DPI button. Yeah, the thing that I complained about so much. You guys remember when
I used to sit here and talk a ton of shit about the DPI button. I was like, Razor, holy shit,
remove this. This button sucks. Fuck this button and fuck you, right? I've done it probably a
thousand times. Not there anymore and I need it right now. I thought he just screamed at me.
No, I don't. You're right. The gate's locked. All right, let's go this way. Move. Wait a minute.
The door. Oh, this door. Okay, I got a flashlight. F. Okay, there's a Vindex. I'm gonna have to
turn the DPI down. This dude's pretty strong. Holy shit. Look out. Look out. The final offer
is circulating. Okay. What happened here? How many people are on this team?
This is a, but it's been locked down. Hold on. Let me get a look. Let me look at that PC.
Okay, doctor. Making fun of a man for his knowledge is a sign of insecurity.
We need to find our seed now. Agreed. Fox, secure the lobby.
Ray, take the stairwell. Rest of you, you and me. The stairs?
What the fuck? It's a thousand fucking stories. It is a thousand fucking stories.
Just making sure he was dead. What's with my hair? I'm sorry. That was my fault.
That was all my fault. I'm sitting here going like, oh, man. How do I look? Hey,
Sergeant, what do you think? This is for a hairstyle. It's like sniped. Oh, man.
That was all my fucking fault. Oh, shit. I'm sorry. Vanity got that guy killed.
Arsenal select. Well, how far are we going? Yeah, it's pretty cool. It looks pretty good.
Oh, man. Yeah. This guy must've been shot in the aorta. I was ready for that one.
Got that one down. One more over here. Got him. Moving up. Oh, what? Hey.
Why did that guy explode? That guy just blew up. Oh, shit. Nice. Let me do that too.
Oh, is this health? Pick up Intel. Oh, all right. Okay. I'm at the vault now.
And plan B is going well. I don't read anything in games. All right. I thought that was a pick.
I could pick that up. This guy was using Windex as a weapon. St. Dead Rising, man.
That's not going to help you. Blue Gatorade. It's a blue Gatorade. Sprint. Is this sprint or is this
Lich Hover? Oh, she's in here. Armor vest. Nice. Okay. Bad news. You got armor. Whatever. You missed
the... Don't tell me I'm going to miss an extinguisher. Are you fucking out of your mind?
Yeah, there goes fucking $40 million worth of stuff. Sorry. What's that? 50 million.
Hold on. I got to... Slow down. I know you think it's funny, Jeremy, but slow down.
Slow down. Hold on. It looks like I got to use my two to travel to get extra speed.
I'm in. Sorry. I'll take a 50-50. I'll take a 50-50 on that one.
Health pack. Z is med kit. Okay. Let's go ahead. That is so funny, Jeremy. I'll make me fucking
ban you. Grenades. G is grenade. Okay. What? I feel like the game's in times two speed.
Anybody else feel like that? Why does it feel like it's in fast motion? It's because it's old?
I'm a boomer. Are you sure? I feel like I'm... Am I seeing the world in slow motion?
Probably because of your DPI. I don't know. The game's going too fast. It's because you're
stoned. No, that's not it. Can I kill the helicopter? Wait, there might be a secret out here.
What was that for? It just ruined a plant. That wasn't even funny. Don't deny being stoned. I'm
not stoned. I'm drinking a coffee. And... All right. Time to come clean. Time to come clean.
All right. Okay. I'm going to be drinking out of it. I'm going to be honest with you guys
because I've got a product here. This is not an endorsement. I mean, it kind of is.
It's not a truly. I'm not drinking coffee and fucking truly. This is a streamer endorsement.
I was not paid for this. I just thought it was an interesting idea and I did it. By the way,
I want to make sure I can tell you very... I know. Listen. There's no soy in this. There ain't no
fucking soy in here. So how dare you say what I think you're going to say. It's a heel. Don't
fucking say it. There ain't no soy in this. Don't say it. There's no soy product. It's not a soy
product. It's not a soy product. I'm just trying it. I'm just trying it to see if I like it.
It's a... I can't do this without sounding like I'm fucking... All right. Listen. Sometimes streamer
snacks, we talked about them and I was like, all right, so like you get baby food that works.
That's the, you know, that gives you some fruits and vegetables and shit. I do that. I still do.
Beef jerky. That's a good one. This is good too for me. It's just like a bunch of calories. It's
like protein and vitamins and shit and I like it. And nobody paid me to say that. I did. I paid
myself. I transferred. I transferred. Yeah, I transferred. I transferred $600 into my account
today. Paid myself for this one. No, all jokes aside, it really is like helpful. Whenever I
told you I was trying to put on weight, that helped. So all honesty aside, that's why I started
doing it and I put on a bunch of weight. All right, let's go. You're gonna see it. I know
people are gonna see it if I took sips out of it. It's not gruel. It all went to your ass.
It was already like that even when I was losing a little bit of weight. Gamer gruel. All honesty
aside, all right, I gotta play the game. Where was I going? And there's no soy. There's no soy in
None. So all of you that want to call me that word, sorry, you can't do it. Okay, fire mode.
B is burst fire. Oh, that's single shot actually. Play the game, you clown. I am. Just hold on. I
had to do my fucking heal endorsement. I really was not paid to do that. I just like it. So give
it a rest. All right, forget about new fire mode. I have to turn the D. Okay, next. When I go on
break, the DPI is going to like two. This guy's unstoppable. Are they talking about me? All right,
headshots only. I think I can do it. Single shots. Okay, headshots only if I don't get it.
Never mind. Just play. Uh, don't I have a health kit? Isn't it Z? Oh, I guess I can. Can I just
walk in this? It's gonna be something with the debt. No, it's not. Shotgun? Sick. Grenades? Sick.
Fuck it. That's all. Pick up what? Orcs? Oh, you can't like throw spoons at people? Shit.
Well, um, turn the fucking DPI down. How do I do that? Somebody help me. How do I turn the
DPI down on my mouse? Like mouse settings, right? Stoned off. DPI plus four. F4. Razor Synapse. I'm
not downloading that fucking pro. I will not download that program. I would rather play like
this than download that. Um, how do I do it? Do I actually have to download that? No, I don't want
it. Term of blue. What? You need to download and fix your game. I need to download a fix for the
game. Are you serious? Don't tell me that. That's a lie, right? PC gaming wiki. Fear 2 mouse fix.
What is this? This makes Fear 2 use raw mouse input and removes the game's dead zone and
sensitivity problems, right? Okay. Extract this. I gotta close the game. I need to- where's the-
where's the save point here? Exit to win- just watch some artwork. I'll be right back.
We're gonna go long today, I promise. All right, let's see if it worked. That image. That image.
The image of me existed on the internet. That I hated. It was the worst photo ever. I was like,
I fucking hate that photo. I wish something would take it over. Something would be more
popular than that image of my face that I don't like. And then the monkey paw curled. And that
image has just gone crazy. And it's just- you- be careful what you wish for, as they say. So,
you know. The monkey paw, yeah. Just be careful what you wish for. It just might come true.
Indebted. Hey, banana bros! All right, let's see if this worked. Hopefully this works. I
did all the instructions. Hopefully it worked. Fix your damn game. We're going long today. Don't
worry. I'm here for a while. It's gonna be more than a four hour stream. Don't you guys understand?
Watch this be like a virus or something that I just downloaded and I'm an idiot.
I looked on the first link in chat and all of a sudden, like, my computer gets compromised.
Guys, I'm in his computer. There's a ton of porn. Okay. Come on, please work. Oh, look at that!
Did it work? Guys, it worked. Everything is perfect. We're ready to go. I'm ready to play
Fear 2. Are you ready to enjoy this journey with me? I hope you are. Let's come on back now.
Oh, shit. That's fucking incredible. Look at how good I looked. Oh, Genos and Smash. I already
read it. You can't make me sad anymore. I already read it. It's never gonna happen. He's just always
gonna be like a fucking sticker for the rest of his life. Oh, whatever. Who cares? Let's go.
Getting to count Olaf here today. I kind of like it. There we go. Look at that. It's a video game
now. There we go. It's a video game now. It's a video game. I can play the video game. God damn
it. Whatever. I was trying to do something cool, but it failed. How do I crouch? Am I dead? Whoa,
what? No deal. No deal. Deanna is forced to sing the Jerma Raid song.
What are you guys doing to her? Okay, I'm good. You forced her to sing the raid song.
What is, why are you guys doing this? Hold on. I have to watch it. I'm playing a video game. I'll
watch it in a minute. That sounded like a character. I don't know what one. That wasn't Adam Sandler.
No. That guy was waiting for me. Do I have any grades? No, I don't want to burst fire, dude. Give
me like the, okay, there it is. You always sound like Adam Sandler. I don't think always. Maybe
sometimes. All right, let's go. I need a health pack. I don't always sound like Adam Sandler.
By the way, I'm having some trouble with this game. What does that bar mean? Better. Is that
health or what? Is red? I don't understand what it means. I don't get it. It looks red, but there's
no, it's not decreasing. Dude, please quit touching your hair. You're making it worse.
Don't you make fun of my hair. Okay, here we go. That was an actor. That was, that was a stunt man.
He even went. All right, watch it. I'll watch it. Hold on. Let's see. You know, this is forced to
sing the raid song. Scream overreaction. That's not her. Let's see. Literally, you're a handsome
Jack. I don't have the things here. Why am I blue? Because it's because my screen is blue.
What do you think I am? Blue? All right, here it comes. That's pretty good. That's way better
than what I do. That came out of nowhere. Clapping my ass right now. Get that off.
Hey, you get off. Don't right now. Don't. Don't actually. I have to hide right now. I have to,
I gotta hide. I gotta turn the camera off. I gotta hide. I'm back. Fucking cooler than ever.
I'm not blue anymore. Clapping my ass. Why is it locked? All right, it's not gonna happen to me.
All right, does this guy just fall off by himself? Come on. He does it every time.
All right, I want more health. Are you okay? I want more health. I wonder what, okay, if I,
what happens if I like go up, hold on. I'm not gonna kill him yet. Why did it not explode? Why
did it not explode? All right, get me in this. I have to go in this. I have to go in there, right?
Uh-oh. Kill it. Okay, whatever. Can I swim? So what? Hidden door. Remember, you look handsome.
How about now? I don't need more. Turn the cam off now. That's a lot of people.
Is there a grenade? I still got it. I don't care about the lore.
Little girl scary. This is the whole game. Okay, what do I, I hurt my shoulder.
There's a piano. Hold on. Piano. Why does it just turn into like a cut oak tree?
Okay, let's go. When do I get the superpowers? Do I get, do you get superpowers in this game?
When is, oh shit. I don't, I, that's all I care about. No, you don't, you thought you looked cool,
but it was kind of cool. But you should have just held the trigger down when you heard the
footsteps in front of the door. Scary girl. Where is she? Scary girl. She's around somewhere.
Why is my instinct to just shoot her? I can't, I feel like she's going to turn around and come
try to kill me. You know what I think it is? It's me just pre-firing the jumpscare because if she
turns around and screams, I'm already, like the gun's already screaming, so I'm already ready.
All right, secret. Hold on a second. Just hurt. It was hair. It was my hair though. It was,
it was my hair. That was my hair. That was my hair. I remember, it definitely fell in
because it was long and it was, it was like blonde and brown. It was this long.
That was my hair. Or it might've been, I don't know. I think it was mine. That was shot out
into the screen if I didn't, I wasn't careful. I was about to just start cracking up with it
in my mouth. Don't ever drink when you, don't ever do that. That's a thick liquid too. Don't
laugh while you have a thick liquid. I'm like talking, I was like, oh yeah, you, man.
I swear to God that was my hair. I know it was. Trust me. I know what it looks like. I know what
it looks like. I just want you to know the things I like, okay? It's a product I like.
Okay, I'm going to lose my mind. I have to relax. He's malfunctioning.
You and your squad are the only hope of stopping Ulma.
No, what do you have here? It's protein. Soy. Okay. There's no soy in this. Read my fucking bottle.
My bottle doesn't have that word. Hey, what's that say right there? Can you read it? Soy free.
Absolutely soy free. This is probably a different product. This is a, this is
bullshit and you're a liar. You can't, you can't put one over on my eyes. I have a game to play
and I haven't done anything. It's gluten. Hey, let's, let's read it. 27 vitamins and minerals.
Fucking POG. 20 grams of plant-based protein. POG, no soy. Omega-3 and omega-6. Six grams of
fiber in this fucking thing. Phytonutrients. I don't know what that word means, but it sounds
pretty scientific. Only five grams of sugar. None of this like fucking 40 grams of sugar.
Bullshit soda crap that you drink. Gluten free and soy free. So what the fuck's your problem,
man? It's good. I like it. I'm going to keep drinking it. Whether you like it or not.
Streamer loves hairy drink. It's my hair. That was my own fault. Water is superior.
Water is good too. I drink water too. Oh, we have to extract this person.
It's her. Stubborn son of a bitch probably just killed us all.
You got a new clip for me? Hold on. I'm busy. What the fuck just happened to you?
I'm playing a game. Is this some kind of, I'm like a simulation or something.
What do you want me to do? I guess I just leave? Shoot. Can't press any buttons or anything.
You're Hue-lucinating. I'm going to catch her. God damn it. I can't believe one of my fucking
hairs fell in. Was that supposed to be on screen? I feel like that was supposed to be a little
bit more blurry. Did we just get nuked? What? Why did we get nuked? Oh, I got to make room for the
fuel. Oh, it's good shit. It really is. I swear to God. Like Agent Smith's or something? That was
the ending to Fear 1. Was it? I don't remember any of that. What's this? You guys are spamming,
you guys are spamming me with a video. I'm getting spammed. You don't pay attention to
Laura. That's why. Guys, I played Fear 1 like three years ago. All right. I'm gonna, I'm gonna,
I'll listen to the video. I'll listen to the video. What do you guys want me to hear so bad?
Jerma is so nice. A piece of slime that's been scraped off of the bottom of a sewer. What?
And Jerma is like a piece of better slime that has been scraped off of the top of the sewer.
He's the top of the sewer and I'm the bottom. Wait, I didn't.
Okay. Um, I think I'm fucking carved out of stone, if I'm honest with you. I think that
fucking God threw down lightning down and Saint Peter fucking carved me out of a goddamn slab of
stone. Zeus struck the lightning down. It turned into me. Exactly what somebody that is at the top
of the slime would say. Oh, okay. Sure thing. Whatever. He's stoned. Okay, I did not expect
that guy to be there. Ego maniac. And use a gun. And if that don't work, use more guns.
Grab it. What are they doing to me? He's alive. Holy shit, that's not how you have surgery done.
What are they fucking doing? Oh my God. Oh, we're gonna we have just as general appendix surgery.
Nothing that we have to be afraid of.
This is just two guys playing surgeon simulator on some asshole.
That was insane. This game is fucking crazy. I don't have any organs left.
I have no organs. Put your gamer glasses on. I don't have any. Google Glass. All right. Intel.
Who cares? Find a weapon. I'm gonna okay. I've been I've swallowed so much air from laughing
at random stuff while trying to drink at the same time. So it's gonna happen. I try I'm gonna try
as hard as I can. This is why I don't put cameras on. I fucking hate webcams. I don't want a web
cam on me. I don't get it off. Turn it off right now. Is that toilet backwards? Isn't that supposed
to be the other way? Why is that? That looks different to me. No, no. Right? No. Isn't that
like the lip is crooked? Yeah, I know. But like isn't the lip this the space is there? I guess
some toilets have the space. I need a weapon. It's not a weapon. Get out of this fucking place.
Oh, are you in terms of service? No, but I'll be fine. I'll be fine. Don't worry. Are you afraid?
I mean, I could be a little a little a little chilly right now. You know, I'm a little cold.
Uh, I'm not scared. You should be. Well, I'm not. Wait, okay. I thought that was a guy leaning back
with a gun. Like N64 style. Like he like he looked like Polygon. I thought he was like had a gun back
there. I was like what the fuck is this guy with a gun doing back here?
Save the game? I think it's doing it. It's automatically doing it. Open. Open the door.
Why do these don't open? Okay. Oh, a professional doctor. Did it hurt me? Oh, it's for cover. I get
it. Blood. Blood. Smash or I don't know. Whatever. Oh no, more blood. Blood. Blood. What a weird
substance. It's so bizarre that we have like human oil that like makes us run. This is weird.
Uh, well, how do what am I supposed to do? Is there another way to go? Restricted area.
Uh, running in circles? No, I'm not. I'm here. Here's. How am I speed bagging this thing?
Jerma, go read an analog clock. Give me one. Give me one. Give me a time. I'll do it right now. I'm
not high. I've not had any CBD, any THC, none today. Zero. Read any analog clock you want.
Can I just go in? Whoa, it's control. Hold on. Is this something? I can't like get out of this.
Come on. What? Oh dude, this is really spooky. It kind of is. What was he holding? Is this a bottle
of hydrogen peroxide? Where did he even come from? It's Pepto-Bismol. I need a gun, right?
I'm getting more. There's more spam going on here. All right. After this, no more links.
Wait, are we going to do this thing? Hold on. I need to put like a different shirt and pretend
like I'm seeing this another day. Give me one. Give me a second. Hold on. I'm going to put like
another game in the background too. Hold on. Give me one. I'll be right back.
Oh, this is fine. I can just put this around my neck and stuff. This works. I have different
hair though. Look at all these cat boys. I'll change my background, right? I'm wearing like
a big elaborate sweater today. I'm not going to be blue. I'll be, I don't know, green. Yeah,
it's like a different day. Yeah, it's really sunny up today. I just woke up in the morning
and like this is like it's tomorrow. I'm going to be like, what the fuck is this?
Sounds like it was bright this morning. Okay. Well, I need the video. I'm going to be fucking
mad that you guys linked this to me this early. What the fuck is this? It's too early for this,
dude. It's way too early for this. I just fucking got up and you guys are linking me this.
When was this? Yesterday? Whatever. I'm going back to bed. Fucking come out of here.
I hate this. Just turn the stream off now. Turn off the stream now. Like I was never live.
No, I have to play fucking Fear 2. I went to bed. It's tomorrow. Restart. You've ruined it. What?
What do you mean restart? Do it again? You choked in the end. You were fucked in the head. Oh,
I read that wrong. I'm not even at the tutorial. Too early for this. All right. I have to play
the fucking game. Don't mind me. I'm here, but I'm Sansom. Fuck. It's just going to do
what it's going to do and I don't care anymore. Yes, I do. Of course I do. All right. Can I please
play the game? It's been ages. I thought he said Colonel Sanders. Colonel Sanders, I've taken them
out. Oh, that's good. Now come back. We're a $5 fill-up box. We can't let them get away with
their secret rash at me. I need a gun. You're a budget Anakin Skywalker. That's okay. Like,
do you think that's going to make me mad or like pissed off or something? Why would that make me
angry? The most powerful fucking Jedi on earth. The coolest, most destructive, awesome force of
a person. Budget that. That's still fucking one of the best in the world. So I don't care. That's
fine.
THC lab. All right. I know. I know. I can't believe it. I can't.
No? Okay. Gotta go to the THC lab. What's this face I'm doing? Ambush. I still need a weapon.
Slow-mo. He's dead? Look at that guy. What? Why did he explode? Was he made out of glass?
That's what it is. Okay. Wait, wait, wait.
All right. I'm fine. I don't want to hear that. X marks the spot. Nope. And links. No more links.
I ain't looking at any links. No more links. I gotta get out of the tutorial first. Hey,
you guys. What the fuck? Oh shit. Come on. We have bugleberry soldiers. I don't die.
Oh, is he still shooting? It was rigor mortis. Oh, he's still alive? Okay. I'm coming to save you.
Open the door. I'm here to save you. I'm here to save you. I'm here to rescue you. Ma'am, open the
door. I'm here to save you. Open the door. I'm trying to get you out of here. Ma'am, I'm trying
to help you. Open the door. Any snacks in there? Watch this. Which one's going to be left or right?
Open, open, open, open. What? Is he dead before we hit the ground? No. Oh shit. Did they remove it?
That was like the best part of the first game. Anymore? Oh shit. Open the... I fucking missed it.
That was supposed to be scary and I just turned around. The camera is out of sync.
No, it's not. It is. What the hell are you talking about? Oh, it isn't. You made that up. They did.
Of course they did. I know they did. Can I get up there? Oh, go this way. Steam hurt? No, it better
not. I'd be pissed if it did. Locate a working elevator to the third floor. Melee. Okay, Melee.
Hey, don't look over here. No, redo that part. I want to kick him down the elevator.
Redo that part. I want to sneak up behind him and kick him down the elevator.
Melee fans. Melee fans. Melee fans. What are you saying that for? All right, let's go. It's
literally a half second behind. That's impossible. There's nothing on there that would... This is
impossible. It's impossible and I'm not even gonna give it any more thought. Okay, here we go.
Just get down there already. Okay, we're good. Who's next? Got a grenade. I can't get in here.
Don't even need to be in there. Who cares? It's delayed. Listen to the people. The webcam is
delayed. I've had just about enough of this shit. How's that? Does that sound good? Fixed. Fixed.
Worse. Worse. Oh, that's really funny because I didn't do anything at all. I just clicked the
webcam on and off, pretended to change the setting, and then you guys pretended it got worse.
I win. I like that blue. It's a nice blue. Stop smurfing, bro. What do you mean stop smurfing?
There's no levels in this game. All right, scratch the itchy face part of my face.
Got a key card. Based. You're based. Smurf. All right. Reflex injector. I mean, where am I?
What just happened? Reflex injector? What does that mean? Urgent warning. No. Tab. Where is it?
Why do I keep teleporting around? Somebody will help me. Whatever. I don't care. This door can
open. No, it can't. Can I go in another door? How about this one? Upgrades the slow-mo duration.
Oh, okay. Cool. Where else am I supposed to go? Did I get everything in here? I don't actually
have to move this, right? You're so bad. Dude, the heal crash is real. The heal crash. Yeah,
because I had to go in here. I can't move this. Press E. I can't do anything. Use your brain. Use
your mind. E. I don't think I am. Where am I supposed to go? I went down here. I've already
been in here. Was there another key card door to go in? Oh, okay. Over here. Why is everything
blocked off by boxes? I win. Did I miss another jump scare? What's the cam even on for if I'm
just going to miss these? Oh, that's a monk at TOS. I shot him. I stopped that. I very clearly
shot that before it happened. Come on. I played House of the Dead before. That's bullshit. I want
my extra one health. They just explode. Damn. Damn. Oh, damn. Any more? Getting just blood splatters
in your face and having bullets hit you in the head is way more scary than the girl walking
slowly behind a glass door. Shotgun. Oh, hell yeah. Finally. It only took 100 million years to get
this. Wait. It's still tutorial, right? Never mind. You already shot gun. What? This way. Getting
close to the lobby. There's some kind of activity. Check out the activity in the lobby. Got it. Oh,
shit. I'm not that scared of this. All right. Which one is she in? We're going to unzip number
one. Unzip number... No. Which one are we unzipping? Who's going to come out of the morgue and who's
going to grab me? Hopefully this wasn't like a prank. All right. Going up. The entire game is
a prank. Out of coffee. That's a problem. Now, how do I get it to move? Here we go. Get to the
third floor. Third floor. This would be the second floor. Is this the third floor? What floor is this?
Why is it not moving anymore? Press and hold. I'm not soft-locked. I'm fine. Lots of body armor,
which I think is awesome. All right. Something behind this door. Slow-mo through here. Nope.
Can't go through here. Of course we can. Of course not. You're right. There's a million clocks on the
wall. Oh, shit. Okay. It is exactly 3 p.m. Three o'clock. Done. See? I'll do another one. Wait,
why would all the clocks be different times? Dude, the guys that explode. It's just... He wouldn't
even aim it at me. Like I was playing VR. His gun was like bouncing all around. Like down, up, left,
right. You got... Hey, you got... Sorry. Room's not big enough, dude. You got to do seated play. What
does that do? All right. Frag grenade. He slowly realized that that was not going to stop and
explosion from killing him. Oh, fuck. Pick it up and throw it back. Oh, jeez. Hold on.
Look at his little... His little like shimmy. Oh, I'm on fucking fire. How do I get to...
Turn the sink on. Oh, you dick. This reminds me of the time that I had a wart on my finger. Me too.
Wow. We're so alike, you and I. How did you miss that? There we go. That was creepy. What?
No, that was like a, hey, you and me. We get it. That was creepy. You never been like, hey, hey, hey.
Hey, easy. Hey, you're an ego. You never been like, oh, yeah, hey, we're going to go over here.
Yeah, here we are. That's like a nudge. Like, hey, hey, you and me. We get it. You know,
ladies and gentlemen, fellas, I was begged to wink every day. Every single day of my life,
I was begged to wink to you. And now all of a sudden, when you don't have to pay for it,
when it's free, you don't like it anymore. What is going on there? I don't know. I thought that
was a pineapple. Too bright. Don't like it. All right. Where are we going? Where are we going?
Get to the THC lab. Let me get into the chamber. Oh, come on. Pay attention. This is like driving
a car and looking over at somebody. Pay attention to the road. I can turn into a skeleton.
I'm adjusting my VR headset. I tell you, this is a VR game. Honey? Honey, it's dad. Simpson's
thing over there. Hold on. I wish I could slow it down. What the fuck was that? Was that a mole?
Did I have somebody on the inside? Did he press the button and start firing at them?
The guy on the left. What was that? There it is. Finally. Finally, we got it. Finally, he says it.
Finally. It took two hours. Holy shit. Oh, I'm so glad we get to hear it again. I missed it so much.
You're just working the angle, Jerma. What does that mean? I changed the camera? So it doesn't
look like I'm trying to work an angle? Should I put the camera somewhere else so I'm not trying
to make it look like I look good or something? What do you mean, working the angle? Like this
angle? What if I sit back here? You're working it. What do you mean? If only I was good at
multiplayer games like this, I could get rid of people like this. Jerma, you're playing dense.
I'm 35. I don't know any words on the internet. Guys, I haven't posted a selfie of myself or a
picture of myself to the internet like ever. The Twitter fucking Thanksgiving ham video was
the last time I did it. I don't know what that means. Hey, Esoteris, thanks for the ten community
subs. Thanks a lot. So two weeks ago. Yeah. And then go back half to two weeks. How long has it been?
Like years. Sing the sub song. Here you go. This is what you want. This is why everybody's here.
Don't fucking pretend like this is not the reason why you're here.
Take it and run with it. That's why you're all here. Did that hurt?
Oh, we got out of the tutorial cutscene. Jerma keyboard font. I don't know what that means.
Wait, you want like a... I can't... I don't... What? You want me to make my own font?
Next grenade type. Next grenade type? Incendiary grenades. Oh shit. Oh shit. This is very flammable.
I feel like he just set that up wrong, right? I feel like I didn't even do anything. Like,
I don't think that should have happened. He installed that incorrectly. The energy of your
stream is off. What do you mean? Energy? What does that mean? The energy of your stream is off.
You're talking about like at my audio level? You need more vibe. Okay. This is for a vibe.
I'm playing the game now. You're too loud. You just walk next to an explosive. Well,
I'm not paying attention to the road right now. I'm looking... I'm talking to one of the passengers
in the car here. So like this is what I'm talking about. All right, hold on. Watch this. Ready?
Do you know... All right, so somebody was just like, you know what? I'm gonna kill both of them
because like this is the chance I got and he's standing there still. So I'm gonna go for it.
Harry, I'm sorry, but this is the guy and I'm just going for it. He's standing still.
Why am I shaking? I love it so much. The whole stream is a prank. I don't think so. What do you
mean? That was a default. Holy shit. Why can I pick this up? How the... Okay. How can I pick
that grenade up? Different grenade type? Yeah. Wasn't I holding five? Your vibes are better.
You could get it. What's this crack that I'm seeing? Oh, fuck. Got him. Okay, we're good.
Wait. How did he burn? What is he doing? What the fuck? He looked at it and it made him catch
on fire. Why? Whatever. Hey, look, we got good vibes now. Where should I go? In here? I heard
grenade. Why did that last so long? Good vibes and chill. Yeah, that's true. That's what I'm
talking about. Boom. Yeah, we're just chilling out. What are you guys talking about? Oh, my...
I gotta use my shotgun for a little while. Hold on, wait. Live, laugh, love.
Hard mode. This is too easy, please. No, I'm just vibing, right? We're just hanging out.
I say it and everybody gets mad. Nice. Thank God. I was gonna be so mad if I couldn't hit
that phone off the wall. Okay, where? Beers? Hold on, wait. Did he just respond to that by saying
shit? What the fuck is going on? Oh, he didn't throw it very far. Back up. Back up.
There's a lot of smoke. The smoke just everywhere. Okay, hold on. Give me the shotgun again.
What was that? Did I shoot myself in the chin? What? What the hell was that? It was the fire...
Wait, those explode that far? That's crazy. That's not what it was. No, guys, that was not what it
was. I want to check that out. All right, hold on. That's a huge explosion. It was what it was. Okay.
I did not think that was gonna happen. Nothing? Okay, down here. How the fuck do you do that? I
don't know. Somebody said, it's okay. Vibes stable. Thank God. I thought that was a clown.
I'm gonna be honest. I thought that was a clown. Whoops. What's he doing? What's he reaching for?
What are you doing? What the fuck is this guy? Die! Okay, give me that thing. Oh shit, nice.
Let's do a spy check. He's doing the thing the stuntman does in every movie.
This thing. When they're on fire and they just go like this, they're engulfed in fucking flames
and they just do the... And they just slowly are taking one or two little steps at a time
because it's like, holy shit, this is a real dude and he's really on fire. So you have to be really
careful. Imagine being in that suit though and just knowing like, holy shit, I am completely
engulfed in fire. Everything from head to toe. I am a golem from... I'm a golem. I'm the fire
golem from Diablo 2. Not a golem. A golem. That's what I was trying to say. Golem from Diablo 2.
Fire golem. It would have been... You would have understood if I said it faster without stopping
and going... And then blocking it in my brain. Delay's getting even worse. Okay, sure thing.
Fix it, idiot. I don't know how. Fucking idiot streamer. Can't do anything.
Fucking idiot. All right. Shotgun. Take it. Shotgun. Got it. Oh no, vibe levels are critical.
What do I do to fix the vibe levels? Why does he move his whole body to dodge things?
Because I don't know. That's something from Super Mario. I got it from my mother.
Anytime my mother wanted to make a jump across a platform or something, she would always do this.
So she would be running, right? Like Mario's running across the screen and she would jump
and she'd go... And it somehow helped. It helped her get to the other side somehow.
And I don't know. It's just that it stuck with me. Mama. That's right. That guy was terrible.
He's alive. Shit. Grenade. What? Okay. I was going to say that didn't... This game's like fun though.
I actually kind of like this. You kicked at his ankles and it killed him. Yeah. Well,
he only had like two health left. What is it? Oh no, his vibe levels. His telesthetic vibe
levels are critical right now. They're off the charts at the moment. Easy. I've been here.
Will he know that the grenade's behind him? He's trying to run away. Where did that guy go?
Holy shit. That was so fucking bad. That was so shitty. That was like... There was just no way he
was going to be in the bathroom. You know what I mean? There was no reason anyone was going to be
in here. In fact, I think that's actually the guy. Somebody said, town NPC death sound.
He walked up to like one of the villagers and just like stabbed him. God damn it.
Can we hear it? Does anybody have it? This stream has been all over the fucking place.
Clip's a band. For what? Link's a band. Oh shit. Because I was getting spammed. Oh my god.
Or not even dead. That's just like you... A NPC in town runs away. Because you pressed Z and
unholstered your shotgun. Right? And it's just like, crazy guy, run! Like that's in Red Dead.
You know what I mean? You have the holster and you like pull it out. And all of a sudden
people are just like... But Link's a band. Whatever. In the saloon, you just open the door.
I didn't even do that. Did I do that? Did I kill that guy? Was that scripted or did I shoot him?
I didn't do that. Is the guy's head talking? This guy's head is screaming. What was that?
You just kicked me like... I can't... Why are you doing this? Stop doing this.
Where are they coming from? Stop spawning.
I need a break. I need to take a break. Why are they... I don't know where they're going.
Why are they all limping? Why is every NPC limping? I'm going crazy pills.
Okay. Every NPC is limping. Okay. That was a little scary. I'm kind of concerned about that.
I'm a little concerned. What happened to that guy? That guy's head's gone.
Oh, shit. I'm afraid to go down there. We're gonna long distance that one.
Grenades go up. What do you think? What do you think? I don't hear like a radio tune.
I just came from here. Yeah, I know. But what? Did that guy blow up in here? Holy shit. What
happened to that guy? You're alive? Impossible. Impossible. Did I get him? I think I got him.
Throws grenade. Throws grenade. Throws grenade. Throws grenade. Yes. Yes, that's true. Well,
if I have them, I'm going to use them. Why would I not use the grenades? They're incredibly
destructive. They're so good. Where do I go? Nade Andy. Whatever. That's fine. I can't open this.
Can I not get this open? Oh, there was a big X on it. Like this doesn't work. I want more coffee.
Okay. Oh, health pack. Nice. 5pm coffee. Sometimes you need a little bit to keep
you going, you know? That's all right. I'd say a coffee after like five or six. You gotta be
careful. You don't want to do too much. But a little one. That's fine. And me, right? Okay.
Time to fight this thing. What? How many are there? Oh, what the fuck? Did I get him?
Okay. We're good. We're fine. We're fine. We're fine. You can't just like bite me and then run
away. What is he doing? He's trying to get a hiding spot. Give me the shotgun. Shotgun better.
Oh yeah. They're like little dogs. Okay. Get out. Out, out, out, out. Move, move, move.
Through the ceiling. Here we go. One, two, three. No. Okay. We're fine. What's going on with this guy?
Can I do anything with this guy? No. This guy's just dead. Why are they filming this? Get that
out of here. What the fuck? Yep. I knew it. I was waiting for it. No, you're going to do it. It's
going to... Didn't do it. Wow. Okay. I'm actually pretty surprised that they did not do that. Oh,
okay. Remember, you promised a sly cooper. When is sly cooper? Yeah, I fucked it up. My PS3. All
right. Those either weren't here. My PlayStation 3 smelled like burnt plastic when I played anything.
So I had to try to find a solution to it. When I play with my PlayStation 3, it smells like burnt
plastic. Bad. To a point where it makes me give me like a headache. So I can't use it. So I gotta
figure out what to do. This button will toggle power to the doors. I just locked them and the
x-ray. Okay. What are they doing? Do an emulator. I actually tried to use an emulator, but I got a
ton of awful interlacing and it was just ugly and horrible to look at. I tried to do a bunch of
different settings, try to change what it looked like and just wasn't happy with it. So until I
can do that, I'm just going to get another PlayStation 3. This is open. Yeah, it was really
just ugly. Frames were blending and it was, there was a lot of weird ghosting and blending
and I was just like, I, I'll just buy another PS3. German put art on so I can eat. Um,
I'll take a break in like 20 minutes. Oh, we're out. Holy. I tried to shoot. That, that guy's
entire skeleton was okay. That was ridiculous. That guy got like slow cooked for like four or
five straight days. All the meat just fell off the bone. Like you couldn't, you didn't have to
try. Holy shit. Watch it. I don't do anything stupid. You got a broken leg. All right. He's
got a broken leg, a, uh, broken collarbone and a broken jaw. Okay. Fix him. I can't. I'm not a
doctor. I squeeze through. I cannot squeeze through that. Play Mega Man. Uh, no, not right now. Get
out of here. It's quiet. It's too quiet. Hey, are you all right? What did he throw? What did he
throw? What just happened? What was it here? He's back. Why did that guy get a respawn?
That guy's back was towards me. Well, really painting the barn. I don't even know what that
means. Gunplay is pretty good in this game though. I like the gunplay. It's, it's really responsive,
really responsive gunplay. See, when I say the word gunplay enough times, you guys will then
respect my review coming later because I said that word and you guys go, oh yeah, he knows what
that means. He's like, he's, you know, the lingo of like playing games, like reviewing him and shit.
This guy's locked in here. Uh, careful. You have to compare this to Dark Souls. I don't think I can
do that. I'm not sure that's possible. I don't think I can compare this to Dark Souls. He has
an extension cord in his body. That's what that is, right? Okay. Whatever. Whatever. It's glass.
I keep thinking it's, I can shoot through it. I was trying to, alt, alt.
He got on top of me twice. Fucking sticky keys. Radio? No. Oh, lower disc. You guys do that too
when there's a bunch of people, you're at like a tourist attraction. Everyone's just taking
pictures and you're like, I have to fucking go. I have to walk by and I'm not going to sit here
for like fucking 25 minutes while like 10 of you take photos. Go down, crouch and you like get
underneath their picture. Who's that? No, I just run across. No, you can't do that
because then you'll end up, you'll be like a blur. What's that? Oh, nice. Crouching is worse.
You end up like, there's like a head and somebody like crouching by. I somehow didn't get hit by
that. I don't know. I don't know how. Uh, can I go? How do I make the elevator go? Go elevator,
go up. Press the, I just made it. Level three recognition.
Fuck. God damn it. I got to be ready for it. It's black. I can't even, I can't shoot through it.
What's going on? Does he swallow it? I feel like he swallowed that. Holy shit. Gulp. Uh, excuse me.
I gotta go down. Worst, worst. Don't do worst noise. Whatever. Find a way out of the outer
shell before it is destroyed. Okay. I can do that. Maybe. I feel like I'm playing Portal 2.
I don't know why. Getting Portal 2 vibes. Oh, he got, wait, he's getting burnt by what?
Oh, he's stood in front of the jacuzzi jet. Careful, dude. You never, don't ever do that.
Come on. Jesus. Come on. Oh, all right, all right, all right, all right, all right. Go, go, go.
Everybody calling me grenade Andy. I mean, you get so many of them and they do so much damage.
Why wouldn't I use them? I think I've thrown 70 or 80 grenades in this playthrough so far.
They're just everywhere. Why not just use them? Of course, I'm going to throw them. Um, what?
I don't know what that was, but apparently that guy killed the other guy somehow. His body,
I don't know. His corpse was break dancing. Okay. A shock grenade. Ooh. Kind of want to try this.
What the fuck? CDPR really dropped the ball here. It kind of is the cyberpunk music, isn't it?
Just goes like, Oh, here we go, man. I'm about to get into a big fight in cyberpunk.
Cool. I'm dead. Whatever. Oh, that's right. He's making a cyberpunk joke. I have to make one.
All right. I got to get down there before they get up. Let me in. What are these guys doing?
Who's driving the forklift? Who's driving the forklift? What the fuck?
Some guys just like backing up for the forklift. How do you feel about your cyberpunk cameo?
I don't have a cyberpunk cameo. All right, come on. Got to get in the door before they get over there.
Is somebody in there still? Punch him. Punch him. Punch him. What the hell is this? An assault rifle?
Oh, nice. I'm doing okay, I think. The music is kind of overpowering my brain.
Throw more grenades. I'm already throwing a bunch of grenades, man.
It's too much stimulation. It's a lot of stimulation. Too much. It's too much stimulation.
This guy's still alive. Is that guy alive? Wait. No, get down. No, he's just stuck in the ground.
Okay, whatever. Good vibes only. Swap weapons. E. I know how to do that already.
He's checking his armpits. He's smelling his armpits to see if he has smelly armpits.
Got him. He's not going to explode, is he? He might. Oh, get. Where's my red dot? Where's the red dot
sight? Oh, we're going to get a comedy fall. That was not funny. A person exploding. That's
not a comedy fall. He was supposed to fall down. Where are they running? What? I feel like I'm
playing on a tiny map in a shooter game, and people were just spawning and killing each other.
Spawn, die. Spawn, die. Spawn, die, die. Spawn, die. Just infinite respawn. Instant respawn.
No reloads. Okay. I don't know. I don't. So, let's. I don't want that. I want the health.
That was a tuber reaction. What, going like this? Oh, it's links. Is that a tuber reaction? That's
not really a tuber reaction. That's just a. Well, look at what we're doing. We're killing this guy.
You know what else? Okay. First impressions of Fear 2. I feel like there's been no downtime.
It's just been spawn and kill people. Just run through. This is just a never-ending instant
respawn FPS map. And I'm doing really well. I'm like fucking 75 and 2. I don't even know
what's happening. What happened to the little girl? What was that? Who puts me down? Gets a big fat
bonus. Really? I don't think that's. Okay, hold on. Itchy mouth. Where should I go?
What the fuck? What are you doing? Stop running into explosives. I'm doing really well this game
with the shotgun. This is a gameplay. This is a good thing I'm recording because this is going
up on the main channel. This is going to be a big commentary about how I fucking 104 best gameplay
I've ever put up. Keep this up. I need ammo for that. Can I get rid of this? This gun sucks.
Okay. What do I want to swap? Yeah. Give me. Why the hell would I use a pistol for? It's stupid.
What is this doing? Oh, shut off the gas leak. Okay. Do it. Chat demands it. Do demand what?
Do a game. Game. Oh, all right. Hold on. Oh, you motherfucker. No. Okay. I'm fine.
How long is this game even? I'll do it. I'll do it. I'll do it. I'll do it.
You ready? Here we go. Hey, what's going on, everybody? Gerber here with another Team Fortress
2 gameplay commentary. And tonight, gotta be playing in fucking 10 years ago. There it is.
Finally. He did it. I'm not doing that ever again. It's the last time you'll ever hear me say those
words. Stop standing up. Talking about sticky keys. Okay. Can I leave? Uh-huh. No. No. You.
Stop. How do I get by that? Stop. No, I wanted to do that. It's what it feels like to be an
NPC in this game. You suck. I'm fine. Find a way out. Okay. Do another joke. Okay. Fine. All
right. All right. Just give me a second. I gotta find like a swamp creature or something in here.
There's gotta be like a swamp monster I can say yell at or something, right?
Do one. Just wait a minute. All right. Here she comes. That's what you're using to hold the
papers down? Like, get a filing cabinet. Why is this like a caveman? Like, a caveman works
in the office? Like, put this in a filing cabinet. Use big rock. Keep papers done.
Chunggo, can you please put those in the filing cabinet? Filing cabinet. Scary. Make loud noise
when open door. That's just, the wheels are a little, we'll put some WD-40 on it. Remind me of
Giant Bird. Okay. Someone else will read it. Chunggo. Scary! That actually was scarier. Fake?
Yeah, and like, very overdone. This little guy from Overwatch. This is Arm. He builds a century
Torbjorn. This is Arm, right? How do I get this open? It wasn't minus two, minus two, whatever.
He said make a joke. He didn't say make a good one. That wasn't clear. Um, is this something I
can press in here or activate? Why is the chat adding and subtracting? Well, they're trying to
tell me how good or bad I am doing streaming. That's pretty much what it is. It's a point system.
If I say something that's not funny, they take points away from me, which makes me very upset.
But if they like what I say, they add points, which makes me very happy. New viewer song.
Welcome to the channel. I'm not, I hate, I'll clear that. I'm not doing this. I'm not going to do that
anymore. I'm not going to be like the guy with the sound board that makes fucking sound. Where do I
go? I have to get this open somehow. Be that guy, please. Live your dreams. Get off me. Hey, get away
from me. Nice gameplay. Don't play me. Oh, the little dog golem guys are here. Data. Now she's
drawn to me. Coveter. You are coveted. Okay. But does it have to be an anime convention? I feel
like that would be like if I was just sitting in my room and I smelled that I would want it.
Like if we get the doctor in the doctor's office and if I smelled pizza, I'm going to be like,
holy shit, doc, you got pizza in here? Yeah. Would you want a slice? Of course. Like it doesn't matter
where you are. Okay. Imagine you went for like just a routine checkup for the doctor and they came in
with like a little paper plate and a slice of pizza on it. And they were like, you want this?
I would eat it. I'd be like, all right, well, a doctor is giving this to me. I would definitely
eat it. Like if this was a random person on the street and they were just like, hey, you want a
slice of pizza? No, I don't know what the fuck you are. Get away from me. You're just a random
person. I don't know. You might be a doctor. I don't know. If a doctor is handing you a slice
of pizza, it's probably going to be okay. At least that's what I would think. He's already
examined it to make sure there's no, like nothing on it, nothing wrong with it. It's actually the
only way American doctors could administer. Wait, what? I didn't even say what you said.
All right. So how do I get in here? It has drugs in it. I just, what did I just turn on?
Something upstairs? I don't see a door over here. I hear lots of, I hear lots of mouth noises.
All right. I think it's up. It's just chat's mouth breathing. Not a big deal. We're fine. Get
away. It was sushi here at her. Now I want pizza. Oh yeah, guys. All right. Let's break this down.
Where am I? Where am I getting pizza from? Where should I get pizza from? What's like a pizza place
that you guys love? Get the whopper. I'll do that tomorrow. I promise I will do that tomorrow.
That's happening to on tomorrow's stream. I promise. What the hell are they doing to this guy?
That didn't kill you. How? This does not look comfortable. Um, that guy, his head just snaked
around. I don't think so. Get out of here. Oh, is he dead? Oh, that's not, that's bad. Oh, get
him down. I have to like blows. I have to blow them up. That didn't even work. Whatever. Okay.
Um, okay. So what do I do now? Just go up. Okay. Just order from a pizza place. It'll be 20 times
better than the main chains. I hear dog. Oh, don't run. What? They fucking good calzones water. What
is it? What is, what is water street pizzeria? Water street pizzeria. I don't even know what
that, what the fuck is that? They have really good council. I don't know what that is. Or please go
to Freddy Fazbear's. That's not a real place. I think they're chasing me down the stairs.
Nope. Chuck E cheese. I actually could go for a Chuck E cheese pizza right now. That's weird
for me to say, but I don't even care. People are like, Oh man, Chuck E cheese pizza. It's so gross.
You know, do you hear that they like take pizza from other pizzas and put it in making a new pizza
and serve it to you? I don't care. I don't even care. I'll just give me that one. I could eat a
Chuck E cheese pizza right now. The whole thing. Why am I on fire? What do a pizza eating stream?
I would, I would, I would cut it. I'd get like one of those big pizza knives and just go,
I would actually ask the restaurant. I'd say, Hey, can you make me a pizza? Don't cut it though.
I want to cut it. Just give me the big circle with just the cheese and everything. I want to
be the one to cut it because I want to have to go like and put my hand down on the knife and go
like down. That's what I want. I'm so hungry now. What do I do? Damn it. I'm so hungry. I'm going
to have to get a streamer snack. I'm going to have to get a streamer snack. Hey, I'm on here.
Get out of here. What are you doing? I need a streamer snack. I need one right now.
All right. I'm going to get a streamer snack. Everybody relax. That was weird. How did you open
the door? Where the fuck did you come from? Did you just drink a bunch of stuff? This is like in
gremlins when they're just drinking all the potions in the scientist room. Would you wink
for us for a streamer snack? No, I'm just going to get some food. I'll be back. All right. Streamer
snack time. I'll be right back. I got some really, really bad news. I don't have any more
jerky sticks. I got to eat. I got to eat almonds. I got to get more jerky sticks. It's like my
favorite. I'm just going to eat almonds until I can't breathe anymore. I'm going to fill my
body with almonds. It's not funny about almonds. They were the most calorically dense snack.
They got a good amount of protein. They've got a ton of calories and they're really good for you.
If you really want to get filled up, have some almonds. I just fucking dropped a bunch of them
all over the ground. God, it's not a good streamer snack though. Plus, this is such a bad streamer
snack. What was I thinking? These are wasabi and soy sauce almonds and they have a film on them
and it's going to get all over my hands. Look at it. It's already happening. They have this
Cheeto dust on them. I fucking hate when people watch me eat. I just picked up two of them and
now I can't even play the game anymore. I don't want to put my hands in my mouth because somebody
will clip it and they'll enhance it and they'll make it huge and they'll use it somewhere. I don't
want you to do that. Look, this is ridiculous. I just took another handful out. This is ridiculous.
That's ridiculous. It's all over my hands too. I need a strategy. What's the strategy here?
You didn't see that. Use a fork and knife? A fork and knife. A fork and Nike. Yeah, you hold it with
the fork and step on it and it'll grind it up and you can eat it. Hold on, give me a second.
Pour them into a cup. Wow, you're a fucking genius. Too late. Too late. Who goes over there?
Good dog. All right, one more handful and I'll play. You hear how crunchy these are? I don't want
it to pick up on the mic. I'm trying to make it not happen. Almonds taste like shit. What do you
think tastes good? If you don't like a roasted salted almond, what tastes good to you? If that
person writes, well, you know, acid, battery acid, oil, like car oil, dog food. Like, okay, well,
I get it. That's why almonds have cyanide in them. Good. How much cyanide are in these? How much
cyanide? Tell me. Tell me about the cyanide. Delicious cyanide. I feel not good.
Did you guys hear the crunch? Auto slug. I feel so much better. I just took in like 700 calories
in almonds. I may as well turn on fucking superpowers. No pizza? Later. It's already
fucking greasy on here. Where do I go? Can you make an Overwatch reference? Sure. I can't do
anything yet. All these bird seeds are gonna come out of my mouth and people are gonna be disgusted.
I can't do anything yet. I didn't even get a drink either. What a fucking amateur. I can't
shoot through like the chain link fence. Okay, that was delayed. Healing potion. Healing potion.
Get them. Look, it is desynced. I'm still eating these. It's taking forever. I promise I have teeth.
This is different. Boss fight. Boss fight. Washing his hand? Washing his hands with gloves on?
He just ate these almonds. I want a couple more. No, I can't talk. Almonds. Let's go. Look at this
paintball arena. I wonder what happens here. What are you gonna do? Nut tear list? I already did it.
All right. Here we go. Let's go. Fight. Fight. Fight. He's gonna show up. He's gonna
come down. Defeat the replica soldiers. Imagine seeing that when you open up the fucking thing.
Nut tear list. I already did one. I did it already. I think I put um... What was number one? I actually
don't remember. What did I put at number one? What was it? Ow. I have no grenades, huh?
It was boppities. Yeah, I know. I remember. I remember that. Boppities. So is he controlling
this? Is this the AI director? Oh boy. It's like a second delay. Actual delay. There's no delay.
I'm not an idiot. You can't pull a fast one on me. I'm sorry. It's not gonna work.
Show me the clip. Show it to me. Not that one. What was that? You just kicked me like...
What was that? You just kicked me like... What am I looking at here? What was that? You just
kicked me like... What was that? You just kicked me like... What was that? I don't get it. That was
matched up fine. There's nothing coming out of that one. What the fuck? When that thing fell,
was that somebody in there? It's like a guy in the porta potty and it tipped over.
Please help. It stinks in here. Get me out of the fucking porta potty.
No, it's one of those porta potties. It was at a goddamn outdoor live concert.
What's going on? Did I win? I won. Shoot and make a noise at the same time.
Oh. She's clipping that to me right now. Do it right now. I want to see it right now.
What I just did. I want to see it. Yeah. Somebody show that to me. Bullshit.
No, this is not even the right clip. I want to see the one I just did. Not scary. This is not it.
This is the wrong one. There it is. Give me. Give me. Give me. Give me. Give me. Give me. Give me.
Webcam is delayed. Yeah. You would know. All right. So here we go. And if anybody talks...
After we watch this clip, if anybody talks about there being an audio delay,
you're going to get timed out for 200 days. Okay. I'm glad we have an understanding. Find out.
Let's find out. Shoot and make a noise at the same time.
It's fine. What's wrong with it? I don't see the issue. Okay. Wait. You're talking about my...
The FPS is a little slower. The video is not delayed. It's like a 20 FPS because the camera
sucks. Here. Ready? Let's see if I can fix this. I don't think you guys even really care either.
I feel like this is just a way to get me to stop playing the game and do something else
to like fucking burn time. How's this? That's better, right? Better. Fixed. It's just the FPS.
I turned the FPS up. I wanted to slow the FPS down because I got a 1080 and my 1080 sucks
and it's burning out. It smells like burning plastic in here. I know it doesn't. I'm kidding.
All right. Seeing the national anthem to prove it's fixed.
Oh, you joker. All right. Let's go. How do I leave? One of these open? Can I go down?
The one that fell over, right? Can I go down one of these?
Is there a door opener? Am I missing something? There we go. National anthem. Oh my god.
Oh, say can you see by the dawn's early light What so proudly we hailed
At the twilight's last gleaming Whose broad stripes and bright stars
Through the perilous night O'er the ramparts we waved
At the twilight's last gleaming And its red glare
The bombs bursting in air Gave proof through the night
That our flag was still there. Oh, shit. Oh, say does that star
I have ADHD. I can't complete it. You know how hard it is to sing the national anthem
like in front of people. I get it now. You know, people just like I was coming out of the bathroom.
You know how people like just they mess it up all and it's like, well, how did you mess that up?
It's actually like when you're in front of a bunch of people you have to like kind of remember
and there's like two major breaks in the national anthem that you think it's going to be when the
rocket's red glare but it's not that point yet and you get caught you're like oh there's another
verse right shit what about canada sure oh canada our hearts and sacred lands shrews
one space well and all thy sons command through glowing hearts we see thy stone
the true north young and free while sloppy joes our food we eat our sunshine shines on thee
god i don't know i don't live in canada this rush that was correct
that was correct i might even give you guys a chance how about russia i don't know any i
don't know russia at all but what england i have no idea i don't even know how the english
uh anthem starts is it god save the queen god save the queen i don't know i reload that's the
whole thing the two people here what about the irish i don't know the irish anthem um
what the heck you know what eat this dick how about germany i don't know i don't know any other
national anthems still almonds stuck in my mouth like all the way you got okay listen to me you
guys ever eat something and it goes the food actually goes up here somehow it's up there
and i can't get it out it's stuck there forever it's like in my cheek pocket all the way up and
it's like up here in this little divot that's like up here in my mouth and stuck there forever
i'm gonna have to go and brushing my teeth is not gonna fix it i have to go and just like put a
bunch of water in my mouth and go like and then spit i got a big ass mouth guys you know that
that was a long jump is it not supposed to do that oh a proximity mine don't i have one you're
gonna regret saying that why i have a big mouth got a big mouth it is huge like if you were to
take like just a cut of this down like right here and like match it up to like steven tyler
you'd be the same image we both have like these big like steven tyler s kind of mouths all right
get me out of here i don't want to play this part i want the part with the girl screams in your face
get up here oh this game stinks play something else um i kind of want to beat this i feel like
i'm more than halfway through the game right now and i beat the first one so i can't give
up on the second one that's not how that's gonna work i have to jump on these or something to ride
one give up the game's only guys this game's only like six and a half hours that's too many
i feel like this should open but if you're but you're slow whatever i come streaming tomorrow
we're fine there we are he's never gonna play saw 2 why would i ever play the worst game i've ever
played on string that's that is by far the worst game i've probably ever played i was so angry with
that game i hate that game i hate that game that game was dog shit like i'm sorry i'm gonna have
to be real i did who did that nobody with a gun who has a gun over here that was weird looking
how did a bullet hole end up over there wait is this a different military it's like the military
too why are they fighting each other why are these guys fighting each other oh stop master chief
kind of all right get out well i want a proximity mine somebody oh canada
where's everybody from mostly north america right it didn't kill them what how tweed and finland
entucky well well where's it don't ever don't say it all at once who's okay press one if you are not
from north america or europe okay really that seems like a lot i lied oh europe is best um
i don't know they're all kind of cool there are that look everything's cool in its own way
everyone has their own cool things and cultures and and um and stuff and like food and traditions
and well they're all cool you you're a globalist oh you know um i think that like all the different
countries in the world they have different interesting things and uh the food and in
culture and it's just globalists but he he wants to have like one currency across the whole world
and then he also then he wants to he's this guy who definitely wants to eat all everybody's kids
i just i didn't say any of that you know you know japan probably sure has good food
this guy's coming he he wants us all to fucking wear all the same clothes and eat all the same
food and he wants us all to use the same money he wants it but it's gonna we're all gonna die
i have a trip maybe coming up soon to go there just kind of interesting to see what's there
oh what a beast he's a based liberal you don't know me you don't know who you don't know who i am
come in you don't know who i am i'm confused you didn't say you wanted to leave didn't you said
you said did you not say you wanted to leave the u.s wait what he's a communist that's it no more
talking no more talking everybody we're no more talking no i okay i let me say this again for the
everyone that said oh wait he must be a communist and i lost like i'm like a cryptocurrency stock
trader that lost his money you know what i mean like i'm you're talking to the guy that like
tried to bet against beyond meat do you think that's the communist he's a but he's a capitalist
he's wall street vets get him what do you mean get him oh really really you've seen an arm that
big before took a lot of pain to make it look like that i took a lot of squishing as hard as
i could up against my chest and popping out the muscle as hard as i could to maybe cause a problem
later now an hour or two from now and you want my political beliefs i'm gonna say them see if
you can lip read them i've never played wind waker before i've never played wind waker
you ain't missing anything i laughed because that guy's about to get like decimated i wasn't
laughing in an agreeance i was laughing in the dude you know i have to run down the street with
like the fucking crowd behind you and i'm just looking out the window through the blinds going
like oh that good that dude's fucked all right where am i going still up there by the way why is
there so much armor there's nobody even here oh automatic shotgun hell yeah auto shoddy play
wind waker i knew that was going to be a problem all right what what do i do here am i missing
something oh this is like an elevator what's wrong with me what am i doing up can i go up top
auto shoddy yeah that's what i said i'll look at it i will just give me a sec my eyes are like
oh they look watery this is a gorillas photo i've seen it stop playing this 1.5 billion we want saw
two it's not gonna happen no i would i would rather you fucking like punch me in the stomach
as hard as you could and play saw two deal no that's not a deal no that's not that imagine
lining up like being at twitchcon i have like a booth at twitchcon it's just like punch me in
the stomach and i've been one of those like old timey like spandex outfits the dude that got
used to the cannonball used to shoot the guy in the stomach i honestly have no idea where the
hell i'm supposed to go i don't see any like doors or anything down or some up can i spin this where
do i go i would not do that because your body is being held together with tape and dreams
fuck this game hold on wait i know i know i know i gotta find a way i'm let me let me pay attention
hold on i have so many of these items but there's nothing to use them on this room like didn't spawn
enemies i don't know um i got an auto shotgun in here and then it was like okay now come up here
and then there's nowhere else for me to go like climb this i would think up there but can i get
up there um this guy's got a few screws loose yeah i know read the lore read the fucking lore
find a lift this kind of looks like a lift oh play this game play that game play this game play that
game play this game i will i'll play your favorite game at some point maybe
maybe what's wrong malfunction hydraulic pressure is low what are you talking about now all of a
sudden this why are they all here now what wolverine origins i know i'm gonna play wolverine
origins i promise i will play wolverine origins for at least one hour when i come back after the
new year's eve stream i will play for at least one hour really i gotta do this like four or five
times huh that game is really good i know don't i'm i know i'm trust me i'm gonna do it what
happened sly cooper i'll play sly cooper when i get a new playstation what is wolf what is origins
on what's wolverine origins on is it ps3 oh well i guess i could play it then couldn't i what the
fuck is that thing what's he doing whoa why is it not working on him anymore g mouth what did he
what did he get hit by oh i can't hurt him okay i need him i need mines
anymore mines proximity mine okay cool what okay hold on i don't think i can kill him new deal new
deal new to read the deal wait oh just open the things and who cares just fucking get them open
he's actually angry i'm not actually angry i'm sort of angry he's pretending he's got it he's got
that tuber face all right wait that didn't even do anything oh fuck you what i went up like six
inches and jumped off new deal i thought this deal was off the table i thought you guys said no
game sucks turbo for the love of god oh nice wait come here do you see that they're like that was
so cute have you dealt you wait you want me to shoot the rat time that person out for like 30
seconds you know where you are you know where you are right now we don't hurt rats here we look at
how cute they are and we let me love them okay let's go to the uh point we're gonna go up look
there he goes there he goes you just try he just look he did look for some snacks nowhere uh okay
well see you later that make like a scary sound why does it make such a scary noise
oh it's a lady the lady the lady the lady where is she raid raid we got a raid was raid raided
oh shit hold on i don't even see it who raided us i can't even where's raid happy hop the happy hop
oh shit what's up dude thanks for the raid welcome everybody happy hot this this is the guy that
like doesn't get hit ever raid song raid song oh there you go he actually does get hit
unlike you no that's what hey what's up thanks for the raid welcome everybody no that's that's
sick we're playing fear 2 uh my name is germa if you don't know who i am i'm glad you don't
because you're probably gonna leave i start singing the canadian national anthem no thanks
thanks hub can i call you hub can i call you hub can we cool now can i call you hub
he just writes no dude like don't fucking say that all right chapter four i'm unraiding you
this is kind of ridiculous oh wait i thought they oh wait no no this is from
i didn't slow it down damn it she must be pissed what was that but was the person working on the
ceiling holy shit i'm detecting a huge power level oh wow padlocks i don't even need to read
that it's in every video game just shoot them body ama no give me the auto shotgun and the body
ama for the love of god this game sucks hold on relax there's a hide in the dumpster this guy
think he's at work what that guy died like three times um he reanimates people with his like
reanimation gloves why's he a briefcase is he supposed to have a briefcase oh shit got him
well that's a new enemy type cool all right let's keep going this game is intriguing it's so
intriguing cool the heck remember you got trolled i know it happens uh threat nobody cares electricity
guy what was that right in my face here it comes oh is the door closing but whatever get up it's
slimer it does sound like slimer is he going into the paintings um okay i'm just gonna you know what
just go get away from me just let's everything have to break in this game every building collapses
everything explodes him alan i keep missing the shit it's pissing me off objective find snake
fist okay i'll try is snake fist the huge guy is that a friend oh this was a plane uh this
was playing crash all right this kind of looks like resident evil this is resident evil vibes
oh come on stop focusing on me there's a this monster behind you fuck off all right he's dead
clock tower who is shooting at me i'll just i'll shoot all of you whatever now where oh i jump i
jumped over it that works oh there's so much more rare in this game have you noticed that
they're rare you don't get them that often
jesus who's got a grenade you okay drop it he still got it off dedication
oh nice it's all over me water is that gonna shock me
town npc being killed all right i got it what the hell is this boy this is a missile launcher
holy shit nice finally oh he's doing it too oh i feel like i just saw my future
whoa new weapon new weapon new weapon do them with the shoot him a new hold on wait hold on
wait forget about the link for a second i need new missiles it's a great deal all right yeah what
is it yet wiping deal if germa makes autos big adventure three uploads it to his main channel
and uses this thumbnail the entire debt is wiped bringing an explosive end to arguably the best
joke of the year i'll think about it i'll think about it if you have my attention i'll think
about it we'll see give me that get out of here that's it one more he's still alive don't you dare
wipe that debt without a dump truck emote hey i'm just going by what you guys are saying nothing
else got him germa lied about the court stream well germa didn't lie about the court stream
germa got denied at a bunch of courts to film a fucking comedy trial all right now where did we
go stop the deal stop the deal he said where'd i go i just ducked all right flamethrower sucks
let's be honest oh snipers i gotta go safer snipers no dump no deal a main channel upload
is big it is the main channel upload is pretty huge reach the new rally point why don't you run
towards it what are you doing no dump no deal no dump no deal fuck fuck no dump no deal no
dump no deal just wait i that's not that's not up to you that's up to the majority
wait who's a sniper sniper duel i cheated where is she where is she where are you
you where are you sniper nice ping yeah pretty good i don't see anybody else where
i got missing something what am i missing here what no dump i'm pretty good with a sniper you
guys have seen my videos i'm pretty good not the best not even great but good what i sure can
here we go i think i just hurt myself destroyed it this game sucks oh this perfect score is gone
maybe it's you that sucks that's true that you could be right it could be me doubt it big music
or i'm not sure yet really where's the other guy new deal hold on stop stop stop stop stop
should go to brazil all right what they didn't hit be them what doesn't even matter what weapon
look at this dude is fucking on fire just electro shoot that guy yeah i drive the car come to brazil
i don't know whatever maybe wait what did i say i said oh i don't know i don't have any plans to
go to brazil but i if i was ever there i'm sure i'd be like all right cool i'm in brazil
should i go up he just promised we have another good deal in chat are you sure when should he's
come visit me i have a good store in a good view i mean a good store in a good view i don't know
what you mean oh fuck don't let him get in wait am i gonna get in that i'm gonna get in this
okay this does this count as a letter grade i think this counts fire missiles dm return of the dmt
robot no i don't this is not d this is no this is just like an artist rendition of the dmt robot
not the same thing it's just it's not it am i stepping on people what was that that was like
the slime sound from nickelodeon where do i go dude i can't see shit right now i think i'm going
this way press v whoa no i don't like that i'm not doing that again yeah this is not as cool as
dmt robot what's so i'm so brainy i can't tell i'm supposed to go yeah no i i understand the
resident sleepers i get it so i get it i understand them give me dump or give me death that guy right
now is like he got out of the armor oh my god this is my chance is he gonna get in the armor
actually stole it that would be so funny this game would get a full letter grade if he stole that
don't do that all right now we're gonna open the door do a ps2 tech demo i actually have some
a 3do disc i have one of the 3do uh like demo discs i think i'm still gonna play more 3do
there's still a shit load of stuff to do missile launcher this thing lore all right how do i get
the door open 3do yeah we'll go back to the 3do at some point soon get back in let's go get back in
like gex i played gex already and i didn't i was fun it was fun i can't wait to eat a pizza
i'm gonna get a large pizza from somewhere i don't know where oh shit we're gonna do a fight here
i get him morning morning morning morning this is seriously i feel like i'm playing this
through somebody else's stream i'm like the lowest quality settings all right all right all right
all right get out i'm watching this on an old tv what the fuck is happening it's movie night in
the fucking 80s hey just just wiggling around a little see if we can get the fucking pay-per-view
channels robocop's on tonight i can't handle this much more i gotta get out of this thing get me out
get me out of this thing right now eject get eject eject eject ah how do i eject i'm sorry
i'm turning it off what the fuck was that oh what do i do oh it's a locked door okay thank god
griffin report yeah it's me uh peter griffin report again uh there's a crazy lady trying to
attack me wouldn't that be great i move this no i'm stuck here i wanted to help that guy
okay oh there's stokes all right let's go back up i'm sorry sorry i held a grenade down
i was trying to cook it in time in time to throw at the lady it's my bad griffin dead
say it it sounds like this sounds like what's his name oh my god the guy from sausage party
what's his name he's a famous actor what's what's the guy's name
it should be just what's his name seth rogan yes this happens she's just like seth rogan
the guy from sausage party really i don't know i don't i can't remember anything
we're gonna be fine you and me don't worry i'm the grenade guy how many grades do you have how many
grades have you thrown yeah i'm the wild one are you walking towards this you might be a good shot
but i blow shit up can i kill you sure to pick it up all right you're unkillable is it good to know
all right come on where we going how do we leave follow me all right guys just get us out of here
sergeant shit was pretty fucked up we're stuck in the middle of it this thing's gonna blow up
and flip over and we're gonna have a bunch of problems you shook up like this she killed
griffin alma you know the name i don't think we didn't know that i thought
pissed off dead chicks is a little outside my area of expertise let's focus on finding
is he gonna shoot her this will go faster if we split up keegan how's that wound
you positive you're up for this nothing i can't handle what about us then you're on recon don't
go picking any fights beckett you're with me good stokes i cannot wait to watch your skin and
muscles get ripped off and turned into a skeleton in about five minutes looking forward to it
stokes you and me i know i know what it looks like all right beckett let's go find snake fist
chapter five provocation key rent teacher con fry noon dismissal third no school bunday
all right let's go seth rogan come on none of these open
guess we're not getting in that way no yeah i'm sure there is let's try to look around the back
follow me over here you definitely could maybe get in through here can we get through this lock
i can't shoot the lock let's try um through this way is there a window we can climb in let's check
and see i don't think there is stokes can we just drive that through the front door i don't
understand why we can't we have a tank just shoot a missile into it yeah you definitely go this way
can we can i can you like give me like 10 fingers so i can jump up it's definitely over there the
hell what's 10 fingers and you lift the person's shoe up what's the great over there by the wall
take a look look great where am i oblivious i know keegan we're heading inside the school
all right let's go me and you let's have some fun watch out there's things in here there's
gonna be a monster in here watch out you good careful watch out for the glass
yeah i never did quite well in school i did pretty bad in like math and stuff
how about you did you do good in school well i'm well we're in the same room so it's okay
there's a ghost in here did she actually fight remember you're firing that weapon
no i this is where i get what this does like monsters i'll let you do the honors hit this
punch it like this remember you're firing that weapon i know i'm firing the weapon i know what
i'm holding it find something damn it i missed it that was such an opportunity and i just i blew
it so bad ow fucking ears did i get lost oh come on i got lost i do i'm coming back i'll find you
i can just keep talking up i'll be able to find you sing us a song okay no no more singing no more
singing i'm too hungry to sing i'm too hungry to make any singing songs but if i can play the
tambourine i will aim is a zero he's got the munchies so bad bro i mean yeah but nothing to
do with smoking any marijuana shut up uh where do i go i think it just went in a complete circle i
did he's getting bored but i'm yeah the last game really carried itself with being able to laugh at
the guy saying oh shit every time it slowed down we we like looked over a fear well fear one was
actually pretty good though oh okay right i genuinely thought fear one was a pretty good
game there's nothing wrong with this one this the games this game's not bad it's just um not
very good it's not bad it's not great it's not terrible it's just kind of it's just kind of a
game i get hit by a chair hey hey get off me i just see her sometimes just randomly
okay i'm just gonna run let's just get through this stokes stokes what am i supposed to do
something here what who's down here you're in big trouble i got a missile launcher what's that
that was like reinforcements i gotta get this gun out of here i'm out of ammo for everything
watch out watch out watch out watch out watch out watch out watch out watch out watch out watch out
all right okay where's my uh teammate where'd the teammate go she's gone i need to replace this
with uh i'll give you that i need ammo dude this game is a lot more burning to death than the other
one did yeah it does it has a lot i don't know it kind of just i don't know that fear one's way
better dollars to it it's really all those through it nothing much to it did you already forget you
got separated yeah but i'm trying to when are we gonna see her i don't think most people what's
wrong don't most people think fear one was the only good one yeah stop what the fuck is going
on here i can't go just jump across it that's my fault oh jesus what the hell i have to fight one
of these things here i have two missiles how am i gonna destroy this i can't kill this how am i
supposed to kill this ow ow fuck fuck fuck you have to use your muscles i mean those are big so
i'll be okay i think okay hello i got a question about the fear franchise so fear one was made and
then they like didn't they outsource fear two and fear three what was the point of having what was
the point of that how would you outsource the next two games in the franchise you made yeah i think i
like this studio though i think this is a really good studio this is the um the guys that made uh
the lord of the rings games the shadow of war and um what was it the other one nothing else of war
yeah it's monolith yeah they're they're a good studio and commit 10 community subs
10 community subs just coming in hot thank you to uh nuclear waffle appreciate it thanks to the
10 subs is this a fear online i don't what i don't know why you do that though okay go
they made condemned condemned is fantastic condemned is probably one of the best first
person games ever it's just so it's like so fun that's one of the best like 2000s era kind of
games isn't it another 10 subs wait whoa whoa whoa hold on a second hold on hold on a second
what what is going on right now just give some john cena is killed gave hold on a minute this
is too many subs wait a second kill him before he kills me okay hold on hold on hold on hold on
wait wait wait john cena is kill gave 10 nuclear waffle gave 10 and then decided to
they were going to do 50 uh hopefully that was not a misclick with your finger
because it's 60 fucking community subs thank you nuclear waffle that's insane and it's still
going west west yule gave 10 kaiser yasawa gave five john cena gave another 10 and artichoke
just gave five too what's happening right now why is it happening i didn't i haven't said the word
i haven't said the p word all day matt matt r aus thanks for the 10 community subs jamie thanks for
five gave me 2803 this is okay this just decided to start happening yeah i didn't say the p word
i didn't say that i didn't say the s word either well thank you guys that's a lot of that's an
insane amount of money thank you i don't i don't know what to say i don't know where this is even
coming from hog don't care thanks for five community subs vander thanks for van dread
thanks for five hack it fast thanks for five bingo thanks for five tona thanks for five
holy shit all right this is getting out of hand this is getting out of hand i'm gonna have to come
with a distraction thank you all of you though seriously that's completely unnecessary but
thank you it's a lot of money 486 dicks three no 486 dx megahertz thank you for the five thank
you pink goat for the five community subs thank you frank the gank for the five community subs
uh natalie watson thanks for the five community subs john cena is back again with another five
community subs okay uh rat gal five community subs all right i gotta i gotta pivot us i gotta
get us i gotta get us away from this uh i gotta get us away from this this it's happening this is
too much um rat gal thanks for five parmigiano thanks for five um have i told you about kill
it's pretty good this is old i don't want to drink that thank you kip for the five thank you rye or
art for the five rye or art fiblis thanks for five nuclear waffle thanks for five this is too much
this is that control i don't know what to do i gotta go off camera i don't know what to do i'll
be back i don't know what to do ruined bloodline five community subs i have two this is too many
triad five shrek five shrekanen where did this even come from why did this even start happening
billy mays three thanks for five community subs i don't even know how this started where does it
come from rip kit fisto gave 20 community subs what are you guys doing this is ridiculous that's
20 from rip kit fisto five from retro specter five from antique mango five from cherry rolet
five from cobalt custard five from razlik corkin i um well i'm not i'm i'm gonna be getting a
mcdonald's meal tonight i'll tell you that holy shit guys i don't know what the hell is going on
but i don't know where this came from but thank you uh j double y 10 community subs i can't even
read them this is fucking insane sean mussels five five from zigsy five i'll get him i'll get him
cods thanks for five i'm being electrocuted who's screaming what happened to that guy
james wolf 1759 thanks to the five five from dorambor five from all knees thanks for shrekin
in front of the five i don't know what the hell you guys are doing all right that's enough no more
no more no more no more no more that's okay that's enough no more you don't have to do anymore that's
enough we don't have to do anymore eight bit zig thanks for five snake mcmahon thanks for five
we don't have to do anymore we don't have to do that was very nice of you guys thank you
uh adrian thanks for five john cena another five you know all right we're done okay well that's
enough that's enough that's too many that's enough that's enough i commanded thank you seriously guys
i don't even know where they came from they came out of nowhere and i don't even know why
i don't know why some of you guys give this channel money like i can't even think about it
it's like just ridiculous am i getting hit by the blade d superman i can't even read them alpha
dr woolley sam the bass man konzin gave 20 ton ton i gave five this is like 500 to a thousand
like right now stops repaying the debt thank you otter pup for the five holy shit guys
i just started firing no no don't pull my skeleton off demon dude legionnaire captain dark 10 frisky
moose 10 auto pop five holy shit well this uh i think you guys have you guys are too much
i don't i don't deserve this thank you thank you young slap with five i thought it worked
you come with me they kill that guy
googly gareth five subs what's up googly does anybody have any idea how many chapters are left
in the game mellow mute 10 community sub i we might be approaching all time high here um and
that's i don't even know what happened i didn't do anything somebody just gave subs and it just
started it just kept happening thanks guys this is too much what just happened behind me
thank you uh mellow mute again for 10 thank you ruined for five sweaty greasy man for five
let's vibe check i mean i'm i'm i'm vibing right now what does that word mean what does it actually
mean force 10 thanks to the five it means feeling good oh okay yeah i feel pretty good i actually
feel really great right now who did that who did that oh it's one of these bad guys how much
healthy you have a skyrocket dog thanks for the five computer d subs all right this guy
is not dying a greater est dane thanks to five communities so i've been just reading
community stuff they're just never ending but thanks guys oh somebody's behind me cry cry cry
cry cry no no crying i don't need to cry sing the sub train song cry cry i'm not gonna cry
hey warm prince thanks for five fucking cry now tj rich thanks for five subs dude what is this
hammerhead oh can't shoot doof soup five make him cry i'm not gonna cry i'm just gonna be very very
shocked and um i don't know you guys this channel sees like a lot of money and it's
i don't know thank you guys i just i don't know i just want to be like a money stream
like a money streamer which is like oh yeah thanks i got like fucking all the fucking two
three thousand subs came in today thanks but thank you though seriously i almost missed that one
rarity is rarity is best pony 15 community subs best pony uh no sorry star scream is the best
you're wrong but thanks for the 15 subs where did i go this is overwhelmed oh right here inside i'd
like to walk the freezer what's this spam you deserve this uh hold on what is this this is like
a this is like a what is this coffee pasta you deserve all this we love you a bunch thanks for
all the content you make for us all these shitty games you play hey thanks for playing all these
shitty games uh i've got nothing to you and you can bet it'll never go away thanks for all you
do you're awesome cool most importantly your gerber 985 best streamer on this shitty platform
oh jesus oh my god um yeah thanks this shitty platform well i'll be around for a while well
i'm gonna be around as long as i can so thank you guys please keep me honest i hope you do
possible what based on what based on what
i like this gun who's next right now this guy
oh man how are you still shooting me oh you possibly concentrate on aiming down
sites with an eye you don't have thank you shrek and again for five more subs and thank you nick
for five subs too oh no that was 10 subs holy shit medic bow it actually is yeah they got to
say a bunch of animal names he went donkey frog walrus cry cry speech cry you guys the toilet i
got you wait do i have a face yeah it's gonna scream at me i know you're i know somebody in
here is screaming me oh my god waffle nuclear waffle what on earth are you doing this is so
much money to give at one point this is too much school's out that's another 50 subs dude
i hope you can afford it it's a lot of money that's an extreme amount of money thank you
that's what at least a couple hundred over 100 over to almost 200 i can't even keep track it's
been so much oh i have to look at this what time is it on that clock eacher what is talking this
thing has an audio card the face cam back on oh shit sorry vacuum it's not a vacuum you got it
wrong it's a swing set wrong again brain wrong football player who is talking fawn thanks for
the five and alpha thanks to the five community subs as well back to back thank you guys make
him cry i'm not gonna cry i'm i'm not even crying uh mood right now who did that i think i shouldn't
walk up here will that happen i think i just jumped over her attack cutscene that's her right
there he's too happy to cry no i'm just i'm in a good spot right now you know what i mean i feel
pretty good he's too rich to cry thank you lgbt rex thank you he's wiping his tears with his
dollars no no i hope you guys don't ever think that i let's be real i really that's not i hope
you guys never think anything like that he's a capitalist though
what happened this felt weird let's keep going to the bathroom over and over again
no oh wait look if you want to see lighting that shows different lighting from oh ugly boy
ugly boy there is this side here's this side here's the front top here's the bottom
okay i've got deep set eyes so when light it light from the bottom hits the top of my uh
nasolabial folds that's not what that is what is that that's here what is that called what is that
actually called this what's it called what did i just say nasolabial folds right i'm sweating
right now why do you look you're a neanderthal i have i have a brow look i have high big cheek
bones and high big brow bone and like a big chin so yeah i mean my eyes are set in a little deep
why is this turning purple yeah that's every angle of my face now you can say you've seen it
he's right this is not in the script like i'm not gonna hide anything from me there's no filter on
this fucking camera this is a real this is what this is what real this is what a real boy looks
like okay there you wanted it you got it i hate when there's this much light on my face that's
better i like being in the darkness like a fucking goblin you look like my grandma
i probably do that's like the funny part naked grandma get away from me
oh shit i feel like i'm about to turn this guy on that guy looks like frankenstein
fine
then that's what's that's a christmas song what christmas song is that called carol of the bells
yeah that's the one um over here um maybe how do i get up there you look like what do a family guy
reference why do you want me to do a family guy reference look at your hair that's grandma hair
that actually kind of was yeah this is this is the grandma hair of the person that like
checks every egg in the carton and then puts it back and then checks the next carton and
checks all the eggs i don't know nothing about this right this i don't like the way this got
spots on it let me tell you where to go stop showing your hairline it's really not that bad
it isn't it's not this is what i got it's i mean it's it's going it's not that bad it could be
worse hey you guys forget how old i am some of you guys just don't remember
some of you guys just don't even pay attention to how old i am you think that like oh that's
my hammerhead i'm not like 20 you know i don't know maybe you might have you might have some
favorite streamers on twitch that are like 22 i got more than a decade on these motherfuckers
and look at still good some people that you know stream on this platform they're like 19 they're
like 24 and i still act like a 20 year old so come on i didn't grow up yet probably should
but you know where do i fucking go my brain cannot focus we are where we dropping boys i
don't know tell me tell me where i'm dropping i don't know where to go i up here but how do i
even get up there it's a window by the vent why the fuck is this don't worry i got it i got this
stepped on it you know my favorite i love uh why are they fighting watch out what do you love um
oh right anytime i die you everyone knows that i have a second so i can pay attention to at
least something in chat and a wave of links just gets spammed updated debt wiping deal
okay same terms if german makes autos big adventure 3 up uploads it to his main channel
and uses that thumbnail the debt will be wiped bringing an explosive end to the best joke of the
year but hold on but there's an extra term added germa must add either germa sus or derma germa
dump truck i would rather have it be germa dump truck but naked then add germa sus but that's not
part of this deal that's not part of the deal that's just how i that's what i said that's not
that's not part of the deal though i need to get like a brush i've been like fucking with this so
much deal deal deal what time is it what am i gonna stuff screaming i don't know
who's shooting walk over that right now walk over that oh fuck you laughing my ass off
laughing my ass off wait he's counting down with his friend okay man we're gonna do this three
two one i opened the door voltage all right factor back to admin nobody say it i know we're going
back to admin just somebody sells it admin the whole time all right this is where i can't go
have to go back to admin am i am i finally gonna get to kill this guy like am i finally gonna get
to like murder this dude that door is locked what about this one locked all these doors are locked
all right so what if i go dude you know what i'm gonna do tonight oh shit listen to this i'm gonna
do a face scrub tonight that sounds pretty sick doesn't it you said no do it now i might you know
you know i don't like this game because this game has like this weird one hidden door you have to
go into i don't like it they tried to make this a horror game and it's not i mean it's not even
scary why do they make it like this why they do this i'm not scared of what it was down here are
you serious i don't know where i'm going this is not a hard can i turn like the turn turn the lights
back on so brave so strong i'm not i don't claim to be strong or brave i claim to be right
what's the lady's name from um here's a story of a man named brady and he had his three children of
his own what's the lady's name in that mrs mrs brunch right that's not mrs brunch bunch brady bunch
not mrs brunch that's a pretty sick name here's the story of mrs brunch clean your face up i'm
i'm going to i did this and i'm gonna leave it like that because i don't even care i don't even
care dude i don't care if like my hair looks stupid who cares now i know why i got tommy whistle
it's becoming pretty clear now how do i leave can i get out of here get out
get out just get away from me get away from me get away from me get away from me get away from me
and what in the morning my face is oh that's american psycho i can't even see i can't even
tell what way is the right way to go everything just looks very similar and like it's flashing
is one of the charlie brown adults talking what the hell is going on
all right i've almost had enough i'm so close to the end of the game too
what am i hitting end of the stream i'm so close to the end though i know i'm like an hour away
finish it hold on what the fuck happened to that guy all right no more saying the f word if i say
fuck one more time and i will give myself a face scrub i'm throwing guns on the ground
all right i i keep asking this and i just don't look at the chat how many chapters are in this
game what's like the actual chapter count i've made it so much worse five seven chapters what
are we on now five or six i think that was the general oh i need a security key stupid siri
unlock how many phones did i just unlock imagine if that worked siri unlock unlocking phone good
thing that's not a good that's not a feature stop dude my phone's going nuts do a coin flip i'm
bored okay mods can we get a coin flip prediction in chat please that would be pretty cool here we
go i would put big money on this one we got it's gonna be heads it's not i'm on mobile oh um well
i think i can i do it how do i do it prediction hold on i think i can do it what's what do we want
oh i want i want to do a coin flip i don't have the power to do it well how was it happening before
i wasn't doing it before here it comes let's go make this a big one i want five million five
million on each side if it were me i would say it's probably gonna be i'm gonna bet on heads
i would say heads that's me but who are you 3.3 million versus you guys are gonna lose all these
points this is millions okay let's see it 6.5 to six it's pretty even yeah but someone's gonna
win all those points oh shit they are okay i need a key or something right haircut well we got time
we'll check it in a minute let me wander around aimlessly to find the one item i need to progress
through this game information it was like a key or in like the register's office or something
right i thought that was a grenade where is this key nurse's office right i don't know
i have no idea like i don't have a single goddamn clue where's my the principal's office
teacher's lounge just flip it already you will run here comes congratulations to
don't yawn don't yawn don't yawn on stream that means that you ever you're
tired and the game's boring what was it it was congratulations to
you me because i stole them all dude this guy in here is not vibing with me okay
what was it i don't know what was the outcome i'm done with this game i don't know i'm done playing
it uh what was the outcome i have to flip a coin oh okay you i have to do it i don't have a coin
um i have something i can flip how about this um okay i have a i have a heal cap if it's up
its tails if it's down its heads okay do it on google no i don't care no don't no do it on
google what the okay all right all right hold on i'll do it oh okay we're ready coin flip flipping
the coin the coin is tails i have to show the screen it was tails why would i lie about this
why would i oh guys i'm a liar i want to just just screw over everybody that like picked
heads show it if i show it now people are gonna think i cheated that's why i want to do the
heal cap and you wouldn't let me hold on this dog over here all crimes are absolved wait did they
did they do it yet did they do it yet they did it go through yet or no are we holding it still
okay hold on to it um i'm gonna go get a coin i'm gonna go get a real coin i'll be right back
look at some artwork for a second we'll just i rl for a few minutes i'll be back okay i got
the coin make sure you approve it's a real coin here you go okay you ready real coin real dog
here see i'm not putting i'm not gonna put that in my mouth you guys ready and i go like this
people are gonna be people are gonna be really mad at me it's heads but tails was the first one
what if i do it okay what if i do it a third time and this is the real one
okay don't bet on anything on this channel ever because i'm always gonna do something like this
what if it's the real one um no but that but one of the first one was tails the second one was
heads is there something else we can do that's 50 50 all right send it back send all the points
back cancel it just send all the points back send all the points back we'll do what do we know
send the points back this instant immediately oh i'm gonna be this is gonna be bad for me
send those points back right now i'm sending them how do i i'm gonna send the points back how do
i send them back what's the command to send points back we got them back get them back please okay
are they back they're back i did it all right okay hey welcome to the casino it's time for us to play
50 50 what's on what side of the coin is on you wouldn't put any money at all up on this table now
imagine you won like blackjack oh uh but hold on the dealer wasn't looking uh that one didn't
count and then you did it again and you got you like lost that wouldn't count either well what
does count this is the real one i got the coin here do the coin flip let's start it activate
activate the coin flip right now okay here it comes what do you think it's gonna be
what do you think it's gonna be here's time for you to predict those points let's go i'm gonna sit
oh here it goes ready predictions started what do you think it's gonna be when i flip this coin
don't do it yet hold on don't do it yet they haven't even predicted nobody's even bet any
money i haven't um you see my hand that was it it's going down it's i have it in the exact
spot i wanted it's going down like that it's in the perfect spot in my hand you saw i flipped it
and i'm about to slap it down this is the exact spot that it's supposed to be in play dramatic
music i'm gonna get in trouble for this this is starting to get really really sweaty and wet in my
hand not a good feeling like i really want to let this go i really want to let this out of my hand
right now guys ready i'm not taking it out of frame okay what does everybody think it's a 12
million to 11.2 million for a coin toss bets are off here we go it's head prediction result is
congratulations for all the people that won 650 fucking million dollars who won the most
23 million goes to sticky brick how come sticky brick is always the first person up here
didn't they win weren't they in first place last time by the way just want to let everybody see
its heads on both sides it's a joke coin it's not let's transparency it's the look it's the
this is this is the same coin i made a like shitty twitter joke like four five years ago about i
still have this i said this was the mega zord all right i'll see you tomorrow i'm done hey this is a
long one went over four hours today but how fucking long that was all right i'll um i'll see you guys
tomorrow tomorrow stream is gonna be early very early like incredibly early earlier than than you
probably think it is we're gonna start tomorrow at like probably like i'm serious i'm not kidding
around probably like 10 11 o'clock in the morning so i'm going around like 10 to like 11 is when
we're gonna start pacific going very early that's my birthday well happy birthday right at the crack
of dawn that's right what are you saying ray ludwig you promised to last week yeah i did let's go
but we have to look at subs first because there was a shitload of subs it's just being scanned
there's so many names here there was so many subs almost breaking fucking the previous record
so thank you guys it's completely i never expect shit like this and i don't i sometimes i don't know
why how people still want to pay me this kind of money but um hopefully it's worth it i'll see you
guys tomorrow somewhere around probably 11 o'clock pacific we're only gonna stream we're probably
gonna stream for like maybe like three four hours or so just trying to get a lot of stuff done
i want to i doing a lot of stuff things are happening yeah we'll go uh we'll raid ludwig
what's he doing right now what is ludwig up to what are you doing ludwig let's see
he's doing serial tier lists oh shit are you kidding me i gotta look at this for a second
uh you click the subscribe button then you hit subscribe free super easy and uh and and yeah i'd
appreciate if you double check to see if you have a requirement if you use it regardless of who it
is does not have to be me i'll be perfect timing oh that is funny
just popping in seeing what he's up to you know and whatever any prime users
uh all right well but what's i want to see the cereals
that's so funny i can't get over that
all right let's go let's go say hello i want to see what the cereal is he's doing
e don't raid the e beggar no ludwig's fucking awesome how dare you speak of ludwig that way
i will uh i'll see you guys tomorrow have a good night we'll see you soon
wait hold on wait wait wait wait wait wait wait well hold on a second dude you said
neanderth just raided right now we got a neanderth raid right at the very end and now we're jumping
is that what happened are you guys baiting me all right well okay all right i just i thought
we were gonna go we're gonna do some bouncing like we did with uh with dunkey the other day
all right get that to 6k make me look good see you guys tomorrow