What is going on guys, Jerma here. I'm bringing you the new Team Fortress 2
update, the Mano Technology update. Huge, huge deal guys. The Engineer, the Sniper
and the Spy all got new awesome items. Gonna talk about them in brief detail
right now. Gonna show you them all. It's so exciting I can hardly contain myself.
Let's start off with the Engineer. The new shotgun is the Widowmaker. On hit
damage dealt is returned as ammo. No reload necessary. Minus 60 ammo per shot
and it uses metal for ammo. The new pistol is the Short Circuit. On fire generates an
electrical field that destroys projectiles and does slight damage to
players. No reload necessary. No random crits. Uses metal and it takes 35 ammo.
Ammo is metal guys, if you're wondering that. It's the 200 ammo you
get. You have to use that as your actual ammo. It's a very strange mechanic but
we'll get into that later. The Sniper got a new sniper rifle, the
Machina on full charge. 15% more damage done per shot and if you have a full
charge it can go through people. The big downside for this weapon guys is it
cannot fire unless it is zoomed and it fires tracer rounds. So no more no
scoping with the sniper rifle if you're going to use this and people are all
going to know where you are because it fires the tracer rounds. On to the Spy. He
got a ridiculous new revolver and a new hat which is actually kind of funny. The
diamond back gives one guaranteed critical hit for each building
destroyed with your sapper attached. Minus 15% damage done and no random
crits. So this is kind of a reverse frontier justice for the Spy. If you
destroy, it works on many sentries as well, so if you destroy a sentry with
your sapper you are going to get one crit and it stacks too. So like I said
it's kind of like the frontier justice for the Spy. I'll show you all these
items now in detail. Me playing with them. It's super exciting. I can't wait
to show you guys these things. They're all ridiculous. Oh the heavy by the way
got a new miscellaneous item but it doesn't matter. It doesn't do anything.
It's just kind of there for fun. Everyone got a new hat too. New sunglasses. New
new hat and stuff like that. It's kind of it's for the Deus Ex human revolution.
That new game that's coming out for the new Deus Ex series. You can get all these
items if you pre-order Deus Ex. The new Deus Ex game or you can find them in
drops and they are craftable. But I went ahead and I bought Deus Ex because I
wanted Deus Ex anyways. So let's get into this guys. Here we're going to start
with the engineer and the new engineer items. Let's start by saying that this is
a very very odd mechanic. Take a look at my ammo count down there. It takes 60
ammo to shoot it. You do not have a clip anymore. There's no reloading. There's no
reload time or anything like that. It's just 60 metal to shoot that gun and it's
35 metal to shoot the new pistol. Very very weird mechanic because you'll find
that you'll have no more metal left to shoot the gun and you're kind of just
like oh crap now what do I do. It's gonna take a lot of getting used to but for a
combat engineer this will be a awesome new item. Especially the new shotgun
because how many times have you been able to not place a mini sentry down
when you wanted to because it didn't have enough ammo or metal. See look at
my ammo count. 113.96. You shoot you lose but you gain. It's weird. And then this
new item here this new pistol it electrocutes people. It's very very odd.
Hopefully we can figure this all out guys in the near future in the next
couple weeks. It works on buildings as well. So if you shoot a building I
believe point blank it gives you let's see here I think it's I think it's 80 to
85 metal per point blank shot. So I electrocute this sniper. It's kind of a
weird mechanic. It's it's like a Tesla coil kind of and it spreads too by the
way. So if you electrocute somebody and there's a bunch of people around it will
hit every single person around there. This also destroys projectiles. The new
pistol. See how I shot that building? How I did watch a see? Plus 60 plus 60. If you
get close enough to people it's sort of like having infinite ammo and you never
have to reload. But the problem here guys is you have to be a good shot. If you
miss all the time if you're not good with the shotgun I do not recommend you
try and get this item because you will just lose metal over and over again. So I
get a little assist with that thing. It's very weird. See 60 60 60 80 80. It's very
very cool. See look at see how this thing is spreading. The electrical charge is
spreading around. Maybe it's a new spy check mechanic. Maybe you can check for
spies. I'm not sure yet guys. This is the first time I've ever played with it. Just
want to make sure I get you guys some cool gameplay with it. You see exactly
how the item works. I haven't tried to destroy any projectiles with it yet with
the with the pistol because I hadn't I didn't really have a chance to be honest.
So trying to get that to work I'm assuming that it's sort of like a
reflect. You just click it just you just click once and that's it. Let's
move on to the spy. This is really really cool. You'll see here I decloak next to
this sentry over here. It doesn't matter. Like I said it can be a mini sentry. It
can be a big sentry. Backstab the engineer. Put the sapper on and look at
the lower right. One crit I missed but it's okay. I just wanted to show you
guys how it all works. I actually do something pretty cool in a minute here. I
get a soldier. It works on mini sentries, big sentries. Doesn't matter as long and
it's an assist too. It'll work on assists too. So if you assist somebody in
destroying a sentry by putting a sapper on it you will get the crit. It just has
to be on the sentry. You see this mini sentry right here. Place the sapper on.
Did I get the kill? I did but that pyro actually helped me and I get the crit
kill. That soldier hundred and two damage. It is insane guys. I can see so many
people using this over the ambassador. I'm going to use this over the
ambassador now because it stacks. If you're a good spy you can potentially
hold three or four crits in this thing if you kill a couple mini sentries. On to
the sniper now. As you saw just headshot of that heavy and you saw the tracer
rounds. It's a direct line coming out of your sniper rifle right to where you are.
As you can see, see how it's still there after I shot the demoman. It lasts for
about one or two seconds. Not really that big of a deal but it kind of can be when
you're trying to be sneaky and trying to hide. People are going to see it. It's a
red flag. See right there? People know exactly where I am. Get a couple
headshots but the big deal about this sniper rifle guys is the fact that if
you make the charge go up to 100% it will do 15% more damage and it will go
through people. Now I don't really get to utilize it. I don't really get to show
you it going through people but you'll see how much damage it does with a full
charge shot. I believe it's 518 damage for a full charge headshot which is
insane but you got to remember guys a fully overhealed heavy is only 450
health. So this weapon if you fully charge and shoot somebody in the face
you're gonna be doing way too much damage. Way more damage than you ever
needed to do in the first place. Where this weapon is going to shine is if a
line of people are in a corridor and you body shot somebody and it goes through
four people. Another downside of this weapon though guys is you cannot no
scope. No scoping is disabled. If you try to do it it just makes a clicking
sound. So this weapon is really catering to bringing back the SMG. That's in my
opinion because you have no other option. You have to be zoomed in when you shoot.
So I think that this paired up with the SMG would be a very very good
combination. We'll see how things play out in the next couple weeks. If they
nerf, if they buff some of these items I have no idea. We will find out. But guys
thank you so much for watching. That's pretty much all I got. I wanted to really
rush this out and give you guys a really really good look at all the new items.
Hopefully you guys got a little bit information from it. I did from doing it.
So take care everybody and have fun with the new update guys. See you later.