my favorite song. I do need to change the title and this yeah the title doesn't make very much
sense right now does it getting to grandma's house does not make sense bust a groove there's also a
bust a groove 2 but i wanted to play bust a groove 1 to see if i should buy bust a groove 2 keep this
keep it just keep this getting grandma's house i'll stick i'll i'll keep it whatever peaceful hailey
just gave 5000 bits 50 dollars from peaceful hailey and there was a wink i got you all right that was
good enough wasn't it that was good enough uh but hailey thank you for the 50 dollars 5000 bits
insane amount of money yo jeremy just want to say thanks to you i feel motivated to stream again
and also thanks to chat for supporting me i'm so grateful fuck yeah also i what happened please
call me also i i plan on going to vegas in like april of may or hold on say that like threw me
off like that somebody just took like a fucking sound knife in my ear uh planning to go to vegas
in april of may is there any food places you recommend or anything at all you recommend oh
of course i've got the fucking perfect recommendation for you chat i want to only
that's all i want to see i only want to see that in chat i don't want to see anything else i mean no
no head on over to the hash house or gogo at the link it's the best restaurant get to
blue if you like if you if you eat meat if you like meat you like hamburgers it's one of the best
they got good chicken too they've got a great meatloaf sandwich do they am i making that up
maybe that maybe they do maybe they might have a good meatloaf sandwich get that one
yeah this looks really ugly is the mic my colors off and they said do you recommend anything else
and again thanks for being a role model um i mean vegas go see some of the shows are awesome like
you know that you could go see pennanteller pennanteller great nice but wait what is what
why am i locked in the bathroom all right the next person that says why am i locked in the
bathroom i'm going you're getting deleted i'm just gonna delete you i can just scroll over to you and
i can just click that button and it's just that was a weird timing but he versus freida wink
uh so this game is a rhythm game and it's based on dancing and moving around and i'm gonna win
i don't want to see this but thank you hailey so much they say thanks again for being a role
model thank you um it's my pleasure here we go uh one player game another fucking wink what
i can oh wait why is it only okay this is blown out to a point where i can't read these names
this is wrong is this supposed to look like this i think it's just supposed to look like that
it's supposed to just look like that
all right uh heat frida sprite ham yeah kelly shorty hero pinky gaso or kitty m
i mean i mean kind of have to be damn ham versus gaso yeah so all right it's just you have to do
button combinations let's go am i doing it wrong i got it maybe i should practice so you go i'm
i don't i get it i don't get it i don't know how to play this all right let me do practice
to find out what's going on here
yeah i think you have to do them both before this beat ends up let's
let's see it was ugly this is a classic this is like one of the most classic games in the place
all right here we go stage one what's up farting and burping okay so i don't get points i have to
do it on the last beat x i think i just have to do this i just have to press it at some point
before the beat is over
so
i don't know if i can handle this right now i'm not sure i can handle this
all right i get it i know how to play this is the song i need this i understand how the game works
hey that was uh break disk on camera um no that's not gonna happen all right i want to be
break disk on camera freedom versus
i know how to play let's kick some ass go pump it up i missed oh fuck he's gonna super combo don't
go i'm tapping my foot right now all right take it take it take it do a move to
throw something at him i'm winning oh fucking get frenzy i know i'm not supposed to do anything
but that was the other song you win oh yeah i just i just scored you triangle on beat is your super
really freedom versus kelly take the house down new song that's a big bottle all right let's go
have the beat wrong one three go one two three go one two three go what's going on
one two three go how's this wrong it's crazy this is fucking this beat is fucked
it's not even on beat this is not on fucking beat
dude this is fucked up just not spinning fast enough to keep this up with on to be on beat
game de-sync no this skipped and it's out of sync is that seriously what's going on
there you go i got killed yeah let's continue all right let's go
like boom boom boom boom boom boom boom it's doing it again oh mother fucker i'll get it i'll just
watch it's off this shit's off dude it's off shit's off i'm trying to time it when the
on like the light feet pressing it early oh it sucks to have to press this like this
two tenths of a second early this looks very catchy though imagine playing a rhythm game and
not trying to do the riddle am i winning somehow so fucking shit slowed down you lose shit all right
all right i'm doing this trying this one more time and i'm breaking the game the game was like
fucking 50 dollars turn off the sound that's not gonna help win writer i just went into water
and came up with a fucking dolphin i'm taking the headphones off i can't hear the song all right
this is for you guys lose kelly okay what are you talking this is what what is what is they're
saying this is something music saying this is this music why are they saying that what does that
mean you win i won i don't just what's that i don't know what that is freedom versus gas oh
all right no skipping i don't hear he's skipping good
that wasn't fair all right hello do something at him triangle triangle
i do again oh he's doing some good work here fuck i screwed it up that's all right
mess it up yes motherfucker
frenzy there's no way i lose this camera won't even show him he's not doing anything important
don't worry yeah i win you win this game is giving me a fever fever time what's this mean
you're about to press the button freedom can you win this do you beat the game
no skipping
no i think it's okay it's all right did i get did i get too close to the butt
and it is off i gotta beat the uh view isn't dropping like flies
oh you don't like busting through
i should he said that too quick let's get out of here i'm gonna bring back later
i think i lost you win i win i win freedom versus kitty in
take the house down okay no skip it's come on stop skipping on me here
oh that's so off actually i can't even look at that i'm gonna take the headphones off
nope even the flash is fucking his brain up getting served yeah it's my disk is skipping around
all right here we go i'm bringing it back right here come on i'm doing it on the life
song slap i would love to hear it no you can i pick another character and maybe the different
character will load better no skip don't beat right now zombie what hey not fair
right it's off beat now
why did i read that i don't know why do i read anything
did i win you win oh okay we can keep going nice i try i was trying to press triangle
freedom versus couple era i was trying to press triangle on the beat and it wouldn't do anything
take the house down why is it two birds one it's a little distracting when there's two people there
do i just hit one of both the camera on me
you from the team what i had it that was correct
there it is
oh
at what point what have i beat the game that was exactly what do i beat the game is it one more
person paper time here it comes see it control build that would be funny freedom versus he versus
heat i remember this because this is the one that was on the demo disk this was on the demo
disk and i played this a hundred times and we're gonna have it all fucked up and goddamn rhythm
game but it just skips you know there's no rhythm exists on the game anymore see i can manipulate
fire carefully let's come on to this because dancing is really really cool but dancing with
no sounds of music behind it it's always just kind of weird right here let's let's go for it
see how interesting this looks and in fact let's add this in the background okay let me
just make sure this is uh this should play correctly for you guys let's try it
wait okay hold on a second okay this is gonna be fucked just want to warn you i'm gonna lose
control of this very quickly just in case anybody needed to know uh in fact let me go let me make
sure i can get this right i have copy and pasted that sound effect 16 times in different tabs
and we're gonna have a silent crowd it'd be a lot of time okay let me just make sure i get
this right i'm in there right you can do i have audio i have audio okay this is kind of a loud
crowd what are they doing what are they all making these noises all right here we go welcome to the
dance-off
is there a chain bike in the background
wait what's playing what's playing planter's cheese balls how to play planter's cheese balls
shooting a basketball in super slow motion okay
okay
our system has detected unusual traffic from your computer why is it matching up why is it matching
up all right i'm fucking out of here let's see you guys later i'm done i'm done that's where the
stream has to end i was only gonna stream for a few hours anyways beat heat i can't it's too
powerful way too powerful far too powerful uh yeah i don't want to go i don't want to go too late
and i'm done with this game it was pretty good it was pretty fun just like i remember playing
the demo disc a hundred times he promised auto yeah but he's not in here he's in bed with he's
in bed with kim i'm not gonna go get him i'm streaming tomorrow uh you'll see him tomorrow
i'm gonna keep putting it off until he shows up we got a wink of course we do i said it yesterday
i'm not gonna go get him out of bed i'm not gonna go drag auto out of bed but ah bring camera into
do you think you're gonna get a picture of my bedroom with my girlfriend sleeping in it
who does not want to be on camera i do hey hey honey i'm just coming in with this like
4 000 people that just wanted to see the bedroom just where's auto how come i couldn't do this
shit that was awesome that was like all right all right let's do the bits and the subs and everything
just a quick little stream that i didn't want to not stream today that was really fucking fun
i had it blessed thanks for joining me we'll see you tomorrow tomorrow now this is important
tomorrow i'm either going to do hidden folks mega man legends or a mystery game
there is there is a mystery game involved but i wanted to i've had this i've had buster group for
a while i wanted to clean it up i knew that that last one was only gonna take like a few hours
so i bought this i wanted to try it it was worth trying it was worth playing i'll go for the mixed
mystery box well hold on 50 dollars by the way i think i might have made that up but i'll see you
guys tomorrow thanks for hanging out for a little while always good to see you we'll see you tomorrow
tomorrow we're starting at the normal time somewhere around two o'clock we're not going
to start this late tomorrow i want to do a full stream tomorrow so take care let's do the bits
and subs when is no more heroes 2 um probably i want to do black and white this weekend i want
to do black and white 2 this weekend friday is black and white 2 that's the plan so black and
white 2 is a couple of streams probably maybe we'd go to no more heroes 2 next week or this
sunday or something i don't know we'll have to see but yes we are returning to black and white 2 the
sequel you will see that when it appears i do have to get this off my screen though because i keep
getting the demo intro screen and it's driving me insane there we go all right good night everybody
talk to you later talk to you tomorrow somewhere around two o'clock
twish you know how it is the bit shouldn't take us very long because obviously i haven't streamed
for very long so let's get back to my regular there it is we had a lot of big money came in today
we had 300 bits from kristen they say shout out to alaska yes of course the western most state
should have known that uh freddy dread a hundred community subs just an absolute community sub
dump freddy is a huge supporter of this stream tons and tons of money i've come in through freddy
thanks a lot man hawaii doesn't exist i didn't i say hawaiian people said that is it hold on is
alaska further west than hawaii no i said it of hawaii and people thought i was crazy
oh no alaska is it is alaska by the way some tidbit of information alaska is the furthest
north east and west state in the country it apparently crosses the 180 degree meridian
of longitude that's weird that's really strange the allusion allutian islands cross the 180 degree
meridian of longitude weird so it's the most it's the west north and east most state but yeah
thank you freddy glad you enjoyed vegas it's a great city a bulbous swag desk who gave 500
bits this ska soundtrack is fucking bopping dude that game was so adorable i'm really happy that
we got the kind of this little bite-sized that was a bite-sized stream but it was that was a
lot of fun i had a blast scruffle thanks for the 300 bits hey they say he says horn they say uh he
says horny alert thank you thank you hey gnarly thanks for the 250 this unlocks my 20 000 bit
badge thanks a lot for the insane support the insane continued support of the stream
it's mind-boggling so thanks a lot guys thanks for making me laugh crying at the tom bergeron's
america's funniest porn videos moment you're the best uh i gotta be careful with that shit man
you gotta be careful with that i could fucking i don't want to make anybody angry
hey felsix thanks for the thousand bits felsix hey i'm gonna i'm a little late but here's hoping
that you're doing all right today love everything you do and all the heart you put into your streams
and being a goofball i've been brightening my recently gloomy days thanks for the huge
amount of money thanks for a thousand bits i'm doing pretty good i had my first pt appointment
today went well and i'm gonna be going a couple times a week and we're gonna see just what happens
over the next few months and see if it improves let me try thanks a lot felsix swiggity swanky
thanks for the 500 bits i'm 32 today happy birthday swiggity swanky i never told you how
i first started watching you most people is because of your tf2 memes but for me i wanted
to know how to be a better spy and five years ago when i first found you i was actually taking your
gameplay with utmost seriousness at first i didn't bother with your funny vids and i wasn't into the
tuber formula at the time but then i found a video where you showed art and that you were a
person the rest is history thanks for keeping me alive thanks a lot glad you could enjoy those
old videos and yes those old videos do have some good advice hey everyone's saying dude those old
videos gave wicked bad advice you don't actually want to play that was back before anybody was
given advice it's like if you if what if i'm the if you if i'm the only doctor in town you're
coming to me there are no other doctors you're coming to me and then eventually like other
doctors put up shop and are way better of a doctor than i am but i mean i gave some decent doctor
advice for how to play tf2 and then that doctor uh realizes that other doctors in the area can
perform the surgery better than he can so he goes into stand-up comedy and he remembers all the
times that he told the jokes to his patients and they laughed and then he took out the wrong organ
and then he became a fucking famous stand-up comedian doctor who's not a doctor anybody
didn't need to be a doctor he didn't even need to be a doctor anymore you can just be a comedian
here we are super redstanks of the 250 thanks a lot they say uh hola germa greetings from brazil
greetings from america i've watched you since late 2011 a long time ago before my high school
soon it'll be 10 years this is my first sub and bit ever on this website which i dedicate to you
i've grown up watching your videos i learned english with you and that includes the swears
oh sorry about that sorry about that now i'm after a computer science degree and have trouble
studying but listening to your streams helped me focus i wish all the health to you on all
your procedures and of course much love thank you super rich i really appreciate that i do forget
sometimes it has been it's we will be coming up on a 10 year anniversary in my next year my first
youtube video was my first like germa 985 i'm uploading a video is with 2011 right june of
2011 talking about june of 2021 will be 10 years doing various forms of online media like youtube
and twitch i'll be i've been around for 10 years it's insane don't know how that's gonna play out
i don't have a crystal ball of what happens after 10 years but i'm still here so let's keep
going thanks a lot rips hey germa sucks i missed these thanks for the five community subs germa
sucks and speaking of those subs let's show them there's gonna be a lot of them because of the
more than 100 plus community subs that have come in tonight there's gonna be a shitload of them
i'm gonna be streaming on my deathbed no i don't think i will no uh let's get the credits rolling
and let's actually move to a different scene because this is not the right one roll them
thanks a lot guys i'll love you one day there will be a last germa stream yeah there will
there will but i mean that's they'll always stop stop saying that stop saying that i just got here
i mean there's gonna be an end to this eventually it just will but you gotta remember that how much
fun this was and it all doesn't go away and look i i'll show up i'll show up in like hollywood
squares of twitch you know what i mean i'll be like 50 and there'll be some new hot streamer
that's like get blowing up and getting huge views and then all like oh and we're gonna do the
hollywood squares i'll show up now germa up there what do you got and i'll be like oh look at me
john and and don't worry you won't you'll never get rid of me what would i do besides streaming
um i don't know i don't know i really don't know what besides this what i would really do
on a daily basis i would probably go back i really would probably just go back to
trying to do something with animals i really enjoy working with animals i've done it before
so i probably get back into that spend you know maybe 10 plus years just i don't know working in
like a vet office or something that's like i would do that it was that's a good question what have
you got banned on twitch i don't know i would obviously try to if that i mean it depends on
what was for go back to youtube the day i get banned from twitch hey guys it's germa985 i'm
back took a little bit of a break for six years but hey got my first video brewing don't go anywhere
not ever on twitch we're here we're here over here now we're here now oh no that twitch thing
was just like the fond new i just did it for a while you know whatever peeing in burkey highlights
no i don't uh i don't think that'll happen i don't have any there's no real road i think
that leads to oh germa985 is permanently banned from twitch i don't i don't see that happening
for any reason although but how how can you predict anything that could happen on a stream
i don't know i don't know i'm planning i'm not planning on getting all right this is freaking
me out thank you yoko nova for the 400 bits you literally beat the boss with your chin here's
some money well half of it but thank you thanks for the 400 bits we only have a couple more things
to go over so just a quick little end of the stream run down here and i'll see you guys tomorrow
have a good night take care of yourselves this is the end we're either going to play hidden folks
or megaman legends or a mystery game we'll see when i get up what i feel like doing uh thank you
to uh nickel cat the 500 bits hey germa remember this bizarrely dark magazine ad for incredible
crisis i was eight and it made me very sad holy shit what the fuck was this a real ad
what no way holy shit this is dark here i'll give you unlike you here look at how fucking look at
how awful this is that's a real ad holy fuck that's nuts i can't even believe it the game wasn't that
dark oh my god anyways that's yeah that's that's pretty bizarre it's not a real ad
wait did i did we get did we get grabbed by fake ad oh well were you freaked out with fun i was
actually it was very fun beautiful jen thanks for the five community subs thank you beautiful jen
we'll be playing beautiful joe uh soon i got them both and then also beautiful jen thanks for the
500 bits thank you for making me laughing my ass off jeremy well thanks a lot for the five subs
five dollars i'll see you guys tomorrow no we got one more one more bit just came in
500 bits from goo berry juice thanks goo berry hello comrade 985 between the first game being
so chaotic and charming and the surprise buster groove stream this has been one of my favorites
and i think that even if this was the last stream i couldn't be more satisfied and proud of you
thank you i'll always love you even if you have to stop streaming someday either way
i'll be broski no matter what you do appreciate that thanks to the five appreciate the five
dollars too yeah i don't have any plan to leave but you guys know i've told you this i'm gonna
be very upfront with this i mean this is not me don't take this anyway besides the way i'm
saying it exactly if i am not interested i'm not gonna do it as net stark once said
if i cannot stay interested and stay engaged and and want to continue to try to do new things and
try to make this drive it has to interest me i'm not gonna turn this stream on just because
i need to or have to in quotes right that's not gonna happen he's a diva so i don't want to do
that i'd rather it be something that i like to actually do and i mean i'm doing this for 10 years
coming up next year is 10 years i don't know it might i might start to want to try something new
20 10 20 13 years i'm probably i if i'm still interested let's go but when i'm not i'm gonna
move on that's just the way it is this is the only way don't give him money so he has to keep
streaming no money has nothing to do with if i'm gonna keep streaming if i okay i could get i could
get fifty thousand dollars a stream and if i didn't if i couldn't do it if i was done doing it i was
like i don't want to do it anymore i that's bullshit you can't make fifty fucking thousand
dollars a day and be like you know i don't feel like streaming today that's a lot um that's like
ridiculous uh destroy destroy all of his other opportunities you sickos what the fuck are you
talking about so your price is fifty thousand dollars okay dot dot dot no no no no fifty
thousand dollars a day fifty thousand dollars a day is what i said not a total i mean a day
now i'll be around for a long time this i don't see myself getting this interested
in anything for the very long term foreseeable future but don't worry i just do i i wake up on
monday morning and i go hey still having fun yeah all right let's go what are you doing this week
uh this this and i think that cool see you again next week when i ask if you're still happy with
what your career choices have been thanks had in my head same time next week you guys know how it
is he hears voices no no you'll see me for a long time i'll take care of you guys why don't you say
that i'll okay let me let me go over that i'll i was gonna say i'll see you later take care guys
and it turned out to be apparently i'll take care of you all everybody just get into get into
a series of vans freudian slip that's all right all right see you guys tomorrow good night good
luck with whatever you're doing see you tomorrow wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait
this is very important wait wait wait wait wait wait wait uh mr sarkis streaming right now
uh this is important mr sarkis streaming
i fucking love this guy all right we're gonna we're gonna raid sark
all right raiding mr sark let's say hello see you guys tomorrow bye