Good afternoon. Where's my coffee? What? It disappeared. I'm here now. Hello everybody.
Good afternoon. We're going to continue Chibi-Robo. Now if I finish it tonight, that's a question.
I should. I don't see why I will not, considering there's only about six hours, seven hours left
in the game. We should do it tonight. Thank you for joining me. Taking an extra second. Why am I out
of breath? If I, well, I guess I just sprinted. That makes sense. Yeah, I did just sprint.
I hit the mute button. Yeah, I'm an idiot. I hit the mute button. I got up and I like
grab. We got a long hallway. So I'm good. Are you guys ready for Chibi-Robo part two?
Coffee's worth it. Yes, it is. It's always worth it to get a coffee.
Mansion. Yeah. When you describe to people that you're full sprinting for more than three to four
seconds down your hall, you have a, I guess you have a big house. It may have been embellishing
a little, but anyways, let's go. I don't need to wait because I don't need to introduce this
because we just did it yesterday. And I, here we are. Caffeine is terrible for you.
Yes. Or bananas, apparently. Yeah. Don't have it. I don't ever do it. Sorry. I don't ever do anything
wrong, right? Don't ever drink caffeine. Don't ever fucking go to an R rated movie, right? Don't
ever do anything wrong. Only drink water and sit in your house and lie in your bed and look at the
ceiling. And every so often get up and stretch and only eat lettuce. Um, well, lettuce is bad for you
too because fucking the Romaine scare. Yeah. Literally don't do anything ever. Way ahead of
you. Live the tortoise life. Oh, don't be in the water because there's all the bacteria and all
the fucking gross shit in the water, in our oceans. No, no, don't go swimming. Don't drink coffee.
The only thing that you should do is fart on your webcam. That's the only thing you should be doing.
Well, what the fuck can I do then? You tell me. All right. So, uh, I have to go upstairs.
Quick recap. I'm a household robot. I fix things. I help with the family. I put sugar in people's
cups. I clean stains off the ground. Uh, mom and dad are about to go through a divorce probably.
Typical robot helper robot stuff. So we're going up to mom's room right now to find out what's going
on, which was the foyer, which we're going to go this way. Yep. Frash. Get it. Oh yeah. And there's
a dead frog outside that I could have saved four hours ago. Wait, I want to give, um, Ribbit Girl.
Ribbit Girl's very sad, by the way. Ribbit, maybe. What is this? Is us in, is, is, oh wait,
I think that's the other robot. Yeah, that, that, because that's, that's the old robot. The, the one
that everyone was their best friend. Yaybit. 13 happy points. Spread the happiness. That's you and
her. We also, we have a con. Yeah, we do. We have frog rings. We have to collect frog rings for her.
She loves them. And there's, I think, six or five more in the house. How many more? Five more. Ribbit.
Everybody loves Chibi Robo. I, where's the trash can? I gotta, I have a lot of trash. Remember I,
remember I went underneath, um, her bed and I picked up like three years worth of trash
under the bed. This game is dumb. I really don't give out permanent bands that often.
Don't make me start now. Hey, we got a Wink. Look at all this trash. Ten. Oh, look at that mound of
spitballs. I have two boxes. Yep. Wait, no, no, do I, no, I already fed the fish plenty of time.
44 happy points. Holy shit. Wet to dry in one frame. Well, you can tell when I was sitting here
testing and making sure it worked and everything for the first time. You can tell when that was.
And it's like probably 40 minutes ago. All right, wait, I'm gonna clean. See, I'm helping.
As per the title of the livestream, I'm going to help. Show memory card are emulated. You can,
I don't care if you think this is emulated at this point. That's not like some thing that I'm
going to be like, how dare you? No, not me. I don't care. You, if you, if you think this is emulated,
I'm glad. If you think this is on original hardware, I'm also very glad. I'm very glad
about those things. I don't care. He did show the memory card. He slammed it in a door. Yeah,
I did two days ago. All right, it's time. It's time to go into mom's room. What's in mom's room?
First, let me charge the emulator. This is pre-recorded. Don't stop saying that. You're
going to get me in fucking trouble. I haven't turned on an actual live broadcast in like two
and a half years. It's not fucking with my game. All this is pre-recorded. I just, I sit here with
it on one of my monitors while I'm watching lost right now on my other monitor. I'm in season four.
It gets good, right? And I just chime in sometimes. You want to know how to use the warp bot. Oh yeah,
this is new. Insert your plug to power it up. When the energy field appears, climb on top of
the utility bot and automatically be transported to the other warp utility bot. Well, where is it?
Let's test this. This is the foyer. It goes to, that's a adorable sound. It just goes upstairs.
Oh, wow. That's better than having to fly over on the banister. I'm really,
really happy you said season four. It's the best season, Jerma. Thank you. I'm looking forward to
it. All right, sorry. Back to the regularly scheduled pre-recorded Jeremy. Okay. Gotta clean
this up. Good, good. Happy points for that one. Okay. 165 stains. Time for a cleaning bonus.
Happy points. Oh, the reverb is on. There was a lot of reverb on there. I was trying to make it.
Whatever. The reverb was dialed up a lot. I got a lot of points for that. Why does reverb equal
pre-recorded? Well, because that means I've opened 30 windows within a 10th of a second
of the same stream. That's what that means. Sorry, guys. I fucked it up. I'll fix it.
I'm getting the trash. I'm going to go to mom's room. That would be a delay echo.
Not if they were all opened within a 10th of a second. You would hear a lot of reverb.
He's wrong. Wrong. I'm an audio engineer. I went to school for audio engineering. I think I know
what I'm talking about. So did I. Show degree. Well, I never said I graduated. I said I went.
I mean, I did pretty poorly and had been stopped after about two classes.
All right. Let's go in mom's room. Let's find out what's going on. It's time.
We're going to find out what's in here. Here we go. He was a neat. All right. Bedroom. New area.
What is the secret in here? There's a frog. Specifically, there's an alive frog right here.
It's dead, too. Dead frogs everywhere. What's that? Let's go and have a closer look.
It looks like a frog. But how horrible. Who could have done such a thing?
You think it could have been Tao? I mean, maybe the dog could have picked it up and
thrown it around. Probably. It's possible. I don't know. I mean, I don't know. I can't
jump to conclusions like that. I don't know. Yeah, you're right. He already has plenty of
food and bones and stuff. I mean, who could have? Huh? It's a Tyrannosaurus Rex stuffed animal in
this room. Chibi robo. There's something over there. What are you talking about? There's
nothing there, Tally. Wait a minute. It really was something over there. I'm going to go take a look.
Okay, so another dead frog. I don't know what to do. Poor guy. Yeah, what am I supposed to do?
I need water. All right, we got to get a good, we got to make a perimeter here.
Ticket stub. Wait, can I drag this? Save him. I can't. Holy shit. I'm strong. What's in here?
Can I open the briefcase? There's probably something in the briefcase, right? Charge the frog.
That's not going to help. Let me clean under the bed first and we'll figure it out.
What's this? For seat one, chibi robo equals crazy moola. I'm very expensive. Okay. Well,
we knew that. Charge the frog. Charge the frog. If I put the plug near that frog,
it's going to zap him and kill him. So, no. Why would I use a defib on a frog that's currently
breathing? The frogs, that's not the point. What are you talking about? Why would I use a defib
on a frog that's awake and alert and breathing and has a heartbeat? He's just thirsty and there's
another one outside that's also thirsty. I just need thirsty. I need to, I can't wake him up. What
do you want me to do? Absorb his power. All right. I got to look for some other stuff in here.
How about, um, wait, I can go on top of this. Can I, can I drag this all the way over? How far
can I bring this? I can't jump on top of here. It won't open if you don't know the correct password.
Oh, we need the pad. This is the secret right here. That's the secret we need to know the
password. We've got to find out. We've got to get the password from mom, right? All right. In the
meantime, let me go over here. Isn't mom going to know that I, that somebody was in looking at the
briefcase? Wait, what about the shoes? Anything hidden? Point. Pull it out. I'm going to pull this
up. Is there a bug up here? There's a demon door. Mom's going to give us her password.
Oh, there's a lot of trash on mom's desk. Jeremy, what's your social? Oh, that's easy. Uh, zero,
zero, zero, zero, zero, zero, zero, zero, zero, one. I was the first person. Can I get up there?
I got to climb. Same joke years later.
Pogchamp. Dude, Pogchamp. Remember when he did that like in 2014? Probably. I don't know.
Is mom going to be mad that I'm in the bedroom cleaning? Let's get a good view. All right. We
got dead frog. This other side ticket stub. Holy shit. We'll get all those doors up there.
All right. I'm going to try to, how do I get up there? That's a lot. Get on the fan. Get on the
fan. Get on the fan. I mean, I can't right now. I got to find a way up there. Let's do the baseline
stuff first. Like over there. I got to get up there on the window sill. What is that? What the
hell is that? All right. Investigate. Mission. You need to recharge your, yeah, me. I need to
recharge me. You're right. It's a good tip. Can I get up there? Can I climb anything over this way?
Is that these ladders? Yes, they are. You almost fell for it. Almost. You got a keyword there.
Almost. Can I turn the radio on to turn on the turntable? I should be able to. All right. Who
the hell is this? I pull the thing and hmm. I can't grab that. It's like a flower freaking out
over here. I got to open up the window. I can't get up there. Can I shoot it? Yeah, look, it's
right there. Can I dislodge it? Maybe I can dislodge it. Shit. I want to get up there.
Can I climb anything else? Hey, let me in. Oh, well. Maybe I need something else. What's this?
I can't interact with the big speaker thing.
Shit. I need the, I need the big, I need the ladder. I think there's not, I need the,
okay, there's a briefcase in here, but I can't do anything with the briefcase.
I guess I can land on this. Anything on here? Can't climb this. Oh, well. Oh, wait, what's that?
Look at that. We need the passcode for the briefcase, but I can pull this.
Is this the blinds? A hat? Oh, it looks like you can use this to climb up. All right, well.
Don't water the frog. I can't. I don't have a means to. Woody Woodpecker charge noise.
That's pretty good. I love it. All right, let's climb up this shit. I hate that Woodpecker. Why?
Why do you hate Woody Woodpecker? How do you even hate Woody Woodpecker? It doesn't make any sense.
Why? Bell? Ring the bell. Wait a minute. This is gonna, I stand on it? This is, I can't hit it.
I'm trying to ring it. Oh, what does that do? Somebody to come open the door? Uh, ticket stub.
Can I fly from here? No, I definitely can't fly from here. I'm just gonna land on the,
I mean, I rang the bell. Hello? The fuck is this? Who lives in here? You open the peephole.
Now you can pass through here at night. Oh, now I can come in here at night. Shortcut. Nice. All
right. Well, how do I, can I climb up this? Look at this. Oh yeah. Look at that frog ring over there.
All right. I'm going to go fly over this way. No, I can't make it. All right. Well, I'll come back
at night. Let me see where this goes. Oh shit. How do I? Okay. Then I can climb up. Okay. I can climb
up the, this thing over here. Let me see. Yeah. So I can climb that all the way up. Good. Good to
know. All right. Cool. Did I miss anything else in, uh, in the kid's room? Yes, you did. Well,
let's go take a look. Remember, it didn't wink. I fucking, I have a thing that tells me if there's
winks, the winks, the winks are real and I didn't even look. I just believed you for no reason. I
have a, is today the last wink day? No, it'll be a day or two. Like it's going to be, uh, Tuesday
is the last day for wings and they're going to be significantly reduced in price. All right. Let me,
uh, do something for it. We can go talk to the Frankenstein guy, but hold on. So almost out of
time though. I had to put this trash, I see trash and I need to get it. I'm obsessed with trash.
I'm obsessed with it. Look, I, I, it's wasting time, but I have to open this and go get it.
You see, I've wasted so much time. I have to pick up every piece of trash.
I think I leveled up too. All right. It's nighttime. We can go into mom's room at night.
Great work out there. Let's adjust your happy points. What about my ranking? I am now in the
top 10 of all chibi robos in the world. Special gift, a brand new bonus battery.
1800. Yeah. 880. So good. Top 10 chibi.
I do have money though. Let's see what I want to spend it on. Top chibi streamer. Speech, speech.
Guys, I just want to say I never would have got here if it wasn't for all of you leaving
your cans and bottles scattered throughout the house and not walking even two feet to the trash
can and for dropping oil all over the ground and never cleaning the vents above your stove.
Without this, I never would have made it. Thank you everybody. Range chip, passive aggressive speech.
We'll start cleaning. How's that for aggressive aggressive? All right. I'm going to get the
range chip. Fire long distance blaster shot. I want it. And I also want another battery too. Yep.
Kitchen bridge. A bridge that stretches far placed near the planter. All right. I got,
I got so much to do. You're an asshole. You made my daughter cry. What? All right.
Let's put the rest in here.
I'm sorry. I tried to do it exact. I got caught. All right. Uh, I can, I have to do a thousand at
a time. You're doing diva. Diva is Elmo is Gollum. We want shit. We need shit. Diva reporting for
duty. It's also one of the Ed brothers. It could be anyone, Eddie. It could even be Elmo. It could
be anybody. Plus two, hire him. Something about being available. All right. Let's go to, uh,
let's go to mom's room at night. Mom's room at night. Where's the warper in the foyer behind me?
I can't stop thinking about woody woodpecker. Yeah. It was a great reference. Great.
Let's hear it again. No, I love it. I can't wait to hear it again. All right. Into mom's room.
Anything new? Okay. I teddy bear. I went, I went into mom's room. Mom locks the door at night and
she leaves the door open all day. I'll handle this. Diva Gollum, double D Elmo quad impression.
Why did you even clip that wrong door? So what does this change at night or something?
Is mom just in here sleeping? Is there anything we do because like, is there something we can do
while mom is asleep? Like go in her drawer and find a key or? I don't understand. Why would I
do this at night? Does mom like bring like this password up here and put it somewhere? I don't
understand. Well, we're going to find out. What are we going to do? These bills are piling up.
On top of that, the electric bill has skyrocketed. See, I am a problem.
He's just hopeless. Okay. We need to, that is what if I make, what if I make my presence known?
What is that up there? Wait a minute. What is that? You see this thing? What is this? Like a secret.
Hi mom. Uh, is it something? Should I make my presence known? Say hello? Uh, yeah, I guess I
could say hi. Hi there Chibo. How'd you get in here? Did you come to check on me because
you were worried about me? Yes. Thank you Chibo. 52. I bet Jenny and her dad asked you to check
up on me. Well, since you're here, would you mind keeping me company? I'm balancing our
checkbook, but something just doesn't add up. Oh, you want me to do math? I'm exhausted.
I wonder if there's a toy receipt I'm missing. I bet he's hiding one somewhere.
It was a receipt. I asked him about earlier and he said, don't worry. You have all,
that was a great impression. When it comes to toys, I don't know if I can trust him to have
any self-control. Oh, can you do me a favor Chibo? See if you can find a hidden toy receipt. I think
I know where it is. Bring it back to me if you find one. If you do, my husband will have explaining
to do. Isn't it like right here? GB robo. Crazy move. A hidden toy receipt.
Shit. That's not it. Oh mom, you're gonna do anything about the dying frog in the middle of
the room. He's just sleeping. No, I don't have it in my inventory. It's hidden somewhere. Hidden
receipt for a toy. Let me check up here for a second. I still have to throw my trash away. I
have a lot of it. Anything over here? I thought those were Pop Tarts and a toaster. That's my,
that's my actually, actually mutated brain. Just thought that. It's like, oh, Pop Tarts and a
toaster. Let's plug it. Let's go to the other room. I can't connect. You're connected. You're
right here. Toy receipt. Where does dad even hang out? Does dad only hang out on the sofa? Is that
it? On the toilet. Dad hangs out in the bathroom. He saw the receipt already. Well that, no, that
was the Chibi robo one. That's not the right one. Dad lives in the walls. It's a wall dad. God. I
want to go back into Jenny's room. I didn't explore everything in Jenny's room. I picked up
trash and had to leave. I wish I could use the Stuart Little Car, but that's unfortunate. I can't.
Why? Why is she so sad? Well, she's upset that her parents are not getting along. It's kind of sad
because she's really sad. I'd hate to see their electric bill. Yeah, she was talking about it.
All right. What have we got? Okay. Thank God. Let's dump all this crap. I have a lot of it.
Look at that. Like five wrappers, can of orange juice, party poppers, wads of junk. What's the 1500?
Okay. What are you doing here? Hello, space hunter robo. Look at that. That towering castle
and all the way at the top of it. What do I see?
Oh, a delightful damsel. He gazes down at me with lost eyes. I can tell her heart aches for justice.
Listen, he's jumping. Space hunter code. He's going to jump up to that table and try to jump
to the microwave and fall five times and then fucking leave. Be like, never mind. This game
sucks. Drake Redcrest must speak to her. She needs my attention. However, a minor obstacle stands in
my way. How am I supposed to get up there? One called Mort will know what to do. I'm at a loss,
but the destiny of a space hunter is to find the truth. All right. Well, hold on. Let me,
let me just get up here. Wait, is he talking about the guy under the bed? He's talking about the
Frankenstein guy under the bed? He was a syringe? That's a squirter from a doctor's kit.
It's probably Jenny's. Looks like you can pull up water with it. Bingo. You can spray it on all
sorts of things. We just saved the frog. Wow. Yes. Okay. Cool. Oh, is this a TV?
That was a really good show. I love the part when the bear got mad at the honey not being in there.
Can I get on top of the TV? I still have time to explore in here. Why not? Bear actually mad.
Bear actually. Wait, that was telling me something. No, you can't just jump. The bear was mad about
the pot. There's music. Well, let's get up here. Red shoe. What is this? Whose shoe is this?
This is a mushroom? Oh, it's a break mushroom. You shouldn't be slacking off.
Get back in there, champ. I can't get over there. Can I go down here? I can maybe sneak in this.
If I hover, I think I can sneak in there. Yeah, I can. I definitely can. Do I even need to?
I don't think I even need to. What the fuck? Did I just clip through?
What the fuck are you talking about? Why am I clipping through this?
Toe. Toe. What? Toe. Toe. Toe. Toe. Toe? Toe. Why is everyone saying toe? I don't get it.
You're confusing him. Yeah, you are. Very much so. I don't know what you're even talking about.
Let's go talk to this guy. Oh, someone did a juke with a toe. Okay.
I get it, I guess. Although I don't. I'm going to pretend I get it.
Let's talk to the bumming again.
Will you listen to my story? Yeah.
It's about the other night.
Why is the bear attacking? Stop, stop. You're going to break it.
Okay, I got that. That's the shoe for the girl up there.
That is what transpired.
The lovely Princess Pitts hasn't left her castle since then.
Her bare foot causes her terrible embarrassment, I'm sure.
I'm very worried about her.
If you find the red shoe, please let me know. What? You've got the red shoe?
I've got the red shoe. Come back up. It's really elaborate and probably pain in the
ass to get in and out of here. I don't know why you didn't ask first.
Did you find the shoe? There it is. Yes. Hurry up and give it to Princess Pitts.
I can't go into the castle because my body won't fit. Another one of life's little
disappointments. I put a flight of stairs in front of the castle. Go ahead and use it.
Oh, shit. They gave us a way out. What's a button on the back of you do?
All right, let's charge up and then try to go up to the top of the castle.
I need an outlet. Where's an outlet? Only one outlet in this whole room.
It's just bad bedroom design. One outlet. All the way over here. Can you play the piano?
Is it a battery? Oh, I'm gonna be able to get that. I can't pick those up. Here we go.
Let's make our way up. This is gonna be a puzzle. Not really. Not that big of a deal.
Now, what is this? Battery. Double A battery. Okay, more items. Can I jump from here to there?
Nope. I don't know if this is like Zelda or something where if I got to the edge,
I just did it. Okay, pull these. And then can I- whoo! Jump onto the heart thing and we float.
This really is Jump King. What's this? This is where you inserted a double A battery. Ah,
nice. I want to hear the whole song. I wonder, should I- I was gonna get on his head and then
we float from here. This game is so cute. It really is. It's just adorable, the whole thing.
All right, keep going. Dude, I just smoked like two grams. What the fuck is this?
Dude, I just smoked two grams. No one said that. Yes, they did. He said, man, I just smoked two
grams. What the fuck? Why? Why? I don't need that info. I don't need- I mean, that's fine, but I
don't- I don't need that info. Should I go left or right? Go right. Oh, the gosh. The
the perspective. It was just wrong. Back to the sewer. I didn't want to wait. Bye. Okay, we're
good. I need another battery. I need another battery. Fuck. Where's there another double A
battery? A D battery. Shit. Where's there a D battery? Man! I'm gonna have to do it tomorrow.
Throw the trash away. I need a D battery. I wonder, is that in here? It's probably on the other side.
I just went the wrong way. I went right instead of left. End of the stream voice.
I just started like 45 minutes ago. What are you talking about? Oh, because I keep saying
tomorrow. I'm gonna have to say in the game. Coin. I'm gonna go down the slide too. Cool. You ready?
Oh, I did the slide wrong. I'm actually- I'm annoyed by that. Okay, water. I gotta get- wait!
What's in here? Why is this like this? Cat can't distinguish the game and reality.
Term is an eggplant head. What the hell is that? What's up? What? What is that? What's that thing
on your- 20. What's this 20? Twitchcon Amsterdam. What? Eggplant head.
That's what it's like when kids first learn the word eggplant. They start calling each other
eggplant head. Eggplant head. Eggplant head. It's because they just found out what that word was.
They ate it like three days ago. Eggplant head. Stop it. Stop calling me that. If German reads
this out loud, I'll do 20 push-ups and 50 squats. Good luck. Go for it. Back to what we were doing.
No, I want water. Where do I get water? Can I get it from a sink? My wife ever finds out
I'm in huge trouble. This should be a safe place. All right. The receipt is in the couch.
Receipt in couch. I'm going to get it. I'm getting it, dad. I'm going to get that chip right now.
No. Yeah, I'm going to get that. Wait, I got to- I'm over- I'm too excited to like-
I'm too excited to snitch on dad. Hold on. There it is. He really doesn't go anywhere
besides the couch, does he? Let's get the crumbs. Bro! What's wrong, chibi robo? Toy receipt? I have
no idea what you're talking about, silly robot. Oh, by the way, the room looks really clean today.
You must have worked so hard. Toy receipt. No, no, no, no, no. You found it. Ew. Well,
don't tell my wife, all right? Oh, I want to pick the trash up. Why would it be ew? All right,
we got to go to mom's room at night. We got to show her. Do we have any more of those things?
I don't have any more of those things. Rings. No. Gone. Man, the news is boring. What a snorefest.
Hey, chibi. Can you change the channel, buddy? The amount of work it takes for me to change the
channel on the TV is astronomical. Do you see how small I am and how little- how much is it
going to take me to do this? It's going to take me so long to do this. I have to go get my ladder.
You can't just sit up and press a button. Look at what- I want you to watch this whole time.
Dad. I don't even know where it is. Where's my elevator? I have to go- I'm going to do it.
It's a happy point. Save the frog. Frog comes after TV. Don't worry. No, it doesn't. Yes,
it does because I'm currently in the room. Look, let me just change this lazy motherfucker's TV
channel. Imagine watching this from the couch. Chibi Robo. Yes? Change TV channel. Yes, sir.
Wow, what's taking this thing so long? Lag. Lag. What do I have for ping?
This thing sucks. Fuck, man. What the fuck are you doing? Chibi Robo. Yes?
Change TV channel. Yes, sir. No, no, no. You were already going up. This fucking thing sucks.
Return this thing. Oh, this won't work. Oh, hooray. I've done it. What the- Hey. Hold it,
hold it. Whoa. It's Drake Redcrest. Thanks for the- Dad just gave you 19 happy points and $50.
Fuck you, dad. I'm going back to the news. Wait, no. No, stop. Put it back. Put it back.
No, no. Keep it on the news. No. You piece of shit. How will I ever be able to change it again?
No, look at him mocking me. Look at him mocking me. How dare you piece of shit. And then all
of a sudden from above the screen, smash, a fucking shoe, a foot, crushes Chibi Robo.
All right. Can I get water out here? I don't think so. All right. I did what dad wanted. Let's plug
in and let's go back. I love this game. There's so much to do. Bad ending. Yeah. Then it just
shows dad going into the store with the receipt. Yeah. I don't know what's wrong with it. Okay.
You just returning it? Yeah. It just stopped working. There's a piece missing, I think.
Okay. Thank you for the return and exchange. Yeah. Yes. Alex, I'll take every single time
someone's ever returned something to a store for 500, please. Stop throwing shit at me.
This happened five times. Yeah. Why are you keeping track of how many times people have thrown
dinner plates at me? Oh, whatever. Let's go. Because it's funny. All right. We're going to the,
what do I want to do? We're during the day. We've got to go back to mom at night.
So I do have access to, I have access to the kitchen because I got the ladder for the kitchen.
You can give it to her in the day. Oh, you can go to the sink. There's no water in the sink.
All right. Where's my, uh, the thing that I bought? I just bought it. Where is it?
Is it, is it, oh, it's up, it's up on top. Why is it up on top? Okay. Well, we have to get up there.
Hold on. Did I already go up? I think I did this already, but
worth a shot. It's to reach the spoon. Ah, this tiny husband video is weird.
Husband, husband video. Why does it have to be a video? What do you mean this?
Oh, and I guess it is a stream, but tiny husband. Oh, I can think of mom can just put us up there.
Can't you step on the lever of the toaster? I just tried to go. So did you find the toy receipt?
This is important. Do we, um, it's do we sit? We'd sit. Yes, we do. Sorry. I mean,
come on. We got so hot rod. Where's the receipt? The husband, we got to get this free, you know,
the husband's really, there's a lot of fault has to lay on the husband here.
She said he spends all their money on toys. I mean, we got to stop that. Another Red Crest toy.
I told him that these toys are a waste of money. Doesn't he listen? Is he deaf?
God, my husband is so stupid. Thank you, Chibo. I think that was worth more than 30. Spread the
happiness. Aren't I spreading sadness and discourse? I've had it with that man. He can do the housework
himself then. I don't even want to look at him. Spread the happiness. Forget this. I'm going to
lock myself in my room. You want to explain this? Oh, where did you find that, sweetie?
Doesn't matter where I got it. Another toy. What is wrong with you? That's it. I've had enough of
this family. I'm locking myself in the bedroom. Oh man, I'm in a world of hurt. Spreading happiness.
Happiness being spread. Tearing entire family apart. Oh, shit. Uh, okay. I got to get up here.
I just need a spoon. It's all your fault. It's not all my fault. They're hiding things from each
other. They're lying to each other. Like, this was going to fester for another 10 more years?
No. Wait, can I suck this up? Water. Yeah. All right. Put it away. Is this like soapy water though?
I'm going to spray soapy water into a frog's mouth. What's all this chemicals in this shit?
There's like chlorine in this water. Frogs can't have chlorine. All right. Let's do this.
Chemicals in the water. I mean, it's the frog. I play this game a few nights ago with my daughter.
My son is playing Chibi-Robo. And in Chibi-Robo, there's frogs. And let me tell you something.
They had a water system in that game. This is real life. Bug. Wait, wait, wait, wait. Stop here.
Stop here. Stop, stop, stop, stop. Stop it here. There's little robots running around. And that's
the future. That's our future. That's our future. We're going to Bernie. Whoops. And these little
robots, they're supposed to be doing housework and cleaning up after you. But it's not happening.
It's not housework. They're going to take over. These robots are going to get AI and we are dead.
All of us. Everybody, you know. That's a kid's spoon. Alex Sanders. Bernie Jones.
I mean, here's the thing. Wall Street. What we're going to have to do is we're going to have to
break up Wall Street. And let me tell you, I drank water today. A little too much water. And it's
flooding my lungs, I think. The chemicals that are in this water. They're too much. A demon door.
Alex, Alex Beetlejuice Sanders. All right. Fuck. But the problem here is it's not about just the
banks. It's about the fact that I'm living on this bottle. And this bottle, it needs updating. I'll
tell you. The tree over there hasn't been watered in over three days. Three, four years, I think.
Nice fucking bottle is what I got to say to that one. Bernie Beetlejuice Alex. I don't even know
what that was. I got the spoon. Let's plant a plant. And I got the demon door too. I got a demon door.
How come nobody's made like a Beetlejuice Alex Jones edit? That's perfect. With the music in
the background, it would be perfect. Let's slow down. You just do it right now. I'm playing
Chibi-Robo. How does it feel to be 6'10"? Feels pretty good. How about that? Not very many humans
are that tall. So, I mean, funny. Oh, he's on his way. What? What the fuck are you talking about?
He's on his way? All right. Let's do some planting. Okay. Now let's plant a seed. Let's plant
nectar flower seed. Look at this. You can't grow a nectar flower here. Let's put it away.
Oh, fuck you. Fuck you. Blue flower. Hey, look. Now we need to water it, right? Is this doing
anything? Well, okay. I can't aim. There's no first person. Oh, sorry. I attacked somebody.
I just had to attack somebody about something real quick. I'm good. Let's plant. I want to plant
the other seed. I have two more flowers, right? Yeah. White flower seed. I put them all here.
Is there a reason to not do this? I guess we can. Does it make mom happy? I'm sure it does.
Don't jump off the edge. All right, we're good. Okay. Good, good, good, good, good, good, good.
Now I have water. In fact, I'm going to fill it up completely because I used it.
There's a lot more water that's in here than I picked up. They're very liberal with that.
That's like not even a teaspoon of water, so that's cool. Frogs dying. Yes, yes, yes, yes.
I'm not out of... Oh, I am out of time. See you next time. The frog's been dying for two weeks.
Well, we're about to go rescue the frog. Let's just run in a circle. Whoa. Fight. Fight.
Holy shit, chibi. Holy shit, chibi. What was that? Chibi. Holy shit, chibi. I love saying that word.
Yes, save. Save. All right, timer. Run out. I bought the... Yeah, I bought 15 minutes, so
we have a lot of time. Remember, you're killing my ADHD. I have it too. Don't worry. We both have it.
We both have it. Don't worry. It's like a disease. Hey, we both have it now. Like what?
It's like a virus. Gloves. What the fuck? You're very liberal with your assessment of ADHD, guys.
Okay. Relax. Would you like to save? Sure. Call it out. Liberal ADHD. What the fuck is going on?
Hey, everybody. Somebody said the word liberal three times. I heard somebody in this chat room.
It's me, Bernie Sanders. Bernie Alex Jones Sanders. Somebody said the word liberal. I hear you. I said
I felt it. What are you going to do? Try to take over our entire world? Not on my watch. Not until
we break up the banks and until we get out. Get back in the box. You're taking me back in the box.
You did this joke two years ago, German. Now let me tell you about it. Get out of there.
German, you're scaring Chibi. Fucking music. Oh, shit. I muted the... What? What happened?
I didn't... I mean, I knew... I thought it was off. I thought I turned it off. Oh, the frog. The frog.
The frog. We're gonna go, go, go, go, go. Frog, frog, frog, frog, frog. Worst joke of the last
two decades. What are you talking about? I was just attacked. I was just attacked.
Was that... That's funny? Attacked by Bernie Jews. Wait, can I dig right there? All right. Yeah,
yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah,
yeah, yeah. He's still alive. Told you. Here, look what I got. Frida just gave you seven happy points.
Frida. Again. Spread the happiness. Come on, Frida. Ribbit, Ribbit, Ribbit.
Thank you for giving me the water I so desperately needed.
I will commence the nuclear attack on this country. Good day. Oh chat, what the
fuck? The frog seems to be saying something.
I don't understand this strange language. Chat, what would you maybe do? What the
fuck? Frog suit. Well, I'll never take this off. Thank
you, Ribbit. I'm fine now, thanks to you. My boyfriend's lost in that house and
I'm tired of waiting around. Now that you're one of us, you can speak
Ribbit-ese too. Cool, huh? Isn't it just the greatest?
Now that we can communicate, I have to ask you a favor. If you find him, I want you to
bring him here. Okay. Super frog. Okay, so what a great
costume this is. I know where he is. Show Jenny the frog
suit. Show Jenny the frog suit. I will, after I do some cleaning.
Who cares about cleaning? This is a frog game. This is a cleaning game with frogs
in it. Sorry, I have to correct when people are
wrong. This is a frog cleaning game. Well, it is now.
All right, let's see what the pose is. That takes... Okay, I'm gonna die.
Run. Run. Run. Use spoon to dig up the... Yeah, I gotta dig up the bone.
I'm out of power. I need to plug in. Press Z and wait. Well, I'm out of
power. I'm gonna die if I do that. No, don't say
F's. No F's. Yes, I am. F is cancelled.
Yup. Okay, I will hold down Z now. We'll see what it does. Ready?
Nothing. You just... That's it. Imagine having a device
that did one small animatronic movement and needed to take thirty dollars of
your power bill. This is not efficient at all. Uh, cleaning
game first. It takes more power to do a single frog
hop than it is to clean a whole living room.
I think there's a bug there. Bonus! Happy point bonus is...
32. Nice. 132 bucks. You gotta keep the house clean otherwise
people lose their minds. The right one is my favorite. Middle one
is my favorite. All right, now we're gonna go
bring the other frog back to life. We'll have to speak frog to the frog
and bring the frog back here. Feed the frog sand instead of water.
All right, we need to go to the upstairs. Jenny, what are we gonna do? Your mom is...
That was what? I thought that was mom again. Mom is what? Your mom is what?
I gotta get over there. I gotta go. Hurry, save mom. I'm going.
What should we do, Jenny? Mom is, uh, ribbit ribbit.
Huh? Wait, that's it. I can look through these slats. That's my smart girl.
Ribbit. It's no use, kiddo. My face is too big. I can't see inside.
Give me a hand, Jenny. Oh, Chibi Robo. She locked herself in the bedroom. I'm a
little worried about her. I need to see what's going on in there.
I can't see through the slats. I'm sure she'll be happy to see you. She's not mad
at you. Can you help me out? Hold on. Let's get the fucking paper.
Cheese crumbs and whatever the hell this is. Book? Oh, well, this is your book.
All right, let's go. I'm in. I'm in. Go check on my wife and see what she's up
to. Say you'll do it. I'm begging you. Okay, she's sleeping. Dead frog. Hey,
you. Get up. Keep her up. Are you still here? What the hell? A Lego dinosaur.
I hope it has the Rex's voice from Toy Story. Oh my gosh. Oh my gosh. Look at
the size of that thing. Chibi, what do we do? Goodbye. You're going to leave?
You're going to leave me? Is mom awake from this? Oh, you're right. My teeth.
You're made of metal. Goodness gracious. I can't be running around without my teeth.
Hold on there, you little varmint. I need my teeth. It really is the guy from Toy Story. Here,
Dinah teeth. Take it. You can have back. Can I have whippersnapper? Give me my teeth.
Bombers not to bite me. Thanks, Junior. This ain't much, but you go on and take it.
Dinah gave me more happy points than everybody in the whole house.
Sorry, I don't need the money. I want the happy points. I mistook you for one of them dang frogs.
What do you expect? My eyes are going and you was dressed all in green. I guess it was fate that
brought us together. Stop by if you need anything. You hear? Bye now. Well, we made a new friend.
It was the frog. We lost the frog. Lening game first. Ease out up. 20, 30 happy points
every time I do that. That adds up. I've done that dozens of times. It's worth a ton of points.
What happened? I've got to get back to Frida on the double. Will you take me to the backyard?
Yes. Really? Truly? I'm counting on you, Ribbit. Not yet.
Counting on you, losing for dead. I did not. When I find that motherfucker that's doing that,
I'm going to spray them with water. That's not going to be water in that thing.
I'm going to go. I'm going to suck up something from the drain and squeeze it. Spray it. All right,
let's go. Mom? Fantastic. More receipts. So many bills. Oh, look at you dressing up like Jenny.
Why don't you go show her? I bet she'd get a kick out of it. Very nice. You've been cleaning
up the house. Thank you, Chibo. All right, we're going to take this off. More receipts, more receipts.
Oh, my husband must have sent you in here. Oh, well, it's not your fault. But let me tell you
something. He's not getting off the hook until he's sorry for what he did. Chibo, could you
give my husband this letter? What's a letter? What do you mean, this letter? Shit. Uh, okay.
Thank you, Chibo. He has to understand. Okay, I'll give the letter. All right, Frog, let's go.
Wait, I have to be dressed like a frog. Otherwise, he won't trust me. And I can't talk to him.
All right, let's go, Frog. Take some of this. Let's go. Okay. Are there breathing holes in my body?
Put them into the trash? I can't. I don't think that'll even work. All right, let me out. All
right, Dad. I've got a letter for you. I need him to fish. Dad, are you still out here? Jenny,
where's Dad? Rivet. Did the evil frog wizard put a curse on you too, Chibi-Robo? Yes. Yeah,
that's what I thought. Just like me. Looks very good on you. Holy fuck, that's a lot of points.
I can only speak to other frogs. How do you do, Rabbit? I mean, Rivet. Can I talk to the bear?
Chibi, thanks for checking on Mom. Looks like Dad's asleep. He'll be up in the morning.
Everybody's sleeping out here. Why don't you need to go to sleep? You're like three. You need more
sleep than all of us. You need to be in bed. Hey, look, I can't sleep. I wish everything was all
better. Jesus. Mm-hmm. It's traumatizing. This is pretty fucked up. It is. All right. Dad's going
to get up in the morning, which means I don't think I can do anything. Can I wake him up?
I can't. Okay. Can I do anything else today? I could probably float from, hold on. There's
other stuff down here that I can get from up here, isn't there? Hey, what are you doing here? Frog.
Hey, but hold on. What are you doing over here? Hey. Well, all right. Let's go bring the frog to
the backyard. Okay. Back to the living room, which is over here. Jenny's too close. Oh, okay. That
makes sense. Have I been to the basement? Yes. I have the charger. I haven't put any money in it,
though. I currently got a family I'm trying to work out their problems. How is divorce any percent
coming along? Not sure. A couple of these. That's worth a lot. Ten. Very good. Thirty-nine happy
points. I got to be in like the top five at this point, right? Have to be. You think I'm going to
be a Chibi-Robo? I'm going to be top five Chibi-Robo in the world and let a piece of trash sit up here?
You are mistaken. Sorry. You wish you were top five. Oh, oh. Oh, I am top five. When I go back and
charge up, you'll see. I'm going to fill this up, though. I'm probably going to need this for
something. I want a full water syringe. All right, frog. It's time to reunite. I wonder who the worst
Chibi-Robo is. I don't know. That's a good question. Okay, frog. Here we go. Here comes the reuniting of
the frogs. Hello, Frida. I have someone. How long is that loser boyfriend of mine going to keep me
waiting, Ribbit? Honestly. Yeah, I found him. He was lying down on the ground. I think he was
shit-faced. Frog divorce present. Fred, you're still alive. You sure got yourself into a mess.
Frida, I'm done for Ribbit. I got mistaken for food and chewed to bits. What did I tell you? That
house is dangerous. You got hurt because you didn't listen to me, as usual. Don't talk so loudly.
My head still hurts. You don't know what pain is, my friend, but you're going to find out pretty
soon. What? Maybe I was better off as a dinosaur snack. I'm sorry. I'm sorry.
Sorry if it caused you any trouble. See you later. Wait, wait, was that meant?
Help me! Help! You just wait for what's in store for you. Holy shit! Do I go in there?
How do I do help him? Hey! Oh my god! Get out of there! Spreading happiness, as usual. Can I do
anything right? Everything I do just goes horribly wrong. Should I? Oh, this thing's a dig up over
here. What is this? Okay. What is it? More digging? The tank? Oh, it's the hidden pirate ship.
Ah, why don't I just unearth? Good job, you unearthed ghost pirates. Do I hop aboard?
A ghost problem solved. It's so scary. Can I dig in here? I just like the song. That was cool.
So I gotta go talk to the pirate again. What else? I'm gonna run out of time. Don't dig too deep. Get
the bone? Dog bone. Oh, all right. There's bone over here. Really? I can't dig this up? I guess I
can. Is it up enough for me to grab it? Dog bone. Okay, nice. Give dog bone to the dog?
Should I have a lot of these flowers? Oh wait, there's nectar in here! Oh! All right, put that
away. Plant the nectar seed. Come on! Drained all the nectar. All right, I'm gonna be top five.
At least six. I got a lot of points. Good morning. Let's adjust your point total.
Oh, well, I made it to nine. Top nine. Citrusoft is sending you a brand new bonus battery. It'll be
at 200. Yeah! 394 more points. All right, I also have to... I got money and I got scrap.
Get the backup batteries? I have one already. All right, let's do some scrap. Kitchen bridge,
living room bridge. A bridge that stretches far placed on top of the bookcase
or the kitchen one. Place near the planter. Which one of these is more useful?
One in the kitchen. Chibi-Robo, put your scrap into the recyclotron and then I'm going to dump
all this money into the battery. Save giga-robo. Yeah, I'm going to put the money in here. I'm
going to do 2,000 gigawatts. Do you want to charge it? Yes. 2,000. 2,000 kilowatts. Fill it!
Ooh, that was not very much at all. Did I break it? Something seems a little off, but...
Oh, well, never mind.
Okay. Well, I'm going to go pee. I'll be right back. See you guys in like two minutes.
Can I ask if I just press the unmute button and fucking scream as loud as I could?
Okay. It's a new day. Time to give dad the letter. How dare you? No, no, no, no. That's not cool.
That would be so bad. All right, dad, I got a letter for you. Where's dad? Dad not on couch.
Dad not watching TV on couch. Weird. Is he still upstairs? I mean, it's a cleaning game first.
I put on my wizard robe for this. What? It's a cleaning game first. It's a cleaning game
first. Divorce game second. All right. That's right. Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait.
Four for footprints. These add up. They add up. Guys, doing side quests gives me sometimes like
12. This adds up like crazy. All right. Charge up. I'm going to go talk to dad. Remember, you
would do that even if it gave one. Yeah, I would. Yes, I would. Because that's seven to 10 points
per cleanup. Do that 10 times. You've just made almost entire battery worth. 30% almost.
What about pirate friend? Yeah, but I mean, priority right now is give the give the letter
to dad. We're doing main storyline quest here. That's one of my favorite noises. He's being
frugal. Yeah, come on. This is how I get my points. I level up. Two, four, six, eight, 10,
12 foot. Like I just did a whole side mission. Like picking up dog hair. You have to read the
letter first. Why? This letter contains some bad news. Are these papers? Are these like divorce
papers? No, they're not. Is this game going to go full dark? How'd it go? What'd she say?
Uh, I mean, this is the chaos route. Release the scurvy splinter and everyone has to like,
oh, everyone get out. And then, hey, is that what I think it is? It is, isn't it? A love letter.
Say it is. Thanks little buddy. Uh, the heart is in half. Oh man, this dude's truly clueless.
I think I'll read this love letter out loud. And then the little girl. Dear dysfunctional
family. Tao tracks mud all over the house. Jenny thinks she's a frog. And the man of the house
isn't man enough to find another job. Well, I've had enough. I'm sorry, but you've pushed me to the
edge. The only option I've got left is divorce. Divorce. Ribbit. No.
No. I got no time to lose. I gotta cook, clean the house, and fix stuff. I have to win her back.
Let's go, Jenny. Come on, Tao. Hurry. Down the stairs. She's huge. She's huge.
Arf. Oh my god. She's, she's huge. She grew. She's as big as dad. What? Okay. Um, congratulations.
She's like 26. What? No. I've never seen him in the same room before. That's the first I've ever
seen him in the same room. No, but wasn't she kneeling on the ground? Wait, what? How have I
not figured this out? She's like six feet tall. She's still like two years old. Jenny's in her
thirties. All right, let's go. Uh, let's go down and see what they're doing. To the kitchen. Yes,
to the kitchen. Yes. Yes. Yes. I got, I just got a bridge for the kitchen, right? Yes. To the base.
Hold on. Go see mom. I know, one thing at a time. I want to see what they're doing. I got a bridge.
I got a bridge in the kitchen. I got to bring back the guy's pirate ship. All right. Hold on.
Okay. Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait. Let me talk to mom first. I mean, I'm right here.
Might as well. Where's it? There it is. Climb. Blow. Wait, I don't know why I just thought I
could just open the door. I'm an idiot. All right, let's go. How much power does a teleporter cost?
A lot. I can't believe I got timed out for typing this TP noise.
And is it not like this? Well, how many times did you write it? Not enough. Jesus. Dog tracks
mud in the house as mom tracks huge prints behind a locked door. You know what? Yeah. How
did these get here? That's bullshit. Hmm. Yes. It's happened seven times. I still don't know who's
throwing those at. I don't know why they're doing. Okay. Mom, let's talk. Let's see. Delivered my
letter. Oh, look at you. Ah, I'm dressed like this. I'm going to. I've been picking up garbage
around the house. 10 happy points. That's as much as I get more cleaning up three footprints.
Just saying. That's a bonus for cleaning up those footprints. Yes, I delivered the letter.
I think you deserve a reward for being just the smartest little robot ever.
Holy shit. That is a big one. 120 points. I never thought boycotting all my housework would be this
boring. I wish there was something I could do. Wait, I know. I haven't sewn for ages. I think
I'll get out of the old sewing kit for a change. Since you've been working so hard and have been
such a good bot, I'll make something nice and cozy just for you. Ooh. Give me a little time.
Okay. All right. Mom, what's the code for the briefcase? 666. Just a minute, Chibo.
Being so tiny must make things awfully hard for you. Let me give you a hand.
Here you go. I know you're small, but you do your best. Oh, thanks. You just saved me some time.
Very nice of you, mom. All right. Now we're going to go down to the basement and then back. No,
we're not. Get off me. All right. Do we have enough? Oh, not enough. We're good. All right.
Back downstairs. Wait. I see a stain that I haven't gotten. Two of them actually. Okay. Wait. A little
bit more over here. Yep. I think that's just artifacting. No, these are scuff marks.
Probably from dad. Scuff marks are worth four points. Scuff marks on a carpet.
Scuffed stream. It's from the car peeling out. Got a cleaning bonus. I think I'm pretty close
to another rank up, right? Look at all this dirt. I just can't have this. Ah! Wait, hold on.
It's your mom. I can't clean on surfaces. Why can I not clean these? I can't scrub on surfaces in
front of me. Only on the ground. I missed one. No, I didn't. I know. I'm going over here.
Water? Oh. Well, I don't have water. I have nectar. Do I have enough power to do this? Yeah. He had
to charge his eyelids. How much power does it take to wink? Oh, let's see. How many? Okay.
You get 2,000 calories in a day. Just sitting here breathing is about... Let's see. Oh, let's pause
for a second. Oh, I'm actually curious about this. So how many calories do you burn blinking?
Do you burn calories when you blink? Okay. Do you lose weight when you blink? What?
How many calories do you burn when you fart? A popular internet claim from 2015 said that
one fart burned 67 calories and that farting 52 times a day would burn a pound of fat.
What a bunch of bullshit. Okay, so if you blink... All right, so by doing nothing...
So it's probably like two tenths of a calorie to blink. So two tenths of one
calorie kilowatt. Don't get banned by doing that noise. 60 calories. So you're telling me
that if you go on like... Oh no, this is going to be gross, but we're talking. This is real life.
If you go on like a farting spree over the course of like an hour, it's going to burn
like a thousand calories? Who the fuck wrote that? All right, I want to go in the kitchen.
I want to see the bridge. I want to see what they're doing. Uh-oh, small spiders. He starved
to death because he farted too many times in a row. That's so disgusting. Gross. Just, just gross.
Come on, I don't want any more random Pokemon battles. I've got cleaning to do. Where's the
family? Why is nobody to be found? Holy shit, look at all this dirt. I imagine somebody opening the
chat because they like Chibi-Robo. The first time they're here and they look at this fucking chat
room and they see fart redeemed. Actual fart. Fart redeemed. Fart redeemed. It would just be like...
Like you just, you just pop the chat out and minimize it at that point, I think.
So you don't have it. We just close the tab. A good bonus. Can I buy the car? Yeah, and I haven't been
able to use it. I own the car and I can't even use it. I don't know what to do with it.
Take the ghost costume off. Take the... Got you. Sorry, I had to do that one more time before I
took it off. So much to do. Look at this. So much dirt on the ground. Oh yeah, there's another
training regimen with the eggs, right? Yeah, I go back there after I do the boat. 39 more points.
I'm raking it in. All right, let's go to the ship. How many side quests? The bridge. Where's the
bridge? Yeah, I don't have enough time. I have enough time to do the bridge. Wait, wait, wait.
All right, all right, all right. Look at all this dirt. No, fuck the dirt. Forget it. Oh, it's so
easy. No, it's not. I want to do the bridge. Think about how much dirt. I haven't done it in so long.
Think about how much junk is up in the, uh, in the fan. Let me check the bridge out because I've
invested a lot of money into making the kitchen traversable. Where's the bridge? Right there.
Okay. I'm gonna run out of time, but I still want to see it. What about the flowers? I haven't
checked down those either. Oh, look, they're little sprouts. It's a bud, chibi robo. Wow.
All right, turn it on. Do you want to know how to use the bridge utility bot?
Insert your plug to unfold the bridge, and you want to shorten it, just tilt down.
Change the bridge's direction, plug in the side. Push or pull the utility bot freely,
so try moving the utility bot to a different location. All right, what do I want to go from
here? Ah, that way. Ooh. Ooh. Oh my goodness. What have you done? It really is. Or it's...
I thought the bridge was complete, and it wasn't. This is a stranding type game. Death stranding.
This is a stranding. All right, this is happening way more frequently. It's happened nine times in
10 hours of gameplay. It's happened like four times in the last one hour. Why is it happening
in more frequency? No, whatever. I can... I'll come back. There's not enough time in the day
to do anything. I'm definitely like eight or seven. The seventh best robo? Eight. Making
into the top eight. More power. That's a lot. That's a huge increase. 230. That's huge.
Oh, chibi robo is a new product available for the online store.
Let's see here. Ah, there. It's some new chibi gear. They call it chibi radar.
With one of those, you'd be able to find things not visible to the naked eye.
You have to buy it and see if it's true. Okay, yeah. Let's go.
Well, it depends on how much it is. Okay, seeds. Chibi radar. I can't afford it.
Let you see things that are hidden from normal view. Okay, I'll buy that next.
I have enough to do this. Living room bridge. Yeah, I can do this. Let's do it. Does Jerma ever
scream? Yeah, sometimes. Sometimes. Maybe like once. It's a utility bot. Where's this going on
the bookcase? Set it out in the living room. All right. I want to go to the basement, too.
But we just... Okay, where is it? Because there's other stuff in here that I didn't get.
Frog ring up there. Where is it? I gotta get higher. Where's this bridge? Top of the TV,
you know? Oh, it's over there. But I can't... Can I get up there yet? I think I can, right?
Hold on. Let me push this back. Ah, a Joop classic. Nice. All right. Can this go any higher?
No, it can't. It's pronounced jump. Can you imagine going into a stream and correcting
somebody on their own thing that they created? Can you imagine the scenario where you do that?
What's the scenario where you do that? When you look through a telescope and you see the beautiful,
big, beautiful, huge planet known as Juppiter. Yeah. Juppiter. It's the biggest planet we have
in our solar system. It's huge. All right. Oh, I can get this. No, stop picking up the cord.
I wish there was a way I could make it so I don't pick the cord up. Let's get that frog ring more.
Okay. I was wondering how to get this for the longest time, and now we got it.
Well, now I know how to get over there. Slow, slow, slow. All right. Now we just drop down to
here. Nice. Demon door. Okay. And I can climb on that too? Let's do this first. Good chunk of
change. It's going to bring me to the ceiling? Oh, man. We're up pretty high. All right. Hold on.
This is... I'm all the way to the top. Okay. What's up here? I could go this way and go over there.
Or what do I want to do up here? Is there anything that's super high up that I haven't gotten? I
guess over there. And here. All right. Let's just walk around. I don't fall, right? Okay. As long
as I'm careful. Can I go in here? Fall and float into this? But is there anything even over there?
There's nothing even there. I don't think there's any reason to do that. All right. There's a space
over this way. What is this? This is a weird spot. Oh! Right there. Okay. I can fall from there and
float into the demon door. I could also... Yeah. That's... And then I got everything.
I've not missed one thing in this room at that point. All right. Let's keep the walk. I'm gonna...
No, I don't want to take the drop door out. Is the demon door under me? Oh, wait. Isn't
the one like... There's one right... Did I get this one? I got this one already! Wow. I knew I got
this one already. I knew I got this one already. Oh, I got it already. I knew it. I was like,
Oh, baited. It's all right. I can get right back up there. I knew it too. I knew it. All right. Charge
up. No save. What happens at a hundred charges? The battery explodes. Same deal. Climb and then
run along the wall and get the secret demon door. Camera. Float. All right. Wait. Maybe something
behind the picture of... Maybe there was... I don't know. Maybe it's something behind there.
What's the fastest way? Get to... I think they're both equally slow. We got to get over there.
We're just gonna have to run this way. All right. Let's go. All the way in the whole wall.
Just run. Yep. Where is it? No. Where is it? It's underneath. It's like right here, right?
Okay. Isn't it right here? It's right here, isn't it? Where is this thing?
Did I pass it? No, it's right there. It's right there. Okay. I just got to get on top of this
and then float into here. Aha! This is the last door that's in here. I think, right? I can check
the... Let me see. Eight out of nine. Who is the ninth one? There's one more. Eight out of nine.
It's probably hidden somewhere. It's probably hidden. Yeah. I probably need that device.
All right. Let's go. All right. What's next on the list? We're going to
the basement. The basement is into the foyer and then basement. Actually, I want to do the... Yeah.
Let's go this way. I want to do this first. German, did you read this important message? I didn't.
It was very important. I'm so glad that you brought it to my attention. All right. Let's
go talk to the beans or the eggs, whatever they are. Private Vegas reporting with duty. Uh-huh.
Sarge has been a tough egg to crack lately. All I want to do is race cars.
Maybe I'll drive away and go AWOL. Tag me when German lies. What the fuck is going on here?
What did I lie about? What are you doing? What was my lie? I didn't lie. Tell me the lie. What was
the lie? Let me know when you want this to stop. Yeah. There was nothing there. He didn't like the
message. A lot about Rain World. All right. Enough with the Rain World. Can we move on
from Rain World? It's a fun game. All right. Where's the captain? I want to do this mission,
whatever it is. Come back to it in like a month or two. All right. Here come the timeouts.
I cannot guarantee you will not be timed out if you continue to spam that.
Uh-oh. MonkaW. What is MonkaW? All right. Basement. Basement. Let's go get this guy's ship back.
Enable it and find out. No. I don't need to. What are the music? Please do. It's better. Isn't it
just... Okay. It's GermaFear and GermaMars, right? That's what it is. Oh, we just had a shitload of
subs coming. That's a lot of subs. GermaSucks gave 50 community subs. Thank you, GermaSucks.
That's a heavy, heavy full bag of community subscriptions. You just dumped it in front of
everybody. Thanks a lot. It's a lot of money. That's a cat puke noise, especially for you.
Thanks for the monumental amount of subscriptions. There's a new GeForce driver for your information.
All right. Wait, why do I have to? This is going... Is it for the GameCube? Shit, I gotta update my
GeForce GameCube driver. Okay, what was actually in the Wii? It was ATI, wasn't it? Yeah, the Wii
was ATI. So it was GameCube. What does everybody have now? Like for instance, what is in the Switch?
Is it an ATI still? Is it Nvidia? What's in the Switch? What's in the Xbox One? What's in the PS4?
Is it all in video? Does anybody have ATI anymore? All right. Okay. Let's talk to this guy and give
him his... Hold on. Xbox is AMD. Yes, for an Xbox are AMD. I'm pretty sure.
It's good to see you. It's been long and long, hasn't it? So you've come to hear this old salt
tale, have you? No, but I'm sure. All right, sit you back and get ready for a whale of a tale.
Hold on. I'm here to keep my promise too. Ahoy there, squid bait. You're looking ship shaped today.
Squid bait? Squid bait! Hi squid bait. Now simmer down. What I'm about to tell you
happened many years ago when Twirl was young. I've got a loading screen for this. A big coin.
That fateful day I found a doubloon gleaming like a wee lassie's eyes.
And the salty scourge of the seas that I was. I decided to seize this shiny treasure from
myself. Oh, what a pretty treasure it was. However, the Sandersons were so poor he could
hear their bellies rumbling like thunder. Giga-Robo blamed himself for their troubles.
Aye, he did. Every pirate swears to be as evil as a barnacle in bed. It be our code.
But I couldn't even steal one measly doubloon. Ah, a foul humiliation it was. As ye know pirates
who aren't evil end up at theme parks. It be terrifying. That's pretty funny.
I hid me ship and confined myself in the briny dark basement. Your the Sanders be out of moolah
and can't be buying food. I'm betting they be dead. Wait, like now? They're dead? Huh? Actually,
the Sanderson family is doing just fine. They may not be rich but they were at least able to buy us.
And were not exactly bargain basement items if I do say so myself.
What's that ye be saying? So they'd not have been troubled if I'd claimed the moolah I foundish me
on? I heard that Mr. Sanderson hasn't been working and finances are kind of tight.
But if it's just a little it's not a problem.
You know what this means. I'm no longer bound to this dank backwater. This treasure in this house
that is and I means to find it. What's the main sale me hearties? Main sale? Oh right it's I have
it. I have to give it to you. Don't you need a ship first? Shiver me timbers I forgot I've got
no ship. This is the quest we just got put on and I have it already. I put me ship in a dry dock so
as to keep her safe but me head's full of fog and me ship's lost. You're me only hope chibi I want
you to find me ship and bring her home. I've got a surprise for you. Stop ad-living. What? I'm going
off script. Who cares? What? I'm going off script for a few words like any real actor does. You know
how many lines you've heard in movies that were not scripted turned out to be the most classic
things you've heard on screen? A pirate in need is a pirate who gets what he wants.
That's the pirate's code you see. Doesn't seem right somehow. Hmm don't think so eh?
You fancy yourself a great thinker don't you? You fly and bucket a bitch. If you're half as keen
as you think you'll keep your blowhole shut. Pirates are not accustomed to waiting now go
find me ship. Yes yes sir uh captain captain sir. Let's go look for the ship chibi. We'll go
ahead and scout around but now that he's gone let me just talk about how I wish I just don't
want him fucking following me around anymore. I have your ship but I don't want to tell him.
I'm just gonna let him go do that for a while. You want to let go hang out? What's that chibi?
Have you found me long lost ship already? I have the scurvy splinter. It's so big. Yeah it is.
Aha so I'm assuming we can fly around in this thing.
Yes it'd be mine ye floating kelp cube. That's me scurvy splinter. Me ship you've earned me thanks.
It's gonna be a lot of happy points. Captain Plankbeard just gave you 66 happy points.
Spread the happiness. There's treasure awaiting and me thinks I'll be getting me some.
All right so have we completed his quest line?
It says there's treasure awaiting. Anchors away me hearties. Probably needs power.
We have to have a new battery charge for grandpa's fucking rowboat.
Barnacles and bilge pumps. I've got no blasted crew.
Oh hi then there's only one thing to do. I need you to find me some brave lads who yearn for a
life of swashbuckling adventure. If you find me four men brave and true I'll have no choice but
to give you me treasure map. Got it. One pirate crew coming up. Get the eggs would probably do
it right. Need four crewmen. Courage me lads. Courage. Probably the dinosaur.
One of the eggs. The dinosaur. What about you? It's probably yeah it's definitely the eggs.
I am. Here we go. Okay so the next order of business. It's gonna be a new day.
We gotta go check out where's the family. We gotta go check up on what the family's doing.
Valley the princess. We gotta go climb the tower. Right right right. Yeah that's true.
All right we have the tower with the shoe. We have the family doing whatever the hell the family's
doing. Wherever they are. We're doing chores. I haven't seen them in any of the rooms. Let's
go climb the tower. We'll do that tomorrow. Maybe I can recruit somebody up here. What does it mean
if your computer says um it means i would turn it off and check to see if potentially one of the
fans is spinning and hitting something in your case that's a very easy fix i would check that
first uh if not then i would be careful with the potential messed up power supply um i wish you
got to be careful with that though electricity don't fuck with electricity go check you want
to begin jungle training um do i have enough time for this no it could be an ssd dying
yep a quiet time with television what do you do if your computer is just a pile of rocks
um somebody has convinced you that your computer is a pile of rocks but behind the big rock
there's a small probably form factor pc that's behind it plugged into the wall and then plugged
into a monitor so somebody's been lying to you for a long time i don't know what your situation
is wherever you are still rank eight check the seasoning and the garlic salt may have dried up
maybe the rock is the case now that's actually kind of cool
carve out of this in the middle of a rock and have your components in there
i think that would be pretty bad for heat conduction flintstone case how is that cool
i don't know people dunk their motherboards in oil in a like a fish tank without any fish in it
people do all kinds of weird shit with their computer setups i think i'm gonna buy
wait do i have enough i do bedroom bridge bedroom basement warp works here from place to place
basement warp bedroom bridge bridge that stretches far placed on the ceiling beam yep
yeah let's see i'm gonna get the radar too
okay do i have enough for the radar what was 1700 gb radar lets you see things that
are hidden from normal view buy it upgrade give it up gb robo let's go
let's test it see how it works gb radar um how does it work
points in the direction of something hidden uses power does something hidden back here
oh dig all right i'm gonna dig dig right here what the fuck sound sound sound
sound makes me grow let me hear sound spoon give me spoon this just reminds me one of those old
weird gifts from like 2001 how much more do i have to do this how big do i need to make him he's huge
full full i am full thank you thank you for sound oh fuck mr prongs gave you 99 happy points
wow that guy had a plug for a head he saw that too right no i just played music for him for 30
minutes he's a name maybe we can call mr prongs i'm totally creeped out right now oh you got the
mr prongs sticker you really are amazing chibi robo sticker sticker oh i'm gonna get so trapped
i'm gonna get so trapped i'm gonna just follow around the radar now we we got all right we'll
do that later let me plug in i used i wasted a lot of power checking on frog girl oh i actually
have our rings for frog girl thanks for the reminder we're getting some mild f's
oh we are dropping frames huh oh actually we're getting massive f this is no longer mild
this is now uh an issue this is an omega f oh it's because i'm playing halo hey get off halo
stop playing halo let's wait this out for a little bit i'm gonna sit in the corner i'm gonna pause
this i'm gonna pause it so there's no movement on the screen here ready i'll this is how you
this is how you work with this scenario so black screen requires no rendering stop all movement on
screen stop playing halo well hmm i'm at 1000k up right now oh this is bad we're going even lower
uh my voice is taking up all the bit rate well we'll see let's give this a minute or two a
wink right now bad time for a wink this is this is going to be a low quality wink i like forgot
how to do it all right you know i'm gonna i'm gonna go brp for a minute let's go check on some
things and i'll be back in let's let's let's try to ride this out and see what happens i'll be right
back okay i am back i think we've returned to normal let's see it says i'm doing all right
let's give it some more frame data i think we're okay right a little that's kind of a major
let's hope that doesn't happen again because that just like kind of killed the stream for like
oh five minutes but let's keep going i got i'm monitoring it over here let's see if it happens
again we'll have to figure it out right all right let's go what was i doing you're muted what i'm
not actually i'm gonna put this in a different spot on my computer so i can really view it all
right let's get it yeah we're fine i just ran into something some kind of weird traffic problem
but we're good all right i gotta give the rings right yeah the rings rings rings rings viewers
vomited well i don't blame them i mean if you if the stream is like dying you know i'd be like oh
i'm whatever it's all good all right i got stuff for you yes here's another one of these
would you wink that way 33 it's their boy 33 per frog ring traffic problem oh shit the rumors in his
house imagine just having like five cars in your living room all beeping at each other
get out of the way i'm trying to get to work and on that though that yes now that is a real one
that's a real one that just came in bang i felt that one i felt that one in my brain all right
next thing on the list was what the hell was the next thing on the list i did the basement
let me look at my items i got a lot of try let me throw the trash away the oh yeah that
i climbed the tower the tower climb the tower all right let me where's the trash i got a ton of
junk do you do links for bar mitzvahs all right there goes all the junk do you no i don't i don't
okay if you have my stream open and you're at your bar mitzvah and you've accumulated 75 000
points sure i'll i will wink at your bar mitzvah now we're gonna go upstairs no no i want to do the
car thing first i wanted the what is it the training i want to do the training it's the only
thing i haven't done over here and i'm i gotta pick up this candy box got it okay now let's do
the training uh-oh are we dying again i'm dying i don't understand what's going on here what the
fuck is this happening for is it there might be the twitch server i'm connected to maybe the
twitch server is fucked up because my internet seems like it's fine it might be like the twitch's
ingest server that i'm connected on all right this exercise teaches you how to shoot at tau instead
of your fellow soldiers okay i climb this vine to head into the jungle intelligence indicates
animals and enemies are in the area eliminate all the enemies without harming the animals all
right i'll try and use your chibi copter to fly down to the drop point
okay i think i got the range all right hurry up up how do i have to go you're no robot you're a
slack bot how do i have to go keep going all the way oh god oh shit can i i thought i had to shoot
stuff all right all the way up then go to the drop point oh i'm fine all right climb it do i have to
climb i'm trying to climb it what are you doing where's the drop point i made it no i didn't turn
the camera i was trying it wouldn't do it didn't even shoot me one i thought i was going to be
shooting and moving and wasting time i'm trying can we just restart the jungle is just crawling
with danger all right can i restart sarge can we do this again sarge i want to do this again
so i want to do this again when the camera turns you end up falling off the fucking thing
no do-overs maggot okay so what i don't understand what happened here i climbed all the way up here
i can't i couldn't climb up the second vine when i tried to climb the second vine he decided to
climb down the one i was going like what do i do from here so all the can have to go up here
turn around i thought we were going just laterally i didn't think we were going back
i'm not going to put the copter away climb it climb it oh my god do not hurt the animals
eliminate the enemies oh come on well i can't wait to do this again in less than two minutes
move to the drop point okay drop point put on the propeller all right where is it
straight down where is it i can't see it where is it i'm gonna do it again two for a time of
two minutes and 20 seconds yes sir well i could definitely beat that record let's go hurry hurry
hurry hurry hurry i'm going i'm going i'm going i'm going i'm going i'm going oh my fucking god
i'm gonna run out of energy great shit come on really no i'm not i'm not gonna run out of energy
oh i'm gonna run out of fucking energy could be faster to die no i have a battery pack
i can't i want to waste a battery pack i have to fucking god damn it man why did i think that
like it was restarting fucking come on why oh my god i'm so annoyed i why can i just
read just turn it off why do i have to do the whole thing i'm just leaving the fucking room
if the timer keeps going i'm gonna be pissed
oh i'm deserting oh my god where are you going if the timer is still up there okay we're fine god
charge and do it again you're gonna soft block yourself that would be funny
for the love of god can i please do this again i've never seen this game before what's happening
you're a little robot and your job is to make a whole family happy save so you can restart there
will be no restart there will be no restart there will be no restart trying to shoot this it's hard
to fucking aim this thing yeah am i dying again all right i'm gonna all right well after this i'm
gonna i'm gonna turn the stream off i'm gonna restart it i'm gonna pick a different server
this is stupid let's get this done i got it i'm gonna try to do a couple things here
all right actually let me try to do this right now the stream might not turn off
let's see what happens ready three two one i'll be back in two minutes not even
it might with the stream might not even turn off