Hey, hey, welcome to Gang Beasts, where you punch each other in the fucking face.
This is stupid.
They're kicking the shit out of that dinosaur.
Yeah, what's with the dinosaur, everybody?
Uh, this game's on Steam right now. It just got into early access.
This guy, everyone's already dead. He's still punching.
Dude, dude, dude.
Alright, so, I'm coming.
Don't you dare.
I'm gonna come to you.
Get out of here.
What are you doing? You're supposed to fight me on the trunk.
I don't want to fight you on the trunk.
Well, that's too bad. I'm coming to you.
Get off of this trunk. Get off.
No, Juno.
You're just tossing you around.
I just close-lined you.
No!
It's not fair. You didn't even knock me off.
Oh, you can get hit by the signs. Do you see that?
Yes. That's what hit me.
Alright, well, alright, you come to me this time.
No, I want to wait for the signs.
I'm a scary monster.
No, no, wait for the signs.
Shit.
Alright, wait for the signs. Wait for the signs.
We will wait for the signs this time.
I'm just gonna hang out, like, right on the front of the trunk.
Hi.
This is so stupid.
You do realize one of us is just gonna get...
Whoa! No, shit.
Wait for the signs.
The momentum put me back.
Okay, let's get on the same truck.
Get on the same truck.
And we're waiting for the sign.
Don't wiggle around this time, because we're gonna accidentally kill each other.
I'm not gonna move.
Whoever survives the sign is the true gang beast.
Gang beast.
Survival of the sign.
Oh, here it comes.
The road doesn't fork or anything. Where is it telling us to go?
We're just gonna get double-closed lined here.
Oh my god, you're still alive?
Help! Help! Help!
I should not have...
Oh, he's still alive.
Help me up! What the hell?
Hold on. I'm gonna get...
I love this game. This game is so dumb.
Alright, I need to figure...
I wanna just figure out how to throw just a punt.
No, no, no, no, no! Seriously, seriously.
That's how you do it.
Oh, okay, there it is. Yeah, it's left bumper.
Yeah, left bumper puts out one hand.
Riding the Ferris Wheel.
Hello? How do I get up?
How do I jump off this?
My left hand is stuck in the Ferris Wheel.
Get me off this ride.
I don't wanna be out here anymore.
Thank you, you saved me.
No, no, no, no, no, no.
Oh dear.
You wanna fight with me? Okay.
You want a real fighting arena?
Come here, you. Come here!
Get over here.
Something's happening on the screen.
You're going... No, no, no!
What the hell is going on?
I don't know how I did that.
I'm just carrying you.
No!
I just was picking you up.
Alright, I guess...
Okay, what's why? If you hold down why,
you can pick the person up.
Come here.
Here comes the choke slam.
This really is just like a tug of war.
No, no, no, no!
Get in, get in!
I think I'm winning.
Why did I lose a point?
Because you died too.
You're not supposed to die at all.
You're gonna get punched in the face.
Whoa, okay.
I've learned my lesson.
You're gonna lose a point?
No, I can get out.
You still lost a point.
Come here.
You dragged me by my hair.
No, no.
Did I go over? You went over.
I'm trying to get away. You're done.
What the fuck is going on? I fell off the edge of the abyss.
Welcome to the abyss, baby.
Alright, it's two and two.
That was a terrible idea.
I'm gonna win right now.
Get in!
Get in the meat grinder!
Get in there!
Let go of me!
Let go of my hand, you son of a bitch!
Let me out!
No, no, no.
Get back in there!
No!
You are not getting out!
You're coming in too, then!
What color are you?
I'm still blue top hat, man.
I don't think these people are playing.
Then throw them off.
Come here.
You're going out of here.
You too!
No!
You can't just hold on to that, it's cheating!
Let go!
You let go. I'm not gonna let go, you have to let go.
No, you have to let go.
Alright, we're both gonna let go at the same time.
I actually didn't even mean to let go.
Am I pressing a button right now?
Holy shit!
Yay!
Alright, you know the drill. At the very beginning,
we dump the other guys off the edge.
Yes, because they're absolutely playing this game.
Yeah, look at these two guys playing this game.
No, I wanna throw them!
No, really! Are you serious?
We were trying to throw those two off and now we're both...
I've got you, I've got you!
No, I can't do anything. Can I like, crawl?
They're gonna beat us!
No, hold on, I'm doing like the crawl.
Oh god, I let go.
They're just blinking at each other.
They're not gonna do anything.
This is gonna go on forever.
We have to like, end task on the game.
Yeah, we have to end task.
You have to alt F4, because there's no pause.
There's no...
It's 6 o'clock, coming down.
We've got a train coming, and it's gonna take you
to Boylston.
And now you wanna get on that train.
You wanna make sure you...
Wow, I thought it was coming.
You need to help me out.
I don't wanna get hit by this train.
Can you like, reach your hands out and pull me up?
Pull me up!
Yes!
That's awesome!
Oh no!
I'll come save you!
Once you see the lights on the train,
that is when we have to try to escape, okay?
Okay, I'm ready.
We have to stand back here.
You have to run for it.
Once the train comes, once you see the lights,
we have to make our way back up to the platform.
And whoever makes it up there wins.