What are you guys betting on? Betting on something? Betting on what?
Predict the coin flip. Oh, it's a coin flip. Free stream coin flip. Okay.
Hello. Welcome back, everybody. I wanted to stream yesterday, but I didn't.
I'm still kind of dealing with some problems medically, and it's...
We're gonna just take it easy. We're gonna take it slow.
I'm trying to make sure that by the baseball stream, I'm ready to go.
I talked a little bit in free stream about it, but there is a lot of stuff going on.
Let's go over... Wait, hold on. I gotta wait for people to get here.
Say you're sorry now. No, I'm not going to apologize.
I'm not going to apologize for what? What am I saying sorry for?
No, no apologies. I didn't do anything wrong.
And I'm getting wicked defensive. I'm getting wicked defensive about it already.
We're worried. Don't... I'm fine. Don't worry. I'll be all right.
Don't be... Don't worry. But here's what's going on today.
Something really cool.
We got a multi versus tournament that I'm going to be participating in.
Ludwig put it together. I think I'm ready to play.
That's what we're doing today.
Tomorrow, still think it's planned to do the Call of Duty thing with myth.
We'll see how that goes.
If anything's changing, I'll let you know in free stream by tomorrow.
Friday, we're going to play two point campus as a... Excuse me. Sponsor stream.
And then Sunday is green screen movie night part two.
Ain't going to cancel on you on Sunday.
Ain't going to cancel on you on Sunday. I can guarantee you that.
And then Monday, we're going to do a free baseball hype stream
where I kind of just shout it out a lot, talk about it, hang out for an hour or two.
And then baseball is next week.
That's the plan for this week here.
Please wear the same red sock shirt that you wore last time.
Yeah, there's your plan.
If anything changes, I'll let you know, but I don't think it will.
Wait, baseball is next week. Yes.
Baseball is next week, the 19th of August.
Do you have a Discord update for it? I don't know.
So anyways, we're going to play. I'm going to warm up a little bit.
Play some multiverses. Get ready, because this is a tournament.
I got to be ready for it.
Happy birthday, Andy.
Is sorcery over? No, of course not.
I just... I was going to be very busy this week into next week.
So when we come back from baseball, we'll do some chill sorcery stuff.
We'll continue part three. Don't worry.
Called the Lamb Mortuary Assistant.
There's stuff that I want to play.
I'm just to the brim right now.
You sound like you're going to sell me a vacuum.
Would it work?
If I held a vacuum up to you right now and I was like, this is $300.
Give me the money. Would you give it to me?
Is this slow pitch softball?
I don't know where you heard softball.
This is a baseball game.
What do you mean, softball?
We told you that you got wrong information.
Somebody just ask, what's the difference?
There's a big difference between how softball and baseball is played.
Very slight differences, but there are a lot.
It's the same exact concept.
All right, let me let me do some warm up games.
I got to get this.
I got to lose to like five people in a row before we get started here.
I don't know when the tournament's starting.
I know it's starting at some point today, the next probably like half hour hour.
I definitely want to at least play a little bit and get ready.
Because I don't want to get embarrassed on this street.
You know what I mean?
Let me get in.
All right, let's do some.
I'm gonna do some 1v1s to warm up.
Oh, no, I'll do maybe free for all so people don't make fun of me.
No, 1v1, let's go.
Move this and hello.
Look at that.
I'll put the cam on in a minute.
All right, who should I play in the tournament?
What do you think?
How many turkeys could you fit in your garage?
What are you talking about?
What a what a weird question.
I was gonna say dumb.
What a dumb question.
Who should I play in the tournament?
All right, I got a good LeBron.
I got a good bugs and I got a good Superman.
We're not testing new characters today.
Should I practice bugs or practice Superman?
I'm not going to play a character I haven't played with.
Where's the handsome?
What's the handsome streamer?
I'm working on it.
Please play LeBron.
Well, it depends on who my partner's playing it.
You want the camera?
Fine.
And it's against Jake right off the bat.
Can't wait to get mad already.
All right, I need to put one on here.
That one definitely.
All right, these are practice rounds.
I'm not going to get mad.
I'm not going to get pissed off.
This is warm up rounds.
Greasy, Greasy Gary.
Villain hair.
You have copper hair.
It kind of is.
It does look like it's been at a fucking like aluminum.
All right, here we go.
One, two, three, go.
What the fuck?
What's going on?
That's why I got to warm up.
Warm up around.
What?
Oh, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
Shut up.
Dude, what the?
Finally, the guy goes flying.
Took a hundred years.
No, no, no, no, no, no.
Oh, my God, he almost just dropped down on himself.
Sorry, sorry, sorry.
All right.
Shake it off.
This first match I played in two weeks.
Relax.
That's the first match I played in two and a half weeks.
Your hair is greasier than by McDonald's order.
Yeah, it's because like, dude, what do you think I do in the morning?
I go get the vegetable oil and I like, then I just go like, I don't do that.
Don't.
That's a joke.
Please don't actually do that.
I believe that.
Don't.
Please don't do that.
All right.
We got that.
We got one.
That was a good match.
It was a good fight.
Let's do some LeBron.
What's up, doc?
Vegetable oil.
Your hair looks like a helmet.
It's called getting out of the shower and just letting it dry.
You need to practice bugs.
I got to just get back into the game, man.
Dude, your brain is exposed.
What do you mean?
Like, just right here?
Like, let me hold on.
Let me jump in.
I got to get in my Discord call.
I think I'm going Superman.
I think I'm going straight up Superman.
Your hair looks fine.
No, I know.
It's shiny because of the light.
I got a light in my face, man.
All right.
That was a good fight against Jake the dog.
Okay.
I'll probably get this one more in.
All right.
Let's make this a good one.
Here we go.
Ready?
Let me just turn around and not look the other way.
What?
Check this out.
Ready?
One, two, three, four, five.
You.
I didn't want to do that.
I'm good.
I think I'm warming up now.
What?
Nobody sees that.
Come on.
Give me a break.
Oh, that was pretty risky.
Oh, that would have been good.
Got it.
Oh, come on, Gwen.
Oh, that is going to jump.
Taking it to the sky.
Sorry.
We're good.
Shit.
I thought I didn't dodge through that.
Holy shit.
How did I not dodge through the grab?
I dodged through the grab.
What?
That was fucked up.
When he went for the grab, I went.
I didn't dodge through it.
I lost it pretty hard at the end there.
Sorry.
You actually threw?
No, I just got combo'd.
Too much grease.
Here comes the heat.
It was the I-Frames.
That was weird.
I seriously thought I went right through.
That threw me off.
I think.
Wait, hold on.
Wait, wait.
I got to put friend code stuff in.
Hold on.
Dude, it used to be good.
What happened?
This is the second game I played in three weeks.
Ban that person for 700 days.
What up?
Let's see if you can...
Can we hear Connor?
Hello.
Can you hear me?
By the way, guys, Connor eats pants as the teammate.
Big reveal.
Hello, it's me.
Did they not know?
Did they not know that until now?
I don't think so.
I think some people do, but not everybody.
It was a secret.
It was a big secret.
So who do you play with?
I play Tom and Jerry and I can play LeBron, Iron Giant.
I can play a good bit of people, I think.
I just lost two games in a row warming up.
I haven't played in like three weeks, though, so that's all right.
That's fine.
That's good.
Oh, how's it going, gentlemen?
God, I thought that was you.
Yeah.
Connor, I thought you changed voices.
I was like, what happened?
What's up, man?
Not much.
I made a song today.
Yeah, you were working on a music career, right?
Uh-huh.
And I'm proud of it.
And that's all.
So it was a great day for me.
Yeah, we're talking strategy.
FL player, it's a whole thing.
But anyway, I just need one of you guys to Discord stream if possible.
Just so I can see.
It's also OK.
It's super impossible, but I thought I'd throw it out there.
Every time I've tried to do that, it crashes my OBS.
It sucks.
Terma, that's bad for you.
Connor, what about you?
Surely this won't crash my OBS.
Surely not.
I got to get your friend code or friend name, Connor.
Oh, yeah.
Bunch of friend names in general, Chad, that you should add as well.
One sec.
Wait, there's friend codes or just names?
I think it's just names, right?
Your WB name.
So should we be adding everybody?
He left.
I don't know.
He went to go hang out with his more popular friends.
Let me add you.
He went to go talk to Psychuno.
All right.
My name is Scarlet Otter something.
You'll see it.
Scarlet Otter something?
It's something weird.
He could get one free name change.
Do you really?
I think so.
I send you a request and then I'm going to...
Should I add you to a party?
Should we be together in a party?
I don't know.
Oh, I see Scarlet Otter.
There we go.
OK, cool.
Yeah, someone took my username.
So I had to be Connor from Dream SMP instead.
Why is it recommending me Shaggy?
Like I just downloaded the game 10 minutes ago.
Try out this.
You must have some bad games.
It was like you should try out this guy instead.
I did all right.
I did OK.
I love it.
Do you like this game?
You having fun?
I think it's super cool.
I like it a lot.
Play Rhyme Dog.
No, if we play Rhyme Dog, no one's going to watch us.
They're going to be like, oh, these guys play Rhyme Dog.
No one cares.
All right, shoot.
Who's going to leave?
Superman or Bugs?
What do you think?
Which one do you like more?
I don't know.
I feel like I like Bugs, but I feel like OK, we're going with Bugs.
So now I think we have to change to like a custom game, right?
I don't know.
Do we practice or do we just immediately jump into it?
Let's see what Lubbock says.
I got my tea.
Are you a tea?
Yeah, green tea.
I don't have any green tea.
Green tea.
I'm going to be honest.
I was going to do like I was going to plan a funny bit for you.
Like you'd have like some funny jokes where I was going to put like
Tom and Jerry sound effects on the soundboard.
Oh, that would have been pretty funny.
And then it turns out I misplanned my timing for this.
And I thought this started in an hour.
And so I was I was actually doing my one like contractual dream SMP thing
for like a month for a little bit.
Well, I promise you I don't have it.
I have literally no gags ready for this stream.
I don't have any none.
OK, so I have zero too.
Yeah, none.
OK, we'll think of it.
If you think of something like, you know, like give a hint.
And I'll like try to we all hit the layup like we'll we'll make a joke.
If we win a game, I need you to say something.
OK, I'll think of something like.
Do you have a good Bugs Bunny impression?
That's pretty good.
It's like a bug.
That was that kind of bugs with his arms in the air like, yeah, whatever.
OK, because if we win a game, we both have to say like, yeah, what's up, doc?
At the same time, it's very important.
Yeah, it's incredibly annoying.
We have to go and join their voice call immediately.
I'm not going to leak anything, but that's very important that we do that.
Don't tell anyone or else they're going to kill us.
Don't tell anybody about sportsmanship.
I could should we do like just a warm up round?
Yeah, let's let's go on.
Let's just do a random team online.
Let's see how it goes.
I think we're on it already.
Watch us do that.
And they're like, hey, we guys out.
That's what always happens.
You played Fortnite, the Ludwig Fortnite thing, right?
Yeah, that's the first time I've ever installed Fortnite.
That's awesome.
I don't know if the Fortnite Friday sometime.
Is it fun?
I love Fortnite.
I think it's the best game.
Do you OK?
Is that you?
Do you ironically but unironically like it's a really fun game?
Like if you just if you just enjoy it casually with friends.
OK, and it's also just cool because like you just start seeing
so many different characters and you're like, oh, here's Goku.
And then there's like LeBron James.
And then there's, you know, Will Smith.
And I made this reference a while back.
Remember the old Smash Brothers Brawl character leaks?
Yeah, that is Fortnite.
Like the one that's just like a giant JPEG.
You can't even tell like what the characters are.
Yeah, the one with the one with like fucking Al Bundy on it.
Yeah, it's like that's what Fortnite is now.
Yep.
Fortnite's great.
All right, let's go for it.
Get a warm up here.
Oh, man.
So did they change the characters yet so far?
Or I think I think they've done some nerfs and some buff.
OK, surely someone in chat knows.
Is that you or was that actually Buck?
It's just me.
I could be honest, I almost just lost this point.
It's fine.
We beat these guys.
There's no way you can lose to a guy named FiercedDayMantis333.
That's like.
Are you sure?
FiercedDayMantis taken.
I mean, my name is Scarlet Otter.
That's just like the default Xbox name.
Oh, it must just be a default name.
Yeah.
Oh, we're so much better, though.
Stop it.
Back me coming in.
Oh, that's actually pretty sweet.
Oh, he's there's no way he's going to make it.
We're so much better.
What do you play in Smash Bros. usually?
Lucas.
Oh, OK.
But I mean, I don't play Smash Bros. anymore.
I stopped playing pretty much.
Yeah, I want your opinion on this.
Because everyone thinks I'm a nutcase for saying this.
So the new Smash Bros. since after Brawl,
it started doing this thing that I just can't get over.
And people go, what are you talking about?
Until they actually pay attention the next time I play it.
There are so many fucking particle effects in the new games
that I can't even tell who's playing the game.
Particle effect?
It's just when you when you hit anybody, when you move,
when you when you do a move, when you jump,
it's just like explosions of like purple green
and like orange colors all over the whole screen.
You'll notice it next time you play.
Um, 20.
Oh, OK.
Yeah.
It starts to get that way once you get that edge.
I'm telling you, I'm going to.
People are going to start to pay attention.
I believe you.
I thought you were just going to say because like Melee is better.
I was like, yeah, no, you're right.
No, but if you watch like Melee and then watch the new ones.
True.
You watch Melee and you're like, wow, this game looks great.
But there's not a bunch of like.
I'm telling you, I put on frame by frame on stream
of somebody doing a single attack.
In Smash Brothers.
And everyone was like, question marks, question marks.
And I saw like at least two to three hundred trues.
That's the worst is when like, you know, you're right
and everybody keeps question mark spamming anyways.
Like, like what I know, I'm right.
I don't need like their opinion and they're just question
marking just to be different.
I like Smash Brothers, though.
I think the game is fantastic.
I just I don't know.
It's like too much, especially when you play with more than one one v one.
It's just like, I don't even know what's what's even going on.
Yeah.
Yeah, I I've got my own opinions on Smash Brothers.
But if I get into it, I'll be talking for ranting for like an hour.
We got a link.
We got to let this run out off on generals.
I think they're starting to go in general.
All right, let's go, Joe.
Wait, can I give a speech?
I will be right now if you want.
I can.
Is that a sheep?
No, I will be shuffling the seating.
You will find out who you are playing in this event in just a few moments.
First seed place, eighth seed, so on.
It is a double elimination tournament.
So if you lose, you're not out unless you lose twice.
Then then you're out.
Get the hell out.
Should I back out right now?
It doesn't super matter.
But just listen to what I'm saying.
What, dude?
Okay, what's up?
You're fine.
It is an eight person double elimination bracket with fifteen thousand dollars
of prize money on the line out of my pocket.
Yes, eight thousand dollars for first place.
Four thousand each.
Five thousand for second place.
Two thousand five hundred each.
And then a final third place match for two thousand dollars total.
One thousand each.
Nice.
All right.
So fifteen thousand paid out net seven hundred thirty five days.
And what we're going to do right now is shuffle the seating to see who you are all playing
real quick before we jump in.
Do not start your next match even if your opponent's ready until I tell you.
So we're going to do all the matches at the same time.
If that makes sense.
So some people I need to catch up.
I'll just put it in the general chat.
Seating is now getting shuffled.
I'm sharing it on Discord.
You guys want to take a look?
I want to take a look.
Hop in hop because I'm doing click the button right now.
Okay, where are you playing?
You have to go.
Seating has been finalized.
Oh, the big dogs.
Here are the matchups.
You guys can enter your own Discord call, but this is who you need to match up against.
It is Stans versus Alpharad or Stans and Alpharad versus Asan and Esewa.
That's match up one.
You guys can now go to your Discords.
Oh, here we fucking go, dude.
Do we all get into the same Discord?
You can if you want to set it up and then go back to your own.
But when you're playing, just be in your own Discord
and make sure to also be Discord sharing your gameplay.
What if your Discord chat is full of people who won't stop talking in your ear?
Then that's a mod problem.
Next up is Dock and Sheep.
You guys are going to be playing Lily and Michael.
So Dock, Sheep will be playing Lily, Michael.
Good luck, good luck.
Best of three, by the way.
Best of three.
Connor, Jerma, you guys are going to be playing Crazy Slick and Jesse.
And finally, TheValeConnell, you are playing Buddha and Saikuno.
All right, I'm going to go off, set up your games, add the friends, get it all going.
I'll add everyone to start in just a few moments.
Thanks, Ludd.
Let's do it.
Appreciate it, gamers.
Thank you.
Bye.
All right, so where are we going?
All right, we're against Slick and Jesse.
Oh, OK.
Hey, guys.
Hey.
Hey, everybody.
What's happening?
We got to set up a lobby.
So does anyone want to do that here?
Or working on my hands?
See.
Yeah.
Yeah, we'll do that.
OK.
What are the rules?
I don't know.
Is it just four?
Did he say best?
Best of three, but what are the maps?
I don't get how that works.
Anything?
I don't really know.
Yeah, is it just any map?
Random.
I don't know.
I'm having a panic attack.
All right, so custom game.
I'll set up custom game.
OK.
And then we're doing 2v2.
Ringouts?
Are we doing four ringouts?
I'm imagining no time limit, right?
I don't know.
I don't know what the rules are.
Hazards enabled?
I'm going to go over there and see.
Yeah.
OK.
Let's get a clarification.
I'll get a clarification.
I mean, hopefully I don't bother him.
Let's see.
Going.
Let's get a prediction going.
Who wins?
Let's do it specifically, because I
think this was interesting.
Hassan Nessua stands out for it.
I think Nessua is the best player in this event.
I think Hassan is the worst player.
He's not better than me.
I got to pee.
I'll be right back.
Hey.
Oh, he's gone.
Shit.
I missed my opportunity.
I missed my opportunity to ask him, because he went pee.
No way.
Was it embarrassing?
Nobody responded?
Yeah.
All right.
We'll get it.
I got to get on this team.
So let me add you guys.
Zoom hazards off, and then the Scooby-Doo stage off, maybe?
Probably no time limit either, right?
Yeah, probably.
So no Scooby-Doo stage.
OK.
Yeah, no Scooby-Doo.
The mansion is.
Four ring-outs, and then I got to add you guys.
So what do you guys, you guys are going to put it in general, right?
I can invite Slick.
OK.
Yeah.
I don't see you online, Slick.
I thought I added you.
I see you.
My name is Scarlett Otter, and a bunch of random bullshit.
I'm going to add you.
There's already three of those adding me.
So you're going to have to.
Are you serious?
I was going to say, what?
Quick.
A lot of Scarlett Otter fans out there.
4366 or 4633?
I'm adding you literally right now, and I'm bringing you to the custom game right now.
I just accepted it now.
All right.
You got Slick in here, right?
Yeah, I'm in here.
OK.
He's back.
You can ask him now, maybe.
I think other people are asking questions, too.
Oh, OK.
Really fine.
Works are fine.
OK.
Hey, another question here.
Maps.
Are any maps off limits?
People saying Scooby-Doo off limits, or are we just keeping everything in?
I think we go hog wild.
Just anything.
In your counterpick.
It's a good point, Jeremy.
You brought up a great point.
You brought up an excellent point.
There are three maps that are fine.
Keep them all in.
Just keep all maps in?
You got it.
All right.
And we fear nothing but God.
And this is unlimited time, no hazards, and four ring outs, right?
Seven minutes for time.
Seven minutes for time, no hazards?
Yeah, no hazards.
No hazards.
You got it.
All right.
Cool.
Thanks.
All right.
We're good.
These are the rules that you see on the screen right now.
And by the way, all maps are in.
OK.
All maps, including Scooby-Doo.
All right.
Are we playing random or what?
That's what I thought we were playing regulation, but OK.
We'll play Ludwig's Fun Rules.
It's four ring outs, and then?
Seven minutes.
OK.
But what if both teams decide no Scooby-Doo?
That's it.
Are we banning anybody?
I don't think so.
I don't know.
Is there enough people for bans?
People call me Question Andy.
I want to go.
This is a $15,000 tournament.
I don't know if I don't want to screw this up.
How much?
There's no details.
And Ludwig is really bad at running tournaments.
I'm going to have to ask him again.
I don't know.
Question Andy.
Oh, is there announcements?
What is this?
All characters?
OK, right here.
All perks are totally fine.
All stages.
Loser picks map.
What?
Question.
No hazards.
You know.
Dude, shut up.
Seven minutes.
Four stocks.
Best of three.
What do you guys play?
Loser picks map?
How do we know which one of us is the loser?
Was it random?
They put a loser in that.
Oh, was it just seeded that way?
I guess one of us is the loser.
Wait, I don't think we even pick maps.
Do we?
I don't think so.
It says loser picks maps.
I'm having a panic attack.
All right, whatever.
Maybe we don't rematch immediately.
So I'm assuming I'm not the loser.
I don't care about maps.
But it's like up to you guys.
Like, for real.
It doesn't bother me at all.
Maps don't bother me.
I don't care.
Yeah, I'm fine with whatever.
All right.
Yeah.
OK.
All right.
Well, good luck, guys.
Have fun at all.
Good luck.
So are we going to be in the same call?
Like, talking shit?
I think we're going to go separate.
Because, I mean, you know, we get in strategies.
Yeah, that's true.
That's true.
All right.
Good luck, boys.
So many questions.
All right.
Have fun, guys.
I'll see you guys tomorrow.
See you guys tomorrow.
Hopefully, I'll see you tomorrow.
What the hell popped in this room?
Popped?
I just heard like a pop noise.
It wasn't like your graphics card, right?
I hope not.
That would be the first time my computer's blown up
while in a Ludwig tournament.
That would actually be the third time that's happened,
which is pretty impressive that that only happens with Ludwig.
Here, Connor.
Hello.
Discord screen share.
Oh.
Maybe he wants to chat.
And it's just like, oh, you know.
He's just coming in with some rules.
Yeah.
How about you share your Discord screen, Connor?
OK, fine.
All right.
I'm going to think bugs in Tom and Jerry.
Do you think that's too?
I think so.
I think we win with that.
Very, very interesting question.
What are we going to do with our money?
You're telling me to give a question.
No, no, no, no, no.
Is Tom and Jerry part of the Looney Tunes?
No.
No, no, no.
So they're just completely separate?
Yeah.
Were they part of a different Tom and Jerry universe?
Because there's these merry melodies, right?
I think Tom and Jerry was, I don't know, actually.
I don't know how that works.
MGM, right?
Looney Tunes had like a similar one with Sylvester and Tweety Bird, right?
Yeah, because the Looney Tunes.
Yeah, Tom and Jerry, I guess Tom and Jerry MGM, apparently.
So what else is under MGM?
I don't know.
I mean, I thought they're all owned by the same thing now, aren't they?
Yeah, they're all under one umbrella.
Animaniacs.
I like the Animaniacs.
The Wizard of Oz.
If he plays the Tin Man, that'd be amazing.
Let's put them all in.
Tom and Jerry were Hanna-Barbera.
Really?
Interesting.
Yeah, Metroid, Goldman and Mayer.
I watched so much Tom and Jerry as a kid.
It was my favorite thing.
I was a Looney Tunes guy.
Daffy Duck.
Yeah, I also did like the Looney Tunes.
I had the big VHS box set that had all of them.
I would watch as a kid.
It's crazy just how many episodes there are of all these old cartoons.
Yeah, there's so many.
People think like, oh, Dragon Ball Z has,
Dragon Ball has like fucking 700 episodes.
You know how many episodes of the Looney Tunes,
just merry melodies there are?
Probably like 1,500.
A lie.
That is more than Dragon Ball Hype up.
Yeah, it's also a lie.
I made it up.
But it's probably something huge.
The lawyers made them remove frying pan jokes in later seasons
because, quote, kids could have access to frying pans.
Oh.
Yo.
Hey.
Apparently, we can start now.
Oh, we're starting now.
Yep, yep.
All right, good luck.
OK, cool.
Good luck, good luck.
OK, so Jerma is wrong.
There are only seven Looney Tune episodes.
Sorry.
Sorry, this might be incorrect.
No, this is not like Trigun, OK?
Give me a break.
I think there's only seven.
A bunch of people are saying that now.
All right, we're going with that same strat?
Yep, I'm ready.
All right, let's go for it.
Remember, if we win, I'm going to do a countdown.
You're going to say, what's up, Doc?
OK.
Uh-oh, we had an error.
You got what?
Does not all players are ready?
No.
Oh, ready, yeah.
I think it's you.
No, I'm ready.
I think they need to be ready.
Oh.
Oh, we need to do our perks, right?
Has anybody else in this whole tournament?
Yeah, I think we have the next screen that we do that on.
I think it broke.
Did it really break?
I think so.
Games and beta.
Yeah, this definitely broke.
What does their screen look like?
Oh, hold on.
Oh, the pleasure is...
You can reset it.
Try it again?
OK.
Yeah, surely it works this time.
Here comes the heat.
OK, try it again.
All right, we should think about perks,
because I think I have...
OK, if you say so.
We can do team perks, all right?
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
So it'll show you in this next screen what I run, I think.
I got 20%.
Is there anything that you really want?
Not really.
This is what I run.
I get projectile speed, which is good for Tom and Jerry.
Yeah.
And the air moves is pretty good.
And then the last one, air acceleration, I don't really care.
Sometimes I do the 100 damage one is pretty good.
I like this one, 20% reduction to ground and wall bounce,
so we're not just going to bounce around.
Oh, yeah.
One additional damage.
I'll run the speed one and you run the wall bounce,
because I think we still both get each other's perks.
Yeah, I think if we have the same one, it doubles up.
Yeah, it doubles it.
All right, well, let's go.
I'm running an iron giant.
OK.
Show them what we got.
All right.
They're doing iron giant.
They might cheese us.
They might cheese us here.
OK.
All right, let's go.
Let's go.
I've seen you win these.
All right, let's go.
Try hard.
Put your try hard shoes on.
I'm going to taunt right off the bat.
There we go.
Oh, you didn't expect that one, did you?
Oh, we're good.
We're good.
Oh, shit.
It's OK.
Shoot.
He's low.
Oh, he's so low.
I lived.
Oh, we just got to get rid of him.
Please die.
Oh, oh, see you later.
Let's go.
Use that momentum.
I'm gaming so hard right now.
All right.
It's fine.
Shit.
We're getting juggled.
We're good.
OK.
No, shit.
We're good.
All right.
Oh, my God.
Slick is such a nerd.
All right.
I'm going Iron Giant this time.
My Iron Giant's better.
All right.
I got juggled.
We're going to match their comp.
I'm going LeBron.
OK.
You're confident, LeBron.
Everyone's saying, oh, no.
We have to win so we can do this.
We're going to be fine.
Everything's going to be OK.
Yeah, we got Iron Giant too.
Loser picks stage.
I don't care what stage we get.
We'll win.
What was that laugh?
That was like a little goblin laugh.
All right, we got it.
We got it.
Pull it back.
I think these perks are OK.
Wolf ball speed, projectile speed.
Yeah, I think those are pretty good.
If you want to match the.
All right.
Yeah, it's all shit.
You're good.
All right.
I'm going as hard as I can for this one.
We win this one.
We don't lose to Iron Giant twice.
No, I got the cooler skin too.
This is going to be a 40 minute stream.
No, it's not.
Just wait.
We're going to pull it back right here.
I've had shorter.
All right.
You're good.
Good to go.
Yep.
Keep that juggle up.
Make him go off the screen.
Oh, he's so low.
There he goes.
He's right here.
All right.
Is there bugs even taking much damage?
I can't even tell.
I don't think their bugs have taken any damage.
He said he was bad.
I can't believe it.
So many iron giants.
We're good.
Oh, my God.
Oh, keep it up.
I can't jump that high.
Give me a kill, man.
There he goes.
All right.
There we go.
There's bugs.
We got to get rid of this fucking bug.
There he goes.
All right.
We got to bully somebody.
Bully somebody.
I can't believe it.
Oh, shit.
All right.
God, I hate this.
This is so sad.
It's all right.
We're good.
Wait, wait.
Is it best of three?
I think it's the best of three.
You guys are down in losers bracket.
But no worries.
Still a lot more gameplay played.
Can we ban iron giant?
No.
All right.
Well, all right.
We just need to figure out a solution to our problem.
I don't fucking care if we lost.
I'm doing the joke.
Well, if you catch me playing Rhindog, I did.
That's how you know I've lost it.
These things are going to get to be like room champ.
I don't want to.
I want to like a nice ice cold carrot.
Even if you're eating a cold carrot.
All right.
We're going to bring it back.
We're going to fucking do it.
Are you doing like a bugs bunny joke?
Oh, we're going to dominate the next one.
We should challenge them double or nothing.
I'm going to play.
I couldn't do it.
I couldn't.
I couldn't see.
Yeah, I couldn't tell what was going on.
Too many iron giants.
Yeah, maybe should have just stuck Tom and Jerry.
But it was a good play.
I thought I had the better iron giant.
I still think I did.
I just, you know, there's a there's a lot of input lag.
Look, and I live like 15 minutes away from each other.
It's like, you know, if we were closer, maybe it'd be better.
Yeah.
I mean, well, there's a thing.
Yeah, they're.
Yeah, they had they had pink advantage.
Amen.
That was a good game, man.
Are we going to keep is there more than like this best of three
or is that the only best of three?
I mean, we can double or nothing if you want.
I don't really see a point in that.
They already just won like unanimously.
I don't know why they would do that.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Were we supposed to lose the second one?
I didn't even get the script.
Yeah, you were.
Well, that would have been ideal.
But it's OK.
Like we German had like a joke.
No, it's OK.
No, it's all good.
It worked out.
Yeah.
Did you guys get the joke off?
Oh, yeah.
No, it worked out good.
Yeah.
Yeah, definitely.
I mean, yeah, I recommend.
Yeah, probably play Iron Giant.
So, yeah.
Next time you guys got to send me the joke before we didn't give you the script.
Oh, that's on me.
I apologize.
I was in charge of that and I made a mistake.
I made an error.
OK.
Anyways, I hope you guys win big.
You guys are you guys did really good.
And you know, you earned it.
You know, you guys played good.
You earned it.
You had really good bugs as well.
GGs, guys.
Good game.
Seriously.
Good games.
Good luck in the journey.
We should have done what's up, Doc.
We should have what's up, Doc.
I'm right at the end.
Just do it again.
Well, these have to last the whole stream.
I only have French fries.
Is there a character that like really likes French fries?
Is there a character that's a French fry character?
I don't know.
I'm trying to think if there's a.
Oh, yeah.
French fries.
Popeye has spinach.
Bugs has carrots.
Rhyndog loves French fries.
Daffy has cocaine.
What else?
What are the other like staples?
Apparently, Rhyndog loves French fries.
Really?
Yeah.
That's what they're all saying.
They're all big Rhyndog fans.
Steven Universe likes fries?
I am playing Steven Universe.
Wait, you're not playing Steven Universe?
I refuse.
Why?
I don't know.
There was a kid in my high school that really liked Steven Universe.
And they were annoying to me.
So it just ever since I was like,
I just didn't ever want to think about Steven Universe.
I haven't even unlocked them.
I have like 30 character tokens
and that character is still just locked on my screen.
So you get it then.
Okay.
So Connor gets it.
Everyone thought I was crazy when I said this.
Okay.
When you play a game like multiverses
or like Smash Brothers, whatever,
that is a bunch of characters from different universes,
different games, different TV shows.
If you get your ass kicked by like a bunch of try-hards
on a single character, right?
Doesn't it make you hate the fucking show?
Oh, a thousand percent.
Right?
The thing is I just hated it prior.
But yeah, you're right about it though.
If they start pissing me off,
there's no chance I'm ever playing a Fire Emblem game in my life.
That's exactly what I'm talking about.
I went up against a bunch of Fins and Jakes
that I got just dominated by probably dozens of times.
And it genuinely makes me not want to watch Adventure Time ever again.
Yeah, I don't blame you.
It's starting to piss me off.
I don't even like Finn as a character anymore.
I just think about him like spinning his backpack around
and I'm like, yeah, it's not entertaining.
You guys talking about me again?
Yeah.
Oh, you ready to boot up?
You guys are going up against Lily and Michael.
All right, let's do it.
Such a big fan.
Did they add us?
How does that work?
We're going to need to add.
Pop it in the wall if they're not doing it off rip.
Everyone's thing is in general too as well.
Yeah, I'll add them right now.
Lovely.
Cool, cool, cool.
How are you Ludwig?
He deafened.
All right, let me add some adding here.
Let me make sure I get this right.
I probably should tell because this is a random fucking weirdo
Scarlet Otter is adding you.
That's not me.
You know what I mean?
I should probably tell them.
Fake Scarlet Otters everywhere.
The guy who took my name felt bad about it.
And then like, so I added Connor Eats Pants on here
and then they changed their name to like,
I don't know how to fix.
And then I tried to change it back to Connor Eats Pants
and then the name is still like gone.
It's just like removed from the pool of names now.
Dude, do you see what I just wrote in the general?
I don't even know my own user.
I'm Scarlet Otter and some numbers.
I genuinely don't know what it is.
It's on the screen.
It's 505.
Is it?
Yeah, it's right below.
Yeah.
Jerma just posted lewd photos in the general chat.
I can't believe it.
All right, let me get Michael.
Oh, that was Lily that added me.
I was like, wow, that person's got the $100 edition of the game
and they tried to add me.
I should have known considering their name was Lily.
How many L's?
I hope I got that right.
That was like, yeah, Michael's name.
There you go.
All right, profile pics.
I can't believe we're getting some e-daters, dude.
All right, here we go.
Good.
All right, no hazards.
Seven minutes, four ring outs.
All right, all the maps are good.
All right, so I'm going bugs again.
Dude, just use your main.
Yep, I'm ready.
I can't believe the matching profile pics.
We got to one up that.
Do you want to do?
I don't know.
What do you have?
Do you have the LeBron profile picture?
The basketball?
No.
I have the...
Just copy theirs.
Just copy?
Put on the Steven Universe star.
Oh, wait, it doesn't change.
No, it doesn't change it.
Oh, I thought you didn't like Steven Universe, though.
I thought you didn't like it.
I just wanted to like scare them.
I just wanted to like match their profile pics.
Then we could like maybe get in their head a little bit.
Why is my voice pitched up?
It is.
I think they mean like when I talk.
Oh, no, it is now, though.
Oh, it is, right?
Yeah, you're like you're more than pitched up.
You're like like a bit of robot pitched up.
Dude, yeah, I got to go XLR.
It's fucking cool.
Yeah, wait, hold on.
I got this.
I don't know.
There we go.
Do you just keep this on?
Should we keep it on?
Let's go.
Let's go for it.
Dude, funny voices stream.
Yes, people love that.
I'm glad you understand like the rhythm of like, oh, we're stuck on the waiting screen
and I don't know what to do for the stream.
I'm just going to start pressing buttons on the go XLR.
Yeah, that's kind of how it goes.
These carrots are just good, by the way.
I got to start having carrots on command.
That's a good idea.
Are you eating carrots and playing Bugs Bunny?
That was a joke and we lost.
I got these big ass just like Omega carrots and it was going to be like,
oh, we're going to win Bugs and it's going to be funny.
It's not funny.
Give like a Bugs catchphrase you can do on command.
Yeah, I'll give it to you.
Ready?
You give it to me.
What's up, Jack?
That was pretty good.
That was phenomenal, Jerma.
Pretty good one.
That was genuinely great.
Oh, thank you.
Are you guys waiting to start?
Peter Griffin.
Yeah, we're ready.
We're ready to go.
Yeah, you're Bugs Bunny and I'm like Peter Griffin trying to do a Bugs Bunny.
That's going to be in my head now.
You guys fucked me up.
We're going to lose.
They should add Peter.
Yeah, they should.
What does it sound like with the filter on?
What's up, Jack?
Are we supposed to play?
What's up, bro?
We should go.
It just sounds like you're going like,
like you just ate the fucking like hot fucking Cheetos.
Should we go?
Are we ready?
I don't know.
Is that?
Did he say blood wig?
Did he say go?
I think he said go.
I think, I think we go.
Are we going to go?
Go.
Go?
Well, I see like the other streams look like they're playing.
All right, let's go.
You guys, you guys can start.
Oh, yeah, we did.
Okay, okay, just getting some lag.
The game is just lagging a little bit.
There's a lot of scarlet otters online.
It's kind of messing with the netcode.
Oh shit, they're in universe.
They get 10% damage buff.
Is that real?
Yeah.
So if we don't get the Scooby Doo stage, then they're going to be triple buffed.
All right, let's just, let's just make it happen.
Let's go.
You ready to have a sip of green tea?
Yep.
We're not going to be on the stage too, right?
Uh oh.
Are we on their stage?
Oh God, that's a net, that's 20% damage.
This might be rigged is what I'm thinking.
I don't know if Ludwig can hear us, but I've heard that there's a conspiracy against us.
Sometimes I heard people were saying that mentioning that they killed Jerry.
Whoa.
There it is.
I got her solo.
There it goes.
Whoa.
We're good.
Oh my God.
We're better, Jerma.
Just keep it up.
Don't say that.
We don't know.
It'll be a massive comeback.
You don't know.
Oh, that kills.
Oh, they have the profile pick buff too.
Oh my God.
We're good.
Get that knockout.
Oh my God, he's so slippery.
So slippery.
All right, we got it.
Good, good, good.
That was an accident, but it worked.
Oh my goodness.
We almost just got double taken out.
That was almost so bad.
Oh, one hit, one hit, one hit.
Just die.
Oh, just one hit, one hit, one hit, one hit, one hit.
He's dead.
Okay, we're good.
Good, good, good, good, good.
Yes.
We got one.
What's up, Doc?
I just bit my tongue in half.
We're good.
I'm so happy.
We did it.
We got one.
I screamed so loud.
That was a really good match.
They could have taken that any second.
We played with heart, though.
They could have taken that at any second.
All right, we're going to stick with what we have,
or we're going to go change it up.
I think we stick with it.
If it works, it works, right?
We've only been beaten by an iron giant.
All right, okay.
I feel like my Bugs is off today.
Maybe I'll go Superman.
I feel off today, too.
Something's in the air.
Yeah, I'm sleeping on my Superman.
My Superman's actually probably better than my Bugs.
My Bugs aren't that great.
Maybe time to bring up Superman next time.
Do you have a good Superman line?
Yeah, believe everything to me.
Yeah.
And then he goes down, and he farts.
The only super media I've seen is the Zack Snyder movie,
so he doesn't really do that.
He's more upset.
Here we go.
Just be careful.
Be careful.
Let's go.
Wait a minute.
There he is.
It's a beta keratin, I think.
That was deficient.
Improved your eyesight.
That's how the carrots work.
I mean, it's been like 20 minutes
since I took the first bite, right?
Yep.
Oh, my God.
Good game, good game.
You went off that game.
Something was in you.
Might have been the carrots.
You were an animal that round.
The beta keratin finally kicked in.
Do you have a mouthful of carrots?
Yep.
I love that.
Congratulations, you two.
Great edge guard on the left side.
Great win.
And you're moving on.
Yeah, good game, good game.
I just kind of popped off.
Like, that's all, is it?
I don't know what happened, man.
Something got in you.
They almost took that first game, though.
That was good.
That was a good match.
All right.
So the biggest losers bracket run of all time
is what people are saying is about to happen.
Essentially the best losers run
in multiverses history.
What the fuck?
I just look like an idiot.
What?
What's wrong?
Look at the lobby.
It looks like I did that and you didn't.
And you were convincing me not to do that.
Wait, you're still the skull for me.
I'm not on my screen.
Oh, that's embarrassing.
Oh, God.
No, but that's not supposed to be like that.
That was something we did before.
That's all right.
Oh, come on.
I feel like, wow, I can't believe this.
That was just Scarlett Otter guy
just changed his profile picture to ours.
That was your fucking idea.
I'm on the star now, too, for what it's worth.
That's not what I...
We were doing the thing at the...
Why did it change now?
Oh, my God.
I hope they understand that.
Please, I hope they understand that.
I'm not trying to be like Dick.
That looks so bad.
These french fries are pretty good.
Dude, do you have any carrots?
No.
Really?
No, I don't have any carrots.
I'm telling you, that's what changed.
I think I do need some.
Oh, wait, there it goes.
It changed back.
Oh, now I have the star.
Stop making enemies.
They're awesome people.
What are you talking about?
Did you ever tell them
the story of you meeting Mr. Beast?
No.
Because I told it...
I told from my perspective that story.
It was really funny.
You can tell it.
I'm sorry.
Yeah.
So I took Jerma to the Ninja Mr. Beast event,
the League of Legends event.
And we go backstage to Mr. Beast's team room.
And it's just a few people in there.
And I was like, okay.
Jerma, you can say hi to Mr. Beast.
Now, Mr. Beast was very much like hyper focused
on like league mode.
He was only focused on that,
looking at his iPad or whatever,
looking over game plans.
And they were sitting on the couch
and Jerma goes like,
I think you said something like,
hey, I'm Jerma.
He didn't say anything.
Like, he was just there.
And I was like, oh, no.
And I was like, hey, Jimmy, Jimmy.
This is Jerma.
He's a YouTuber.
And he was like, oh, okay.
Hey, nice to meet you.
And I was like, okay.
Well, kind of saved.
And then I'm like, no, no, no, don't worry.
He definitely watched your TF2 videos.
He's a busy guy, right?
He's a busy guy.
But he knew who you were after.
Well, even if he doesn't, that's fine.
You expect everybody to know who you are.
It was kind of funny, though.
Yeah, it was probably funny.
He's the sus guy.
Tell me the sus guy.
Yeah, he's the sus guy, right?
Yeah.
But, okay, let me ask you something.
Yep.
Would MrBeast know me more as the sus guy
or as the guy that used to make TF2 videos like 12 years ago?
I think, honestly, TF2 videos,
he's a very old school YouTube guy.
He is, right?
Isn't he?
Maybe sus guy, too, though.
That might ring a few bells.
How'd it even happen?
I just remember randomly at some point,
it was like sus was now associated with you.
Just like appeared.
Somebody made a meme, which was like,
oh, look, when the imposter is sus,
and I put it on my screen for five seconds.
That'll do it.
Wasn't there the guy that like burned that image into his TV?
Oh, yeah.
That guy was full of shit, though.
It's 10 years, not 12.
Well, it's 2022, going into 2023.
It'll be 11.
Sorry.
I've been making videos since 2007.
I made a, I would recall.
How old were you?
I was eight years old.
What?
I got a camcorder, my mom's camcorder,
and I would use the macro function
to zoom in from far away to the focus work
on my Nintendo DS Pokemon Diamond Wi-Fi battles.
Wow.
That's unbelievable.
Eight years old.
And I was bad.
I was very bad at the game,
and I didn't understand how the tiers worked.
I'm like, why couldn't you use certain Pokemon?
Because they were too good.
And so I would join battles,
and they'd be like, you can't use this guy.
And I would just be like, no, I'm using this Jirachi.
I want to use it.
And it was just like a completely cheated Pokemon, too.
But I enjoyed it.
Remember, you were like 60 when he was eight.
Someone said, so that's why you were like this.
Yeah, no, that is why.
That's what happened.
As a kid, I was pissed they didn't let me use Charizard.
Okay, well, you're just wrong,
because Charizard's not even that good.
So he's never been banned.
I made that up, acting like I don't know the tiers of Pokemon.
Come on, now.
What's your favorite Pokemon?
Favorite Pokemon?
Probably Wooper.
Who's Wooper?
You don't know Wooper?
All I know, I know like 10 Pokemon.
Okay, I know all of them.
Oh, you do?
Name all 150 original Pokemon right now.
I honestly, there's a 20% chance you name a number of the first 150,
and I might be able to tell you which one it is.
Okay.
Um.
Eight.
Vermilion.
I got to get like a thing to see.
Original 150 Pokemon.
And they had their numbered?
Is it?
Okay, let's see.
That was a softball one, was it?
Okay, hold on, let me see.
Let me get the list here.
Bit of a softball.
Was it a softball?
Yeah, because the first nine are all starters, right?
And so I just remembered it started Bulbasaur,
then it was Squirtle, and then it was Charmander.
So then number eight would be Charmeleon.
What?
How do you know that?
Okay, so hold on, let me get, I got one here.
All right, I'll give you, let's get you a tough one.
Oh, it's Wartortle?
Oh, nevermind.
I messed up then.
Oh, you messed up?
Yeah.
All right, how about number 30?
Um, I think, I think Raichu's 26.
God damn, I have the wrong,
this is original 150 Pokemon according to my boyfriend.
It's like they're all just fake names.
Hold on.
Oh, well, let me take,
give me a hint as to what that one's boyfriend name is.
They're blue?
Oh, Nidorino, Nidorina, one of them.
Um, one of them, the one before it is,
they call it Water Mouse.
It's a blue mouse and it's like,
Oh yeah, Nidorina.
Okay, but the one after that is the one that's apparently 30.
Uh, wait, Nidoran is one of them.
Okay.
Oh wait, here's a, here's a list.
Here's an actual list, okay.
How about, um, 39?
39, um.
Do you want me to give you a hint?
Jigglypuff, Jigglypuff.
That's so much more than a hint.
That's, it's Jigglypuff.
Oh, okay, good.
You got it.
All right, what's the name of the Pokemon?
What's 41?
You said Jigglypuff was what?
39.
Trousy?
Sorry, it's Zubat.
Yeah.
Okay, how about, let's-
I could at least name every Pokemon up to like,
if I saw Silhouette, I could name, I think almost every Pokemon.
That's so cool.
All right, what about, who's 149?
Not 150.
We know, we all know who that is.
149 is, uh, Dragonair.
Damn, okay, what about 148?
Dragonair.
All right, what about 147?
Keep it up.
Dratini.
Damn, okay, 146.
Articuno or Moltres?
Moltres, you got it.
145.
Uh, Articuno.
Very close.
Yep, 144 is Articuno.
It's Articuno, and then before that would be-
143.
Joltia?
Mm-mm, mm-mm.
Is it one of those Eevees?
Nope, I'll give you a hint.
Very sleepy.
Oh, Snorlax, Snorlax.
You got it.
That's it.
Drowsy, I'm like, he's not that far up.
Well, you got a lot in a row.
That was impressive.
No, yeah, you're like, this is really cool,
but no, it was bad because like, in school,
all of my knowledge was just reserved for Pokemon information,
and I did really bad because like,
my brain just wouldn't care about like,
knowledge I needed to know for tests.
It was only reserved for Pokemon.
Yeah, I mean, that's, I mean, you had an interest.
Yeah, that's true.
Can you imagine-
It ended up working out.
Okay, but can you imagine if instead of just like,
random stupid dumb math problems, they made it so like,
oh, like Sally has five carrots,
Jason has 15 carrots.
Don't you think if they just made it,
like Squirtle has 15 carrots,
and Charizard has seven carrots that you would care more.
You'd be like, oh, six, Charizard's got carrots.
Charizard's gonna care more.
Why don't they do that?
I don't know.
When I was in kindergarten, I went to a like,
church school, and then they banned Pokemon like,
right when I got there.
They were like, you can't talk about Pokemon.
And then my mom complained.
It was like, my son likes this.
He's gonna talk about it.
Sorry.
And then I was allowed to talk about Pokemon
during recess only.
Only during recess though, not during school time.
Not every kid likes Pokemon though.
Yeah, but couldn't you pull the class on like,
on a ranked system?
Okay, you got like, the Looney Tunes.
You got like, Rugrats, Ren and Stimpy,
Steven Universe, whatever.
Just have them rank how much they like it,
and then base the whole curriculum.
Just replace all the dumb boring, like a train
leaves Boston going, you know, 200 miles per hour,
and you know, 10 miles to go visit New Jersey, right?
Just make it like Steven Universe,
just traveling 200 miles per hour to go visit Charizard.
Not my son.
My son is not gonna be learning from Steven Universe.
Not on my watch.
He'll be, it'll be Bugs Bunny.
It'll be Tom and Jerry.
It'll be Ren and Stimpy.
It'll be not that, anything but that.
So they're moving way too fast.
When is our next game, sir?
How does, are we just like ignoring people?
What's the deal?
I think we just been, we were seated so high
that we're waiting for our next game.
Oh, that makes sense.
It's like a bracket.
My physics teacher used to make tests
with Dragon Ball characters.
Yeah, and did you get an A+, because you loved that anime?
I did not care for anime at all as a kid.
My friends really liked Dragon Ball a ton.
Like, they would always like, they pretend
and like, be Dragon Ball characters.
And so I watched the show and I didn't care about like,
the super like, Saiyan characters.
So I found out there was a turtle.
Like, there's a character that just owns a turtle.
Like, it's like an old man that has a pet turtle.
And so I would play pretend by just curling up
in a ball on the ground and then being the turtle.
And that was how I had fun in that.
How long was your like, recess?
Like, 20 minutes.
20 minutes?
This wasn't recess though.
This was like, I wouldn't do that at school.
Kids would have made fun of me.
This was around close friends.
Oh, okay, that hurt.
Hold on.
I'm just imagining you at recess.
No, no, no.
That would have been bad if kids were like,
why is he being a turtle at recess?
No, no, no.
That would have been bad.
That would be like, I mean, who didn't do, wait,
you didn't do the let's pretend to be animals at recess?
Yeah.
Well, maybe.
I think, yeah, I definitely did that, I think.
Yeah, that wouldn't be out of the ordinary.
No, no.
When my close friends like, hang out at their house,
like our parents are hanging out, right?
Like, so we're just upstairs playing pretend
and they play Dragon Ball.
I'm like, okay, I'll be the turtle.
Because I didn't care.
That's awesome.
Wait, people in chat are saying, you know,
the things they usually say.
So wait, there was not one point when you were younger
at recess where you went around going like this
with your arm, going like, why can't,
you know, are they like an elephant?
Like, you didn't run around like an elephant
or like a horse or something?
Like, what are you talking about?
Yes, you did.
I don't know if I, yeah, I mean, I recall like
doing the arm thing, I guess, to be an elephant,
but I don't know if I like chose to be the elephant.
That was never like one I went for.
Like, I'm a bear, like, rawr.
I didn't mane elephant.
I was more of like a cheetah guy or maybe a lion.
Yeah.
That's not furry behavior.
That's just your, like, seven.
Yeah, I want to know which furry is like an elephant.
I've never heard of that before.
Yeah, that definitely exists.
My mane.
I didn't mane elephant that I did.
Guys, I'm not streaming with a furry.
It's okay, guys.
Okay.
It's pretending to be Sonic Count.
I think so.
I love to be Sonic.
Yeah, but so what, so wait, how come, so when it's a cool animal,
that's okay, but when it's an elephant, I'm the weird kid.
What are you talking about?
You're pretending to be a hedgehog running fast.
Sonic's like super fast, though, and elephants are really slow.
So?
That makes Sonic cooler, though.
He's like the fastest thing ever.
But it's still a hedgehog.
It's like a different, though.
Like, if you saw like a real hedgehog next to Sonic,
you'd be like, yeah, those are two different things.
Yeah, that's true.
Even Sonic doesn't pretend to be a hedgehog.
Yeah, I don't even know if he is, honestly.
He might just be insane and thinks that he is.
We pretended to be Dragon Ball characters.
Step up your game.
Yeah, but there's all kinds of fun media to pretend to be.
When are they going to add John Oliver to the game?
He is Warner Bros now.
That'd be cool.
I don't want to do it.
Don't make me do it.
No, don't make me do it.
Don't make me do John Oliver.
Don't make me do it.
Was that the reason that guy came here for the first time to ask me
that was to try to bait me into reading it so that you would do the John Oliver?
I'm not going to do it.
No, I can't.
No.
About John Oliver doing a what's up doc.
All right, gamers.
I thought that was it.
I was like, wait a minute.
Your time.
It's your time.
You want to go?
Let's go.
Who are we going against?
Stan's in Alpha Red.
All right.
OK.
So go ahead and set that one up.
You can start that up whenever it's ready.
Cool.
OK.
I will add them.
These guys are pretty good at gaming.
They are?
Well, so are we.
We'll be fine.
We're better at gaming sometimes.
Hey, so are we.
This could be our day.
I'm not playing Rhyndog, guys.
I'm not doing that.
Unless I lose.
If I lose the first round, I'll play Rhyndog.
Yeah, we'll switch it up before you lose.
Oh, OK.
What is Alpha?
There we go.
OK.
Rhyndog be like, mmm, french fry.
Yeah, he does be like that.
That's what he does.
All right.
I've sent them both invites.
Change profile pics.
You don't get caught using the Steven Universe one.
Thank you for reminding me.
Oh, oh, shit.
They're in a game.
Oh, they're in a game.
See, we just talked about, like, playing Pokemon.
We didn't practice.
We could have been practicing this whole time.
We could have.
Wow, it's been like 20 minutes, too, hasn't it?
Yep.
Well, whatever.
I think we're OK.
Did you at least, like, eat more carrots?
I'm on it.
Carrots are wearing off?
Nope.
I'm going to make sure there's a stream of carrots.
Wait, Connor, is your birthday?
Is it actually your birthday?
No, it's not.
My birthday is, like, not this Friday.
Two weeks from Friday.
Well, happy birthday.
Happy early birthday.
Thanks.
It's my birthday.
Here we go.
All right.
All right, let's do a repeat of last time.
Oh, this guy's got a cool profile picture.
OK.
Oh, he's the loony king.
Jerma, do you have that one?
What's the loony king?
It's the profile picture Alpharet has.
I think he gets that from being, like, really good at Bugs Bunny, I think.
What?
Reached mastery level 14 on Bugs Bunny.
Are you not mastery level?
No.
Oh, no.
I always get to, like, right before mastery and change character.
Because I don't want anyone.
I don't need that to be good.
Right.
So we can go whenever, right?
I get really, like, self-conscious about, like, if people can tell that, like, I've
played the game a good bit in an online game so that I can always have the excuse of, like,
oh, well, like, I don't even play that much.
Like, get a life, go outside.
And then, like, I leave the game.
That's what I do in, like, Valorant.
Like, Overwatch.
Let me just make sure.
Should I go right when we're ready?
Or are we waiting for the go ahead?
I'm assuming we can start.
But I could be wrong.
Change character?
You could try Superman if you want.
I could try Superman.
That's a good call.
I'm going to go Superman.
Change it up.
Here comes the heat.
I don't think I even have perks on Superman, though.
Oh, well.
As long as I'm standing.
Oh, shit.
Hold on.
Uh-oh.
No way!
Hey!
It's all right.
You get time here to do it.
Cool down duration?
What are you playing as?
Commentary.
Yeah, yeah.
You can do cool down if you want.
Cool down.
5% melee damage.
Oh, hell no.
How you guys feeling going into this?
I feel pretty good.
Level 18 Velma.
I mean, I don't have a perk, which is, you know, should be illegal.
Oh, they're matching perks, too.
I would never do that.
Hey, watch this.
We're good.
Stacking perks is like a sign that, like, you're afraid, I think.
Here we go.
You ready?
Let's go.
Yep.
I got beta keratin flowing through my bloodstream.
I'm getting gaming stints.
Shit.
Oh, my God.
The top of my control stick fell off.
Oh, man.
OK.
Sorry.
Literally, Jerma, like, the top of the Xbox controller thumbstick fell off.
You got a controller problem?
It fell off of the controller.
There's no stick.
We got to get rid of this fucking Superman.
I know.
I'm trying.
There you go.
One more time.
What?
Oh, you're being arrested.
Oh, my goodness gracious.
Good.
Sorry.
All together.
Speed up on the Superman.
They're going to be hitting gamer fatigue really soon here.
Yep.
They're too confident.
That's not what I meant to do.
Oh, I had it.
There it is.
We're good.
Good.
Velma.
No.
Spiker.
Sorry.
We almost brought it back.
Man, listen.
If we had host, that spike hits.
Sorry.
That was a good game.
Good game.
Very close.
Oh, my God.
A 3D2.
All right.
I'm going.
Here's the plan.
Ready?
I'm going back to Bugs.
OK.
No, I think I stay on Tom and Jerry chat.
I know you guys want rindog.
But I don't think I'm going to win with rindog.
I don't know how to play that guy.
And I ran out of carrots.
This is the part you don't eat.
Oh, no.
You have to eat it.
No, it's the part you can't even eat.
It's the part.
You have to eat it.
OK.
Fine.
Hold on.
Wait.
Let me just do my level up spell.
What the?
What?
Whoa.
All right.
Let's go.
Show them what we got.
We can pull it back here.
We're going to win.
I know you can eat that part.
I'm kidding.
Hey, Connor, even if we lose.
You still want to play multiverse really well?
Yeah, I'm down.
We're going to win this one right here.
You ready to get out of that thing?
Keep it up.
OK.
Let's try again.
Tried to bait him.
We're good.
Shit.
I tried to deal with him.
We need a spike here.
Ah, fuck that car.
Here we go.
I got Velma.
Let's go.
Go, go, go, go.
She's low.
How did that not hit him?
He's just baiting us.
He's baiting us.
We got hit Velma.
All right.
Go, go, go, go, go.
Velma, let's try.
Oh, help.
No.
How do they keep?
No, no, no.
We got it.
Oh, sorry.
Sorry.
I don't understand.
Damn it.
I missed the spike.
If I didn't miss the spike, we would have won.
Oh, fuck.
I missed the spike.
I just don't understand.
Things that usually work weren't working.
You guys are doing great.
Honestly, their strat of having Velma in the back,
Superman in the front was pretty hard to deal with.
And I think you guys adapted pretty well.
I'm saying that we're the most honest team in the tournament
is what people have been saying, actually,
is that Tom and Jerry and Bugs is potentially the most ethical.
Ethically and morally, I think you guys are in the lead.
I have mixed feelings about Batman deciding to kill in this game
after signing a lifelong vow.
So yeah, you guys are spot on.
It's true.
That was a good match.
We almost had it.
Well, you guys are free to go.
Thanks for your playing.
Thanks.
I still have like $100.
Wait, does fifth place get anything?
Are we fifth place, fourth place?
You guys are fifth place, tied for fifth.
You get nothing at all, but a big high five.
OK, that's a high five.
It's fine.
So not bad.
Not bad.
Anyway, enjoy the rest of your streams, gentlemen.
Yeah, thanks for the invite.
Every time you've been here, I've been chewing on a carrot.
I feel like that's rude.
I think you do it after every game,
and that's just when I come in.
Yo, we got to invite you guys.
We're next up.
This is Dr. Battle and Sheep for Hire.
We lost.
We won.
Oh, you lost?
I'm sorry.
I thought I was going to be one.
I marked the bracket wrong.
Oh, he marked the bracket wrong.
Sorry.
I thought we were going to play.
I was just looking at the bracket.
I'm sorry, guys.
Yeah, we went off script, actually.
I didn't mean to do that to you.
I was rooting for you guys right after us.
We're Stans haters.
We hate Stans.
Wait, I love the Stans show.
Calm down, all right?
The Stans show's dead.
That's why we hate them.
Task manager was better, they say.
Where are you guys in the bracket right now?
We're up against the Stans.
Oh, all right.
Okay.
Yeah, we got our ring game.
Connor, we tied with you.
You want to, for honor, do you guys want to, you know, just go onward?
Do you want to decide for fourth place?
Yeah, I'm tied with you.
Yeah, I'm down.
Yeah, let's decide fourth place.
Let's do it.
Cool, cool, cool, cool.
Connor eats pants, yeah?
Yeah, no, Connor from Dream SMP.
Okay, got it.
I've already sent you a request.
Wait, you're the, you were on the Dream SMP, weren't you?
I am on the Dream SMP.
Oh, R, okay, wow.
Like, wait, so do you know Schlatt?
Yes, yes.
Dude, no way.
I think you're the four, like, Valor guy, stolen Valor.
Sorry, Jerma, this happens a lot.
There's a lot of-
Oh my God, dude.
Yes, hey guys.
My younger sister loves you guys.
I know, probably.
I'll invite you to the lobby.
She was wondering when you're going to start posting
Minecraft YouTube videos, though?
Tell her that, tell her Connor eats pants.
He retired, he's a new guy now.
They recasted him, he's different now.
Who's playing him now?
Jared Leto, I think.
That's crazy.
No, hopefully not.
I didn't approve of that.
Well, you don't have to, you don't have to approve of them, really.
Well.
You don't like Jared Leto?
No.
Andy Carrot, someone's really upset that-
Yeah, that's all I have.
I'm just like, oh, remember the guy that was at the multiverse tournament,
that ate carrots, like, that was what was funny?
Oh, there's like fucking like a hundred thousand people
probably concurrently watching the stream.
I'm the funny guy that chews the carrot.
Yeah, like that's all I have right now.
It's literally the only thing I have today.
We'll just run at random.
Cool.
This is for all the glory.
It's for all the fourth place.
This is to get the one point in Mario Kart.
I said that I would gift fourth place a sub, each of them a sub to Amaranth.
Okay.
I didn't say that.
You say you're already subbed, Connor?
Oh, yeah, no, I'm like on a 14 month streak, I think.
And it's tier three, right?
No, no, I don't have it like that.
Ready to go?
Oh, I'll tell you what, I'll tier three, yeah, then we'll do that.
Okay.
Good luck, guys.
All right, I think we stayed, we stayed, what we got?
Oh, they wanted to play Rhyme Dog.
Yeah, I'm not doing that.
Maybe next time.
Are you guys going for fifth?
No, this is fourth.
All I want is the one point in fourth place at Mario Kart.
That's all I care about.
Cause then-
Did you eat another carrot?
Yeah.
Good.
Cause then we placed, right?
If you come in fourth place, you place.
Well, like do we win something?
Cause I don't think so.
No.
But like we do place fourth, which is like right below like top three.
Yeah, I'm okay with that.
Yeah, it's for fifth, not fourth.
Oh, okay.
Well, top five.
These guys don't even have any perks.
Well, let's get that fourth place.
Put on your chapstick.
How did the top come off the controller?
I have the Xbox Elite controller so you can switch out the thumbsticks.
And then I was gaming so hard that the left one popped off and it was just a little nub.
Let's go for it.
All right.
Get that.
Oh, nice attempt.
They almost had it.
Yep.
It cost them their items.
Where the hell did this come from?
Oh, that's you, right?
You can pull out an item.
Yep.
Oh, I got him.
I got him early too.
Oh, I could have gone for the counter.
There it is.
Dude, you are on point this game.
Yep.
There it is.
Nice stuff.
There we go.
You were on point that game.
I was gaming.
I probably did like 30 damage that game.
You're probably like 500.
You hard carried that game.
This place matters.
Four KOs, damn.
Nice game.
That was good.
All right.
I'll play Rhyndog now, guys.
We got to solidify the win.
You don't want to play Rhyndog?
You can play Rhyndog when we're just goofing around.
Oh, okay.
That's fair.
See, I agree.
They were just...
Some people were really...
There was like two Rhyndog fans that were really losing it.
He's literally like an original character.
Somebody just said, suck my ass.
Time that person up for like 35 seconds.
That's probably one of mine.
Yeah, that sounds like something one of my guys would say.
35 seconds or 35 years?
Somewhere in between.
Let's take the average.
All right, we got to solidify fourth place.
I'm happy with fourth place if we get it.
He's like a reindeer dog.
I just now realized that.
I'm trying to get the early knockout.
Hit that spike.
There it is.
Oh, what?
I guess not.
I almost got it.
There it is.
Nice job.
All right, get it.
Double it up.
There it is.
Nice job.
Okay.
We've done it again.
That was a good fight.
That was good.
We did it.
Fifth place.
No, this is fourth.
Looks like somebody is a sore loser.
They kept saying it was for fit.
You carried again.
Yeah, no, I just wanted to...
Yeah, we just wanted to goof.
Gift you a sub to Amaranth, really.
I'm just...
Thank you.
Good games.
Appreciate it.
Trying to fund you guys.
Let me just get those going real quick.
Let me just exit out of multiverse.
This is a bad game.
You know what I mean?
That's a great game.
No, it's bad.
I think it's phenomenal.
It's a fantastic video game.
It is.
All right.
Well...
It's truly great.
Jerma, what are you eating?
Ham sandwich.
Any cheese?
No, no cheese.
Just mustard.
Just mustard and ham.
I like it.
Mustard ham and two...
Man of class.
One piece of whole wheat bread.
You don't even have two?
It's almost like a hot dog.
Your bread lasts a lot longer that way.
I mean, I guess that's true.
Is it a wrap then, almost?
You could fold it and eat it like a slice of pizza.
Interesting that you went with pizza on the fold it one.
And it's ham and mustard.
Ham, mustard, one piece of whole wheat.
Fold it up like a piece of pizza.
Take a bite, you're golden.
Maybe a little smoothie.
Honor, here's your tier...
I can't give the tier three to you.
Open face liar.
Told you, I'm already a son.
Wait, you're lying?
No, dude.
I just gifted Connor Eats Pant.
No, no, no, no.
Fuck.
Connor.
That is a 25 dollars down the drain there.
Oh, no.
Okay.
That is too bad.
You're not a sub, you piece of shit.
So I just...
Whoa.
Is this edible?
You're taking an edible?
What?
No, I said, is this edible?
The tier three sub?
This piece of this carrot.
This is not even a carrot.
This is like fucking spinach.
Oh, it was for the aesthetic.
And that's what it was.
Jerma, would you both go to...
Let me just make sure I don't type in the wrong one.
Jerma, nine, eight, five, right.
Would you guys do me a favor and go to her stream
to validate that I have, in fact, given you tier three emotes?
I'll find out.
Why can't I gift you a sub, Jerma?
I don't know.
Give me one?
I might have already been gifted this years.
Okay.
Is there another streamer that you would like a gifted sub to?
Um, Conrad Smith.
My God.
Incredible choice.
Holy shit.
Jerma.
Wait, I might be subbed to you too.
Wait, let's see.
Jerma, nine, eight, five.
Hey, I've got a chat I don't think he's subbed to.
No, you're good.
I got it.
Oh, okay.
Here you go.
Got it.
Okay.
Not.
That sucks.
There you go.
Now you can use the...
What do you have?
A gold car?
You got it.
Yeah, you got the gold frog.
Oh, shit.
There it is.
It's a tier three.
I thought we were doing tier one.
All right.
No, tier threes.
I think there's an emote of just some guy's face for tier three too.
Wait, let me do some emotes.
All right.
Let me try.
Where are we?
All right.
So what's the tier three?
Connor six, that guy's face.
Connor six, that guy's face is what I typed.
Okay.
Yeah, there's shit.
Well, it's like capital T and then G and then...
Connor six, that guy's face.
Connor, in your chat, can you use a tier three emote so we can...
I got to see that guy's face.
What is that guy's face?
So I did an emote contest and then like he submitted like emote ideas
and then one guy just submitted a photo of his face
and then it ended up winning for like tier three.
Really?
That's incredible.
Now there's an emote that's just that guy's face that I...
Connor six, that guy's face.
How many of these can I do?
There you go.
Okay.
Well, there he is.
There you go.
There we go.
What does Ammo have?
Does she have that guy's face?
I don't think so.
Maybe, we'll see.
All right.
Well, we're going to go play online.
I will see you guys.
Yeah, you guys have two letters.
Good match.
I appreciate it.
Good games.
Yeah, have a good game, guys.
Thanks for the tier three.
Yeah, dude.
No problem.
Anytime.
Get some good emotes now.
Nice to meet you.
Yeah, you too.
All right.
Let's show them up online.
Let's show the public matches.
You want to do some public?
Yeah, let's do some public matches.
We can just leave this right here.
I think so.
I think I can.
Oh, I got to pull you in again.
Oh, yeah.
I think so.
There we go.
I had to verify that was the real Scarlet Otter.
Yeah, so we got fourth place.
I'm OK with that.
Let's solidify that.
Fourth place is fine.
Maybe in the next one, we get third.
That's all right.
Once they add Johnny Bravo to the game.
Wait, how was it fifth place?
Is it really fifth?
No.
I'll say that.
How many teams were there?
I thought there was six teams.
You tied for fifth.
Four and a half place.
Fourth loses to third.
The tie was between fifth and sixth.
Oh, there were eight teams.
Oh, so now wouldn't we be tied for fourth?
Four and a half.
We're four and a half.
Oh, well, whatever.
That's right in the middle.
Why is the streamer so awkward?
That's just how I am, dude.
That's just like my phone.
Who said that?
Did they say that in my channel?
No.
Better not have.
Buy the Rhyndog skin.
No, we didn't even win the tournament, guys.
I don't have enough to buy the Rhyndog skin.
Oh, these guys have the buff.
They have what?
Oh, yeah.
Wait, is that actually a thing?
No.
Because I kept committing, too.
And I was like, wait, maybe he's serious
because we're getting kind of screwed up on this stage.
No, Velma is just really good.
Velma is really good.
Bugs is really good, too.
If you know what you're doing with Velma, you are terrifying.
Whoa.
I don't know what that does.
That was kind of crazy.
I'm just pressing buttons.
And maybe I'm a Rhyndog guy.
You might be.
Whoa.
How did he just didn't go off the screen?
That was weird.
Well, he's dead.
Why would I hit him up?
The Rhyndog is awesome.
You like Rhyndog?
He's awesome.
He's a little dog.
I don't know.
What noise does Rhyndog make?
He's a reindeer dog.
Yeah, I don't know.
Rhyndog?
Oh, that makes a lot more sense.
You got all four KOs.
Man.
Yeah, the Rhyndog thing.
The person just said, wait, I need to eat?
Did they just write that?
What?
This person just said, I got to go.
I have to eat.
I have to eat dinner or something.
Are they not allowed to go eat?
Was that like an emote?
It had an emote that said it.
What are you talking about?
Jake just said, hey, I got to go.
I got to eat.
Oh, OK.
I see.
I thought you're saying somebody in your chat said an emote that said,
I got to go eat.
I was like, what are you talking about?
What did it take up with the whole chat?
I was like, yeah, it's kind of a weird emote.
Hey, I got to go.
I've got to go eat.
It's like a 50-part emote.
Just if you leave the game, they have some dialogue sometimes.
This is a great choice.
Holy joy.
I forgot to.
I didn't pick Rain Dog.
That's so surreal.
Make sure you're filling up your thing.
Wait, get this off.
I'll put the Burger King guy on.
I think I'm going to try this game.
You actually should.
The game's fantastic.
Genuinely speaking, the game's very good.
It's really fun.
Oh, we're not sponsored today, guys.
Sorry.
That's not what this is.
This is not sponsored.
We're just playing.
I liked the game before I was sponsored.
You know what?
Me too.
I played it back when it was first in that little alpha.
They did whatever it was.
Don't you come talking smack to me.
That basketball just ruined everything he was doing.
You went Daffy in this game, right?
Oh, so bad.
That'd be cool.
It'd be cool if he had Duck Dodger's moves, too.
Missed that one.
My bad.
What the what?
Oh, my goodness.
Your favorite Looney Tunes episode?
Um, it's it's Tiny Tunes.
It's how I spent my summer vacation from franchise.
Oh, I used to love Tiny Tunes.
They were like different.
They weren't even like it wasn't bugs.
It was like different rabbits.
Yeah, they were like it was how I spent my summer vacation.
Happy Worldland.
It was the Flucky and Porky the Pig's son.
Oh, yeah, yeah, yeah.
I don't know what you're talking about.
I liked for Looney Tunes.
I like the one where like bugs like ghost like different.
Forgive me what it was.
Like different animation that mostly looks like it's like trap.
And then no, is it is it Daffy that does it at the end?
He's like, I can't even remember how to recall it.
Someone knows what I'm talking about.
Daffy gets like stuck in like something.
Sorry.
Sorry if I startled you.
No, you're fine.
Maybe so.
I don't know the name.
How am I still here?
There we go.
Oh, I missed it.
I can't believe LeBron James in this game.
It's crazy.
He thinks the next real person will add besides John Oliver.
So you don't have to do it.
Okay, the next real person.
Gandalf.
Yeah, no, that makes sense.
I mean, Gandalf is a the depiction of Gandalf.
They're going to use in this is like a real guy.
They're just going to use Ian McKellen.
Yeah, it's just Ian.
You know, I wouldn't be surprised if like they can't get the rights to like Gandalf
and Tolkien Estate.
So they just put in Ian McKellen and he has like some like wizard moves here and there.
Gandalf would be awesome.
Shaggy is not a real guy.
He's a cartoon character.
He's not a real person.
Actually, no, he is in the movies.
I kind of wish they just had like Shaggy that isn't like the meme Shaggy.
Like a Shaggy that's fighting with Scooby or something.
There's no way Scooby Doo is not in the game.
Yeah, that's crazy to me.
But I would have liked like Shaggy and Scooby as like a duo team
rather than like, oh, he's like he's like doing the meme like sing Tiny Tunes.
See if I can remember it.
We're tiny.
We're toony.
We're all a little loony.
Oh, my God.
And in this cartoony, we're invading your TV.
Fuck.
Hold on.
I lost.
I couldn't remember it.
And then you immediately brought it back to me.
We're tiny.
We're toony.
We're all a little loony.
And in this cartoony, we're invading your TV.
We cracked up all the sensors and Tiny Tune Adventures in a dose of harmony
when in Acme Acres, it's a whole wide world apart
that sets alone and made of stone and cartoon work of art.
Expect the expected.
Expect the unexpected.
With Tiny Tune Adventures, it's about to start.
I don't know.
It's something like that.
Oh, we're doing double.
I just realized what we're doing.
The thing I like doing with the brawn is you just bounce one of the balls down
and then you steal another.
So that just stays out.
There is like a thing that they keep bouncing into.
This is hell here, by the way, especially having to deal with this here.
What?
How did I live?
Oh, my goodness.
This dude.
Wow.
We.
Whoa.
That was weird.
You think LeBron even knows he's in this game or like when he signed this space jam contract,
it was like this was in here.
He didn't know this was here.
And he didn't know.
That's wicked funny.
Oh, he's just begging to be knocked over there.
OK, we're good.
Imagine like his son's like playing this game with his friends.
He walks through and he's like, is that me?
He's like, yeah, like you're in the game.
Do you think he's just like, all right, whatever.
Probably.
He has his voice.
He's like, is that me?
I can't tell.
Is it me talking?
I don't remember recording this.
Please change Omega L2.
Wowee.
It's not his voice.
Wait, it's an actor.
Yeah, it's not LeBron that voices him.
So there's a very real possibility that he does not know he's in this game.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
You're right.
Wow.
OK.
Did you see space jam too?
No, it was probably one of the worst movies ever seen.
It was really that bad.
I saw that movie and I enjoyed the first space jam as a kid.
I know it's not great looking, but I was like, OK, it's fine.
Fun movie.
This one is just so unapologetically awful.
It hurt me.
Like I was in the theater.
I'm like, wow, this is upsetting.
Like, I actually want my money back.
What was wrong with it?
It was just none of the jokes were good.
The Looney Tunes weren't even like the Looney.
They didn't do any Looney Tunes like funny bits.
They were just kind of like character archetypes that weren't the Looney Tunes.
Really?
Yeah, it was very weird.
And then like LeBron is like his performance is awful.
I hate to say it, but he doesn't know how to like, you know, do that.
He doesn't know how to talk the Looney Tunes.
And then also like E3 was like a major like plot point of the film.
It didn't make any sense.
Hold on.
Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait.
E E3 E3.
Yeah.
So LeBron's son is like, dad, I want to go to E3 camp.
And then LeBron's like, you can't go to E3 camp.
And then he's like, no, but dad, I want to.
And then the movie, it spoilers.
It ends.
The kid goes to E3 camp.
Oh, all right.
The whole time I'm watching, I'm like, E3 is not a camp.
E3 camp.
But it's literally the logo for E3.
Like they had the rights.
I don't know where it came from.
I'm like, it's not a camp.
That's so, that's strange.
That's odd.
And then it's like, they're all in a video game.
It's like the idea.
Like, oh, LeBron, you got sucked into the video game.
But then the video game is just like Don Cheadle's like AI imagination.
I feel like you're just making stuff up.
I'm literally not.
I mean, you can ask Chad.
I'm telling the truth.
And then, but like, it's like the metaverse.
I think it's the idea, but it's the metaverse.
If it was only Warner Bros characters that they own.
And so they jump like the entire first 40 minutes of the movie
is then just jumping between different properties
that like they are just Bugs Bunny and LeBron.
Like, they're like, oh, we're in Game of Thrones.
What?
And it's like, what?
DC?
Where's Batman?
And it's just like, remember all these things?
That's so weird.
I'm like, wait, where's like Daffy Duck?
Like, where is everybody?
So wait, how many minutes is Daffy Duck in the movie for?
He might have like three lives.
What?
Oh, I'm not even kidding.
You got to be shitting me.
Oh, my God.
I just got stuffed.
I got stuffed on.
I sort of went way quicker than that.
That was dumb.
Sure played more LeBron earlier.
I forgot I'm good with him.
There it goes.
I thought they were going to drop down more.
We're good.
I get to watch it and give it.
Should I?
Okay.
Should I watch the new movie?
I'd like to hear what you thought.
You want me to give you like a full review after I see it?
Yeah, I would like to hear it.
I mean, I also like don't want to wish that on you.
I feel like you'd be really upset, but.
Should I?
Okay.
Should I be interested?
All right.
How about this?
I will watch the movie and I will write you like a three or four paragraph
professional review of the movie.
Okay.
And you will you will read it on your stream.
I'm done.
You don't do that?
Okay.
Yeah.
All right.
Just give me like back in action.
I love that movie as a kid.
I don't think it's very good looking back, but I used to love that.
Just give me six months.
Okay.
I mean, you got to make sure it's like proofread and those paragraphs are good.
Live tweet your reaction.
Great if like one of your like five, like four to five of your tweets in the year
are just like throughout Space Jam 2.
I actually think that's kind of funny.
Half of my tweets for the whole year or more are a live.
I'll lose thousands of followers, but do I really care?
If I tweet that much in one day, people are going to remember that they followed me like
eight years ago because they'll see me, right?
Because they never do.
Because I'm only in people's feeds like once every like three or four months.
So they will they will see it during the day and be like,
oh, should I follow this guy?
This guy sucks and unfollow me.
They're like, wait, who is this guy?
They click the link in your bio.
They're like, yeah, he hasn't uploaded in like eight years.
Yeah.
That's worth it.
Whatever.
Shut up, you asshole.
All your tweets get a lot of likes.
No, they don't.
Do they?
Let me check.
All right.
Connor, go read, go read out loud the last five.
That's not that's not the going live one.
So you have no, not the going live one.
We have I spent the last 20 minutes going line by line translating this old note
I had on my iPhone.
It was from a year ago, freaking out, trying to decipher its meaning.
Was I hacked?
Did I do this in my sleep?
Demon shit?
No, it's just the default pages template template with lorem ipsum.
I got 60K likes.
What did why?
I don't know.
Apparently it hit.
Even your hashtag ad, we got 10K people excited to see if we
we have everybody twerked and everybody gave a drug PSA.
Good luck.
Okay.
That's for the green screen footage.
You're probably going to go back a year, by the way.
I'm like looking through trying to see what like isn't like an announcement.
They are nerfed as again, or is he still like amazing?
I think they nerfed him pretty hard before complaining.
What happened there?
That was kind of a mess.
I don't know.
Honestly, I just couldn't get back.
I guess I ran out of specials.
Oh, nice.
Nice try.
Whatever.
What's the worst movie you've ever seen?
Like currently before saying special.
Stop doing that.
Stop doing that to me.
Okay, we're good.
Stop.
Oh, my goodness gracious.
We got fucking diarrhea on.
What is that guy's username?
Readableboy44.
Okay.
Well, then that guy's name is focus on these.
We can't lose to these guys.
We just did bad.
We can't lose to them.
We just did very.
All right.
We're going.
I got an idea.
I knew I should have taken that carrot at Albuquerque.
Double Rindog wins this matchup.
Level 21.
It's not fair.
They should they should delete your account when you get to level 20 on any character.
Yeah, like you got to play something else.
It's a free to play game.
Come on now.
Let people have a chance.
No, did you have a least favorite movie?
It's been a while since I've seen a movie that I genuinely really hated.
Yeah, I didn't have a least favorite until I saw that.
Honestly, that's become that's become least favorite ever upset me.
Well, because like even as like a kid, right?
I'd be like, oh, maybe they'll make a new Space Jam movie.
Like, oh, it'll come out one day.
And then it finally happened.
And then it was like, and you just hate you hated it.
It was everything I hated about what it possibly could have been.
Oh, how did that not hit?
What?
Excuse me.
What the fuck just happened?
Oh, oh, got it.
Hey, do you guys want a TV?
Do you guys want a TV, too?
I mean, wait a second, remove a game for a second.
I thought this was the person that we were playing in the game.
And I was like, is this voice chat?
They added that.
I'll chat.
Oh, we got we got it right there.
All right.
That's that's one on one.
That's one on one.
Do you guys want to play when you're done with this, though?
Or not?
Yeah, we'll play a game, too.
Yeah, I'm done.
Okay.
I'll add you guys.
Did you put your info?
Yeah, it's in there somewhere, I think.
Yeah, I have mine.
Do you both request?
Sick.
Thank you.
Mine's not really in there.
It's I forgot the numbers.
Yeah, it's like Scarlett something.
Look, it's focused on these join the voice chat.
Yeah, it did.
I don't know.
I don't know my username.
And your username?
Why?
I don't want to be German 985.
Someone probably already is German 985.
Yeah, guys.
I'm sure it's probably been taken like 5,000 different versions of the name.
Why not?
Because back in the TF2 days, this is a real story.
Back in the TF2 days, if I was if you were like making YouTube videos
or whatever, if you were streaming, whatever, not not back then.
But if your name was like German 985 and it was like confirmed that that's you,
it'd be 30 people lining up to high five you and the game would be ruined.
I'm trying to take myself out of the equation.
It's not me.
This is just a person playing the game.
So I always just ever since I did it like that.
That's what I when people recognize me in a game, I'm just like,
oh my God, is that Connor?
I'm like, no, I'm just a fan.
That's why I used to my names used to be like car dealership,
like 200 or something.
And people just be like, who the fuck is this guy?
200.
Yeah, I've played with that guy.
Yeah, he was pretty good.
Watch that hit.
Oh, my God.
That was disgusting.
Oh, my goodness gracious.
That was a that was a delicious combo.
That was ridiculous.
All right.
They're going to try to run back here.
Careful.
Good, good, good.
Oh, he almost finished that Superman.
There he goes.
Oh, he grabbed me from behind.
There it goes.
All right.
Here we go.
Good fight.
That two one.
That is it.
Yeah.
You fucked up, boy.
Yeah, we kicked their ass.
Good to hear.
I sent you both friend requests so we can add you.
Uh, German, I think you're the host.
Oh, yeah.
I added it.
Dr. Battle.
Yep.
Oh, wait, we're not doing a we're just inviting everybody to a party.
Can you do that?
Or are we doing custom game?
I was just going to do it the way I didn't turn custom.
Yeah.
Oh, OK.
I've got the custom set up.
Oh, yeah.
Yeah.
Are we friends?
Because I have that Dr. Battle, right?
Gave me error except.
Yeah, I got you.
Oh, I got Scarlet Otter.
OK, sending an invite there.
Uh, German, you may not have to invite me.
And then you could invite him and I'm going to invite you.
Yeah, I'll pull them.
Is there a bracket or a mainstream for this tournament anywhere?
The guy's on YouTube and not on this site.
And then I'll pull you now.
Very cool.
So yeah, who's did they finish?
Who's who's?
No, they're they're in like losers finals right now, I think.
Or maybe they're starting grands.
I don't remember.
Who's who's one and two or who's like the top four right now?
It's Stans and Alpharad.
I think they're in game three and they're in game three.
And then it's Jesse and Slick waiting and winners of grands.
And me and Sheep got fourth place.
Yeah, we had the worst seating.
Yeah.
Would you guys start off against Slick?
Oh, yeah.
Yeah, they were in the same.
They're very good.
That was the only one because we lost to Stans as well.
But I felt like those were close, but Jesse and Slick.
Fucked us up.
Yeah, we we were pretty close on the second game with them.
Yeah.
Here comes the heat.
You know, please don't play on the Steven Universe stage again.
Well, we can't we can't.
Well, everybody hates the Steven Universe.
The Rick and Morty stage.
Actually, can we adjust the map pool in a custom?
I think so.
You can pick a specific one, but can you just like take one out?
Yeah, you can take one out.
I don't know how you pick a specific one.
I don't either.
Oh, shit, I got to pick a character.
Why aren't my my perks aren't like unlocked?
That was weird.
I just played.
I just picked a bunch of perks.
I don't know.
Well, we haven't locked in yet.
Oh, I enjoy.
Oh, that's why I was like, what?
Look who it is.
Oh, yeah.
Those guys, one of them had an iron giant, right?
I heard they were reducing iron giant size by like 70 percent.
He's going to be shorter than like Bugs Bunny in the next patch.
They heard a lot of times.
I know.
Iron guy.
Iron gentleman.
It's that orchestra one.
Please, we can't hear it anymore.
We'll turn the sound off and put on
put on like your favorite podcast.
The Stains show, which needs a new episode.
We've been working on it.
I'm going to laugh if we're just on that stage.
The person is going to leave.
It's Rick and Morty.
Oh, yeah, it's Rick and Morty.
Rick and Morty.
Let's do it.
Freeze.
It's true.
You cannot guard LeBron.
Oh, he's six foot eight.
He's the goat.
Oh, so you can hit him with the car.
You're into that shit.
I should have gone LeBron against iron giant.
I feel like he fucks him up.
You are LeBron.
I know.
But when we fought slick.
Oh, I was like, I was like, oh, no, that was supposed to be a punch.
Oh, oh, very cool.
Superman.
Oh, my God.
How am I still on stage?
I don't know.
Oh, that was close.
What did you bounce off something?
I don't know.
I like bounced back.
I feel like that happened to me a couple of times in the tournament, to be honest.
There I go.
I don't pay to lose or to die.
Oh, no.
Get out of here, LeBron.
Oh, I'm in gun mode.
You're not a gun.
I feel like the gun mode is working.
I'm in it, too.
Shooting.
They don't know what to do.
Damn.
You guys are sticking around.
That ain't good.
We're all right.
You're like another hunter on me and I'll be done.
Oh, my goodness.
I thought you flew off.
How the hell are you not dead?
Iron giant.
It's OK to die.
It's not OK to kill.
Boy, the Superman.
Damn it.
That was supposed to be a punch.
Grab me.
Oh, no.
Oh, goodbye.
Whoa.
That was sick.
I almost brought it back.
I tried.
That was really close.
Superman's tough to finish.
Yeah.
He's so annoying.
He's tricky.
I feel like the iron giant's got that, too.
Like, you got to follow up on him to kill him
because it's going to be hard to kill him just from the stage.
Yeah, you got to like bounce, bounce, bounce.
Just follow him up.
Especially when you start flying.
It's just like just going to the feet.
Just trying to knock him a little higher.
Yeah, that's what I'm saying.
He's huge.
Stop eating raw pork.
I've been eating carrots.
What are people talking about?
Real carrots or baby carrots?
Raw pork is very dangerous.
Just the carrots that are like a big pencil.
You know what I mean?
OK.
Yeah, it's audible.
It's very clear.
Any doctors here?
If I eat carrots for four hours, is that bad?
I've been eating carrots for two straight hours.
No, that's fine.
You probably can't OD on carrots.
I think if you ate carrots for four hours straight every day,
then eventually you're going to start shitting weird or something.
But I don't think you're going to be in danger.
God.
You can turn orange if you eat too many carrots.
That sounds like a lie.
How do I look?
It's double LeBron.
Oh, no.
Yeah, we'll be in weirdos.
There's going to be so many basketballs.
I know.
Two, I guess.
But I think you can have four active though, can't he?
Like two, I mean, two at a time.
Yep.
Can you have one that's like free falling
and then he can still do basketball moves?
Yeah, if you bounce one, his down special.
OK, I said I turned orange eating too many carrots
one time at the hospital.
What?
That's what that guy said.
I don't say that.
Watch out.
Wrong way.
Jesus, I'm getting dunked on by the all-time scoring leader.
Yep.
It might be a double LeBron team, Jeremy.
This might be us.
We've been playing well with the double LeBron.
Oh, I'm trying to play around here.
That was close.
Oh, my God.
We're going crazy.
Bounce, bounce.
I don't think teams should be allowed to have
eight finals wins combined.
That was lucky that I stayed alive.
Give me that ball.
Oh, my goodness.
Oh, I thought I hit him.
Oh, it's all right.
Good.
Yeah, that was that was.
Oh, we're saying I thought we do you end of the game
when you've got Connor.
I thought we knew when we won.
Look at how happy LeBron's are.
How come they couldn't get LeBron to do the voice lines?
We were talking about that earlier.
He doesn't know he's in the game.
I heard that they're working on that, though.
I watched a video that talked about this game
and they said that LeBron was going to do the voice lines.
Either they're misinformed or they're not.
I guess it has to be one of them, right?
All right, let's change it up.
What do I want to do?
People just like lie for no reason sometimes.
Yeah, it's true.
Kind of insta locked LeBron.
I should have changed it.
Jerma, your eyes are turning orange.
Yeah, a lot of people have been saying that.
LeBron's really fun to play.
Yeah, he's great.
Play Bugs Bunny, you carrot eater.
I think I played bugs all day.
What we got?
So how do you guys like the game?
I think it's fine.
I don't I play melee mostly, so I don't know
how much I'm going to not play melee for this,
but I'm having fun being there and giant.
Yeah, I like it.
I don't know how much competitive legs it has, but it's fun.
You were playing a lot during the first day, right?
Or do you think I saw?
He yeah, I played a decent during their first video.
I played it off stream a lot, too.
I really like it.
I found it.
Yeah, it's fun.
I like just the netcode alone.
It's like enough for me to want to play it.
Yeah.
Amazing how like Nintendo still doesn't have like an online system.
I mean, the idea is if, you know,
if Warner Brothers is going to support this and really care about it,
then oh, yeah, hope they do.
Yeah.
Did you see that information about how much people like Evo is this last weekend
and like fifth place for multiverses, which was a side game,
got more than like first place for some of the main games?
Really?
Yeah.
Like, holy shit.
I think 17th place for multiverses.
Again, a side game got more than like fifth place for some games or something.
There was a practical task tweet about it.
I can't remember all the details,
but Warner Brothers put a lot of money into this game.
They should do something for this tournament.
That'd be cool.
I think maybe four, even fifth.
I don't know.
Tied for fifth place should have seen,
you know, seven hundred thousand dollars or something like that.
Yeah.
I take which means fourth place is probably one point two at that point, right?
Yeah, that'd be like one point three.
Yeah, maybe.
Say that makes sense.
I'll take like two bucks or something at this point.
That was crazy.
Did you just run out of resources?
Yeah, I just was hoping I caught somebody in it.
Ran out of basketballs.
I mean, I feel like you guys just went easy on us
because you didn't go double LeBron again.
My Taz was not was not very good that round.
Yeah, I mean, like, I don't know, like a 50 to 100 million dollar tournament.
You know, the first hundred places get, you know,
place 100 gets like two hundred thousand something like that.
And it's just people that Ludwig knows off the top of his head and in the tournament,
not like top players only or anything.
Just, you know, what's the biggest?
What's the biggest prize pool ever?
Is it that Dota tournament?
Oh, like ever, ever.
But it's not a lot of big ones.
Don't just have like 10 to 20 million, right?
I I want to say it's got to be Dota, but I'm not 100% sure.
I know that I know CS has had some really big prize pools,
but I don't know if they can.
Yeah, your Dota two had a forty seven million.
Wow.
I was saying that as a joke.
That actually happened.
How many people get a million?
Like, is that just the winning team or is it like the top?
It's a prize pool.
So I imagine it was spread.
That's probably probably spread.
That's like winning the mega millions jackpot.
That's like the type of crazy number.
That's like life changing in a way that is changing
like the future generations of your life of your family's way, too.
That's going to be like a money laundering.
Eighteen million over 18 million went to team one.
There's no way.
How much was team two?
Because team two got like nine million.
Can you imagine playing a game of Dota for nine million dollars?
I would I would shit my pants.
I better hit you at the right time.
Otherwise, I might lose nine million dollars.
I probably would fucking puke, right?
Like it's so much like nerves like, geez, like 10 million, 20 million dollars.
But at the same time, you've already won nine million.
So maybe the nerves go away.
You're like, I'm already sad.
This is just extra difference between nine and 18 million dollars.
Really true.
Hey, what's the best liberon that I can just use?
Uh, his side special is like almost instant kill
if they have at least 50 to 60 damage or at least like 70.
Don't it has no priority, though, so you really have to land it.
Whoo.
Don't don't.
Damn.
You hit me like seven times.
That's what I kept missing in the tournament is the Superman is a Superman.
What the hell?
Oh, I enjoyed it.
Did I hit you with that bat?
That was crazy.
You were like far away.
Oh, oh, my God.
That I'm alive.
I'm alive.
Oh, my God.
I've never seen someone with faster knockback than in that move right there.
It's so I got deleted.
Oh, I'm living.
Oh, I was I was out there to try to kill you in case he didn't.
Oh, I'm dead.
I'm dead.
Oh, so close.
131.
Oh, my goodness.
Oh, my God.
How did you through the floor?
Oh, that was unbelievable.
Did you go in the floor?
I did the dunk and he was jumping up through the floor.
Wow.
As it happened, that was insane.
I came.
Yeah, I came up through the tunnel.
All I do is get kills.
Was it no damage?
Hey, that's what you need.
You need someone.
You need someone to hold the line or need someone to throw the ball.
You know, like that was crazy.
It comes.
Somebody win this tournament yet.
What happened?
It's probably wrapping up.
I'm not totally sure.
Now, we're going to take it back up tomorrow.
I guess they got to review Ludwig and Alpharet together.
Wait, really?
I think Stan's at the dip.
Oh, OK.
Yeah, Stan said he had to leave at 425.
That would be it.
So I'm guessing that they made it to Grands and then playing.
Oh, shit.
Yeah, I'll take his money.
Wouldn't mind.
He only deserves second place money.
Even if they win, he doesn't deserve the first place money.
The amount difference between second and first should go, I don't know, maybe to fourth,
I guess.
Right.
Just go to fourth.
I'll split it with Tide Fifth either.
I mean, it should probably play should see at least, you know, 100, 200.
Maybe.
Yeah, that's what we were saying.
We were saying 100, 100 bucks for fourth.
Ludwig was pretending to not read it.
Oh, Steven Universe, that person's fucking gone.
Oh, if I really don't so hard, the ball disappears.
Oh, crazy.
It's like that in real life, too.
They have to bring like 20 balls to the game.
Actually, there probably is 20 balls in the game.
Do they go through basketballs like baseball goes through baseballs?
I think so.
Or do they use the same ball the whole game?
I don't.
That's a great question.
That's a really good question.
I feel like no way.
I feel like basketball probably goes through eight balls for no reason.
Every dunk, they switch it up.
No football.
They switch the ball all the time.
They do.
Well, teams get their own balls, too.
They bring their own balls to the game.
Yeah.
Because some pitch, like some quarterbacks like the ball to be
inflated, really worn out.
Yeah.
Really worn out and some like.
Oh, yeah, they do that in the Super Bowl.
I need to kill Jerma.
Yeah.
What's up?
Oh, I thought you said I need to tell Jerma.
Like, I need to tell you something.
No, he needs to kill you.
I need to be honest.
Everything you've known about me has been a fraud.
My whole life.
What are you doing?
I lost the ball.
I was chasing it.
Couldn't get it.
Doesn't this come back to you?
I feel like using is a cool thing, which is fine.
I'm not upset about it.
LeBron throws the ball to Rhyndag.
He should say fetch.
Oh, my goodness.
You're very high there, Jerma.
And not just on carrots.
Getting high on carrots.
Yeah, I've been like smoking these off here.
We got to get some kills here.
I'm going to say.
Jerma's already dead.
But I'm also very happy.
It was just like homing onto you.
You're cool.
Loving this.
Oh, my goodness.
Oh, there I go.
Like halfway to kill.
No, let me go.
We are very high percent.
I'm working on it.
I don't know what happens when we get tied together.
I think there's like a button that you can press that like leashes him back to you.
No, I was in the middle of comboing.
Oh, I could have.
I probably would have dropped it, but I felt like I could have got it.
Hey, game three.
All right.
This one's for all three.
Game three thousand dollars.
This one's for all.
You had six hundred damage, dude.
Rhyndag was just kind of hitting everybody.
Support character, huh?
Oh, my God.
Yeah, it looks like you turned on the stream by accident.
That's how I feel.
Sometimes I'm like, what does that mean?
OK, if it's all the marbles.
It's kind of funny because I know exactly what they mean.
Like I, I get it.
I know what you mean.
Like you're just chilling playing multiverses, you know.
Yeah, we're just like chilling.
Yeah, that's that's a sometimes it's like that.
Whatever.
That's how streams should feel.
Ever heard of Clint Stevens?
Ban that person, ban that person for one full 60 seconds.
Stop enjoying the game.
But I like the game.
That'll teach him.
Yeah, then VIP them, then ban them again.
And then put them on stream
and they can say literally whatever they want for 10 seconds
and then permanently ban them and then VIP them
and then permanently ban them.
You're just tossing them around at this point.
I really want to just like, you know, fuck with them.
Trunk on carrots.
All right.
This is for the marbles, right?
Yeah, every last marble.
Oh, I can't believe that.
Oh, man.
Oh, damn it.
Oh, my God.
Holy.
Oh, that killed.
I did not.
Holy.
They're doing pretty good.
Didn't want to throw the ball.
Might be a random toy now.
Maybe not.
No, he's still very good.
Oh, it's trying to bounce that back to you.
Oh, there I go.
Oh, yeah.
Oh, my God.
That's what I'm talking about.
Okay.
That was good.
One for blue.
This is even though.
Oh, careful.
Whoa, let's go.
Oh, man.
That's gay.
I was like, maybe if I'm going off stage,
it'll bring me out to you.
And then we get to play in the tournament.
That would have been exciting.
That was a good matchup.
I think it was pretty even.
Rock with the four kills.
300 damage.
You just like I've always had 360.
Why do we didn't get the best match
of the day on a stream?
You know, he didn't.
That was probably a more entertaining
two best of three is both more entertaining
than every set.
Love a guy today.
That was a good fight.
Good match.
Let's play you guys.
Oh, that was awesome.
I had a lot of fun.
Hey, multiverses.
Let's do more events.
More events.
It's fun.
Weekly Ludwig tournaments until one of us wins.
Yeah.
And so we all like get a couple thousand dollars.
I think all the placements should just make the same.
I mean, why?
You know, why word based on how good you did.
Like that makes people feel bad.
So let's just, you know.
Hey, I'm all right being fifth place.
About eight dollars to fourth and fifth.
Or four and a half.
Right.
Technically.
Yeah.
Hey, you guys have good streams.
I'm out now.
Yeah.
All right.
Let's play now.
Run.
Thanks playing, guys.
You may be in the next Ludwig event.
Who knows?
Yeah.
Ooh, Fortnite.
So can I keep playing?
Is that it for you?
How do you feel?
I think I might go play something else a bit soon.
All right.
It's been fun, though.
It has been a good time.
Hey, we had a good showing.
I think we did.
We played pretty well.
We really did.
We lost to the two winners finals teams.
I think grand finals teams.
So, you know, at the end of the day,
some are saying we were the best team there.
Yeah, I say one of the best team.
We're one of the top eight teams there.
That is true.
We were in the top eight.
Yeah, it's always a pleasure, dude.
Dude, of course.
It was fun.
Have a great rest of your stream.
Yeah, we'll talk soon.
I'll see you.
Take care, dude.
All right.
So that's that.
That was multi-versus tournament.
Yeah, honestly, we played really well.
We probably could have been fourth or third.
We probably could have.
That was a lot of fun, though.
It's fun to play a game and be like kind of good at it.
Like be okay at it.
Are you going to leave?
Yes.
So for those of you that aren't aware,
I'm still dealing with an obnoxious fucking medical problem
that it just comes and goes, comes and goes.
And it's causing me a ton of problems.
I'm fine.
But I need, like I said before,
I want to do more streams this week, but less time.
And I didn't stream yesterday.
I wanted to go like Tuesday, Wednesday, Thursday, Friday, Saturday.
But we started on Wednesday.
We're going to do Wednesday.
Tomorrow, I believe, I'm going to go check and see.
I think the myth call of duty thing is tomorrow.
So more networking Andy tomorrow.
That should be funny.
Okay, because I played well today.
I'm going to be the worst fucking player on any team tomorrow.
It's going to be embarrassing.
So if you want to watch me make an absolute fool out of myself in call of duty,
it's not going to be funny.
It's going to be embarrassing for all of us as a collective entire community.
So I hope you're ready.
But if that happens, if that happens,
it'll be, I might stream my perspective.
If not, it'll be on Myth's channel on YouTube.
We'll see.
But on Friday, we're going to do two point campus.
And then maybe mortuary assistant.
And then Sunday is green screen movie night.
And then Monday, we're doing a hangout stream where we talk about baseball.
And then obviously baseball is a few days later.
And then we'll do sorcery when I come back from baseball.
So we'll see.
But yeah, I'm trying to not sit here for too long.
I'll leave out the minute details.
But there's been annoying things I've had to deal with over the last week or two.
But I'm all right.
I'll be fine.
I'll be good for baseball.
But I'll see you guys tomorrow.
We'll go for like another three, four hours tomorrow.
And then Friday will be a little longer.
Because we're probably going to play two games on Friday.
Is it the back problem?
It's a combination of a few things that have just,
it's just been a thorn in my side for the last two or three weeks.
But I'm good.
I'm all right.
I feel, I feel, I feel okay today.
Right.
But I don't want to go too hard.
But I'll see you tomorrow.
Keep an eye on what's happening with the Call of Duty thing.
If there is, if for some reason there is no Call of Duty thing,
then we'll play something tomorrow.
We'll do something else.
So there'll be a stream tomorrow.
And with that, let's, we'll raid Connor.
Because we were just playing with Connor.
I think Connor's still streaming.
Yeah, that was a lot of fun.
Also, obviously thanks to Ludwig for the invite.
I don't, if they, if they, are they still doing there?
Is it, is it over?
I don't know, but that was, that was awesome.
Thanks for watching, obviously.
You're around tomorrow?
Either the Mortuary Assistant or Myth's Call of Duty event.
I'll put a sus command when I figure out everything.
Yeah, we'll raid Connor.
Let's go for it.
I need a horror game.
The only reason why I wouldn't do the Mortuary Assistant tomorrow
is if I don't want to be like screaming and tense up and have a problem.
And then fuck myself up.
So we'll see tomorrow.
There will be a stream tomorrow.
We'll see, we'll see what it is.
But I'm, we'll wing it.
Thanks again, guys.
And here we go, let's raid Connor.
Whatever Connor is doing.
Thanks, I wasn't paying too much attention to much
because I was focusing on obviously trying to win.
But that was Multi Versus.
Go get it.
Go try it.
The game's free and it's fun.
That's all that needs to be said about it.
What time tomorrow?
Probably around the same time I started today.
Like probably around two or three o'clock Pacific.
That was a chill tournament stream.
Yeah, sometimes you just play games and that's fine.
You know, I got to prove that I know how to use a controller.
I got to prove that I don't hold the controller upside down every stream.
All right.
Good night, guys.
See you soon.
Take care.
Bye, mother.
Have a great night.