Hey, what is going on everybody? Jerma here with Rayman Jungle Run, a little gem of a game.
Welcome to Little Gems, guys. My name is Jerma. Nice to see you, nice to meet you.
If you don't know what this series is, this is probably episode 5 or 6 so far, where I cover a iOS and Android capable game.
This week is going to be, like I said, Rayman Jungle Run, which is a free-running, parkour, Sonic the Hedgehog, Bit Trip Runner combination game.
And I will get into more detail, obviously, on that, so do not worry. I'm not just going to throw that out there and go,
yeah, that's the whole game, alright, we'll see you next time.
That is not going to happen, so let's get right into this here, talk about the basics.
This is, first of all, not a canon Rayman game. It's not canonical...canon...canon?
I have no idea how you say that, but this is not a canon Rayman game. It's not like Rayman 1, 2, 3, and then oh, Rayman Jungle Run.
This is a side game, a sort of spin-off game of the series.
So what do you do in this game? What do you have to do? What is the point of Rayman Jungle Run?
Well, according to the title of the game, you're going to be doing a whole lot of moving and shaking, mostly the first one.
So it's a game about running really, really fast and picking up these golden bugs.
There are 100 of them on each level. Trying to beat your old scores is your number one priority here.
There is no storyline, so you don't go from level 1 to level 2 and try to figure out some kind of murder mystery or something.
You're just going for high scores and for the smallest amount of time completed.
And just like Super Meat Boy and games like Bit Trip Runner that require a lot of memorization and repetition of levels,
you are going to become so addicted to this game that you have to repeat the level.
You want to get every single bug because it's not impossible.
It's incredibly challenging, a lot of levels in this game, but they are not impossible.
You just have to get the memorization down and the repetition down, and you will flow through these levels like butter,
which is quite the sight to see sometimes.
You will step back after a session of this game and say to yourself,
Oh my word, I was in a real rhythm right there. I was just flowing through these levels. That was awesome.
The one complaint that I have about this game, and it's a complaint that I have with other runner type games,
is you can really get into this thing that I call Blendovision,
where you kind of lose control of your mind and you just forget what you're doing and where you're going,
and you just end up losing because you're blending every single one of your thoughts together in the game.
I don't know if that makes any sense, but let me know if you understand what I'm talking about.
But with all that said though, you're going to get a fantastic game.
It's a universal app, by the way. You can get this for Android, iPhone, iPad.
It doesn't matter which one. The links will be in the description.
But you're getting a beautiful game.
This is probably one of the best looking games I've ever seen on the iPad,
and it's not because of some amazing 3D graphics engine or something like that.
It's the art style and how the colors just pop out at you,
and how it looks like every character is just created from this crazy imagination of somebody.
I love that so much.
And talking about a little bit more of the gameplay,
you start out just being able to jump just by tapping the screen,
and it evolves into being able to hand glide with your head,
being able to run up walls, being able to punch through walls and stuff like that.
And eventually, you have to put all these together.
You have to combine all of these abilities into the same level,
which makes for some very interesting gameplay,
knowing when and where to use your various abilities,
which is the real challenge of the game.
And I also forgot to mention this. There's nine levels in each one of these sets.
Jump is a set, Fly is a set, Wall Run and Punch are both sets as well,
and they all have nine levels.
There is a tenth level in each one of these sets,
but the only way you can unlock it is if you complete five levels in one of these sets.
Let's say you complete five levels in Wall Run at 100%,
you will unlock the tenth level, which is the hardest.
But final closing thoughts on this game is you're going to get a lot of content.
It might take you less than an hour to blow through all the levels,
but, but, but, but, to actually complete them all and unlock the hardest level sets,
it's going to take you a lot longer than that,
because at the end, in the Wall Run and the Punch levels, very specifically,
it's a lot harder to 100% those levels.
And even when you do 100% them,
you're going to want to go back and try to beat your old times as well.
So there's a lot to do in this game.
It's currently priced at $2.99.
I think it's a great pickup for how beautiful the game is
and how much fun you're going to have with it.
I suggest it absolutely.
And that is going to wrap up the video, guys,
so thank you so much for watching, I really do appreciate it.
And go have fun with this little gem, baby.
I'll see you guys all soon, and of course, take care, everybody.