Hello everyone, it's Jeremy's grandfather here again. Time to do an epic time-lapse
of Minecraft proportions. Today I'm gonna be doing a time-lapse of the Taj Mahal
and it's a place that's in India and it's a big building and it's gonna be so
much fun. So I hope everyone's ready to go on a magical journey. Let's do it
together. Here we go. That's uh, that's it. But don't even fucking look at me like that.
This game is hard, okay? This is one of the hardest games I've ever played. So what?
So what if it doesn't look like the Taj Mahal? You don't even know what the fuck
the Taj Mahal even looks like, you shithead. You're talking to somebody that
fought in the World War IIs. I fought in the Dinosaur-Human War of 1966 and I
fought in World War II as a fighter pilot. So if you want to fuck with me,
buddy, you got something coming and I will stick a knife into your face. And another thing, if you...
Rampart! What? Rampart, hey, Family Feud is on. Wait, what's going on? Family Feud is on. It's Monday, man.
Holy shit. It's Monday already? Yeah, let's go. That's the best show on TV. Holy shit. Fuck you.
Stop it, dude. Give me some food.