Hey, remember me? I'm that guy that's supposed to be live right now for the last two hours.
How are you? And look at what it looks like now. Look at how it looks fucking fine. It's fixed.
Here's the... Okay, listen, hear me out. I've got to tell you something right now. It's very,
very important. You need to hear this. So, plugged in right now is a webcam and there's a USB 3.0 and
a USB 2.0. I don't think data was going fast enough into the... I had to put it in 3.0.
The same exact thing happened last time. Fuck! God damn it. All right, we're here. Hey,
let's turn it off. Let's turn it off with a good look at me. What do you think about that?
You can use that one somewhere in your fucking school project. Oh my god, I'm so fucking annoyed
and so annoyed right now. And I've moved everything. I've moved everything.
There's nothing... Hold on. Let me get this shit the way that it was supposed to be.
Dude, you don't know how sad I just was. Do you have any idea of the absolute just sadness?
Why is everything shaking? That was weird. How are we? I'm coming for you. You're the one I'm
going to get. Bad. Okay, welcome. Dude, I looked over here this way and I see all these costumes
and all these devices and all these things to play with. And it's a fucking mess over here.
There's like 75 items over here. And then I'm looking over here. There's a door right there
and there's a big exit sign. And I'm just looking back and forth like... Oh, fuck me. I am
fucked if I can't do this right now. It was like car, bring it back and forth in the car,
back and forth. My goodness. All right, here we go. I am going to fix the angle.
This is the way it's going to be. I think it's the way this is cut. If you noticed, it's a little...
Plus as long as I can stay inside of here. All right, give me my list. Where's my list? Okay.
Did I get lower? It's tested. I want to get all tested to make sure everything works good.
We got a shadow behind me, but it's kind of... Not much I can do about it. I tried as hard as
I could. I got two lights over here. It should be fine. I'm going to go a little bit lower. Let's
go a little bit lower. Well, thank you for sticking with me here. Thanks for sticking around.
I've just been like... I've just been like mashing my hands together. I almost... I almost... And I
don't do this ever. I almost smashed right on the laptop's keyboard. I was like, I'm smashing it,
but I was like, no, I don't want to be a baby. That's what babies do. I never do that shit,
but I got close. I got close to just healing the thing right on the fucking ground. All right,
that looks good. Is it a little too low now? The fuck? Oh, God. Here we go. Hold on, bitch.
Remember that joke I said about Bugs Bunny? What does it look like, guys? Let me see. Remember
where I did that two hours ago? By the way, did you guys see? I went live accidentally
for like 12 seconds. I've been recording and going, but I can't fucking believe I did this
last time. You know how it's like... Did you see it? Could you actually see it? Yeah. I think I
turned it on and I thought I was trying to record, but I hit the stream button and I think I went
like... I was testing the FPS and then I think I said, fuck, and I had a mad face and I turned it
off. It's crooked? No, it's not because it's the way that this comes down. I don't think it's exact.
I don't think it's perfect because this is... Might as well get started. Yeah. I'm really
enjoying the school dance. Should I come a little closer? So do you have any math homework that you
have to do tomorrow? Yeah. I have Mr. Stevenson. She's the worst. Yeah. Don't people get... Don't
people... I probably shouldn't do that. I probably shouldn't do that. That's probably what not to do
because people do that. They record themselves pretending to like... I don't know, hang out with
you and talk like ASMR like I'm at the dance with you. All right. ASMR, I'm at the dance with you.
I got a list over here. I'm so excited. I'm so happy. First things first. One of the things
that people were asking for was a good close-up of my face from every angle. I guess we didn't
do it last time. I never realized how fucking ugly you are until you get close. Oh, all right.
All right. That's my face from all angles. Look straight. Hey. Hey, how are you? Hey, it's me.
Good thing I caught you. Good thing I got you right at the beginning of the video.
You're going to want to skip this one because this one sucks. What do you want? What do you want?
Good? You got me looking like a nerd neck? Should we do... Wait, how about... Wait, I got one. Guys,
I'm going to be here all night. Do you understand how long I'm going to be here for? I actually
have to probably make a phone call to the person that runs the studio because I have to say that I
am a fucking moron and I have the IQ of a six-year-old and I might be in the DB for a couple hours.
All right. What's that? Yeah, they go like this. So this is like a before and after, right? You
guys could inflate me. What's next? We're going to do a lot of walking and running routines.
Okay, here we go. I forget how to walk. Hold on. What am I doing? Wait, do that again. I'm not
listening to music. This is how all ladies fucking... They have the two weights. Give me two weights.
Give me two weights. I want this. Here's every old lady during the fucking spring and summertime.
Too real? Well, they should be... Okay, got that one. Is he wearing underwear? Wait, did anybody
even say that? Did I just make that up? Is he wearing underwear? I think I just made that up,
but yes, I am. All right. What's next? Oh, running, running. Okay. Last time I tired myself out before
the fucking 20-minute bar. Fucking animal. I don't know. Somebody wanted an animal run.
How the fuck do animals do that? How do animals move? Let's solve this. Let's solve this. Oh, dude.
Dude, you know those movies? Ever see a movie? When it fucking pops up from the top,
it's a boom microphone. Isn't that funny? It's going to be loud. There. Now I got way more room.
Okay. What's next? That fly is going to go on. Okay, do the mashed potato. Do the mashed potato?
How do you do that? That's this thing, right? Where you go like, bump this song.
Mashed potato. You can do the potato. You can do... Shit. Screams over. Do the runescape dances. All
right. Here comes a runescape dance. Runescape dance six. That's for you. Okay. What's next?
Oh, hiding. Hiding in various places and doing monkey ass. I was spooked.
I was spooked. I almost did. Thank God I didn't. That would have been embarrassing.
Oh, the green screen right here. Oh, my God. All my career is over. Hey, hey, hey, hey. What career?
That's what you're going to... Monkey ass. Monkey ass. Oh, monkey ass. Monkey ass.
That's bright. Monkey ass. That's the one. Is it hips? What's wrong with my hips? Oh, okay. I like
this one. Look around like you're speaking telepathically. No, I'm talking telepathically.
Do you? Hey, this guy's a fucking idiot. This guy's so... Hey, he can't hear me because I'm
talking telepathically to him so I can talk out loud. I can say whatever I want about this
fucking asshole. I think he might eat his own shit. I really think he... Oh, hey. Didn't know I was on
the subway with more than 30 people. I'll make my exit now if you could. Look at me. Somebody
wants more of these? Sure thing. Oh, excuse me. Those were huge. Laying down from all angles,
okay. Like just on the ground? Oh, that feels good. Wait, should I put my arms on my sides?
No, not yet, not yet. Am I supposed to be dead? Oh, fuck you. I was doing something.
What the fuck? I was doing a pretend butt thing. I don't think any of you knew that I could do this.
Didn't think I could do that, did you? By the way, I'm so glad that I took a bunch of extra
strength Tylenol because I'm gonna feel it tomorrow morning. Pretending to shoot a bow. Okay. Wait,
wait, wait. I gotta hold it. Almost got him. You stay right there, punk. Oops. Ooh, right between
the eyes. What about you? Got him. Stay there. Stay there. Oh, shoot. It was a boomerang. It was
a boomerang bow. Don't use that one. Delete that one. It's gotta be from. Yes. What is $12? That's
right. Those don't cost. That costs way, way less than that. I have 10 of those. Celebration. Look
at you. Wow. You won. You did it. You get to go up there. God, that looks like fun. That looks like
a lot of fun. I wish I could get up there. You son of a bitch. Bob, what is $3,200? Wait, wait,
me? Wait, me? I get it. I get to go up. No way. No way. Right here, man. Ah, fuck you. You're not
getting a high five from me. Maybe I'll give you one of these. No. No? All right. Really? No way.
Oh, yes. I'm such a fan. All right. All right. Right. Okay. So I spin the wheel and then I. Okay.
I just want to say I'm a huge fan of yours. Can I say, can I. Well, okay. You know, I'm really
sweating right now. So I'm sorry. All right. I'll just. Okay. I'll spin the wheel. I'll spin the
wheel. You look. Okay. I get to do a hit, right? I lost. I know I can't say that for on TV. Thank
you. It was a pleasure hanging out with you. Oh, it's broken. Can you just even look at it? It's
broken. Your shoe is undone. Okay. Moving on. I don't really want to do this one, but I will.
Should I do this one? This one is pick nose and eat it. Skip it? Should I skip this one? No. Yeah,
you're right. Nevermind. I bet that's too gross. Okay. Naruto hand signs. From what I know about
Naruto hand signs. It's this thing, right? Where you go like, boom. I've never seen the show. It's
like, right? You go like that. Perfect. All right. Let's get some better angles. You catch up to him.
Oh, wait. I'll catch up to him. I mean, you catch up to him. You catch up to him. I'll take care of
some stuff. I'll give us a barrier shield. You're all the way over there. Hold on. I got to turn
this off. No, no, no. I think I just killed an animal over there. Hold on. I'll get you in a
minute. It's raining. This shoe. Why does it keep... The other shoe. What the fuck? Hug the camera
and say, hey, chin up, kid. How does that work? Hey. Bring it in. Come on. Come here. Keep your chin
up, kid. Hey. Bring it in. You and me. I know you. We're going to do it. We knew you were going to
do this. Yeah. Okay. Fucking. Ooh. Ooh. Hey. Hey, you. Nice work. Awesome. Hey, by the way, tie your
shoes. I haven't even got the costumes yet. Hey. Why am I addressing with hey? Like, hey. Just do
it normally. Just come for a hug. How do you... I don't know. How do you give hugs? I don't know
how you get... How do you give a hug? You people just kind of do that. You just go like, hey, like,
hi. Nobody comes like this. Like I'm a giant, like Venus flytrap. Fuck, like squish you.
All right. Let's try one more time. Hey. Yeah. Yeah. Very good. Hey, you too. Give me.
Mm-hmm. Ooh. A little tight. Okay. Okay. See you. See you tomorrow. How can I forget you? George.
George. Yep. Mm-hmm. That was a fun party. That was a really fun party. Next time,
I'll bring drinks. Delete that one too. What is going on? They said they wanted me to hug people.
Okay. Transform into a transformer. But you're just a guy. Okay. Omega Tron. We've got
Decepticons coming at us from two angles. One. Two. I'll make sure to change into my super flying
jet monster. Jet monster activate. What's his name? Oh, what's his name? Prime. Optimus Prime. Okay,
that's what it was. Thanks for the wine. Now, this is too many of them. Shell. You go that way.
Boomstick. Out that way. I'll handle this. I'm the only one that can fly. That was a JoJo.
All right. How about this one? Time to change. Transformers. Transform into object of flight.
Ow! Ow! Ow! My fucking bones! Ow! Ah! Oh, it hurts every time. Just like Wolverine.
Eat this. Decepticons? That's a family guy. This one requires a chair.
This is play a slot machine from all angles.
I don't even care if I win. This is the rush of the colors.
We got any cigarettes, by the way? Yeah, I'll take it back. There we go. Bonus. Come on.
Come on. Fuck. Thank you. I can bring it over. No, I don't think I know how to smoke a cigarette.
I'm exhaling while I put, okay. I can't get this. Hope I'm a big winner. Let me put my feet up.
Ah. That's a pretty good, that's a pretty good view. I don't know what this is. I'm just going
with it. I don't know what I'm supposed to be doing. I feel like I'm a baby in a car scene.
Perfect. Wow, look. It's a tree. Two trees. Hey, mom. Hey, mom. Mom. Mom. Did you see a tree?
Hey, mom. Hey, mom. Hey, mom. Where are we going to go to Wendy's? Mom, where are we going to go to
Wendy's, bitch? Hey. Okay. Hey, dad. Hey, dad. Hey, dad. Control. Why am I a big baby?
Use the chair like what? There he sits. Fall out of the chair.
I want to go to McDonald's. Mom, I want to go to McDonald's. Okay. But can we go to
McDonald's now? Jesus. Slow down. There's a sale on Wendy's. Oh, mom. Mom, you didn't put my seatbelt
on. In fact, I don't think you've ever put my seatbelt on. Hey, it's me, the Joker. This is a
fucking terrible one-man show, by the way. The chair? Hey, when we get older, we think.
Our brains develop, and they reach into us, into ourselves. The great philosopher Galileo once said,
if I can't see it, then it must not exist. I was 18. I found myself in the high school dance,
nervous for all of us, except on this particular day. Huh? Okay. We have a guy back here.
What's that, sir? I'm kind of in the middle of doing something here. No, that's disgusting.
Can we get security to take care of this guy? Okay. You could be funnier than I am.
I highly doubt that, though. What are you? Get out of here! Wait, what? Oh, I blocked it.
It's crazy, people. No, no, no. That's all right. It's all right. So I leaned in,
and I was going to go. I was thinking about douching. It was my first kiss,
and it didn't happen. It's okay. I was really in love. I knew it. Just give me a minute. I'm
kind of winded. You can probably imagine. I'm going to get some water. I'll be back.
Ace Attorney? Wait, at what point in Ace Attorney does a guy start fighting people with a chair?
Does that happen in Ace Attorney? I'm going to get some water. I'm going to refill. I'll be right
back. You never notice how hot hot is until you have lights at every direction pointing at you.
Moving on. What's next? Oh, yes. Exactly. Yes. I've wanted to do this for a very long time.
This is the I'm at your birthday party. You can put me wherever the fuck you want.
I'm going to be at your party. Ready? Actually, I might need this. We'll keep it over here for now.
Wow. Two years old. They grow up so fast. Wow. Three years old. They grow up so fast. Four,
you say? Four years old? Wow. Getting bigger, stronger. Five. Five. That's a milestone,
all right. Five years old. Getting old. He's an old man. She's an old man. Old woman. Wait,
isn't that Jeffrey's birthday party? Sorry. Six years old. Holy shit. That's ancient.
You know what I mean? That's ancient. Seven. Seven years old. Wow. Lucky. Seven. Eight. Nine.
Ten. You're 11. You're 12. You're 13. You're 14. You're 15. You're 16. Sweet. I'm so glad to be
invited to Your Sweet 16. Mike, Dave, Anthony, Sharon, Crystal, Carl, Matt, who's Tom,
Jennifer, Jessica. I'm happy to be here. I'm here for your birthday party. Hey, everybody.
It's blowing out the candles. That's perfect. Okay, wait, wait, wait, wait.
So glad I got to go to your birthday party. We're going to have so much fun.
Everybody's here. We're all here for your birthday. Happy birthday. Hey, guys. Holy smokes.
It's about to blow out their candles. Everybody get on out here. Go on. Happy birthday to you.
Come on, everybody. Come on. Happy birthday to you. Happy day, dear, oh. Happy birthday.
Fucking God damn it. It was so close. It was so close. Everybody gather around. It's about
to blow out their candles. All together now. All of us. Happy. No, I can't. You do it. I get
nervous when I'm around a crowd. Happy birthday to you. I'll get it. I need a break. We need some
angles from back here. To you. Happy. What's this? How does it go? To happy. Oh, I gotta say their
name. You guys are going to hate this one, but I don't care. If I solidify my online legacy with
one thing, let's have it be this. Happy birthday to you. Happy birthday to you. Happy day, dear.
Happy birthday to you. All right, that's it. We had so much fun. Wow. Your birthday was a great
time. Look at what you got for presents. That'll be $200. Thank you. Hey, Jones, blow the fuck out
of here. That was really, that was probably the worst thing. Oh, wait, what about the chair?
Wait, it's going to be my birthday. No, not my birthday parties. I'm moving on.
Who is that? Amnestic O.W. Just gave 40 community subs. Holy shit. Thank you. That's a lot.
That's so many subs. My birthday's public domain. Yeah, I know. Put your arm around a fake person.
This could probably be a chair. Hey, just the two of us hanging out, having a good time. You,
you and me, we're in this together. Always. Right. I know. It's unbelievable. I can't believe it
either. An asteroid might hit the earth. What? When did you read that nonsense? Uh-huh. Right.
Oh my goodness. You're the funniest person I think I've ever met. What was that?
A little too close to the ear. It was loud. So what do you want to, what do you want to go?
No, no, no, no. Let's not go there. Right. Okay. So, you know, I probably told you that you're my
best friend. Well, I am. Yes, I am. Sure. Sure. Okay. Over the, yeah. My arm really hurts. We've
been doing that for like six hours straight and the blactic acid's building up. I kind of just need
to move. Oh, we're still best friends. We are. We are still friends. Just, I mean, maybe because
we'll just switch arm. We'll switch. Come here. Okay. Yeah, that's, that's probably better.
Okay. Yep. Thank you. I don't know why, why do we have to do this? Why can't we just,
yeah, just stand that way? I just said, in fact, I've always never, I've never been comfortable
like just like holding onto your like a neck for the last few years. I just, stupid. I don't know
why we do this. You know how hard it is to put my fucking clothes on? With like, with twins.
All right. I have no idea if that's what you wanted, but that's what you got. Offer something
to the camera. This is valuable. Worth a lot, probably. Oh, hey. Would you like one? Here.
Take one. Only a few of these left in existence. I'm certain of that. And I'm giving it to you.
That's right. Take it. It's yours. Don't sell it though. I don't know. Don't sell it. Do not sell
that. Wow. What? You see this? Do you, I don't, do you want it? Here. Take it. Take it. Take it.
Take this. Take this from me. Take this from me. Take this from me right now. Take it from me.
Take it from me, dude. I don't want to fucking hold it anymore. Take it from me. Take this thing
out of my fucking hands before I freak out. Take it from me. Take it. You don't have to take it
out of my fucking hands. Listen next time. What's next? Skipping, skipping and frolicking.
Oh, look at the guy with his shoe untied. Every time something happens, he has to bend down and
tie his shoes because his shoes are like a size too big for him or something. And I don't know
what that even means. What does that even mean? I haven't skipped since I was probably eight.
How do you skip? Like this. It's just becoming this. I don't know how to skip. I don't know how.
I did it a little bit. Somebody said, do the joker's stare dance. Let me just tell you that
I'm going to be honest. I've never seen this movie. I'm just going to go by what I've seen
in the trailers. Oscar. Big bits of shit they were. Dude, every year I get older, I just slow it down
with a Q and B. Jesus Christ. This is a shitload of money. Let me load up the dashboard. Okay,
first of all, Dr. Noobstein gave a hundred dollars. Can you please say something nice to my nephew,
Matthew? I'm going to turn into a virtual card for his second birthday. Okay. Wait,
I got, I did not already get you. Hold on. Hold on. I said Matthew, right? Just in case.
Matthew. Matthew, it's your birthday. Look at all these balloons. Look at all these balloons.
There's balloons everywhere. I can't even get away from them. They're just surrounding me.
Matthew, happy second birthday. My goodness. You're getting so old. You've grown up big and
strong. Eat your vegetables, especially that broccoli. Wow. What's your favorite color? Mine,
tween. Stop. You're scaring him. You're scaring him. He's two. You're like a guy like coming over
like at you. Like that's fucking scary. You're right. That's scary. Hey, hey, Matthew. I heard
it was your second birthday. Don't give that one to him. Seriously. Don't give that one to Matthew.
Thanks for the 100 bucks though. That's a lot of money. You're cursed.
Somebody wants me to do sneezes?
I'm going to sneeze. I just want you to understand I'm going to sneeze and I don't want you to be near
me. I'm not held in. No, don't sneeze. Don't sneeze. Don't sneeze right now. Do not sneeze.
I can't sneeze right now.
No, people are going to be fucking. How are you?
Getting close to the props. Oh, all right. Fine. Fortnite default dance. Let's see if I can pull
this from memory. Isn't it like, is it? That's a single ladies dance. What is it? It's like,
I'm just going to do orange t-shirt kid. That's the only one that I know. I don't know any other
dance. I'm like a fly that's getting stuck to a fly trap. Shit. This is bad.
Sing solid notes. Okay.
Done. That was good. It's going to go higher. This is fucking stupid.
How many years has it been since I was last powered on? Two minutes, you say?
But why do you look so much uglier?
Get kicked out of the casino. All right. Fine. This thing sucks. This thing sucks. I just put
$40 in here. What the fuck? Hey, machine. You ever get fucking anything? Hey,
are you going to pay me some money, buddy? That was really, really bad. I'm going to redo that.
Let's go back to zero. What's that? $14 down the drain? Un-fucking-believable. Piece of shit
doesn't pay any money. Doesn't pay any money. Never. Doesn't pay any money. Oh, look, you are.
You want a jackpot over there? Good for you. Good for you. And what about me? Where's my jackpot?
What's that? No, I just put $14 in there and I didn't get $2,000 back. What's going on with this
crap? What are you, dumb? I was just kidding. Look, I put money in here. All right. All right.
All right. Don't. Okay. All right. Why do you have handcuffs? Are you cops? What? Wait, how did you?
No, I just put one of my money back. I put $14 in. All right. Stop. Ow. Ow. Ow. Ow. Ow.
Ow. I think they're too tight. Hey, by the way. Wait. No, I got it. Okay. What am I under? I'm
under arrest apparently now. I'm under arrest. Okay. That's a little tight. Okay. You can't do
this to me. Do you have any idea who I am? You have any idea who I am? Yeah. German985. Look me up.
How many followers you got? Ow. Ow. Ow. Okay. Ow. Ow. Ow. Ow. Ow. What the? God damn it.
I didn't do anything. Yeah. 200,000 followers at last. My check. Uh huh. Uh huh. Yeah. Uh huh.
Okay. Sure. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Sorry to say. I've got more tricks and tricks up my sleeve
than fucking Houdini. Okay. Yep. Yep. Yep. Yep. All right. Yes. Yes. Yes. Yes. Yes. Yes. I will
listen to you. I will listen to you. Got it. Ah. Yeah. Damn it. That hurts. I think I broke them.
Yeah. Okay. Oh shit. Ah. You bastard. They got me. They got me. Yeah. Okay. Hey. How does it feel
for you to be caught up in this shit? Don't move. There. Yeah. How do you like that?
Now you're under arrest. Bastard. He's sweating. All right. All right. Okay. All right. I can't
move as you can tell. What do you want? You ain't gonna get anything out of me. Nothing at all.
You think you get it? I won't talk. Mosquitoes out tonight? Mosquitoes out tonight?
She farts like a grandma. You're not gonna get me to talk. I'll promise you that.
Shouldn't I be bleeding by these open hands? All right. Bye. Enough. The coordinates are
60. Wait a minute. Got it. What? What do you want from me? You fiends. You bastards. You villains.
Oh. Oh my God. Okay. My bank account is 212-999-4. The coordinates are 6.
My grandmother's address and my grandmother's famous recipe for tomato sauce is two pounds of
butter. I know it sounds like a lot, but man, why didn't you went right for that? Two pounds
of tomato sauce, three pounds of sugar. You boil it and then you take it off the fridge for two
hours. That's the secret. What the fuck is wrong with you? Right here. This is where babies come
from. And you're gonna do that to me? Okay. Okay. Yeah. Where am I gonna go? Where am I gonna go?
Wait, what? Oh, that's. Shit. I was trying to have it stay connected. Do a curvy inhale. Oh,
do a sob bit. Oh, I gotta take off. There's a tag on here. Official major league baseball.
Official hell of a major league baseball. Leave the tag on? I can't. Oh, there's a boom mic.
Boom mic in the shot. It's better. Hey, where am I? What is this? What the fuck is this? No,
no, no. This is a dream. This is a dream. I'm having a dream. I can't, I can't.
No, you sick fuck. How am I supposed to get a key out of my stomach? You don't even give me anything.
This is due to my hands. It's not gonna work. It's not gonna work. What the fuck? Oh, what are you
ordering? Food. Okay. Why are you still on my line here? That's weird. Can you get me some food?
Can I get number two? You didn't? Yeah, you didn't hang out.
That was the most work I've ever done in my life. Oh no. Steve, oh, you fucking got me. Wow.
It's gonna die. I mean, you put me down here. Oh, bachelor party. All right. Are you shitting me?
Let's go. Oh my God. I can't. Oh, it was so easy. Get the party bus. Let's go, man.
Let's get on that bus. Okay. Now we have to do one where like my head actually explodes.
So that's the comedy one. This is the one where like my head explodes.
There's no way I can get that out of my stomach. No, no, no, no, no, no.
All right. That's where you, you have to end the video there. That's how you end the video
with my head exploding. Let me give you a hand. Is this fucking fucked up? I can't tell.
All right. No, this is like, I don't like that. That's, that's weird. That's like,
this is fucking twisted. This is twisted. Why am I like getting murdered in a Saw movie?
I'm putting way too much time into this. Why? Why do I want to get like fucking slaughtered
on camera? What the fuck? What's wrong with me? One guy said do saw. You got too into the role.
Do it without the helmet on. The helmet's supposed to crush my head. It's supposed to like squish my
head. I can't see a goddamn thing. So I cannot even tell if I'm in the right spot. How do people
wear these? How do people wear these at sporting events? Is it on backwards? I can't see shit.
You can literally put anything. You can put like a Pillsbury Doughboy's head up here. In fact,
let's go for it. You can just put the Pillsbury Doughboy. You were too tall.
Fuck. My scrumptious, my scrumptious croissants will make you and your family very happy.
Stop. It's cursed. Mega cursed. Mega cursed. Okay. We're not even in the meat and potatoes yet.
Do Spider-Man? Hold on. We've got so many copyright characters over here. You gotta just hold on.
This is gonna be hard. I got it. I got it. I got it. I got it. Where's it going? Oh, that way. That way.
Leg, leg, leg, leg cramp, leg cramp. I got it. I got it. I got it. I got it.
No, it'll be fine. It'll be fine. It didn't sound broken.
That's not how you lift things. Look at the thumbnail. What's the thumbnail? What's the thumbnail?
I can't click it. It's going too fast. I can't click it. It's going too fast.
It's too fast. I can't click it. I'm using a track pad. It's a hostage video.
Thumbnail. Is it a hostage video? Was it when I was getting into the chair?
That's the scariest fucking thing. Look at them. You can see like my, you can see my like busted
up nose through that thing. We had a raid. I can't even see who it was. Who raided? Charborg? Thank
you Charborg for the raid. Welcome everybody. We're in the middle of the second green screen stream
about two years ago. I got in front of this thing and people made a bunch of really fun shit and
I'm going to give like five times more footage. Thanks a lot. Welcome guys. It was one year ago
it was like two. All right what's next? The classic, you want to see how good I'm,
I'll show you how good I'm going to be at this. The classic Jim Carrey sneak walk.
What's this thing? No neck. The camera's fucked up. Oh the camera's fucked up. Move the chair.
Pretend to be a puppet on a marionette. Hey everyone. Welcome to the show. It's me,
your host, Charborg. I'm breaking out of here. No, I've had enough. I'm getting out of here.
The blood is rushing through my entire body. This is what it's like to be a real boy. Wow.
This feels great. I can do this and I can do this. What else? Different waving cuts. Hi there. Cool.
Hey. Hey. Hey. Hey. Hey. Okay. Next one is dodging bullets like the matrix.
This one's going to be fucking impossible. It's so sweaty. Change the shirt.
Lose the shirt. I can't lose the shirt. Oh fuck. Oh man. This is like spilled water on myself. This
is not even. Oh boy. Hold on. Keep the shirt for consistency. I love her look. Okay. Stare at
various things with no emotion. Ew. No, that's emotion. Okay. There's your no emotion. Peewee
Herman dance. Oh I know what this is. This is da da da da da da da. This is the. There you go.
Caramel dancing. Caramel. This is crack. Do it. Do it. Do it. Hold on. What is it? Wait. Caramel
dancing? Let's see. What is it? This is scary. I'm not doing this. Nope. This is what. This is
just what you do when you're trying to get like you're trying to get your armpits in the shower.
You go like. Oh nope. You're going to come back and bite me like in the ass. How about
doing my own version of it? That's worse. How was that worse than. What do you mean worse?
What. Why is this video. Why are these people look like the old emoji commercials?
That you. Text. Wow. Whoa. Like then the face goes like. Like into the screen.
Text two two one eight five and text the word funny to get crazy emotes and it's like.
Get annoying ringtones.
Why is that? It's those faces. Choke on a lozenge.
Choke on a lozenge.
Take two. Watermelon.
Tell him I'm fine.
Not today.
Quit. Quit that shit. Dude how are you doing this like. I'm going to like actually pass out.
Don't wait for me.
Disgusting. He's in my body. I just. I just ate him. I just like.
I have a job interview in a fucking 10 minutes.
Come on. Hey Mr. Smith. Hey Mr. Smith. I have money. Fuck. Oh I'm late.
No more bugs or lozenges. I'm done. I will do this though.
How do I do. How do you make contact. I'm not doing car mode dancing.
Make contact is this right. Is it one arm in the air. Holy shit.
I got to change clothes after this one. One arm up and one arm. Like that right.
It's like a clock. You point to like three o'clock on a clock right. That's right.
Yes. Very good. All right what else. The Carlton dance. Carlton dance.
That's you go like. How does it. It goes like. How does it go. Close enough.
They're all just German walks. Captain Morgan. This thing. Wait that was dumb.
Sit at the family dinner table. Dad's chair. Ow. I hurt. I got hold on. Costume change.
I'm going to put it on. Make sure you guys can see. I'm going to be like naked back here.
This is not going to go to those moments. Right. This is not going to be one of those moments.
Where like people found like Shia LaBeouf's flag because they saw a fucking like a star.
Like it's you're not going to be able to zoom in there and see like a reflection of my like
naked body or something right. I'm going to the other room. People are too good at that.
People are too sophisticated with that shit that they have. We're back. Of course. So.
In my in my in my paranoia to not have you see me take my clothes off.
I walked out here. Walked out there. And I take my shirt off. And this is security camera.
Right there. Right. Kind of just. If they have it off they're just like OK. Here he is.
Oh no. I just don't. Don't. He's an idiot. OK. I'm going to get my dad. Why would dad have it?
Here comes the first costume. I'm going to sweat this off in about 30 seconds.
So we've got to get used to this shit otherwise. I only got two of these.
I'm going to sweat this off. All right. I need to see the mirror. I'm going to go to the preview.
Super Mario. Super Mario. Oh. I'm breathing the nose. I'm breathing the hairs in my nose.
I have to breathe out of my mouth for this. Am I going to a Jerry Garcia concert?
This is a pretty weird dad. Now forget that. This is a baby hat. Human suit jacket.
Dad at the dinner table. Dad at the dinner table. Dad at the dinner table.
It's you. I'm not going to be able to fucking do this because somebody just said
Geraldo. Well I mean it's kind of it's kind of insane. Here. I can't. I can't. I've seen
the viewfinder. Who cares. I'm going. I'm ready. OK. So what do we have tonight? Look at that.
Delicious. Potatoes. Mashed potatoes and gravy. You've about done yourself.
You passed the salt plate. Don't throw it over here. OK. So how was your day? Son? Wow. In class.
That's unbelievable. Susie? My kids. My kids are the smartest. Straight A's.
That's a little tough I think. A little tough. A little overdone but it's still good.
Well my day was pretty interesting. I got fired and then I got hired by the company next door.
Just walked out. Brought my briefcase in. This is the big DLT guy. Perfect. Oh my god. I'm so happy.
Oh my god. I can do this. I can do this. Hot. Hot. Keep it cool. Cool. Keep it. Holy shit.
I'm so happy right now. This is the best day of my life. This is the best day of my entire life.
I'm eating mashed potatoes right now. Right. Get out. Go back. Back into the scene. Come on.
So I heard. Who's you got to fight today son? OK. Let me tell you something. If you can do
not do it diplomatically then you shouldn't be doing it at all. I heard that you punched him.
Did you? You punched him? You punched him in the face? My son doesn't do that.
Diplomacy only. You know how much trouble I could get in? I'm in the. I'm in the gosh darn.
I'm getting heated here. My son. A United States representative. That's your. I'm your dad. Yeah.
I'm the representative. Not you. That would be strange now wouldn't it? You got to do things
diplomatically. Or you're grounded. No. You know what? I can. I'll handle it. You are grounded.
You're grounded. We don't fight in this family. Eat your gosh darn. I. I keep saying that stuff
and I don't want to. Now listen. Family. If we could join hands. No? OK. I. What is this?
What is this? What? Oh boy. Gravy. Potatoes. Meat. Cheese. Onions. Tomatoes. Peppers.
Yes. Oh I had a long day at work. Let's go.
That was fantastic. The best meal I've had in probably a week. Could you believe it? Now.
Down to business. We got to go to grandma's house. You and me. That's right son. And you and me.
We're going to end this spit because where are you going to use this?
Where are you going to use this? I don't think there's anywhere it can go.
You need to put me in a dinner scene. Or I can talk about my son's diplomacy.
I don't think it's possible to use this. You understand? Good luck. It's just been word soup
for about 13 straight minutes. Soup. Oh dear look at that. I didn't know we were having tomato bisque
today honey. Wow. I'm full. And I don't want to hear anybody talking anymore. Go ahead and leave
your dear old dad here while he just relaxes for a little while. Yeah. Son you are in big trouble.
Hey I want to go to McDonald's. I want to go to McDonald's. No I want to go to Wendy's too.
Mom I want to go to both. Mom I want to go to McDonald's. Feed me this shit.
Only McDonald's. We're a McDonald's family for Christ's sake. We only eat McDonald's.
Okay done. Get this shit out of the way. What is this a link? You can't use that anywhere.
Mr. Potter. Okay hold on. Is this Slytherin? I got a whole routine plan for this by the way.
Death eaters. Expelliarmus. Procutify. Harry. Hurry. I just hit him right in the skull.
I just cracked his skull. Oh no my cloak. Quick into the castle. Expelliarmus.
Oh that's disgusting. It's illicit. Oh I can't look at this. Harry. Harry it's uh
I gave you some leverage here. Thank you. On the count of three. One. Two. Three.
Don't tell me. That was weird. Expelliarmus. Expelliarmus. Expelliarmus. Expelliarmus.
Other words they say.
Cyanideus. Just hold on. I gotta put this on the right way. We're skipping to the props.
Even though I don't want to. It's Geraldo. Okay hold on. Oh the Wizarding World of Harry
I can't wait but I'm gonna do my sorting hat routine. Is it my turn? Oh great sorting hat.
I know exactly what I'm going to get. I'm a Slytherin. There we go. No I'm a Slytherin.
No. Now stop laughing. No I don't. I took the nine question test on Pottermore.
That's an in-depth person. I. No I'm not a Ravenclaw. This is uncalled for. Remove this
hat from me immediately. Do it again. Torturing people. Murdering people. Murdering them.
Oh see. See I told you. I told you all. Hey you and me. You're evil too right?
We're probably going to be really good friends. I hope we don't jump across each other.
Yeah fuck that guy. And their whole school. That's what we do. We're going to fuck with them.
Yeah we're going to be friends. I know it. I'll probably die in the third movie.
But you'll get to live through the whole series. And there'll be people that use my face
as their profile pictures on Twitter. I can't wait. I can't. Oops. We were pretty mature on
that one. Don't want to be evil too quickly. Slytherin me. I believe. So see it's probably
a little warmer. Wait what do you want? What? An 11 year old with a mustache? Whatever.
Hold on let me put this back on. I don't know how to put a tie on.
I don't know how to put a tie on. Oh I'm going to stay in character.
It's two ties okay. It's two. That's right.
Harry's an idiot. Get him. Get him Malfoyle. Oh my god. Harry you're a poopoo idiot.
Excuse me you think you can do me? Wait wait wait. No no no no.
Why are you cheating? You can cheat codes. You have an entire family behind you.
We're all lost people. It's unfair. I'm fine if you don't die in these PG-13 movies. I'm fine.
Oh but they do. Oh Harry. I'm not going to put up with it anymore Harry.
You attacked my friend Malfoyle and for that you'll pay.
Oh god. Now Malfoyle I'll take it off.
Stupid boy. Oh shit. How did you do that? Oh I've been foiled. Okay you got me. Ow. Shit.
Ow ow ow.
It instantly broke. It instantly broke. Instantly. My immersion. Oh no. Okay well now.
Now you can't even see. God damn it. I'm in trouble now. I'm in trouble now. I found the one joke
that I want to do for like the next hour. Shit. God damn it. Where is it? Yeah Harry. We'll see
you on the field of Quidditch. And we got it. Ha ha. Whoa. Dis. That's two points Harry. Stupify.
Stupify. Am I still alive? I lost connection. German no. What? Hold on. Let me get some water.
Holy shit. My iPad is dead. Like bad. It overheated. That's why I couldn't see Jack.
I sweated the mustache off. Water. I can't believe my like to death. It's dead.
I think it's brick. Wait. Hey I can see you guys now. Wow. Do the come up. Let me go back to this.
I want some good close-ups. What am I doing? It's like this. I did this shit in the mirror.
I still. I don't. I still don't understand this. Yeah Harry. You. Oh I feel like somebody like
ordered this. Don't you feel like somebody ordered this and I'm fulfilling an order?
Yeah tell them. Ha. Trying to think of what to say. You have no idea what's in store for you Harry.
Me and Malfoy are going to destroy you. Oh come on. When I grow up I'm going to be a death eater
just like my father. Guys I'm an actor. I've been acting the whole time.
Yeah I know it seems a little weird at first but I can assure you this started as a small experiment
where I was going to come in here and pretend to be a I was going to pretend to be a teenager
and come in and try to fill in and then I got way too involved and started to make friends and stuff
and this is this is pretty much my movie now. I don't. Yeah I know that. Look Harry. But I mean
this is this is my movie now and it's called A Kid in the Castle. Check it out on ABE. Don't say
copyrighted stations. Go to Best Buy like this? I got. Hold on. I'm going. I'm skipping ahead.
Let me just get this one out of the way please. Let me get this one out of the way.
Yeah. Look at how big that slide is. Oh look at how big that one is. I bet you you puke on that one.
Dude I bet you I won't even scream when I go down it. Wow these are great. Look at these.
But that has to be four or five thousand feet tall. Called the bleeder. Oh I gotta get in line.
Oh right there down. Oh man. Is it fast? Is it fast? Is it fast? I hope so.
Hey give me a high five. Whoa. Holy shit.
Oh
Stop the top the right. Stop the right.
That was awesome. I think I need to go. Jeans and shoes. Oh dude it's lip and slide. Are you kidding me?
Oh that was fun. Hey. Wow cool. That looks like fun. Hey get out of the way. Get out of the way you
little shits. You think I need this? I go bare ass. Now don't stop me. Okay. Oh it's not. I'm gonna
get arrested after this. Oh well. Hey there's another guy. What? Hey there's another guy going
down the slide right over here. Oh we did it. High five. What are the odds? Don't even tell me the odds.
This sucks. Why do people ride this? Hey I'm doing it. I'm doing it. I'm doing it. This has
got to be a record I think. Ah it's a record. It has to be. Keep tracking this. 30 seconds.
All right let me get. I gotta get back on track. Okay people want more driving.
Hey you remember that water park? I heard it's really really good. This road sucks. It's such a
bad road. I'd really hate to take you this way. Oh watch it. Oh Lyft? No that's not me. That was
my twin brother. I mean I drive for Lyft too but he was a twin. I swear it's not just me again with
shirt on. You do drugs? No. Well I don't even. Hot out today. What was that on the road? I have
no idea. I don't I don't want to hit it. I don't want to hit this thing. I'm gonna go slow. I'm
gonna go really slow. I have to drive over it. Is it alive? I don't know. Oh okay. I think I'm fine.
I think. Weird. You're holding a giant doughnut. We heard your spine crack. Yeah welcome to hell.
Hey that's the window going down. Why don't you get in. Let's go for a ride. You and me. You got
the stuff. Come on in. We guys I don't want to break up your little fun little uh thing you got
going in backseat here but we got company. I'll handle this. Hey hey. Oh hey oh you want to go?
You want to go? You want to go? You want to go? You want to? I think I broke my arm.
That doesn't work. Oh that doesn't work it like it does and I'm doing bad over here.
I'm doing real bad. Milky sit down. Oh I could sit down. You're right let me sit down. I could just
sit down. Not going so good over here. It's a nice car. It's a it's a really nice car. Buckle up.
Nice smooth nice and smooth smooth. I know I love left hand turns. Maybe I should try going right
but I can't. I've always gone left. I was going a big square. I can't. Okay this time this time
you can do it. You can go right. Hey fellas I'm gonna go right. Never mind. No I'm not. No no
I'm not. Never mind. Never mind. It's too comfortable to go the way that I know. I'm sorry.
I know I'm taking this. I know but we just the bank was but I can't. I'm just let's just just
bear with bear with my bullshit for a little bit. Come on man. We're good. Oh I'm bumping into shit.
Why didn't somebody car themed green screen? You know what? All right what anything else in the car?
Do a pilot. I'm not doing a get run over. Oh actually yeah this was one. It was walking into
the street and just like walking like around the street. Hey Gary. Yeah I mean I don't I
looks like it's. Get his plate. Get his plate. Holy shit. He had to. He was probably going 200
pounds per hour. I didn't even see him. I went this way. I'm supposed to go that way.
He scraped me. Holy shit. That guy's going to jail man. Okay sunny day outside. Road. Road. Safe to me.
I think I'm Superman. You okay? Hey you all right in there? Yes yeah I'd like to report a accident.
Uh yeah I'm on one two three four five six seven eight nine ten street. Uh-huh. I punched I punched
a car and it crushed in front of me and I think I might have superpowers. No don't don't tell the
government about that. Okay okay have fun. You too. Bye. Open a window and scream at somebody.
Excuse me. Can we be quiet please? Some of us are trying to sleep.
What the fuck is going on? Oh no. Hi. Hi. Hello. Yes. How are you? Shut up. Shut up. All of you.
This is ridiculous. It's like this every single day and I'm sick and tired of hearing it. I can
hear you all the way up here and I pay rent too. Unbelievable. He hates us? Again. Again. Again?
Really? You're gonna do this again? I words cannot even comprehend how it. Oh you've got a mouth on
you don't you? I'm coming out there. I'm coming down there and I'm gonna fuck you up. And then
talking still huh? You stay right there. Don't move. Oh bad idea. People's elbow. I'm gonna do
the home alone face which is this. It's like a Pee Wee Herman scream right? He goes. Right something
like that? Voice crack. Dude. I like this one. Reach behind the camera and do a YouTuber out and
about vlog. Hey. Can you believe where I am? I can't either. Disney. Wow. Don't say Disney
World. I just started good. Cut. Cut. Welcome back. Hey everybody. Guess where I am? That's right. On
vacation. Take a look. I never get to go out of places like this so it's so much fun for me.
And before we video get started if you could please give me a thumbs up for being on vacation.
Well you're not on vacation. I'm doing all this cool fun shit and you're not. And I'm gonna continue
to do all kinds of really cool shit and you're just gonna watch me do cool shit and give me money to
do it too. And I'm gonna fly around the entire world and I'm gonna do a bunch of cool shit. Hey
you and me we're friends. Look at that. It's a palm tree. Can you believe it?
Hey. See this what you guys. Holy shit that hair is bad. You guys. Are you guys ready to see
what happens before the video starts? Hey. Fuck. Fuck. Hey what's going on everybody? I am here
on vacation. Do it fucking right. Oh my god. So bad. Stupid ass channel. Hey what's going on?
Better than that. That's not. You sound like you're fucking at a goddamn funeral. Hey everybody
welcome up on vacation. Vacation vlog coming your way. Can you believe that sight behind me?
It sure does look beautiful. Anyways I gotta hurry up and get to a cut before I blow my stack.
So. You're choking us. Like I'm talking to you. Like you're the person that I'm mad at.
Hey. Hey KU. Hey. Oh fuck. Listen to me. It's a selfie stick. Hey grandma. Happy birthday to you.
Just want to give you a quick little happy birthday. I'm here. We're wishing you the best
Although I know I haven't probably seen you in 10 years. I do these little videos for you
because
No, it's the least I can do
I'm not grabbing grandma
Hey
I can't do this one
Hey, what's going on? Hey, welcome to my channel. Welcome to my vlog as you can see
I'm i'm out and about right now and i'm having a ton of fun. It's so cool
I don't you wish that you were here with me right now
Choking somebody
No, is this weird? Is this gonna get like fucking weird?
if i'm like
This is so
Bov guy fucking murders you imagine that
Hey, yeah. Well, hey guys, welcome to my asmr channel. I fucking murder you. Yeah, that's the name of the stream
That's the name of the title of the video here. So remember before we get started. Hold on. This is funny
Hey, welcome back to I murder you
My favorite asmr channel that I run before the video starts before I virtually murder you
Just please give me a thumbs up and a like
And maybe spread the video around to maybe show it to your parents, you know and try to get me some followers
Yeah, okay. Let's get started
This is a simulation where I fucking murder you. Oh my god. I have to get this done
Whisper
Why would you ever ever click this video? Why do you want to be like virtually murdered?
Okay, and I imagine
I imagine that this person has like 700 videos and they're all just being just strangling you
Die you motherfucker
So remember if you like that video follow me on my journey what I virtually will kill you virtual murder
Virtual asmr murder. Oh, I can't it's too stupid
Okay
Hey, if you like that video, make sure you follow me and check me out some more. It's me the virtual murderer
That's right. I upload two or three videos a day where I virtually murder you
Give me a thumbs up and give me a share. I'll see you tomorrow in the next video. Have a great day
and remember
Okay
Oh
Like i'm punching you the thing is you could use that for a lot of different things
wait
Oh a couple more
Please what what what is it? I can't believe i'm dead the virtual beat you up virtual murderer channel
Okay, what's next I think i'm gonna have to bring out a classic by the way
Buy something at best buy
I don't know how well you how do we do that?
But how do you know just go to best buy? Okay
I love this story
Here it is. It's exactly what i'm looking for
a big flat screen tv
Yes, i'd like to buy this flat screen tv, please
Thank you
I love this place
Best buy
Yeah, okay
Great prices
You guys got great prices
Thank you
Have a nice day
What was the point of that do the spider-man dance?
Of course, you know, I don't I don't know the slide
What's the slide?
Okay, it's time
It's time to do this
You guys remember sequel
What the hell is this thing? Oh fuck. I hope you can't hear that get on what kind of fucking fingers are these?
You can put whatever you want there
The gloves are coming off of this one. Wait a minute. What? Hold on. You know, I don't understand
We're incredibly intelligent monsters and people don't even take us seriously. You know the people I've eaten. I absorb all their power
God the nerve of these scientists. They think they can tell me how to act and how to do my life
It's bullshit
Don't believe a single word that they say
God
They get me so so worked up
Oh
I don't like to get animalistic here
But I will oh god, why did I get the other thing?
Hey, what do you want me to do? Yeah. Yeah, you want me to walk around like i'm a fucking monster and start biting people and eating people
That's what you want me to do, but i'm not gonna do that. I got a brain up here and it works just fine
Oh, by the way, I got a 4.0 gta in college. What did you have?
Shit
I hope this one works
Shit, I can't zip it up
I can't
I can't zip it up
This feels terrible in here. Well, it's because i'm in here
Hold on. Let me
Almost got it
There's things like it's like ac in here. This is actually awesome
Come on zip
Oh, I caught the fucking thing in the zipper. There we go
Where are the hands? How the fuck does this thing work?
Holy shit, it's actually filling up
This feels really fucking weird
Where's the lightsaber?
I'm excited
Help
Help he's falling. He's killing me
Oh that hurt
Wait
Let me try
I'm gonna do it. I'm gonna do it. I'm gonna do it. I swear come on you wanna go
He's trying
This time it's a dinosaur
All right, get me out
Take your gun
He's trapped
Like a kid's birthday party
That is hot out. It's hot out today. It's like 100 degrees outside
Oh, oh god, just keep it together
Keep it together, Larry
I'm the rich. I'm the awesome rep prepared and I am here. I gotta get out of this thing kids. I
kids
Give it a fuck out
I can't get out
It's not real kids, I'm not a real dinosaur, okay
uh
real talk
Because I was zipped in it
I didn't think I was getting out
I literally thought I was gonna have to tear through with like my teeth and shit
I'm gonna get some water water break and I'm gonna make a phone call so I'll be right back. Give me one second
Okay
so
I have
I have about
40 minutes left at for studio time
So I gotta get some more stuff that I want to do
so
Uh, maybe an hour
I'm trying to try to get as much stuff in the in in an hour as I can
Because then I gotta clean I gotta like
Clean up and get the shit out of here
Uh, we're gonna go to sports
specifically
Uh, I got requests
to do
uh football like running throwing
and
Football game stuff a little bit more baseball stuff
Yeah, i'll get the brb
So I need my I was like doing like a song routine
I've been doing a lot of like, uh, yeah, I fucking die shit today
This is weird dlc. This is an interesting dlc
Like my head explodes i'm like strangling the audience and shit like what the hell? All right
Let me get this on. This is dog hair all over
Mcdlt don't worry. I'll get it. This is pretty this is comfortable
Having this on now
Aids attorney i'll be an ace attorney. Don't worry. I'm gonna just blow up through sports
Am I this sweaty that I can't put this on?
Okay blue 42
blue 42
Okay hike
Shrimp shrimp cocktail
Shrimp cocktail hike and jump
Are you guys ready? Okay. Are you guys ready on the other team?
You are
Set up
Trying to get you to go off sides
You just fucking hit me
Ready hit me. Yeah, pull the whistle. What the fuck?
All right
and
Go go that way. Come on. Come on. Come on. Come on. Come on. Come on. Yes
Nice job. That's how we get it done
That is how we get it done
All right. Hey, are you ready?
Hey, hey, get your fucking head in the game, man
These are the bruisers
All right, let's go
Good catch
Nice well, I came back. I thought I got it. I oh shit
shit
Oh dad, I got it. I got it. I got off you
No, this is like i'm gonna poop out a football lay an egg
All right, here comes my son
No, no, no, no, I said
Touchdown
I'm going for a touchdown
Beth you suck
Yeah
Touchdown
Yeah, hey, look at me
Oh
I ran that fast my whole life
Almost fell forward a beard chunk
Yeah
touchdown
Oh
I don't even have to try
Hey, hey watch this play
Yeah
What's happening? All right. I'm gonna die take a rest. All right
I'm gonna sit down
Take a load off. Yeah, I did. I already did
Lives in all directions like a star
and scream
Fine
You want caramel dancing?
fine
Touchdown. Yeah
Touchdown
You guys ever heard of this one? Hey, hey, whoa. Whoa booze booze. Hey
I thought he's throwing shit at me. Fuck you. Hey guy
Guy in the green shirt. Is he all right? He's blind. He's bleeding. Hey, but come on
What an arm what an arm, right? The guys on the bruises aren't gonna make that throw
Whatever just give him whatever give him a hundred grand
Give a blank check like that fucking recall the caulking movie. Oh, wow. I look
disheveled
baseball
So I I love
Doing baseball green screen
I cannot wait to see
I'm gonna give you at least like a dozen clips
I got some things in mind
I need the helmet again. Why is it so much fun?
I feel like time's just like disintegrating. It's been like four hours three and a half hours time is just disintegrating
All right, let's go
He's throwing too fast
Slow down a little he's throwing
So fast like i'm not a bear
Oh I have a picture
Oh god
Safe and home plate. Yeah fist bump. Thank you. Thank you. Yeah another home run safe
Bunt here comes a bunch ready and this better be a home run. Holy what the fuck
I don't I just suck all scientists. I don't know man. What the fuck was that home run bunt
All right, now this is just getting fucking stupid
Is the only glove I could get
It's a fucking children's glove. Why do they wear jeans?
If I give shit
Good game. Nice guy. Nice guy
Nice job big hit to the outside of the out of the bounce. Nice job fart on camera. What the fuck?
Nice job. Good eye. Good eye
So i'm sorry, I was um saying just just recharging bro
Just getting a quick little recharge
Too much baseball content not enough baseball content. I love baseball. It's my favorite
All right, i'm tired
You need to do an umpire. All right. No, no more baseball content do the dlt
Oh, right. Right. Right. Wait, why am I putting this back on? Why does it all direction like a star?
Wait, okay. What does this person want?
Put your hands out in all directions like a star like this
Like a like a star
He's gonna roll down a hill with a tire god
I have like so many more things to do
What do I want to do? Oh somebody wanted this
Oh, wait, these are green
Shit, these are green
Does it matter?
Somebody wanted me to do like that. Hey, like put it down. There's a circle of people
Here wait
Nah, we gotta stick to the plan. We gotta stick to the plan, man
Hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey
Relax
Put it down you put it down
Put it down put it
I just I killed him. I I shot him. I uh
You good. You want to split it?
Okay. Yeah, um
He bought it
I get all the money
Yeah, no, no, relax. Relax, man. We got one job dude. We're gonna do that job
Okay. Uh, hey, all right
Put yours down
Now you put yours down
both of you
Put your guns down
I ain't gonna say it again
No, put it down
No, you put yours down
I'm not putting my gun down
No, no, no, no
Bullshit
It was your idea in the first place
No, we could i'll be here all day. Uh, go ahead come i'll tell this for an hour
I can do this for three hours
How are you guys, uh back muscles?
How are your how your lats?
I'm not putting them down
I'm not gonna put them down. Fuck this is starting to hurt me. Why do people want it?
Okay
On the count of three
We're all gonna put our guns down
ready
one
two
three
Hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, put it down. Yeah. Yeah, just come on man
I don't want it to shoot either one of you
But I I will don't uh, come on
really
Don't relax. Okay. Everybody relax on three. We're gonna put our guns down. Just listen to me. Trust me
And kick them over there
Ready?
Come on do it. Don't be a fucking asshole. Come on, man
One there you go
Two and kick it over there two
Three here we are. See
see
Didn't think I had a fucking light chamber. Did you?
Wait, you what you have one. Why do you have one? Well, you both why do you both have one? This is not
shy god
Rotate in place in a circle
Watch out. I got you back rotate. Okay now
I want to do the lower thirds
Uh commercial in the like in the bottom of the tv show that's like right like here
You know what i'm saying?
With the letters and it's like, oh, it's my stream
And then this
I watch my fucking stream
All right, that's it now, uh
What is a fluoride stair? What's the what's the fluoride stair? What is I don't know. Is that like a
Look it up
All right, the fluoride stair is that's a fortnight dance it has to be
Dlt, all right, let's go
I'll put the mustache on
Um, so many things I have to want to do
There's at least like another hour stuff that I want to do shit
dlc 2
Yeah, we'll do another one
Did someone do the dumb shit that I want to do we'll do a second dlc pack
All right, let's do the mcdlt
Yeah, I gotta be out of here
I want to make sure I clean up well, too. So I gotta get out of here soon
I'm running out of studio time
Rotate with the guns
All right. All right. Well, I don't know where the other gun is. So i'm gonna use a screwdriver
Hey, put it down man. Well, hey, hey, watch out
I don't want to fucking I don't want to shoot any of you easy easy easy easy
You know how good I am with this shit
Put down drop it. I do
You're making this real hard for me
both of you look
How do you guys seriously get you guys getting hungry? I'm getting hungry moving on this job for the last two or three days
And I am fucking tired. I am tired
Of hamburgers in this town that don't quite make it. I just wish just once
Just once that my cheese was soft and cold and my lettuce was cool and crisp all at the same time
You know
Well, I say you got it
I'm talking about the new
Dl. Uh, I forgot the wine. I'm talking about the new mcdlt
Hey
I'm talking quarter pound of beef on the hot hot side and the hot
Stays hot the new mcdlt. So hot
Crisp lettuce and tomato on the cuckoo side and the coop
States coop the new mcdl. I feel like this is oh my god
What you've been watching the last four hours has been
Especially with the harry potter show the lightsaber. That's somebody that's fan fiction. This is just the day. This is the fan fiction dlc
Like I feel like somebody wrote this and i'm acting out their dlc like their uh, their fan fiction
Like the mcdlt thing is my fan fiction. It's fucking freaking me out. All right
Dad at the dinner table
I have like all fucked up teeth and a robe and shit. I was gonna do a whole emperor palpatine thing
I'll be back. I'll be back sooner than you think
Okay, uh mustache
Plus i'm starting i'm starting to cramp up as you know
like in my chest
So that's that's kind of the time where I need to say. All right, I got I have to stop
I'm having too much fun
Wait, it's a fucking mustache
Beyond my brain right now
Where is it?
No, I have to find it found it. Let's get the briefcase, right?
it goes
It's the breller a stalin
Hello
My name is jernema russian jernema a little bit out of gas at this point
Nothing of oxygen going into brain
so
Can't come up with anything witty or creative
unfortunately
Needs more fruits and add vegetables and mix them together and and juice them
Okay, I go now
Bang that's not even it i'm not even doing it right god damn
This is the kid
This is the crazy frog kid. You can tell i'm tired
Okay
I'm gonna get I I will get back here
And we'll do more
There's still like another two or three hours of shit that I want to do
so the next
I don't know maybe
A couple weeks. Maybe i'll try to get back in here. I have no idea how i'm gonna feel tomorrow
because
I've done a lot of fucking move. I've moved around more than I have
in like
four or five months
I hopefully am not like a brick tomorrow
Sonic the hedgehog
I will say that me as dr. Eggman. I can't believe that's sonic
He's taking I need that power
Oh dastardly
That's all I see
Hey sonic
Sonic you want to come at me dr. Robotnik?
Oh, it's fast
Too fast some would say too fast
Some would say too fast
Oh, I see
But what's this?
It's electricity
It's in the trailer
He has this like a little blue lightning thing and he like it like shocks him
Just you watch the trailer
Hey penis
Do pickle rick
Hey, um, I um, I hey rick
Hey, hey morty
Oh, what is it?
Turn myself into a green screen
Oh, no
Yeah, morty you can be whatever you want in front of the green screen
I don't want to be you rick. Yeah morty get over there and be me. No, I don't want to morty
I said just something names wrong. All right. I'm out morty. We're gonna be on reddit morty
We're gonna be on reddit here on the green screen
All right, okay, I gotta say my goodbye I could be but that was a lot of fun. We're gonna be back. I'm gonna do more
Enjoy your was it four something hours of random shit?
Maybe you can use it. Maybe you can't
I look forward to seeing some of the very specific things in some of your videos soon
Here it comes. Goodbye. I'll see you later. I can't do the bits. I have to leave
I have to get the fuck out of here or i'm gonna get a lot of trouble and I have a relationship
With the people in this studio
So I don't want to be a dick. So i'm gonna i'm gonna get out of here
I have to go so tomorrow is supposed to be community content night
I we might see a delay
If I wake up tomorrow, I can't get out of bed because that's possible
We will see
I might be fucking dead
All right, good night guys, i'll see you later if I don't see you tomorrow and i'll see you in a couple days probably
I'll just check the sauce
Good night. Thanks for watching
We'll see you back here sometime soon the next few weeks
Good night