I'll put it on the screen so you don't miss anything. Where is it? Where is it? Okay, come on. Go go go go go go go go go go go
I can't miss this and then it's in bed. Did it work? All right. Just you watch that. I'll be right back
I gotta pee. Why is it doing this? Is it broken? Wrong stream? Which is it just Bethesda?
Oh my god, just give me this. All right. I'll be right back. Just just relax. I'll be right back.
Okay, I got something. I got something. Do it. Do it.
Bethesda seems they've done a good job at sometimes like pulling these surprises out, right?
Even fallout 76 I think was like kind of a surprise. What if we saw a Bethesda who has a
many awesome worlds? What if we saw Bethesda auto chess? Wow, that was really... I think
this is serious. We're apparently less than a minute so your final thoughts. We're just
naming games we enjoy and asking Bethesda. Can you make Pokemon snap Bethesda, please?
A shinder made by Bethesda. Wishing well. I want Rio to start just off. Wow, Bethesda.
I think we'll find Elder Scrolls online. What? Yeah, we'll see a little bit more about that.
They released earlier their lineup for this year. Even within three. Be together.
That is what we are about to be for the Bethesda E3 showcase right here E3 on Twitch. It is day
one 2019. We still have so much coming at you this entire week. We hope that you'll enjoy
this next press conference. We'll be back afterwards for the post-press conference
or we won't. You'll be with Drop Frames. You'll find out when that actually happens.
Don't forget we also got Devolver and the pre-free show. Ladies and gentlemen,
enjoy the next press conference of day number one. But don't forget we have just got started.
It is time now for Bethesda. There is no game without the players. Really, it all comes down
to you. There is no game. There's no one to play it. No one to interact with it.
Keep us in check. And we appreciate that. And through all of it, you're always there with us.
Damn it, man. I pissed all over the toilet. I had to clean it up. It was bad.
I fucking, it was out of control. It wouldn't stop.
I used to take a week off every time Bethesda game came out.
My name is Mark Diaz and when I was eight years old, I used to sneak over to my
buddy's house to play Doom. I'm Rich Lambert. Daggerfall was one of the very first games
that got me into the Elder Scrolls world. I'm Dana Christo and I started out as a
16-year-old gamer who just wanted to bring joy to others through video games.
And now I'm game director at Arkane Studios. Now I'm a game programmer anywhere.
Now I get to be a part of building that world as the creative director on Elder Scrolls Online.
Now I'm a UI programmer at Bethesda Game Studios and it's everything I could have dreamed of.
I see you. I see you. I see you. We see you because we are you. And together. Together.
Together. We are all. We are all.
It's our Andrew W.K. Party, party, party, it's time. Right?
This is not Awkward Teen.
That is our, yeah, that is like the Andrew W.K. Awkward Teen.
Too loud. I got you. I got you. I got you.
That was three games. Yes. Thank you. One of them nobody likes.
Here he comes. Oh.
Yeah. Thank you guys for being here. Thank everyone watching around the world
to tuning in to watch our fifth annual E3 showcase.
You're welcome. We're here for you. This is a night dedicated to those who love games,
who love the incredible entertainment that games provide.
This past year you fought demons on Mars and Nazis in America.
You were assassins in the Empire, adventurers in Tamriel, and survivors in the wasteland.
And you've embarked on these amazing adventures on PC, console, VR, mobile,
or wherever and however you choose to play. And that's the key. You take the worlds that
we create and you make them yours. You share your experiences with other players, with
friends and with family. With our games you've built large global communities that truly matter.
This year we want to give special recognition to the extraordinary Bethesda community.
As you showed, as you saw in our opening video, you mean everything to us.
I've almost been at this company for 20 years. And when I first started.
I do? Oh, I mean, I mean everything.
First started, one of my first responsibilities was moderating the community forums, chatting with
you and keeping you up to date on our games. It was a great way to start my career at Bethesda
because it was the perfect reminder of why we do what we do. And like so many others at
Bethesda, I've spent a lot of time with you at events around the world. Is that him?
I've enjoyed meeting so many of you. Is that him from like 20 years ago?
Oh, first, all right, never mind.
Taking time throughout the show,
let's do what I used to do in the Bethesda community.
We are thrilled tonight to show our fans the lineup of great games we've been creating
just for you, including the premiere of some exciting new games. And we'll go deep on Doom
Eternal. Stop cheering. They didn't see anything yet. So if you're ready, let's show you
like a screenshot of concrete. And he's still going to cheer.
One of the most celebrated development studios in the world, Bethesda Game Studios.
Please welcome studio head and my good friend, Todd Howard.
I don't know. I can't even look at him. I can't even look at the screen.
Is he there? Is he there yet? Tell me when he's there.
Thank you. Great to see everybody.
Hey, Todd.
We have had an incredibly exciting year at Bethesda Game Studios.
Given some of that excitement, impressed you're still here.
Actually, over the last year, we've had over 60 million players in our games.
And it's all of you.
It's all of you who have made these worlds what they are. Take Fallout 76.
All right. This is a good one.
A type of game we'd never done before. Had a lot of difficulties at launch.
Like this.
A lot of well-deserved criticism.
And you kept playing it. And through all of that, something amazing has happened.
It's thanks to all of you. This game has one of the best online communities we've ever seen.
It's me, my mom, my grandma.
And everybody's nice to each other.
They don't go on killing griefing sprees.
They leave food and water for the newbies and wave to each other.
I don't know about you.
Come on. Come on.
I paid good money for these seats.
We're in store this year for Fallout 76.
But first, our latest game, The Elder Scrolls Blades, is in early access.
And thanks to all of you, it became our second straight
number one mobile game after Fallout Shelter.
Absolutely incredible.
This is the only game I've ever played in my life.
I'm not kidding. This is a full, real statement.
Within 25 minutes, the iPad hit me almost in the face because I fell asleep.
I fell asleep playing the game.
I actually went to bed.
Like I passed out asleep and the iPad went like right on my bed.
I've never done that before.
It's really good sleeping.
And thanks again to all of you for making Blades number one.
I didn't even get past this tutorial.
Someone who's worked on The Elder Scrolls for 20 years.
It might be good. I don't know.
To bring this world to your friends in an all new way.
We still love those classic dungeon crawlers and it's clear you do as well.
And whether you're exploring a dungeon or rebuilding your town,
it's great to be able to do it wherever you are.
Since it's E3, we're releasing our biggest update yet.
Featuring all new jobs and solo arena battles.
Jobs? We're getting more jobs here.
And a brand new dragon quest line.
What we understand is the unemployment rate in The Elder Scrolls Blades
is by far the lowest it's ever been.
It has even more, but best of all, it's coming out tonight.
So download free tonight and give it a try.
And we're also hard at work on our arena mode for this fall.
We'll feature PvP, your own guilds, and visiting your friends' towns.
But most exciting this year, we're also bringing Blades to an all-new platform.
Switch Blades.
That's, who cares?
If you don't have a phone, you know what I mean?
If you were going to play this, you would have played it on your phone.
Everybody has a phone. What, you guys don't have phones?
Right? Is this the new Skyrim?
Are they going to release this like 12 times?
Blades is coming this fall to the Nintendo Switch.
And yes, it's still free.
Thank god.
If it was money, I would have been upset about that.
For the Switch, you can play on the go, on your TV, and with motion controls.
But best of all, it's cross-play and cross-progression with the mobile version.
So you can...
People are real fucking excited about this.
So you can start tonight on mobile and all your progress will carry over.
And it's viable here in our booth and Nintendos.
Yeah.
Between my iPhone and my Switch.
Oh, help. Somebody help.
We also have some special rewards for both our Apple and Google players this week.
They're paid actors.
And let us know what you think.
Thanks again.
Now, let me introduce Jeff and Tom to tell you what's coming to Fallout 76.
There are some really excited people here.
Hi, I'm project leader Jeff Garter.
And I'm co-studio director Tom Mustaine.
On behalf of everyone at Bethesda Game Studios,
we want to thank the millions of you who have played with us,
stuck with us, and helped shape the world of Fallout 76.
Absolutely.
It's incredible what the game has become.
You've told us how much you've loved this year's updates so far.
From camp building, legendary weapons, player vending,
and of course, the dreaded Sheep Squatch.
Sheep Squatch.
We've also been working on our biggest update yet.
It's called Wastelanders.
And it will fundamentally change the game.
All I remember is Rick and Morty played this.
That's it.
I don't know anything else about this.
76 opened its door.
This is like a Rick and Morty play this game.
We all discovered that Appalachia isn't quite what it used to be.
I'll get out of the way.
We encountered a lot of things.
Some people are interested.
Overcame a lot of things.
I don't think any of us expected for people to actually come back.
Are you from that vault?
Can you help us?
We've traveled pretty far.
I heard there's hope here in Appalachia.
Folk rebuilding.
I mean, nobody cares?
We'll fight too.
What, do you think this is like a giant astroturf?
Didn't you say there was like a million players?
We've been seen everything.
And the one thing we've learned is this.
You got to claim the wasteland before it claims you.
Question is, are you with us?
With them.
You guys think this pumped in crowd sounds?
No, no, it's not.
Human NPCs are coming to Fallout 76.
Heck yeah.
Not just NPCs, but a full quest line, new rewards, and as you saw, full dialogue trees.
This is a long-term story we're telling.
Year one was about the vault doors opening and all of you settling the wasteland.
Year two is about people coming back to reclaim it.
Like previous Fallout games, these characters have their own stories and goals.
It's up to you to choose how to interact with them and live with those consequences.
The Wastelanders update is coming this fall and will be free for all Fallout 76 players.
Fall?
That's kind of a ways away.
And in the spirit of free, we're doing something special just for E3.
Fallout 76 is going to have a free trial for everyone starting tomorrow.
It's free for a week.
And let me tell you what we're doing with Fallout 76.
It's going free for one week.
And it's growing community have become.
We can't wait to welcome all of you.
And because so many of you are going to be joining us,
we thought we'd also give you a sneak peek this week at an all-new game mode.
Check it out.
Your first test was making it to the vault.
Now, your real trial begins.
I wouldn't be surprised.
Here are vault 51.
Perhaps you will be the one nuclear winter.
We are in serious need of leadership.
So I have devised a unique process.
A battle to the death is the only sure way to judge the superior candidate.
This should prove interesting.
This is what we call in the industry, a pivot.
There could only be one overseer.
Good luck.
Fallout 76 pivoted to a PR game mode.
Just like Fortnite, it'll probably be the only thing that anyone plays.
We put a battle royale in Fallout 76.
How do they censor and stuff?
Nuclear winter is a battle royale born from the Fallout universe.
From power armor to perk cards.
From camp building to contending with wasteland creatures.
And of course, my personal favorite, nukes.
It's a great free addition to an already huge game.
We love playing it and we think you will too.
That guy wasn't excited.
That guy got burnt.
So he dropped the cigarette on his lap.
Remember all of Fallout 76, including nuclear winter,
is free to try this week.
Somebody took their bare feet, took their shoes off,
put their ice cold bare feet on that guy's back.
Jump in tomorrow.
We can't wait to see you.
Thanks again.
Fucking PR mode.
Everything we've talked about that's coming this year is free.
I like that jacket.
We get to represent hundreds of passionate developers across
four studio locations in North America working on multiple projects.
Yes, we're still hard at work on our next-gen RPG, Starfield.
And of course, Elder Scrolls 6.
We know how precious these game worlds are to all of you.
And they are to us.
We know the time you spend in them is important.
Keep telling us what you love, what you'd like to see us do better.
Thank you again, everybody, for your support.
But really, even more so, I want to thank everybody for believing in us.
Thank you.
Is that the end?
Please welcome the Foul Gameworks, Mr. Shinji Mikami.
I was going to say that's not very good.
What's Tango Gameworks?
What do they do?
I'd like to start by greeting my team in Tokyo.
Tango Gameworks.
What do they make?
It's Monday morning there, but they are watching.
Evil Within.
I am not a big fan of that game.
I am excited to announce the next game from Tango.
Ghostwire, Tokyo.
Ghostwire.
Hold on.
Wait, we got something.
This is new.
Hold your judgments here.
Hold on.
It is an action-adventure game in which you will fight paranormal enemies
and rid the city of supernatural evil.
I think you'll love it.
Okay.
That guy definitely has a camera pointed at him.
I'm going to upload it later.
Ghostwire, Tokyo.
Here is creative director at Tango.
Come on.
This ain't even Cox doing this.
This is just a bad feed.
All right.
Let's see.
I'm intrigued.
I'm very intrigued.
I'm very intrigued about this.
It's hard to do.
People are vanishing in Tokyo.
You must find out why.
Spooky.
You have to explore the world.
Face challenges to uncover the truth and save humanity.
In the game, you will meet spirits, some dangerous, some peaceful,
and survivors that each have their own stories.
You will need to ask yourself.
It is normal or paranormal.
This is Men in Black?
This is Men in Black.
The aliens are among us and you have to find out who's an alien or who's a ghost.
I just missed a really good joke.
We are very excited.
Let's take a look.
Thank you.
What happened?
Was it the rapture?
That was pretty cool.
Don't fear the unknown.
Attack it.
I'm interested.
That looks different.
Looks interesting.
No gameplay or anything.
I work as a mechanical engineer.
I work in a hospital.
I used to work with kids.
Interesting concept.
I'm an electrician.
I'm an event planner.
In real life, I'm a systems administrator.
Program assistant for a private school for children with autism.
I'm trying to be an artist.
I like to think of myself as one.
Make like back-end systems that it's really fun.
I'm a streamer.
Maybe permanently or temporarily.
I'm a full-time streamer.
I got a YouTube channel.
I make my own yarn.
I'm a social worker.
Teaching inmates.
I'm a game developer.
Working at a video game cafe.
I've been a Doom fan since the game came out.
I remember being in the eighth grade and a buddy of mine gave me the shareware demo
on three and a half inch floppy disks.
My older brother picked up Fallout 3 and I took his copy and played it when he wasn't home.
Fallout 4.
Oh, it was in Boston.
I like Boston.
The scope of that game was just like a lot bigger than things I was used to.
Just setting foot in Shimmering, the first city that you go to in Somerset,
it was amazing.
You would look out and you'd be like, oh, I want to go there.
And then you could go there, which was wild.
Go out into the world.
Just go in any direction that you want to go.
The exploration and the weirdness and the alienness of it.
I played Oblivion.
I tell you, it probably saved my life.
It was one of my first experiences with a fantasy world that was that immersive.
Love the dragons.
Gather the dragons.
When you take down a dragon, you can definitely take down any illness.
Don't ever stop adding dragons to your game.
Add dragons to Fallout.
Add dragons to Rage.
Add dragons to everything.
I'm a dragon.
Mecha dragons.
More dragons.
Stop doing that.
We want Doom.
You'll get it.
Doom's coming up in like 10 minutes.
Probably not even.
I just want to shout out to our friend Greg there,
the one in the video that really loves dragons.
I'm happy to say, Greg, The Elder Scrolls Online has dragons.
I don't mean any disrespect by this at all.
Right now, in fact, players are decent to the season of the dragon.
Our year-long story about greed, revenge, cat people, and of course, dragons.
Tonight's focus on the community resonates with me and everyone at Xenomax Online Studios
because ESO literally would not exist without you.
Watching you play the game, streaming, telling stories, hearing your feedback,
we understand that you are the most important part of the world of Tamriel.
It's fun, and it's fun, right?
Thank you.
Thank you for making ESO the extraordinary adventure it is today.
The past year has been a huge success for ESO.
More Game of the Year awards.
Millions more players have joined.
So many, in fact, that we recently had more server capacity just to support
all the new players in Tamriel.
I just want to make sure we say, can I just say this?
Can we please stop serving alcohol?
Before the show's getting bigger and better.
Come on.
Just a few days ago, we launched the Elder Scrolls Online Elsewhere,
the latest chapter in the game where you're able to visit, for the first time,
the homeland of the Khajiit, as well as control the dead as the new Necromancer class.
And if you haven't played it yet, Elsewhere is the perfect starting point for new players.
When we announced Season of the Dragon, we kicked it off by showing you a video
about how dragons were unleashed on Elsewhere and we ended with a cliffhanger.
I feel like that guy doesn't have a shirt on.
I'm really excited to show you what happens next.
I feel like that guy has like a football kind of logo painted on his chest
and he's got like a full paint on his face.
He's got like horns on.
He's just screaming in the crowd.
For a second, I just, I was like, what is going on?
It's just a cat.
I forgot this is Elder Scrolls.
Nice.
I don't know about the umbrella.
Thief.
Oh, magnificent Smaug.
Your impressive body is none other than I could ever see before.
Nice.
Dude, that was so awesome.
Why don't we take a look and see how that scenario would play out in the actual game.
That's right.
You may have recognized the return of Sai Sahan,
the legendary Redguard Swordmaster.
He's the legendary Redguard Swordmaster you met as part of the original five companions.
He's back as the leader of the Dragon Guard,
a group of dragon hunting warriors you've seen in other Elder Scrolls games.
He'll be featured in our fourth quarter story DLC named Dragonhold,
which will complete the season of the dragon.
We've got a lot more to share about the return of Sai and the Dragon Guard,
which will unveil at QuakeCon later this summer.
This guy's gonna call his mom later and be like,
Mom, mom, it's been wild.
Sorry, I got Larry tight.
I've been fucking screaming.
They did not introduce two new dragons.
They introduced a new cat.
I can't believe it.
All right, I'll talk to you later.
Love you, mom.
So much for your support of the Elder Scrolls online.
We're humbled by your enthusiasm.
Your enthusiasm for the game motivates us every day.
You guys are seriously awesome.
Thank you.
Dust is gonna start coming out of this guy's throat.
I'm concerned for this dude's health.
He's gonna be like coughing up the sand.
I have something else to talk about.
The Elder Scrolls online isn't the only game in development at ZeniMax online studios.
We have several other projects, one of which we're ready to reveal tonight.
And to tell us all about it is the game's creative director, Kira Schlitt.
New game.
All right, new game.
And now for something completely different.
Yarn Free.
Whatever it's called.
A classic Saturday morning cartoon in free-to-play mobile game form.
Let's take a look.
What?
Saturday morning mobile free...
TV?
Commander Keen.
This feels like a fake game trailer.
That's gonna be like another reveal.
This is a bait, I think.
Didn't it feel kind of like it was gonna bleed into something else?
That was gonna be like, I mean Commander Keen, whatever.
So there's a new branch on Commander Keen's family tree,
and they're heading to iOS and Android.
If you're hearing about Commander Keen for the first time,
it was one of the first PC action games created by id Software in the early 90s.
Yeah.
It starred boy genius Billy Blaze, whose alter ego Commander Keen protected Earth.
I thought it was like Mark Keen.
Want to give a really big thanks to our friends at id
for trusting us to deliver our modern take on this classic game.
So tonight, as we introduce Commander Keen to a new generation of players,
we're also introducing the next generation of heroes.
Meet Billy.
Billy Keen.
Billy and Billy Keen.
Two geniuses who follow in their famous father's footsteps.
Is that Fortnite dance?
The new commanders are of course funny and powerful,
but the game is also full of enemies, allies, and some really bad bad guys.
The twins build wacky gadgets from household items
to save the Earth from certain alien destruction.
Drag and drop gadgets to summon allies,
attack enemies, and move through the environment.
Choose from a caboodle of contraptions to conquer challenges,
and try saying that five times fast.
The tomes go on adventures and stories,
which tell some of the classic Commander Keen tales,
as well as a whole bunch of brand new ones.
In story mode, you'll overcome aliens,
collect power-ups, and explore Mars and beyond.
You can also go helmet to helmet with other players in battle mode.
A real-time head-to-head race through an alien landscape
where you need to control checkpoints
and claim the flag to gain ultimate victory.
Commander Keen will soft launch this summer on iOS and Android phones.
You don't know the worst part about this.
It's not the fact that everyone's like, oh bad Beth.
You guys realize that mobile games like that make more money
than like God of War did probably.
Unique in-game rewards and hot Commander Keen launch updates.
We really can't wait to kick some asteroid with you all.
That game is going to make more money
than the global fucking theater run of Avatar.
That's just the way it is.
That's just the way it is now.
We, like you, love mobile games.
In addition to Blades and the upcoming Commander Keen,
millions of you have enjoyed Fallout Shelter,
which has now reached over 150 million downloads and counting.
I told you, how many people saw Avatar?
How many people saw the movie Avatar?
For fans of collectible card games,
we brought the Elder Scrolls Legends to mobile
so you could experience the Elder Scrolls in a new way.
This year, the Legends community has continued to grow
and a lot of upgrades, new features, and new content.
It's a great experience for a night of gaming
or a quick match over a cup of coffee.
I gotta get out of here.
Oh no, it's taking over.
It's over, guys.
Mobile is the new, it's taking over.
Somebody said, no, what if we like,
it's not gonna work.
You can be upset about this, but you understand something.
You're just one person and a hundred grandmas
are gonna fucking download this.
You think you could win against a hundred grandmas?
I don't think you could.
They want like everybody to be playing this in homeroom.
But I told you, that's gonna be a fucking homework reminder.
Got reported?
It's the future, guys.
See, dragons.
It's the future.
If you enjoy other card games
but are looking for something that provides
a little deeper challenge,
you can download Legends for free on the App Store
and begin playing tonight.
Legends' next expansion, Moons of Elsewhere,
will be available on June 27th for PC, Mac, Mobile, and Tablet.
You can head over to BethesdaNet
to get a glimpse of the new cards and content
or play it this week in our booth.
There's two different mobiles now.
I'll see you there.
It's Mobile and Tablet.
Aren't they both mobile?
Breaking them up.
Speaking of new content,
three weeks ago we released Rage 2
and now Insanity rules for millions of players
around the world.
But we wanted to do more than just deliver
a critically acclaimed open world shooter.
We've already added community challenges
that reward you just for having fun in the wasteland
and we've got a lot more planned
with new features rolling out this week.
Porn?
The world of Rage 2 will become even more unpredictable.
I wish I was watching porn.
What did that say?
Puke explosions.
Don't say shit.
I'm not gonna play Andrew WK.
I got yelled at last year
for doing that too many times.
New cheats.
Surprise for you all.
No, I'm not gonna do that.
That's something blue.
That's fucking blue.
I'm not doing that.
Please welcome executive producer at Machine Games,
Jörg Gustafsson.
After liberating America from the Nazi scum
in Wolfenstein 2, the new Colossus.
Wolfenstein 3.
This year we take you back to Europe
with two new Wolfenstein games.
First, we are bringing Nazi killing
into virtual reality with Wolfenstein cyber pilot.
As a hacker working for the French resistance,
you will take control of Nazi war machines
and turn them against their creators.
Cyber pilot will be available this July
and it's playable this week in our e-free booth.
And if you haven't fought Nazis in VR,
you don't know what you are missing.
As I said, we have two new Wolfenstein games.
This summer, we are going to be launching
Wolfenstein Youngblood.
Wolfenstein, Wolfenstein, and then Wolfenstein,
another Wolfenstein.
With a gameplay experience that is bigger
than any previous Wolfenstein game,
you will have more weapons and weapon upgrades
than ever before, more ways to customize
your play style, and of course,
even more evil Nazis to kill.
What is it for?
It's not a tablet.
In Youngblood, you can kill those Nazis
with a friend.
You couldn't do that in Wolfenstein 2?
Was it on Singapore?
Yes, Wolfenstein is going co-op.
Youngblood is set in the 1980s,
two decades after the new Colossus.
BJ Blazkowicz is missing in Nazi-occupied Paris
and it's up to his twin daughters,
Jess and Soph, to track him down.
In Youngblood, you can still play by yourself
or you can partner with a pal
to double up on shooting, stabbing,
and killing Nazis.
Check it out.
Nazi country.
That's where Papa is,
so that's where we're going.
We can find him together.
I may have an assignment suitable
for two Nazi killers.
Do we get to kill Nazis in this one?
Somebody said, uh, I think, probably.
I think so.
Wolfenstein Youngblood releases on PlayStation 4,
Xbox One, Nintendo Switch,
and PC on July 26th.
I mean, that comes out like now,
in like less than a month and a half.
And if you can't wait,
stop by our E3 booth to play this week.
Thank you.
And now I'd like to welcome to the stage
my dear friends from Arcane Lyon
who worked with us on these two Wolfenstein games,
Dinga and Sébastien.
Did I mute myself?
No, I didn't mute myself.
We love you too.
Hi, I'm Dinga Bakaba,
and game director at Arcane Lyon.
Is this for Wolfenstein or is this a new game?
In the same studio.
So along with partnering with our good friends
at Machine Games on Wolfenstein,
we've been working on other projects at Arcane Lyon.
And tonight we're excited to announce
our latest first-person action game.
It's something innovative,
stylish,
and different from anything we've done before.
Innovative, stylish, and different.
Let me begin by saying
bienvenue to the frozen island of Black Reef.
This is a place of mystery
where our looks can kill.
The game takes place during what we say in French
is the période de folie,
a time of madness.
And now that we've given you
a small taste of the world,
let us introduce you to our two deadly rivals,
Colt and Juliana.
Is it just concept art?
It's not, is it just, no, okay.
Yeah.
This place is in a paradise.
It's a prison.
Out here.
Out here?
We're trapped.
We're free.
In this endless, eternal cycle.
Your life's purpose is on this island.
I can't let this go on any longer.
Days I repeat.
The longer that I'm out here.
The more certain I am.
1v1?
To protect the cycle.
The only way to break the cycle
is to kill you.
It's gonna be like a 1v1 action adventure game?
Multiplayer?
Is on my side.
Deathloop.
All right, let's get some deets on this one.
Let's get the details.
I want details on this one.
Deathloop combines a mind-bending story
with meticulously designed levels,
and of course, arcane signature gameplay
that lets you approach every situation
any way you like.
Because in the endless clash
between these two extraordinary assassins,
how you play is up to you.
Plus, I think it's really fucking cool.
I mean, yeah.
What is it?
Yeah, maybe, maybe you should have said
that in French actually.
Maybe, maybe not.
But, but it's also pretty fucking true.
Are we allowed to swear on in person
but not like on the trailer?
And we really hope that you enjoy it.
They're really emphasizing like the F word here.
They're like, oh fuck!
But their trailer has like, I don't understand.
It's a wonderful way to get away
from all the pressures in life.
I think the sense of community
has really helped me as a person
because I'm typically very isolated.
It's definitely very confidence building.
It's brought me out of my shell
and stopped being an introvert.
I could like be a hero and do all these things.
You find really creative, really fun,
really talented people.
Meet people who are in my group
that I've only known as a character.
Probably made more friends online than I have.
The games that you bring out
just helps people honestly.
My parents were refugees from the Vietnam War,
which is why I'm also fascinated
by elements of war.
Playing these games just kind of put me out of
the worry and the stress.
I was in a dark place for a while
and I told myself I wasn't going
to be there anymore.
And so now the only dark places
that I'm allowed to go are in dungeons and ESO.
Just being someone who is LGBT,
it's nice to be able to sit down
and play these games
and feel accepted for who I am.
It's really nice to see that their storyline
has some sort of emotional effect on me as a player.
And I just really admire the creativity
that goes into the process
of making these big worlds
with these amazing stories.
Good shit.
This is old, John.
This is like old milk.
Building these fantastic worlds
and telling these stories
comes from a passion to deliver
the very best experiences for our players.
Hi, I'm James Altman,
director of publishing at Bethesda.
What do you got for us?
Robert Duffy.
Starlight, whatever it's called.
Starfleet.
What's the name of that game?
Stargazer.
What's the one everyone wants to see?
Starfield.
We have some exciting new technology
to show you that can dramatically
improve gaming for millions.
So for the past two decades,
we've approached game development
not by looking at what is possible today
but with a vision of what can be possible tomorrow.
And at Bethesda,
we're proud of our legacy of innovation
where again and again
we've changed the industry.
We were the first to use physics-based engines
for sports games.
We were groundbreakers with
go anywhere, do anything,
open world RPGs.
We are the inventors of the first person shooter
which is now the world's most popular form of gaming.
We are pioneers in downloadable content
and the first to bring mods to consoles.
And actually, since we first brought mods
to consoles in 2016,
there have been one billion
mod downloads for Fallout and Skyrim.
We of course developed the first
commercially viable VR technology
revealed in our E3 booth in 2012.
Yes, that is the original VR headset
held together by tape
and worn by our very own Tim Willits.
They're taking a lot of credit.
We also invented corn, maze.
And of course, we are well known
as developers of best in class.
I invented the hamburger too.
Innovation and creativity is in our game.
Weirdly enough, we also invented
the dentist drill.
To improve player experiences.
So tonight, we have exciting
new technology to announce.
We're going to show you the result
of years of research and development.
Cutting edge game engine based technology
we've developed specifically for game streaming.
Now we'd like to introduce you to Orion.
Streaming? Streamers?
I heard streamer.
I'm a streamer.
I'm not going to like this.
Maybe I'll like this.
Orion is a tremendous breakthrough
in streaming technology.
It is our name for a group
of patented technologies
that optimize game engines
for performance in a cloud environment.
Orion can work with any game engine
and will improve player experiences
no matter which game you're playing
or whether you're streaming
on Stadia, on Xcloud
or another streaming platform.
So how does Orion work?
The exciting game streaming services
you've been hearing so much about
have largely focused on hardware solutions
to address the complex challenges of streaming.
That's a lot of words.
We used our expertise
in developing game engine software
and took a different approach.
By incorporating Orion technology
at the game engine level
we're able to stream game content
up to 20% faster per frame
leading to a dramatic reduction in latency.
In addition, an Orion-enabled game
can stream with up to 40% lower bandwidth.
And happily for game developers
Orion technology is easy to integrate
with your game build with RSDK.
But what does that mean for you?
It means that streaming games
will be faster and better with Orion
and Orion substantially reduces
the cost of streaming
for players and for publishers.
So it won't matter
if your friends and family
are sucking up all the bandwidth
or if you live far away from a data center.
With Orion,
you'll still be able to stream your game
at max settings.
But that's real.
I mean max settings.
It's a big deal if it works.
Now as with any new computer technology
one must ask the question
can it play Doom?
He said the word.
Question, can it stream
an unrelenting first person shooter
with native 4K resolution
at 60 frames per second?
Let's see.
Oh, it's really doing.
I want to see this.
So I wish I could see doing right now.
I can't wait.
I'd like to introduce Shale Williams
tech specialist from id Software.
Oh, here it comes guys.
This is it.
It's coming right now.
So Shale is streaming
an Orion enabled Doom 2016
right now to that mobile device.
Holy shit, he's actually doing it.
There is no reduction in visual fidelity.
This is the greatest thing
I've ever seen in my life.
At 60 frames per second
without perceptible latency.
And we want you all to
experience the power of streaming technology
yourself as we test and refine it.
So for a chance to be among
the first in the world
to stream Doom 2016 for free
all you need to do is join
the Doom Slayers Club
by registering at slayersclub.com tonight.
Holy shit.
Are you kidding me?
This is fucking the greatest thing
I've ever seen in my entire life.
What the fuck, dude?
I'm okay.
Everybody could use a little more
Doom in their lives.
We'll see you in hell.
What you interfere with now
is bigger than you can imagine.
Continue this wrath.
It is written.
It is their time to give penance.
You are but one man.
They are no longer your people to save.
Holy shit.
I'm gonna need some help.
I'm gonna need help.
I can't.
I fucking clogged so much.
I don't.
I shrunk down into my fucking clothes.
I can't get out of here.
This is awesome.
Thank you so, so much.
I'm Marty Stratton,
the executive producer of Doom Eternal.
And I'm Hugo Martin,
the game's creative director.
As you just saw,
we're not just building a world for Doom.
It's an entire universe.
Earth is on the brink of annihilation.
It's being consumed by demons.
And your crusade to save it
will take you across dimensions
to locations never seen before in Doom,
from heaven and hell
to the sentinel home world and beyond.
Yeah.
There is so much to see and discover.
But Doom is first and foremost about gameplay.
And Doom Eternal promises to be
the ultimate power fantasy.
The fun comes from mastering the experience
because you are the Doom Slayer,
the strongest, fastest demon killer in existence.
And nothing can stand in your way.
Absolutely.
Of course, the challenge in Doom
is all about handcrafted combat,
but also engaging level design.
And in Doom Eternal,
the game always has something
new to throw at you,
even deep into the campaign.
Let's take a look.
This is gonna be good.
Doom's combat was a ton of fun.
The chat's way behind.
There's like a two minute delay on the screen.
That's just for stream snipers.
What the fuck was that?
Was it a brain?
Thanks.
You know, it's so important to us at id Software
that every aspect of the gameplay
has real meaning to you, the player.
Every enemy is different.
Every weapon has a purpose
and every decision you make really counts.
The only path to victory in Doom Eternal
is to aggressively control the fight
with amazing agility, powerful guns,
and critical resources.
That's right.
I'll tell you, we absolutely can't wait
for you to play it.
And some of you won't have to wait too long.
If you are lucky enough to be in the room tonight.
In the room tonight.
Not like Open Dead E3.
You'll have a chance to play it
immediately following the show.
What the hell?
Why am I not there?
I want to be there.
And for those not here.
Look under your seat.
I got one.
Playable in the Bethesda booth all week.
But enough talk.
Let's see how it all comes together.
And watch as this perfect killing machine
goes to work.
So what are we looking for here?
Guys, guys.
Hey, what are we looking for?
Is Doom Eternal the only game
that has shown this much gameplay?
I feel like we haven't seen very much gameplay
this whole conference.
Or is this game player or is this not?
There we go.
I mean, it's definitely,
it's going to be scripted gameplay,
but we'll see.
It looks great.
Missed chest.
Guys, I'm not playing the game right now.
I'm not doing this.
This guy sucks.
This streamer sucks.
You guys are vicious.
Looks fun.
It does.
Turn up your FOV.
No, I don't play with higher FOV.
Here's me an advantage over other players.
Yeah, this is a lot of gameplay.
It's pretty foreign in the world of E3.
Louder, louder, louder.
Lava.
Don't just want to put that lava
on your ice cream.
Like let it cool down for a little bit
and then drip it on your ice cream.
I feel like lava is a spicy orange flavor.
Like a spicy,
like clementine flavor.
Thanks.
Thanks, guys.
That was awesome.
Did the scream guy get up?
Maybe he got up and started screaming.
Because the gameplay that you just saw
is just a piece of what you're going
to play this week at E3.
But I bet a lot of you are wondering
when do we get to play Doom Eternal
at our home?
Well, you don't have to wait too much longer.
Not quite tomorrow.
September.
But Doom Eternal will release
September 4th.
On November 22nd.
That was close.
It's already been,
it's been out for two months.
How did you miss it in the Steam store?
An amazing collector's edition.
We're really proud of.
Yeah.
That's an actual helmet.
Yeah, you could wear it.
You could wear that thing.
He's already got one on.
Lucky.
This guy's already got it.
That's right.
Already a badass.
He's already got one on.
All right.
Well, we've got one more thing.
We know that you've been waiting to hear about.
He's like, actually, no.
I'm a fucking astronaut dickhead.
I just got off the moon.
We've been developing this in-house, it did.
And it's unlike anything you've played before.
Yeah.
We've been so pumped to share this with you.
This is pure doom, but with your friends.
Where two player-controlled demons take on one
fully-loaded slayer in a fight to the death.
2v1?
This is a first-person fighter.
Where it's demon strategy versus slayer skill.
You know, we can't wait.
2v1?
Because we know you'll love the different play styles
of the various demons.
Because each has unique movement, attacks, and abilities.
They can even spawn AI-
This is reverse evolve.
To control the battlefield and help you take down the slayer.
It's strategic, competitive, and it's a ton of fun.
And we can't wait to share more details with you
this year at QuakeCon.
Oh, it's in already?
There's a lot more to share at QuakeCon.
But before we go, we do want to take a first look
at Doom Eternal's new multiplayer.
Oh, we are going to see it.
On behalf of our amazing team at Id in Dallas
and Frankfurt, Germany, we want to thank you
all so much for your support.
Thanks, everyone.
2v1.
Demons versus one decked out player.
Fight.
Demon health critical.
Yes, Jerma.
2v1.
Yes.
Slayer killed.
True.
Oh, is this-
Is this 2v1?
2v1, I guess.
Fight.
No, I mean, it's-
It looks alright.
It's kind of just-
It'll be fun, by the way.
And now introducing Goldust.
And for everyone at our studios around the globe
that have worked so hard in the great games
you've seen tonight, we say thank you.
2019 marks 25 years of Doom.
So, to celebrate, we will be going all out
with Doom at QuakeCon this summer.
No, I'll just go with 6 and no Starfield.
Panels and activities dedicated to Doom,
which we call DoomCon.
DoomCon.
See what we did there?
We took out the Quake and put Doom.
We hope you can come hang out with us in Dallas
at our inaugural event in London.
If you can't, please tune in online.
Until then, go to Bethesda.net for more info
on all the games you saw tonight.
If you're here at E3 this week,
we'll have hands-on with many of our games,
so be sure to stop by our booth.
In the meantime, thanks for playing,
thanks for watching,
and thanks to all of you for being part of the-
No, they'll do like an Elder Scrolls 6 teaser, right?
I mean, they did one last-
They did one last year, of course they are.
They did one last year.
They teased it last year and it's not ready to show at all.
At Bethesda, we're in the business of creating heroes.
But the true hero is you.
They already confirmed no-
It's like we hand you this malleable clay
and you do these extraordinary things
that we never could have imagined.
We get to build these worlds and these communities,
and you all come in and you play
and you bring these worlds that we create to life.
Need more PR.
You help us build richer worlds.
You add meaning to everything we do.
We are glad you're here.
We're so glad you're here.
To the heroes.
Shit, I don't have a drink.
To you.
Well, there it is.
Bethesda Conference. Done.
Got a lot of mobile games.
Got a lot of-
We got to see a lot of Doom Eternal, though.
You got to see a lot of Doom.
Got to see it.
2v1.
Looks like it's 2v1 in that mode.
I'm not sure it could be.
And that's it.
That's it.
That was me singing, by the way.
It was?
Am I going to pretend to be a streamer?
All right.
Well, that's what Bethesda had to offer there at E3.
They mentioned Fallout 76.
Hell, they gave it an expansion.
And then they announced-
Did they close my stream?
Did they turn me off?
You guys just saw the Bethesda Conference.
We don't want you doing this shit!
So prepare thyselves.
Co-walk us through the Fallout 76 stuff.
If I could play back the VOD and just highlight your face
the entire time, it would maybe tell the story-
Highlight my face.
Let's hear you put it into words.
I already pretended I was on the panel like three times.
You want me to do this joke again?
It was a funny joke.
That was the punchline.
Actually, and it turns out at some point
we slipped into the worst timeline.
I don't know exactly when that happened,
but we just kind of slipped streamed on in there.
It was pretty impressive.
As far as I know, there's still some major, major bugs
with Fallout 76 and that whole thing about-
which is one of the reasons when Tom was like,
yeah, we have such a great community.
That's because your PVP mechanics are broken.
That's why they aren't killing each other.
It's because that system is fundamentally flawed
and people don't use it.
You want to, but you can't.
Yeah, so it's a little interesting.
I don't know.
Here's the thing.
I knew there was going to be blade stuff.
I knew there was going to be ESO 26.
This is the kind of thing I had to do.
Sorry.
These are all things that are going to happen.
Right.
But I will say the Commander Keen stuff.
That was-
Yeah.
That kind of hit me on a spiritual level.
I grew up with Commander Keen and it was the kind of thing where-
I'm just going to go ahead and pretty much make the same joke.
It's the kind of thing where-
I do that every day.
I had to watch Command and Conquer, go mobile,
and then die this public execution-style death
where everyone just gave up on it.
And now we have to do that with Commander Keen.
And it's just like, oh man.
It sucks.
It's unfortunate.
It's like us old people have to watch our favorite franchises become our worst enemy.
Mortal Kombat says hello.
It's just unfortunate.
Should we just go into the conference talk at this point?
Zeke, me and you are out on Fallout 76.
We played it for a day and then we're good there.
Nobody who played it.
Spent some time with the game.
And you also are-
Follow me.
I'm sorry.
Is the BR at all interesting?
Is that-
No.
What's your guys' favorite fast food?
Movement in everything of the Fallout games has never been my draw to it.
So why would I want a game that relies on movement and shooting
when those are the things that are not good about the game?
That's Fallout 76.
Wendy's is probably the best, I think.
They're also still having pretty major server stability issues.
Yeah.
Another thing they are, you're right.
Small groups of players on spread out servers
and they're wanting to do 52 player games now?
Somebody in my chat just said it's fucking hilarious.
It's just the game isn't-
Somebody in my chat just said-
Hold on, hold on.
Listen.
The story in my chat just said that Burger King was the best.
No, I'm sorry.
I'm sorry.
I don't mean to interrupt you.
It's in a different dimension.
The Burger King really-
I don't know, man.
The death is what happened and then the-
That's unbelievable.
I can't even-
Slowly rolling down the hill without any-
I'm sorry.
I really don't mean to fuck this whole thing up.
My favorite thing, I think-
...about the Fallout 76 portion is the crowd member that when they said
that the server capacity was being raised just lost his shit.
He just really was all about the server capacity.
What was going on with the fucking crowd?
The whole conference-
That guy's screaming!
...up until PSO was done-
That guy's fucking screaming!
...was really into that shit.
Right?
Maybe a little bit too much.
You get it.
There was employees up front.
Do we have a direct source that was saying it?
Well, they were all wearing Bethesda shirts so I think that was the-
I went to a conference like two years ago and they had our seats in the very front.
So I'm assuming that that was what they did before.
Right.
But I'm not positive.
There are still-
I gotta go?
Thanks for inviting me.
Even 76 has-
I gotta get out of here.
They weren't kidding when they said that 76 has an active player base.
I know people that are still-
They put all the stuff to the side and they're still enjoying those games.
And ESO is bigger than it's ever been.
So, I mean, there's, you know, there's, there's-
If you can drink the Kool-Aid, if you like that kind of stuff, then, you know-
Kool-Aid's not-
They're there.
They're around.
Yeah.
I'm sorry, guys.
I gotta go.
I have to get out of here.
I'm supposed to be for like two hours but-
I gotta go to Burger King because people think it's a joke that I like it.
Like, how much do you love Fallout 76?
Or, excuse me, how much do you love Bethesda?
And they gave out t-shirts and said, we'll give you a front row ticket.
Should I just go?
Make sure to be really enthusiastic.
Sure.
Yeah.
I thought, my name's Jerma985.
Please.
You'd think they would know, like, maybe tone it down after a little bit.
Well, we got, we gotta be careful.
Let's not yuck their yum, you know?
Yeah, celebrate it.
They're enjoying it and having their fun.
If I could get a shout out-
We'll have our negative opinions and they can keep having fun.
Jerma985 is my name.
Exactly.
The other favorite thing, I think Zeke caught this.
I don't know if Anne or Co did, but Zeke lost a shit when they said it.
In the Wastelanders trailer that they showed, the voice-acted line was,
we didn't expect anyone to come back.
That was-
I'll see what-
That's pretty on the nose.
You'll just get somebody else.
That was so, so delicious to hear that.
Just like, we didn't expect anyone to come back.
I was like, really?
Yeah.
The next line was, I can't believe you idiots are still giving us your money.
But we were all laughing, so we went over.
Exactly. That's right.
Co, the other stuff, and you brought this up as we were watching it.
The human NPCs, full quest line, and dialogue trees.
Didn't they say that stuff was never going to be in Fallout 76?
They specifically marketed the product to not include that.
It's just kind of hilarious because when the beta came out,
everyone and their mother was like,
this game could totally have NPCs.
You should put NPCs in here.
And they were like, no, no, no.
That's our decision.
We are here deciding not to do this.
This is going to be awesome.
And then a year later, they're like,
okay, guys, we're putting the NPCs in.
Okay.
They're going to have quest lines and dialogue trees.
We're putting them back.
It's cool.
It's just kind of funny because it's like, dude,
that's what they were screaming at you from before the game was out.
Now, maybe if they start listening to all that stuff,
hey, maybe Fallout 76 can get good.
Maybe it's a step in the right direction.
Nothing's not saveable, given enough work and time.
Yeah, we'll see.
We'll see.
We will indeed see.
Right after that, I think the show's starting to
get some life into it, I would say,
with Ghostwire Tokyo, which is from The Evil Within Devs.
This thing looks pretty good.
It's an action adventure game.
We didn't see any gameplay at all,
but the trailer was sick.
That was a really good trailer or teaser
or whatever the fuck you want to call it.
But also, you know, we'll see the gameplay,
but yeah.
Think about Evil Within.
These are the same devs.
They did a great job of translating their CGI stuff,
which they initially just showed,
into an actual pretty well-made game.
I had a great time with Evil Within.
Yeah.
And not only that, but it looks like,
and yeah, I've known at every point of my life.
I like Evil Within one day.
I didn't.
I really didn't.
But with this new thing, apparently something I didn't pick up on
is the guy that introduced the woman
introduced she is like his protege.
Yeah.
So it's kind of like we just we just kind of
this passing of the torch, which is kind of awesome.
And she was great, by the way.
Oh my gosh.
She was adorable.
She was great.
That was awesome.
I think this is a sequel.
The aesthetic was awesome.
A lot of stylized elements.
A lot of really interesting imagery.
If the gameplay is good, this could be this could be big.
Yeah, I thought about Zeke thought.
Yeah, well, I like like it's just a scene like that.
Like, look at that.
There's I thought those are going to turn into worms, by the way.
Sorry.
Interrupt.
Yeah, yeah.
Hey, no, hey, no, what are you doing?
No, I want to be part of it, too.
The look of it in the intrigue, the like, you know,
not knowing what's going on, but how cool it like it's compelling.
And I really make intrigue to see how this.
By the way, let me just say all those people there,
they're really fun, nice people.
Just don't ban me from Twitch.
I didn't do anything.
Devolver is happening right now.
I mean, you can hear me.
You can hear me or not?
No, no, no, no, no, no Devolver.
I want to watch Devolver like downstairs with like a bowl of spaghetti.
I just want to eat a bowl of spaghetti downstairs and watch.
Devolver is only like an hour or like 45 minutes, right?
Less than 45 minutes.
I'm way too loud.
No, I'm not.
I'm fine.
I'm not going to eat a bowl.
No, I'm not going to.
I'll see you tomorrow.
I'll see you tomorrow for what's the first.
What's tomorrow?
Let's take a look.
Tomorrow is Ubisoft Square.
We'll catch those months.
Go make duck broth.
We're going to play Cooking Sim tomorrow
because I have to kill like an hour or two again in the middle.
When is the PC gaming show as well?
That's at like 10 o'clock in the morning, isn't it?
If I...
Okay, is that 10 a.m. Eastern?
10, 9, 8...
I got to get up at 7 o'clock in the morning?
Please don't leave me.
You might see me for the PC one too.
Don't go.
Skip it.
Yeah, we'll see.
I got to get some food to me.
I will see you guys tomorrow.
That's the end.
It's been six and a half hours.
Holy shit.
Watch Devolver all the across.
Oh, let me mute this before everyone hates me.
Yeah, I'll be live for at least Ubisoft and Square.
We'll play something in the middle.
If I get up early enough, maybe the PC conference.
But I don't think I'm going to get up at like 7 o'clock in the morning.
Was there on my mic?
Is my mic fucked up?
But interesting stuff.
I'm really looking forward to Phantasy Star Online 2.
That looks pretty great.
That's because I'm peeking.
Something's not right.
Devolver doesn't need content.
But that's what I mean.
Devolver is like its own complete edited video package.
And me just kind of in the corner.
I don't think I don't really want to do that.
For the other ones, it's like live and people are talking.
Devolver usually does like a full just edited video, right?
I don't know if I want to just sit there and...
I can't really add anything to that, I don't think.
I felt the same way about Nintendo too.
We'll see.
But we're going to do the bits real quick.
Thanks everybody for watching.
I hope you had a fun time.
I hope you got to see some things you liked.
I'll see you tomorrow for more of the conferences.
If you catch it, you catch it.
If not, then maybe we'll see you again soon.
Thanks a lot everybody.
See you tomorrow.
And for those of you that are sticking around,
for a few minutes while we go over the bits and the subs,
we had 250 from Deja.
Thank you Deja for the 250.
Lego Forza sounds like a PS2 cheat code and not a $10 expansion.
People are probably going to love it though.
Tingy, thanks for the 250.
Lego for next Germa Rumble.
Like just a physical Lego?
I don't think I can even make that.
Thank you Turbo Pasta for the $3.
Master of Comedy has competition.
Thanks for the last.
And they link a Twitter.
Somebody made a Germa the Giant Twitter.
You guys are fast.
That's not an officially endorsed Twitter account by the way.
Thank you though.
Thank you Demonic Cucumber for the $3.
It didn't mean much to you,
but the Lego Speed Champions left me hyped.
The map had an Easter egg to this failed Lego theme.
Plus the Lego Star Wars announcement left me sobbing with joy.
Anyways, for the everything is Lego joke,
I have to agree as we got Lego Stranger Things
and Lego Minions announced within a month of each other.
It just does really well.
The Lego is just completely timeless forever.
A timeless, timeless classic thing that will never go away.
It's as old as dirt, but thank you.
Thank you also to Mini Clips for the $10.
I heard Todd Howard adopted two kids and named one Todd
and the other Howard.
I'm not sure that's real,
but thank you for the $10.
Appreciate it.
Hey Zalaski, thanks for the 250.
ISE3 2019, where we celebrate 24 years of gamers pretending
at a trade show for investors and retailers,
a convention for them and flipping out
when it doesn't live up to their expectations.
Kind of increase those stock prices.
Thank you.
I'll store H2O for the $5.
The Microsoft conference felt like they were a bigger pitch
to PC gaming, like they're keeping their options open
for an exit from the console market.
Do you think that the big hardware makers
focusing on high specs in exchange for price accessibility
is the better option for the next generation of gaming?
All-in-one entertainment consoles like the Xbox One
seem to have failed.
But I worry that in going in other directions
might make any console that's not the switch inaccessible.
I think a lot of the hardware makers
are almost really, really desperate to have
CD lists and subscription-based content
that's starting to really...
They can cut back on so many costs.
All these people...
They don't have to make product anymore,
like actual on-the-shelf product anymore,
if that ever gets to a point.
Think about how much Xbox desperately would save
and all these other publishers will save
if there's no more physical boxes anymore.
And that's not really a good thing
because we've seen so many times,
oh, yeah, it's just a stream.
It's a service.
It's, you know, download the game.
You don't own it.
We do, but it's our server.
But you get the little key to it.
That could be bad.
But that's the direction a lot of them want to go, I think,
because they can save so much money
on manufacturing costs.
Somebody mentioned the death of music and CDs.
Look at Spotify.
Spotify is what you do for music.
90% of the people in this chat right now
probably just have Spotify.
And maybe you still have CDs,
but subscription models or what?
It's kind of the future, I guess.
Interesting to see what happens.
There are pros and cons for both of them.
But thank you.
Hey, Zellgrote, thanks for the $5.
I was watching your Super Fight stream
and would love to see you in Star
and it's Alex played again.
By the way, Todd is in your cupboard.
He got to Las Vegas real quick.
He must have taken like a bullet train.
But that's the game where you
you have to argue your way
over somebody else with like a monster
or a power or something, right?
They probably updated it a lot.
Might be worth doing.
But thank you.
Thank you, FlyingPixels, $30 earlier.
30 bucks from FlyingPixels.
You made me laugh so hard that I cried.
That hasn't happened in a while.
Thanks for the laughs.
Thanks for the 30 fucking dollars
and for hanging out
and choosing my stream to take E3 in with.
So thank you.
Really appreciate it.
Freudian Weapon, thanks for 250.
No message, just 250.
Thank you.
Jerma lied and didn't draw sticks.
Thanks for the 250.
You're a dragon.
You said scalies were not people.
You aren't a person.
What?
No, I said I said a dragon.
I said a dragon is not a human.
Because they're not.
They're a lizard.
A layer like a lizard.
A dragon is not a person.
They're a they're a dragon.
How is that incorrect?
Spliceable Spleen gave five community subs earlier.
Thanks for the five subs.
Dropped him about 10 minutes ago.
Thank you.
Thank you so much for the five community subs.
And then finally here we had let's get the
let's get the credits on here while we have a second.
Join us tomorrow where we do it all again.
We check out some of the other conferences.
Enjoy the rest of tonight's E3.
There's Devolver going on like in 20-30 minutes.
And then probably some after show stuff if you, you know,
go check it out.
There's a lot of great streamers doing this.
There's a lot of good content.
A lot of good live stuff going on I think after too.
So check it out.
Let's roll the credits right now.
Here they come.
Oh my god.
With this many subs?
Holy shit.
That's a lot of fucking people.
I didn't know that this many people sub tonight.
Wow.
That's a lot.
Thank you to everybody that continues to subscribe to this stream.
You had close to 8k viewers so yeah.
And that's I thanks for watching that.
Hopefully you thought it was fun.
Feed your guild members will do right when I before I close it out.
But thank you to PeacefulHaley for the 250.
Thank you PeacefulHaley.
Hey Jeremy, how are you?
I'm doing pretty damn good.
I haven't been here in a while but this year's Bethesda conference is probably the worst.
Just completely dull.
But at the same time I don't like shitting on the people who make these games.
Because they work hard and are excited about it and I hate seeing people shit on them.
Even though I can agree yeah this is pretty boring and meh.
Hope Nintendo will save the day.
Anyways enjoy your night.
Yeah I mean it's look there are some great things that were shown today.
We fell for the bot again.
What bot?
What did I do?
Jeremy has read more bot messages?
What bot?
I have no idea what you guys are talking about.
My chat just crashed.
What the hell is going on?
My browser just crashed.
Oh anyways um I mean there's a lot of things that aren't for me.
But there's a few things that I would say that looks pretty great.
The problem with game conferences like this.
A lot of it is just let's all like pretend in a room for an hour.
You know what I mean?
Hey let's just like get a bunch of people together and let's like just
game some excitement for stuff that may not be as exciting as it looks.
But that's just the nature of the business.
That's just the way it is.
Look people have talked shit about like the fake goofy E3 presentations
and game releases and game showings for years.
And they're not really changing.
They kind of still follow the same formula every time.
Yeah it's just a giant sales pitch.
It's a giant pre-sales pitch.
But obviously Microsoft announced a new console which that's not just like hey
buy uh wash dogs 4.
I mean that's a new console.
But it is what it is.
I still enjoy them.
They're still fun to watch.
They're still interesting because they're just like announcements
and sometimes they're exciting things like the George R.R. Martin
and From Software collaboration.
How could you not be excited about something like that?
That's a big that's a huge deal.
That'll be a lot of fun.
Hopefully.
But thank you to Peaceful Haley for that little tidbit.
Fajita Meat thanks for the five dollars.
Seems good.
Had a great time watching you watch E3.
Quick question.
What's with all the angry faces on your video thumbnails in the German stream archive?
Wait what?
What do you mean angry faces?
Well there's there's there's only like one angry there's only one angry
there's no angry face.
Where?
I don't see any angry faces.
I see a little a couple of awkward weirdo ones.
I don't see angry face.
Well I I don't I don't control this channel.
The logos?
Like the the J?
I don't know.
But thank you for the five dollars.
And finally thank you C4G for the 250 final plus two score was 1876.
I don't know if the bot posted or not when it was called.
Not bad.
That's an 1800 plus positive.
But uh see you tomorrow.
Thanks for watching.
Go enjoy the rest of the last conference that's going on.
See you all soon.
Take care.
And here's uh I'm gonna feed the guild.
Good night guys.