The music stopped because I'm opening another game, as you know, as you are aware.
I'm gonna mute this one more time. Give me one sec. Okay, I need to change this. I gotta change the
game as well. Move you over. That looks better. That's better, right?
That looks good. So from last time, I was about to lose. Very, very, very awfully. My partner was
doing terrible. But let's see if I can do anything here. Here's my magic three. The yellow bar.
I'll get rid of the yellow bar. Ready? Check this out. Gone. Not even there. All right.
Updated load game. It was a single scenario. Which one was it? I have no idea. Timeline two.
Battle. Do we have times on these? We do. Is it conquerors? 530? No. 529. 530 at 2039.
530 at 1808. Original team timeline. There we go. Yeah. 2358. That's just before midnight.
I think this is it. Am I not playing Sam and Max? I just did. I completed season two. Now I need to
complete this. That is what we're doing today. All right, let's go here. I think this is it.
Let's see. So it was purple was doing nothing. Purple has like a dwarf in here, right?
I need to finish my losing camp. We have to get closure, but it's not lost yet. Remember,
I was wiping out people. I was taking people out left and right. He doesn't have very much
left. He has this. And that's it. Change the game. I already did. You need to refresh your browser.
Refresh your Twitch browser, please. It's not over yet. See, he's starting to build up a little
bit. Red is almost dead. So let's see what I can do. Let me try to remember what the plan.
I still have like good army. I'm going to be making money. I have tons of money. Let's go
down here. All right. Lots of money. What do I want to build? Behemoth lair. Let's build it.
I got the money. Oh, let's just start. Look, get him. Okay, we got a behemoth. I still can
move around here. What is this? This is the big one here. And then, yeah, not that well
defended. He only has like one castle that has anything in it. Two maybe, but if I can...
I just... I just need purple to do anything. All right, here we go. I'm going for it.
Like right here. Let me just take this. Everything's good down here.
New day. Did you actually just take that from purple? How is red still alive? I don't understand.
Like red sucks. I have to send somebody over here to do something about this because this
is all red has. They don't have anything else. Okay, what do we got? Let's build some more
stuff. Chris's goblin production. Orc tower. Upgrade the behemoth lair. Maybe. Just to have
better behemoths. What's the difference? Target enemy's defenses reduced by 80%. That's pretty
awesome. Curse that volume just a little. All right. Things are not looking bad. I have tons
of troop availability. I just need some money. Let's just even them out a little.
All right. You got several. Few, few, few, and few. He has... I don't... That's not enough.
That's not enough to get this. It's enough to get... I really should just go up here.
Or all the way up here. Well, just get all the resources. You're fucked. Yeah, I know. I know.
But still. It's still possible. Well, these guys are gonna run away. Give me this.
Several... I think I can do this. What do we got down here? Tons of fucking people to buy.
And I just go for it. All right. There's red. There's red. There's red. They're both out here
now. Come on. Go for it. Take something. Help me out here. Build. I already got this stuff.
Yeah. Just claim all the resources. The map is shit. That's the problem. I played a tough
game, but was able to use the map to my advantage to pull off an upset. Yeah. But it's
still possible. I can't just give up right now. I mean, this was such a good comeback.
I had such an opportunity. I can't. I'm like sunk cost fallacy right now.
I just gotta get somebody up there. Where's my nearest castle? Right here. Either right
there or right here. This is probably faster because it's a straight line. All right. What
can I do in here? I got plenty of fucking people next time. What about you? Let's go
with you. Several horde lots. What do you think I can do it? Think I can take this castle over
right now? What button do I press to hire all available units? I'll show you. So in here,
right here, this is a little castle building. You click it and it'll show you all available
that you can buy and you can just buy them all. No, I can't. I have to take like a...
What about this one? No. What about up here? These are easier to take. You know, just like
get over there. How far away is he? He's really fucking far away, isn't he? Yeah, he's like too
far away to do this. What do you have? Fuck. Is this a dead game? This might be dead.
You horde pack. Fuck. No, I was doing so well too. I'm playing it out. Here comes red.
Here. Which, what do I have here? All right. Let's get some units in here.
You have horde, horde. He has a lot, but horde of fairies is nothing. This should be okay.
I'll give this another few rounds and then decide if it's time to throw the towel in.
How do I get up here? I am claiming a bunch of shit, but it doesn't matter. They've...
Damn it. Here we go. They're coming in. I might be okay here. What's the most,
this is the most dangerous thing. This. I wonder if I should just fly out the dragon,
but probably not. I can't, no spells, no hero in here. 50 elementals. Yeah, but they have to get
in. I have one unit in double digits and it's the frog. Well, I'm not going to get out there
yet. Like, they can fly? No, they can't, can they? I mean, they can. I have like minotaurs
too. I should be all right once we... I mean, this is just one harpy here. Fuck, they can
fly. Yeah, this is bad. I don't have a hero to cast any spells. Hey, look at me. I'm gonna go over
here. They still have to get in. These are all powerful units. I think it's time for me to get
out here. He's just gonna fly in. I can kill these guys. There you are. Kill. I could go
out there and meet them on an open field. I'm not, I'm not gonna do that though.
Here they are at the front door. Just cheese them. Good, be the bait for the range attacks here.
Fuck, it's open. Well, they can get in now. I think I should just fly out here.
Stand like right here. Get down here. Nobody do anything. Get in the moat. Right in the moat.
Nice. Perfect. Come on. All right, where's my dragon? From this angle. Get him. I could
probably kill these in one or two hits. Get the dragon in the way. Come on. I don't want to fly
him out there. They're gonna get in. Block the entrance. This is not terrible. I'm okay with
this. It's all right. It's not over. This is the only unit that's really scary. Get rid of
this. No, come on. Good. Head down here. It doesn't matter. You're not gonna do shit.
Ah, fuck. I just blocked the angle. Completely. Go up here.
Chimera's gonna die. All right, come on. What do I have? 50? 12 to 20? They don't do that
much damage. Get in there. God damn it. Die. Why can't I shoot anybody from here? This sucks.
Out of ammo. Oh yeah. Well, unfortunately, this is going to be really, really close,
but it's not going to be enough. It's game over. 50 of these things. Didn't have a hero in here.
Let's just fly. Just run away. Eventually I'm going to get hit by that arrow.
Yeah, eventually this will kill me. Yeah, I'm dead. Oh, this is so sad. Now this might be
unwinnable. Can I look at like stats? Can I see if they've done any damage to any other
player? Fucking 2v2 in the tavern. I want to see. Number of towns. Gold. Plenty of wood and ore.
Look at this shit. Attack is zero. Zero two two two. How can you not be there? How is it
possible? Can I steal this? Can I take his ore? Warrior human explorer builder. It's not
completely. I still have the one. I have this one really good army. I'm going to go for it.
Like fuck it. Let's just go for it. I'm going to stack units and then we're going to go.
Bone dragons. What has like the best? Let's see. You got good shit. All these places have
good shit, but I don't have money. I might as well just buy all this and then bring you down
there. Eventually the vampires will do work. Yeah, I just, I think I'm just overwhelmed at
this point. I don't think it's like possible. It was worth a shot. What the hell are you doing?
Because I need to go to here with you. So you got to get up there next turn.
Literally nothing. Although you are right next to it. More heroes can do more stuff.
Yeah, that's true. But it's remember it's 2v1 right now because purple ain't doing shit.
Purple's walking around in the circle picking up the same three resources. Can I get anything
from here? I guess I could just, just to take them. Take the unicorns. Just to have better
RV for now. I guess I could take these too. Just in case I run into somebody.
All right, anything else? So before I go up here and get some more vampires.
Guys, Dwarf's going to take this one. I'm going to get this one. Restock,
take over this one and see what happens. The vampires. Do they not? They don't have
upgraded vampires. How do you not have this? There are bone dragons here. Okay, next day.
What? Did he just take me on? I don't think he wins this. I'm gonna have to, okay,
I'm gonna have to do some, I don't have like ice arrow. Who's more dangerous?
Wyverns. Fuck. He has eight Wyverns. That's very bad.
Just hang out here for a second. What the fuck just happened? He just did Armageddon.
Come on. What? Everybody's dead. I had a chance. Hold on. Can I, let me just try and
take this out. It's not gonna happen. Is it? Come on. Kill it. I'm so defeated right now.
That sucks. I probably would have done it too. Yeah, there goes my other hero. Let's see what
purple's up to. I wonder. What did you do? Let me see. Nice, nice. So you walked from like
here to here. Cool. You better stack this fucking castle up. Now. Plan doesn't change.
We're still going to this castle. Jerma's angry already. I'm just remembering how
annoyed I was with my teammate. I know I'm like the salty boy after, you know,
you can't blame the teammate, but yes you can. You can. I'm sorry. I'm gonna drown here. I'm
gonna drown. He has to take something. Please take something. This is, I put like nine hours
into this campaign. I can't give up on it. Get over here right now. Come here. Give me all
your stuff. Give it to me. I can't take it from you. I can only give. I can't take. No,
no, no. I don't want to give you my fucking dragons. What? No, no, no, no, no, no, no,
no. What just happened? What did I just get in return? Split creatures. No, I, I can't. Oh,
my fucking God. It's okay. I just said one guy just said it's because my army is full
and now I just gave him my fucking angels. Somebody said it's because your army's full.
I've got to watch that stress. I, you just got the best fucking.
Uh, I, uh, why can I give, but I can't take from my ally? What if he's not going to give
to me from my fucking computer? You really close windows, select left hero,
and he's not going to do anything. He's going to take those units and walk around the circle
down here. Just don't press the check mark. Can I just exit? No, no, no. These, I needed
these so bad. I think that's, I think this is the point where I quit. I haven't saved in
a long time. When was the last auto safe? Let's see. Is this it? It is. Okay. Thank God.
Don't ever listen to Chad. No one's ever played this game. No, I mean, if it's a good,
it was a decent theory. The losing campaign continues. Yes, it does. All right. If I'm
going to lose, I'm going to lose. I'm not going to just quit. You got me to
download this game. Good. It's fantastic. I hope you enjoy it. It's a really,
really good game. He already owned that windmill and he touched it again. I hate this guy.
All right. Let's stock up again. Got more vampires. I'm going to leave the angels
because, uh, what do you think? Angels or, um, dendroids looks kind of good.
And here is my only hope. Are you ready? It's called turtle forever and just try to get like
15 dragons and like 150 vampires. I need to upgrade the skeletons though. That's my only shot.
Somebody's got to come out with these. This is like not a bad army either.
I'm making a new hero. Jeremy, you already made this Australia joke.
Well, at this point, it's not a joke. It's real life. I'm living in reality right now.
They're coming for me and I'm not going to, I'm not going to go down. Winners don't turtle.
All right. So I want, uh, this one upgrade the skeleton. I have already upgraded. I need to do
this. What do I need for that? Dragon vault. I already have dread nights. All right. Dragon
vault, 15,000 gold. We're doing it. Let's just save the money while we have the second here.
Let's get a new hero because there are, uh, ancient behemoths that are here now.
Okay. We need resource silo, freelance goblin barracks, ogre fort, escape tunnel.
No, let's just get a hero. I mean, yeah, I really, it needs to be this person.
Okay. You hang out there for now. I'm going to get you an army too.
You take this because no one has even secured it. What the fuck are they thinking?
I got the new spell. I'm ready. They're all working together. This is,
he has so many heroes. He doesn't know what to do with it. This one just stood still.
He has like 12 heroes across two players and now they're coming for me.
No, what do you have? Uh, I don't think it's possible to defend this pack of,
uh, God damn it. That's when I think I'm, I get a minute to breathe.
Well, I'm going to try. I'm going to try to defend it with my level one hero.
Ah, two more days through until a new week. What do you got? Lots of this game.
I don't think I'm going to be able to do this one. I need like a final battle though,
just so I can say that I completed it. It was game over two hours ago. Yeah, I know,
but I just had to see it again because I left really abruptly.
You come with your firebirds. The behemoths didn't do anything.
No, this is just embarrassing. Really? Yeah. At least I'm trying, right?
Start a new map. Um, I don't think so. I think I'm going to hold onto that because starting
because then we'll, the same situation will happen. I'll get like a quarter of the way
through a map. I'd rather do like a full, like seven to 10 hours stream of the game
rather than play it for like another hour or two on a new map and then we save it
and it disappears for two weeks. Tomorrow is cooking simulators. We're not doing it tomorrow.
I may as well just die. Do a real cooking stream.
Worth mentioning that this is three nine, three dollars and 39 cents right now on good old games.
Just get it. This is less than a fucking medium coffee at Starbucks. Go get this game.
Seriously. Unfortunately, the first stream I did, the game I think was 10 bucks
and this is where we lose. I need one more big battle.
There's going to be one more big battle that I have to at least go out with.
You know, I can't just let, I can't just lose. I'm sticking my tongue out at them while they rush.
I got it because I saw you playing it. Yeah. It's very interesting.
It's a very, very fun chill game. Big one sided battle. I don't think so. Next,
this next week here, I'm going to, I'm taking off and we're going to see what we can do
with upgraded bone dragons. I'll take six of them. Jeremy needs to get spanked hard
before he goes to his room for good. No, you're talking about like in the getting
beat in the game. Oh my God. What the fuck. All right. It's almost time to go out here.
I still live in the castle. Podcast listener just gave 50 dollars.
Podcast listener. Thank you for the 50 bucks. 5,000 bits. Love your streams, dude. Thanks for
everything you do. German heart. Much love back to you. Thank you for 50 fucking dollars.
5,000 bits. Podcast listener. Thank you so much. A lot of money. 5,000 this lot.
There was, they've been like three or four of these tonight. Thank you guys.
Twitch added a reward system. They did. What do you mean reward system? You get like bits
or something. What does that mean? I don't know what it means. All right. Here comes the next
week. I'm ready to move. I'm going to, I'm going to fucking explode here. I had to go
out with a bang. I have to take somebody with me and like part of me is like actually
thinking about declaring war on purple and killing him. Can I do that? Is that possible?
Can I? Is there a way? Did purple go through the same portal loop three times? Probably.
System option scenario info. Is there declare war? No, I can't declare war. That's
unfortunate. All right, here we go. Two more dragons. Four more of these.
Eight more of these. I should have a substantial army at this point. Some more skeletons.
And then we're going to upgrade the dragons and then we're going to get the hell out of here
and I'm going to just steamroll somebody. Mow the lawn IRL. I'm not sure you're aware
of this, but there are really, there's not really much thing as a lawn in Las Vegas.
It'd be mold of rocks. Hey, let's do it again. Back to bed. Rake the sand. What do I need?
10,000? 15,000? I think he just took something from me.
Damn. Damn it. Okay, here we go. Dragon vault. There it is. Now I need to wait
one more day. I may as well just wait the whole week. What did he just do that for?
He's just playing with portals now. He just did the portal infinite loop thing for fun.
Five super dragons. Look, let's just wait the whole week. I'm just waiting the whole
week. Who cares? I already lost. It doesn't matter. I don't care about this. Nothing
matters. Don't even give him satisfaction. Run through the escape hole. What is this?
No. Turn on auto combat. I can't even surrender. There's no one to surrender. Hey,
at least I took out one of their sand wind people. This is sad. Sad. It's okay. At least
I've saw to its completion. That's all I care about. Here's what I will be really mad about
though. If I lose before purple does, that's what's gonna happen. That's so I'm gonna be,
I'm gonna go to sleep tonight angry. I'm not supposed to get angry. What does purple have?
Purple has like two castles and like two or three heroes. What does purple have? Does
purple even have a house? Yeah, look, he's, I mean, doesn't have shit, but still. Oh,
here we go. Yes, I could stop this right now, but I'm not going to want him to die.
Just so I can at least be the one that survived. Let's watch this one boys and girls and see how
this happens. No, you're not going to do it. Habitage. All right. This is the end. Eight
ghost dragons. 29. I gotta wait to get some more vampires. We're gonna wait.
Here's the thing though. This really might be really powerful and I might kill these two
or three of their heroes and then I'll die. It's okay. At least I'll die going down.
Wait, no, at least I'll fight. I'll take them on. Whatever you, what I'm trying to say is just,
give me another week. Yeah, I'm gonna sell them. Sell, sell everything. Sell all. Marketplace.
Where's the marketplace here? All right. This is, I don't want to do this, but I am.
Sell it all. Wait, what do I need for the dragons? I already have as many as I can get.
Sell. Who cares? We'll clean it out. The coffer is here.
78. All right. What? Anything else? I got $10,000. Should I get? All right. Chad, listen to me here.
Unicorns or 60 whites? I can up, what do you think? Super whites? Unicorns or 60 upgraded
whites? Let's see what they look like. 3 to 5, 18 health. 18 to 22, 90. There's only four
unicorns. Yeah. All right. Last week. One more day. Somebody said, what a disaster.
It's all right. We're just, we're just chilling. We're just having fun.
We're just hanging out. Thanks, purple. He noticed I had zero in everything.
You know, it'd be really great if you did anything else besides give me like
10 of each resource. All right. Drain's enemy mana. Undead. Regenerating.
Aura of magic resistance. Blinding attack. Hates devils. This is it. This is the team.
I'm ready to go. Where do I go first? All right. You decide. Where are we going?
Top left, top right, bottom right, or bottom left? Which one?
Stay put. Wait, you want me just to sit here? Stay put? Hold. I have to get out of here.
You want me to stay? I can't just stay here. It's never going to end.
They're never going to stop running around and collecting resources.
No, I got to go. I got to go. They won't even come over here. I have to go to them.
They're never going to come over here. I'm going. Getting 999 skeletons. That's going to
take fucking like seven more months. I'm going. First course of action is top right,
I think. Middle right. We're taking this. Let's go. I'm not fucking, I don't care
if I lose my capital. I'll get one. Top right? I mean, that's where we're going.
Right here. I'll take this. We're in Orange's world. Yeah. We are in an orange world. And
then I'm going in this thing. And wherever that ends up, whatever. Here comes a battle.
There he goes. Just waiting for me to leave. Purple's dead. That was very anti-climactic.
Purple, I think, officially is dead. They don't have anything. You have one hero,
I think, right? That's all you got. This dumb motherfucker still has default skeletons.
I hate this guy. Might as well go with a fighter. It doesn't matter. I'm going to get your
castle anyways. Did more than you. No, he didn't. No, he didn't. All right. Well,
you don't even. What's earthquake? This earthquake. Do I have earthquake?
I'm getting a meteor shower. Sacrifice. Armageddon. Clone. No, what are we going
to do? Fucking meteor shower. Right here. Right here. Right in the middle. I think so.
Get free people with it. Oh, boy. You get stronger every day. Come on out here. One hit.
Let's go right here. Is that open yet? This is open, right? We're opening. I can't go
into the moat. Thank you for coming out. Easy. Casual. He's expecting the AI to carry him. No,
I'm expecting the AI to get out of the backpack that's on my back.
Just weighing me down. He curled up into a ball and he's just in my suitcase.
Let's get in here. Done deal. Castle's mine. And then, okay, that's it. I'm going to get
his artifact. Oh, fuck. Ballistics. Two aim shots at max damage or rearrange troops. Two aim shots.
Mine. Okay, good. Now it begins. No. Top left. Here we go. Okay, I don't think I can take
this. Yes, I can. Oh, fuck yeah. I'm going to take them both. Pack, pack, few, pack.
Defend the capital. I don't even need to defend the capital. It doesn't matter. They're dead
anyways. Pack, pack, few, pack, pack, pack. Just fly. Just cause damage. I'm back. Is
Purple still alive? Yes, but not for long. You need multiple heroes? Yeah, I know. It's
just too late for that. I have really nothing. I thought I had multiple heroes when I had a
friend of mine playing. I didn't mean to gag myself. This guy doesn't do anything. You
may as well just do the chef. Kill the dragon. At least kill one of these dragons. You can do
it. You're so bad. Worst unit in the game. He's getting toxic. It's not even good. It's
a bad unit. It's not even a good unit. No, it's the starting... I was the wrong
character to start with. This player's not even good. This guy's not even good. I just
picked the wrong starting hero. This guy's not even good. It's really annoying. I should
have fucking won. I picked the wrong fucking hero in the beginning. This guy's not even
good at the game. You don't have a friend like that that you play games with or you
played games with and every time that they died, it was always like... No, this game's
bad. That guy's bad. I am that friend. All right, here we go. Let's go. I need music for
this. Good music. Hold on. I gotta get pumped up. No, not Doom. It's gotta be like epic
fantasy music. Not Benny Hill. Does this have a song? It does have a song, doesn't
it? All right, I'm gonna be quiet and you're gonna be able to watch the epic
battle, okay? Does Matt just pretend you're watching a movie? Where's that guy from?
Was that guy in the last movie? What's that guy's name? Fuck off! Hello? No, I'm
in a movie. Yeah, it's like this fantasy movie. It sucks. Put that phone down! Oh,
no, I'll call you back. Fucking dickhead! You threw fucking popcorn at me,
motherfucker? What did I do? Sit the fuck down. Fuck out of here, fucking idiot.
Somebody get security! Get away from him! Get him out of here. Get him out of my
fucking mouth. He hit me right in the fucking mouth. Piece of shit. He threw a whole bag of
popcorn at my fucking friend. No, I don't want you to take my name. I don't want you to take
my fucking name. No, you don't need my name. This is like the best part of the movie.
I won. I did it! All right, now get my stream not claimed, please. I didn't even
lose anybody, either. Let's go. Have you ever had a girlfriend? Yeah, I got one right
now. We're in Ips camp. Is there an after credit scene? Where am I? Oh, he's coming for the
house. We've rested up. Any replacements? I think we can go down. Unbelievable. Unbelievable.
Unbelievable. I have a girlfriend, but she goes to another school. I mean, that's a classic.
Just I want you to keep in mind something very important. Just look at this.
Where was that? Was it down here? You need to see this. This is fucking so important.
I'm about to throw a bag of popcorn. Where is he? This purple is just standing and they walk
to buy him. Where is he? There he is. Red walked by him. Isn't it like seven days and
you automatically die of starvation? Why is he still alive? I can't understand.
Your unintelligible Boston accent speak more clearly. Fuck are you talking about?
It's another castle. What's that? I'll take another one, please.
What is this music? Oh, it's the castle. Turn off teleport if you do another game. Yeah,
this was the random map. Everything random test. So it's cool. I actually probably
rather play one of the scenarios just because remember when we first started this?
There was random shit everywhere. Almost like as if it wasn't supposed to be where it was.
Well, here we go. I get punched in the face in this movie too.
There we go. I fixed it. Okay, I'm thinking we got eight versus nine. Same dragon,
but not anymore. Tell those vampires. I feel like I kind of need to just get in here,
but this is my strongest unit. I don't know what to do. I don't know what to do. I have
no idea. I have absolutely no idea. No idea what to do. I get going to get the first hit.
Going in. Fuck it. Get in. Everybody get in. Get in. Is my microphone? No, it's not.
Save the dragons, please. God. No, the dragons can't be saved.
I'm trying to keep the vampires alive. Those are the ones that I think actually really
matter here. Ah, that hurts. Sorrow? Stone skin? Bloodlust? I think so. Save him. You're a
heartless owner. He's gonna be fine. I need him to take hits and be able to take out the
dragons. He's doing very, very good. Okay, angel. Angel's gonna die here. No, that means
like a super crit. Okay, I had to get rid of them first. Can I make it in here? I don't
think I can. I can't really get over that. Can I walk over this? I have to. She's dead.
Notice people have blood that I can steal. This is game over.
The vampires can't drain any light because there's no light to drain.
No, not yet. It's not a complete lost cause yet. Get in. Get inside. It's unbelievable. All
right. Um, clone, frost ring, anti-magic. I'm thinking what's death ripple? Sends a wave of
death across the battlefield, which damage is all non-undead. Everyone's undead here.
Ice bolt. Onto them. Decent. That's decent. I'm gonna beat it. I'm gonna do it, right?
Yeah, I am. But what did it cost? What did it cost? We already had one.
I just ripped my shirt way more than it was. This is ridiculous now. Now this has to go into
like the garbage. Did you guys hear that? This is now like a piece of spaghetti around my neck.
No! It really, I can't like save it either. I just grabbed it like fucking idiot.
No, I have to like, I have to stitch, but if I stitch it together, the fibers are going to
be all screwed up. Is this premium? No, this is not a premium. This is not a
$20 premium t-shirt that you can get from the German 95 Teespring store.
$20 for a premium shirt. This is just a Hanes. I killed the dragon.
It doesn't matter. I'm like, I'm not going to win this. I'm going to win like this
match, but am I going to look at the fucking units I have. It doesn't matter. It's fine.
I'm like, there we go. I got 12,000 experience. Basic learning, basic error. Hey, I did it.
This is my original home. I have five vampires. I took my home back. That's all I care about.
And I'm going to go take this one too. Did you make ads for the Teespring so that
you can play it when chat asks for ads? Yeah, that's true. Every time you guys ask
for an ad, I'm just going to tell you about my t-shirt. Holy shit. 37 of these. This is
the real end here. That's too many. Is this the same castle? You'll never take me alive.
I'll blow this place to kingdom come before I go with you. What is that? I got to do my last
I'm still standing and everyone's watching. They have the respect and they have the
dignity to let me at my own dignity and my own free will go out of the castle
and have my final stand. Purple lived. Purple lived without a house just walking around.
That's the third time I've lost my fucking head. I want to see stats from that game.
Show me stats. I want to see the after the game scores. Bad military leader. Yeah,
it's all right though. Go to the autosave and look at the tavern. What do you mean?
Uh, no. Back, back, back. Autosave and look at the tavern. The tavern where? Uh, what about it?
Oh, you're talking about here. Yeah, he didn't do anything. He got the most wood. I was number of
towns. Goal. I was up here. I would have been up here. He just collected resources and sent
them to me sometimes in the mail. Yeah, I don't have the best hero because my hero's dead.
He just died. See that the game doesn't even think that I have a 10, 3, 6, 9 hero. How about
doing triple time? Second place against the AI. Yeah, this is a hard game. It's a hard game.
Fake wood more than one hero. I had, I had like three or four heroes in the first like four
hours of this campaign. I did. Purple just was in a fucking luggage and I was storing
them overhead all day. I need to worry about my own luggage. Streamer eats four gyros? Oh god,
it's not a real Heroes of Might and Magic 3 stream. It's not eight hours. No, I can't
do that today. We're coming back slow during a colon. Here we go. He, he's gonna say it.
He's about to say, he's gonna say it. He's about to say it. No, no, no, don't say,
don't, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, don't do it. Guys, that's gonna be the...
I paused the stream. Did he say, did he say it? Did he? I paused it. I'm gonna unpause. I hope
he doesn't say it. End of the stream. No! He did it. Don't do that. Nah, yeah, I'm,
I need to ease back into this. I've already been supposed to take it easy today and I,
like, was screaming and yelling. I just can't have a fucking, I can't have, like, a calm stream.
I just can't. I don't know what it is. Every time I say, oh, I'm gonna play Shaman
Vax for an episode and then do it, I always end up screaming. Is there a way that I can
just, like, not get high energy? I'm just gonna eat, like, a bunch of pasta before
my next comfy stream so I don't, like, do make any noises. Get a lobotomy. Whoa.
Nah, I'm kidding around. But for real, colonoscopy went well. We cleaned up some stuff. I just kind
of want to have a chill day today and scream and make noises and be very loud and scream some
more. Tomorrow is Cooking Simulator. That's gonna be a fun one. I can't wait. I've been
really looking forward to it. Hope you enjoy it. Tomorrow, regular time, same place, same
network. Thank you, everybody, for watching. He hates it. No, no. Have you seen the trailer?
It looks very detailed and very fun. It's like House Flipper but only in the kitchen
and you only cook food. It's very detailed. I think you're gonna like it. But take care
of yourselves. We're gonna do the bits and everything. Not quite ready to leave. It's
not like House Flipper at all. Well, I'm just saying it's one of those, like, simulation
kind of... you'll see. You'll see. That's what we're gonna call it. Why is Sam and Max still up?
That was incorrect. But let's do the bits and the subs. If you've taken off, hopefully we see
you soon. Maybe tomorrow or the next day. Normal time tomorrow. We have between three and
four pacific. Hopefully see you there. So let us rewind five hours to the beginning of the
stream. Let's go over some of these bits. What do you say? Am I gonna play Layers of
Fear 2? I don't know. I really don't know. I've seen such wild mixed things about it.
I've heard it's really awful and not in, like, a fun, funny way. Just not fun and not good at all.
And then I've heard, no, it's actually pretty great. It's so mixed. I don't even know
what I want to do. But it seems like it doesn't really have great response so far.
What are we talking about? Layers of Fear 2. He hates it. Hey, thank you to Atrolux8trucks
for the 250. They say Pride 100. Pride 100. Pride 50. We fucking love you, Jerma. Those new meds.
Huh. You can do this. P.S. Happy Pride Month. Happy Pride Month. Those new meds.
We fucking love you, Jerma. Those new meds. I did get new medication for my,
I was gonna say my bum, but that's what it is. What am I gonna pretend that's not what it is?
Uh, it's, it is a little weird. I'm trying to get used to it.
But we'll see. Thank you so much for the 250. Really appreciate it. Marvosh Magali,
thanks for the 250. Hi, Jerma. I missed quite a lot of streams. The only VOD I watched was
the Talk to Transformer one, and that got me in tears. Glad the colonoscopy went good.
Did your mum enjoy the tour? Take care. Yes. My mother had a great time here.
When she was here last month. It was a great time. It was great to see my mother. She's
wonderful. Hopefully I see her again soon. And yeah, the colonoscopy did, it went well,
from my understanding. There's still tissue that's being examined. I have to wait a few
weeks. That's how long it takes the biopsies to come back. But I was told that there are
no major concerns, but in a few weeks I will know for sure. There's some tissue still
being examined. Colon tour. It's just a long tube. Am I gonna stream E3? Yes. I'm going to do
the same thing that I did last year and do the major conferences.
So you can expect that? Absolutely. But thank you Marvosh Magali. Thank you
Daft Skeletor for the $15. There's no message here, but 15 bucks is a large drop of money.
Thank you. Appreciate the $15. Thank you so much. What were the minor concerns?
Uh, I mean I have irritable bowel disease. I've had like colitis for 15 years almost,
12 years at this point. Since I was like 24, 23. It's been almost like, no it's been like
10 years. Something like that. So I still have those problems. It's just I've never had a full
colonoscopy before. I've had sigmoidoscopies, which is the same thing except they don't go
as far in. So yeah, there's IBS and there's IBD. IBS is irritable bowel syndrome.
IBD is irritable bowel disease. I will have it for the rest of my life. You cannot get rid of
it. So that's just the way it is. So I have to be a lot more conscious of my intestinal
and gastro health. So that's why a lot of people were asking. I know we talked about
this in the beginning of the stream, but some of you may not have been here. I have to be screened
earlier just because of all the gastro issues that I do have. So and I was having a couple
of symptoms that I didn't really have an explanation for. So we went down the path of
just getting it done now. There you go. But thank you for the $15. Daffskeletor. Thank you
C4G for the $5. Jerma, I'm begging you do a dollar on high stream. Maybe when chapter five
comes out on Thursday. No, I can't play those games in front of people because I make like
decisions that are so bad probably and aren't like completely correct and everyone would just
make fun of me. You try to tell me that if I like had lethal and I missed it,
the chat wouldn't be like making tons of fun of me and stuff. No, I know that I don't
know how to play well. I don't want to be told that. I already know it. I do everything
so incorrectly that you guys would send me to the guillotine if I streamed that game.
Talking about Hearthstone. Not only do I miss lethal, but sometimes I do wrong trades and then
I go oops, oh it's okay. I'll just do the spell to him next time. And it's completely
incorrect, but it still works. I'm the kind of person that does like the deal two damage
to an enemy to the hero's face. I do that sometimes. Just people are not going to be
happy about that if I do that on stream. I'm the guy that you go up against in chicken league
rank 25 that the first thing he does is do the two damage hunter spell that costs what one
mana to your face and you know immediately you're going to win. Yeah, arcane shot.
I'm the guy that does the arcane shot to you turn one to your face and you are guaranteed
to win that game. So that's why I can't stream. But thank you. I appreciate the enthusiasm on
the way. Thank you C4G. Hey trust no one. Thanks for the $2.50. December 2018 you announced
green screen encore. That was a long time ago. Right after that I got lots of inspiration to
produce 10 videos. It's summer already. Jerma lied again, but I still want to share my
works with you. Have you watched them before next stream? Want to bring fun to chat fellas?
Or no. It's always up to you daddy. All right you ready? You ready for this?
Are you ready? You have to hold me to this date. Are you ready? Are you ready for this?
Because I'm gonna make a date. I'm gonna give you a date here and like we have to do it.
It is June 4th 2019. We are going to do a watch the video stream on June 29th.
June 29th. I want to give people time to get them ready. June 29th of 2019. Can't be this week.
Can't be next week. I got like the E3 stuff is this weekend. I've got these like unlock
escape the room card things that I want to do on cam and then like the the week of the
like the 17th I've got something. You can clip it. Don't let me forget.
And I will give you some details about that. I want to give like a couple weeks so I can
get the some of the mods involved so we can actually set up something like last time.
This is not a re-watching of this would be new videos. Videos that were not
on the last stream and I may even if we I don't know maybe we just turn maybe we'll
just turn it into like uh I don't know let me think about this. Let me let me think
about this because I've got some ideas. Maybe they might not all have to be green screen
videos. You know what I'm saying? If we might maybe we could do something here
because people make lots of great videos that aren't necessarily only about green screen stuff.
I mean obviously they'd have to follow some criteria where it'd have to do with the channel.
Like you could don't just don't just like send me like a video of like Shrek playing
like the flute or something like what that means not what does that have to do with anything.
Well I'll figure that out. I'll start talking to some of the mods about it.
June 29th will be the day we do it. Arrest that guy. Now it has to happen. There you go.
And we could turn we could make it uh we can we might be able to make it interesting too.
Not that the last one wasn't interesting but maybe add a couple of things.
Maybe put some incentives. Maybe do like a charity thing. I don't know maybe. Let
let me just explore this. I'll explore this for a little bit. 29 guest stars. We'll see.
But I have not forgotten it's just kind of a lot of random shit has happened.
A bunch of people have visited here. I've had like friends and family and medical. Like
there's just been things that have been happening that I just can't really focus on
any of the projects that I want to focus on immediately. There's been a lot of just like
guests strangely enough. Some unexpected. But yeah it's that's just the way it is.
We're gonna push forward. But thank you trust no one. Look forward to seeing your videos.
Hey cornflex. Thanks for the 15 dollars cornflex. Hey German just quit my job and I
feel fly but I hope you're doing good. Here's a bit of snack money. Keep doing
you. I will buy snacks with those. I will buy 15 dollars worth of snacks I promise.
Uh quit your job. Hopefully you can figure out what to do next. Wish you the best of luck.
What do you mean I'm not gonna buy snacks with that. Guys like 45 percent of my whole income
goes to snacks. Like this is six pantries here. I can't stop. I eat like two bags of chips
every day. I can't stop. I eat a loaf of bread every fucking morning. I just soak the
bread in water and then like. I do not do that. But thank you for the 15 dollars cornflex.
I'm doing pretty good. Thank you for the snack money. After schmaff. After schmaff. Thanks for
the three bucks. I love everything you do. You're my favorite content creator by far.
Haven't caught a stream in a while because of emotional problems. So I'm glad to see
nothing's changed. Here's all the rest of my bits because you deserve it. I also wanted
ask you are you going to stream cyberpunk 2077? Okay well soon. Yes. I feel like you have to.
That game is just looks like it's so full of stuff to do. Whenever that comes out whatever
the criteria is for its release I feel like everyone. There's gonna be a day on twitch
where when you go to the browse by game category there's probably gonna be like
six games on that list and there'll be like fucking 40,000 people streaming 2077
and then like Hearthstone, League of Legends, and CSGO. Everyone's gonna play this game. So
I'll be one of them. 2077. Yeah 2077. 2077. Normie. Come on. Normie stream? What?
We just played like Heroes of Might and Magic 3. Why is cyberpunk 2077? What are you talking about?
Heroes of Might and Magic is so normie. What do you mean normie? What does that even mean?
What does that even mean? That's pretty normal. Heroes of Might and Magic is the most played
game of all time. Oh yeah? How many hours do you guys have in it? I bet I see a lot of
zeros. Two because it blue screens my computer. I'm sorry to hear that that's not cool.
Zero because I'm not a normie. I feel like if uh if you guys like watched me eat like frosted
flakes I'd be like a normie cereal. Right? What is not a normie cereal? What is not what is not
normie in like the cereal world? Brute Loops? No that's normie. Raisin Bran? That's normie.
Nothing. Everything is normie. Don't you understand? Honey Bunches of Oats? That's
not what are you talking about? That's very normal. Apple Jackson for Chad's?
Apple what? Honey Bunches of Oats? No. Bacon Flakes? Cookie Crisp? No that's bullshit.
Cookie Crisp before the recipe change. Maybe I would agree with you but they changed that
recipe. It doesn't taste the same. Fruity Pebbles? No I don't I disagree. Fruity Pebbles
you pour the milk in and before you put the spoon in to bite into the cereal it turns into wet
napkins. I disagree. Count Chocula. Now that I can get behind. I can get behind that. Anyways
what? I think Pops is a pretty... I think I could get behind that too. Or uh Smacks. When
was the last time you had Smacks? That's what it's called right? With the frog? Yeah Honey
Smacks. Honey Smacks. Those were awesome. I can get behind those. Those are the ones that looked
like coffee beans. They were little coffee beans puffed up. I might just go buy some.
I'm just gonna prove how much of a not of a normie I am. I'm gonna just eat Honey Smacks.
What are you linking me here? Kissed. I don't even know what that is. Cereal Unboxing. All
right let's keep going. Thank you Dr. Low Note for the five dollars. Pogchamp. Pogchamp. Pogchamp
Pogchamp had my LSAT yesterday. Glad you're back. I hope you're feeling good. Feeling pretty good.
Hopefully you did well on the LSAT. That's a Pogchamp yeah. Thank you for the five dollars
Dr. Low Note and hope you did good. Dorkcube7000 thanks for the 250. Now
when you went to get your colonoscopy you made sure to show the doc your fire watch photos
right? Doctor didn't need to see fire watch photos. He saw way more than that. Fire watch
photos don't even compare to the images. I have these images by the way. I was thinking about
they give them to you. It's a bunch of images but I don't think I can show them.
I'm fairly certain that that's like I don't know I think that might break TOS.
Autograph them. Post them on Twitter. I can't do that. Can't you get it? I can't do that.
Autograph? No it's like bad. There's like inflammation and stuff. You don't want to see
these but I already have new fire watch photos that the doctor took for me up my ass. That's
the fucking like comedy there. Put them on discord. No I'm not gonna like I'm not gonna
like fucking sign and show and sell my colonoscopy photos. That's like fucking
apocalyptic like dystopian world. Me selling photos of my colonoscopy. Me signing and
sending them to people. Welcome to 2020. What the fuck. But anyways yes thank you for
the 250 door cube. Thank you Devakitty for the four dollars and 25 cents. Happy pride month.
Take the rest of my bits in memory of the people like Marsha P who fought so hard for civil
liberty. Lesbian pride. Transgender pride. Happy pride month. Thank you so much for the four
dollars and 25 cents. Dr Oz did it and he's a doctor. Dr Oz also had a fucking tv show
where he was a doctor on tv. I'm not a fucking doctor on stream. I'm not Dr Oz. I don't go
on tv and talk about my stuff. Let me tell you something. I went to the store and I got
some lentils. I do a pretty good doctor, don't I? That's what he talks like. That's what he
talks like. Why are you comparing me to Dr Oz? That wasn't Bernie. That was that was Dr Oz.
Hello everybody and welcome to the Dr Oz show. I'm gonna fucking prove this right now.
Today I have a very important thing talked about on the show and that's colonoscopy.
At Dr Oz, I want to talk. Listen to me. You ready? I can't wait to prove everybody here wrong.
It feels so good. Hi Dr Oz here. Welcome to my official youtube channel. Hey Dr Oz here. Welcome
to my official youtube channel. Welcome to my official youtube channel. And I'm wrong. Every
week you're going to find healthy life hacks, recipes, workouts, behind the scenes. You find
healthy life hacks, recipes, behind the scenes stuff for Dr Oz. Moments, collaborations with
some of your favorite stars, and lots more. Plus I'll be answering your health questions that
I don't get to discuss on the show. So submit yours in the comments on my Facebook page or
on Twitter with hashtag ask Oz. You can subscribe right here with hashtag your health
questions that I don't get to discuss. Your health questions that I don't get to discuss on
the show. To submit yours. Come on guys. Give me a break. Update my Facebook. No,
I'm gonna delete that Facebook. I'm gonna push the red button on that thing.
What's the next big thing that's gonna come along? Is it TikTok? I feel like that already
happened. Did TikTok take our children away from Facebook? Or is it Discord that took our
children away from Facebook? What's the second internet? I missed TikTok's birth and death.
I, yeah, I, I thought I, when I always thought of TikTok, I thought TikTok was
Vine. But then I was shown videos of what TikTok is. And it's people, people lip-syncing
for like eight seconds. And that's it. It's like Vine, but you lip-sync for like eight seconds.
It's just, it's a shittier Vine for Gen Z. It's Evil Vine. Evil, Evil Vine.
Why does that sound so funny? Vine was Gen Zoomer though. Well, why did they need another
one? Oh, it's because they deleted Vine. That's right. They deleted Vine and then Vine,
then TikTok took all the Vine kids, right? Oh, fuck. All I remember from TikTok is people
sending me videos of everybody having like vampire teeth. I swear, I think I have been shown
10 or 12 TikTok videos. And I think eight of them, they had vampire teeth. I'm just,
I'm just telling you just anecdotal things. Zoomers can't stay with something for more
than a couple of months. It's because they're fucking always moving. Vampires are normie.
Their brains are too small. What the fuck? Why? That's not, hey, wow.
We found the boomer. We found the boomer. I, you guys call me boomer.
Zoomers, yeah, sure. Their brains are all so small. All they do is drink fucking
Mountain Dew, game fuel, and floss and watch TikTok. That actually, is that what you do?
Is that what, that's what actually happens? Kind of. No, I'm talking about teeth. Like they
floss their teeth. Boomers don't floss their teeth. Neither do millennials. Zoomers are flossing
their teeth. That's one thing you got to remember. That's important. Mine is too beyond
that. That was funny. Anyways, thank you The Yellowist for the $5. Thank you, Yellowist.
Hey, Germo. There was a huge gap around 2016 where I couldn't find you in YouTube and didn't
know you made the jump to Twitch. So there was a ton of old content I missed, but I found them
recently. Just the streams in their entirety. So I'm going to get watching. PSU Sorcerer
streams were amazing. You got a lot, you got a lot of stuff to watch. Because unlike YouTube,
which was, you know, six to 12 minute videos, there are lots of five to 10 hour long streams.
You have hundreds of potential, hundreds of hours of stuff to go through. And you're going
to see some of the best fucking content you've seen in a decade. You thought Auto's Big Adventure
was good? Just wait till you see The Sims 4. You thought that GTA 4, One Day I'll Die
From Laughter, you think that was a good video? Just wait until you see the family dinner stream.
You thought, in your head, in your own mind, you thought that Breakfast with Doofus and Goofus
was a good video? Just wait until you get to the video content live demand of me playing
with the Nintendo Labo. I don't want to spoil anything for you, but you've got some good
things to catch up on. Maybe skip that one. No. No skip. But thank you, Yellowist. Welcome
back. Glad you could find me again. Don't watch the Skate 3 one, though. You'll come
across it and then like think I'm a bad person. Daft Skeletor. $30. No message,
but just a lot of money tonight and community subs. Thank you, Daft Skeletor
for your large, large amounts of money and your community subs. High, high contributions.
Thank you. It means a lot. And we had Atomic Fox for $15. Thank you, Atomic Fox for the
15 bucks. They say Pride. Jerma, happy Pride from a big gay. Been watching you a long time.
I don't have a lot of money, but I hope this is something. Gay Rides. Happy Pride Month.
Thank you so much for the $15. And you've been watching for a long time.
Thanks a lot. From a big gay. Thank you. $15. Big Gay Al. I forgot about Big Gay Al.
Jerma lied about the Clown Car. 5 community subs. Adventure MF Dan. 5 community subs.
Thank you. There were a lot of 5 drops tonight for community subs. You guys are awesome.
Thank you. Thank you Trampston for the $5. Local little man gets wallowed by his own
colon on stream in a fit of rage. Were you meant to say swallowed? Thank you for the $5.
Jerma lied about 5k subs. Thanks for the $2.60. Thanks a lot. Thanks for the $2.60.
I didn't lie. I just said I'm not doing it. That's not a lie. That's just me saying no.
I'm not going to do it. I mean is it a lie? No. Go back and watch it and get the whole
context there. Thank you Night Team for the $10 Night Team. I was excited to play Clone
Heroes today but the adapter that came today didn't work. So I have to wait 10 plus more days
for a new one. 10 days? In 2019? What's up with that? Glad you came back to stream.
Glad you came to stream to a now not so disappointing day. Hope you get better soon
Jerma Hart. Thank you. Thanks for the $10. And I'm doing pretty good. I'm still a little
crampy. I'll be fine. I'll be good. Thanks for the $10 Night Team. A wild Meryl thanks
for the $15. Just show love. Show love, show love, show love. Thanks for the 15 bucks.
No message. Thank you so much. A wild Meryl. Meryl. Thank you. Freudian Weapon thanks for
the $2.50 Freudian. Hey Jerma. Glad to hear everything went well. Good to have you back.
Try not to over exert yourself too much. It could be a real pain in the ass.
Sorry bad joke. Please don't ban me. Ban that guy. Thank you for the $2.50. Appreciate it.
Abomination Zero thanks for the $5. I was having a really really rough night but you
made it a lot better. Glad you could stream. Love you man. Thank you.
Sorry to hear you're not having a good night. Hopefully it gets better.
Thank you so much for the $5 and I really hope that you night really turns around. Thank you
Abomination Zero for the $5. Coconut Sales EO thanks for the $2.65. Hey Jerma. Worry not.
One more inch sir. I've bought one of your shirts. Thanks for the opportunity to buy one.
I just wanted to say after purchasing it I'm thoroughly impressed. Impressed sorry I meant
depressed. I used to be happy. Well you don't have the shirt yet so hopefully when
it gets there you'll be very happy about your purchase. Thank you for the $2.65. If
you bought a shirt I hope you love it because they are high quality. Very very competitively
priced but very good. You're gonna love it. But thank you. Hey Vilemi thanks for the $25.
$25 from Vilemi. Hey Jerma now that you're done with the colonoscopy you can finally
get back to chugging Mountain Dew like the gamer god that you are. Here's some bits so
you can stock up on that gamer brew I know you're craving. No I'm not gonna drink that
shit. Thank you for the $25 Vilemi. But I mean technically I probably could drink it but I'm
not going to. Hey FlyingPixels thanks for the $15.02. Much love to you and chat. Y'all are
awesome. I agree. Thanks for the $15 and yeah we got a pretty good chat here. We have some
pretty fun people here. Asana Genova thanks for the $3. I know it doesn't really fit with
the thematic of the channel but I made this hypothetical germ of room emote. Hope you like
it. It looks like a like a video game like go kart character. He's so cute. It's like the
Baron. I really appreciate it. Unfortunately there already is a germ of room emote that
is going to be coming very soon. Thank you so much for that though. It's very cute. It's
very nice. We actually have a lot of things coming. Bloor Dau is currently very hard at
work making a lot of new shit. There's going to be like five to ten new emotes. There's going
to be a bunch of new music. There's going to be a bunch of new stuff. Some new screens,
new animations. It's coming out. Bloor Dau is currently in the process of doing it now.
New music. Oh yeah there's going to be like 10 to 15 new tracks. I'm not making that up.
That's real. Jerma did not lie about Bloor Dau making 15 new music tracks.
I did just say 15 but it's like 10 maybe 12 maybe. It's going to be good stuff. But
thank you Sun of Genova. That's a very very cute emote. I love the scarf. Why don't we get a
Jerma popcorn? Like dog popcorn? Let's get the subs on the screen. Thank you everybody for
your subs. Here come the credits. We were actually, me and Bloor Dau were actually
talking about this. About how to change the credits a little bit maybe. Make them some
maybe more interesting. Change them up so it's not just a scrolling text. We might try to do
something with it. Should be fun. See if it's something we can do. But these are all subs
and wow there's a lot. There's a lot of reason. I guess I haven't been around for like four
days huh? Thanks everybody. Thank you. I know that you know some of you guys only have
like a few subscriptions. Some of you guys only have one sub that you do. Whether it's
like Prime or just a regular sub. And a lot of you guys have been subbed for a
just concurrently for a long long fucking time. So thank you for choosing me. If you do,
thank you. Because there are a lot of other people that stream on this platform so
I'm honored to have the people that sub to this channel sub. Thank you. We have a
couple more bits to do. We have five dollars from iCain, iCainling, iCain. I'm just gonna call you
iCain. My brain is having trouble. You can propose- I don't want to see spoilers. I don't
want to see season three spoilers for Sam and Max. I don't want to see spoilers for Sam and
Max season three. They say Max is extremely hot and if any of you disagree you're lying to
yourself. I'm just gonna fucking Homer Simpson into the bush. Because I don't- I can't- Thank
you for the five dollars. Dragon breath 75 thanks for the 250. Hey Jerma, I wanted to bring up
something about what it was like for me on the anesthetic. Reminder, I'm the guy that was
blabbering your name after my wisdom teeth removal. I do remember that video. It was very
funny. While I was out of it, I swear I had a dual personality experience. The voice in my
head sounded like me talking normal and I was yelling at myself to say normal things but
nothing came out right. Did you have any experience like that with your colonoscopy?
No I was completely- I was completely aware of all the things that I was saying and doing.
I have had that experience before on a different anesthesia where before getting
the IV, I remember saying to myself, oh I really hope I don't say anything stupid or
funny. Don't say anything dumb. Don't say anything funny. Don't say anything stupid.
And as I was getting the medicine and I started to kind of go out, I said to the person that was
administering it, hey do people say anything funny on this? And they told me to stop talking.
They were like stop talking, stop. Your brain's weird. It does just strange things. Yeah I was
told to stop. I was actually told to shut up by the person that was doing it because I was
just so- I was floating out of existence and the one thing that I thought to say was,
hey do people ever say anything funny on this? Because I was over and over again telling my brain
not to say anything funny. So I was trying to pretend to be completely with it for some reason.
Like hey do people ever say anything funny on this? Because I'm not going to say anything
funny because I just told myself not to say anything funny. It probably came out really
fucked up. Yeah it was probably really embarrassing and so was me telling the nurse
that this is not my first rodeo when I'm trying to put my shoes on and almost put
my head through the drywall. Brain altering, brain chemistry altering drugs, hard drugs like that,
just fucking turn you upside down. You didn't hear that part? I told the story at the beginning
of the stream. But I remember everything. I remember waking up. The last thing I remember,
I remember on my side, because you have to lie on your side when they do the colonoscopy,
and the guy said, hey you're gonna feel like a sting in your arm. It's pretty,
it's normal. That's what happens right before and I felt a little sting and then I woke up.
So but when I woke up I was completely aware. It's not like oh I have no idea about anything
I said. I was completely aware of where I was and what I was saying, but I was still saying
fucking dumb shit. And the nurse came in and was talking to me and I kept on talking about
how great of a practice it was. And you guys are all pros. You guys are all pros. You guys
are pros. Let me tell you. I may have, I don't, I have this weird half memory of saying this.
I might not have, but maybe I did. That I was going to give like a Yelp review.
Can you even give a Yelp review for a hospital? Is that even possible? I guess,
yeah, I guess it is. The cafeteria. I give review for like getting like surgery and it's
like the cafeteria in the hospital. Everyone there was a pro. The colonoscopy was fantastic.
The doctors were so nice. The nurse when they were doing the IV and it's like,
uh dude, how was like the, how was the fucking toast? What are you talking about?
But yeah, I almost fell down like three times putting my shoes on.
I was trying so hard to be normal. That's the worst part because you know you're so fucked up.
You know you're on hard drugs and you are so desperate to be normal. You're doing,
you're trying so hard that you try too hard and you do something stupid. And then in
your brain you go, a normal person wouldn't do what I just did. I have to correct this.
Hey, don't worry. This ain't my first rodeo. I have to correct that. And I,
normal people don't say that either. You completely go over what a normal person does.
But the thing is I was, that was not incorrect. This ain't my first rodeo. I've had two
sigmoidoscopies. So maybe my brain was saying like, no, no, it's fine. I've had this done
like before. Or the nurse probably thought I was talking about how I do drugs all the time.
Right? Like we talked about in the beginning of the stream. Sir, sir, sir, please sit down.
Please. No, no, this ain't my first rodeo. I do drugs every day. Oh, oh, okay. They have
both of those scenarios work. Yeah. But yes, Dragon Breath, that is, drugs are fucking
ridiculous. I don't do them. I don't like doing them. Rock Esper, thanks for the 250.
Random question, but I've just been curious. Many streams back, you mentioned listening to
the Lost Odyssey OST in your car. Do you like that game? Because it's one of my all-time
favorites. Also, you're cute. Yes. I told you, yeah, I did tell that story about how
I had some like people that I worked with. There were some acquaintances that were in
my car and I was driving people home and stuff. And I was playing that. And they
thought I was fucking crazy. Lost Odyssey OST. Remember, this is more than, this is like 15
years ago. Can you think of anyone in your entire life that would have the Lost Odyssey
OST in their car in the CD player? Besides me and besides you. That's why it was so
embarrassing because it's just like, I don't know, maybe like part of it was trying to
seem like interesting or something. Hey, what music is, what are you gonna put on? Oh,
put this on, I guess. Look at how interesting I am. Oh, you're listening to like
classical music. No, it's video game music. Oh, look at how interesting you are. Yeah,
I am. Maybe part of me like thought that was what I was doing. I listened to OST. Yeah,
well, not 2019. This is a different time. Back in like, back in like 2003,
there wasn't like Overwatch costumes at the spirit of Halloween stores.
You know what I'm saying? This is like before, this is before games were like cool.
This is back in the day where video games were still kind of like video games.
Well, what's a PC gaming? I've heard of that. So like listening to like a video game OST in
your car now is like, oh, whatever. But in 15 years ago, it was kind of like, why are
you doing this? Back in my day, we had put you know, 15, not 50, 15. But did you Oh,
yeah, let me answer the question. Did you like the game? Oh, yeah, I did. I liked the
combat system in that game. I thought it was engaging. It wasn't just put cursor on this
person and let them get hit. I liked the timed hits. I'm a huge fan of Super Mario RPG and in a
traditional turn based RPG that gives you some kind of control. I like better than just putting
a cursor on somebody. timed hits are more fun for me because it engages me in the game.
Yeah, I thought it was good. I was sad to see that they weren't going to do anything more
with that franchise or that series. Because it wasn't um, what's the designer's name,
he was commissioned to do two or three games for the Xbox. And then that was it.
And there was talk that he might do another one, but never came out never happened.
The same guy that did Blue Dragon, right? Blue was Blue Dragon, right? Am I thinking
of the right thing? Am I excited for cooking simulator tomorrow? Oh, hell yeah. So yeah,
I did want to see another installment in the series. I thought if they had a second go at
it, they could have improved on some of the things that I didn't like it made a better
game. And, you know, I think it was like a solid game to begin with. But yeah,
but thank you for the 250 Rock Esper creamy sensation. Thanks for the $5. Appreciate it.
No message. Thank you. Sergio, but thanks for the 250. I've been under a few times
and each time has been such a trip. I had a liver biopsy at like 17. And I was still
young enough to be in the pediatric hospital. So I came to just slurring. Oh,
fuck, that feels so weird. I can't even feel my eyes yet. God damn it. Next to a five-year-old
playing on his iPad. Oh, that's a good, that's a good story. That was a good story.
Oh, fuck, this feels so weird. Thank you for the 250 Sergio, but and then Space Dad rules.
Thanks for the $15 right at the very end. They say, I love you. Thank you. Space Dad rules
15 bucks. Not even a minute ago. Thank you so much. And that's going to be it for tonight.
I will see you guys. I will see you guys tomorrow. Tomorrow is going to be a new game
called on this show. That's not the name of the game. The game is going to be called
Cooking Simulator. I'm going to show you some healthy recipes that you can have in your home
with low spices. I promise on the next Actas. Maybe the whole stream is Dr. Roz. Okay. If I
didn't, if I didn't say anything, if I just, if I talked like that, just from the beginning
of the stream, people would be fucking so irritated by that. I think if I didn't like
make it a joke, if I was just doing that, I would give that like 15 to 20 minutes before people
were like, stop doing this. Stop fucking doing that. Why are you doing that? And I just didn't,
it would, I would get too self-conscious and have to stop it unless it was like a very
specific bit or routine that I was planning or doing. I couldn't talk like Dr. Oz during the
whole stream. You say you think that would be funny, but after five minutes, let's see.
Dr. Oz for Jerma Rumble. Okay. Yeah. Yup. Oh, you better fucking believe it. I swear to God.
I swear to God. Yes. I'm seeing a lot of nos. Yes. I don't care. Dr. Oz is going to be like
in the next ladder match. You heard it here first. It's going to happen. This is a one-off
joke. Yes. I know. So the 13, 1400 people here, you're the only people that are going to
think this is funny. No one else is going to know what this is. And that's, I don't care.
That's fine. And scan his face and like put it in. People are going to be like, why is Dr. Oz
here? Do you watch Dr. Oz? The only way that would be possible is if I watched Dr. Oz every
day. And I like was a fan. I'll just pretend to be a fan. Yeah. That sounds about right.
Now. Yeah. Now I got to watch Dr. Oz to get some info so I can make some
interesting references. I'm going to do some Dr. Oz research. Yeah. I got to find out
what kind of shirts he wears, the pants he wears. All right. I'll see you guys tomorrow. Have a good
rest of your night. But hold on. Moo means Moo just came with five dollars. Moo means Moo hospital
Yelp review. They got my order wrong. I went in for blood work and they took out a kidney
instead. Terrible service. One star. Thank you Moo. All right. See you guys tomorrow.
Cooking simulator. Should be fun. Take care. Have a great rest of your night.