Uh, good evening, or good morning, for some of you.
Ahem.
I was gonna stream tomorrow, the Resident Evil 4 Remake.
But, very big but, I thought the game was coming out tomorrow afternoon.
I was ready and prepared for the game to launch tomorrow at like 1pm Pacific.
But, it's out right now.
Came out like 30-40 minutes ago. 9pm?
That's pretty reasonable.
And I'm very excited.
So let's, let's go quietly, cause it's a little late.
Let's go.
Probably gonna be playing this well into the night here.
You're supposed to be asleep?
I hope you have a good rest.
It came out five hours ago in Canada.
Well, I don't live in Canada.
I live in, uh, people lost me.
Took a little bit to download. There was no preload.
Which, is a little surprising.
Usually, day before, two days before a game usually have a preload, but it's fine.
Had to start downloading it at exactly 9pm.
But, I'm very excited for this.
And I'm gonna tell you how excited I am, because this is a different scenario.
Resident Evil 2 Remake, one of my favorite games.
For sure.
Resident Evil 3 Remake, not so much.
It was alright.
But, I've heard really great things about this one.
Resident Evil 4 on its own.
The original one is probably one of the best games ever made.
It's definitely, I would say, deserves to be in the top 10, top 25.
So, let's do it.
I haven't looked at very much info of this.
I know there was a demo. I didn't play it.
There's been videos and comparison footage. I haven't seen it.
I've seen maybe one minute of footage of this game.
There's an FOV slider.
So, don't worry.
I'm not gonna stay, I'm not gonna freak out.
There is an FOV slider in the game.
So, we can relax on that.
I have adjusted it accordingly.
And I don't want to waste any time because other streamers are going faster than me.
So, I have to hurry up.
I got the, I got the deluxe version.
I don't know. It said there was like extra stuff and I was like, should I get it?
I don't know.
I got it.
Now, the weird, this is gonna get really weird.
And I'm kind of concerned.
I don't know what difficulty to pick because I don't think you can change it.
But anyways, yes, I can confirm.
The lights are off.
Lights are off.
Scary.
This is a scary game.
Lights are off.
I'm not playing on the like super difficulty, no way.
All right, so let's go.
Main story, I'm playing keyboard.
Although maybe it's not a good idea.
You can now change character costumes and accessories in these.
Should I like go do that?
You can change the, you can now change the original music slash sound effects.
You guys can't even hear it.
Okay.
Extras.
Leon's costume.
Okay.
Of which one of these am I gonna, I feel like this is gonna fuck the whole game up.
You know what I mean?
I don't know if I want to do that.
I feel like it's gonna change everything.
Won't it change everything?
I'm just gonna go normal for now.
All right, we're gonna go normal.
Accessories.
How about sunglasses?
That's like a remake thing to put on, right?
Okay.
I'm gonna stay with the defaults.
What is that?
What is the hero filter?
It's just they took the gamma slider and dragged it all the way over.
Original music?
I don't know.
How should I experience this?
Default A and D.
I can change this later.
I'll be all right.
I can change it later.
Why are you so nervous?
I've been looking forward to this game for a long time.
I'm like, I love Resident Evil 4.
And 5.
I'm like, let's go.
I'm so excited.
All right, let's just go.
We're gonna go with the remake.
I want to be able to give you a real review.
So none of this, we're gonna keep all this off.
I'm not nervous.
What are you talking about?
Are you guys ready?
Resident Evil 4 remake.
Okay, this is the problem.
I'm not gonna do this one.
Standard.
For players who have not played Resident Evil 4 in 2005.
Okay, this changes to easy if you die at game over or whatever.
For players who have played Resident Evil 4 in 2000.
I have played Resident Evil 4.
Does that mean I have to pick this difficulty?
Stronger enemies and harder challenges.
Higher prices for certain items.
How, this is the problem with Resident Evil games though.
How much harder is this than standard?
Because I can't change this.
And I don't want to get somewhere and be like, what a fucking disaster.
How much harder is it than standard?
It's about two and a half times harder.
Moderately.
Don't do it.
How would we know?
It's too hard.
Find out.
All right.
How about this?
If the game is too, I can't like restart it.
I'm just gonna do standard, right?
Like what, I don't care.
I don't, I think once you cross, I think once you cross 35 years old,
I can pay, I can pick this.
You know what I mean?
I can pick that.
When you go, when you're over 35, you can pick standard.
That's fine.
And like, oh, come on.
Like, ah, yeah, that's fine.
You're over 35.
Yeah, we're good.
I'm almost 40.
I can pick that one.
The expanded treasure map has been applied.
Okay, what does that even mean?
You can see the locations of hidden treasures?
All right, everybody quiet.
Blood.
September 30th, 1998.
It's a day I'll never forget.
The cop inside me died that day.
That night, Raccoon City was wiped out.
Thanks to the bioweapons created by Umbrella.
Somehow I made it out, but too many others weren't so lucky.
This is Resident Evil 2, by the way.
I was asked later to join a top secret government program.
Not that I had a choice.
The training.
Punishing the missions.
Nearly killed me.
But at least I kept my mind off everything.
If I could just forget what happened that night.
Even for a second.
This time.
It can be different.
It has to.
Okay.
Waiting for this game.
For at least two or three days.
So tell me Yankee.
Why did you come to this horrible place close to nowhere that
I've ever seen?
Let's just say that someone must be very important.
The chief gave the orders himself.
Help him.
Not very sunny right now.
I'm sure your boys didn't come all the way out here to roast
marshmallows.
You have a strange sense of humor.
I'm going to let you in on a little secret.
Just between us.
It's quiet.
Seems like it's kind of loud.
And it's been that way for a while now.
Should be just another day in the office, right?
Gonna get loud just to give you a warning.
I mean last week there was a search for some missing hikers.
I'm sure you'll do your best to help me.
It's like Duke Nukem Netflix adaptation is because the glasses
because the glasses that's what you're saying.
Nature calls him.
I'll be right back.
That was pretty good first look.
So that's it.
I'll see you guys tomorrow.
We'll pick it up right where we left off.
I think.
Just want to get a good feel for the very beginning and see
how it was.
The opening cutscene to me is very important.
I need to kind of digest it for a day or two.
I'd say maybe three or four days.
I need to kind of relax on the couch for a little while and
kind of process everything.
So and about yeah, it's going to be probably a few days.
He sure is taking his time.
Did he fall in?
Maybe you better go and take a look.
I want to take the glasses off.
It's ruining my remake.
It's ruining my immersion in the remake.
So much for helping me.
Here we go.
It looks pretty good.
How does it run though?
Hold on.
How does it run?
That seems it seems pretty clean actually.
I'm so glad I could turn the FOV up as well.
It seems pretty clean.
Wait, there's a jump scare right now isn't there?
Yeah, there is just to give a quick warning for everybody.
Birds fly down and scare you in like five seconds.
From what I remember.
How far could you have gone?
In three, two, one, cue the birds.
Cue the, the birds are coming soon.
I need to change that.
Sorry.
Give me one second.
E and F always need to be flipped for me.
I don't I don't know what happened in the last five years
of gaming but F replaced E for some reason and I've been
trying to figure out why for a long time.
F replaced E and it was always E and I think it's because
E started to become lean.
I wanted E.
Sorry.
Knife and parry.
That's fine.
Space.
Pick up item.
Examine F.
No, it's E.
And melee is mouse button.
Reload.
That's fine being R.
Isn't already knife.
Okay.
Attach remove mines.
G is fine.
Move backwards.
Move camera.
Run and shift.
That's fine.
Crouch stand evade is C.
Come on.
What year is it?
How can we change these things?
Even staples for years.
Or control, right?
What is control in the game?
Command Ashley.
Oh, okay.
C.
All right, we're good.
Unable to apply some changes.
Wait, what?
What was wrong?
I don't know.
Make this like...
No, stop.
I don't know.
Make this like Y.
We're good.
Cut it out.
E.
There it is.
And then melee.
There we go.
We're good.
Oh, no, that wasn't it.
Wasn't that it?
That was fucking pretty scary.
I remember this house.
I wonder how much of this I truly remember because it's
It's actually been a really long time.
The last time I actually played for Resident Evil 4.
I mean, it has to be
10 years.
Has to be 10 years.
Maybe a little less.
Maybe I don't know.
Maybe a little more.
It looks great though.
I'm so glad I avoided all the footage.
Anyone home?
Might be a little too loud.
But it's okay.
We'll figure that out.
What's that?
Should I pretend like I've never played this before?
That's probably a good idea, right?
Just like pretend like I've never played this.
Isn't that that the YouTube video will be so much better?
And I'll get so many more engagements.
This place looks so much different now.
It's crazy.
This feels like a different game.
Even though I know it's not.
Sorry to barge in like this.
Say it.
Do it.
We're all waiting for it.
That's loud.
Sorry, I'll fix it.
Okay.
Important.
I know people...
I know I'm breaking your immersion and breaking my immersion,
but we got to get this right.
I am a toggle
aim down sights person.
Now,
I don't...
I know that
offends a lot of people probably,
but I don't care.
Is it in the game?
Cursor lock.
Control...
No.
Auto reload.
I actually don't like that very much.
I don't like that either.
But I'm going to do it.
Aim assist off.
Where would it be?
But aim assist is off.
You're literally a psycho.
What?
Is there a toggle aim down sights?
It's in the camera settings.
Okay.
Oh, right here.
Hold on a minute.
When aiming,
this is camera inversion.
Field of view.
Where is it?
Is it here?
Field of view.
Camera sensitivity.
Camera inversion.
Camera acceleration.
Camera speed.
Does anyone know where it is?
Then controls.
Accessibility maybe?
Control type.
Quick turn type.
Crouch.
Type is toggle.
Repeated input.
Oh, you got a toggle for crouch, but no toggle for...
Really?
Oh, come on.
Play.
I, I, this is how I like to play.
Is it actually not in the game?
Two to the right.
Down three in camera.
Aim.
Wait.
Whatever.
I'll deal with it.
That's all right.
This sensitivity has to come way up, but...
And I'm going to fix it.
You do your settings.
I couldn't get in here and do this before because the preload,
there's no preload.
And there, just wait.
Sensitivity.
Is it camera speed?
These, these settings are kind of confusing.
That's better.
All right.
I might fix it later, but we're going to see.
Man, that stinks.
Those were controller settings.
Turn up the FOV.
FOV is at the highest it can go.
I think it's a good spot.
All right.
HUD looks good.
Yeah.
Okay.
Let's go.
Leon's jacket would be way too big for you.
So order me a small.
Of what?
I, you can't, oh, you can't get me a small police jacket?
What are you talking about?
Why, why would I put on somebody else's jacket?
Creepy.
Not extra small.
I'm a men's small to medium.
Don't change that.
This game is fucked up.
There's no way you're a small.
I'm a, I am a, I'm a men's small.
It depends.
Hey, here it comes.
I read you.
Let me sip my tea before we get into this.
What's your situation?
Take the glasses off.
I, not yet.
I'll leave them for one more cut scene.
This is way scarier.
Ah, see before I could kind of, I could hide behind the
fact that it was the graphics weren't, I mean, the graphics
were good at the time.
But if you go back and play the old resume before it's
like, oh, okay.
Like this current gen graphics makes this way scarier.
I don't know why it just does quiet.
I'm so glad I didn't play on the fucking hardcore.
I'm so glad I didn't play on hardcore.
Wait, how do I do it?
Oh, it's a, it's mouse button.
It's mouse button.
It's a mouse button to do the melee execute, right?
So glad I'm not playing on a fucking hardcore.
When you're 35 and older, you can pick this.
Once you drop out of that, okay, any bracket that says,
Hey, how old are you?
What is your, what age are you in?
You know, it's usually 18 to 34, right?
The second that you go over 35 plus, like when you go to
the next bracket, just pick the regular difficulties.
There's no reason to.
Was there anything else in here that I needed?
You've changed.
Yeah, I fucking aged.
You are correct.
You are.
You are absolutely correct.
I have changed to very, I have changed a lot in the last
10 to 20 plus years.
I'm a little older now.
Hey, you kids don't even know.
Don't you have to pull bookcases and stuff?
Are you, I don't want to spoil it for anybody, but
I'm trying to remember how this plays out.
How many bullets left?
Take the glasses off.
Bruce, this is Gondor one.
Hunnigan here.
What's your sit rep?
President's daughter, baby Eagle.
It's likely she's in this village.
Our Intel was correct then.
Well done.
Need a location on a nearby lake.
We'll do comedy mode later.
Copy that.
I'll see what I can find.
Something's happened to people here.
My escorts are.
The audio is so much.
They spent a lot of time on the audio.
I don't have any bullets.
Did I pick hardcore?
I wanted to look directly into the camera and go.
Wouldn't put a stair though.
Boom, big music cue.
You know what I mean?
Just how we know what game we're playing.
Glasses off.
No, the glass is staying on.
For at least 10 to 20 more minutes.
That crow.
Raven was as big as a dog.
I think.
Yeah, it's E.
Yep.
Handgun ammo.
Good.
Gonna need a lot of that.
What do I want to upgrade though?
That's the thing.
I always pick something different.
Okay, save it.
And attach it.
Case has been added to the customized case menu.
Charm has been added to the customized case menu.
Deluxe weapon has been added to the menu.
Okay.
This is cheating.
Is this isn't this?
I have two free weapons.
This is cheating.
I got the deluxe edition.
I'm a big fan.
So what we don't have to use it.
I just I'm a big fan.
So I got the deluxe edition.
I won't use it.
We need to stay true to the original and I'm going to be
I'm going to have a gold case because that's I think that's kind of cool.
Increased drop rate.
Wait, this is cheating.
Increased drop rate for gunpowder increased drop rate.
Wait, wait, this is the actual case does this too.
Is this new?
I don't remember this.
Well those bonuses in the regular game.
I would I'd rather the handgun ammo.
Okay, very good.
Continue.
Ooh, very nice.
This is the village part, isn't it?
All right.
This is the first real test that handgun ammo.
Thank you.
Do I even have the knife yet?
I don't think I do.
That's money.
Whoo.
All right.
So that's how you do the execute.
Okay.
All right.
That's how you do the execute.
So you're going to knock him down then go over and stab them on the ground.
Very cool.
These people were friendly.
I forgot these existed.
I forgot.
I think it's been 10 years since I played this.
Oh my god.
Somebody there are herbs in this game.
You got to combine them, right?
Or did they streamline that somehow?
Flash grenade.
Change weapon.
Okay.
Yep.
Cool.
I'm going to save all those to the end of the game and throw them all
at the t-virus whatever it is.
So I'm going to make sure I probably will have like 30 or 40 flashbangs
at the end of the game.
Which is fine.
Looks great.
Cool.
I'm coming.
Why not?
Oh my god.
That's the worst place for that to be on my thumb button.
Oh fuck.
You're doing it hard to suppress this.
Shit.
I suck.
What's quick turn?
It's Q.
Ow.
Yep.
You're fucked bro.
No, I'm fine.
I'm fine.
This is so much scarier than the other one.
It feels like two.
It feels like more real somehow.
I don't know why it just does.
Oh shit.
Oh my god.
This is not one of these guys in the original.
Wait, was there?
Oh shit.
Whoa.
Get out of my way.
I should have picked the system.
That was my fault.
Oh my god.
That's so much worse.
I need ammo.
Get the fuck out of my way.
Oh shit.
I have to change this key vine.
Oh, oh.
How do I do it?
Five.
Press five.
How do I do it?
Why can't I throw the grenade?
Oh fuck all of you in there.
Give me that.
I need that money.
Oh shit.
What?
Get away from me.
Ow.
I need more healing.
How do I win?
Don't you?
There it is.
Okay.
I was saying what the fuck?
I was like you got to just live man.
I was going to say.
I feel like that took longer.
That was so terrifying.
It's so much worse now.
I got to collect all those items.
Jeez.
Where's everyone going?
Bingo.
That was awesome.
That was actually really cool.
I very very vividly remember this part, but
wow, that was
that was something else.
All right.
So the issue it's you have to get to here and then press five.
It's not you don't just press five.
Wait, I can just press five.
Why wasn't this?
That wasn't working before kind of panicking.
All right.
Let me explore first.
I'm not doing good.
Copy that.
I look like shit.
Okay, good.
Map.
You could become lost.
You can check your map position and objectives on the map.
You have a treasure map.
You'll be able to see the locations of hidden valuables.
That's cool.
I love these games.
No, don't throw that.
Reload the gun.
Ah, you take some ibuprofen or something the shotgun.
Oh, nice.
Nice.
Even if I take ibuprofen, it's gonna take like 45 minutes for it to
kick in.
Okay, I actually I am going to heal.
Item crafting certain materials such as resources, gunpowder and knives
can be used to craft different items.
The types of items that you can craft can be increased by obtaining
new crafting recipes.
This wasn't in the old one, was it?
Maybe it was handgun and was it?
What is that a burrito?
What is that thing?
I know just wait till you can do complete herbs.
I don't know.
I doesn't matter.
I don't care.
I should probably put I'm just gonna do this.
Whatever.
I should assign this.
Oh, you can't.
Cool.
I'm gonna explore a little bit.
I don't want to forget anything.
I don't want to leave anything and I know because everyone this is
a beloved video game and everybody's played probably five times
each all of us.
I'm gonna miss a treasure and it's gonna be spam in my chat people
screaming at me because I missed it.
So I'm gonna do my best.
Very good.
I know that there's they put the treasure on the map now.
So there's one in here.
I had never played this before.
I'm not 37.
That's true for some of you.
Maybe this is hurt.
No, I'm good.
All right.
So the treasures in here covered maybe.
No, how's the audio and visual?
Is it brightness?
You're blocking your health and ammo with your face cam.
Oh, that's gonna be fixed.
Is that better?
That's better, right?
It's a little too dark because I thought it was a little too dark
when I was doing the initial setup.
So I'm probably gonna turn it up a little bit if I do that.
Good luck finding that.
I don't have super resolution on my way.
I was there.
I missed it.
Okay.
Yeah, I see we'll go like we'll go up to the middle.
I think that's looks good.
The better it was a little better.
I don't have a key for this.
All right.
There's one more over here, but it's a locked door so I can't
get in up that it shows everything on the map.
Now that's actually incredibly useful.
All right.
Where did I throw that grenade?
Because I want to go in that room.
Who's in here?
These people are sick.
All right.
So this is where I threw the grenade in here and there was a
bunch of shit on the ground.
Okay, nice.
Oh, think of that's everything.
Now.
I'm not going to get everything.
I'm not going to get everything people might expect.
Why do you not going to get everything?
I'm not going to get everything.
One more spot to look is in here.
I can I go in here yet?
I cannot.
This is a little bit later.
Get everything.
I'm not going to get everything.
I know.
No, I'm going to go up here and look.
Can you please not stream till 3 a.m.
Again?
Oh, I can't promise you anything.
All right.
So over here, there's a treasure.
My whole body hurts.
Everything hurts.
I just like had a heart attack in one second.
That's I don't remember that happening.
Ooh.
Yep.
You get gems.
You combine them.
So the worth way more.
All right.
I think we've got everything we needed from here.
It's time to continue the playthrough.
Bloody Vamo like did everything.
Now we have to go back this way.
Right?
I don't remember this.
I don't remember that.
Did I get everything in here Ruby?
That wasn't even on the map and I got it.
Please don't spend all the treasure you get on that family
guy mobile game app.
I can't promise that either.
I drank all my tea already.
Must be a stressful game.
All the tea is gone.
I'm going to get a refill already.
There it is.
I got to be way more conservative with shooting our resources.
There we go.
Now I can make some bullets if I want to go.
It says standard, but I might be a bug in the game because
I picked hardcore before starting.
So the game is hardcore.
I think it's on hardcore, but just kind of says it isn't
as I think it's a known bug.
So how much better is this than the other shotgun?
Can I look at the damage on it?
Who cares?
I'm going to use it.
Fuck it.
Why not?
That's my hand good made for Leon.
Sentinel nine.
It's cluttered now.
I'll fix it.
This is going to turn into the lawnmower bag when you're done
at the end of the day.
This is kind of just a cut a bunch of cut grass in here.
I'm a cheater.
It's fine.
That's fine.
I'm going to put this on here.
Okay.
Hey, I'm not going to combine any of this.
Yeah, this is fine.
I'm going to put this over on.
Yeah, there we go.
Okay.
This is a good bit.
What's the bit?
I mean, this is I got I got this because I paid an extra $10
for the game.
It's going to be cluttered.
Ah shit.
You're right.
No, whatever.
I don't care.
Not in the very beginning of the game like this.
It's going to be fine.
Let's just test it and see how it is.
If I don't if I like it.
I like it.
Give me that.
There's a jewel right here.
Oops.
Oh eggs.
Thanks for the oh, the deluxe gun is pretty good.
There's a bacon lettuce and tomato on this one.
Blue request notes.
You can take on tasks by collecting the blue request
notes posted around the areas and destroy.
Okay, destroy all the blue medallions.
I've only got three more.
So it's a good question.
Good.
I mean, this ain't a speedrun.
So hold on.
This ain't a speedrun.
Hurry up.
I want to check all this out.
I'm not trying to go as fast as I can.
It even all right.
It shows where they are.
That's useful.
I guess you don't have to really look for
them is just because it's a deluxe treasure map.
You have the cheater map.
It's because you paid for it.
Really?
Is that for real?
I have the cheater map.
Are you serious?
That's actually whatever.
I have the cheater map.
Oh, I do.
Hey, when you get to be 35 and older.
Sorry, you can get the cheater map.
Sorry.
So then that where's this one then?
Up here.
Right there.
So what do I get?
Hey, I got it.
Challenge complete.
I want that.
Where is this lady?
I don't know.
Let's go.
I see it.
Okay.
I know it's pretending that I couldn't see it.
Remember the cheater map just turned this from a 30-hour
playthrough to a 130-hour playthrough.
Kind of true because I'm going to be like, oh look, this
one other go that way and go get that.
I need to look at the map a lot though.
I'm a map user.
Oh, somebody bought the deluxe edition.
Sorry.
Let me see the other deluxe edition.
Oh, you get a gear.
I got to fix everything myself.
Mm-hmm.
Anything else I missed in here?
That is what what does that drop down?
Is that what that's what the chest is, isn't it?
Ask the cheater map.
Maybe it'll know.
Oh, interesting.
Yeah, down here.
Yeah, no, I knew where this was.
I looked at it.
Get the barrels.
I will.
Ooh, nice.
I didn't look at the cheater map for this.
I saw it through the door.
What the fuck was that?
It's a knife.
There's the dog.
Go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go.
Damn.
Get out of here.
Come on.
Come on up.
Get out.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
Oh shit.
Get away from me.
Is he up?
No.
Where is he?
Oh.
Get out of here.
Is he dead?
This guy's still alive.
Nice.
I used a regular guns.
Is it actually safe to go down there?
Ooh, nice.
what are you doing as a popcorn person that person that was fucked that was awful
that person just popped like a kernel what the hell okay was there anything else over here
sure don't miss anything i think we're good okay so now i'm gonna take this
weight there is a treasure over there why am i afraid of chickens no that body popped up
from the ground it's crazy all right um i don't think i can do anything about that right now
i already got that what is this treasure oh it's bad now let's go um i want to get these first
i got some money nothing else oh i could have just walked this way oops oh what i wanted to
explore you got the key from the boss did i what do you mean your opinion equals ignored play on
a real difficulty what are you smoking crack all right here we go why is this guy so oily
i have very perspiring skin it keeps me moisturized plus this light is shining over here
yeah i'm e3 walking that's fine been it's been like 30 years since i've seen this game and i'm
gonna enjoy it so i'm doing it the way i want to go the pace that i'm gonna go and if you don't
like my e3 walking then then you know what um you can i don't know something annoying there we go i
knew it i don't even need to fight you what do i care go the right way over here and then they're
gonna miss every time so who cares oh that was brutal but out of my knife what's wrong with my
knife the knife breaks i didn't know that the way the knife breaks now did it break before i don't
remember that i don't remember this i don't remember this thing i don't know do i remember
this i don't remember it's so dark in here with my flashlight come on leon take it out please point
your flashlight out here oh you have a thing that's gonna explode come on dude did i just
aggro everybody oh no that's not good oh he made the fucking head what was that what did i just do
i just dark souls parried that guy really wait hold on well that's awesome oh wait you can't
parry that's actually really cool what's this somebody's what's that sound what's going on
you hear that right what the shit i have oh grenade stop stop when did where did where did
that come from oh don't where is this lady on the roof you throw that in here i'm gonna be pissed
oh you can actually get it in here okay what is it where are these people
oh what's going on why did i not that was weird get him off me this
fucking thumb i gotta take this off of thumb one i take it off of thumb one i'm sitting there going
like this am i all the way back here dude okay like melee i like it on there though
can i just make it v wait secondary v so i can just go open map is m okay so if i tap
i can tap v pretty quickly then wait one that's okay i gotta what do i hear beeps whoa
why would you throw that over here dude we're fucking dead
put that down oh my eyes hurt ow i blocked it holy shit i'm phenomenal stop wasting someone
okay everybody chill chill out for a second for one second oh my god
i can't be don't back up don't back up if i back up i'm fucking dead
okay jeez i'm gonna eat this egg i have so much bullshit in here i'm gonna make some i like
shotguns so i'm gonna do shotgun ammo oh wait a minute i can do i can combine this so this will
be a suit that's cool that you can do this before you couldn't do it i'm gonna do it because that
would be uh red um green yellow i could do this but i don't think i want to it's always good to do
all of it because when you do all three it increases your max health right yes very important
if you do all three i'm like you guys even see me i'm so dark i like yeah the room can you guys
even see when you can see me all right that should free up some space you know just is this this is
storage right or is this me throwing it on the ground no i know okay i see i see let me get this
right inventory management time this thing is broken so i i know that like people like to say
that however your inventory management is in resident evil games is like you're taking a
meyers briggs personality test so i don't know how well you guys can decipher from this but this is
how i do it auto sort why would i i don't know i want to do it i like it much cleaner looking
much cleaner all right we're good now auto sorted and ruin it so what do i get for personality
what do you think somebody said this is an average tick talker awful normie normie will bring
everything is that true yeah yeah yeah exactly all right don't die this is where i lost before
can i get around there because somebody died up there yes i can good good very good i got a lot
of money all right let's take a look at the cheating menu take something cool over there
that's not hurting me anything back here no got everything it looks really really good i don't
even have every setting turned on either it looks oh i get those glasses off hero filter i imagine
playing with that on the whole game what about the villain filter i just feel like i have low
health that's a nice it's all right but i'm i don't think i'm gonna turn that on
i gotta use q more often the quick turn just saves your life so many times i love the parry
the path all right now i'm understanding we're hardcore could have been all right
the parry is a very interesting just addition anything else i can't open this shoot the water
shoot the water shoot the water shoot the water wait shoot the water why lol lol lol why do i have
all right hold on a second no i i think don't isn't that no no no no no no no no i know i know
and i'm not starting this fucking whole section over again i know what happens i'm not starting
the whole section over you can pet pet laugh all you want i'm not gonna start the whole section
over is there a safe point i'll just for all the people that safe point is so far away i've never
seen it before please just do it wrong spot you're wasting but what do you mean wrong spot it's the
end of the pier it takes 10 shots what are people just making this up this is not even the right
dock is this the wrong dock it might not even be in the remake did i just shoot like 20 bullets
for no reason it's the wrong dock it's the wrong dock wrong lake i didn't need that ammo anyways
who cares it's the wrong game dude you know it's the wrong game no that's i didn't i didn't even
need the bullets i'm fine look it's literally one packet of bullets i'll be fine look already
i just replaced them already everything's fine it's okay i have the delight somebody said to
take the deluxe glasses off that's how i can see everything this is the hud my deluxe glasses
now i can't take them off how do i pull this up reliably i guess i'm all right damn it heck like
all the everywhere isn't there shit under here or something what's that noise that parry is
that parry is so fucking cool what an insane addition they added that's awesome you could
probably play through this whole game and parry you broke the knife again it doesn't matter was
it what it was in the other one i don't know wasn't probably missed a few things but okay
can you parry the chainsaw i that is a great question i have no idea that's a good question
though i'm kind of too afraid to do that it kills you in like one or two hits i need another t
hurts you know it seemed like you really wanted to talk how observant senor now uh say uh you gotta
smoke i know those things will kill you oh maybe just untie me then huh
not this guy who are you just stop right there
oh guys what happened oh my god guys all right give me the results completion points
oh oh oh oh enemies killed 42 one death 71 accuracy that's pretty good i'm gonna take out
some of these other items can i pull the handgun ammo out of this maybe i'll want to use it i mean
if i'm gonna have the dlc glasses on i'm gonna keep you know whatever i need to see what the
power levels are can you see that eventually don't you eventually upgrade and it tells you
how much damage it does check my new examine it sacrificial lamb will receive our most sacred
different voice actor different uh different voice actor stop it name leon take the stupid
glasses off guess you me the wrongest spot to vacation hey hey stop it you move i move
and i'm beat up in office i can see you're thinking bet you've been in spots like this before
i guess you're here looking for someone one more guess maybe some missing senorita young girl
well talk now all right see her chatter about moving senorita i said saw trap where who knows
but later saw some men dragging someone to the old church
hanging with you not help
back
hey we're not done here do you guys think they're gonna remake this game in 20 years what do you
think my gear baby oh they took everything didn't take the glasses condor wonder roost
i've located baby eagle it sounds like she's being kept in some church great that's good news
i heard it from this guy i met said his name is louise sara there's something fishy about him
i need you to run a background check we'll call condor one i'll see what i can find
in the meantime make your way to that church right i'm probably due for confession anyway condor one
out chapter two so i have nothing head for the church i don't want to spoil it or anything
but i don't want to spoil it but what do you mean is that later i feel like that was early like
very beginning what i didn't say anything for those that know i'm just curious where it is
wide sweeping slash attack you can also do the quick stab with while holding space
oh yep the lighting is gorgeous hey that's my gear my stuff i don't know i just was trying to
lock i just tried to lock onto this guy i just was how how do i what's my lock on you have a knife
you can parry yeah yeah yeah yep yep yep time it right wait so this is a prompt i'm just that good
i don't even need the prompt i'm just that good yeah what difficulty you're playing on
it's none of your business i don't want you to see my menu you know what i mean like this is
none of your business okay this is none of your business this is my menu i almost walked in it
i open it from here now check the cheater map stealth kill where's my shit where's my stuff
he's he's a little confused shit beautiful game there we go all my stuff exactly where i placed
it combine the herbs no i can't i needed red green yellow i can't combine these i need them
combine herb no i don't want to combine them stop hoarding i i could do two but wait a minute
oh red okay red just does more heal i could do two green and one yellow you have seven scroll
down everybody everybody relax roll every hey relax red with green is a full hill three green
is also full hill two green and yellow yeah relax i'm fine i actually not get through here
all right i got all my stuff now we gotta go through here oh is this um who's that
thank you let's do some business get rid of the rats that have taken up in the factory we don't
know if any are carrying any diseases did i get these three spinels from before where would they
be can i do this wrong i can i screw this up oh maybe i shouldn't do it yet then what did i get
spinels spinels what are they i got three of them so three do you like to claim it somewhere no you
didn't the merchant will give them to you uh okay get rich quick you know that you can trade the
okay i don't even need to buy this welcome weapons and items can be bought or sold to the merchant
using uh pitas you can also upgrade repair your weapons and equipment yes you can uh merchant
request once you've completed a task received from blue request note you can claim the reward
by talking to the merchant nice work give you to the point where your neck is like it's just you
just need to just like you can't get the air it is okay we're good all right i got it i've got
something new for you mate oh what's that should i get this have we procured these curiosities
punisher yellow herb or yellow diamond key items that no longer serve a purpose can be sold to the
merchant you know does it what does it tell you that it doesn't serve a purpose anymore
it probably wouldn't be on this list if that were the case right let's sell this for 7500
okay we're selling only okay so these you just sell these these can be inserted
so i got ruby sapphire maybe they go they can go in the uh flagging
still have some new items you might be interested in 4 000 bucks to repair the knife
knife needs care all right this is what i needed to look at could be the difference between
life this is 1.0 it's 1.10 so they're both the same exact power this one just costs more to
upgrade if i if i upgrade this it goes they both go to 130 10 19 reload speed is 1.9 it actually
is better rate of fire one rate of fire this is slower though wait one point no that's faster
this is just a better handgun listen to the chat what what are you talking about
sell all you wait wait wait wait what's going on softlock not locked stop reading
nerd nerd nerd what happened what's going on and his money mate ah this is how you compare
what what's going on what do you mean let me go back here because this is this fit here
so i did this red and blue that's fine right or shift you can redo it red and red is worth more
then i can't do red yellow and blue in the other one yeah it said i didn't need the key you can
take them out okay 3000 plus 3000 so remove them so this is plus 4000 two color bonus is worth more
okay let's go that's worth more there you get a bonus or save them now why not the duo bonus
is better is it no but but that's 3000 3000 do a bonus times 1.2 is 12 000 that's 4000
this is worth more it's worth more by a hundred that's worth more than by a hundred
it's a difference of 100 wow well only 100 it's still more that might be the one bullet
that i shoot the boss and kill it save the sapphire you know i'm like so paranoid i hate
i don't i hate doing these we're pulling them all out okay because i like i know there's other
shit that i can do later all right let me prepare this okay your weapons are in good hands mate
i'll see you right so i mean i'm gonna use the dlc gun and i know people might be very upset
with me all right so what about this hours lower on the sunglasses gun reload speed is
much faster rate of fire is faster but really not that big of a deal the regular one's better i
think i'm gonna use sentinel 9 with the ammo in it we're all gonna get replaced anyways maybe
i just won't upgrade anything and say and just have like a million dollars at the end of the stream
this is where decisions come out though that cash in your pocket all your life easy choice
mate a bit more space never hurt anyone i need it perfect size for you stranger stocking up while
you can face choice bolt thrower yeah okay i'm not even gonna upgrade why not try your hand
a new gun stranger might save your life a well-tuned weapon can make up for a lack of skill
friend dlc andy all right i it's time i gotta breathe in once i'm using the dlc gun this kind
of work is about finesse stranger little b goes a long way you'll see well then what can i do
you i'll hold these for now don't get yourself killed now i need a storage tank is there one
over here somewhere there it is brave streamer using the deluxe pay to win gun hey i did breathe
in and i was like okay i gotta i gotta i gotta like take a breath here because whatever i'll
move okay how do i move it storage oh you have to okay discard no i want to move it
i want to move these i don't want to discard them this is good for now and i'm gonna do some
um let's auto sort who would even do it like that it's ugly i don't like it at all but i'll
stay with it for now you can't read simple instructions no i didn't i had to click on
it first i thought i could just like drag it over sell the guns that you're not going to use but i
don't i'm not sure yet i'm certain of this one i gotta move these two by the way okay that's much
better one and two more ammo in this gun gotta get the eagle all right i am good that was fun
what about the rodents
wait
maybe on another playthrough maybe playthrough playthrough number two
glasses off glasses off glasses on yeah wait a minute take it in i don't i don't get i'm gonna
get swarmed if i don't all right we're gonna go yellow what's happening oh we're fine shut up
what the hell are you doing why would you do that over it's an over reactor
stop saying that right now hold on how did you you've got to be kidding me that was like a 55
minute fuse over reactor instead of the react harder it's cool down cool down
do it you make leon look bad um no i'm fine oh my god what i parried sorry must have slipped
damn all right now he's overreacting on purpose you get it the ruby let's stay up
be late oh all these people have families dude there i'm being attacked by with weapons they're
trying to kill me right anything up here they are trying to kill me shit oh no that's not a
barrel i don't have to get every single item i'm fine i could have just opened the window
i want to go up oh what's going on oh my god that person did something weird i'm doing all right
i'm doing okay die stop coming up the ladder was that person holding up you can't throw that up
here is everybody dead so much money out here next okay cool all right i need to item collect
stop i gotta collect items come on okay there's look there's more stuff up here dude go to the
next area i want items all right it's look look at it's right there where's the eagle it's down
right where's the eagle oh shit where's the eagle back here right where's the eagle back here it's
behind me right i'm pretty sure it's behind me why are you not using sorceries um do your homework
oh it wants me to okay i've just i don't know how the controls worked no no no no i just confirm
it space is confirmed i'm trying to just push it i swear to god listen to me it's the a and d
and q and e i i'm i promise you i'm not i know how i'm supposed to do this i promise it's just
the weird like a and e q and you know what i mean it's i promise i understood how that was
working late night huh how you guys doing good how you guys doing tell me tell me how you're
doing i asked such a long time ago wait sneak oh my god wrong button that max hp now hope you
guys are relaxing hope you guys are having a good day killing with some resident evil four oh no
don't come over here and don't oh you already stepped in it distance between me and you
no you idiot i'm trying to who's even next to me i don't you you punched me in the face
the traps are the hardest enemy in the game oh shit we did have a couple of raids what we had
uh nestle what came with the raid thanks that's what how long ago is that was a long time ago
no like five minutes standard mode by the way what what i don't know uh yeah automated too
thanks auto wait i want that i want that cheshire crest how do i get there don't miss the ammo
is there a way i can go around how do i get that oh resources large there it is wrong button red
sorry about those sapphires
i want to do a quick poll do you sprint or walk through games like this destroy the windup dolls
do not forgive those aristocrats oh yeah you do enough of these and somebody lawnmower oh
dad dad's out there mowing no is there anything come on damn it yeah all right they put them here
too fucking for me to hit you know what i mean these are here for me to hit like they perfectly
placed all these the exact route that i take and i'm just so absent-minded it just there's nothing
i can do about it how far back am i somebody said that was a mobile game ad
yeah it was that's so accurate for what just happened the only problem is it wasn't at times
three speed you need to speed that up to times 10 speed what the fuck dude 75 sprint wait don't
i gotta get the items again did i get the chest i think i got the chest at this point right
all right let's go dude i'm gonna kill this motherfucker what the fuck are you doing you're
a silly goose that's okay i got the chest right let me check the treasures i did get the doll
i got it all right let's go i'm gonna i want to kill this because they usually drop something
good so i'm not gonna run away i'm gonna waste a bunch of ammo let's go come on where did you
come from wait they oh no no i'm running never mind whoa i forgot they're right behind you oh
shitty get out of my way get out of your fucking the movie get out of the way
all right no more screaming it's midnight i don't want to sprint no more screaming i gotta stop
screaming this is the point where we have to stop screaming midnight it's like 3 a.m for a lot of
you sometimes it's like 5 a.m for some of you but i got what i wanted i got i forgot but i don't
even know what i picked up from that guy but at least i don't have to worry about it anymore
shotgun best weapon i always upgrade the shotguns to full i think i looked over instead of reading
chat for the next you know what i mean how do i do this i can do it without i pick it up after
through the cheat map nope let's go they're like good oh my god dude i can't play these games like
that if something's on the ground i'm gonna step in it every time i will step in every single one
of them it's just i'm i just backtrack and run in circles and look around and try to find stuff i
just i don't it may as well not even be on the ground those who that watched my dark wood
playthrough people like oh he's like stepping in them on purpose go watch my dark wood playthrough
i would love for you to go watch it because i stepped in almost every single one of them
my own traps that i put down let's go the right way that game was so horrible god how awful that
game really was it was so scary and so stressful not this time i thought it came out of there and
was a trap be so fucked up as you're getting imagine get being in the bathroom and having
somebody kick you in the sternum to a point where your back flies up against the wall next to you
the force is so much that without even wiping your ass you get kicked in the chest and your your back
is planted against the wall and your head up there but the such an awful way to go is there
anything even in here no it's just scary i remember this part not too shabby smoky someone has shown
up their neighbors i remember this part old photos good wait any other um treasures in here
jesus i have a lot of grenades i give up more photos i spin it at last flesh of our flesh blood
of our blood give thanks and rejoice think that's good now i have to be prepared because we go
upstairs that's not what that said all right how do i feel about this let's do red and
make these two put again i always need some yellow herbs and we're good i want to see a boss fight
um i don't want to spoil the game for you if you haven't seen it but they are in the game okay
people are for their most prized positions the farmer his finest crop slight swine herd stoutest
pig regularly grandadman her beloved babe crop big babe now where have i seen those before three
things wait guys oh that's not big crystal marble ooh you have any thoughts on counter
strike two not really i don't really play counter strike at all it feels like a new enemy type
with the necks like this played csgo in like 2011 yeah it's been a long time though counter
striker is always too hard for me and i'm completely fine admitting that and accepting that
counter strike just felt like it would just just took so much skill to play it
if you're good at it good for you it's actually kind of hard to control the mouse got it somebody
can read that later that's not that's really not even a lot of lore either i thought it was going
to be a lot he has accepted the gift oh yeah i forgot i completely forgot that a to uh is in
this game what do you mean spoiler what those sunglasses are so bad i mean capcom put it in
it was the remake it was 81 accuracy find me another streamer that can do that
you know what i mean find me like another live streamer on the internet that can get in yeah get
you an 81 percent first try moist head 90 moon moons on hardcore critical has 90 you're you are
lame you're so lame is that funny because there's so many people streaming this probably right now
there's a lot of really good players like imagine actually making that statement you just did i'm
kidding it was a joke don't make me put on the pay to win case whoa wait wait wait what are these
equipped left equipped center i got these little toys what i just do how do i take that off charm
perks plus 30 handgun ammo craft bonus frequency oh are you serious i've been waiting to do this
stupid joke for like a week or two come on dude that's so annoying i haven't sneezed in like four
like probably five or six days because i just so badly want to just do this but i'm not going to
whatever all right i mean are these part of it whatever i'll keep them on how many chapters are
in reasoning before just to be a researcher for should have left him in that bag i'm sending you
the details take a look but baby eagle is your priority copy that making my way to the church
condor one oh i can't go up there i need a right okay i believe this gets a little wacky here
somebody in chat somebody says can you somebody in chat please help me why do i sneeze when i eat
chocolate are you allergic to chocolate would be the first guess maybe you have a mild allergy
to chocolate i don't know be careful food allergies don't work like that i'm not allergic to anything
it's a bathroom okay wait don't i i swear something's here maybe not well i have the key
oh you too come here come here come here i got you you all right take care of yourself buddy
good dog good dog i can't go that way i can't open this yet right i can but wait is something
else back there i'll see now this is the way i went before game progress okay creepy
resources where there's snakes mr treasure it's okay let's get on the next playthrough
there's no way i'm not going to play i'm going to play through this absolutely guaranteed at
least like another two or three times probably not on stream i'll probably just do it in my uh
my own time or something at some point let's do the real treasure hunting so far this runs
perfectly i'd say it's perfect i haven't seen anything really bad so far i'll like slow down
so there's been a little bit of a stutter like just a hint loading up some a new area but it's
it's pretty smooth it's pretty solid at like 144 it feels like i have v sync on but it seems
really seems pretty good it'll stutter sometimes in the rain um i think that's all right from what
i remember this resident evil 2 remake engine whatever it is was phenomenal it was very very
good it's probably one of the better engines i've played our game on what the hell i thought these
were friends i thought they were friends open oh god oh no no no no no no no no no no no shit
well that's unfortunate where is it on the stairs okay wait wait wait wait wait i know i gotta do
this lock up all these doors shit i'm not taking a i'm not healing yet can i close this door okay
i think it's the other way yeah it's the other way i gotta go through that building i think
shit well where are you i'm good i think i have to go through that building through the window
yes i do okay we're good late stream yeah oh shit that's bad uh so the game launched at 9 pm
and i just could not wait another day i want to play it and that's what we're doing can't open
these right cool cool late stream is scary well it makes the game a little scarier because it's
dark i actually like streaming with the camera with the lights down because you can't see all
like the weird tendencies of my face i like it it's so it's pog oh i don't have let's go i didn't
even get tea i need to get some tea snake did i get it oh there we go viper medium-sized snake with
a unique modeled pattern if the poison glands are removed and may be eaten can be used to restore
health don't they sometimes drop really nice stuff if you get that because they they run away
quickly i remember that correctly okay no load this up i like the smokiness that was creepy
they always do that illuminados four nine sleep well and flourish dear child as your body grows
your mother's shall sew new small clothes at seven quintile of wheat and half a bowl a day
you have outgrown you a pen flourish dear child the sake of your brothers and sisters who cannot
is this the onion ring guy no that's my twin brother we share an account i do all the gaming
sick of constantly running out of ammo well have i got a treat for you the bolt thrower is something
else mate its bolts can be retrieved and reused so you can keep shooting forever also don't forget
to buy the bolt recipe to turn your extra knives into well bolts never worry about ammo again this
is new and that's not all you're gonna fix the bolts with attachable mines to quickly turn the
weapon into a powerful mine thrower shoot an enemy to see them explode instantly or at a surface
to set a proximity mile you'll lose the bulb but it's worth it said that really fast so this is
new content then interesting welcome got some rare things on sale stranger a well-tuned weapon
can make up for a lack of skew it's so expensive
discounted items discounts are only available during the chapters they appear in
well it really wants me to buy this bolt thrower i feel like i have to buy this
i feel like this thing sucks though that'd be all then it's gonna be just like a i don't want to go
pick up arrows that cash in your pocket or your lot but it's on sale easy choice i need to buy
the recipe too then it's like almost all my money try the new content out sad that's true
that's true won't do you much good i'm not gonna use this so i'm gonna sell it i'm just not gonna
use it i know i'm not i'm just not gonna use this either i just i'm certain of it a deal well struck
i guess i'll try it you'll get some bang for your buck i'm gonna do it it's new content i'm gonna
get it not only will you need cash but you'll need guts to buy what i'm gonna do it i'm gonna do it
is a commodity these days i can't believe i bought this thing the fucking nerf gun if you want a
fighting chance out there you best tune up your kit try that on for size give that the care it
deserves mate anything else oh should i get this to uh all right it's time i'm it's time to sell
i'm doing it i'm doing one blue one red sell it what are you done okay now sell that
this one is four of these so i could do bang bang bang and i could now i'm just gonna wait
or i could do red no no i can't do two blues no no it's i have the same color we already proved
that it didn't matter i get a hundred more for doing the two we already did that we just started
welcome what can i interest you yeah it was 12 one with the two and it was 12 even
with the double got it i got it damn this thing's 29 000 holy shit man that's good
blues are worth worth more than red it doesn't matter i what i want all of them in here
two blue is better it's not blue is one k more yeah but then i but then i won't have a blue in
this one yeah i want to do all the colors in this one yeah i'm selling it we're good thank you
smash smash smash smash how dare he all right now i can do more tune up durability yeah definitely
see how that feels mate i do the pair i do the parry all the time right away a well tuned
there you are as you wish okay i think i'm good but a selection of good come back anytime how does
this thing work that's fine there so that's on my knife now all right how does this thing work
new content let's see is it just kind of a attach a mine okay this thing might be actually really
good is there a snake charmer willing to lend a hand sell three vipers oh okay so i have one
i'm gonna take a quick break and get some tea we're getting into the late night hours i still
want to play so um i'll be right back i'm just gonna refill my tea get some water stretch a
little bit and we'll be right back see you in a second that song was a little too intense
we're gonna go with something a little nicer a little well nicer as in a little slower hey
that sounds better okay a little longer than i wanted sorry about that i wanted to eat something
i was just like you know what holly was making uh tortillas i could smell it i was just like you
know it was the the pie on the window sill was floating around this late yeah sometimes it's
what you want that sounds like pretty good weed no uh that is not what uh that's not what just
happened i told you guys before uh i i don't do that on stream not anymore i didn't really
do it that often anyways but no i just can't i physically would not be able to stream like
it's been pretty clear after you couldn't read a clock yeah but it was more than that though it
was just i it just my ability to even talk like oh i'm streaming right now what are we gonna talk
about it was just like i i can't even what this i don't know the streams were kind of like i don't
even know how to explain it but you know what i mean i thought they were funny they can be fun
and funny and everything but i also don't want i also don't want to have it be a thing that i'm
just like oh look i look at how cool this is i'm it's funny i'm high isn't that cool
yeah it's funny to talk about but obviously i don't want it to be a staple of this channel
anyways i think i'm ready no you get it i don't have to say anymore let's go uh all right make
sure it's not too loud because of the music i had before good pretty okay that kind of scared this
shit out of me all right so we good why am i i'm like blue right now why it wasn't like this
before was it all right i got what i need i got what i wanted i've got my new weapon i have no
idea how good it is i have no idea how much damage it does i have no idea if it's worth
actually using we're gonna use it the game is saved let's go i'm gonna send you a strongly
worded letter um well just just put it in here i mean you can i think you really can do like
100 200 characters or something but just put it here make mines i'll have to buy the recipe
it's okay i'll do it in a minute ooh a church i made it how much longer you're gonna be live for
that's a good question i don't want to go too too i'm like doing fine i'm very much awake very much
awake i don't want to go too too late i was at least through the first boss i think that makes
sense to me that's a good place to stop for tonight i'm trying to think of the schedule for
this weekend too because i even want to do like technically whatever would be tomorrow like
tonight tomorrow and maybe sunday or tonight and then saturday sunday trying to think of how i
should do it probably saturday sunday you can play diablo 4 nah nah i think i got what i wanted out
of it um it's definitely kind of not enough for me to understand if i really like it or not
it was fun but i can i can see i can see some cracks that i don't know if it's gonna be
through all the whole release through the end game of the content i don't know and i think i'd rather
just just wait it's i'm just gonna wait right miss damn it condor one to roost the church is
sealed up and baby eagle negative nothing yet but they sure do have this place locked up tight
i see i can think of one reason they'd want to do so oh she's here that's for sure i'll find a
way in condor one out but also i mean i don't i don't even know if i'm gonna play d4 i think
the reason why i wanted to play diablo 4 was just because everything i heard leading up to it was
hey diablo 2 remember that game we remember that game i think that's why i was thinking
about playing it but yeah we'll see if i play it i play it if i don't i don't i don't have like a
really a plan to um but yeah we'll see we don't talk about diablo 3 diablo 3 was all right it
was fine i i mean as much as i just wish it was a different game it was the game that it was and
i played a lot of it i played i've got i got a lot out of that game i did those traitorous twins
should not be allowed to rest in peace for joining that evil cult someone anyone destroy
the emblems engraved upon their tombstones destroy the tombstone emblems oh that's easy i can do that
right now is it back here also i said this earlier i think before playing d4 i think blizzard's in
kind of a weird spot right now where they really kind of they like they need to have something
right they have to kind of i feel like i haven't really cared about a blizzard game in a long time
like the last the last i want to say five years have been they've been pretty
fucked up so i don't know is this it does that count is it what does it want me to destroy
i said the the twins or something right is it these ones and i look at that note where is it
those traitors twins should not be allowed to rest in peace for joining that evil cult i think it's
okay let me in here lakeside map test bro he outsid his om for the irl locker and the
church and weight orders from your lord until then keep the church door shut
if you'll be held in the cave on the other side of the you didn't really hide this that well
the monster will deal with the it's this didn't take that long to crack didn't you just tell us
that you weren't high yeah i'm making i'm making a point that this is not that well somebody was
trying to hide this text i didn't do a very good job this is a youtube poop transcript let's hope
for no more surprises i want to shoot somebody with this thing but watch me not even shoot one
person the whole game with that weapon it's probably gonna happen i would not be surprised
oh yellow diamond i needed that one that's a good one was there anything else out here
let me just check down here or something i feel like let me take a look at my cheating map
there is look at that where is it oh it's right there hell yeah how can you play so late at night
and not be scared um i don't know if you were here an hour ago but uh i was it got me a few
times at least my camera seems to have auto adjusted though because now it's kind of weirdly
lit in here um is there already get the emblem no i didn't this webcam is like three pixels what
happened to the one you had in november i have only increased the payments for webcams over the
last six months i started with a c920 and i used it for years i then bought a logitech brio
which was way more expensive than the c920 and then i bought the razor one which was i believe
even more expensive than the brio so i just keep adding i just keep throwing money at this problem
and it doesn't seem to be fixing it this like corporate andy over here is there a problem
yeah here just i don't know just take that and make it better take that and make it a little
better for me it didn't work well whatever i don't know just take more of it wait i'm supposed to be
looking my immersion i think this one looks fine i think this one looks the best out of the three
of them there's also really dark in here that's come on we gotta be fair what i didn't know that's
what that was a beautiful lighting effect go on down here oh that's a lot of you hold on hold on
wait till they jump down before you walk over here very nice somebody behind me more fun to
play in the dark i actually really don't like no no no no no no no i actually don't really like
bright ass lights really lit up really bright rooms and i hate it it kind of hurts my head
this room has light in it it's a little lit up but i um i much prefer it slightly dim
no it's not dark dark in here but it is dim i prefer it that way i would wear sunglasses all
the time i would be this i would do that i feel like having a little bit of tint darker is just
makes me feel better what is going on here what is going on where are these people oh stop throwing
how did i light on fire we gotta go this guy is so bad jesus
one down more like 10 that guy got in my head because i missed three shots i gotta hold
didn't i get a yellow herb bolts bolts for the bolt thrower i wonder if that was stupid why are
you so red because i got a lot of blood i'm gonna try it you can retrieve the ammo which is good yeah
what does it even look like let's i'm gonna shoot it okay that's pretty cool can i pick
them up indefinitely what's the reload on it really long very long let's check it out
kind of blink uh oh that's a good grab good luck finding someone big enough to use this thing
why do i have so much blood i'm just very very my circulation is very good i have very good
circulation except my hands get cold all right this is blue medallions and we can actually cheat
i bought the deluxe edition uh okay actually i should probably heal but
and let's just go for it you guys already uh this this is one of the coolest parts of the
game if you guys don't know so in here see all these crows a huge raven boss flies down here
and picks you up by the back that's why there's all these birds and shit and you have to fight
the bird while you're flying around um it's unbelievable it was really really cool
in the regular game i'm just really curious how they do it in this one
because like you actually have to fight and shoot the bird well it's like it's like clawing you back
and stuff and it like swings around you go past the church and past buildings this whole aerial
fight there you go can i take the bolts out yep this thing's actually kind of good i actually
this is actually pretty good okay we're good all right here we go where's the bird um in a minute
i had it wrong i see you took care of a request well done i can't believe they cut the iconic
bird fight i don't think they did now there are enough weapons here to get a party going
sell them an extra cash upgrade weapon do you do use uh-huh get all the expenses you put back
into it okay well you've proven yourself reliable what you're buying what a good ring rubies all
rubbish it makes no difference the price well that's our choice to make well these you just
get rid of these for selling only that's good a deal well struck take these two vipers well done
stranger and one more viper i still use all this stuff you're much good in here sure there's some
things money can't i think i'm gonna buy with this right this is probably not a bad idea
i don't think it's a bad idea i'm gonna get it you can't go wrong with that all right bolt
thrower probably maybe ammo capacity ready to fire are in good hands mate i'll see you right
i'll just make this thing deadly yeah this thing is filthy now an idea of your tastes
friend 1.8 this thing is filthy where would it what can i do don't get yourself killed now
all right one more viper and i get that okay let's make this i have a two don't i here we go
wait a minute hold on wait wait wait how come i can't put that it wants me to use two of these
but i already have one don't i already is this gonna take two and make another one don't i
already have one last option yeah that's the right one yeah i was gonna try to put it in this one
but i forgot i had these two i forgot i had these two red and greens so that's good all right so
this is a i'm probably just gonna take this now it's a full heal now wait until you really need
it all right let's do it i'm gonna be using this actually because it's the best thing i have right
now what is that hexagon piece a there's more to do down there you need to go get the treasures
yeah i wasn't gonna leave yet this is like an elevator here and everything hold on
i kind of sprinted down here and there is something else here that right here can't do this
i can see that but people are gonna be make fun of me so whatever where is it up there filled
sauce on like rattlebeast shirt oh no i've put some uh get some get some um
what do they use get some um get some oxy clean or something i don't know club soda yeah club
soda where does this go i don't even know where this goes this is new this is a minigame wow look
at this food oh we can earn some stuff here okay what is this token machines free silver or gold
tokens at the token machine to win a random charm what gold tokens you use the greater your chance
of getting a rare charm i don't have any tokens though what do you get tokens shut up destroy the
pirates and shoot for the high score weapons and ammo are unlimited and it's all free earn tokens
based on your score the page turning sound in 3d movie maker it's from 3d movie maker windows 95
okay um you can destroy several targets at once by shooting at nearby dynamite a set of explosions
be careful shooting a sailor will deduct points some targets cannot be destroyed with one shot
shoot as many shots as it takes until they break if certain conditions are met bonus targets will
be added however these conditions will change from game to game this seems kind of fun well
i need to earn some tokens so it's an unlimited ammo my whole face is itchy bad very bad very i
can do better than that you can tell my sensitivity is too low because of that my sensitivity is too
low you can tell because i couldn't track it sensitivity is too low now i understand why it
doesn't play pvp games i'm i'm not hey 35 plus that's pretty good for 35 plus my fucking hands
my fingers hurt fucking hand hurts i kind of might just made the room red why did the room get red
wasn't it just blue why am i trying to shoot them in the head i don't have to what are you talking
about i'll take it shotgun time that's not a shotgun that just freaked me out so bad how do
you zoom in how do i wait is it already zoom oh alt just restart just restart how do i restart
the game i got a really bad score this one doesn't even count just do it i want to do it again
i can't leave it's a very generous c up movies hands are shaking around shit shut up
all right i can do it again i can do much better than that i can do so much better than that i can
do better than that what this wasn't even reloaded i need to switch between the weapons
i almost 100 percent of it oh shit we got a big raid that's from c dog what's up c dog
holy shit that's a big one that is a large raid you wasted time switching weapons it's all right
i got an s i got an s i got s and everything thank you c dog how's the uh how'd the how the
cycle ago the cycle ago how'd the cyclothon go good what's the uh what's the total 322 000
holy shit wow hell yeah that's awesome holy shit that's a lot of money well going to a good cause
so that's great but welcome uh thanks for the raid for playing resident evil 4 i can tell you
not for much longer so i don't i don't know how much longer we're gonna do this for but i i'm
about to open up a bunch of um a bunch of fun boxes you guys ready enter the stream voice no
no no not yet i just want to the raiders that came in we want to make sure we have a clear
indication of what's going to happen here all right i got three coins so should i do three just
go all in with three what is it charms charms can be swapped out via the customized case menu
dr salvador 20 percent rifle ammo craft bonus well that sucks why did i get a common i just put
three gold coins in there magnum ammo crafting these are all commons i'm gonna put that one on
that's a couple of magnum how do i get more coins i want more coins how do i get them all right i
gotta have 100 the whole game i have to 100 everything i have to get all the skulls how do
i just turn it off turn it off just turn it off turn the game off how do i turn the game off just
turn the game off i fucked it up already i can't just exit but the mission i don't think i can
hit escape oh quit shooting oh come on come on let's go go go go go
whoa what a miss wow what a mistake wow what just happened there oh my god what just happened i
fucking crumbled like a piece of paper where are the where's the way where where where where where
how do you hit that how do you hit that it's so hard what
i have to do it i can't leave
fuck my eyes like a bulge you got in my head we're good we're good everyone relax relax relax i
gotta you're killing me oh my god why didn't you do that why did it go what was that what the hell
was that why did it go like i didn't do it i held the button down what was that for because you
moved what what i mean i moved look look what see look throw a grenade over there i can't i would
i didn't get it i hit the thing behind it i don't know how but that's
what happened i missed it how did i miss it come on all this to gamble on that fucking machine
so i can't fucking do it i can't do it guys i can't do it i can't do it i can't do it
just stay in one place i know but i have to i need i gotta know where it is
that was hard moving around get out of the way how many more are there too there are 10
what's the 40s what what happened what what what was wrong with that
did i miss one does it come back did i get it it doesn't come back damn it okay i got everything
but come on so that one that flies across the beginning i gotta be ready for it
i'm gonna shit start but sorry hurry up hurry up go to spring load again fuck shit because i got
him though i got it i got it i got it okay i got it got it almost got 100 okay this one's
gonna be a lot harder and i'm gonna do something weird does he have one on him i we haven't seen
one yet i just want to see where they are nobody has one on them nobody not yet this whole time
no one's had one the whole time there's one someone did one i i don't i don't even care
that's not what i'm doing here holy shit oh i've ruined everything
did i get them all i think i got them all i got them all didn't i i got them all what did i miss
spinning one sometimes have a skull on the single side in the back you mean okay so i'm
all right that was a very bad display go go go go go go go go go go go go go
are we good are we good are we good i don't know five out of seven again where the fuck are the
other two where are the other two the first spinning sword pirate has one first spinning
the first spinning pirate between the two sailors has one in his chest but only on one side it shows
first spinning one at the beginning it's hidden behind the person with the barrel what okay let
me just see where they are really that's how many times did you shoot that guy have one okay
all right now i know where they are we're good so those are the two that i was missing
just don't fuck it up i said don't fuck it up
reload that quick that's it i got it i got i got i got them all right i got them all got them all
yes okay let's go let's go give me more plus 30% attachable mines craft i mean that's
okay but what i use i wouldn't say that's worth three golden coins are there even any other
rarities in the game well i can't get many i can't get any more gold coins from this
there's probably more later i need to go into my inventory that was really fun though that's cool
mix the coins up next time well three but i mean three gold coins that should give you something
i am bright i can look over and see in the obs preview i am red what happened well that blood
came up to my face okay so customized case i should probably put this one on then right this
is you get more do i want more handgun ammo or more money probably money are we done for today
not yet i mean i feel like that's pretty good they stack don't i craft shotgun shells all the time
yeah this is a cool idea i like it this is a cool addition uh speaking of crafting breaks over i
let's go ahead and do that now i need gunpowder okay let's keep going i don't really have any
money i did what i wanted to do and let's continue okay um should heal with the herb um i will
eventually so the i have a question listen the the bird boss right how come the bird boss didn't
activate you know why did the bird boss not activate right you know what i mean it's it's
different okay you're good you're good okay on the way back okay this is really really great so far
it's really good i mean this game is just phenomenal on regardless of what version it is
but it does feel pretty great to come back to this so we talked about how i wish i could like
wipe my memory and play all the from software games again this kind of feels like that so this
is really cool really enjoying it so far is anything i do anything hey is that the right dock
i don't i don't think so there you are i can't do anything else here i think i just have to leave
okay goodbye and then we go out to the right so wait no it's wait where am i going here okay
it's okay why are you up so late because the game released late and i wanted to jump in on it at
least on the launch day because i was very excited for this and it's really really cool and i'm glad
i did because it's been really fun i'm going to continue playing this this is pretty much what
i'm going to be doing all weekend so yeah i'm going to finish it this weekend whoa although
there was a raid from prezzo earlier too thanks prezzo appreciate it i don't know if you're still
here or if anybody's still here but i miss raids it's it's like actually a problem i promise i'm
not ungrateful i'm just scattered shoot the water shoot the water but i appreciate it though thank
you shoot the water shoot the water hurry up the boat fuel is stored with the generator fuel inside
the processing building at the fish farm take only what you need all this i bet there's a snake in
here thousand bucks though that's a lot got a lot of ammo that's good shoot the water shoot the water
shoot the water yeah i will in a minute you'll come on fill the tank when you're done hey it
happened i did it well now i gotta go back down and do that i gotta pick up all this
shit okay hold on can you do it again i missed it i have a really cool trick that you are gonna
learn right now if you miss something during the stream then i am red like this has to change now
like this is ridiculous my room is red right now it's not me i swear it's the color correction on
the camera see what i mean look look what just happened this is what it actually looks like in
here it looks like i still am red i'm a red i'm a whatever it's too late to get annoyed by this
that's better that's fine that's fine you need to put the hero filter on to match this
i don't care there's so much blood swirling around in here i told you guys that people like oh wow
how can you stay so thin i mean how do you stay like that you must exercise no guys i burn so
many calories just by existing i swear to you my body is just constantly just revved up machine
i have these dreams that are real life up here it's like i burned more calories than i in my
dreams than i do when i'm awake i'm constantly my body is constantly just producing energy
if you like put two little wires on me i could probably power a fucking clock like a potato
he's flexing on all us normal people that that did sound a little braggy that sounded a little
braggy but that's not what i meant by that that was that was a little braggy okay i admit but
that's not what i mean all right back to it i got everything right jeez germa i wish i had super
powers too shit hey can you shoot the water um no no i'm good i'm if i'm shooting the water
might be kind of funny though i was not in there before was it interesting okay this stuff is in
different places now what is in here it's random wait it's not placed individually it's random
i didn't know it was random i thought there was actually place there come on fill the tank when
you're done get me out here most resident evil games were that way i don't remember them being
random i guess certain key placement is certain items are there not random need two more of those
nice well i'm about to craft one of these anyways so let's go i'm gonna blow through these i think
at some point here not enough gunpowder reroll the loot shoot the water that was pretty good
louie i don't want to reroll it all right back to did i get everything oh wait a minute this is
what 10 extra dollars buys you or is it under the dock yesterday please turn the thanos filter off
make yourself green all right i gotta damn it there's the last one oh come on uh i'm just
gonna take one of these i needed it anyways oh my god oh my god oh my god oh my god oh my god
oh my goodness oh my goodness run i got him where's my where's my bolt where's my bolt
get off me this gun is fucking stupid do it it's not that bad i did lose one of my bolts though
i don't know why they're in the water somewhere whatever right right right i didn't do it right
but i tried it's too late to do that dude stop there's so much more money and shit down here
yeah keep going where i came from right yeah i don't know you're going to blow up like the
guy from big trouble in little china what why do i why do i know what that is do i know what that
is that's a classic movie swing what the hell oh whoa they're behind me oh somebody swung at me
where'd they go see that did you see the axe when i what it was weird sit down oh i need to
there we go good that should free up some space it didn't free up any space i need to craft some
shit uh all right i'm gonna go two two green herbs just free up some space you look like a very tired
john wick yeah i'm thinking i'm back what you told me i'm gonna say something if you say it like
you don't you can't minus two that many times you'll crash my computer don't do that you're
gonna crash my computer if you do that stop i hear beeps oh my god thank goodness i didn't do that
if you say that was funny and then you write minus two it is automatically not counted
i just want to make sure you understand that but the algorithm picks up if you said like how
omega l minus two and that does not count you negate it i understand the appeal of this thing
and i'm starting to get why it's kind of cool because it's effectively infinite ammo if you're
good at shooting which i don't know how good i am with that where is this beep sure it's good
for stealth uh there's one more of those where is it where's this medallion i think it's probably
on the outside oh chest i can't carry any more of these i'm just gonna eat one of them where's
that medallion there it is last one need one more just a lot of these i can't take anymore
an egg boat fuel go back to the boat who just puts an egg in their pocket this is a little
weird but is it really stays fresh i don't like it as long as you don't break it i'm gonna leave
that there in case i need to eat it later you look like you want revenge today oh my god be careful
but i just ripped it oops a lot of money all right back to the boat i wonder how much harder
hard hardcore is because the parry makes hardcore i think not as bad it's a lot harder oh well i
think with the parry that would be wouldn't be too awful as long as you did the parry right okay i
gotta go back up this way it's too hard you're a baby you know about me anyways what do you know
about me what do you know about me too much somebody said uh i want to save the game because
i'm a little concerned that i'm gonna get killed here and i don't want to go all the way back i
don't think there's a checkpoint before this so i'm gonna save don't listen to the haters you did
nancy drew on senior mode yeah yes i did what am i going idiot i want to go back oh it's this way
did i get any more trinkets to sell because i kind of want to upgrade the shotgun
took care of a request did you i knew i could count on you oh what you're buying a well-tuned
weapon can make up for a lack of skill friend this kind of work is about finesse stranger little
b goes a long way you see did i already do the viper thing did i do the viper thing already
pleasure doing business with you that should be it right all right cool a job well done deserves
payment in kind where would it what can i do you there's some things money can't buy
i'm not sure i'm not sure it's kind of cool maybe should i see what is better
or just get the laser sight treasure map i think i already have it it's a bad gun i think i already
have the treasure map because i have the lux edition are you guys lying or is that real let's
get the laser yeah laser sights you can't come back anytime okay i need this laser sight didn't
this used to take up inventory space did they change that i thought it took up inventory space
it still does it does i thought it was an actual item in the oh it is right there okay yeah yep
okay do i want to store anything i'm all right oh i got a bonus why is it so dark in your room
uh because i turned the lights off because it's a scary game well relatively scary
you can turn it up a little bit now though there that's a little bit
sell the necklace please uh i don't want to sell the necklace because i want to fill it welcome
got a selection of good things i want a full necklace because then it's probably worth like
40 grand she makes no difference the price at the treasure map that's our choice i have a yellow
but it's not the right size it needs to be a square or rectangle okay let's do this part
i'm now confident i have a save point i'm good let's go or something maybe i should just store
this yeah i like it but taking up a lot of space right now you have the stench of i also need to
i need to i need to throw some flashbang these things are just taking up so much space
throw some flashbangs throw some grenades why are these not in a stack like these are
what these are in a stack of four why is that how come these won't stack oh oh that's a hot key
that's okay i see i can't store the bolts and i don't want to throw the bolts away because
how am i going to get any more i don't think you can store um ammo put it down yeah i can't
store it that's okay i have plenty of room uh i got plenty of ammo i wouldn't want to use this
here anyways because i would lose all the i'd lose all the bolts anyways all right let's go
i'm ready uh probably gonna call it after this encounter here i did say i wanted to put a kind
of a cap on it to some point before 3am so here's what's gonna happen i'm very happy to play this
i'm i cannot wait to keep playing it i'm very excited to continue playing it so here's the
plan for this weekend this weekend we're gonna go probably very long on saturday uh saturday is
probably going to be a long stream i'm going to really grind this out on saturday sunday is going
to be another stream where i really kind of grind it out on sunday i think that's probably i should
be able to beat it in another three streams or so but i here's the thing i don't want to rush this
so i've been obviously this game's awesome it's probably one of the best games it's going to come
out this whole year i'm going to take my time with it so we'll see i'm imagining i'll probably
stream it at least probably four or five times yeah it won't be like this uh on saturday because
i had to start really really late today because it came out really late i was just itching to play
it so loud are you gonna do a massive bong rip on cam for 420 i don't think so this is so loud
why did it get so much louder okay yes you didn't say no throw harpoons right in the mouth where you
going where you going where you going where is he whoa how do i turn up what do i go all right why
is this not driving oh i ran into there what you can swallow me i'm moving oh shit come on aim better
god damn it whoa what the hell oh that hurt there it is just as easy as it was in the original
it's a cool fight though i like it shades you're playing on the baby mode no i'm playing on
standard okay that was interesting it's late at night i don't care i'm gonna tell you um i
i just was leaning back and i was i kind of put my hand well on like the kind of bottom lower back
part of my back just to kind of stretch a little and i ended up i kind of with my other thumb
lifted kind of my pants and went i kind of pulled them out a little like oh i'm just gonna like the
elastic here i'm gonna pull back it was like 180 degree air that just came out that was hot
it was burning hot air that just came from that area that was like hot like burning hot
i'm telling you i am on fire all day people think i'm a liar i'm i like i'm just like on fire
take 80 come on you're sweating dude shit yourself oh my god that's so stupid dude have you had a
fever for the last 10 years
they're even on in my nightmares i don't know if you would have the sunglasses on in a nightmare
these things are welded to his head this is part of his body those are just his eyes
you wouldn't condor wonder roost do you read me condor one you've been radio silent for three
hours are you all right yeah i'm fine why did you sleep in the boat i'm still looking for whatever
key i need copy that i mean once that big monster is dead i feel like it's probably relatively
safe out there in the boat kind of away from all the crazy shit like once you get rid of the big
monster just be right in the middle of the lake and just go to bed i think you'd be pretty safe
unless there's a second monster which look i feel like the first monster encounter would have woken
up the second monster so there's definitely no second monster there's no way you sleep through
that if you're a second monster you're a second monster you hear that and you go investigate be
going anywhere in this thing uh i'm gonna wrap it up here i'm gonna just get to another save point
which i think this one probably right here soon okay i thought that was a demon or something i
thought this thing attacked me i thought it was a giant moth i was like what do they add to the
game why is it what is this i do like the little additions here and there though it's very fun
okay that's where i came from go over here it's just like hurt my eyes what are you doing i would
somebody said cs go maneuver yeah i was trying to flash him because i think they're up on the hill
imagine you're like doing like a religious chant and up on the hill like it's some crazy cult or
something else like a flashbang lands in front of you would you notice or would you be still
doing this and what would happen do you stop the chant or is it like oh we gotta keep going like
we can't stop how does that work i was wondering what they were gonna look like in the remake
what is this place some kind of shrine same mark from the church okay i need need an item here
i do not have okay monster investigate the two locations okay i have to investigate the
over there investigate the over there very cool let's go good morning oh that's right it is
probably morning for you right morning eu and good afternoon australia those of you that know
i'm an australian time zone streamer now it's eight p.m in australia right now wow it's so
ridiculous to me just how um it's how far ahead australia is from the west coast of the united
states wait what am i what's going on here investigate the two locations because i gotta
go up here the boat doesn't work though wait come here did i screw this up i messed this up
didn't i think i have to go this way make yourself red i mean i already am pretty red right now if
you get ready for school young man i still have school dreams i didn't see this oops okay sometimes
i have dreams where oh no i gotta turn a paper in it's like dude i have not been in a classroom
like 15 to 20 years and i still think that i'm like wait oh i didn't turn my paper in
i'm fucked and it's like i wake up and i'm like i'm like 40 yeah like i don't look like moths okay
someone fetch me a rare golden chicken egg what will i do with it well sometimes it's more fun
not knowing those drop pretty frequently from what i remember all right i want to go if i
remember this let me see i think this stuff over here there is i do remember the boat what was in
here i think it's like a jewel or something there we go all right i just made like 40 grand
i can oh i can complete that um necklace whatever it is red nine that thing's pretty good from what
i remember i might just upgrade that thing to full that gun used to be the beast that that is the
right one right that's the one that you just always use that one they probably fixed it they
probably changed it so the other stuff is better i remember that thing was unstoppable okay i
need honestly i need to i need to save where's the nearest safe point i'm gonna go this way
probably in here wait a minute he was gonna go to bed 20 minutes ago i need up i need a safe point
get out of the way if you don't save i will drink it to sonny whoa i'm going i'm going i'm going
what what come on dude what are you talking about you know i actually holly and i did a water taste
test just for fun one day and i don't remember i think dasani was not even that low for me yeah
well we we just do things sometimes we just hang out together i forget what my my favorite one was
my number one was that dasani was not even really that low it was pretty low but it wasn't like f
i probably would surprise people with where i put something i'm gonna i'm gonna get punched in the
face for saying this i think i'm good someone is going to to be very upset with me there they go
they're already punching there look at they're already punching um core water is like i think
it was like pretty low i didn't really like core water the one with the blue cap it's blue it's
kind of slim looks like it's like a got a blue twist off big blue twist off cap yeah um what
did i give i wait i gave dasani a b no i gave no i didn't i gave dasani a b no no no no no
that's wrong that's wrong it's wrong it's wrong that's not smart water was an a you're sleep
deprived show the list we don't really have a list now dasani was what dasani was was a c
but core was was the lowest for me what would you what about tap water depends on where you
fucking live i mean this some tap water like tastes very different i don't know i like vegas
tap water versus like california tap water versus like hawaii tap water versus massachusetts tap
water it's i don't i don't know very different new york city tap water yeah it's very different
new york city tap water versus vegas tap water i assure you is very different oh my goodness okay
i water our water is fine whatever i don't prefer it asani though smart water is usually what i would
want fiji okay fiji doesn't count for me because fiji would just blow everything away i don't think
i i i don't think i'm allowed to put it on the list because i don't know isn't fiji fiji's like
you can't even come close i don't buy fiji though i don't actually buy it you know where i buy fiji
water it's one of the only places i buy it the airport that's it i don't ever buy it anywhere
else it's just at the airport and it's funny because fiji's already kind of expensive isn't it
so it's even more expensive at the airport so i'm buying arguably one of the more expensive
waters on earth at the most expensive place on earth it's like the water is very very expensive
in the airport vacation packaging crystal geyser is s actually i would probably agree with you
all right that's a weird flex no i just i just told you i don't buy it i buy it at the airport
which is just like oh yeah sure fiji you know what it is because you want to make sure like anytime
i travel i want to make sure that i am in peak performance mode peak physical hydration peak
mental fortitude and a fiji water to me is like all right that is that's good shit and i'm going
to make sure i drink that because i i'm about to go on an airplane i wanted to be the best
because i'm going on a plane i planes suck already everybody knows that all right we'll see you
saturday i need to be peak performance to get on a plane doesn't matter remember what would you do
if you got the t-virus um i close myself off in a room and just i don't know like booby trap the
room i'm in because like the t-virus is going to get out of me and try to get out like it's
gonna be like an alien right so i'll just like booby trap the whole room just stay in there
and then eventually like it'll get out and i'd like run into the fucking home alone shit that
i made for it it won't know it'll it'll be like like out of my chest and go to the door like
and then a big paint can just hits right in the face and falls back onto the toy cars i put all
over the ground i would contain it his ass is not ready to stop streaming no i'm good i'm good it's
getting late all right we'll pick it up on saturday thanks for watching guys uh very late very late
take care of yourselves it's been real the game is phenomenal i kind of was anticipating it would
be it's just really really cool it feels like visiting an old friend that is like doing real
good doing real well for themselves right this is like holy shit you're doing well cool all right
you're doing great like good to see you again yeah thanks for the raids too uh sea dog came
in with a huge one over 320 000 dollars raised which is amazing if you still hear from sea dogs
thanks maybe we'll see you again another time among all the others that obviously rated too
what about hitman oh man i know i've got such a backlog of things i've told you i wanted to do
yeah sea dogs awesome spent some quality time um hung out with sea dog at the streamer awards
he's really cool super chill dude all right breath of the wild will be next week i want to finish
resident evil 4 first as long as that takes us maybe three streams four streams maybe i guess
it depends on how fast i go through it take care of yourselves get some sleep or good morning hope
you have a good day some of you are probably just starting your weekend we'll see you saturday so
technically tomorrow technically because it is technically friday right now see you saturday
call your mother see you soon