So hey, what's going on everybody? Welcome to Total Distortion.
This is a game that just, you know, recently came out 20 years ago and...
This guy sure does talk a lot of shit. That's all I remember.
Let's go to bed. Falling asleep? That's okay.
The dreams are racing down the road. The winner will take over your mind.
Stop the bad dreams from entering your brain with the dream gun.
Okay. So my dream gun's on the right. I don't want that dream there. I seem to be...
Okay. Well, this is...
I'm like real fucked up right now. Son of a bitch.
It's hit me every single time. I didn't even get hit by that. It's bullshit. No.
Oh! Look at my metal face.
Can I cut? Can I counteract this?
Minus 46. Holy shit.
Index of books. Uh, there's a lot of books here.
Let's go. Let's go with Facebook book one.
That looks like a good book. I wonder what this is going to be about.
I wonder what tale this is going to tell me.
Oh, it's in fact not a book at all. It's just some guy.
Oh, this is a good book. I like the part where the princess revolts against the alien.
Sledgehammer Fists. Battle practice. That sounds like a pretty good book. It could be anything,
right? This is also not a book. How do I punch again?
Am I on the left or the right? I'm pretty sure I'm on the left, but I'm dead.
So the purpose of this whole game, from what I remember when I was like 12 years old,
is you have to make music videos with their crappy video editor,
and then you have to sell them to people on Earth.
Let's go ahead and have a car. That'll be the opening scene.
Yeah, we're going to have the second scene will be some cement because we need to be solidified.
We need to be set in stone. We need to make sure people know that we're like stonescaped.
And we'll have, I guess, I don't know, this car stretching like a clay car.
And then we're going to have guitars flying around.
Scene three will be pretty easy, too. So we'll have stones to show how solidified and how stone,
how rock solid we are. There's like a knife flying by, too.
All right, let's take a look at our music video that we've created.
Dogshit Burrito. Oh, man, that fucking sucked.
Hamburger bun, peanut butter, cream cheese. You know, I love mustard on my peanut butter
and cream cheese sandwiches. And you know, let's go a little strawberry jam.
That's good, too. Let's go ahead and make it.
You would have to pay me like at least 15 to 20 dollars to eat this sandwich.
I would not eat this for anything less than that, but we're going to see how it tastes.
This is going to be disgusting. Milk, hot sauce, and like Coca-Cola.
Oh, God. How is that good?
You want a lettuce sandwich?
Do not come any closer. You know what? Fuck it. Guitar fight.
Yeah, eat shit. We're going to be shooting guitar.
Did he serve?
That's bullshit.
Or I will destroy you.
No, fuck you. I'm going to kill you with my guitar.
I'm going to do you a C and then a B. Hit him. Hit him.
All right, so I spent some time in the video editor. I had a couple of sandwiches.
I had the blueberry and sardine sandwich and I started to feel a little bit more creative.
And I decided, you know what? I'm going to spend like three to four hours on making a new music
video, which I did. And here it is. How could you pass this up if you were a producer?
Let's go ahead and take a look. Should I bring the lights down, please? Okay. Enjoy.
Now we're cooking with gas.
All right, let's shop this thing around. Let's make a sale here.
Hi. I've called you before, but hello again, Stevie. Stevie Groovy.
Thank you very much. I think we can possibly, you know, send it to you right now.
Here you go. Please come on.
Thanks. I'll get back to you after I've taken a look at it.
Come on. You have to like this one.
I'll take that video. I'm not sure it's hit material.
What? What? Hold on. All right. She's going to take the video. I don't think I've ever
sold a video on this game before in my entire like 29 years on the planet. Hold on. Okay.
Like this. I can't. What's your offer? What are you going to give me for that?
Here's my offer.
10 million, 20 million, 500 bucks. That's it. I kind of want to pitch it around. I mean, if she,
if she'll take it for 500, maybe somebody else will take it for 600.
Hi. You don't know me, but I just want to say, how are you? We can, we can cut to the chase here.
I'm a big fan. Yeah. You know that I'm going to send you a music video right now and you let
me know if you like it. And if you have, you know, if you have more than 500 bucks on your hand,
then maybe you and I can, you know, work together. All right. Let's go see what he says.
I don't, I don't speak. I don't speak this. What are you saying? Did you just hung up on me?
Yeah. Stevie Groove send video to Stevie Groovy. I'll take the 500 bucks, please.
Thanks. I'll get back to you after I've taken a look at it.
Yeah. You've already seen it. Trust me. But I'm not sure it's hit material.
I know. I know it's not a hit. I'm aware of that right now, but just give me the money. Thank you.
I will take it. She dropped her offer by $200. You tell me I've been spending $50 per call.
This past like 15 minutes, just jumping around, shopping around my video. I've dropped like $500
and collect calls to people. The $300 fucking dollars she just gave me won't even cover the
cost of these phone calls. How am I supposed to break even? You know, in this, in this economy,
how am I supposed to break even in this economy? You were hot. Guess what? You're not.