Some foundry with... there's a briefcase here? What the fuck is going on there? They added
hookshots to the game? They added hookshots? This is a fucking Legend of Zelda now? How do I get one?
Where do I get one? Where do I get one? How do I... is it Q? It's gotta be Q.
It's not Q. So this item... all right, let's do... let's start hookshot. So this is just capture the
flag. Oh, watch out for this guy. So this is... this sticky new sticky launcher is all about
the quick detonations, huh? It max charges faster. This is like a combination of a lot of different
items because I can do stuff like this. What I meant to say was... what I meant to say was just
bottle this guy. That's what I meant to say. Now you know we're gonna get a hookshot.
He didn't even know what had happened. This guy didn't even know. That guy knew behind me,
but the scout in front of me doesn't. What is this? Give me this! Ooh, I got precision power-up.
What does that mean? Precision power-up? Do I have... holy shit, do you see how far that goes?
Oh my god, dude. I could like snipe... oh, you ruined it! Why am I walking around when that's in the
game? Why am I not going all over the place with that? How far does it go? Can I go all the way up
there? You've got to be shitting me right now. And these places are no longer... get up there!
No, don't fall! This guy... come here! He's gonna blow up from that one. Give me the Batman!
I got the vampire power-up. So I'm assuming I heal off of hits or something, right?
That's interesting. I'm gonna go be Batman. Be a bird of prey! I'm gonna just snipe people with
this thing. Oh my god, are you serious? I get to stay up here? This guy's not even gonna know
where I'm hitting him from. Lookit, he's just like... oh, he's hookshotting me. He's like,
what the fuck's happening? Where am I? You think you can hookshot away from me?
I'll hookshot to you! Hookshot heavy is crazy, man! Oh, what? Hookshot spy is even crazier.
Invisible hookshot. This guy's toast. That is ridiculous. You can't see me!
Where did I go? I was invisible the whole time, you see.
Again. Let's see if I can stay. No, actually, I guess I have to stay. That is so messed up.
You can just do that all over the place. And you can be invisible! It's like, really?
I have four crits right now. I gotta make use of this. Get back there. I see the mini-sentry.
I see you. I don't even need to disguise. Why would I disguise when I can just hookshot around?
Like, what's the point of disguising? Let's see if I can... I do have crits. Oh,
the warlock. Give me the warlock. I'll wait for him. Let's see. Ready? Ready? Ready? Ready?
Okay, if I can get him when he comes up. Oh, it worked. It worked. Sort of. Sort of. No,
I don't want to give up. Come here. Come here. Come here. Come here. If I just had only swung
a second earlier. Get me out of here. Oh my god. I'm freaking out right now. All right,
put a disguise on for the first time in the entire time you've been playing spy. Put
a enemy disguise on. Okay, good. Look, I'm just a demo man. Hi. I'm a demo man using my rocket
hookshot thing. Cool, huh? Oh, what? How did he know? This must be super speed.
Hookshot this way. Oh, come on. Oh, what? I should have hookshotted up there. I'm stupid.
Is this their spawn? But they're protected though, right? We can't like immediately insta kill them.
No, we can't. Whoa. I'm gonna try to hookshot kill this guy. I'm gonna go for a hookshot kill
on this guy. Where is he? Dammit. What the fuck is going on? Let's make this happen. One, two, three,
four. No, don't let him get away. So this quick fix medic. I wonder if he's going to follow me
all the way up here. Let's go. Hey, I seem to be levitating this medic. Come with me. Let's go.
We got places to go. Let's go this way now. Come with me. Let's fly. No.