All right, so welcome everybody to the meeting of the beers as you know
We do this meeting every single month to make sure we agree on things. So let's just get started
Cheeseburgers. Yeah hot dogs. Yeah donuts. Yeah bar fighting. Yeah bug collection. Yeah
Okay. Well, that's it. That's uh, the meeting of the beers has commenced. I'll see you all next month. Yeah
Germa
I'm coming. I'm coming. I'm good. Put your weapons away. Put your put your fire cars away. Okay, hold on
Don't make a scene. I'm trying just to back this
So it doesn't cause a scene. Oh
Cause the scene. All right, this thing's I
Caused the scene. I'm sorry. You're my girlfriend
Okay, if you
Take okay, take my hand
Not that hand this way
Let's go on a date. No, don't so fast. I can't keep your
Show we're going in here
All right, let's go
You're fucking asshole. You know that no, it's dude. What are you doing?
You said you want to play GTA
Yeah, that doesn't mean insta crash the server like the second we get in less than 10 seconds get again. Get me out of here
You're gonna get quit out
Oh
Wait, wait, wait, wait. Yeah, don't don't scare him. Whoa
This is a dead ninjas
In here. Well, this is dead ninja turtles lying on the ground over
Tell me what happened. I would put that in the video
What you sneezing that there's a dead ninja turtle. I liked it
Clip you sneezing like that's the dumbest thing anyone has ever sneezed
All right. Let me get on that thing. Let me try something
Let me try something. Please. Can I try something?
Let me get on the noose the caboose the goop
Seriously, I want to get on the front. I want you to shoot me in the face. Not like in my butthole
Oh my god, you are such a dick. Hey everybody. My name's star. I like to troll people because
Where am I off stop getting stuck in the fucking wall?
Can you see
That is a forever on fire
Man that was crazy. I can't believe that just happened. Hope it doesn't happen again
Yeah, yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah
Protect me my BS
Protect me
Where are they going?
They don't even know where they're going
They're awful, they're not even attacking anything. They're just running you guys suck
Come on
Somebody
Something
Get him get him beer. Yeah, you want to fuck with the beers
This goes out to the broken hearted
It's my life and it's now or never
I don't want to live forever. I just
Well, I died with God mode on I have no control over my character
Just on fire, how are you on?
So