Hey, please can you do another dot to dot stream? Oh, yeah, that was kind of fun.
That was a fun day. What's up? How you doing? You're late, Mr. Yeah, but you know what,
let's go. Let's talk about this. No streamers on time ever. This is a streamer issue. It's not
even a me issue. It's a streamer issue. It's just like, we all kind of just like things kind of,
you know, there's a lot going on right before we got to get ready. This streamer, it's us streamers
do this stuff. You know, there's tons of people that stream on time. That's excuses. You're the
problem. Nice copium. I'm at work right now. Well, be careful and you should just I don't want to
get you in trouble. Anyways, how are you? Merry Christmas. Happy holidays. Happy New Year. Let
me say all those because after today, you are not going to see me until after the New Year.
I was thinking about just not streaming and just kind of going on break and coming back in the
new year, but I feel that was kind of too long. Like two and a half weeks or something. No.
So I have some time and I have a lot of random stuff from the Christmas show.
So that was a wild day. A lot of people were a little confused, but you know, dude, you're muted.
How would I be muted if you have I'm reading comments of things I'm saying?
Yeah, that was a lot of moving parts. A lot of stuff happening on that show,
which I've wanted to do this show for about two years and just trying to find the right time
to. All right, we're going to go through that. All right, I want to go through that now.
Like bread and bread. What the hell is that? Dude, why is my P green? I don't why are you asking me
that? That's something you should you should go to urgent care and ask that question.
I don't have an answer for you. I don't know. Your P is like bright green.
I don't I don't know what that means. Answer him. I just did. I don't know. I'm not a doctor.
Did you plan to pour the coffee out with a truck beforehand? All right. Well, there's a lot to go
over. And I know a lot of people have a lot of questions. So we can just start from the beginning.
I got my throat so froggy right now. I guess I have been talking a lot.
Who? How was Santa? Who was Santa? Santa. All right. Give me a moment. Let me clear my throat.
When was Santa? Did you film the whole Christmas song? All right. So let's start. Let's start at
the very beginning. This stream had its inception about two to three years ago. I was trying to
find a way to do this, trying to find a way to make it so I would have this big event that just
would get ruined. And I feel like this was a good time to do it. It was from November 2020 based on
chat logs. That's another thing I was a little concerned about years ago. You know how sometimes
I just am in the chat, either an offline chat or post stream, pre stream. And I just kind of say
shit. Yeah, there are receipts. People link. Don't don't tell me no. And you don't know what I mean.
The amount of times that I've been linked the hamster stream, because I just write stuff in
pre stream. I just write stuff and whatever. Do I do it or do I not do it? So a long time ago,
I wrote this exact stream joke into the chat saying, oh, yeah, I was thinking about doing that.
Maybe it's funny. I don't know. And I finally did it. Obviously, a lot more elaborate than two or
three sentences in a chat room. But, you know, please, please, please do the hamster stream.
I don't think people would like the hamster stream. I really think people would have,
would be very, very uncomfortable with that. I would be uncomfortable with that. All right.
But yeah, this is something I've wanted to do for a long time. But I want to do it in a way,
too, that wasn't, you know, I know the first 10 minutes of the 15 minutes of that stream was
kind of fucked up. But I also didn't want to just kind of ruin the award show, because there was the
idea of how long should I do this for? How long does this start for? And I think after because
honestly, those first five to seven categories were dogshit categories. That was it was intentional
to be there. People were like, dude, why is worse Peter still on the list? Well, it was to buy us
time to do the real awards. If you would like to know a few of those early awards were just to make
sure that I could do the real ones on the main channel. Dude, why is worse? These these nominees
for worse Peter are terrible. This category is awful. Why is it even still here? Well, now you
know. It was filler. It was. I remember getting okay, we're getting a little ahead of ourselves
here. But I remember getting to the point where I think a lot of you thought that that was what it
was going to be the whole stream. We got about six, seven awards in. And the extinguisher was just on
the main channel. And I think a lot of people were like, I don't like this. What are you doing? No,
stop this. This I don't want to see this anymore. Please don't doll. I was looking forward to the
awards ruining Christmas. I saw the coffee pasta. I'm like, oh shit, people are like actually getting
sad. And then there was the reverse coffee pasta, which was fun, too. Yeah, that was funny. But yeah,
I wanted to make sure that we did the routine. And then okay, we're now we're just gonna do the
awards and we're gonna chill out. It's gonna be a fun cozy stream for the last hour or two,
whatever it was, right. So that's why I played out that way. Did you actually randomly mod people?
Well, how about this? No. Hey, hey, hey, the mods were in on it the whole time. The mods were in on
it the whole freaking time. No way. It was a fun stream. It was definitely it was definitely fun.
I would say that was probably I was a I was very concerned about this stream because there's a lot
of moving parts. I'm actually more so than maybe a lot of people think trying to do a stream where
you fight another stream at the same time and need to converge the two timelines together
with delays and, you know, live transcoding delays to each other. And it was very wait,
so it was a joke. Oh, no, no, no, no, no. No, no, of course not. Was it actually live? Yeah,
the whole thing was live. There's only one thing that wasn't live. And it's this guy.
This is the only thing that wasn't live. Yeah, there is. Is he okay? Bugleberry is okay.
Confirmed we had a conversation over the phone. I was very concerned, but no, he said he said he
was completely fine. He said he had a little bit of a he said his shoulder or his back kind of
hurt a little, but he'll be all right. How did he get out? I don't that's another question for
another day. I don't know. But yeah, let me put this in. So I want to ask you. Hi. Yes, I'm here.
I want to ask, do you do you guys want to watch the Bugleberry segment just without anything?
You can see like how that played out. You want to start there? Because one of the hardest things
of this whole entire stream was that and trying to work with Bugleberry. Somebody just went, nah,
not really. All right, let's let's actually let's watch it because it cut away a few times. And I
think during this portion is when we were mixing the streams together. So people were going to go
on all over the place. There was a lot of chaos. There was a lot of screaming. So do you want to
just kind of see how this actually played out? It was dim the lights. So this is this is the
actual segment. We can skip through it. We don't have to watch the entire thing. I just want to
say there's a few places that I just need to be seen because of how awesome I thought it was.
And the the BTS crew, the on the summit. Oh, they absolutely destroyed this. They killed it. It was
awesome. So anytime that I write up stuff, yeah, be on the summit. Beyond the Summit was the
production crew for the show. And it's the group that did all the camera work, all the set designing
and all that stuff. So they did an unbelievable stellar job. So but when you work with a production
company, it's really I'm so happy that there are at least a few of these companies in the space
that can listen to this crazy nonsense. And OK, so anytime I start a show, an idea for a show,
I just write a bunch of shit. I'm like, I want this and I wanted this. And here's the whole scene.
Here's a whole scene is going to play out. He's going to open up a portal to hell through the
middle of the table. And then the screams are going to come out of that. He's going like,
I just I just write shit. And then I clean it up and we get meetings and I kind of go line by
line and see, like, is this possible? Can we do this? And to hear people say, I don't know,
but we're going to try is actually very encouraging. So whenever I it's just so whenever
I get to set, right, I say this is exactly how I want it to look like. This is what I want it
to feel like. And then I get there and it's time to go. It's I love that. I love getting in there
and like directing and OK, no, I think they should be over there. Oh, what do you think? Yeah. You
think that's good. Yeah. How does it look in the camera? Let me take a look. I live for that.
Director Andy, you're a control freak. No, I'm the director. I'm the director. Dude thinks he's
Christopher Nolan. But creative direction is like some of my favorite shit. I did. That's why I do
all this stuff is because you're an aspiring film student. I'm not James Cameron. Hey, give me a
break. But my whole point with this is when you get a group together that are as passionate,
as full of passion as you are for the project, everybody just comes to work and it's like,
let's do this shit and make it awesome. So we'll go over some of this stuff.
Film student Andy. So the problem with this segment before we start, we're just because,
you know, we're going to watch it because it's an awesome segment. The problem with the segment
was trying to time talking to Bugleberry. It's going to be 10 minutes. No, we'll skip through.
So I don't want I'm not going to ruin the magic, but Bugleberry is here right now. Right. And I
had to talk to Bugleberry after, you know, Bugleberry's segment was playing. So trying
to time out how to talk. Don't skip. Okay. Trying to have a conversation with Bugleberry. It was
very hard to do. We rehearsed it like four or five times in a row. And you'll see Bugleberry,
what are you doing? What are you talking about? There he is. No, no, no. I'm going to do my
cooking segment. What are you talking about? The thing I was the most scared about was getting
it wrong. That's not fair. That's not fair. Gerber, you told me. For instance, during rehearsal.
Very specifically. You said. Watch this. Oh, Bugleberry, you can have one segment this year.
Oh, okay. You can do whatever you want. This is my one segment. Are you going to take this from me?
Yeah, I'm going to. Why exactly? Well, I think that you just have to, we're looking for you to maybe
help out and maybe cast a spell on the hacker's computer. And we're looking to. What did you do?
Oh, shit. I think I got it wrong. What did you do? Oh, I got it wrong. What websites were you on?
Let's look at your history. Right. If you get it wrong, if you can't cue up this conversation.
Is that what you did? It ruins the whole bit. Oh, okay. Which was so, that was in my brain the
entire time. Well, what do you want me to do? Let him cook. I don't have anything here. Okay,
we don't have to watch this whole thing. I don't have any of my spell books. I wonder what he would
have made. I came to make a holiday dinner. You told me to leave all of my things at home.
What was he going to cook? Don't bring the spell book. You don't need it. So it's not here. So what
do you want me to do? I just want to watch the, okay, I won't skip. Oh, bugleberry, bugleberry.
Can you please come on the show and make a turkey? Oh yeah, sure thing, German. Oh no, people that
are showing up right now. This is full screen. It happened again. We need bugleberry to do this again.
And what is this for? Is this for a hacker? Hacker, hack you? So this part in particular,
I remember we were sitting there trying to figure out how we were going to actually do this. I'm
going to do what I can, German. Just hold on, hold tight. And underneath this table,
which obviously we cut a few times, but under the table there were two people from BTS
ready to pull all this shit down the hell portal. We had to get this right. This was one take,
by the way. We couldn't do this more than once. So what you are watching had to only happen once
because otherwise we've ruined the tablecloth. Everybody, I need you to stand back and that is
you got to one take Jacob. Sometimes stand back. Everybody watching, please be careful.
I don't know what could happen here. If we got this wrong, we would have had to get,
I would have reset, get all new tablecloth, all new everything. All the stuff has already got like
stomach catch up all over it. We would have to reset the, it would take like an hour to reset
this whole scene. So as we go here, you'll say, Oh yeah, I, I take my sweet time doing this.
I forgot. Can you feel it? Can anybody feel it? I can. You need to hold on to something.
So they're under the table. These are their hands and we blocked it out in a way.
Oh, it's so cool. We need to see it again. Hello. Oh, it was very loud, but it's all right.
So again, there are people under this table and look, this is behind the scenes.
If you don't want the magic ruined, then don't put on the director commentary stream. Okay.
This, look at how this, all this stuff perfectly goes in. This was all practical. None of that
stuff was, was none of that stuff was put in after in post or anything. We actually really did that.
I think it was probably one of my favorite things I've ever done on screen.
It was fucking perfect. And all that was, was just pre people sitting under the table
ready to pull it. And we practiced it a few times. Oh, I could watch that over and over again. I love
it.
That part too.
This is a real portal to hell. Wait, what is it?
None of this is acting.
Somebody said this before, and I'll kind of add a little bit to it. Somebody said, I used,
somebody said I hated Bugleberry until it turned out to be something that when Jerma puts the mask
on, director commentary, by the way, no spoilers, and gets to kind of do whatever he wants.
And it's almost this therapeutic acting. I, I, this is my, I love Bugleberry. I love the,
I love the, the, I love Bugleberry. I don't, I don't know anything about Bugleberry besides
the fact that I, you know, I know him. The Bugleberry arc, trying to describe the Bugleberry
arc to people is so difficult because they, they, they look at you, they're looking like I'm crazy.
It's like, oh, so what, what, why, who is, what is this? Who is this guy? Oh, I put the, I did
this thing and everybody hated it. And everybody talked about how like, please don't, please God,
don't ever do that again. Please. Like that was just not funny. It was uncomfortable and it was
embarrassing. And for Bugleberry to go where he was five years ago or so, to here, where I,
I think he's one of my favorite things on this whole channel. I love this character and people
like, wait, so people hate him? Well, yeah. I mean, unironically, a lot of people do.
Why are you doing this? I don't know. Cause I feel like it. It sounds like it sounds funny.
You got him on the third try. That's right. The hot tub stream was where I think people started
to flip on them. What? What are you talking about? I cannot put the spell back in.
The spell is here now. We need to sacrifice. Also you care about very much. I'm realizing
this right now. This does not have the audio distortion. So Bugleberry real voice leak.
How about the presence under the tree? Oh, no, no, you don't want to do those. Interesting.
No, we're not going to start. That's not happening. It has to be something that you
care about. Not something that anybody. Oh yeah. Timing that too. Cause if you time that wrong.
So let's say I didn't cue that up. There'd be question marks in chat.
It'd be like, what, why did he just say that? Not happening. It has to be something that you
care about. Pre-recorded, pre-recorded. Oh, it's a bit. Let's go get those presents.
Yes. That's what we're doing. It's the only way. It's the only way.
They come get the presents. And you saw that obviously.
There's no going back. Like I already said.
Hello. Is this a new iPhone? They get bigger every year.
I love that. Can you hear the screams? I can. What's this one? Oh, sounds like an Xbox.
I don't know why I was so obsessed with Xbox. Maybe it's not.
Oh, it hits so hard.
Wait, what was that? I didn't hear that.
Is it art? I didn't know that. I didn't even hear that.
By the way, I know a lot of people were mad hearing me say this.
I don't think this game sucks. I did it for comedic effect only.
I mean, I've never played it really.
So at this point here, the hardest part of the day besides obviously doing this routine back and
forth was how do we get everybody that's on the other channel over to the main one and have people
not miss anything? And let me tell you something about fucking ads. We had to run ads in very
specific places to get rid of pre-rolls. So if you don't know, there is a system on Twitch where
if you run ads, you disable pre-roll ads on the channel for a certain amount of time.
So if we're going to be making people go back and forth, especially during an incredibly
important part like this, well, okay, the streams are coming together. We had to make sure nobody
was going to get ads coming over back to the other channel. So trying to time, all right,
run 60 seconds of ads right here in a spot where we know because that'll turn off pre-rolls for 15
minutes and then they can come over and we can time it in a way where they won't get a pre-roll
when it was a lot. You dislike ads very much. I don't dislike ads. I dislike ads that ruin content.
That's just the way it is. And if you can, running ads in certain places,
okay, it's a BRB screen or, okay, hey, I'm going to take a quick break and people know it's coming.
People know it's happening. If you have ads run during content, it just destroys what you're
doing. It just ruins what you're doing. Ads do make sense in certain places. They do and they can,
but not for no reason in random spots. And yeah, it ruins the bit. It ruins the magic. It really does.
If I'm doing something like this and you, oh, I heard, oh, German's doing a stream. Oh, oh,
there's this thing going on. I'm going to go check it out. And we're at this portion and you get like
a 30 second pre-roll ad or like a 60 second ad or something, you're going to miss this entire routine,
the whole thing. You can turn off mid-roll ads. Oh yeah, you can, but you can't turn off pre-rolls.
Pre-rolls are there. I cannot adjust them. The only thing I can do is run
mid-rolls to make sure that there are no pre-rolls for a certain amount of time.
So, and another thing too, and I don't want to get a go kind of off on, you know,
ads and money and stuff, but I'm going to for a second. Trying to, look, if I take a BRB and
let's say that there was like three or four minutes of ads or something, that means I have
to take a three or four minute break. That means I have to. That means I need to figure out a way
to do it. And if I'm in the middle of something and it's like, oh shit, I know that there are ads
that are going to be ran here for two or three minutes. Oh, okay. I'll stop what I'm doing to
make sure I don't ruin the content. You know what I'm saying? Two minutes of ads, a minute of ads,
three minutes of ads, five minutes of ads, which is why, and I'll be very honest, I'm not, I'm not
going to do any of that. I'm just not, I fucking hate it. I hate doing that. I hate fucking up
people's viewing experiences. Now, I also do very specific kinds of content like this. And that's
why I have such a strong opinion on ads, is because if I'm doing something like this and
somebody misses it for some reason, it annoys me. But I do something, I'm not, this type of shit is
where I don't want ads, but sometimes you can't avoid them. But anyways, I'm kind of going off on
a tangent here, but you are not, I'm not, let me just be very honest and tell you what's happening.
And I've said this before and I'll say it again. I'm not going to ever take one of those incentive
things, ever. It's not, it just won't happen. I can't do it. Because even if it would be a shit
load of, of, of money or something, I just, I don't want to do it. I just, I, I think of
me sitting in the chair and watching a bunch of ads and it's like, oh, but this sucks because I
missed, I literally missed this because there was a two minutes of ads in the middle of this.
Or there was like, oh, I had a pre-roll or something. It, I just hate it. I really do.
I like that part. Oh, is that a callback? Is that a callback to the pottery stream? I think so.
Oh boy. Hey, remind me to never do that again.
Actually, hold on a second. Oh, the lighting. The best part is this is practical effect lighting,
haunted house style. Cause remember Bugleberry is a Halloween character. Having the cool haunted
house type lights is what we need. Can you feel it? I can't. What do you mean?
Just a dude doing a flashlight on and off. I mean, it's a bigger, it's a bigger than that.
And you just direct the movie already. No, no, because movies are, are way more expensive than
this. They're way too expensive. You should just crowd fund it. No, because what if it sucks?
Do you really want me to do, all right, man, here it comes. Kickstarter or something for my new
movie. The new movie. Bugleberry's haunted hayride or whatever, whatever the hell it would be. I
don't know. A Jermis movie. Oh yeah. I need to make, yeah. I need to raise a two and a half million
dollars, five million dollars to do this. And I do it and the movie is dog shit. I don't, I would,
I don't know. It would keep me up at night forever. It would keep me up at night forever.
Stuff like this is just, I'm going to do it. And if I can get it paid for, cool. If not, then I'm
going to have to figure that out. But I don't know if I could take on like a large multimillion
dollar movie project and have it be terrible and ruin everything in my whole life. Oh yeah, dude,
you still owe, you know, $475,000 to this vendor. Oh, you went over budget. Hey guys. Can we do a
second Kickstarter? This is the Kickstarter to pay for all the over budget. I know the movie sucked
and you all hate me now, but can I have another 500 grand? I don't know. It would have to be
something very specific. Do a, do a subathon? No. You go into real debt. Yeah. Just do super low
budget stuff. It works. Just look at this. The, all right. The thing is though, the only reason
why this happens is because I think of something that I think would be funny. And then we go,
okay, how do I develop that? I don't just, I don't want to work in reverse. Working in reverse,
I think is a problem where instead of having something that I want to do first, it's, oh,
let's make a movie. Okay. What's the movie? If I had something that I wanted to make into a movie,
then yeah, but I don't want to work backwards. Everything you've ever seen on this channel that
took more than a few weeks to make, it was never working backwards. You just confirmed the movie.
I did not. And sure has there been random things where I've said, but yeah, but how do you make
that right now? I'm focused on some of this, turning some of these live ideas into reality.
And that's it. I don't know. I have no idea what, what the future is. You want power,
you want magical mystery. I'll give it to you. But there, these are natural. The reason why I
think a lot of people go, Oh wow, that was fun. I say, I say it's an iPhone. Wait, hold on.
That was way too big for an iPhone.
Oh, that part is so cool.
Cool iPhones for Christmas.
I don't want to go visit my grandmother.
All practical. Yeah, come on. Oh, come on. That wasn't all practical. Yeah, sorry. There wasn't
real fire under the table. That is the Fugleberry segment. I think we have, there's a lot of photos
too. Some of these you're going to very much enjoy. For instance, here are the, I'll come back for
this. Hi. So the, we took a bunch of these photos for his, and I, I, it's sad that I didn't have
that on. I wasn't wearing that during the actual shoot, but just kind of figured it would fall off
and get in the way. Especially during some of the stuff where I had to put my hand down and I didn't
want to get caught on it or anything. So Chef Fugleberry, seeing this face in 4k is, is horrifying.
Here's some of the BTS guys helping me put the hat on. Chef, please do actual Chef Fugleberry.
Yeah, like why would he do that though, right? Some of my favorite parts of Fugleberry's character
and just kind of going back and forth with Fugleberry is what is he doing here? Like why,
what, what is my relationship to Fugleberry? What is it? Why is he here? That, I, like,
am I, are we related? No, I hired him to do the scary stuff, but we've now become this,
oh yeah, Fugleberry is just going to be there. Why? And why would he do it? I don't know. It,
it just, it, I love it. I like that. This is one of my favorite photos. So yeah, this is the,
I believe this is the day, one of the rehearsals where I think we were all trying to figure out
how exactly we were going to pull this thing through. Don't typecast Fugleberry.
That's the, that was the whole point of having him show up. That whole point of having Fugleberry
show up is he, I, he wasn't typecasted this time, but he ended up having to be typecasted.
Think about that one. All right, so this is me obviously doing an impression of Fugleberry.
I'm just doing an impression of that, of that person. I figured, I was here a little,
I was here early, so they let me kind of come in and, you know, pretend like I was
doing whatever Fugleberry was going to do. See under here? That's all that was.
That's what that was. Fake magic. Every time I see that, the, the air in this room when we
nailed it first try was, we, we essentially, we, we cut the cameras not long after that
and we watched it back and we were all just sitting there going, that was fucking perfect.
That was perfect. We didn't, we're not going to do that again. That's worst impression 2022.
Get out of here. Stop ruining my immersion. Hey, this says behind the scenes of the Christmas show.
This is, you're listening to the commentary track. So yeah, that was that.
There he is. See, he showed up a little later, but you can see the setup here.
These were the lights that they were flickering and they also, we had these under here to kind
of turn them on a little higher. Why is Fugleberry wearing your sweater? I don't know. Maybe he was
fucking cold or something. And he was like, can I borrow your sweater? How come there's no picture
of you with him? We haven't seen all the behind the scenes yet. This is, this is just so, it's
so weird to look at this. Like why is he in, why is he here? Worst Boston moment. That category's
not coming back. That was a filler category for this year. Is there a penis on the wall?
There's no penis on the wall. Yeah, I know this camera is fucked up. Whatever. 15 minutes on
Friday. So here's, here's part of the rehearsal with Santa, who the, that real Santa, that real
Santa was amazing. Took direction incredibly well. Was super funny. Just an absolute pro.
Just a comp, just an absolute complete pro. And we're obviously just kind of going over
how it's going to be and minimum one hour lunch. We'll hash it out. I'm actually sorry.
Did you sit on his lap? No. Because okay, it was like, what, what, what do I want to do when he's
in here? And no, you should have. It's literally Santa. Yeah. Why are your thighs so big? What is
going on? Why do I have such huge thighs? What is, this is unedited. This is unedited. What is
going on? No, no, this is something weird here. I think it's because my pockets were full of stuff.
No. All right. This is what's happening. This is what's happening. In each one of these pockets
is a microphone holder. We were doing audio testing and these pants were a little tight.
They were a little tight if I remember. So there was two huge things. I had like my phone. I had
a mic pack. I had an audio pack and it was inflating my hips. That does look crazy.
That looks so fucked up. Oh my God. I feel like there's another, I feel like there's a body
going back and another pair of legs. Like this is a centaur. You know what I'm saying? Like there's
a back this way and legs here. Holy shit. What's happening? All right. Anyways, behind the scenes
that was Santa Santa. We, we only had Santa for a little while. So we had to really nail that,
which a lot of the stuff really just, there was so much stress and anxiety on getting to these
points correctly. Every meeting we had, every time we were sitting here on the, on the deck,
which is essentially a stage kind of going over where people are going to be standing and how it's
going to play out. Okay. In the back of everybody's mind, it's, are we actually going to be able to do
this? I don't know, but we're going to find out really soon. And I think that's what I,
that's what I like the most is, is this going to work? Will it actually make sense? I think it's,
it's challenging in a way. Pixar mom. Well, it's a live show. So yeah. Yeah. It's a live show with a
lot of stuff happening. Stop talking about his thighs. All right. I'm going to move on from this.
This one better not be worse. So this is practicing the bugleberry segment,
which was, we did this probably five times over the course of a few days.
The channel, the channel was hacked. I'll make it up to you. We need some help. I need, we have
engineers here doing all kinds of shit. It's not there. Yeah. So that's this rehearsal.
Who played bugleberry? A mystery, a mystery actor, mystery actor. What do you mean actor?
Who played, what do you mean? Yeah. Let's go back a little further. What do you mean?
The real person. What do you mean actor? But yeah, that's some video footage. There's a picture or
two. This is weird to look at. This is just a kind of a view of the whole set. So originally I was
going to walk behind the tree and destroy the tree in the beginning. You know, in the beginning where
I'm kind of yelling at everybody, I'm telling everybody to shut up. One of the, originally it
was like, I want to go back here and I want to pull the fucking tree down and walk back and get
backstage here. But turned out it's probably a dangerous thing to do.
Pulling a tree down like that, connected to a bunch of wires. It was just, it was like,
eh, we probably shouldn't do that. That would have been probably pretty bad. So we decided not to do
it. Somebody in this building did. Now this is the rehearsal for this. Otherwise you and I had done,
by the way, this was made for us. Jerma, Jerma, Jerma, hey. People's heads like high heels.
Otherwise you and I had done, by the way, this was made for us.
The strut. So people were asking if I was supposed to throw the coffee in Atriox's face.
And I decided not to. No, I wanted just to dump it on the ground without even mentioning it because
what a fucking piece of shit. Like this is just, I'm just going to dump this because it's not the
way that I wanted it. And I can already tell that by looking at it. So I'm just dumping it on the
ground and someone's going to clean that up for me. But no, it wasn't because I didn't want to
throw it. Actually, Atriox actually did say, hey, dude, throw that coffee in my face if you want.
I'm just like, ah, do you want to do it? He's like, yeah, dude, if you want to throw it in my face,
just throw the coffee directly in my face. And we decided against it because he had to show up a
little later, obviously, for the 1v1. But we also, if you look at how it played out,
well, it doesn't show it here. But the scary part was because the person that's back here
with a huge camera and the concern was dumping it on the ground right here because this,
the cameraman follows me through when we were blocking this whole thing out.
All right, you're going to follow me through here. We're going to go this way. And being in this
position where the cameraman had like 40 pound camera, this was dangerous walking through that.
So what we had to do is I had to make sure that I dumped it kind of over almost in this doorway,
like back here. So he could walk through it without having to be scared of tripping.
This is a pose. This is a pose. Stop. Stop it. This is a pose. I'm not getting any height from
this. It's the pose. This is a pose. All right, let's prove it in real time.
Okay, still doing it. Still doing it. Where's the height? Where's the height change? There is no
height change. It's exactly the same. Exactly the same. Proving that it is a pose again once
and for all. There is no change in height from here to here. It's exactly the same.
Somebody said, I, before going to look for these two, I go, where's Ludwig? I need to talk to him.
And then I finally run into him and I just go, I don't want to talk to you. Get out of here. Go
clean that up. I was like, well, I, that's who I was looking for. Oh, here's the, uh, here's the
toast. I know it's, I mean, whatever. It's a thing. So before every show, yeah, I got caught on the
hot mic. I got caught on the hot mic. Whatever. So before every show, if people want to do it,
we do a toast. And it's, you know, it's like, if you, if you don't, if you don't drink, if you
don't feel like, if you don't want to, obviously if you have stuff going on later, don't, you know,
don't be drinking and shit, right? So you don't have to, but we do this thing. Everybody takes
a shot of whatever we have, whatever anybody wants. And we go, let's do it. People say a few
words. It's a nice way to kind of just be like, let's go for it. Alcohol Andy. What is in here?
I think that they had, I want to say this was Jim Bean or Jack Daniel. It was, it was, I think it
was Jim Bean. What did you drink? I think it was just Jim Bean. But yeah, I, the, the point is not
with this, the point is not to, oh, everybody, let's get drunk. That's not the point. It's just
a kind of a, it's like a toast at a wedding, right? Except it's not a wedding. Did you do the cat
puke sound? This is theater kids simulator. Um, theater kid. What are you, what, theater kids
backstage? What are you talking, drinking? What are you talking about? What the hell do you mean?
I am an adult. Your feet aren't on camera. You're on your tippy toes. All right. I banned that person
actually for an hour. I want that person timed up for one full hour and then reduce that by,
by 50 minutes. I want them timed up for 10 minutes. Time the person up for 10 minutes.
But yeah, it's, it's just something to do. It's something to, it's so funny how I treat a lot of
these events. It's important that everyone has fun. That's one of the most important things.
So if everyone's here having a good time, it's treated like a fun get together in a way. Everyone
just has more fun and everybody cares more about it. So I like doing that kind of stuff. So it's
not just like, okay, you're everybody, you do your job. You do your job. Stop. Okay. You, you're
going to talk to me only when, when we're going to talk about work stuff and you're going to show
up here and then, okay. And then we'll talk maybe for five seconds and you'll never see me ever
again. No, I would rather do it and have everybody essentially treat it like it's a time where we're
getting together and have a fun time. They're not visible. Again, time that person up for one
minute diminishing returns. So this is the end. It was so good. I was blown away by how unbelievable
top shelf vocalist. Can we just give a round of applause for a second? That was so, that was
unbelievable. Four people, right? Four. They just, it just sounded like a whole chorus of like 15
people. It was so good. See you later. I felt so bad too, because when we were going over rehearsals
and like directing, what's going to happen. Okay. So directing, right? Directing. So it's like,
okay, well I, what I want to happen here is this is what's going to happen. This is how it plays
out. We're going to be standing here. And what I want is, you know, you're going to be singing
and then I'm going to join you and we're going to get cut off. And cutting off a very talented
singing group within 10 seconds of their first song is just that, that sucks. And we wanted to
make sure that they had a very good amount of screen time to get a full kind of five minutes
on camera doing a few songs. It was evil. Yeah. But I thought it was fun. And they were super,
super into it too. They were so fun to work with. They got it immediately. All the elves here too.
Oh, the cookies. Right. Oh, Bugleberry. Yeah. This is, this is literally the lap. I think the
camera was off at this point. Look at how tall everybody is. All right. Can we go over this?
Look at how tall all the off-brand guys are. They're gigantic. They're so, look at how tall
they are. They're towering over everybody. Come on. Everyone talked about, wow, dude,
Santa was so much. Santa was like six, five, six, six. He was a very tall man. See you later.
That was the end. Oh, a dog that, uh, BTS had just kind of dogs hanging out. They were, uh,
people would bring their dogs to work, which was, it was so cute. Good dog. It's a presence.
This is just, we're taking pictures of stuff just to remember it. Oh, audio equipment. I think these
pictures just show how much thought went into what, because this was just a set. Nothing here did
anything. Nothing. All of this stuff was just to make it look like this was a room that was a
behind the scenes room. There's nothing here is like connected to anything. Oh, that's a good
picture. That's a Christmas card. And these two were connected to each other. So they were just
part of the set. Holy jolly Christmas. Oh, there he is. There's the, the coming into the clutch.
That thing was actually full of toys. That was a full bag of toys. That's a great photo too.
Now here's the beginning. Yeah, there is the hacker. Well, we'll go back for a second here.
So in the very beginning of this stream, I think people were saying, what's wrong with him?
Why is he acting so off? It's like trying to do that overly kind of that overly positive atmosphere.
But in like a really off putting way, somebody said, dude, you look like you made out of wax
and stuff. Like this is, this was scary. People said this was scary. The way that I was like
acting and talking the first like 20 minutes of the stream, you were acting like Ellen. It was very
off putting. Good. That's what I wanted. Do you have make? Yeah. I have a bunch of makeup on too.
These look like stock photos. He was awesome. Here's the real production room. Not the fake
one that you saw already. This is the real production room. This is where they were all
adjusting things, pumping in the videos, getting things ready, adjusting, switching cameras. This
is the actual set. This is the, yeah, this is the NASA set. This is the real one landing crew.
You should have used this. Well, I mean, no, I can't because the whole point of that fake production
room, I mean, look, you're on whatever XQC six consoles. Anyways, when you're gonna do a moon
landing stream, that actually would be kind of funny to have a huge set up like this with like
a hundred monitors. And it's me going into space and just a bunch of shit goes wrong. And there's
a whole room of like 50 people issuing me commands and stuff. Do it. I don't know. Space station
stream. How would you even do that? I don't know. How did we do this? Just figure it out.
Yeah. So again, this is the fake room. We had the two engineers here. Those were, those were just
actors. They just sat there just typing the whole day. Who the fuck are you? Oh, that's right.
I love it. So this is, we're going over kind of the, how the day is. So this is, this is probably
15 to 20 minutes before the stream, maybe like 30 minutes before the stream. And we're going over,
just because a lot of people showed up for the day. You're, he's short. I'm a very, all right,
you know what? Time out that word. There's no pose here. Look, there's no pose. All right. I'm
not going to address it anymore. Do you know how tall people really are? Good. You know what? I'm
a little bit smaller. Who gives a shit? You know how fucking strong I am and how tough I am?
Anyways, a lot of people showed up the day out. So trying to get everybody up to speed that wasn't
around for the last four or five days of setting up all this stuff. So kind of have to give the
overview of exactly what's happening for the day. Extinguisher exposed. He was, he's in this photo.
How did he do that? So to me, this is, the show's over, right? And it's just like, oh, thank God.
To me, that's like a, oh, it's done. Everybody working. Here are the elves just hanging out,
preparing for the day. They were awesome too. Every single one of them was just kind of,
when we did the breakdown. Oh, look, Doug. When we did the breakdown, it's just, okay, so you're
going to do a puzzle, but you don't actually have to. You can kind of do whatever you want in here.
I probably shouldn't have said that. I probably shouldn't have said, oh, you can just do whatever
you want. Don't even do the puzzle if you don't care. It actually made it way funnier, I think.
When I, when we checked in halfway through the stream and there was, it was just pieces on the
ground and they were just sitting at the table. What was the purpose of the elves to do the puzzle?
And we were going to check in on them and see their progress. It's just pieces dumped on the
ground. To be fair though, let's be very fair. That picture, I don't know if we can see it,
the picture that they were doing was that promotional picture from about four or five
days before the show. Almost every piece is the same color. I think it was actually impossible.
Look at just this one because it's actually pretty hard to find or buy a puzzle that's 10,000 plus
pieces. So these are four individual two or 3000 piece puzzles each. So it's just a quadrant of
the image and they were supposed to put it together. So how do you even do this part?
Because this part just is this part. It's just a image of lights. How would you ever do it?
Impossible. Even getting a border would be impossible. I think at one point we would like,
we just kind of like, oh, is it really hard? Just try to do the face. The face, this section is the
same color as all this. It's just the same thing. Every piece was like red or orange. I don't know.
I just want to see what would happen. You have a fucked up brain, man. Yeah, well, is that right?
We'll have fun here. You have a fucked up brain. So this was the camera op and this, he wasn't
supposed to do this. He came up to me and was like, hey, do we have any extra elf costumes?
I'm like, ah, I think so. Maybe. Let's find out. He's like, I just kind of want to wear one. So I
make sure I'm in the shots dressed like this. I was like, all right, that's perfect. That's a great
idea. Go for it. But look at that thing. Look at this camera. That's why we were concerned about
putting the Dump in the Coffee directly on the ground, because that's scary. Oh, look, an elf.
I love that rig so much. This was elaborate. This was spring loaded. I swear when he was
walking around, it was like, he was like a robot. This thing was like compressed air and spring
loaded. It was crazy. Oh, look at that. I don't think we're gonna, you know, I didn't think we're
gonna put in the wholesome Ludwig hug. Come on. Which the off-brand was awesome. And when I
originally trying to pitch the show around to a production company or a group that wanted to
tackle it, it was, all right, who has time? Who wants to try it? Who wants to go for it?
And off-brand, they were just like, let's do it. And it was a really short time frame, too.
Um, I kind of got the urge really, because this show, I wrote all this stuff probably
a year and a half ago, two years ago. Didn't ever do it. I swear to God, this show sat as a
document in a folder of just a few, like three or four pages of just shit that I just let sit there.
And I finally was like, you know what? I'm doing it this year. I want to do it. So, uh, talking to
off-brand to try to get it off the ground was just, they were so into it immediately. And I
believe it was like the last week of October where I was like, hey, I want to put together a whole
elaborate Christmas streamer. A bunch of crazy shit happens. And here's, here's the, here's the
script and here's all the stuff. Here's the, here it is. And they were just like, what the fuck?
Holy shit, dude. All right. Um, yeah, let's go for it. And we banged this project out in one month.
It was one month, maybe even less than that. So they didn't know they did a hell of a job.
Oh, of course there's more elves. Engineer. It's like the, it's like the creep. Like I just looked
like creepy. Wow. This is scary. I don't like this photo. Holy shit. This is right at the turn.
Oh, do I have gray hair? This photo is actually pretty scary. Uh-oh. Mask coming off. And this
also too. What is wrong with you if you were to do something like this? Oh, I'm going to join in too.
What do you, sit down, you idiot. Sit down. You're not doing that. You hire a group to come and do
this and then you're just going to be part of the group and sing with them. This is the kind of shit
that if you're at like a company meeting or like a company party, and that's where a lot of the,
a lot of the ideas that I had for the show were from that kind of thing. Like company party,
where the CEO gets up there and tries to kind of act like, um, yeah, it's, well, I'm, I'm,
I'm one of the workers and I'm super smart and I'm super funny and I'm very talented
and I'm going to show you and everybody here loves and respects me. That was the vibe. So why,
what are you, what are you doing up there? It was just so painful and a lot of people,
I'm looking back, I've seen a lot of clips and stuff and a lot of uploads and highlights and,
and comments. It feels being like this part, I hated more than anything. This is the worst part.
Michael Scott type beat. I was just going for, because you got to let people do what they're
good at. And I think a lot of this stream was let people do what they're good at and don't
implant and insert yourself into other people doing interesting things, I think.
Super in character. He's ready, he's reading, he's getting ready, getting ready for me to grab him.
Why do you look so mad? Did you watch the stream? You see what happened? Do you have any idea what
happened to me that day? Still got it. Still got it. He was furious. He's still mad. By the way,
do you see what this says? I think this says late night with Ludwig. I believe that's what
that actually says. So by the way, this is actually the run of show. So what a run of show is. So a
couple of weeks before we would get into meetings for an hour or two every couple of days, I'd say,
and we go over point by point exactly what is going to happen at every moment of the show.
And when you get one of these, you need to stick to it. Otherwise, it can really go off the rails
when people just don't know what's happening next. So if you change a run of show, you have to make
sure that everybody knows you're changing it. And we did. We actually changed the run of show.
We were not supposed to do the we were not supposed to stay with the awards. We're supposed to go all
the way through, I believe, like 12, 13, 14 awards before we did the merge. So we essentially I
thought that was going to be too long because as we were doing the first 20, 30 minutes,
it was it was becoming pretty clear that I was I want this to go a little faster.
I want to merge sooner. So we kind of copy and paste. Oh, shit, sorry. We copy and pasted.
This is during the show, by the way. This is during one of the BRBs. It was like we
took the parts that happened before the merge and just moved them forward so we could get right to
it. I didn't want people to stick around because when it became pretty clear that people were
actually thinking that this is what the joke was and that was it. I was like, oh, this channel is
compromised and he's on this other channel just doing the awards. All right, that's kind of funny,
but like, it's like, I don't know. I'm out of here. So we wanted to make sure that we got through that
faster. You got to go sometimes. But I think it was right at that perfect time period where people
started to go, what the fuck, dude? Please. So we just moved it immediately. Were you afraid of
people reporting the channel? Yes. And for weeks we talked to Twitch to tell them this was happening.
Hey, Twitch, this is happening. This is not real. And they had to, I mean, because obviously they
had to know. If they didn't know, then that would, I'm sure the channel probably would get turned
off pretty quickly. No, this is the puzzle. Do you see, oh, by the way, behind here, this is the snow,
the snow part. How did you merge the streams? So, I mean, German985, this channel was just live
and we've raided my channel from the other one. And then when the raid happened after the raid,
we made sure it went through. And then the other, the other stream was turned off. It just,
we just turned it off. So there was only one place where everything was going to be.
What is this pose? What the hell, what is this? What is this? Oh, very rare, complete back of the
head, by the way. Very rare. And I'll tell you, it's a, it's thinning a little, but pretty clean,
pretty clean back of the head. Probably could've used a little, I probably could've styled it a
little more. He's balding? Oh, I mean, not really. A little. Whatever. Fine. Oh, this,
where the thing hits me in the head. Nice Lego hair. Yeah, I pressed the wrong button. A stage
weight hits me in the head. Was it scripted? Yeah. It missed you. It hit me like on the forehead.
It went like, it scraped the top of my head and like scraped my nose. It's all right. It still,
doesn't matter. It still worked. How heavy was it? It was very heavy. No, it wasn't heavy at all.
The ice pack. I think I am going gray. I think it is happening. Right here, look. 4K camera.
You can't hide it. Maybe a little. Uh-oh. Uh-oh. This is right after the break when we came back
of me yelling at everybody and getting hit in the head. These things always fall out of my ear.
I remember this was such an issue for me. Uh, that before Dollhouse, we actually made a custom
one that I had to actually go, I had to go to a special lab to get a, a mold of the inside of my
ear. Just because these things always fall out. I always have such trouble with them. This feels
like it was upscaled. That's how good this camera is. Oh, best bro. That's the first one. You look
completely different in every picture. It's just, it's just angles. It's angles. So my,
my face is, and my hair is kind of different. This part of, this half of my face. Remember,
I've talked about this before. People that go, dude, why do you look like a different guy
in this picture? I'll tell you. Because I have an angular face. My face is pretty angular. So my face
kind of goes like this. My face goes like this. It's kind of sideways. So when you see from this
angle, you're seeing it go this way. When you, when I go like this, you're seeing the other part
where it's angled a different way. You know what I mean? My chin's a little more pronounced on this
side. It's because it's angular this way. My nose is kind of this way. Yeah. So it's just, it looks
a little different. You know what I mean? You're making this up. I am not making this up. That's
why everybody says that. Troll face. One thing I'll tell you though, one thing I am very, very
concerned about. I'm getting concerned about this and that's how you know I'm getting older.
I'm starting to get the turkey neck. Do you see what I mean? It's happening. I'm getting,
I'm kind of getting that like tortoise turkey neck. Uh-uh. Uh-uh. I'm gonna start moisturizing
that area. I'm gonna start to like, moisturize this area. Tighten it up. Uh-oh. It's starting.
Yeah, it's starting. I'm getting, it's happening. This is what happens when you turn 40.
Moist neck Andy. You're insecure. No, I'm really not. I'm just messing around. I'm very
comfortable with uh, with me. So I'm good. Another scary image. I love how he's just not
paying, he's kind of just ignoring me. Just hanging out with the boys. There it is.
Watching it on, that's funny. How the hell were they ever gonna do this? How are you ever gonna
do this? Let's be real. How were you ever going to do that? These swabs? Oh, oh, right, right,
right, right. For, okay. I was like, why does he have cotton swabs in his hand? Because we did the,
oh, I'm boxing, right? Okay. We're gonna give you like the, on the lip. Give you the uh, the ice pack.
The water, he kept squeezing the water and I opened my mouth and I would close my mouth and he would
keep squeezing it. You're doing COVID testing? This is a great shot. He was stealing your DNA.
I love the green of the room too. It just comes to life here. So if you want to know, the, the
set designer is the same set designer that did Juiced. You remember Omega Juicer, right? It's
the same exact person. They did an amazing job. She's one of those people that you can just say,
this is what I want it to look like and here's uh, here's some, a few paragraphs of what it looks
like. Can you make that a reality? Bet your ass I can. And it was better than I ever imagined.
This set was better than I thought it was going to look. It was just way better.
Bottom left face. That is a face. You're right. Did you actually play Cod? Yes. It's like,
ah, the bros, the bro is cheering on their bro in the finals of his fantasy football league
is what this looks like. Why do I look so weird? Like the last game of the season, man,
I could get the whole pot. I come with the whatever. This more Bugleberry.
Was the loss scripted? Yes, it was. Sorry to say. And when I was up like 3-0 in that first round,
I was like, oh shit, I actually can't win this because we had to, it wasn't scripted.
It wasn't planned. I'm lying. I'm sorry. I lied to you. Throwing for content. I was up 3-0.
I said, was the Bugleberry footage pre-recorded? So we, um, at the beginning of the stream,
we went over the whole thing. Yes, this whole thing was pre-recorded. Um, it's, I'll give you
a quick fun story. So, chess boxing, if you remember, I did the announcing. I actually
missed the rehearsal for chess boxing. I couldn't go because we were filming this. So, the day
before, before the chess boxing event, I was supposed to be at rehearsal and this was our,
we already planned to do this. So I missed the rehearsal and did this instead. And then the next
day, chess boxing. And then a week later, did this. He was directing Bugleberry. He's a director.
How come the extinguisher isn't streaming right now? I think the extinguisher did a stream
and talked about some behind the scenes stuff. It was awesome to work with. He, honestly, he came
in at such a clutch because originally the extinguisher was going to be one of these two.
That was what that actor was going to do. And we lost our, we, we had somebody cast as the hacker
already and we lost out on that. Um, there was some issues with getting that person to be able
to be in that, in this spot at this time. So very short notice. And this is, I'm not, I'm not even
talking two days before the show, three days before the show. It was somebody else has to be
the extinguisher. So came through and the clutch actually crushed it. And that was on three days
notice. Not even probably. Yeah. Well, Josh just linked the, if you want to hear some more behind
the scenes stuff from the extinguisher's point of view, there's a link in the chat right there.
But yeah, it just all came together and the room turning red with, we had the portal and everything
It got really weird. Yeah, there you go. Was the hacker always called the extinguisher?
No, we, we kind of bounced around a few names and it was like, should I be German986? Should I be,
you know, um, you know, like the murderer or something? We were just trying to figure out
random names. Nice theater shot. You said there's a shit stain on my pants? Oh, you said there's,
whatever. Why did I even read that? Why did I read that? This is what I strangled him.
Yeah, there was a, there was a production person that was just hanging out under his desk, just
like out of frame. And every time we, we obviously rehearsed this a few times and figured out exactly
how it was going to happen. It's actually so funny because I don't know if we should, if I could show
it, but when I put my leg through, this is a different pair of shoes. This is like, there's
not, I'm very clearly was wearing dress shoes and they were just these nice sneakers. So what
happened? You going through a portal, change the shoes. It was, hey, portals, fuck with stuff.
It was a poor, hey, it was a portal. Can't be perfect. Santa again. And you are going to
apologize. He was the real deal. He, you knew when he was walking around, he made noise. You could
hear Santa from down across the entire studio. He was wearing bells. It was just like, when he
would take a step. I think we actually had him take them off. So people weren't, wouldn't hear
it through the mic. My God, what the fuck? My eyes don't even look real. Those, my eyes don't look
real. They don't look like real people eyes. This doesn't look like a real person's eyes. Why are
they so like gelatinous? They're gelatinous. That's weird looking, the puzzle room. Oh, they actually
got Santa back there. I knew he was back there. Cool. See how big looking Santa is, is really
tall. I think this is when we chilled out and we just did the awards. Yeah. At this point,
I think it was like, it's time to relax because now we don't have to worry about any weird,
crazy shit. We're just going to do the awards now, which I hope that as the kind of day went
along, I was really hoping that people would, after all the weird stuff. All right. Now we're
just chilling. And this is just, we're hanging out now. I hope that came across. Yeah. Okay. Good.
It was good. Yeah. Cause I know a lot of people were looking forward to this and
every year we do this and I didn't want to ruin it. I wanted to kind of keep that same vibe. When
we did get back on the main channel, I wanted to have that same vibe from previous years.
We were just kind of chilling, hanging out, laughing. There was no rumble. No, there was no
time to do a rumble this year because this has obviously took up all the time that I would have
done something like that. And plus, I mean, if I, if I can't think of, for instance, okay,
should there be a rumble during this? I don't think it would have fit. I think it would have
been too much going on. So it essentially replaced it. I think it would have been way too disjointed
if it's, okay, guys, the channel we got, it's on a different channel and we're going to do the awards
and here comes the first match on the channel. Am I going to do it? I feel like people would be
like, what? I can't even pay attention, dude. Like, what the fuck is going on? But I, I don't want
to give away anything, but there, there I do. No, we're not going to talk about it. We're not
even going to talk about it. But no, there's not going to be a, there's not going to be a stream on
New Year's this, this time. I'm going to take some time here after this stream because it's been a
very, very busy, pretty chaotic few months. And I definitely want to just take a little bit of time
and spend time with people that I want to spend some time with, friends, family. There's, there's
a lot of catching up to do, I think. So I'm going to, after this, just kind of take off for a little
bit. When is Battleaxe? You'll see. You'll see. But yeah, I think this is getting to the end.
Oh, this is the best singing. That's right. We did best singing, worst singing, and then they
actually came on and did their routine. I'm just saying. I'm just saying. Top shelf vocal. Looking
for to hire a group that's phenomenal. I'm telling you. Oh, the misery. Had any of the actors or
production crew watched your streams before? Were they unfamiliar? Some of them did. I would say it
was probably 50-50 of people that have actually seen the stream before versus people that kind of
knew that the channel existed. It was probably, I think most people knew what the channel was,
but maybe not to the extent of some of the stuff that was happening. Did Atriok know who you were?
Yeah, I've hung out with Atriok many times in real life. He said, no, he didn't know. Imagine
he just didn't know who I was. Like all the times we've spent in real life together and he just
doesn't even remember. He's like, oh, I've never heard of you. That would be so awful. What would
you even say to something like that? Can you imagine if it's hanging out at least, at least
three times in real life? And this is not just, oh, hey, nice to meet you. It's like, oh, no, no,
we've literally been in the same room for six, seven straight hours together, multiple times.
To have later on, it'd be like, what's your channel again? What's your name? It'd be like,
dude, oh, come on. No, no, of course not. He's awesome. I don't know if you knew this,
but one of the elves is the best Smash Brothers Melee Donkey Kong player in the world. I did hear
that. I did hear that. That's awesome. In the world. Yeah, it was Ringler. Everyone was so nice, too.
It makes me happy every time doing something like this, just after the effort's all done.
It's just like kind of the smiles on everybody's faces. That's worth it. This stream is loud.
It's not. Volume's fine. You're getting one guide. Okay. Do you feel, do you feel pressure to remember
everybody? Um, I don't, I don't really see it that way. It's kind of just if people show up and
they're having fun and maybe I've heard of them before, maybe not, because I don't really know
very many people in the space. Very recently, the last year or so, I've actually even really
started talking to other streamers. That's pretty new. So I kind of don't really know very much of
the space already. So do you know me? I don't know. Yeah, off-brand connected me with BTS.
That was integral to this whole thing happening. So I thought we were friends. I don't know. I'm
sorry. I gotta be realistic. Is this the first time you worked with BTS? So in a production setting,
yes. Not, I mean, I was on Juiced, an episode of XQC's show, and they were doing it. So I've
worked kind of with them before, but never as, you know, part of the team to get a show off the
ground. I showed up and was on Juiced and obviously met most of the people that worked on this show,
but didn't, it wasn't part of any production stuff until this one. This is, I'm not punching
somebody, okay? This is, this looks like I'm like, I think we were, I think I was describing
something that I wanted to have happen. No, I'm not punching anybody. He was awesome too.
The Bugleberry video editing was between, I think, a couple different people, because there was the
VFX stuff that was on, there was the actual editing, and it's just, everybody did such a
great fucking job. Practical effects. Dude, stop showing your vacation pics and play Yakuza.
That was a good one. Don't time that person out. That was a good one. Hey, the snow! The snow.
Here's the thing about the snow. BTS is going to have at least a year or two worth of packing
material, because they're going to just repurpose this. Oh, didn't I, I put this in my, I chewed this
up, didn't I? I did, I picked, I picked up this, I was chewing it, it was on ground. Why did I do that?
I've just, I had like, a memory just kind of unlocked. That was weird. Yeah, and ruining the
puzzle too. Yeah, I did. Was that not on camera? Was it not on camera? It was, it was, okay. Now,
that's my desktop background. I haven't changed my desktop background since Windows 7 came out,
okay? Just for you to know. Why? I don't know, because I don't, when I get on the computer,
I go. It's time to do whatever I'm going to do. And it's not, I don't have any time to look at my
background. It's just, as long as it's just an unoffensive thing. Okay, mountains or a beach
or water. Just no, no, nothing going on. Just something that I don't, I just don't even need
to look at it. I usually turn my computer on and within five seconds of it booting,
a program is open taking up the screen anyways. I just don't, I just don't look at the background
and I don't think about it. Yeah, I used to change my background, but then I would be lazy
and it would be wallpaper for a game that came out four years ago. Or you know, no, no, not even
that. Like wallpaper for a DLC that came out. And it's like, that's not even relevant anymore. And
I just spend so much time. I think the last time, honestly, I think it was Reaper of Souls came up
and I was like, oh yeah, I'm going to put that angel as a background and stay there for like
three years or something. And I just, I was like, why do I have this elves playing in the snow?
Of course they are. There's bugleberry hanging out with some dogs. I think some of you have seen
this already. Not a real PC, fake PC type loud. There's, there's their script for the engineers.
Not a real PC, fake PC type loudly. Just, hey, pretty good. Hey, pretty good. Yeah, this is
obviously, this is the off-brand group. There's bugleberry's cookies. Don't leak the script.
Jerma, are you bugleberry? I mean, that's impossible considering he's in the room right now.
That's not possible. Pretty good hair here. Pretty good hairline. That's well lit too. That's a light
beaming down on the top slash back of my head. But no, this is a good moment. Why did you not,
why did you give them fake computers? Because I didn't want a real computer there. They're just
supposed to be pretending to be hacking and engineering, right? If there was a real computer
there, they would have been opening up random stuff. You know, they would press like Windows
space, like G or something and open up like the help menu. No, it was just, there's nothing there.
You look pretty tall here. Sick. I like this picture. They're all tall. It feels good though.
Finally, putting to rest the rumors that we are the same person. Finally, putting those rumors to
rest. Magic is real and I just proved it. There's no way, there's not a chance that during the live
portion of this stream, somebody was being a body double and put the costume on to do some of those
routines to make that seem like a real thing. Out of the question completely. There's no way.
Not possible. Magic is real. Don't believe the haters. And then here's the crew. Tons of people
here did a lot of stuff that you didn't see. BTS and some of their connections, they was great.
I'm so happy with it. Three of you are doing the same pose. Yeah, it's a picture. What's with you
guys and where hands are in photos? You know what I mean? Okay, can't go like this. Can't go like
this. Can't go like this. Can't go like this. You don't stand like, come on. People have different
ways that they stand in pictures. Did you increase the elves pay? It's funny you say that. I actually
a day or two ago sent a message to the group, to like the BTS group. It was like, hey,
let's actually do that. We should actually do like, we should give them an extra.
I said that like a few days ago, so it's fun. Five times zero is still zero. How did they even get
this in such a short amount of time? And then one more. And that's it. I accidentally used my Prime
sub and I'm now a founder for the RealGermaChristmas channel. Yeah, how many people subbed
to that channel? Could you have? I wonder what happens to those subs going just, all right,
well then whatever. That'll help pay for the stream. How come everyone's pointing? I don't know. I
think one person did it and then we all did it. Like, yeah, we're, let's go. I don't know. Why
did we all start pointing? I think it was like, number one? I don't know. Why did we point? Did I
start going like this? Or am I following somebody here? I wonder who the first person was to hold
their finger up. Mario post looking ass? Mario? That's actually fucking perfect. Mario! It's
Super Mario! Oh! I don't know. It was supposed and it was cool and everybody here is awesome.
Nah, hell of a job. And that's it for the year. I'll hang up for a little bit longer. Anybody have
any more questions about it? I don't want to give every single thing away because I feel like it's
more fun that way, but I gave a lot away. Switch between the two images really fast.
Yahoo! Oh my god. Was Puzzle Girl scripted? No. Before we started the stream, I genuinely went in
there and just walked around for maybe 15, 20 minutes and just was talking about stuff to do
in here and said, you know what? You guys are kind of free to do whatever you want. As long as, I mean,
obviously gave them a list of rules to follow for the grand scheme of things, right? But they were
able to creatively just kind of have fun, just do whatever. Was the face paint scripted? No.
Atrioc just kind of showed up with that. I think he found it somewhere. And I thought that was one
of those ice packs. So I thought he was icing my cheekbones. I was like, yeah, yeah, so come on.
You're going to come over here. I'm going to be sitting and you're going to give me snacks. You're
going to grab a bottle of water, hyping me up, you know, maybe put some ice pack on my face,
like as if I just got punched in the face during boxing. And that's what I thought that was. So he
just put it on. I was like, okay, that's what this is. Do you think next year you'll fail as if you
have to top the production quality? No, I don't think like that. I think that can intrude your
brain a lot. And if it has to be bigger and better every single time, you eventually hit a point of
no return where nothing can happen now because you've gone too far. So it's just if I have
something that I think is a fun idea, I'll just do it. That's pretty much it. There's no rhyme
or reason to it. There's no special quota that I want to hit or special amount of money that
something has to cost or how many people have to be involved. If it sounds fun, I'll do it.
And sometimes those things can happen very quickly. There are a couple of ideas that I
want to do this coming year that are not going to be huge, huge, big, big events that require
tons of people, but they're there. Maybe they will be. I don't know. Are you going to upload
these somewhere? I think a few of the highlight channels are starting to get the footage and
they're starting to upload them. The second channel, I think I'll have to get in touch with
the second channel people. Something's wanting to be perfect prevents it from happening. It's
better to half-ass something than to not do anything. Well, I don't think half-ass is the
right answer, but you're the first part I think is correct. If everything has to be perfect,
you'll never get anything done. Now, some stuff can be perfect. You can make sure certain aspects
are perfect, but if everything has to be perfect, it will never happen. And you put a lot of undue
stress on a lot of people that are working on it because if from the very get-go, this has to be
perfect. Every single person that you are telling that to or that you're making that kind of aware
that that's what's happening, you put pressure. There's a lot of pressure now to, well, fuck,
I can't screw this up because then I ruined it. Did you have that guy squat there on purpose?
No, nobody's squatting here on purpose. What about Grotto Beasts? Grotto Beasts is done. Let me just
make that clear. Grotto Beasts is done. But because of the scale of that project, there's a lot of
stuff that, and that's been, that project has been in the oven for a long time. And the idea was I
wanted it out for Christmas this year, but it's just, I don't want to just run it out the door.
Just to get it out there and release it. A lot of work and a lot of time has gone into it.
And it's, I told you guys this before, that project is, I mean, it's kind of just a huge
kind of community oriented project. It's a bunch of stream references. There's a bunch of jokes.
It's a bunch of things that over the last decade or so that we thought were interesting or funny
or whatever. So I want to make sure it's right. And I want to make sure it comes out correctly.
So yeah, it's done when it's done. Not very much longer. Very, very, very short amount of time.
There's a lot going on with that project, but I can promise you this. You'll get it at some
point very soon. Just not in a week. If you want more updates, Grotto Beasts team, you know,
they're working on some cool stuff on the Twitter. Go follow the Twitter. There are card reveals
happening all the time. They've already revealed a lot of cards. Every time Polly makes a post,
she's just excited. She's just like, I can't wait to press the tweet button. Just like,
it's awesome. When are you going to change your pin tweet? That's my New Year's resolution.
Can't wait. Yeah, that's been a long time coming too. Wait, it's actually a playable card game.
Yes. I will give a ton of details when I'm ready to do so. It started out, that whole project
started out as just kind of, I was like, wait, that would be kind of fun merch, wouldn't it?
Having kind of cards based on community references and stream stuff and put some
original characters in it. And it was going to be just kind of collectible, just cards.
Then I was like, wait a minute, it can be made into an actual game. And we have a game designer
that's been working on it for almost two years. Is it an NFT? No, it's cards. Like, you know,
sorry, I just punched you. Next year, are you going to do the live action Elden Ring thing
similar to Dollhouse? I've said this before. I don't really do, I don't like, I don't want
to do sequels. I think I've said that before. I don't want to do a sequel to Dollhouse,
but Dollhouse 2 could just be something else in that same world. I don't want to just do it.
And I know that, and okay, you want me to get real? Okay. Okay, you asked for it. You asked for it.
You want me to get real? Marketing and getting support for stuff that is not a concept that's
ever proven is hard. You probably noticed there was no sponsor on this show. There isn't. It's
hard to describe to people in the world of marketing, in the world of, you know, supporting stream
or something, right? I need money for this. It's like, what the fuck are you doing? Why are you
doing that? That's stupid. Or like, that's weird, but okay. Because there's no, look, if I wanted
to do Dollhouse 5, because Dollhouse 2, 3, and 4 have happened already, and they happened in the
last six months, then it would be probably very easy. But Dollhouse 2, 3, 4, and 5 would probably
be not very good. It probably wouldn't be good at all. Maybe, depends on what I want to do with it,
or what we want to do. Could it be better? But then that just goes back to the problem that we
talked about earlier with, are you concerned that things have to be bigger and better every time?
That is the problem with something like a sequel. That is a problem with something like a series on
the same idea. How do you keep it fun? How do you make it so the first one and the second one
are in the same world? Would we just do the same jokes? How do you do more? What do you do?
And that's been the motivation the whole time, has been making sure that something seems like
a fun thing to do, and it's new every time, and it's different every time. So trying to convince
people that shows like this, I think they matter to me a lot, but they're hard to sell to people
because they just don't, it's just like, what are you doing? It's like, oh, but we did Dollhouse.
Do you remember Dollhouse? Yeah, but this isn't Dollhouse. I'm just gonna hack your fucking stream.
What are you talking about? Oh, but it's gonna be fun though, I promise. But we don't know that.
We don't know that. This stream could have been awful. We don't know that because we haven't done
it before. That's the problem for a lot of people in the marketing world.
Dollhouse 2 is Dollhouse, but it is just a stream of you playing Yakuza. What, in the Dollhouse?
You can go off numbers though. Not really. Not, I mean, not really. You don't need to be in the
Dollhouse. But yeah, a Dollhouse 2 to me, and people have asked this many times, like what
would that even be? It would be something like we were just talking about. It would be a different
concept, but in that same world of interaction. Chat, marketing, experts, incoming. But yeah,
to cap that conversation and to kind of put a lid on it, it's still trying to get shows off the
ground and have them financed is still the thing that's not simple. Sometimes you don't need it.
I don't think, honestly, I think a sponsor would have taken it probably away from this show,
don't you think? I don't think I would have wanted one anyways. And we were talking to people. We
had some lines out there for what this could be. They don't all have to have sponsors on them,
but that needs to come from somewhere. And sometimes when a show is, I mean, I don't want to,
I mean, I sort of want to lay out financing to anybody like, oh, here's all the money.
But shows that cost more than 100, 200 plus thousand dollars, they, you almost need to be
secure. You need to make sure that it's possible. Most of the stuff that you've seen on this channel,
that was a big elaborate kind of show stream, were over, over a hundred thousand dollars to do
for each one. Not all of them, but most of them, some of them much higher. So it is,
it is a struggle sometimes. And look, I don't have to, it's very easy for you to do back in
the napkin math on this channel. This channel makes a good amount of money. This channel makes
a lot of money. But even still, it's still, even with that, it's still, and I'll have to say,
I don't want to just, you know, go to fucking zero, right? Just to do this stuff. It can be scary.
But no, it's still a concern. Now, thankfully, there's been, I've done a lot of sponsors this
year. And I think they, I enjoyed myself on them. So I'm happy to do those. But it has to be,
I don't know, I just don't want to fuck it all up. I hope that, if that makes sense.
I don't want to fuck this all up, because it's, you can. And trying to balance money and content,
and I want to still try to be creative, but seeing things to be paid for, I just don't want to fuck
the whole thing up, if I'm honest. And there's been sponsors where I've kind of gone back and
forth and then been like, no, nevermind. But yeah, and I also don't want, here's another thing too,
that I don't want to see. And it's not that I'm, you know, see it or anything, but I also don't
want to put myself in the channel upon a pedestal, because that's a bad idea. I don't want to be this,
oh, everything has to be fucking so good. And oh, wow, I've got to make sure, I don't want to,
you know, you got to be careful. Because this channel, a lot of really nice things are said
about this place. So I'm just going to keep doing what I'm doing, and try to do it as good as I can,
and try to do everything the way that I would have always done it. But it can be hard.
Because, you know, when people talk about this space, and people talk about, oh shit, wow, that
was so awesome. Like, that was really fun. But I don't want to fuck it up. And I don't want it to,
like, get, actually get into my brain, and kind of ruin the way that I see this place. If that makes
sense. What about the infomercials? Yeah, we'll watch more infomercials. Of course we will. Nice
lava cake here. Yeah. We need to see, what did you say? We need to see the document of German lore
you sent to the extinguisher. It was, it was, okay. You know what it was? I was in mod chat,
and we were talking about all the things that I didn't do, that I said I was going to do.
And I was like, do you guys have any more shit that I keep lying about? So the mods got together,
and I think some of the community people were tapped into to be like, what have I said that
we can just give this guy? The mods were in on it, by the way. And I don't want, I'm not going to,
I don't want to spoil anything, but who was modding the other stream? I wonder. Interesting.
Who could that be? Random people. Do a Blue's Clues stream. No. But yeah, I know after doing
stuff like this, and when we go over behind the scenes, and you get that kind of, that post fun
thing kind of slow down, where it's like, oh, that was fun. Oh, do you remember when I was there?
That was so fun. Oh, okay. Yeah. I like being involved in stuff like this. And I think the
future of my life, wherever it goes, whatever it is, I hope is in spaces like this. Because I
find this to be some of the most fun, and some of the most engaging. And maybe doing some more,
like, creative directing. Maybe start doing more writing, if I can. Come up with some stuff.
Maybe help other people. We're not using this photo, though. The Jerma movie. No, I already
shut that down. I already shut that down. I would, okay, if I had like a five million dollar budget,
a million of it would be blown on having like five hot air balloons take us to set every day.
And it'd be like, why is he doing this? Tell him to stop spending that money. Be like, I have to.
We have to. It's to get everybody into the right mindset. Add another million for hair product.
You just win the lottery. I already did. I already did. You understand? Think about it.
I already did. And we could sit here and talk about like, oh, man, like, man, I'm doing big
shows, man, I really wish this would happen. Oh, man, you know, I loved it. I already did hit the
fucking lottery. So whatever happens from here is extra. So because I know that it's a huge,
huge fucking it's very difficult to be able to get into this space. Cheesy Charles. Yeah,
Cheesy Charles is showing up to tell you that. Cheesy Charlie. Dude, bro, I'm crying. Stop being
so sappy already. This is the last time I'm going to see you until the new year. Come on. I'm allowed
to be a little sappy. But no, this is, this is the stuff that I find the most fun. And I would like
to continue to do it. But yeah, not even sappy. Why was I not even sappy? How am I sappy, Steve?
I said, no, I said, fuck. I said, who gives, I, well, what the fuck, right? That's no, it's not
sad. I'm not cheesy anymore. I'm cool. Cheesy fucking Charlie. Yeah, you think so? I just swore
a few times. All right. That's going to be it. I was thinking about playing something, but I got a
lot of stuff to do. So let's talk about some stuff very quickly going into the new year.
Going to be bringing back. We're going to be going back to the basics a little bit.
There's no major, major things planned for the month of January, really into February. We're
going to be going besides Grotto Beast, obviously, which is going to be a huge deal. I'm going to go
back to kind of normal streams, going to bring back some more chill streams, maybe play some games
and go from there. So in the new year, you sound like a teacher, whatever. Yeah, there's potentially
some Elden Ring stuff to do. There's lots of games that I didn't play the last few weeks because I've
just been very busy. So yeah, we'll get back to it. Back to the basics. Can we do some meme react
video? Maybe. But yeah, those are my thoughts. I think it was a great way to end the year.
Everybody did a phenomenal job. I'm very, very happy about it. And I feel good. It feels good.
And that's pretty much all there is to it. Vampire Survivors. Yeah, I have a very, very,
I have a confession. I played the DLC already and it was very fun. I'm sorry. I didn't have time.
I'm sorry. I didn't have time. By the way, very quickly, did you guys know,
somebody please correct me because I cannot believe this. Vampire Survivors is on iOS now
and it's free. Is that correct? I'm trying to find the catch. It's just for free. Full game is
for free. It's free. The whole thing. There's no catches. It's just a free video game on iOS
right now. Is there ads on it? I don't think so. Are you sure? I haven't seen any. How long
did I play it for? What do you say this? I'm going to be bat chested. Stop. It's ads to revive.
Only ads are there. Yeah, there are ads, but it's free. Who cares? The only ads are if you
die and want to respawn for like extra coins and stuff. Who gives a shit? That's fucking,
the whole game is free. The catch is you have to play it on iOS. Pepe laugh.
Can we get one more cat puke to end the year? No. All right. I'll see you guys later. Thanks
for watching. I know the last few streams have been just kind of hanging out and then the Christmas
thing, but we'll get back to it in the new year. I'll see you guys soon. Take care of yourselves.
Have a great holiday. Have an awesome new year's. I probably won't see you. I'll be back
probably on, probably the second or third of January is probably when I'll turn the stream
back on and we'll just kind of go back to normal. Yeah. Merry Christmas. Happy holidays. Happy new
year. Thanks for playing along on that stream. I really could have gone either way and I'm glad
that for the most part people were having fun and playing along and even after the two streams
converging, I'm just happy to see everybody had a good time. So see you later. Take care and let's
do this. Thanks for the subs. Didn't you Lala? At least you promised. Lala. See? I'm keeping my
promises now. Was that the real Santa? That was a real Santa. That was a real Santa. That was Santa.
Why are you even asking that question? Okay. Now I actually do the hundred subs. Oh shit. Yeah.
I actually don't think I can right now. All right. On the first stream, the first stream
of the new year, tell me to do that because I will. That's new year's resolution. We're going to fix
some of these. We're going to right some of these wrongs from last year. Please bro. Yeah. Again,
huge thanks to Offbrand, to Ludwig, Atrioc, obviously Nick, Stans. They were great to work
with. I'd love to work on stuff with them again. BTS. Everybody was so good. All the set design.
It was just so good. I'm so thankful and so grateful. Yeah. The Extinguisher. There's so
many people to thank and just so many people that contributed a lot. But yeah. Have a great holiday.
Can we get one more scorn for the year? Sure. Let me figure out how I'm going to do that.
See you guys later. See you in the new year.