What's up? How's everybody doing? Welcome back. Hello. Hey, so today, today's stream.
All right, you know, you know when you like add a game's title screen and here I'll just show you
and when you're a game's title screen and usually you got you usually you get like a minute before
it goes to like the automatic cutscene demo thing that's not happening here it keeps cutting me off
and it keeps fucking with my it keeps fucking with my head all right so I'm gonna go here
to make it so it doesn't do that there we go anyways we're still hold on this isn't dead rising
is that what the title is I didn't put no okay I thought for a second I thought the category
was dead rising I was like how did I fuck that up uh we're gonna play beautiful joe I've been
trying to play this game for like two months and just was like you know what I feel like playing
it today we'll probably play today and tomorrow I'll probably beat this fucking game you know
what I mean uh I'm probably gonna play president evil I'm probably gonna play resident evil 3 next
week that's the plan is to just do that first thing we do next week I probably can get that
done in one stream but something else that we're gonna try to do this week uh we talked about it
two days ago I want to give it a try I'm we're gonna watch a movie on Friday probably on Friday
we're going to do a watch party stream it's gonna be a piece of shit I'm gonna be very
honest with you I gotta be upfront with you it's gonna be it's gonna be a shitty experience
probably but I'm gonna do it I'm gonna stream on Friday we're gonna just do like a just chatting
stream for like an hour or so and then we're gonna use that time to pick the movie we're going to
watch and then we're gonna do it that's the plan on Friday I don't think I don't think we can do
a bugs life I'm not sure that's available where we're gonna watch it I think we can just do it
here can't we just do it here that's like the point is if we all watch the movie together
it's gonna be TOS no it's it's it's actually it is terms of service it's part of the terms of
service you can watch a movie on twitch as long as you use their feature I mean nobody uses this
feature we'll give them some good feedback we'll be like oh hey this thing sucks or hey this thing
sucks but here's some other things you could add to it all right let me I'm gonna do some more
research on it over the next day or two let's watch ratatouille well I gotta see what's available
well we'll pick a good one people have to pay to watch you do it's it's prime only oh well
we're still gonna try it I want to try I want to try it I want to give it a try it's us only
why is it us only it's prime only and us only I'm actually gonna tell me yeah it's it's it's
Nevada only I wonder if I can set that up I still want to try it though he hates EU yeah you guys
in EU are gonna be like looking through the window like there's a party going on in there
but no actually no you won't be doing that there'll be there'll be blackout shades
on the windows you'll just know that there's a party going on inside I'm sorry yeah you'll have
like big earmuffs on so you can't hear anything and like just a these shades on the window so
you're gonna be that's kind of sad I'm sorry don't blame me blame it's twitch it's a twitch thing
they're the ones that that's they're the ones at fault not me he really hates us this stream was
sponsored by no it wasn't all right anyways let's get going we're gonna do beautiful joe if you
never played beautiful joe I got people were uh giving me question marks and they were saying
like minus two and shit I was doing references to this game and they're like wow I can't even
understand how many of you have never seen this or played this game because I said in the chat
henshin-a-go-go baby and it was like what the fuck shut up what are you dumb bad what is this
reference huh and I'm just like wow I'm I guess I am pretty old huh who the hell but how do you
nobody we're gonna break we're gonna we're gonna revive beautiful job right now let's go you're
about to see why this game is so beloved this game is awesome it's fast paced action there's
voices there's voice acting there's characters there's boss fights it's and and there's time
manipulation whoa some of you just freaked out god damn stop doing that so we're gonna get started
welcome everybody let's play beautiful joe stop fucking doing that new game let's go kids are
adults this is hard or easy and this game is very hard but I can't pick I can't pick the kids
because if you're on twitch and you pick the difficulty that says kids you're not going to
live that down let's go oh by the way beautiful joe's about like movies and shit cool and it's
gonna awesome soundtrack not the soundtracks fucking like 10 out of 10 all right cool here's
the cutscene this hurts my head looking at this all right this hurts do I just like do we just do
audio only for this part this actually I actually can't look at this it's giving me a headache
joe is this your idea of a date movie I had a more romantic time eating popcorn in the lobby
joe honey oh by the way d bradley baker that's the goldfish on american death
I should cut it out they don't show these old movies all the time you know
this forever been forward to this for a long time too we haven't been out on a date in forever
you can't do this you can't do that in a movie you can't like all right it's fucking hurting
my head again oh you can't do that in a movie theater what do you mean we can't hear it yes
you can wait you can't see or hear oh what can you hear now what the fuck all right you know why
because this flick hit the screens way back when we were still little babies
but that guy in the blue mat I know I've seen him some
the girl is mine and shall serve as the object of my revenge
this game's so good no stop that just look away Jeremy look away Jeremy
that's an actual like seizure warning for real it's probably bad
it's six gene it's a 4d movie 4d joe the hero here comes the music here it comes here comes the
best song of the whole fucking game oh my nostalgia meter is going on the charts
my nostalgia my mustache meter hey wait a minute am I my inside the movie bread dirt
I am no longer able to fight because I have been defeated you must take my place
as the new action hero that voice it really is captain blue you're the new hero can I get
your autograph no already gone I beg of you to take up the torch of justice young movie lover
now go the world is in danger your lady friend is waiting for you is he gonna say
what I always want to try one on oh we didn't say it yet we got huge money that just came in
all right here it comes joe saw the skull icon that indicated the incoming attack but it was
no match against joe's smooth moves joe effortlessly ducked to evade the lethal attack
and if he goes for the legs but if you hit up ow my eyes when you've had enough press the z
button here we go oh I remember this game is so good it's a side scrolling beat-em-up time
travel game this game's so good I'm so fucking happy yeah yeah it's crusty because we're
we're in the middle of a fucking pretend movie guy oh fuck that hurt all right hold on we had
a huge money come in let me see it we had 5 000 bits from sir canine 50 fucking dollars from sir
canine germa I've hacked your cpu exactly 10 minutes ago and found a 10 billion byte large
folder after seeing its contents I must say chat I can't believe I watch him this man is a fraud
every file is a secret rat movie what definitely not resubbing shaking my head read the first
letter of each line then watch this what read the first letter of each line for what J T L S J
J Bill said I don't understand read the first letter of each line and watch this with a wink
is that a code what is that uh thanks for the 50 dollars it's just gibberish oh um and then
chunky baloney gave 50 dollars back-to-back two fucking huge bits chunky baloney says this is one
of my favorite game cube games of all time but there's one room that is beyond obnoxious the
room before the level two boss is an awful bomb solving puzzle thing that I would get stuck on
as a kid for so long if you complete it if you can complete it in less than five minutes I will
gift 20 subs that's probably not gonna happen but thank you for your generosity
thank you both of you that's fucking insane that's huge money right now I haven't even been
streaming for 10 minutes all right I don't want to die this is not adult I have to be
fucking actually careful I'm gonna die I died well I got I got like taken out of the game I
was reading I I was paused then we go here we go let's start it over again and it's fucking
cheeseburger oh shit give me this oh I can only get two oops all right you fight you fight you
fight people in waves I'm feeling it I feel it again you're not forgot to just like an immortal
combat do you think he'll be in smash do you think they'll make a beautiful joke spree and
actually utilize this fucking franchise and how good it is you sure you don't think so
Capcom has it well Capcom's been on like the upswing here
oh all right this is the first tutorial boss but this game is harder than Dark Souls oh fuck that
hurt it actually is it I know it is it actually is I didn't jump over just kick his ass I'm
gonna get an A's okay just so everyone's aware that not in a million years Capcom can't even
remember what Ken looks like street fighter what do you mean hey what are you doing
there it is now I get to be the superhero and I get 10 times faster speed 10 times faster attacks
10 times faster punches and I can go like that you can slow down time now and by the way there's a
speed up time spoiler just fucked up the whole game for you this is one of the best games on the
game cube you can punch through people and shit this is gonna be fucking awesome like this ready
I love it you gotta spring combos together you guys love combos this game is like crack yes it is
I'm glad some I'm glad some of you guys understand like that well I don't want you to
I don't want to promote like smoking crack oh isn't there a dodge too does it get this again
I was gonna say there's an indoor dodge no shit there's no blood in this game yes there is
no blood it's fucking everywhere I just turned it off wait give me those I need these uh these
I need these v bucks I think that's actually what they're called I really think they're actually
called v bucks I really do think so shit I'm terrible wait turn on blood fuck I have to get
them here I'm gonna squeeze you like an orange what are you talking about oh whatever I don't
care and there's a container I just jumped into that adopt them oh give me the coin of course
there is what are you gonna do it's so fluid the combat is so fucking fluid I know it's the
easiest thing to say that's like the simplest fucking way to describe any video game oh I mean
it's so fluid what'd I get and damn it come on no oh wait a minute I can do this I can cheat
I forgot I could cheat all right now we're gonna do uh burger burger and burger
cheating he's cheating he's cheating I know you missed it I'll get it again hold on he sucks at
cheating you can't suck at cheating you either cheat or you don't like if you cheat you just
get you win all right full health where is it there it is all right now let's go again
let's do v deck oh whoa I don't even know this is here oh I can get them all no no no no no I'm
not done well I got a d on time because I spent it all doing the fucking I don't even need to slow
down time for this maybe I should oh god can they get hit by that too I got 30 beautifuls for that
one oh by the way uh the sakiro stole this from this game oops oh it's so much fun and just wait
till I fucking get the flow when I get a good flow you'll know because I'll scream I can break
this fucking thing why would I swear what's the point of swearing there that doesn't do anything
there's a double jump too well I didn't know that till right now oh I forgot the uh you can double
jump into this shit seems like he hates this game it sucks and oh don't get cocky this guy's kind
of kicking my ass oh my god he's gonna kill me fuck he's gonna kill me I'm gonna die oh my god
I'm dead oh right I remember I remember I remember I remember my back I remember I remember okay all
right I remember if you get hit when you I get it okay remember ready sure if you get hit well if
you get hit while you're in slow motion you actually dodge it I forgot about that what was
my fucking story all right stop fucking making noise for no reason to play the game there we
go get out of here where's my dive kick was this game even any okay I was gonna scream is this game
even any good to like push out a bunch of energy I was just gonna scream out a bunch of energy for
no reason but I'm glad I didn't all right we're good let's beat this guy I can think I can punch
the bullets back too oh fuck that's not how you do it come on I can't hit it fuck I can't do this
right I'm not punching it how am I not it's gotta be like exact let me try to let me get this right
there we go all right it's you gotta it's gonna be much it's gonna be much more cute
there we go I get it I got it let's go what give me that book why are they all using guns
it's kind of not very right is there there's a crack stash today I don't think that I don't
think there's a crack stash today I think that's just normal uh I think that's just normal chat
uh cat is strange I got them all 22 out of 50 that's bad see ah crappy see for crappy
kick them back what the fuck is a crack stash uh it's when you have crack stored somewhere
in your house um I guess I'm trying although I'm concentrating I can't really say much
because it's a concentration game it's uh it's okay whoa can I land on this no I can't what the
fuck what I mean can I land on this when it's slow what how would I be able to do that all right I'm
turning them off that's cool right because you're slowing down time now this is fucking cool
don't watch this why would I click a random video I'm not gonna click on random fucking video
especially when half of you say don't watch this like you're giving me a warning already wait can
I I can get up there it's very much to the benefit of getting as many of these v bucks as you can and
I'm gonna keep calling it that I don't care because it gives you the extra uh power bar
how high can this go fuck really how do I get up there that makes sense I I really think that's
what they call they're like video bucks yeah I think they are like v but I think that's really
what they're called streamers gonna get used what all right I need a key oh put a face cam on
please no I've I've I've come I don't like the way I look today I don't like the way that I look
today I don't want to I don't want to lose face cam right now I don't like the way that I look
today I heard a rumor that you live in a suitcase is that true yes of course it is I'm not gonna
hide it anymore I live in a suitcase very big suitcase it's about it's about as large as a house
house size suitcase so that's a lot of money oh you got the key let's go all right I'm about
to get my ass kicked over and over and over again from the level boss because that's what the hard
things in this game is are trying to get the level boss trying to beat it and I'm gonna get my ass
kicked although I might get another bar I will but all right time to get my ass kicked oh it's the
helicopter fuck all right I have to move he comes flying by you punch the uh things I don't think I
can hurt him yet okay here we go fuck all right I got it I'll get it I'll get it again I get it
here comes that come on come on yes good this game is just like nintendogs you know you know
it is you know it is it actually is no fuck are you just ready okay I'm in trouble oh
shit okay I gotta kill these guys and not take damage from this shit oh wait here we go
there it is and there it is okay it's gonna be a nice plot god damn it don't do it don't do it
please don't do it don't do it is there a hamburger over here I gotta jump up I think and be in the
right where is he nope all right I gotta punch him up I'm dead oh that was so lucky all right
I'm dead I'm dead I'm dead I'm dead I'm dead I'm dead I'm dead I'm dead I'm dead I'm dead I'm not
dead oh my god you fucking idiot I need a hamburger right now what oh I fucking walked into it I'm
dead please right did I not punch it oh fuck oh fuck oh where am I wait what wait I is it
this beginning of the whole fucking entire level oh shit so me dying just to test out how the game
worked oh that was not very good but it's because you're on adult mode all right oh well oh let's
do it better well now I'll get all this shit now that's good really we're never gonna see level two
I just started playing like 10-15 minutes ago
oh yeah I started streaming 30 minutes ago but I didn't start playing till like 15 minutes ago
all right I'm not I'm not gonna get hit one time from this one guy watch this ready he's dead level
two yeah well you are in the level two waiting room because we're gonna get there eventually and
then you're gonna get called in you're gonna say but you're gonna get called into another waiting
room for level three and it's gonna keep going forever get off me what the fuck all right I want
to fill up my beautiful bar next game waiting room well you're gonna have to wait a few days
because this is what we're playing you're gonna be in the waiting room for a couple days
sorry to let you know it's a sleepover time why do you have so many shitty magazines in here to
drive you fucking nuts on purpose because I know that you're gonna be sitting there going
does he have what why is there like fucking better homes and gardens from like 2004 here
it just is that's the only that was the one I got for free I got that one for free I don't even need
help I want the money though no I want the money I want the money I want the money I want the money
I want the money give me the money yes that's a lot of fucking money worth it I don't need help
all right got it uh I don't need help all right let's go nightbot is a little cocky lately
what does that mean nightbot's acting a little cocky all right I don't want to I got full health
full everything time to fight that hind I didn't even have I had one bar by this point I was
playing looking shitty I'm gonna have three bars by the time I get there see you later remember
how much I was going anymore I'm gonna get fucking decent beautiful writer anymore yep all right time
to go you're almost pot increase the fov sure to work didn't how that's weird I'm gonna return
the computer I'm gonna send this fucking computer back where I bought it uppercut him fuck all right
no losing to the helicopter here I'm gonna concentrate the fuck out of this guy he's
emulating why is that even all right well I got a question for you guys what is that so when I
told everybody that I wasn't emulating they they went what are you fucking stupid what are you
dumb why are you not emulating yeah you should be emulating what a fucking idiot and now when I'm
on an emulator which I'm not but if I'm on an emulator to you guys he's on an emulator
what a fucking idiot he's not even on original hardware you see how that is no winning here
all right I still got it no I didn't punch the thing the only move is to not play there we go
that's correct all right give me another bar I need at least three or four bars with it
I'm on adult mode crappy but it's all right 45 46 47 48 29 50 turn my voice down I think you're
the only person in the history of this entire live stream that's ever told me to turn my voice
down not up and we're talking over the course of like seven years that's a very interesting
statement die why are you still alive fuck off whoa dude relax relax die he doesn't know he's
even muted nudity in this game oh shit there is whatever I didn't look at it I didn't even look
at it I'm down kick him down kick him when he comes down when he comes down kick him bye remember
won't put face cam on because he's wearing a bra what would that have to do with face cam
what does that have to do having a face cam on it's not uh like bra cam all right I got three
all right I'm gonna I'm gonna yeah this is this is hard shit somebody said they guaranteed I
wouldn't beat the first boss well that first is bothering me dead fucking wrong oh come on really
go quiet everybody quiet come on get over here that's not gonna work out oh boy this is bad
I feel like I have to give me the juice give me the juice give me the juice give me the juice
well I gotta kill them all give me the juice give me the juice fuck you god damn it
ah god damn it this is fucking hard I forgot this game's hard oh boy I'm dead
you literally said it's harder than dark souls earlier yeah I know and it is
it is I'm doing this so wrong I can't wait to make it so I don't get hit five or six of
them in front of me I'm going too early fucker hold on what the fuck wait okay I gotta get that
okay hold on you motherfucking swing holy shit I can do that I didn't know I could even do that
I just fucking know I could do that shit I can knock him in I win this game's fucking
out of the dogs that's what they're there for all right cheeseburger a thousand points restore
one life produce bombs from out of thin air instead of flying with a kick hold down the
kick button and pull the vroomerang smooth move that lets you use the v emblem like a boomerang
let's get along the ground and kick a slick boom here's red hot kick this is what I want
fantastic aerial dive this is dive kick I want this right now finally this is important have up
to four of yourself appearing and moving at mock speed beautiful forever strike a pose that's too
cool and damage all enemies on the screen a killer technique when you're hit react to the fall and
reduce damage to a minimum a magic move that thing's important get four cure I want an extra life
gauge even if all your lives are gone restart from the point where you died I mean that's pretty
important too I'm doing this again I'm doing this again for life is beautiful Joel gets one more
life that's important too though sliding all right sliding it's just down and a it's sliding
and I'll get the life thousand yeah sounds good to me okay that's all I can afford you're buying
the new power-ups whatever save the game onto my game cube memory card there it is
but
all right there we go you didn't think I was getting to level two where's that guy that owes
me a hundred dollars uh speaking of money uh red planet of mars gave five thousand bits
fifty fucking dollars they say what if you stream tf2 is a one-off day haha just kidding
unless dot dot dot no I'm not gonna do that there's the kick yep oh the slide is so good too
what the fuck is it all these bats are pissing me off okay the bats are pissing me off get out of
here get these bats are making me angry come here man fuck this game what what's wrong with you
why what are you talking about what am I missing here am I what am I going to do an entire stream
in a bostonian accent um I need to oh wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait what we
okay I got it I have to hit it up um I don't I okay you're freaking me out right now um
I'm supposed to hit this up like over and have it land on this all right first of all I'm from
Massachusetts why would I need to pretend to have a boston accent what the hell are you talking about
oh shit oh okay I'm good dude you should do a whole stream in like your native dialect
that's like saying hey dude you should like oh come on dude you should do the whole stream in
english no stop touching it I'm gonna get a bad grade for time go go oh that's gonna be an app
no give me the food though hey this is this is the part level two like part one
level two part two waiting room level one part two waiting room waiting room for the waiting room
waiting room waiting room waiting waiting waiting waiting I missed god this game's so
fucking good if I keep saying that over and over again people will be like oh this game must be
good to keep saying it's good it has to be a good game then saying it out loud they can go
like wow this is fucking good I should like it too instead of saying magazine waiting room
oh dear what is this it's time for your next try boy don't kill me don't kill me captain tutorial
ready action it's all right we're right here that's the beat level two just kill them
just kill them excuse me got it all right let's go let's go grandpa
chooses adult and plays like a kid I love it it's time for your next try here I come
I'm not a kid look I made him again I'm not a kid I just did the thing that when you like
when you go out to fucking dinner and there's a kid's menu and you're with somebody that's like
eight there's like oh what do you want yeah there's the kid's menu I'm not a kid um yes of
course but here are the four chicken tenders and the macaroni and cheese that's what you like
I just did that exact thing all right mock speed Joe grilled every porcel that stood in his way
with his blazing knuckles with electric fast combo attacks he can smash through even distant targets
it's you get super speed it's fast motion so you can go like this cool huh that's your button
mashing yes of course I am and you have to use them together pay attention Jeremy oh who cares
just do the one quick and fast but every time did I see the smash leaks last night no I didn't see
the smash leaks chicken tendies waiting room dude what the fuck where's like it's chicken
tendies waiting room can't even fucking see me dude can I go up no crap mac and cheese waiting
room oh what do I do what do I do what do I do what do I do what do I do I have to run away
from it probably oh I'm I missed uh things oh whatever I'm not going for one million percent
playthrough fuck I'm mad about that I'm actually upset I'm gonna do something whoop but that's a
good bonus boom I need to do a Minecraft let's play not ever in a hundred million years in 100
million years maybe so like dinosaurs would have to wait like we'd have to get dinosaurs to roam
the earth again and go extinct again before I play a a Minecraft let's play and they would
be like the wait at the cave man cave men's go through everything again and then maybe
maybe after that it would progress with it out of here another one of these oh god what do I do
slow down whoa sorry I got the food still I care about bad be for bad
German going on a went German going on a rant waiting room imagine going to what you like a
doctor's office and it's just me like you have an appointment and it's like oh yeah I'm here
for it to see mr albertson uh if I have a uh I have a 230 yeah go ahead and see and you wait
there for like 30 minutes and people come in and go and I just fucking rant at you when you come in
I have a stethoscope on my neck when I never check your fucking blood or anything I never
check your heart or anything you just sit there and I'm just like you know you know I was at the
fucking drive-through yesterday and it's like a 30 or 40 minute session where I just rant to you
and then you leave why do you want that and I'm all on fire yeah you gotta let them all
can I get it not quite uh that open that shit open open fucking open
wow they were all on fire wait is this the broom oh there's one more over here this one more
I didn't realize it was a fourth one I didn't realize it was a fourth one I did it wait there's
no safe point here though that's not good what should I do I buy another life boomerang a smooth
move that lets you use the dm boom like a boomerang hold down the punch button
I'll get it should I save yeah I'm gonna save up I feel like I should buy another life because
I that there's no safe point here you know what I mean I feel like I'm gonna I'm gonna need that
all right just don't die just don't lose just don't lose got it nice did them all yeah
oh
all right I almost got a full gauge I love that oh oh no that's great oh I don't like this already
dark theme
all right got to play right
isn't there a shark in this one he freaks me out the shark does
look out boss fight he turns into bats good good got it shit whoa what's he doing
do I have to get them all I wish I had that what's that boomerang move I didn't do it
oh easy watch out watch out watch out watch out watch out watch out watch out
just take a shit out of him with this move come on come on come on come on come on come on come on
come on come on come on did he hit me holy shit okay I'm all right one more all right he's dead
fuck this guy oh yeah yeah I just had to Joe wanders into the world of the movies
and gallantly fights evil to rescue Sylvia with the help of his superior strength he is able to
reign triumphant over the dastardly bats because a psycho Charles the third why am I why am I a
psycho is she safe is she even alive intolerable anxiety tears at Joe's heart what did they do to
her what would be a good hero me so hard searching for Sylvia Joe tries to track clues as to her
whereabouts little did he know that the clues would only lead him to more problems
the next episode is some like it red hot see you there
a a b a a c b b b a b b b pretty good report card if you ask me okay goodbye episode two
I love this song so much all right what we got I want more help I'm gonna need it
five thousand who combo in the air combo in the air that's way more important and I'm gonna get
an extra life because I'm fucking loser what was loud and crunchy
this is dmc it's made by the same people that made that so that makes sense
yeah wait oh this is where the combo start to fly like rain no other way
point oh so much fun to play say it again you make me don't think it's cool
say it again Jeremy say it again say it again say it again all right he's saying again
whoa do it ah times four I didn't what I was ducking I was talking
nobody you swing oh I can't see what's happening on the screen all right will you
fuck off kill him he's not even on the screen that's what's going on he's not even on the
fucking camera all right whatever I keep going this way I don't think I can this game is so
good yes it is it is so good oh what was that what was that big red v thing okay well whatever
well I know what to do here kind of whoa wait there's something down here whoa what the fuck
just did oh it's one of it's a guy okay what the fuck is up with that give me the burger
close that gap he's dead what the fuck there's another guy out of here all right oh a time
please a ad make sure I didn't miss anything I know people can say I missed something but it's
all right so can't you already see his fucking moves and smash brothers I guess that's his upbeat
we already know what it looks like you're too slow am I oh yeah am I yes
I need a hamburger everyone does the same thing in smash that's not accurate I go down
oh fuck okay hold on a second this is just a well wait can I
shit hold on how do I can I hit them both at the same time
no do your down B and have a down B I don't have the power up yet
that's unfortunate oh well he lacks vertical information yes he does
yummy this is your last trial if you overcome this trial he's going to be a me costume when
they add phoenix right to smash what on earth would they add phoenix ah I can't say that they
had to fucking refit trainer right like that doesn't work oh is it just hit me kick him in
the air kick in the air now I got oh I went the wrong way what an asshole no how do I get how do
I avoid that what don't die don't die oh all right I got it bb that flourish from your instincts
exploit them for good deeds he's got this world like a big fat stomach the world is waiting for
you joe go now vbd what time zone is that with you uh virtual something time the final vfx power is
on check out the extreme zoom on that good looking joe watch his enemies freeze okay joe
you got their attention now give him something to look at oh I can do it now I can do it now
you can do the zoom the pose is he doing the pose he sends like a raging twister in his descent
makes the world shine the light of joe is the hammer that smashes through the darkness of evil
jump uh-huh back down again cool all right let's go get it that's cool all right let's go get that
activation thing how do I do it how do I go oh that's how okay I get it let's go back and do
that thing he sounds like he hates this game why how do you tell if I like a game how does that
work there we go right secret you beat the game in a single stream now that's that's like I see
where you're going on this one I see what you're doing here what oh come on it went through the
fucking wall I get up there I can't I can't I can't I gotta go like this oh I can only do it twice
shit how do I get up there oh wait I know just fill up the shit okay is that it
well I guess I have to stay here is this poisonous oh there's a fucking laser right here
don't ah you have to zoom with a c stick c stick zoomed all right I could have run by this really
fast there's a lot of free v stuff this is working out pretty well I almost have the
second little unlockable whoa that zoom's freaking me out a little oh shit
oh fuck okay okay I got it I got it I got it I got it I got it did I miss one the fuck off me I'm
gonna hit that off oh where oh I'm down at the bottom okay um come down here get down here
where the fuck is it there it is I wouldn't care but I'm so close I need help you are crappy
that's all right there's so many fucking bats everywhere
okay that comment was actually pretty funny like what the fuck was that comment
what did it say hold on Jeremy you can't play beautiful joe you haven't played VR in so long
why won't you play VR beautiful joke goes brr okay I have to pay attention
that was the dumbest thing ever it was just fucking nonsense you can't play beautiful joe
beautiful joe yeah you can play VR in so long why won't you play VR beautiful joke I was brr
all right turn the shit off I need to plug this in how do I pick this up there's like a just a plug
on the ground how do I do this does it matter is this gonna kill me he hates completing games he
missed vbox I'm not even the same plane bingo oh god whoa all right I gotta pay attention
we'll die this are you all right stop screaming dodged it twice magic haven't hit him fire fire
oh my god you're pissing me off all right get him oh my god I held the button down too long
so just do it slow
ah oh sorry somebody said he's dead is he is he though oh is he though how do I get this
oh I have to zoom in on this don't I I want food like I should say sorry I can see it just fine I
don't even need this again I want money too no don't do three in a row
you can't play VR in so long why what the fuck is this bullshit beautiful joke goes brr
this can I put can I put that as like my favorite comment of the year
we'll go back to VR and in a little bit and a little bit just relax how do I get this box
how do I get this zoom can I get it I can't get it zoom it doesn't work it's mock speed
had to hit it with a red hot by timing the slug machine with a mock speed attack
that's not gonna work you have to hit enemies jump jump they're only gonna scream on zoom I
don't know what that is back to normal slide uppercut slide slide attack uppercut
I just got hit by a fucking car are you kidding me how did that happen
who are these people driving right come on I can't get over that shit man
Jerma play this game well maybe this game how about this game or this game Jerma please play
game Jerma I'm begging you Jerma hello Jerma play game I like Jerma please hello Jerma play something
else oh my god you can't just play what you find fun with the with the fans and we want VR now
you haven't played VR in so long put this on the screen that's just like what the fuck is this
it's the money oh I want to get up there you can't do this we're the fans we want this
it's you haven't done it in so long oh wait
how do I get that one nice I know what to do on this check this out I don't
oh that's an extra life holy huh I'm down whoa whoa all right um there's seven here
let's bring it together check this out ready one two three oh one two three zoom in
oh can I break these oh okay this is a new new character watch it bang
watch it fuck you got an a finally oh my god what oh my god oh
it's acid it's acid it's acid it's acid it's acid it's acid oh my god
I've seen it before I've seen it what do you want to click on when you're
all right we're gonna do this again oh I get over there now I missed the cool thing
I have to re-trigger the they're eating her what the fuck
never not be funny I'm in a funny laughing mood now now he's padding for time did I just get hit
by the fucking bus while I was on the bus I how long do I have to sit on this floor
how long do I have to hold the button for did that work I you have to get the thing to go really
fast and then you have to speed up time don't do speed just just only slow really uh scope
I maybe just don't hold it down just tap it a little bit okay that's weird shit oh I can get it
wait what am I not getting it was it money I don't know two of these oh
bad very bad bad bad bad bad this is very bad this is very bad
where is it going let's do this again here we go all right relax got it yes
oh are you serious how did I know
cheeseburger here yes yes all right we're good get that thing back there get that one
get that one oh I got it no I didn't what stop flexing into the camera
that shit distracted me so fucking much that just I think I just lost
oh I thought he was gonna go all the way around to the other side fuck I didn't know he's gonna
turn around that quickly I still understand how why I can't hit that thing all right well I got
the full help come on you fucking idiot do it do it why did he not do it that's the one to swing
at me what did I just actually get hit you motherfucker you gotta be kidding me oh my god
I gotta sit up I'm being stupid I can't just okay come on man do it I'm gonna attack this way
that's what I wanted to see okay I got one hit yeah I can't cheat like that it's all right
there we go there fucking idiot fucking dumb fucking idiot fucking idiot all right hit me
why am I not fucking hit anybody oh what oh boy this is bad it's okay it's all right
what am I doing don't jump into it what are you fucking crazy I went I wanted to go the other way
god that was fucking odd everybody said he wasn't gonna get angry I don't think I'm getting angry
if I'm getting in I'm thinking I'm getting involved getting involved all right I got points
I need to spend these points take two even if all your lives are gone restart from the point
where you died that's pretty good that's really important how often can this be activated that's
a lot of v bucks yeah but buy more life yeah it's true it's probably a one-time use I actually
don't remember it might be all right shock shocking pink but try this I let me get the
let me get the rumor right let's hold down the punch button if I have enough for another life
no have enough for getting it aren't you
just don't get hit okay that's good advice
a rhino hotel all right this is maybe this is what we have to fight
I'm getting strange flashbacks right now of this level specifically the boss of this level and
being very upset something about it I don't know what it was something about this though all right
how do I do this kick thing oh it's a bomb how do I use it if I just kick it oh shit it just sits there
where's he going what if Reddit was real Reddit is real Reddit is a real website
I remember playing beautiful joe 2 when I was a kid those are some good times
really I turned off right when I get hit just fucking do you I want beautiful joe 3 I think
all of us do anybody that's really ever played the this series definitely is like so just wants
one so bad I don't think we'll ever get one unfortunately it's the sad truth it is the sad
truth oh and go up there red hot rumble is good I never played it that's the one where they did it
like a smash brothers right I cannot stand on that I cannot stand on that huh oh that's annoying
doesn't work a capcom anymore no wait to knock these down what am I missing here
oh was I when this kid I was 17 was I what does it do here oh I've been missing subs
we got seven community subs from dead oh dead oh thanks for the seven subs we also had five from
germa sucks you know where they got that guy sucks thanks to the two of you subs he hates
themselves ah there we are I know I find it eventually why is he so mean what does I mean
to a viewer what's the last time I was mean to a viewer what a dumb thing to say okay can I get
over there still don't get that I don't understand how do I like go to the other plane he's evil
okay I can't pick up both at the same time what is this you're always on the same plane
yeah but how come I can't go on the same on that that same the same plane as the yellow box that's
what I'm saying he asked me if a card was mine and it wasn't this is the worst stream oh I see
something over there if they hit the enemies into the background boxes just try and do that earlier
I guess it was not good enough at it right now got a key a couple of red hot kick oh you know I
will say though we'll probably put that helmet back on sooner than you think because like I've
said over the last like probably two or three weeks of sitting down less I've actually started
to feel a little more loose and I've been feeling a little better okay I gotta pay attention get it
come on slide oh that's you just hate to see that couple all right what do I do with this
the green screen yes the green screen stream will be sooner than you think it will be soon
probably within the next 30 days I hope so that's what that's the plan is I gotta knock you into
that shit oh did I not uh really reloading fire fire I want to knock you into this
all right here we go I'm gonna try to knock you into this shit no I gotta get an uppercut right
here fuck no hey sorry I'm late start the stream over all right hey what's going on guys how are
you doing today five here I'm gonna lie about hope I didn't lie about hope hope is being delivered
at some point in the future
don't lie oh don't get our hopes about hulk ultimate destruction I'm not gonna what makes
you think I would get your hopes up about ultimate destruction too
I'd be concerned about this oh there's a bomb am I good oh I could have just before it gets
over here oh shit I get it hurry up hurry up hurry up hurry up oh my god really
oh no no I need to god damn it god damn it it's almost here it's here this fucking thing is here
give me the key oh oh I'll go in hulk is here or the hulk is here hulk is in the building why do I
need to slow that down this is the bomb puzzle no this is not the bomb puzzle it's not the bomb
puzzle all right it might be the bomb puzzle got it on the first fucking try no I didn't
I just got hit four fucking times in a row I think what just happened do something swing at me
I know what to do got it no I didn't oh shit this is the hard one this is the one they were
talking about oh okay you're gonna do it slow the whole time slow get out of the fucking way
oh you're annoying wait which which one have to blow up right side first get it can I get it
oh shit I just did it I didn't even whoa jump jump zoom it all right now fucking move out of the
okay I'm good now we're good now we're good the red socks with no brim what does that mean
what's the red socks with no brim mean I'm just at it no I get it you got I know I get it I know
check this out I know what to do didn't think I was gonna figure this one out did you
oh that was it no brim what are you talking about what does that fucking mean
what are you saying oh that was it I'm gonna go further out
oh just wait hold on and then we have to go what wait hold on what's happening there
doesn't what okay I okay I'm looking at this don't have a brick okay I'm not looking to chat
anymore like not for at least five minutes that was it that was it you gotta go you gotta go up
that's okay I know what you gotta do let's fucking out here I know what to do check this out
oh that was it that was it what what the fuck are you talking about thank you unbelievable
I need help oh I that was a there's a laser in here ready action okay that would have been nice
that would have been fucking nice it would have been nice wouldn't it at least I know what to do
do what I gotta kill this person again make it fucking easy just hit me not even a chance
not even a chance sorry I don't buy it would you actually just dive kick me dead dead finally
all right here we go had I do this before I don't remember it was like okay I remember I remember
I know I know I know I know how to do it I'm gonna get rid of these fucking guys these guys
are a pain in the ass wait I don't have a good view can somebody fill me in on this on this
like what what the hat brim thing is somebody like give me a fill me in a little bit here
it's a meme oh he doesn't know no of course I don't how would I know
die get out of my way oh my god you did you seriously just do that to me okay get
you fuck off you just dive kicked me too you are such an annoying little shithead
get out of here oh my god yeah don't swear anymore my mom's in the other in this room
no all right fine I won't fine you have to promise to be a good for the rest of the screen are you
kidding me dude he's pushing that bomb over here dude guys I gotta be careful all right easy make
it I'm not fucked I'm not flying around anywhere they can fucking die if they want to what
get this bomb out of here man do it okay oh okay now I have to I gotta go I gotta get out of here
oh I have to get this thing lit this thing has to get lit
all right lit this thing light it lit this thing up this is gonna explode on me I think it
what is it how do I light this thing up aren't you a bunch of times I have to be super fast right
okay excuse me goodbye what what is that there it is thank you oh it's okay
all right let me try to get this let me try to hit this thing into it but into you into you
this fucking wee sensor bar I'm gonna rip it in half with my teeth let's go string it together
we'll just hit them okay this is where it gets really bad oh you got it come on come on come on
ah
fire shoot me shoot me shoot me please shoot me what are you doing are you stupid
get the fuck over here and shoot please oh you're really pissing me off
oh my god I'm fucking losing my mind oh my god what a pain in the ass what an actual pain in the
fucking ass angry and now he's fucking angry yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah stop zooming in get the
fuck out of zoom ah get die die oh where are you come on let's go fire oh please that's it go go
okay I'm fine shut up who am I talking to let's go all right I'm good to go yeah
how many lives do I have two all right good I got two lives
do I have enough for the final beautiful all right good
thank goodness I have another beautiful who is he talking to it's lock machine time
he plays the machine get the fuck over there so I can hit him with the red hot kick
oh that was pretty good that was what we call pretty good
this dude thinks we're real yeah you are all right I did that for one person I don't want that
oh I want the hp good now we want money we do this for money you're gonna wake up I'm awake
joker made him to smash before beautiful joe oh no excuse me what's up with that
people job has way more fans me burger boy 100 of you that's optimistic that's optimistic I
don't think it is people love this character this is like one of the most beloved game cube characters
ever all right boss time I got two chances to not fuck this all up just don't mess it up
oh we're good okay here we are we're gonna get an opportunity to get another beautiful bar
oh that was pretty good I love when you just do that side swing slash you know none of you know
what I'm talking about I don't even know what I'm talking about all right gotta make a pizza
do you think I should make a pizza I love pizza and speaking of pizza I'm gonna go pee I know that
that makes no sense but we're at a break point here I'm gonna go pee up your back see you hey
here my knees what photos when you play pat upon two I gotta play pat upon one before I play pat
upon two don't you think doesn't make more sense all right I got money double the rate of recovery
on your vfx gauge that's so good that's I would say that's probably the most important thing in
the whole game mock speed have up to four of yourself appearing and moving at mock speed
in slow dodge enemy attacks and zoom in so dodge and then zoom does this take two and I need to
how many how much I'm gonna go with mock speed mock speed and I'm not gonna use this shit I don't
think another health take the take the extra health for the take two take two oh god take two oh god
should I take two now all right I got it is there a safe point of course there's not all right I
gotta play well because there's no safe point here I gotta do this right I got two chances to beat
this otherwise I can do the whole thing over again I'm ready j this is the sucky room oh
this one's the one that sucks wait I I do remember this I remember getting so that this the the the
screaming he says the same line over and over again yep I remember this and you end up falling
all the way down you hear him say every yeah I remember this here we go god okay so hold on
this goes up here and then it's got a light and then get
get used to hearing that up the wall it's gonna blow up gonna get it oh
don't touch it just hold on it's gonna explode it's gonna explode it's gonna explode it's gonna
explode it has a nudger with your body there you go ready oh you piece of shit I need a full
charge here fill it up and then I gotta wait till it's full it's a good sub sound if I still had
them okay good cool uh Zorro Carlos gave 10 000 bits I just got 100 from Zorro Carlos thanks for
the 100 I said hey Jeremy listen about two years ago I was in a really rocky spot I had a lot of
fallouts with friends and my mental state was just not the greatest but I want to thank you for being
there and giving me some laughs to stay sane since then I took some therapy and have successfully
recovered from my very very long depression I've now been accepted into an art school to study
animation that's fucking awesome and once again I want to show you my appreciation for being a
light in those dark times thanks a lot Carlos I wish you the absolute best I'm glad you have
gone on the path here sounds like you're doing pretty good that's really great to hear nice
fucking work awesome getting into a fucking school starting in shit animation maybe you can try
animating this ego immediately maybe you can try animating me is that an ego fuck um I gotta like
I'm gonna I'm gonna like go on a fucking mountain retreat or something I'm gonna like get on the top
of the mountain just breathe and then maybe it'll go away right well that will go away
well I still like will I be on the mountain just being like ah all right I see how it's supposed
to be now and then when I look on the car driving home I there's a red light and I'm just like why
is this red light red it should be green for me I should have a fucking green light right now why
is this red exactly that's probably gonna happen does that mean that happens every time I pull up
to a red light but thanks for the 10,000 fucking bits dude I'm glad you're doing well
and then chunky baloney gave 20 community subs because they said if I did it in five
minutes they were gonna give 20 subs and there they are there they are thanks a lot chunky baloney
I love this guy
iron ogre hulk davidson
I'm gonna get my ass kicked
watch on your arm man what do you think you're some kind of mega man or something
he said mega man pretty cool huh I'm here to avenge captain blue just call me
I haven't come up with a good name yet
here we go what do we do pause he's going this way he's gonna swing up all right he blocks
block but wait wait wait till he swings don't get cocky he's a tough boss all right I'm running
out of power here just oh god what's he doing oh he just cracked it whoa what's that he's doing
a move oh he's got missiles and shit he blocks it okay I have to knock him down and then what the
hell is this more of these oh I'm on fucking fire I think I have to run fast to get that off
so he blocks I have to make him okay I gotta get him off guard all right so here we go check this
out here we go boom he's gonna go for he smashes his head and that's when you go like this and I
missed and I that's okay maybe that shit wow that hurt I want that swing at me mother pearl
he's gonna run oh fuck please wait should I jump around him I just jump behind him
no I guess it's gonna I guess it's going all right okay here we go swing it's a real wink
it can't be good there's no such thing as a real wink right no I'm too far away I'm doing
all right slow and steady I have more than what I just got killed in one hit why did I look over
a chat what was the point of that I don't know what they say he throw his axe why the fuck would
I look over a chat in a game where you have to pay attention to every second of the game why would
I do something like that it was going so well all right don't get touched back it up I can't
believe you just almost killed me oh shit what does that do oh he was gonna swing
I thought he was gonna catch me in midair
oh my god it's take two take two I'm so glad I bought it zoom in that didn't even fucking hit
him all right don't be greedy he's finally zooming frog oh my fuck where is he where is he where is
he where is he he's over here I had to fucking block it what am I wasting this for oh Jeremy
what are you doing just do it the way I was doing it before what am I fighting for
what is happening uh this cannot go on what am I fighting for you can't be serious oh wow
just figured out how to fucking fight the boss you can't handle it you can't handle it uh oh
uh oh uh oh what he was in the air fuck no smart smart plays only okay don't be fucking stupid
no no no where is he oh I'm fine there's a fire where the fire fire fire fire fire fire fire fire
fire there's a fire fire fire there's a fire there's a fire fire fire okay
okay break it where's this
that was uh way more intense than I think it should have been that's a pretty good
youtuber reaction not to say I couldn't win unhurt of course I'm amped the fuck up
the frightful power of hulk davidson but on the blueprint that had fallen into his hands was
the most terrible of plans the shadows seeking to stretch it sucked where's the blood
to the ocean itself had planted a bomb in the underwater city of oh I remember this yeah this
guy water was starting to flood the city oh yeah he actually does but to abandon the search for
sylvia and race to rescue the innocence of moon dang this is horrible I can't even read this junk
but more importantly a superhero needs a super ride pretty bad handwriting
and it barks on a mission to save the underwater city don't forget to see the next installment
two million leagues under the sea till then ta-ta bb bb cb a bb bc ccb
okay we did it it was terrible streamer I I haven't continued since the tutorial level what are you
talking about I don't have enough for anything just save them it continued on the tutorial level
yes I did two million leagues under the sea wait what oh this is awesome
it's like cuphead funny practice on this one I played Icaruga oh I can do a huge bullet oh
hey oh it's like a dodge okay and I have oh all right that's cool can I do rapid fire this is the
hardest schmup you know about odd schmups dude all right hit them back at them come back at them
please you should play toe how is harder I can't move what's that oh super just do this just spam
all right I'm good oh I upgraded my uh bar cool and oh what hit the guy underneath what
what does it do when you slow down the bomb just explodes a bunch oh that's nice
especially you know I'm getting too overconfident with that okay that just almost that just almost
instantly killed me oh my fucking lord are you serious okay it's getting it's getting kind of
out of control okay we're good we're fine we're fine hold in it but all right bomb
ah yeah did you get for cheating to Icaruga what do you know about Icaruga
okay well he just walked out of the screen of course I can't hit him now all right you're
being a real dick like come into frame so I can shoot you you're being a dick finally oh boy
okay well that way I gotta go slow slow him down slow him down slow him down
I'm gonna go like this we should be able to get a bunch of them with a couple of bombs pretty sick
and not bad what's he doing more of this shit that's fine I just drop it on his head
oh okay I get it holy shit that feels good okay don't fucking blow it here I'm gonna blow it here
okay slow slow slow slow ah bad bad fuck bad where is he what side is he on what the fuck what
oh my did I get hit by something I can hit how oh that couldn't have been any better oh shit oh
shit oh shit oh shit oh shit please don't kill me please don't kill me oh my god I almost killed me
oh shit I've blown it now I've really done it now did it then I should have went underneath him
god oh I had it too I'm so upset right now I'm getting a hit I'm so upset
I don't have one hell I've got only two after this he said shit yes I did
let's go go that's making me fucking laugh I can't help it once you get something in my head guys
it's gonna stay there for probably five or six weeks now I'm grounded what I can't what am I
supposed to do I can't listen hey you're not supposed to watch the screen or something I guess
your mom said no what whatever blow up blow up dude dude dude okay seriously dude
shit everywhere shit everywhere shit everywhere okay I'm getting like upset now and I look at the
health I should have full fucking help right now I'm just trying to rush through this because I
lost at the stupidest time good things a full dinner there thank you pick up the dinner
catch them all give me a full dinner I'll be happy I promise thank you it's not like you have an OCD
probably
hope she made lots of dinner dude there's a full dinner should I get it
okay god damn it please I have to
beautiful joke over here tap tap tap tap tap tap tap tap okay let it go
tap tap tap tap tap tap tap tap tap tap tap tap tap tap tap tap tap tap tap tap tap tap tap tap tap
tap tap tap tap tap tap tap tap tap tap tap tap I got hit again come on get it get it get it this
is important I can kill him right now kill him right now kill him kill him kill him kill him kill
thank you how is he losing in a slow motion Mario Party game ban that first I got some
I got some he's a tyrant thank god there's a save point and there's a power up all right what
did I need I have two lives turbocharged save for the turbocharger let me save for the charger
yeah there's no way I'm gonna do this without it are you the dude that ate a shoe yeah welcome
to the screen thanks for stopping by thanks for checking us out you can't be as good if
you take a lot of damage yeah probably is haha that's yesterday's joke wait isn't the title
well the title is yesterday's joke what is it if beautiful joe appears as smashed you'll see I'll
eat his shoe I gotta change that you're right if beautiful joe appears to smash dlc no how about
how about um that wasn't yesterday those two days ago if beautiful joe oh okay will beautiful joe
be in smash and I'm gonna write ongoing poll and then I'm gonna do uh show the results so far
yeah we're doing an ongoing poll
so people know when they come in okay let's go
burger looks amazing warning warning almost didn't get it no no just get them okay oh zoom in oh I
oh I almost got them all
I need this other bar okay you're killing me here you're killing me with this bullshit
oh pissed restart I can't restart you drown oh oh my wait wait wait wait oh my god it knows that
I'm bad wait I can't take it out I'm not gonna be restart Randy I only have two I only have two
continues whatever it's not gonna happen too late okay you can take that crusty audio does that
sound crusty audio that sound crusty audio feel that one all right keep moving maybe these
beautifuls what the fuck just happened it's just slow my computer's fucking slowing down
oh okay stop joking no more fucking jokes okay that's what I that's what I deserve for like
trying to make jokes when I need to dodge pixel perfect shoots just do it it's like
filter the water filter it's fucking with my brain like I'm seeing double no that's crap
is it though
what are you gonna do fuck out of here where's this bomb that they're talking about
think it's time to do this no
oh
hit somebody in the head fix your levels what are you talking about your five levels
will you just come on and do this bullshit again the audio is popping that's because
it's being pulled through a terrible dogshit capture car that no one should ever fucking own
for any reason talking about the el gato hd60 do not ever buy this for any fucking reason
in full life that's reverse psychology well I would that's not my intention it's fixable lower
hold on wait wait wait I gotta tell everybody that I've done everything um so they say lower
the levels coming from the weed of the capture card already did it we did it in real time like
two weeks ago sorry I'm just gonna I gotta be gotta be clear I gotta I gotta gain I gotta gain
I gotta gain right turning it off and turning it on again how about I spike it into the trash can
maybe that'll help ah I'm running out of juice here come land on it I guess they're underneath
him when he does that oh my god I hate these guys and I'm running at time zero speed
did I not hit it how do I open this oh like this right what
can I wait can I take oh okay we'll come on in here hey guys is the bomb been armed or what I
don't know good question cool let's go well I'm gonna give an F on that one what do you mean
you're gonna finish this and then go for it I immediately what wait what why am I what post
oh half the time I look over here I have no idea what the hell you guys are ever even talking
come on yeah do it yes now what did that do oh a secret bomb I needed that that's good
this is gonna be a pain in the ass get out of the way guys get no you know what I have to get
what what's a good capture card today I feel like nobody makes them anymore because like
nobody buys them now fuck you get a band-aid can I stand on this
no I gotta do right in the middle there we go I can't wait should I jump up into this
okay so yeah you gotta I gotta you gotta jump you can't fall into it you gotta jump
up all right here we go it's a bit right all right oopsie daisy you didn't mean to do that
oh fucking in zoom in shit get it okay go go go go go I haven't finished it's
infinite it's infinite it's infinite what does that matter okay that's what you gave me this
infinite shit at the worst possible time in all of history it's electric shit everywhere
yo but yeah okay yeah what does that say guard guard I was saying guard wait oh fuck I thought
I could dodge them if I was wait why don't I just take another what I took two things
of damage there what the fuck is touching the floor that motherfucker got me right in the fucking
back give me a break man fuck get out of here all right come on I still have to do something
over here somehow what is it doesn't want me to do turn them off turn turn the bomb thing on if
I can it's part of the video game punch I okay all right all right I don't understand the hell
this month how does it look like I'm not wearing my glasses for effect okay that was okay all right
I've all right this game I wish the game looked like this this entire time I really don't think
you wish that thanks thank you the sprained arm well I would call this horrible but you know
I oh burger thank you oh fine remember there's a bomb that needs to be disarmed
I know I'm all right I'm gonna I'm gonna put it in fucking c mode only mode thank you only 29
oh I don't need this today I only have one more health before I am so dead I hate these rooms
they are the worst I don't like this level that's level deleted really all right I caught
him in the air I need to regenerate regenerate regenerate regenerate there it is there we go
times two oh let's knock him over there yep bomb has been armed morning oh
swing at me where'd he go he's dead yes all right 20 000 what do I need I need 30 000
shit this bomb has been off for a solid 30 minutes yes I know I wish I could turn it off
but I can't I'm stuck here I love this game but I didn't like it when sections like this were in
yeah this is annoying but it's still part of the video game you still enjoy yourself
you don't want people to chat to think you don't like this game be careful you think I don't like
it I want this guy in smash brothers you think I'm gonna be like water level suck
no I'm gonna be like that's water levels like guys that's all right you know I decided oh my
fucking god I missed you okay all right this is where it gets a little embarrassing I'm trying to
rush it I know you're trying to rush because I know it's I get it trust me I'm there I'm with
you there I mean it's actually me that's here and I did it again and I'm just trying I'm trying to
get the fuck through this as fast as possible Leon Kennedy's gonna be in smash no he's not
Leon Kennedy's in smash L what just happened there what just happened it was on it now we
can move on with our fucking lives oh I can't even see this fucking ticker up top is blocking
this still why does it have to be up here what's the point no it's all right it's okay it's okay
it's cool it's all right it's okay any beautiful that's cool that's took damage I just got so mad
that I just took fucking damage get me the fuck out of here give me this credit card holy shit
I did it don't worry guys I did it that was a pain in the ass now what there I gotta go back
now go back of course 450 beautifuls good oops we're fine
back it up finally full health okay good good good good good good good good good good good
don't what do you mean slow slow I want to hit it in there why you tell me to go fast
no what the thing was telling me to go slow he's omega lol so bad he wouldn't have done that
you didn't know what this game is you came in here five minutes ago and you were like I don't know
this is but this guy's not yeah you didn't know this is don't make me laugh I'm probably missing
out on so many crunchies this shitty Kirby game imagine having such a such a poor attitude that
you think that that's such a bad attitude to have for beautiful joe whoa okay that was dumb
I agree with you how what does this have anything to do with Kirby only 24 000 shit what do I do
should I get another life no it's I have to win I probably should get the cheeseburgers to get
full health I can't do the vfx here to like 30 000 so I gotta wait do I get in should I get some
health max health now I'm probably gonna get health before the boss oh I gotta be good this
is the boss yeah take two no I can't it's too much money beautiful joe is a good game it's
just not a good Kirby game I can agree with that all right just play good just play good
I'm just gonna try to play good just play good go I'm gonna go here we go play good this is the guy
that goes oh yeah what are you doing over here yes I swear to god people are gonna be like oh
that's make sense fuck this guy I think this guy's hard this guy's scary from what I remember too
he scared the shit out of me when I played this before because he goes like ah and he's Grand Bruce
goes to your hideout
never mind okay but yeah you have to know mate we need that girl for our destiny plan to escape
movie land
I think it actually does a Jaws theme song too it goes like
Dun dun dun dun dun dun dun
I think
yapping about escape movie land
yeah
you best shut up mate otherwise I'll show you your hindquarters like a big stickle
gum gum gum do I have to spell it out on a chalkboard for you yeah so
there we go he throws up trash that's a GameCube oh oh god I can't get out get out get out get him
off me now we're underwater fucking fantastic where is he oh ah this is what I'm talking about
oh he I get it I get it yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah he gets he grabs a bump
don't get too cocky on this guy oh yep it's stressful where is he don't even fuck around
for the bombs okay over here he's gonna go raw you get one you got one what oh all right easy
easy easy easy easy down down down he's so fast I don't like it okay wait wait just kick him in
the head once where'd he go where is he where'd he go oh shit where is he there is oh right there
he'll jump right into it he got one shit back it up back it up back it up back it up
oh fuck no I jumped into it I'm so mad he's healing oh fuck he is healing I gotta
ah grab this one right in front of you oh that's not good I'm dead oh god damn it oh he sucks
this is the last chance he heals on the water I gotta get him out of the water
oh my god I'm trying to get the fuck away oh this is bad this is very very very bad
right here grab it all right get out of the water dude holy shit
where are they right here just go right into it he's gonna go right into it run two three
am I what's going on huh oh my god where the fuck is he get out of the water
shit okay I need a good one I need one that's right in front of him why is he not doing it
come on dude do the all right right here what he went a weird way oh wow I thought he went a
fucking wicked weird way nice good placement right here god damn it oh I'm in oh he's healing
again he's at full fucking health guys this is insane holy shit he just regained to full health
and oh come on what is with this placement all right get out of the water where you go
don't go with the fucking oh come on what the fuck he's just regaining what
I'm dead whole level has to happen again oh this is painful oh no oh wait do I get to try from
right there do I get to try from right there do I I think I do I think it's right there yes
oh this is beautiful this is absolutely beautiful I was about to be very mad I'm not even mad I'm
excited they actually give it to you because this guy's hard man are they gonna get me through the
whole level again it's a hard game I gotta zoom in and do more kicks I know we have to do we do
have to watch the bit no we don't all right let's go that's all right it's okay I got cocky for no
reason but here comes a look at that good start really good start oh man what's he doing down
there what's he doing down there I'm right over here right in front of me right here oh shit oh
shit I don't know what direction he's in is he regaining he's gonna run into this one right here
hello ah where where is it where is he you come on what the fuck give me that full one
what no fuck this guy sucks he's so scary it's fucking making me panic
fuck off me bootie empty Jesus oh no he's not gonna regen right hey hey hey hey hey god damn it
where is it oh get the fuck out of here he's regening nope oh my god what happened out here
oh shit what the fuck is happening anybody know no no no no what the fuck
okay now get the fuck out where you go oh shit man here we go stay right here oh please just don't
hit me get the fuck out get the fuck out get the fuck out get the fuck out get the fuck out he's
gonna get me get the fuck away from me sir don't you regen don't be a fucking asshole about this
oh you can't be serious don't move he's gonna hit the one right fucking here I am
excruciatingly upset by that I thought he was gonna get the hitbox oh my god damn it this is
fucking stop RNG fucking bullshit and then that hit the box there you go oops get out
give me a good RNG it's not what I wanted it's good good good no he's gonna ram me
I gotta stop get out of the zoom in oh my god and there's nothing he can do about it
he's about to be in deep shit he's about to be in deep shit
his feet it's too scary okay we're still in this one still in this
you put a bomb next to me man hello where is it huh oh oh oh oh oh it is a guy okay I gotta make
this is more take a guy yep it's an M I don't know anyway get the fuck out of my life that was
horrible I didn't even have any words I couldn't speak that was fucking the hardest shit that was
insane my whole body is like on fire right now that was fucking hard as shit
what was the last part uh what did I just say uh I said this guy's coming after me
I only have to hit him two or three more times and I win and what good RNG
placement I think that's what I said will this trail eventually lead to Sylvia will the ship
become the next Noah's ark for Joe or will he become the next bait for Moby Dick to find out
don't miss the next installment of beautiful Joe the beautiful escape oh that guy was horrible
oh and is a save point ah praise be to the light you're bad that's fine that's fine that's okay
I'm playing on the fucking hard mode dude come on grounded because you said dick
well then get out of here you gotta get even more trouble you're gonna get in so what you're
gonna get in trouble again all right vfx turbocharger got it yes all the money we have
that's rude no it's just realistic
that curtain comes up and it's mario 3 the beautiful escape
wow that's a missile coming out can I get up there no missile incoming
nice dodge nice dodge that was pretty good can you hear the buttons can you hear the
bye bye another one coming oh shit floor guide bridge machinery room engine room
be careful for dangerous stuff all right so we gotta go up into the engine room we gotta go up
into the bridge uh okay that was a little odd but whatever what did it put me well okay I'm
confused right now I've got knocked off around the whole level all right let's go up to the engine
room well we gotta go down okay I think I can bring that other thing with me now this is one
back here right oh shit there's some toys ah there we go I want to hit by this oh wait do I
have to protect it I didn't even see what happened to it oh shit okay I have to bring it down with me
okay let's go come here come here come on come on come on come on down down down down
all right now we gotta go up whoa oh well this is sad I kind of want to just die and then
continue because having one health here is just is bogus I would consider this to be pretty bogus
you know what I mean I can hit once in a bit hopefully there's food up here oh yeah
fucking blew it come on come on come on oh you gotta get on what the fuck what the fuck
why was I going through it why did it go back what what what yeah I huh no uh I that's bad
right there I don't know I'm gonna I'm gonna I want a better shot at this
just kill me I gotta I gotta get this is the beginning of the level
I can't be down one health one continue already that'll be bad just kill me look I got no clothes
on attack me I got no well I got no suit on whatever then you take double damage right
ready all right kill me kill me kill me kill me kill me kill me kill me kill me kill me kill me
boy I can do that myself why am I I could have just gone no what do I have to pretend
go crunch man's killing me do my street fighter knockout line sure okay fine
all right I'm gonna get hit now what the fuck the audio is muted oh shit
oh
all right let me get to a save point and I'm gonna go I'm gonna I'm gonna get up and move around
remember those who didn't know the new german na5 streaming schedule is four to five hours a week
that's not it that would be fucking terrible that would be not even screaming that's four to five
hours four to five hours a week oh boy well it takes me like it takes me more time to brush my
teeth take a shower and take a shit than a four hour a week how long do you think it takes a
week to take a shower brush your teeth and take a shit a week I'm gonna say it's probably it's
probably like what is about 10 minutes in the shower like five to ten minutes in the shower
two to four minutes to brush your teeth um and then about 15 to 45 minutes depending on
what you ate last night okay I'm getting hit too much so you're talking about like an hour what
like 15 15 minutes 30 well like an hour and 20 minutes a day feeling like taking a shit and
like brushing your teeth and taking a shower yeah so that would be yeah that makes sense what
do you eat well sometimes you just want to hang out in there people that say that are I know you
guys know are you know my stance on this already anybody right now that's saying like what the
fuck are you talking about no it's okay you can pretend on the internet it makes sense like you
can you can pretend on the internet you can be anybody on the internet right now but all of us
here know you don't have to we know I know that they might be like they might be like
I don't know you might be trying to hold on I can't fuck this up give me a second
what were you saying why is derma beating up toaster strudels strudel oh that like they look
like the toaster strudels all right I don't want to screw this up again all right where's the
where's the bomb what's the what's the thing babam bill I know where I know what it is
get down here babam bomb bill right bullet bill okay and excuse me excuse me why excuse me what's
going on here why can I not get on this excuse me excuse me excuse me uh wasn't it just it wasn't
it there it was right here the fan yeah and the thing was the thing was right here I have to drop
it down into the fan oh this is bogus call this a monumental pain in the fucking balls is what we
call this okay come on I'm not gonna miss those no crack stream today guys that was me two hours
ago I'm not sure there's a stream that happens now that's not a crack screen you know I'm saying I
think we've gone too far I think we were point pass the point of no return I mean at this point
like I open up chatting like people I see I just see wild wild shit I see the most wild shit
stuff that I would never even repeat out loud for instance did the did the shrinking curse work on
your penis all right like I'm gonna say that uh I'll tell you I was so it's not gonna happen
because it's just I think it's a little too it might be a little too much for for her because
like she has she's like that's not what her twitter is for but I asked him if she would write
hey I don't know what the fuck's going on but Jeremy's dick is way smaller and like it was
kind of there like it was there maybe but I that's like that's like I think too that might be too
too much maybe all right what the hell's because of all the curse stuff I thought it may be funny
but then it's like who actually would think that was funny that's well I don't know she was like
yeah I'll do it and I'm just like yeah you could yeah and then I was like yeah maybe you shouldn't
maybe you shouldn't three two one wait a minute just go for it forehead what's the boss of this
one oh new enemy what's this new enemy do ready sure well how am I supposed to know what this
new enemy does let me know where I am how am I supposed to know what the new enemy does if you
don't do a song I won't give any bits it's okay to take yours to take care of you give up some
money hey keep your money all right keep it it's yours what the fuck man you gotta hit him in the
bum oh wait now he's a different character you gotta hit him in the space wheel like I'm not
sure what hit him in the space wheel beam no I need those tnt
little tnt little tnt kane he's your brother kane want me to do it really loud
he's your brother kane got it I see you missed one it's all right
and you know I don't want like this like I'll fucking probably I'll this I don't know I'm about
doing this hey we got a safe point you know what that means buy enough what am I going to do an
only fan well I'm not going to do an only fucking fans account this channel that's like 6,500 subs
right now why do I ever do with only fans what the hell would I do that for this channel has
65 fucking hundred subscriptions is there would there be a reason for me to open an only fans
that's for your fans that oh what he's bragging no I'm telling you that there's no but why why
would I have like another place for you hey you know I have I have there's a shitload of you that's
subbed to this channel and there's like thousands of you hey all of you do that again over here this
time but keep the twitch one going too you don't do two I want like three Netflix subscriptions
of you subscribed and then and fanning to me on four different websites oh by the way on one of
these websites yeah you're paying you pay like five ten dollars a month and oh maybe I'll do a
Facebook post every uh maybe two or three weeks and then maybe I'll do I'll do a video for like
two minutes going hey what's up my supporters and thanks thanks for thanks for triple dipping
how does he not know what it's not like a patreon what is it how do you have a website called only
fans and it's not like a fan's like sign up to make money and interact with your fans that's
what the tagline is this doesn't this is only fans sign up to make money and interact with your fans
how it works look this is just like a person like on camera anyone can earn as far as we're
concerned if you if you use one social media and produce your own content you should be using
only fans right whether you're uploading tutorials tips behind the scenes footage or endless selfies
right this that's what this what are you guys talking about number of followers how many
fall okay how many followers do I have let me follow up what I have I have 200 let's just round
it up to 300 000 okay how many number of followers no number follow okay my monthly subscription
price is 15 dollars a month that's fucking outrageous you could earn between 45 000 and
225 000 per month what hold on wait a minute wait you could earn 200 000 a month based on
an estimate between one percent and five percent of your followers subscribing that's not going
to be accurate is this a hold on this is saying that if I have 300 000 followers that between
30 and 40 000 will subscribe that's not accurate it's more like 0.2 or something and it would be
no this is inaccurate it would be like five dollars it would be five dollars a month
and I only have a hundred thousand twitter followers so you would earn between 4900 and
24 000 a month that's a lot of money it's a lot of money oh no when I say only I mean only fans
I didn't say the fans part afterwards only feet it's porn it doesn't look like it from here
it doesn't look like it from here this is the only fans porn videos no there's no porn videos
oh maybe it is only fans has put x-rated entertainment in the hands of the entertainers
the paywall of porn oh yeah but can't you hold on a second but can't you do like if you have a
patreon can't you do like a you do like a is this porn not allowed on patreon could you like porn
patreon patreon porn you do like a point so what's the difference it's not it is it's all
it's allowed oops I just that's a pornhub link I can't I it's not opening right close everything
alt f4 every fucking thing I'll turn the stream off all right that was a pornhub link the first
one so I'm not gonna I clicked it but I immediately x is gonna make it two hundred thousand dollars a
month that's that that's like that's like retire that's retire like that's like retire in six
months money if you're making three hundred thousand dollars a month for like a year
that's literally you're done forever and it's tax free that's horseshit that's there's no uh guys
there's no such thing as tax free okay let me let me just be honest with you
move on I make double that I make four hundred thousand dollars a month
if I made four hundred thousand dollars a month I would have already reached out to
fucking Danny DeVito's agent and he I would have tried he would have streamed in my place
with like a like makeup on to look like me are you fucking serious you really think I wouldn't do
that are you are you kidding me if I made like half a million dollars a month I would make I
would I would hire a hundred clowns just to fucking sit in the room silent with me
like for a week straight and I would never address them you guys I'm dead wait what just
happened what's wrong with me what the hell's going on here did I wait okay I'm gonna hold
you to that when you really really make it big oh what the it's knocking me back into the other
part of the level the stream potential the jerk has plans what else would I do
just okay we're fine what does this want me to do what else would I do I I mean I'm full of
fucking stupid ideas I know that that's like a you hear a lot of them but there's stuff that
I've really always wanted to do but I mean who knows now come down if money was no object what's
the most out there idea well I I really really really really want to do another live action
germa rumble but I want it to be I want it to be like actually live like on twitch and I want a
bunch of crazy shit to happen on that stream I want it live on twitch not like a video come on
I'm trying to fucking make this happen I'm dead oh my god am I dead I'm dead I'm not I'm alive
I'm good I'm alive I really want to see you well here's you want here's something that's
actually kind of funny germa rumble live action 2 is already written already it's already done
it just has to be made that's a secret that I've held on to for a probably a couple of like a year
and a half it's already written the whole thing the whole thing's done everything is there the
only thing that would need to change is some characters that may have been more relevant
like a year and a half ago would have to just be replaced but there's this stuff in there that
hopefully if I ever had like an opportunity what the fuck if I ever had the opportunity
it would be a lot of fun I have it only for fun though well it's not even necessarily
there's there's like other options too and it's not because all right the carnival the carnival
was just like a fun thing to do and something I really really wanted to do and it was it was a
ton of fun I have blast doing it had a ton of fun making it and it was a blast and that was
I paid for the whole thing there was no sponsor there was no outside help it was literally just
I just was like here it's just a bunch of money okay do it if there was someone if like a sponsor
or something and as we've talked about it before the guys that did carnival we've had a lot of
conversations about this if it was possible it maybe that would be an avenue maybe maybe having
somebody that could could pony up a ton more money to do something crazy like that right I
don't have to make five hundred thousand dollars a month to do germa rumble life too the way that I
want it it would just have to make sense and it would have to be something that I that I didn't
I never wanted to get to a point where I take money on this stream for fun just because it's
there like the reason to do a sponsored stream like that would be solely to make it actually
happen it wouldn't be burning really any other reason I gotta go down it's not gonna happen
how do I do this oh it's gonna crush me I can't move I think I do I have the right idea what have
you sold tickets no I would want it to be free I just want I want to be able to people watch it
and not to pay for it and pay per view no that's too much that's too far I don't I wouldn't want
to do that how can I not do this I can jump through that contact yeah this we'll see I think it's
just to see it live would be fine yeah but the thing about venues like that you just have to
remember it it would have to be wherever it was filmed it would have to be you know obviously
protected and safe from anyone just kind of coming in and just hey I'm here I'm on the stream now
so having like a private venue is probably better especially if it's like a scripted event I gotta
make sure the right shit is done right people are involved because if it's just like oh hey guys
by the way we're at this venue welcome everybody to turbo rebel live twitch edition then oh and
there's five cars that just pulled up and there are just people are coming in people are knocking
on the door oh you can punch that guys he can punch that guys he can punch that thing the heck
but that's another thing like funding for a fuck I'm done I said all right I said we'll call it
her I'll see you tomorrow hey 500 dollars dude don't read that out loud because it's outrageous
uh so are we gonna fund this no no no what I was gonna say is I don't want to have a large stream
be the sole responsibility for you guys to pay for it hey I can't wait to do I'm gonna hype you
guys up turbo rumble live too I just need a hundred and twenty five thousand dollars guys
I just need like I need like seventy five thousand dollars everybody come on let's go like I don't
want to do that we have a number now no that's not even accurate not even accurate because there be
I would want you know obviously if you can get like a sponsor to cover a majority of that that's a
big deal it's gonna be more than that maybe the shit that I want to have happen on that stream is
like that they're gonna have to let's just put it this way it's gonna have to be uh four or five
different units on set for that so but there's other things that have been worked on just I don't
I'm not talking about them because why talk about something unless it's ready to go or makes any
sense or is real what kind of unit well you thought I was gonna do it no but uh yeah well
we'll call it here did I even explain what the new schedule was before I feel like I started
halfway and then I just gave up and like somebody called me stupid and I like yelled at them what
happened did I even explain it to anybody all right so what this channel has been used to has
been about three days a week for six to eight hours changing it because of my medical problems
it's better for me to do this in small doses but I'm going to do it more times a week
so instead of three to four times a week we're going to go four or five times a week
for about four to five hours a stream that's the plan so the streams will be shorter but they will
be at least one more day so it'll it'll actually turn out to be probably around the same time
streamed but just spread out a little more but yeah he has a yes make them shorter but funnier
I mean I just I don't have an I don't know how you can't how you do that
shorter but funnier
is that even I don't know how do I even how just be you have to be funny all right
I contrary to think popular belief here there is no plan when I turn a stream guys I'm not just
like okay I've got these 200 jokes ready I've got they're all lined up in front of me on
six pieces of paper I'm gonna go bullet to bullet it's kind of just kind of shit just
kind of happens show the joke list you have to break a leg use the sneeze macro it's gone
this thing had to be unplugged and like I did deleted shit leak the joke list
maybe I should start writing stuff down well I do have a lot of stuff written down would you
like to see would you like to hear what some of the ideas are written down they're gonna happen
in the next probably month or so I'll read them to you streams here we go I'll read a couple to
you let's see if I remember what any of these are green screen DLC obviously that's still
going to happen the iPad stream the iPad stream that's somebody had this this interesting concept
where you go to like YouTube on the iPad and click on every ad that's for a video game downloaded
and play it for 20 minutes and just do that continue to do it I'm gonna need a fucking new
iPad after that but you know that was one of the things to do like all those just mobile game ads
click of and download them but then I'm gonna get like tracked for life so that one hasn't happened
yet the easy bake oven stream is still on the on the plants here just have to buy a few more
things for it but that's gonna happen sooner rather than later oh another one that's gonna
happen soon you I was gonna get a bunch of those old kids board games like slobber and Sam
and like mousetrap and just get like a two dozen of them and just try to play them and like over
like a two stream period I was thinking about maybe even seeing if other like people might
want to do that get like four or five people to try to play these stupid shitty games from like
1995 that's another one that's coming up probably what else we got all right we got mad world for
the week that's written here for some reason that's here uh monster lab for the week we can
go ahead and delete that one what else is on here deadly creatures we can delete that one the
bachelor for the we delete that one that one's gone uh mario sunshine i haven't updated this
in at least a couple weeks as you can see but i've been busy uh death jam fight for new york
is on here but i don't have it okay i gotta get it dead rising three is on here city skylines
played that one oh mu gun mu gun insanity right and this is bringing back some some more ideas
i was going to download every single fucking character in mu gun every single one and uh play
and try to play through it like just pick random character and play and see how far i can get with
each character that's probably a terabyte of space that's a hundred terabytes are you serious
some characters have viruses but what if i just get another computer like can i use like an old
laptop or something or an old like desktop and just get a one like two terabyte drive and that's
just the mu gun computer and like even if it gets a bunch of viruses who cares that's money no i'm
talking about my like an old computer i'm not gonna go buy i'm not gonna go buy a computer to
break it with mu gun viruses what it would be a mu gun computer and i would just pull the video
through feed through the i said the thing about malgato being the worst thing ever right fuck i
feel like i've said that like 10 times that was like the worst piece of hardware you could ever
buy and that's like not even true it's an 100 that's 100 terabytes how many characters are
every character in mugen like 50 000 how many characters are in mugen there's more than 50 000
characters what people are still me yeah that's crazy well i'll get the ones that don't have
viruses i'll get ones that are verified uh drew crew is on here let's go ahead and delete that one
uh the cooking simulator food network update is on here that come out yet
uh magical quest starring mickey mouse that's another one what is it what is it ufc3 what is
ufc3 oh this reminds me i gotta get that olympics game that's gonna be a that stream is gonna be
fucking nuts that just like the 2012 like london olympics or whatever game
i'm gonna i'm gonna destroy that game am i ever gonna play doom there are like new games that
i have to play i i really have to try i gotta do at least one like triple a game that's not animal
crossing animal crossing is the only new game in 2018 to 2020 besides what was it uh
out of wilds and animal crossing are the only two games i've played that have come out within the
last two years in the last like four months oh mario sonic of the olympic games that's another
one i got a lot of shit here and there's other things that are on here that i'm not gonna say
out loud because whoa they're whoa whoa they're big deals whoa don't want to get your hopes up
on these but uh big deals coming up here wow i'm gonna go ahead and delete these because they're
not gonna these are bad spoiler leak one i'm not gonna leak one no you'll just it'll just happen
you'll see it tell us tell us nope nope nope easy bake oven i'm gonna make a bunch of fucking
child size cupcakes and and shit there you go that's happening i by the way those of you
those who think i'm fucking bullshitting you i'm just a fucking bullshitter
oh he's not there's no way he doesn't he doesn't even he doesn't even have an easy bake oven
he doesn't even he doesn't even have an easy bake oven be right back
he's flexing it's like a christmas photo dude show me your christmas hall man yeah this what do
you think that's a christmas hall tweet that's an empty box i was about to pick it up and shake it
but that's a bad idea by the way a quick question um can an easy bake oven burn you it's made for
like seven-year-olds right i can't get like burnt can i can i get burnt somehow i can all right so
i'm gonna have oven mitts and shit because i don't want to get my hands burnt you're gonna get burnt
i'm not gonna get burnt i'm gonna have big oven mitts on and if this thing is made for
seven and eight-year-olds what's how many wait hold on danger to prevent electric shock do not
immerse in water i got my easy wake up i'm gonna take a fucking bath and drop it in the bathtub
are you fucking kidding me why would you do an easy bake oven like in the bath what's the age is
for what what are they how how old do you have to be to use this what is it this thing has to be
plugged in what age is nutrition facts one package of what wait there's already wait how this stuff
has been in here for a while can i still eat this chocolate brownie vanilla frosting and rainbow
sugar crystals these things probably aren't edible anymore they don't really have a name
produced what does this mean what the fuck does that mean hold on yeah i need to take this you
need to see this produced with hold on if i eat this am i going to turn to like a fucking mutant
i need to open this for a second okay by the way what is what is what is this what is this
what is all this what is what is all this why is this like this what is this why is it like this
what is this is this some kind of a line there there's a comedy line i've said all right look
at can you read that produced produced produced with produced produced with genetic engineering
what the fuck does that even mean produced with genetic engineering
it's a 5g easy bake oven most food it's well it's a gmo oh that means gmo why did they say made with
gmos why they put genetic engineering that makes it sound like a resident evil plot
mixes contain wheat milk egg soy and trace amounts of peanuts tree nuts and something else
allergen information okay uh mixes contain wheat milk egg soy allergic to soy trace amounts of
almonds you know those of you not allergies uh peanuts tree nuts and and so and a fucking like
pokemon and sulfites sulfites what is a sulfite wait this shit's got dye in it sugar
carnauba wax confectioners glaze yellow five yellow six red three red 40 blue one blue one
lake red 40 lake i just gave you the coordinates to my house what the fuck is that okay well
this will be fun the ultimate oven i'm gonna i'm gonna i don't want to get burnt though
that's important i'm gonna be in like fucking gloves what did i walk in on uh me leaking a
stream to you that's that's a stream leak do you think it said do you think in there it says like
do not consume alcohol when operating the easy bake oven right probably probably bad idea right
well it's for kids so it's right okay i know but what if it all right okay no it's not this is not
a nintendo labo this is a large piece of fucking electronic equipment that i could burn myself
with so i'm not i probably shouldn't have like any wine i'm gonna look up like how many glasses
of wine can you have before using an easy bake oven one well what the what uh it was designed
to be used with a dumb brain it's made for what it's made for kids yeah but that doesn't mean you
can you you can still get hurt what's the temperature that it gets in there oh this is
kind of freaking me out is this thing getting like i hate ovens by the way have we never even
talked about this i know the spring is supposed to be over but i hope i fucking hate ovens ovens
freak me the fuck out i hate them we talked about this right i just think that uh have we not gone
over this have i been too embarrassed to talk about this okay well it's an oven is this box
that's in your house and you turn it on and this box gets to be three four hundred plus degrees
like five fucking hundred degree little box that has gas going into it and it this i did the same
thing i've said we talked about yes i have all right okay you're doing the same words i know i
just got to be clear that's i asked i asked i know i know i've talked about it before so
how what is what does it get to be like 400 degrees in here how hot does an easy bake oven get
like 350 how much is how hot does it get it's a children's toy with gas no you don't hope
does it feel like a gas line i'm just saying how hot does it get it's it's wait an easy bake oven
is a light bulb it's a fucking light bulb it cooks with the light bulb is that can you you can't how
oh that's not even accurate i put my hand up to some like halogen lights before and been like
oh shit that's fucking toasty i never thought to put like sprinkles on it so it's just it's
just a light i could have a glass of wine if it's a light if it's just a light bulb
i'm gonna look that up it's heat remember don't eat the light bulb i'm not gonna eat the light
bulb let's see how hot how hot does an easy bake oven get to 375 fucking degrees guys that's not a
light bulb that's 400 degrees that's your oven gets to be 350 400 that's gonna fuck i'm getting
hurt it's a light bulb how hot is the light bulb in this room right now how hot is this light bulb
let's see that's hot is that 375 degrees though okay let me ask a question i actually have a
question for you guys so when you touch a light bulb and you go fuck that's hot how hot is that
what degrees what what at what degree are you like whoa that's fucking hot like your light bulb
the light bulb in your room i'm sure you like right 200 200 okay so you tell me that that is
gonna get 175 degrees hotter than the whoa that's hot okay i'm afraid to put i'm afraid to use this
in my room i'm gonna like i'm gonna do the stream like in the garage i'm gonna go to i'm gonna do
like a garage stream that's gonna be creepy as fuck by the way what a creepy fucking stream
i'm doing an easy bake oven stream in a garage that's terrifying let's have bugleberry do it
no that's you know how hot bugleberry gets do you understand that how hot bugleberry gets
in his skin how hot bugleberry's skin is when he's sitting there with the trench coat on and his big
fucking face you know how hot it is in that trench coat probably pretty hot i would say if i was
bugleberry and i was sitting there for like 20 straight minutes in if i was him i haven't used
light bulbs for easy bake ovens in literally decades so what is in there i'm gonna be like
wicked safety about this i'm gonna be so safe with this you have no idea because it's not just easy
bake oven easy bake oven is probably the main event of that stream i would say i'm gonna get
a bunch of those little like kits those little uh like cooking kits like remember the thing i
tweeted out i'm gonna get like three or four maybe five six of those and do them blend no it's a
fucking toaster yeah but i would don't be like scared of a toaster i don't know anything that
generates heat it just kind of yeah for some reason it freaks me out i know it's like safe and
shit but even a toaster it's like this is this is little it's a little these wires in there and they
just get to be like six fucking million degrees just so concentrated concentrated fucking heat
and i just like i don't even know i want to cook i wish like i wish i could cook with the sun
if i could cook with the sun i'd be that'd be great if there was like in everybody's backyard just one
beam of fucking insanely hot like 400 degree heat light that was just in your backyard oh you just
like put like a hamburger fucking out there and like underneath the light it was like
you flipped it you live in vegas you can do that not until august the sun is way hotter all right
when you go like this i know we're supposed to be ending the stream but i have i have questions
when you like a line like this and it's 120 like 115 degrees outside how hot it's 115 degrees
it's gonna say how hot is the sun on your face it's 115 degrees that's how hard it is outside
that's how hard it is i don't know why i thought that like it was like a chemical reaction on your
face i don't know why i'm thinking that when the sun that's 115 like is hitting your face there's
like a chemical reaction that goes up to like 180 you'd fucking melt your skin would be peeling
up humidity that's what i'm doing everybody hold on a second humidity right if if it's like
if it's like 75 humidity then it'd be 115 that it would go up to like 130 how hot is hot
if it's humid it's nice no it's not absolutely horrible thing i just heard somebody say
humanity is the worst thing in the world it just is i would i'm such a lizard fuck i dry just dry
dust air is i wish i i what do you mean i wish i lived in that i'm in like the driest fucking
dustiest place in the united states of america next to maybe arizona god i wish i lived there
what's that oh you're hiding me i just sit in a chair in a room i don't know where the fuck i am
literally next to arizona yeah dry heats is yeah wet heats sucks how you guys doing we're good
all right i gotta go i gotta go i want to get up and move around end the stream waiting room
i'm gonna ban you for at least 15 minutes maybe you'll think about that over these i'm gonna ban
you know i'm gonna ban you for 115 minutes for each degree that it is outside how's that sound
okay see you later dude you just lost a sub okay what the fuck am i doing
see you guys tomorrow tomorrow what are we gonna do mark you know what maybe i'll finish should
i finish beautiful joe tomorrow got like another probably a few hours on it finish beautiful joe
tomorrow and maybe why are we saying no why do you guys hate this game why do you all right
why do you guys hate this game why does everybody hate this what this game is like fun and exciting
and there's like characters and what you guys hate this game boring it's a good game it's fun
it's engaging i don't like dislike it i love it germo fuck the haters that fucking hates this
guy they hate it chat hates this and that's real that's not even like oh he hates us joe
you guys hate this i don't know who said and we actually hate it it looks awful
it's fun to play i don't like watching it damn it okay but we're playing it tomorrow and i blinked
like twice that's how like okay no and when i say something and i say and i blink like okay
that means like oh he's fucking actually like annoyed by that and like now he's you can see it
in his eye blinks no i don't wanna look i'll hold the right trigger down the whole time so
it goes twice as fast we just annoyed him i'm doing it again i am wicked blinky though i'm
like a blinky person another reason why i don't have the webcam on all the time because i usually
just sit here and go like he's a lizard i know that's okay i'm gonna cry tomorrow when the
stream begins why because it's beautiful joe i like i like it but i we'll see i'd probably if
i don't finish beautiful joe tomorrow and just now i'm like oh germa germa you never finished
games germa you know you always get halfway and then you you'd like just give up like what the
fuck's up with that why do you do that well uh take a look at the chat right now and everybody
why is he not gonna finish beautiful joe it's not working what's going on oh they all hate it and
they're all screaming at me to stop playing does that watch work right now germa's gonna resign
he's mad mad enough to eat a fucking battery on stream no i don't want to put that that scares me
because can you like touch if you okay this is the plus and minus if i like touch my tongue to the
plus and like this is like a current on the my i like it i'll just shock my mouth i'm not gonna
do that that's a fucking terrible idea that's a mistake you could actually get you could actually
get hurt by that all right what's more dangerous putting a battery in your mouth
or operating an easy bake oven the way that it's supposed to be by the manual
like if i went like this and stuck my tongue on the battery is that more dangerous than operating
the easy bake oven with with with parent adult supervision the way that it's intended to what's
more dangerous where does iq go i have 124 iq by the way 60 performance iq but like 100 visual and
then like 80 linguistical that's actually real i did a real like four hour long iq test when i
was like 17 or 16 i did it again when i was 20 because i wanted to find out what was wrong with
me and it turned out i was really fucking smart but i was really stupid at doing things correctly
there you go it was on facebook no oh yeah click here five minute 10 questions yeah those are just
ways to find out how you lean politically by the way guys oh question number three solve this uh
solve this cube this cube you have to move some pieces around uh thanks for clicking on our iq
test nice nice okay next so it's over here it's over here is joe biden and then bernie sanders
is over here uh which one of these two would you would you say you lean more towards uh this one
okay okay so question six is um solve for x that's all they care about they don't the questions
one two three five six seven eight nine ten are fucking meaningless they just want question three
answered and you'll do it remind us collecting data he actually took a facebook iq test i think
i did it on this stream like two months ago the stream is never ending i'm just chilling
sometimes i just hang out those years ago no that was when i was in vegas for our adhd exam stream
i couldn't it's it's it's not even embarrassing me selling telling you this because
hold on i'm not done i said my streams are gonna be like four to five hours we're
almost five which is this is like a hangout session um if i took a like a high school test
right now like a real one an actual high school test geography math science social studies
whatever history i felt i would i'm gonna be realistic very realistic i'd get probably
between five and ten points on the test without question i would not get more than ten points
stand up and pace why stand up and pace and talk to you oh yeah because i can move around
okay so i mean if i took that test right now if i was in your classroom this is weird to me
i don't i don't like this i hate this i need a microphone right here if i don't have a
microphone right here then i'm just like i'm just like a guy in a room like walking around like no
vr headset or anything i'm just standing around and talking so if you gave me a test right now
and it was a high school test and by the way why why do i always just not look at anybody
right if there's a whole audience here i'm never looking at anyone in the audience literally ever
i'm looking at the exit signs that's a tip by the way for those of you public speakers that want some
public speaking tips just look at the exit signs back and forth that's how you do it so what you
do is you go like this there's an exit sign over there i'm going to talk at that exit sign and i'm
going to move our eyes over here and talk to this exit sign over here i'm going to make a couple of
points over on this exit sign and then somebody's gonna i'm gonna i'm gonna lock i'm gonna lock
fucking eye contact with somebody randomly in the audience and it's gonna freak the both of us out
for a split fucking second it's gonna go something like this so if you gave me a test in high school
and you said jeremy jeremy if you gave me a test in high school you said jeremy find me
software software why i'm not sure i'd be able to do it and there's a reason why the reason is
when we get older we have two or three years after we graduate from school before we start
to lose some of that information that sucks and then you you're in the chair too and you're like
he looks right in my fucking eyes like we look yeah like well i'll never forget that short
please try to do a math test i can't i can't it would be embarrassing
hold on let me do the thing i did that hey hey hey hold on a second let me ruin my career
real quick like i did a couple of years ago remember this oh i'm gonna get off the chair
and i went oh fuck right and then it literally ruined my whole career there we go no remember
remember this bullshit with oh measure the door measure him next to the door measure him next to
the fucking door we can see how he is next to the door handle okay you want to play this fucking game
we'll play this game there you go there's the door measure him next to the door handle fine
assholes i'm pretty tall next to the door get closer to the door if i can't get any closer
because i'm gonna hit my fucking head this is like this is fucking close if i if i go closer
this is gonna be bad i mean liar i'm not get closer i just wait i'm fucking as close as i can get
i can't do you want me to do it again fucking assholes i swear to god you're making me do this
crazy shit i'm bleeding i can't even can't see all right goodbye i'll see you tomorrow i'll see
tomorrow okay bye what's going on with the hair i can't get a fucking haircut right now guys
didn't you understand i didn't get a haircut in fucking february and you look like hillary
hillary clinton hair hillary clinton hair just do it myself should i cut my own hair no
all right good night see you tomorrow goodbye oh forget we're gonna do this i didn't do the bits
for some reason i thought we did them and i was just like burning time for no reason
all right let's hang on to the bits i don't know if you guys hate beautiful joe that's like sad
work it off stream the haircut no that's odd all right let's teleport back hey the jewish bro
thanks for 500 bits thanks a lot say watch um manos hands of fate it's so bad it's a good movie
i've heard that before i think i have heard that before where's the music it should be playing
right now it's not now it is hey sticks renegade thanks for the 250 i bought i brought my sticker
car into the mechanic originally it was thought to be a 400 wheel bearing job but it ended up being
some rust cleaned up cost me 80 bucks so i'm passing off a few of those savings to you germ
boy by the way i forgot why you won't play it but can i suggest jackie chan adventures with
playstation 1 one of the most frustrating games of my childhood um i think i vicariously lived
through star making that video because we used to hang out in calls every single day and i got the
whole rundown pretty much every level he was everything he did it was a different game oh
that's not the same game jackie chan adventures what was the one that star played
what was the stunt master oh i didn't know there was more than one jackie chan game for
the playstation 1 well i'll look i'll look into it hey jason thanks for the 250 can we
watch auto big adventure please no doctor ducks thanks for the thousand bits ten dollars i didn't
know i didn't know strong bad had a game whoa shit that does kind of look like strong bad
but i that that they're different characters and strata that would keep a beautiful joke has been
off for a long time wembley ttv thanks for the 250 join the boopers germ i don't know what that is
but uh no i'm not going to join any boopers uh captain nemo thanks for 300 bits you should
watch who killed captain alex it's not copyrighted it's on youtube so it's perfectly fine to
restream it the plan is on friday we're going to come up with i want to try that feature
but maybe we'll get we'll come up with like a movie to watch like a public domain one maybe
we'll figure that out tomorrow thank you jason for the 250 you incited us that the game was so
hype only to give us a seizure on the start screen this game gets a minus two out of plus two well
there's only two ratings there and by the way minus two and plus two are not ratings for video
games there did you think the last thing said was funny and you're not using the rating system
correctly i think a lot of you have not been using the rating system correctly for a little
while now no it's for right and for yes okay whole of one zombie thanks to 250 when you're
when you're doing a doctor filled co-op stream also how come you never mentioned kfc thoughts
mr mcchicken um i like i don't really like kfc's bucket of chicken i don't really like anything
else from kfc if i'm gonna go to kfc i want the bucket of extra crispy chicken macaroni and cheese
and mashed potatoes that's it that's the only thing i ever order nothing else is i in my opinion
there's no reason to order anything else from there but that's just me uh when am i gonna go
on dr phil i'm not gonna go on dr phil sir canine thanks for the 250 my master plan failed because
of a twitch chat formatting problem feels bad man sorry about your plan uh friddle shits thanks
for the 250 i always thought this game looked so cool when i was a kid but i actually never got
to play it i'm so glad now that i'm finally experiencing it through my favorite streamer
so you like it oh should i change the title to who likes this game do you like beautiful joe
okay here we go i'm gonna change the title this title makes sense still ongoing poll do you like
beautiful joe and i don't have to change any of the numbers there don't have to change anything
thanks for participating and thank i'm glad you enjoyed it it's a fun game
hey robo fussin thanks for the five dollars hope you're feeling better kid worried about you i'm
doing fine i'm doing just fine don't worry about me you burr the uh that for i i that whoever that
was if you're still here probably not even still here you probably said that and then we're like
i don't know the beautiful joe sucks and you probably left 20 minutes later but you're that
was funny uh sticks renegade thanks in the 250 sorry i think i said jackie chan adventures i
meant jackie i meant jackie chan stunt master so you did mean the one that started the video one
if that's the case then i kind of already like i said have i curiously lived through it
that's by the way that's one of the best videos on youtube if you're curious
that's like one of the best video gaming related videos on youtube thanks to the 250 dude what
happened to my thing what do i think what the fuck happened to my thing
ours basically videos were brilliant yeah he's funny dude very clever he's a very clever dude
i have a thing yeah i have like two things open why is this not working is it working no
drew crew is back no they are not no they're not they are not no there we go all right i got it
uh we had 250 from yen wen president artist and they say uh i was thinking of recommending a game
that's by the same video i was thinking about recommending a game by the same developers as
beautiful joe clover studios which was founded by capcom however the game is around 30 plus hours
i'm about 34 hours into my play through him at the last level the game is okami i've actually
experienced okami before a great game the painting paintbrush the dog i think that's correct i think
that's the right game because you're a little you're a dog right you have a paintbrush you paint
with the paint for the wiimote yeah that's great it's a great game when you have a germa 985 video
about it i don't think i made a video on okami but i have played it so i probably wouldn't stream
it but it is fantastic it's a classic and then they didn't they remade it they remastered it
once or twice right he's played it get out of it but thanks for the recommendation yen wen
it's a great game hey drax von tour thanks for the 500 bits germa my brothers and i have loved
watching you for years and my dog is your biggest fan so this is from all of us hey thanks drax
von tour's dog also you should play the wonderful one-on-one when it comes out for the pc directed
by the same guy who directed beautiful joe another great game i have played it i played it when i was
on the wii u because it was one of the only games on the wii u that were worth buying
now there's probably four uh and that was one of them i have played it and it's very good i'm glad
they're actually gonna put it somewhere else but thanks again it's time for slime what's going on
time for slime thanks for the thousand bits 10 bucks you should filter out all caps chat messages
for a day just as an experiment see how much it throws off chat or to go another step further
uh shadow ban people that write paragraphs in all caps but here's the sad part about doing
something like that is we remove we then remove a person like the beautiful joe go brr thing
that was all caps that person was just fucking that person just that person was just thinking
they were gonna get banned you know what i mean they they probably was just like you know i'm
probably gonna get like timed out for this did they i'm not even sure they did like that was a
fucking paragraph in caps does everybody like have that message where is it what was the exact
message that is now in all caps mode if you ban me it was long it was super long and i it was just
i don't think anybody can i don't think it's like an elusive beast i don't think anybody has it
i don't think anybody has it but yeah maybe sometime we'll try it maybe one day for fun
thanks for the 10 bucks though appreciate it thank you trans scalp for the 500 bits
jerma trapped me in a mason jar and forgot to put holes in the lid jerma please it's so dark in
here um unfortunately i uh if if there it's been about four and a half hours um i hope the uh so
we got uh it's been a long time you you all right no error for four hours
uh whoops thanks to the 500 bits though you're really trying to get my attention to let you
out of that jar hey shadows one disciple thanks for the 250 hey king that's me i guess i want
to meet up on club penguin after tonight's stream uh visit my igloo and i can get you an invite to
cracking gamer the service comes out in a couple weeks also in regards to your recent medical
problems i wanted to give you a hearty better shop it means get well soon in my language dutch
better shop well thank you you want to do an invite to cracking gamer we already are there
every day we already are at cracking gamers it's everybody here everybody here is on crack we
already exist there i don't need an invitation but appreciate it thanks for the 250 have fun
in club penguin i can't believe that service is still on silent serenity thanks for the 250
asking chat what game they want to watch seems like asking 5 000 toddlers what they want for
lunch the only way to win is to give them the streamer equivalent to mcdonald's aka play family
feud why is it so true it's such a what that's such a true statement drew crew played jojo
beautiful joe sucked out like i don't like burger king all right fine we're gonna go to mcdonald's
yeah yeah everyone that's so happy everyone gets so happy when you say that
i think that's also like obviously we're making them we fuck around a lot on these streams
but i think the nature of playing a different game almost every single day this stream never
sees the same game like there's not like a game that it's like oh i play that we're gonna go to
mcdonald's there is no mcdonald's on this stream there really kind of isn't because there's a new
game every two or three streams at least so we kind of just try different restaurants every
single day and some people don't like those restaurants some people want me to go to another
restaurant some people want me to go back to a restaurant that they really like that they love
eating at and i love that restaurant too i think that's part of the reason why there's a lot of
requests you're the guy for the area of streaming i take two bites of the burger and then i leave
and i go oh that was that's killer oh out of the park man oh you nailed it you nailed it and then
we play another one the next day and in the background and in the background you just
or
there's two different songs there's oh there's only two songs only two on any episode of
dinos drives and dives there's the i'm gonna give you a list of stuff that this restaurant does
i'm gonna give you and it's gonna guy get a guy's gonna be like this he's gonna have a plate and
he's gonna just like throw the plate into the camera it's gonna go ding ding ding ding ding ding
ding don't wear it to join and then he starts explaining all the things in the menu that's that
one the other song is that i'm about to take a big fucking bite of your hamburger so it's
oh i got no i don't want to put that on camera that's weird he goes in for the bite and it does
that
there's only two songs on that show but it works and that's a great show i love that show
that show is fucking phenomenal i i'm one of these i'm a weirdo i like to watch guyfieri take bites
of hamburgers while i eat my bucket of kentucky fried chicken i i love eating with guyfieri i
love watching him like oh where is this like crepe restaurant oh cool man
i'm eating food too and i love my i like my food i'm watching you eat food while i like to eat my
food too where's he now oh those ribs look good another bite of my fucking taco oh man i love
food if you don't do that then i also don't believe that you don't spend 30 minutes in the
bathroom sometimes you do fiery mukbangs so who cares he's i really like guyfieri i think he's
great i really do i i like him i really like i think he's i think he's fucking phenomenal he's
such a swell person he seems like a cool dude yeah he he does i bet you he's if you met guyfieri
you were out somewhere and i'm like you went it was in one of his restaurants he was there
i bet you'd come over and i bet you he would he'd be so happy to talk to you yeah i really
believe that that's what i hear what is he your best friend
he's best friend material i'm not going to talk to a grown man with a flame shirt
no no but but you'll watch a grown man in a star wars shirt and you see how that logic is kind of
a little flawed you'll watch a grown man eat his shoe right i'm not that different than guyfieri
except my hair is not as cool pronounce it right it's fieri right fieri fieri it's not fieri it's
it's it's it's fieri fieri guyfieri yeti there it is i knew it i ate my burger while you were
eating your shoe he's got a shirt he's gets it's like a brand it's an image he's like a he's got
his own brand like who cares he wears like the bowling shirt he's got the hair it's a brand
thing it's like an image thing so you now you you know who he is you could recognize guyfieri
from a mile away you would know who he was what's the germa brand i don't have one i don't need a
brand toilet water that's not a brand that's a delicious drink anyways all right we're getting
close to the end here we're going to do uh bar broski thanks for 500 bits my mom overheard me
watching you she said boy that's an angry fellow hey streaky thanks for the 500 bits free money
i'll take it gray blob thanks for the 400 bits hash house a go-go baby how could i have not
thought that how could i have not thought that how is it possible that i didn't come up with that on
this stream hash house a go-go baby why i would have said it a thousand times nice work hash house
a go-go baby fuck that i would have said i would have loved that uh thank you clinks for the 10
community subs five back-to-back thanks clinks a gnarly thanks for the 250 these 250 bits will pay
for one tenth of glue man's cape in the live rumble if i keep this up you'll have the stream
ready in about 30 years see you then thank you for the contribution thank you hey the plushy
thanks for the 250 plushy hey germa my birthday is coming up soon i have no friends sick mom and
nothing to do but drink and play games hope you can stream on the 13th would make my day 13th is
let's see we're going we went today we're going thursday we're going friday we might go maybe
saturday if not then we're gonna do probably monday yeah we'll probably yeah i'll be i'll be
live on monday i will i'll be live yeah i'll be live on monday i mean happy birthday on monday
i'm relied about birthday stream no i'll be live on monday i don't see why i wouldn't unless
something comes up but i don't think it will kim and i are at the absolute finish line now so
everything should be good to go hey where's my keys thanks for the three dollars 299 chocolate
factor stream maybe uh there will no there will be no stream where i have to interact with other
people and this is absolutely the case until the coronavirus stuff is taken care of and slows down
and gets to a point where we can kind of open back up because there's no way that a chocolate
factory is doing tours right now not during this whole thing i would not there's no way so we have
to kind of just let that let's see what that does coronavirus is still very bad is the stream over
yes the stream is over back tomorrow but the when it's safe to do that and when it's
you know a little bit further down the road hopefully soon i will make a few phone calls
john cena is kill thanks for the 250 germa don't worry so much about not being able to stream in
longer periods my brother soft properties from p oh that's funny is this it wait a minute he
penile shrinkulosis that's not what that's not real right it's tough for him to you have that
it's real and you have it what the fuck no i don't all right all right all right all right all right
all right all right all right all right you just wrote ha ha ha ha then omega low pick one all
right pick one it's either one or the other hey sir canine thanks for the 250 it's funny because
the easy bake oven stream would just look like germa cooking with a funny pink oven or something
i'm gonna take i'm gonna be in like i'm gonna be in like a suit of armor
kus kus thanks for the 250 hey germa hope you're feeling better soon i'm going through some scary
hell stuff right now your streams help me forget about it for a bit hope it does the same for you
it does it does being able to hang out and just buck around and laugh and chill is it's it's a lot
of fun it helps thanks for the 250 let's get the credits rolling i'm gonna bump you in the
face a little bit here sorry about that about you all right bumped you and let's run them here come
all the subs today flying by in just a moment just a second what's gonna happen here it comes
here it comes we'd like to thank you for subscribing to the channel thanks a lot appreciate it
thanks ollie clap shit movie you're doing a great job a great job that's one of the best
that's okay that's if that's the second best video on youtube no that's the best video on youtube
i'm gonna just stamp that right now and it's not even a video that's how good it is
that shit's not even a video it's audio only it's the best video on youtube hey vertical giant
thanks for the 500 bits i was curious about the mugen stream so i checked the character archive
and there are about 71 500 characters most of them are around 10 to 100 megabytes
so assuming they average around 50 megabytes downloading every character would take about
3.57 terabytes jesus 71 fucking thousand characters how what does the character's
select screen look like it's just a bunch of dots it's not even possible that's almost but
oh i'm gonna do it there's a hundred pages of characters holy shit is that can you even
play the game like that you just screen for porn oh i will don't worry you're gonna fucking brick
a pc well hopefully it's an old one that doesn't matter one that i haven't really cared about in
probably five plus years i'm just gonna have to put a hard drive in it a few of them can you buy
okay what those not an ssd because a five terabyte ssd would be like 2000 fucking dollars
a five or 10 terabyte hard disk drive would be you can still get this for pretty cheap right
yeah like a 10 terabyte s uh hdd would be probably a couple hundred bucks hundred bucks
okay that's much better than like two or three thousand all right i'm gonna have my mugen drive
drive i see everybody doing a link here the whole chat is purple so i'm gonna just i'm gonna
screen it see what it is this is a six second video this is called crew crew take a look it's
off six seconds long check it out it's the true crew why does it take me so long to pull something
up uh because i don't have browser capture on by default because every because every time there are
links that like spammed in the chat and i like have to close them and look when i when i become
a professional streamer i'm gonna have a completely separate cap device that just pulls a a browser
window and it's gonna feed into the stream just i've got a i've got to grow up as a streamer a
little bit and sometimes it takes me a little while okay once i upgrade from a 1080 uh
graphics card is when i'll start having that easier and plus i don't like i don't want to
click on random shit just open it it takes me a few a few moments to make sure it's i have this
is a legal thing to show on stream because i know i've heard of streamers in the past they just open
up fucking every link that they see or they get sent to and then there's like a dick on screen
and then there's like uh something horrible or something bad and then they close the window
real quick and then they get uh yelled at or they get in trouble they get banned
you know that's possible uh hey thanks for the true crew uh we're gonna go to the end screen
see you guys tomorrow starting around the same time still have uh some bits left to do but
and wind down hey large 27x thanks for the 600 bits german please don't play this again for
the love of god just please and there's it there's got i think my my stream just crashed
okay ready dread just gave 50 community subs and my computer hung for five straight seconds
holy shit uh thanks freddy for the 50 subs dude thanks for the insane amount of money you've given
the stream you continue to you keep giving the stream this shitload of money dude thanks for the
fucking crazy money another 50 subs from freddy hillary clinton shit
it's the same it is the exact same hair that's not good i haven't been able to get a haircut in
like three months i have to get a hair okay kim's gonna cut my hair i'm gonna ask very nicely
give it kim um i'm gonna show kim this image i'm gonna say kim i have hillary clinton hair can you
please help me and we'll see what it looks like do it on stream no i'm not gonna do a haircut stream
let us cut it how would we go about doing something like that hey thank you thrag
thrag nel for the 500 bits german next time can you please eat your shoe and similar items
and stream it under social eating with absolutely no context one day
click map on head nope because i know exactly what you guys are gonna do you're gonna you guys
are gonna you guys are gonna give me the hulk hogan the worst haircut you could possibly ever
have as a human being that's that's the long that the hair stay the same length on the sides in the
back but the whole top is shaped i know because that's what i would do if i had the choice to
pick a haircut for somebody and it was something okay i'll get i'll do any haircut no buzz it oh
what the fuck i'm buzzed nope dude just cut randomly nope give him the hulk hogan
that's just it looks bad on everyone no one looks good with the hulk hogan haircut not even hulk
hogan does and he's the one that he's because he's got it has it he's got it like made it up
a mullet no a mullet would be longer in the back shorter on top the hulk hogan is shaved
and bald on top long everywhere else hulk hogan's haircut the hulk hogan is like a shower curtain
you know it's just like a shower curtain around your head starting at your your temples and going
back around the back of your head the term is skull it jerma all right that's not even like
fair somebody just that's they say well hulk hogan is just ugly no that's not even he's not
like hulk that's not even true hulk hogan's not like ugly go back to like hulk hogan in like the
80s in the 90s he wasn't a bad looking guy he wasn't an ugly guy that's not even fair
he's insanely ugly what the fuck no he was not what the fuck are you guys talking about
hey like this is like hulk hogan when he was like fucking 35 you that's the ugly man that's
what are you talking about he's like fucking handsome this is like 37 year old hulk hogan
he looks like you he's this hulk hogan is a handsome guy yeah guys i got news for you
when you turn 70 you don't look that great anymore like that's when you turn like 68
you get older and you look like wrinkly and shit he's a handsome guy let's try another one
look you just saw that one here he well that's not a very good we'll try a different one look
he's a fucking handsome guy he's a very handsome dude well hold on back in the 80s
just picking like the worst pictures he's a handsome guy and uh you don't know what the
f you're talking about anyways let's finish this is the hill you want to die on i've you know
how many hills i've died on on this channel like 7 000 hey kilken thanks for 300 bits germa don't
forget about rain world already did if you don't play it slug cat will starve to death he already
has uh you wouldn't want that to happen would you i wouldn't but it happened that would make
you a germa psycho i am thank you for the 300 bits peaceful hailey thanks for the 250 manos
is also one of mst3k's most popular movies they have rift that's where you know it from have a
good night probably yeah i've seen a lot of the old mst3k it was so good they you guys understand
that that mst3k is your original like react channel except they were funny they had actually
funny things to say no yeah i know i've seen them they they still do shit don't they
doesn't um they do rift tracks right does mike um mike nelson still does rift tracks right
don't they stream on twitch do they have at least like one to two thousand viewers to stream if
they don't i'm gonna be very upset and very sad there's a rift tracks rerun stream oh okay
do they do do they do live shows on twitch they do no they do not do live shows on twitch oh
okay they just do reruns okay it's a 24 7 rerun stream oh okay that's still cool though
i used to love that shit they were hilarious mike nelson's a real funny guy they do live shows
somewhere else raid rift tracks we could i mean i don't think there's gonna be anybody there to
react to your raid but we could some some like it guy is gonna be like what the fuck hello
i'm not sure anybody's there we'll see i'm here for this stream or for the stream all right let's
let's finish up let's finish up we took we've spent the last probably hour and a half just
picking around that's i i'm happy about that uh cheek zilla thanks for the 250 put an ad on
craigslist for someone to come to your home and cut your hair i spent money to pass you this
message to sleep on it i'm not gonna do that there's no way i'm gonna have somebody from
craigslist that i've never met before come into my house with a sharp object i don't think that's
something i'm going to do sir canine thanks for the 250 germa walk minecraft rafters in chat
germa walk i'm not gonna do a minecraft let's play it's not gonna happen i just want to make
sure everyone knows that very very clearly uh skinny peter thanks for the 300 bits this game
looks pretty cool thanks germa thanks one of uh 15 14 other people had voted yes thank you uh
locky man thanks for 300 bits have you thought about playing the strong bad flash game someday
they might not be online after adobe stopped supporting flash some will probably convert
them um there's probably somebody that would get in there and get the code and turn it into
the html5 or something probably what about ftk ftk is not a let's play of minecraft 1.0
but uh probably not i would i never really got into the home star runner stuff it's not that i
didn't like it i just it just didn't really get into it uh produces a sand thanks for the 500
bits always miss you when you're gone for a long while king it's another king laughs help a lot
especially through these tough times it means a lot can't tell you how much thanks and have a nice
night party thank you thanks for the 500 bits appreciate it dr ducks thanks for 600 bits a
germa can't imagine how weird it is to hear but have been watching your content for roughly a
third of my life and i have to give credit for shaping my sense of comedy throughout high school
and beyond you got the great streams inspiring thousands like you've been doing since you started
doing the silly voices i mean it's it's hard i i it's not hard to hear or weird to hear it's
i mean for me it's weird that i've been interested for this long i am so all over the place that it's
shocking to me that for almost 10 straight years i've i've never felt really once like
oh i don't really fucking feel like that doing that now i don't want to do that right now
that happens all the fucking time to me leave lead leading up to this i used to drop shit
immediately within six months so i'm happy and surprised and lucky and blessed and everything
you want to call it to be doing this as long as i have and still really enjoy it 10 fucking years
later so thanks hashtag no you know what i'm like i'm just giving you adjectives hey fart guts
thanks for the great username and the five dollars uh spaghetti spaghetti one nero thanks for the 300
bits so glad i've been able to watch your streams live this is probably my second is stream and both
have been pretty fun i'm good that's good to hear i'm glad my social media strapped me down to a
chair and forced me to watch all your clips i hope you feel better thanks for making quarantine cool
yeah welcome second stream that means by the third one you're going to figure out if you're
going to stay here long term that's tomorrow if you're here tomorrow i gotta make sure tomorrow
is a good one i could tomorrow but it'd be a good fucking stream otherwise that's the third stream
i might lose you find out are you still doing a community content night on the 10th
fuck right i did say that i want to do it ah shit is that all the public domain movie night
oh right right right right right oh fuck uh i gotta figure that out i gotta figure out where i want
to do that there was endless promises catching up to him endless promises uh we'll do it we'll we'll
we'll do it we'll do it within the next like seven days i promise i get i know i mean i'm full of
endless promises and lies and just nonsense i'm bullshitting i'm not bullshitting you right now
though i'm trying to make sure that future me does not bullshit you here but he might and i can't stop
him because five days from now future me might have someone else he's doing and i'm gonna i'm
just trying to tell him in the future just do it on like the fucking 14th or something
you got you can do it then listen to me future germa is out of control he is because he i'm
gonna rep you guys someone's gonna flip this and show it to me on the 15th when we didn't do it on
the 14th and i'm gonna be like oh well you know i had all these things to do and we gotta keep
future germa honest coming soon hey off butts thanks for the 450 hey germa high chat haven't
been able to see more than like an hour of streams lately because of school i hope that you and chat
have been doing well and staying safe thanks for all the laps king king again okay okay i'm gonna
not i'm not gonna reference king anymore i'm not even gonna read it i'm gonna say thanks for the
laughs thank you thank you for watching uh fart guts gave another five dollars yankees yankee
with no brim with pug champs still don't know what that means they're going to look it up after the
stream uh chunky baloney thanks for the 250 if you're taking game cube recommendations
eternal darkness is one of the best and if you don't have it if you don't have it already i do
i have eternal darkness sitting right behind me uh ps been watching second gerbavids during
the isolation and in the octogen video from 2018 you basically tell chat to smoke crack
this is the origin of crack streams look it up what octogen where octogen
second octogen oops all penguins when did i tell people they smoke crack feel the cool mist
and maybe some some girl will walk by you and throwing fucking trash contract what is the what
what this is what i do when i turn streams on what the fuck is that the whole class is
gonna laugh at you okay when do i tell people smoke crack four minutes and 84 seconds
wait that doesn't make any sense there's not 84 seconds
i saw the 484 sorry here it is i saw the 484 of the time stamp no this is not even the right video
why are you linking me this why are you linking me a q a i did from like fucking 2011
no i want the octogen clip i'm screening this oh it's irrelevant right okay
okay we can listen to this fuck quick story actually for you guys i'm sure some of you
would think this is actually kind of interesting so quickly i'm like wow when i first did my first
team fortress 2 commentary a couple months ago i did two in a row and i uploaded them on the same
night and the next morning i woke up and i said i don't want to do this this no one's gonna watch
me i'm too old for this i can't do this so i deleted all the videos and i was going to delete
the account it's true that did happen i deleted them all because i was like i'm too old and this
is 2000 this is 2011 by the way uh i'm 35 this year oh am i too old yet mr albertson have i
reached that point mr albertson this is this fucking 25 year old what the hell does he know
he doesn't know shit thinks he knows everything about the world no you don't and then i talked
to a friend of mine who said you know what it's also true you might as well just go for it yeah
thanks for that thanks for the advice if you stop streaming i swear all right where's the crack part
where's the why did you link me this where's the that where i tell people to smoke crack
do that there was absolutely no reason for that that's gonna be the reason why i lose
why me i'm dead i'm gonna i need time stamp for the crack part
everybody have time Jesus Christ uh i think if i just stop talking for a minute where's the crack
part the bees and have them on one side make any very easy wow you got two artilleries for
shooting at me 747 launcher artillery oh it's artillery fuck you got two artilleries for a
shooting at me fuck god i don't even want to watch this every other video game that they've
ever made in the last like seven years has been the worst game i've ever seen last like seven what
what every other video what am i talking about true i mean like the quality model warfare was
good it was all right you know black ops is kind of fun every other video game that they've ever
made in the last like seven years has been the worst game i've ever seen he's backtracking
look you have to backtrack because somebody gets really angry look if you don't don't you
know understand like politics and social interaction 101 if you say something that
you know is going to really piss off a ton of people backtrace it reiterate and say it's my
opinion but it's not there were some good things that came from that series backtrack backtrace it
and then put some passive tracing i don't know whatever backtrack that's the
origination of backtrack where is this crack part i don't care got it but you can be smoking
crack in your car and i do what they don't give a shit if you're saying an illegal meme though
you're gonna get pulled over they'll pull you over they'll check your phone they'll they'll make
they'll check what your browser history to see that they see what like the things you've been
saying in chat rooms and stuff you could have like a pound of crack in your trunk or literally you
could be smoking crack in front of the meme officer and he's not his jurisdiction i have no
idea what that even means but i guess we found it hey anyways let's finish up the stream ending
here sometimes i feel like another person said this stuff you know what i mean like
we've talked about we've talked about this before we've talked about this before
we've talked about this before we've talked about this before we've gone over this before
we've gone over this before we've gone over this before i've talked about this before we said this
before i've talked about this before but uh i say a lot of i talk a lot on these streams and it's
weird to hear a person that i don't even know who that is talking it's weird to hear like a point i
was trying to make like three years ago i'm like who the fuck is this person anyways hey
thanks for the 500 bits mf doom is to the rap game as germa is to the internet that's
you have a wide meme reach but it still feels like for some reason you're the internet's biggest
inside joke in a very good way something i've observed deserve more clout for the effort you
put into your content um i don't know i feel like it i don't even i know it's like really this is
cliche for me to say this and i know it's i'm gonna say it and people are gonna be like i'm
gonna hear your eyes roll into the back of your fucking head you're gonna hit the back of your
brain when i say this and i know it but i don't i really like don't care about being famous i just
don't i don't care i know i'll okay i rolled all the way back but i just don't i don't care
i don't want to be like famous i don't like what that like sucks that would that would actually
kind of like suck i don't want to be famous oh this again i know i know we're done we're done
i'm over he just cares about the money he's literally lying no i don't i don't like want to
look okay there's like known there is popular and then there's famous famous is
almost everybody knows who you are everybody like that we're talking like you have maybe
potentially been on the ellen degenerate show that's famous like you're famous i don't want
to get there i don't want to go on the ellen degenerate show i'll embarrass myself famous
kind of seems like i don't want to be famous and there's like popular which you're you're big and
they have a large super famous kind of popular presence in the space that you're in right you're
like you're popular okay cool but guess what like the guy that throws the football fucking 80 yards
is popular too in his high school and that's whatever and then that we that guy doesn't become
famous i mean maybe he will maybe he becomes payton manning and he throws and he can and he's great
and you know but that's popular but ellen is here ellen is a couch no no listen popular is like
you're you're famous like in like a small circle known is oh shit i did this wrong popular i flip
flip it around popular is before known known is before famous so popular is you're like cool and
people like you and you spend your space known is some people might know who you are but you're not
like famous nobody cares famous is famous i like to sit somewhere between um like
the six of us at the lunch table and we're all playing magic gathering and nobody fucking knows
who i am that's where we are known popular famous germa nine eight five no no no one comes after
popular because you can be popular but you might not be known that's what i'm saying like the guy
like that the guy that plays high school football and like he's popular and people like people know
him he would be known fuck long story short tldr uh i'll eat a fucking shoe tomorrow okay does it
make you happy i'm not eating another shoe probably everywhere again tomorrow what if
i did that tomorrow all right let me like try to wrap my brain around the thing i was just
trying to say i don't want to be fucking like ellen degenerous famous i don't i don't want to
be on that couch like hey ellen yeah well you know i just started streaming on twitch and yeah
oh yeah i'm here now i don't and i don't i don't want to do that
okay i've got five questions for you jeremy oh five questions what are they have you ever
eaten ass oh what have we talked about what no no i was supposed to get over this when i became
famous i suppose you're supposed to ask me though you're not supposed to ask that question i'm
supposed to get over this when i'm famous i'm not supposed to tell me that anymore just give me
give me talk to me talk about what my favorite car is and i'll like leave it behind you my
computer crashed no it didn't okay listen i thought my computer crashed uh what happened was go to
that uh octogen oops all penguins video go to 20 minutes and eight seconds pause the video
and then i want you to move your mouse around on uh i have an i have more than one monitor
and i move my mouse around and that mouse is on the screen and i thought that the i thought the
computer was crashed okay yeah it's not my mouse is here he's a nut i'm fine all right let's go
i'll see you tomorrow goodbye good night hey seleno just thanks for 300 bits jeremy thank you for
being so funny and good i love watching your content it makes me feel happy and less lonely
i'm getting a little cold my chest is i haven't laughed in a long time and your content is just
too good please take care of yourself and this goes to chat as well good night and thank you
this is a really nice fucking message thank you appreciate that thanks a lot hey mr bob a buoy
thanks for the 15 dollars jerma awesome stream as usual check your business email and you have a
chance i have not i've not opened the business i have not opened my business jerma email
in i'm gonna be completely up front with you and realistic probably four to five years but
thanks to 1500 bits thanks for the 15 dollars
open it on stream no why would i do that there could be like info in there
he's famous and he has an agent and then finally goo berry juice thanks to the 250 also here's
some memes you missed during the stream this is fucking disgusting
okay enough of that uh i'm actually uh yeah i missed that one sorry i'm missing now
uh also there's another one here this will be germa in 2021 duncan donuts reward system
i don't even like i don't even have like the mental energy to like go over this
but i thought that was shit coming out of his ass and i was about to say thanks a lot
i'm just never gonna be a pretty long shit i don't like an arrow pointed at it
and then again there's one more there's one more apparently this one says we've done we've all done
it all of us it's a twitter video the worst place ever this should be the source right here
find out i already know what this is and you know whatever don't fight you want to fight
you don't fuck come out don't you want to fight you don't fuck come out don't
they say i promise there's no porn you can ban me permanently again if there is also i was wondering
if you could give my uncle bugleberry some attention and at least give him let him appear
in the easy bake oven stream no no you don't understand the bugleberry story arc that's
coming at you not anytime soon but will hate it you're all gonna fucking hate this
but i'm gonna do everything possible to make this a reality hey just wanted to thank you for
the stream today's my 19th birthday that's it's burger time and you made it so much better take
care of yourself everyone thanks burger time thanks for the three bucks and that's it this is
a very long end of the stream but we were here for about two hours after i stopped playing
beautiful joe but that's all good sometimes they're gonna be four hours sometimes it'll be six
sometimes it'll be five sometimes it'll be six sometimes it'll be four sometimes it'll be four
and a half but yeah the the most that a stream will be going forward will be somewhere around
the five to six hour mark at least for the foreseeable future for the foreseeable
future i missed a donation here from dinosaurs rex i did 300 bits from dinosaurs rex and another
one i read that couple actually that were down here i don't know how i missed them uh dinosaurs
rex says i need at least five different usernames from the top of your head for my new usernames on
twitter dinosaurs rex one dinosaurs rex two dinosaurs rex three dinosaurs rex four pot
hot shovel hot no no no get over to the hot shovel shovel you dig it
um no sorry at a two at the end of that
raid rift tracks all right let's go i'll see you tomorrow uh we're going to i don't know
what we're gonna do tomorrow everybody hated the thing i played today everybody hated it
nobody liked this beautiful joe i was ever that was gonna be a pog moment for everybody but
everybody hates that game you know we're gonna do we'll do a pre-stream chat tomorrow we'll see
how you guys feel uh dinosaurs rex thanks for 300 bits i'm not asking for your help again
stop baiting i'm not baiting everyone hated beautiful joe and it makes me sad i was about
to just press the sound of the car alarm button on my keys it just was like i'm gonna press it i
don't know why that would have been fucking bad i would have to just disappear think of disappearing
we're gonna raid rift tracks how do you i f f t r a x you guys can get a little taste of what they
did and what they do they're fucking awesome all right uh here we go i mean it's it's a 24
hour channel so it's not like someone's not gonna pop on the stream be like what the fuck
raid it's just it's just channel that's running stuff i'll see you guys tomorrow good night take care