We're gonna go with- we're gonna go with like tiers. We're gonna go like building to building. See if you can eventually get me-
No, no, stand still, stand still.
I can't believe it.
Oh, you ruined my keyboard.
Hold on. Seriously, wait.
Oh my god, I spit that everywhere. I came- I-
Shit, hold on for- hold on a second.
Hold on a second.
Whoa.
Yeah.
No, no more stupid trucks. No.
It's funny because like, you couldn't even see them. You could just hear their-
Always happens.
That's like- that's how you know here comes like the star truck punch line.
Cause you just hear it.
Good joke.
Here we go, let's try this one more time.
Wait till I get on it.
You're gonna ruin everything. Okay, ready?
Do it. One. Do it.
Oh, baby.
You made it?
Why did it?
Yeah, I made it.
But I did this like pancake.
I laid out flat like I have- I was gonna use my parachute and I just pancaked on the ground.
That was awesome though.
But you didn't die.
No, I'm up here. I made it.
I made it, man.
Alright, now try to get-
Idea.
You have no idea what he said.
Wow, this looks so interesting. I love Liberty City.
It looks so cool. I'm glad this was only a quarter.
No.
She didn't move.
Everybody's fine.
Every single person.
She went back to re-
She went back to looking at the thing.
Your character's like bent over laughing too.
What was that?
I can't believe that.
After all that, after all the chaos and a car smashing over there, she's like, oh my god.
Okay, let me go back to looking through this.
What was in those binoculars that was more interesting than this car going berserk?
Tunnel.
Ooh, a tunnel.
Let's see how fast we can make it through the tunnel.
Whoa.
We made it.
We did it.
Whoa, is that like a destroyed bridge?
That's really cool.
Alright, you know what we just did?
Did you see that?
No.
What happened?
Okay, hold on.
On a more important note, remember Men in Black?
We just did the Men in Black, like go through the tunnel.
Go watch it.
You'll remember.
Was it Men in Black 2?
It was Men in Black 1, I believe.
It was when he was first showing in the car, and he's like, look son, this can do a bunch
of crazy stuff.
You better keep an eye out.
You better put your seatbelt on.
And Will Smith's like, oh yeah, yeah, yeah.
Yeah, we just did that scene.
We just recreated that scene.
Get in.
Hold on a second.
Hold on.
Get in.
You just did like a complete magic trick right there.
You were in this...
I can't.
I can't get in that thing unless...
Can I?
Hold on, stay there.
Don't move.
Don't...
That hit me...
This building is a magnet.
Dude, that hit me very, very hard in the face.
This tree...
This tree saved my life.
Remember guys, trees are stronger than steel going 500,000 miles per hour.
The Man of Steel?
Are you serious?
What are you?
This is like a Stephen King movie.
You're just like sitting in this alley waiting for me?
Like seriously, I just turn the corner, jump down, and it's like...
What's the car's name?
Carrie?
No, what the hell is the car's name?
I think it's Johnny.
Johnny.
You see, I'm just getting better and better at cheating.
This old ass lady again.
In like the same spot.
This is the same spot.
She really is in the same spot.
This has got to be the same building.
Yeah, this is the same old lady.
You could have another conversation with her if you'd like.
Okay.
We'll do it again.
We'll do part two conversation with old lady.
She said, hold on, let me move.
Alright, she's in a good spot.
So, I remember last time I saw you, you got like wrecked by a car.
Do you have any thoughts about that?
How did you not hit me?
How did you miss me?
Hey, I'm getting good at cheating.
I don't understand how you hit her and not me.
Happy?