Hey, what's going on, everybody? Jerma here with Recoil.
I just was spectating. I was trying to spectate a guy that knew what he was doing.
Looks like Artman's gonna go in. We're gonna see here.
Going for the double shotgun shot. Gets the shot. Gets two shots on him.
Right there we got Artman gonna be going in for the kill.
They're gonna see on the top left staircase. Gets the pistol out.
Is he gonna get in on time?
He's dancing. I'm not going with the night kills.
Is he gonna get in?
This is so unexpected.
So I guess now is a good time to do a player profile on Chizzy Boy.
I guess now it's time to do a player profile on Clidio.
Clidio is one of those players you just love to watch, guys.
He has a lot of things in his arsenal.
He's one of the best AK-74 players in the world.
And he also plays the piano, so a good little bit of information on the player that I like to see it.
Now I'm gonna do a player profile on V2FXXX.
He is one of the best SMG players in the world.
As you can probably imagine, having an SMG is a lot better for movement and to be able to get the speed that you need.
Now we're gonna do a player profile on Cat.
Now we're gonna do a player profile on Chizzy Boy.
Chizzy Boy is another one of those characters you love to see.
Now we're gonna do a player profile on Zeyosio.
Just like that, we get a two-piece.
Just like...
Oh, yeah. Stop him. Stop him.
Me and my teammates.
Me and my teammates recoiling all over the place.
Look at that.
I'll teach you how to recoil, guys.
What you want to do first, you want to turn a corner with a fucking grenade in your hand.
And you just want to throw it into their spawn.
I don't even know if that's their spawn.
I got a couple hits.
Tango down.
Charlie down.
And...
Guy in the window.
Down.
I gotta get...
I gotta string something.
What the hell is that guy?
What the hell?
This guy got like face paint on?
I want to like see his broken ass neck.
Yeah, he's got like face paint on.
This guy looks like a WWF wrestler.
I want to be like a WCWNWO wrestler.
There it is.
Killing machine.
Oh!
That's two!
That...
Fucking WCW guy killed me.
The fuck happened to you?
I definitely want to be a WCW guy.
We got this WCW guy.
This guy is just kind of crazy looking.
He's kind of creepy.
And then we got tattoo guy.
Why is tattoo guy the guy with the face paint?
And then this should be tattoo guy.
Something I've noticed in every video game that has this gun.
The Draugnov always sucks.
Has there ever been a game made where the Draugnov like wasn't a fucking piece of shit?
Has that ever happened?
I just got three kills in a row.
So let's just pretend like I didn't say that.
Ooh.
Somebody's...
Somebody learned how to play.
It be a part of war.
I'm going to teach you guys how to make pancakes.
All right?
It's going to be pretty easy.
There's the first ingredient.
That's two eggs.
Around this corner we got some butter.
And then of course you cannot forget.
Fucking God.
This is the secret recipe for pancakes.
Two eggs.
Then you got to also put in the butter.
But I can't find the butter.
The butter ran down here.
There's the butter.
I missed the bowl with the butter.
Fucking God damn it.
Hey, what's going on everybody?
Jerma here.
Welcome to Cooking with Jerma.
This is a new series I'm doing.
Where I show you how to make a very healthy, very nice breakfast.
And what you want is you want a bowl.
Bowl large enough to put a bunch of stuff in obviously.
Because we're going to give you my secret recipe for pancakes.
So what you want to do is of course you want to put in, you know, what we got here.
Two eggs.
A little bit of butter.
The butter ran away.
Hold on.
The butter fell on the floor.
I got to pick up the butter.
There's the butter.
Butter's in the bowl now.
Then of course you got to add the flour.
Flour is shooting at me.
Flour's shooting at me.
It's okay.
Flour killed me.
Welcome to Cooking with Jerma guys.
In this episode I'm going to teach you how to make pancakes.
Those of you that think you know how to make pancakes.
You got it all wrong.
You see, first you got to get a bowl.
Then once you get that bowl you throw in two eggs.
Once the eggs are in there you put in the flour.
Once the flour's in there you roll your sleeves up.
Get your hands a little bit dirty.
And you add a little bit more butter.
Fucking god damn it.
Do you understand how hard you're trying to make one of the worst jokes I have ever heard?
I'm getting behind them.
I'm getting in their spawn.
And it's going to be a big fucking surprise when I get in there.
Speaking of big surprise.
What is this?
What is this fucking Gumby?
What is that like fucking?
Stretch Armstrong in like a fucking taffy factory.
And we're coming out of the wire here guys.
This is the final moment in the 2016 Recoil Tournament.
Welcome. I'm very glad to do it with you.
We're very glad to cast you.
Very glad to do it.