Right on time. That's right. You guys bet on this one? Okay. So, uh, the reason I tried to be very,
very on time today, because I- I don't know, I thought people were betting on this. So I freaked
out like two, three minutes ago. I was brushing my teeth. I'm just like, oh fuck, what are they
betting on this? And I like, oh shit, and I like sprinted. I got in here as fast as I could. I
turned it on. Because I was like, what if people have- people have channel points on this? I don't
know. I guess not. You know, it's like funny. When I think that people are betting fake currency on
something and like gambling, I'm incredibly interested and I'm going to be right on time.
It's interesting. You have a good dirty teeth. Uh, I like to brush my teeth for every stream.
I have a nice like clean, fresh mouth. I hate the fact of having a dirty mouth. When I'm sitting
down talking, I hate that feeling. I can feel all individual, every tooth. It's just like slime on
it. And I can, like, my breath is heavy and dense. Blah. I hate it. Especially when you're talking,
you can like, you can feel that heavy air. Blah. Get rid of it. I hate it. Brush your teeth on
stream. I just did. All right, give me a sec. Beer back. Gonna tweet this. Did I get that right?
Okay. I don't know why, but for some reason, I thought I spelled my Twitch channel wrong.
Where are my headphones? Fuck. Hold on. I'll be right back. All right, I got it. So today,
we are going to play, uh, probably the remainder of what we're going to do in Spore.
Can I hear anything? Let me see. Hold on. I can't hear anything. There we go. All right,
and now I can hear you. You're not even talking. Oh, now I can hear you. Uh, yeah, we're gonna play
Spore. What is this title, bro? Uh, that's Jeremiah 420. It's, I don't know. We were in
pre-stream and somebody thought it was a good idea. It makes sense. I guess it's perfect for today.
You're muted? Do a tooth cam. No, I'm not putting a cam. Look, I am not putting my teeth in the
camera. I'm not putting my, like, nose in the camera. I'm not gonna, like, put my feet in the
camera. I'm not gonna, like, show you my elbows. No, I'm not, I'm gonna, I'm a fucking statue in
this scene. I'm not doing, I don't want, I'm not doing any of that. I'm not gonna, like, oh, dude,
open your mouth and show us, like, your, all of your teeth. Go like this and pull the teeth, like,
pull your cheeks out and go, ah. It's gonna be wicked funny. Just do it. I'm not doing that.
Anytime somebody tells you something, something, something, dash, it'll be wicked funny. I don't
know if I trust that person. I don't trust that. I was just gonna say, it'll be wicked funny.
Why do you want me to do that so bad? You think, you think that you're kind of bouncing off of me.
I think that I'll think what you just said is funny because it's, it's a pretty odd request.
So therefore, it might be funny. I might think it's funny, but you don't think it's funny.
I think I get you. I understand you. Play Spore. It'll be wicked funny.
Play the game. It'll be wicked funny. Shit. He has wooden teeth. That's why. Federal Reserve
bailed you out. No, they didn't. No more. What are you talking about? All right, let's go.
Dude, you should totally like eat a bunch of grapes and like food with your hands and like
eat a bunch of apples with your hands and get like bacon and hands and bacon greased all over
your mouth and stuff. It'll be wicked funny. I gotta watch out now. I gotta watch out for,
it'll be wicked funny people. I have to watch out for that now. Here we go. Camera's not on, right?
Good. Hey, it's like showing your desktop accidentally. Like the I'm naked. The webcam
just turned on accidentally of like being on a computer. It kind of is, isn't it? Yes, it is.
All right, here we are on the planet Zircon. Like I'm so glad this doesn't pop up very often.
I kind of care about this. Like it's just, that's so default wallpaper Andy. We went over this
yesterday. Oh, by the way, you notice how like I've dragged everything off. It's just a
background. Every time I know I'm going to capture my desktop, it's like, well, click drag over to
the other monitor. You don't want you to see any of that shit. Oh guys, I have just like a clean
desktop. I don't have anything. I don't even use a computer. It's just desktop wallpaper. I don't
have anything on my desktop. I just have, I don't even use computers. You do the same fucking thing.
You do the same thing. You did the same exact thing. If you know someone's coming over
and they, oh, hey, dude, by the way, can I use your computer?
Oh, okay. Hold on. Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait.
Yeah, no, no, you can't, but why, why couldn't you? Hey, dude, I'm going to be like in town for a
little while. I'm not going to have access to my computer. Can I use yours? Oh my fucking God. It's
It's like panic and I for no reason to like this. I I don't like there's nothing on this computer
That's like bad. It's just like I don't know it feels weird feels like somebody's like sitting in your skin
Doesn't it feels like somebody's like sitting in your body like in like is your bones like controlling your hands and stuff
It feels weird. I kind of feel the same way of like if you if somebody was like, oh, hey
Hey here take the keys to my house and just go in and do whatever the fuck you want
I go in the fridge go like just go into the pantry sleep in the bed, too
Like here's the keys to my house. I'm gonna be gone for a week
It feels the same way even though the second bad in my house or anything quick take everything out of the fridge
But I don't know. It's a guy. It's just weird. It's a Zorn. It's Zorn. No
It's not Zorn related. Okay. Here we go. We're at the tribe of those who that missed yesterday's stream
Here are the germa bites. I thought he's lit on fire
Are they already designed very uh, I don't know why I made them that like green teal color
All right, gather fruit meat or fish. We're gonna go over here
What do I want to do?
Because let's get fruit everybody go over here get some fruit team fortress to gather food you dummy
Oh, I just sent them over there. Oh, here's the our friends that we made that I apparently didn't get smarter
This is kind of sad. Don't you think like rank and the rat like we evolved that they didn't that's kind of that's kind of sad
So they're just dumb and we're smart. I got food click on your hut and add a baby
These guys are freaking me out add a baby is ten food. All right, so should we get should we eat people?
What do you guys think? Should we eat people? I think it's very scary looking. All right, let's get another baby
Should we eat people? Click on the hat icon to open the tribe member panel so I could just I you know
What here's the thing about spore? I think a lot of you can relate to this most of you I think can relate to this
I got to this part of spore and said this game's stupid and stop playing you got everyone did that
I think right everybody does the cell stage makes the creatures and has the fun putting like the
Extending the nose and making the head big and make it a big fat belly and and walking on and dancing
And then when you get to this part, you just uninstall the game because it's like I'm done
This was stupid this stage like in forward. So this is all brand new to me. I never played this stuff ever
I really didn't I did I didn't even care. I just like all I was dude
I'm done like extending the funny animals nose. I'm done. Let's go face is the worst one. Hmm
Well, we'll see. All right, click on the hat icon to open the tribe member panel roll over your tribe member
Then click the edit outfit. I already did this. Yeah, I didn't already do this. Yeah
I did this already to uninstall it now. Yeah, we're good to go
Instruments wouldn't wait. Okay, I need to collect wood. Is that three to six? Oh, I can have up to six people here
All right, did I send somebody over here? It's like an envoy. All right
I'm gonna send somebody over as an envoy over here. Wait, I don't want to attack we give them food
All right, I'm gonna bring them plates of food who these people a rival tribe of Trey ten have formed on your planet
The tribal chieftain leads your tribe your tribe can go into combat without his chief
Oh, it can go into combat without the chief
But the chief is necessary for any social encounters with other tribes the chieftain also invokes any of your tribes
Consequence abilities to use a consequence ability first select your chieftain and they click on the ability you'd like to use
Well, I want to like make friends with these guys
Need at least 15 food to feed an animal. I was just you have a dog bone
Why can't I be friends with these guys? I mean I get 15 food
I want to make friends with this tribe gone go back to what you're doing. What do they eat 15 food?
That's not a tribe. These are animals. What baby burger? Well, I mean that we're doing over here
You better not feed them. If you feed them, I'm gonna be so pissed. Stop that kill kick his ass and tell him
Don't kill him though. Just get a beat him up. So he's to run away and tell his friends eat him
All right. Listen, listen up burgers. I got something for you. What do you think about this? It's food. You like it
I'm gonna try even try you like food East master flying fish. What the hell's that mean? He's a vegetarian
I just gave him fruits. Oh, there he goes
He liked it. You have too many domesticated animals at this time. What is happening? What are we doing?
What am I doing to him? Am I stealing this guy? Wait, I'm
Not
Jim care of man on the moon Annie Kaufman. Oh, they're waving. Okay, at least they're friends
I have like a group of animal friends. You try to domesticate him, but you have too many
So wait, so I still have a domesticated bronc bring gifts to the brown village where they're pissed off
I haven't even had I need to hold on. They might make some more babies
Bring gifts to the
Okay, wait, not these guys. Wait, it is these guys. Well, we killed I killed somebody here. What are they doing?
All right, do they want what if I gave him fruits? All right, let's go here
Are they holding kill their entire tribe? Well, they're very close. I don't want to wait to say they bring in food, too
Oh, this is gonna be awkward
This is this is when you order like uber eats from three different places because you want like a sampling of three different places
That day like three uber each drivers show up at the same time. I promise it's not a prank
I just wanted to read you I wanted to sample three different foods. Have we friends who does that? I don't I'm making it up
I
Don't do that. I do not order from three different places to have a sampling of three different foods
I think 85% of every uber eats order I've ever done was McDonald's and I'm
90% sure that that's accurate. That's disgusting. Why is that disgusting? That's way too specific. He does that I
Don't fucking do that
Okay
I like the brown village by playing music for them
Well ally tries to bring your tribe gifts or I need to make um, I need to make a musical instrument house
It's only 25 food. All right collect food back to getting food all of you rich streamer each meets McDonald's
I love McDonald's. I love that place. I
Really do I love McDonald's?
How many times I have to say that before people think it's true
Like the eggs you dipshit what eggs eggs
The game nobody talking about eggs. I take you take their eggs
Next to your domesticated animals. What they're laying eggs in here
Okay. All right. Let me make a musical instrument place and press neighboring tries with these horns
Mmm over here. This will be the music hut egg time. I do like McDonald's a lot
It's like one of my favorite places to eat
It really is
Is that a pizza? He's got a he's got like an egg pizza. What are you doing with that? Wait, you just have it
Where's it going with it? Oh shit. Nice. Okay. I need fuck a 44 food. What else can I do now?
One is better than McDonald's
Right, but I mean, I don't care though. There are a lot of places better than McDonald's, but that doesn't
Take away from the fact that I eat there all the time. I mean should I make an instrument?
Why not? I can't but why not weapons? Ooh, that's the chief. Oh, okay
Alright, so I got a horn. All right, you get a horn too. I'd much rather eat a Burger King Whopper than a stinky Big Mac
Yuck. That's all right. Grab a horn. We're gonna go impress the village. I need a I need the chief
Don't I? Chief come with me wooden horns. You can only use that ability during performance. All right, let's go
Who actually eats in at McDonald's? Oh, I didn't say I didn't say I was eating in the restaurant
I mean you can what's wrong with that? All right, here we go. It's time to play some music. Here we go
Oh, they love it. You like this
They love that. We are now friends
Alright, so now we're friends
We need to be allies with them though. I would keep doing it. Maybe she could move people with horns
Oh, they want the horns. Okay. I see they want horns again. I want it again
Not enough. Oh, I got it. Alright, the new tribe is your ally. They love it
I like McDonald's. I like Burger King. I like Wendy's but if I have a choice in the matter, it's McDonald's
I don't know. I just like their I like this. I know exactly what to order there
I go to Burger King. I don't know what to order
And I go I don't fucking know and I put my glasses on and lean into the menu and I go which one is good here
Wendy's I usually get a junior bacon cheeseburger problem with that though. I got a problem with that. It's always cold
I've never ever experienced a hot junior bacon cheeseburger from Wendy's. It is always cold every single time
It's very good. It tastes very good, but it's cold every
Single time i've ever eaten it in 20 fucking years of going there across states across the entire nation
Across all of the united states of america
It's like that every time and I don't know why but it's very it tastes very good. I guess i'm new. Oh, wait
What did that say?
Your mouth is too warm
Does that look like an extremely hot mouth? That's what it is now. I've had
Burgers from mcdonald's that were cold. I've had big macs that were just lukewarm in the middle
But not every time your tribe grows in prestige
You have a larger hut to show for it and your tribe can now sustain up to nine tribe members
All right, cool. Let's get some more babies babies
More babies and let's get some food big mac or quarter pounder. I prefer a big mac
Uh, okay. I think i'm good, right? Where is everybody? All right, everybody get over here
We get some we chop down some trees
We need more food if garbage tastes
I don't like but does it really matter though?
I really go over this
All fast food is gross
It just is
Does it really matter if you like burger king or mcdonald's more like they're both gross in their own ways
But it's delicious and yummy and quick and usually pretty affordable and it's really easy. It doesn't really matter
But honestly the affordable part i'm not so sure of anymore
I've been to mcdonald's a lot of times and the order like if you got like two there's like two or three people in the car
It's like okay, we're gonna get this we're gonna get that okay, and okay, that'll be like 28 dollars drive around
Please it's like wait. What how much should we order?
We order how much do we order? That's a lot of food. No, it's not was it
You can go like down the street to a place. It's not like a mcdonald's and it's like 20 bucks to eat
Like I've really got two three people in a car. It's like really what's going on here?
Like 35 dollars for us to order like a bunch of a couple of meals
It's not four fucking dollars like for like 15 items
I'm put up saying like there are other restaurants that are not mcdonald's that are better than mcdonald's where you can get food for cheaper
exist
Why is everybody holding eggs return the eggs?
Why put the eggs in here?
And then why would you get mcdonald's because it takes 10 seconds to get your food
All right, everybody I need to expand
Can I just do we get weapons?
What's that raiders spotted another tribe is attacking?
What oh shit, oh shit back back back back back back spears spears spears get him get him get him
Those are horns. Those are horns. Those are horns
Everybody get a weapon
Everybody get a weapon. All right now kill
Kill these guys have so much health
Oh, thank you for the raid
I appreciate you guys coming from the other stream. Hey, welcome. Thanks for the raid
Now kill them
Bronc is helping. He really is. Yeah
All right, we did it success
I upgrade this
What happened to the cow?
The cow is dead raiders have been spotted. They played to steal your food. What what are you talking about?
It's one guy
Are you sure this is not just a guy that was walking around? Oh my goodness
That person get away
All right. All right. All right. We gotta get back to this
I gotta I gotta upgrade
Bring gifts to this village. They just attacked that guy some mcdonald's what most psychopathic tribe in history
All right. Hold on
Uh, let me go to the editor here
all right maracas and
Fishing spears equip tribe members with fishing spears to maximize their fishing bounty
Yeah, put that over here
and then maracas
Uh right here. I got some new. Um
Tribe stuff, right?
I did here we go
Oh, all right. I'm getting all right. All right. All right. I'm gonna get a bunch more food
And what do I have for a mask now this?
This one social. Oh get that social shit out of here
Don't have enough fuck. Um 25 for gathering
Yeah, I am going to war
It's not immediately
They sell the rings in the mustache
All right. This is one more somewhere. Oh, let's see get rid of this
All right. Now we're gonna put the combat mask on
And we're gonna go destroy that village
All right. Perfect. Hey jerma, it's me your best friend mcdonald's is gonna be very happy with the ad
Me your best friend. Hi. Thanks best friend. Okay now I got some combat prowess
I have to I don't want to lose everybody though. Let me domesticate an animal
There's already somebody there. These guys already like us a lot. I want them to be friends with us
All right, you come here
Mesticated a member of the burger species good. Well, I need you. I can I send them on missions for you
I have a special mission for you
I'm gonna send you on a great exploration to pick up a rock
And throw it as hard as you can over at somebody's head at the other village
And then what I want you to do is I want you to hide behind a bush
And when they come out looking to see where the rock came from you point
over there at the other village
and say
Rock and ready. It was a fight and then I will come in with food for both
And explain how I can't believe that this conflict is continuing
All right
Seriously, you want to come in you want to fuck around?
Just get him get him get him get him focus. This is what I do in rts is this why I lose every single game
Um, I just focus every single unit on one person at a time
Like this, I don't like press a attack move and then click over here. Nope. We kill one person at a time instantly
We just firing squad one person at a time
Even if I have like a hundred units, I just like go like this
You deserve this i'm sorry, but it's true
You deserve this kill the chief he's surrounded by babies
Did he just scream?
You see us going he's dead now just wipe out the I can't even say that out loud
Kill them
I can't say it out loud
Defeat the enemy babies. There you go. Now. It's family friendly
All right, take it out
Claim this village
It is ours now
What are these things?
Something's coming to steal my food
shit
Stop them. Stop them. Stop them. Come on grunk
Oh, no, my pet burger is about to be killed
Come back. Come back. Come back. Come back. Everybody come back
Quick quick quick. It's all right. They don't get shit right now. That's fine. We that was a good raid
Oh god, damn it. How do I attack move?
Brown village is offering your tribe a gift with the basket to accept it. Um,
Can brown tribe come and help?
Come on. Come on. Help me. Thank god fishermen
Help us
What are they doing?
Yes, thank god
Reinforcements i'm so glad
I'm so glad you tp'd here
with two people
Red blue green yellow. They're all attacking me at the same time and you're gonna tp here with two footmen
Thanks, you're next by the way, just want to make that clear. You're next. You're going to die. It's over. I'm exiting the game
All right, I want the gift take it
What is it press three three one? It was a bunch of food. Thanks guys
Press three fat fuck. What i'm pressing three. All right, we're safe back to what we were doing
Press three and oh
three
Don't let them don't let them surrender
They had that opportunity like fucking three days ago
Don't let him surrender
Three what just happened wild animals are coming to steal your food. Why just kill this village already?
I'm sending one person back you steven. What's his name spearman?
All right. Come on. Come on spearman. Is that the wild animal?
Wait, that's me. That's one of my guys
What isn't that one of my people? That's a traitor
What
You have destroyed the pink village your tribe has carved a second totem piece to remember this momentous occasion
It spoils the battle and now tools and outfits
Find them in your tribal planner. What are you doing here?
We're gonna eat them
Okay
Well, I took over the village. Let's go
I need some can I just take anything? Can I steal anything else?
Everybody go back an epic gecko
That thing's awesome. It's like the geico gecko. It's like gecks. What?
Kill it kill it kill it kill it kill it kill it absolutely kill this thing
And then take all of his food
God, this is fucking crazy
mate
Funny thing happened
When it's one time what the tagline should have been
Me my crazy old me said it should be 15 saved you 50 percent more. Have you seen that commercial?
Can they can they stop fucking doing that already?
Stop doing that
Stop doing that commercial
They keep doing that commercial. They keep doing like the gecko is a real person
You guys pick up on that yet?
They're doing like the geico gecko is a real guy behind the scenes. He's a real person. It's not like a lizard
actor
Why are you doing that?
They like have like people chattering in the background like pretending there's like a set and stuff and he's like, oh, yeah
Oh, I can't keep i keep laughing at you mate. You're so funny over there
Why are they making him a real person?
It's weird and that's the whole commercial. There's no commercial
He just like acts like kind of like ah candidly behind the scenes, huh? They've done like three or four of those
I don't get it
But it's not like behind the scenes. This is the actor talking behind the scenes
It's the geico gecko is in front of the camera and we're on set and the gecko is real
I don't get it flying fish. What the gecko is real. I'm already sit that person down
They've got a lot to talk about
We've got a lot to tell you I have I just want to let we got to go over a lot of mascots
All right equip members with gathering canes to maximize fruit
Yeah, oh, I want that healing rods and didgeridoos geckos real. It's just
Wait, I have maracas, right? Those are horns
Healing rods throwing. Okay. I need maracas. Oh, they destroyed it, right? Can I repair it?
Well, can we repair that? No
Cannot repair it maracas and didgeridoos
Yeah, we need to inform jerma that he has abilities
He can use the shiny blue buttons that he refuses to press
Everyone spam this press the buttons for free food and other things, please the shiny blue buttons. Okay now gathering canes flying fish
Free food blue buttons press the blue button. I didn't get any free food
Beast master, I didn't get anything mandalorian. I killed that I guess
Kill that thing
We need its food kill. It's got like a gold bar on its back
Everybody kill that
Kill it
Wait, why are we all fucked up? What's wrong with us? It's your friend. No, it's not
Is it why we all confused?
It is my friend
Um, oh is that what that button does because he gives you like a random animal friend
I've never pressed that guys. I've never played this part. I don't even know what this button does. They didn't tell me what it does
It's just a button down. There's a button down here that says beast master
I have no idea what it is
St
What are we doing?
What does this do?
I mean that was really cool. But what did it do?
All right, let's get gathering canes. Let's get some more food. We need to go out to the trees and get some uh,
more food
Hey, what are you doing?
I just like spanked him
Why?
What are you doing?
Get back here. Get back here. You idiot
You mess with my friends. This is my house
Get out of here. Get away from me
You're not gonna die. Is he?
Somebody help him
Somebody help him. Somebody help him. Somebody help him
Stop, stop, stop, stop, stop, stop. Somebody help him
Somebody help him stop like skiing around
Okay now take eat him
We gathering we are okay speaking of saving the game. I really should do that. Shouldn't I it's been a while
Aggressive aggressive tribes try to exterminate the competition. They ruthlessly attack and hoard all the resources for themselves
That's not what happened though. People are attacking me
Are we watching the same game? Are we playing the same game?
I was sitting there trying to dance and do the horns and dance for the other tribe and I got attacked three times
So I retaliated what I can't retaliate nice ron
Fuck
Is only defending. Yeah, i'm just defending
Is everybody has those little sticks, right? Make sure everybody has one of those. Yeah, they do
self-defense massacre
um
I mean
What do you want? What do you want to say?
I I need to I want to let's go to brown. How's brown doing? Okay, they're doing. All right. Yeah
All right. There are there's
This group over here have they attacked me before I think they have I don't think green has though
Yeah, they had these guys attack all the time. Well, maybe okay. I'm gonna go over there with some instruments
Maybe I can be friends with them. They're dicks. Okay round village is offering your tribe a gift. Ooh, okay
Thanks guys somebody repair. Okay, they can repair it. Yeah repair this guys the village is under
There's a lot of stress here on this village
Here they come. I gotta give them a gift too. They just keep giving me presents. What is it? Is it food?
Thank you
What is in there?
Oh shit 10 food. Yeah. All right. I'm gonna give them a gift
I'm gonna bring them a gift of what should I bring them?
about um
The gift of dance. How about that the gift of death?
No
The gift of dance raiders are spotted another tribe is attacking or are they fears?
Who is it? It's all right. It's green
I'm gonna wipe out greening by the way greens getting wiped out after this i'm sick of this shit
Get the spear stop preparing it to get a spear
Okay attack. It's freaking me out that green is purple
Don't you think that's weird?
Green is purple
Are they green? I guess they are kind of green
Wait, am I even blue? I'm red. Oh
Kill the chief. Okay. What about I do I have healing rods?
All right. Here's what we're gonna do
I'm not going into attack yet. I'm gonna make some babies
Two of you guys are getting healing rods
There's three mcdonald's one
Okay, two healing rods. You're holding a broom. All right, you go good come over here
Group up together you guys one of you guys is holding a gathering stick. So, um, please get a spear
Okay
Is everything repaired?
It is all right
so
Going over to green
And i'm gonna kill green. Let's move
They're all babies. They're fine
They got nothing either but we're gonna conquer this whole place
Kill the chief go right for the chief right for the throat get in there attack. Where are my healers?
heal
Heal
I can't even click on anybody
They're just babies kill them. I mean defeat defeat them
You know what I mean, you know what I mean
All right, we're gonna take this village
Green is now mine
Take it out
We're okay, right?
Yeah, it's going down
Make sure everything's good back here. Oh a good one was one guy back here. Good. Perfect
Just pre-celebrate for us
These guys could just come in right blue could come in right now and ruin this whole thing
Everybody doing good on health
Chief is almost dead
We need to focus on okay, you just heal the chief. That's it
Don't do anything else but heal the chief
Just pocket medic the chief
What is he doing with his neck?
I got two more things to put on was that one more village to conquer
You destroyed the green village a third totem piece adorns your tribal totem the tools enough
It's taken from the fallen tribe are now available in your planner
Befriend blue
Oh cool
Your hut has upgraded again and you can now grow your tribe to its maximum potential of 12 tribe members
All right
All that exists is lavender and cyan
Interesting, okay
Well, we need to get some more food. So might as well get some from here
How many more babies let's get uh more babies?
another baby, please
Remember your tribe is the fire nation
Who's attacking me?
We'll probably get this food back
Oh, it's they're right here
Just cut them off
Put the pizzas down just cut them off right here
Get out of the way get these like fucking balls out of the way
Cut them off. We're already here
What the fuck is that?
Are you guys still coming over here? Just kill them?
It's uber eats
Uber eats delivering mcdonalds
Uber eats they're gonna I would laugh so hard if they just dropped like a bomb right here
Um, okay, leave us alone, please
Okay, i'm gonna use
I'm not gonna kill that tribe
I'm not gonna kill them
We're gonna use diplomacy
Because this is a this is their last chance to surrender i'm gonna go over there with maracas
All right, we're gonna send an envoy
Bring a variety of instruments. Yeah, i'm gonna bring we have 12. So i'm gonna do four eight
I'm gonna do four maracas four didgeridoos
Just don't attack me. Just please leave me the fuck alone. All right, we're gonna do
didgeridoos
and then
Four maracas and then horns who doesn't have an instrument
Who doesn't have an instrument right now, I feel like this is like a fourth grade class who doesn't have one of their instruments
Who doesn't have an instrument?
Kids just picking their noses over here
I want to be have a maraca. Okay. Um, well you're supposed to have him horn
No, I want a maraca
Okay, fine. Fine. You can have a maraca. Fine. All right, that'd be that lead. That's three horns five maracas and I want to play maraca, too
Okay, that's that's six maracas two horns
And okay one of the horns is broken. He just broke he dropped it down the fucking stairs
Okay, that's one i'll just give it just give me the horn
Just give me give me the horn. Give me the horn. I'll be the horn. We can have seven maracas and four. Uh, I don't know four
um
What is the other instrument a didgeridoo?
Okay, here we go. Are you all ready?
Okay on my lead and three
Holy shit
kids
Everybody call their parents everybody call their parents. We're gonna make a lot of money
make sure one of them brings a fucking cell phone and
candidly films this
Tomorrow and uploads it to fucking youtube. We're gonna make a lot of money
All right, let's go
I'm gonna bring a gift
Brown village is offering your tribe a gift, but they they just bring me that was an uber eats doorbell
God damn it
Who's fighting? Hey
What happened? Why did you do that? All right, i'm going in to what is going on with the instruments. Fuck it
We're gonna take this gift you raiders spotted. Oh my fucking god. Is it purple?
Can you guys stay here?
But we just were ready to do our music. Okay. What if I just can I meet them at the door and do music?
Stop where you are. Stop. Stop. Stop. Stop. Stop. Stop. Stop. Stop. Stop. Stop
Look, I brought a gift
Take it
Stop the assault
It works. Holy shit. Really diplomacy works
maracas is too
Shit, hold on. Hold on diplomacy works
Good thing they're hidden. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah fucking diplomacy. You think this is fucking diplomacy?
We're just we're beating the fuck out of one of your guys back there. We're distracting
You're gonna take you out one by one behind the fucking back
They can't see shit
That's like this is one of the main guys back here. Hey, hey, let's do it again. Come here, man
You want to like hang out like place of instruments and shit?
Bronc rip his fucking head off
I missed my cue. I missed my cue again. I'm watching on the i'm literally watching the fight over there. I'm missing my cue
Seven that's okay. All right. It was just
I can't I have to pay attention to what's going on over here
No, no, no stay distracted come here. All right, we did it. It's a new day
Friends. No, they don't want to be friends. Come on
That was a 9.0
I let the rat die. I did
I killed the rat. Oh
I can't I
Stupid fucking horns, man. It's two different horns
Just get stay here. I'm just gonna kill them if I fuck this up again
I'm gonna kill them all
It's my last opportunity to do this and before I kill them my frustrations are i'm just gonna be taken out on the other tribe
Not enough. I need more of uh
I need more of something. Yeah, it's not enough
People don't have instruments
Well, I guess I I couldn't fucking tell
Wild animals are coming. Well, hold on
What else put the horns on?
I need more horns
Who else doesn't have an instrument they do? Okay
All right, come on back. Where are the wild animals?
Apparently wild animals coming to steal from me
Is this a wild animal?
Wait, oh, they're bringing me they're bringing me presents
It was another one of me. Why is there like this tribe that just doesn't i'm so confused
Okay, we'll take the gift. We accept it first
What do you think about this?
What do you want to hear give us a request? Yeah, of course. These guys want maracas not horns
Oh, come on
All maracas in a row
10 10 10 10 we are now friends with the
lavender clan
I love that
Take these flowers. Look at me
Only three of them exist
Okay, your totem is nearly complete their tools and outfits are now yours. There's only one more. Um
All right
Bye
Oh, wow, that was a big jump. All right, I have to so
You've unlocked the torch tool
Zion village is the only one I have to make friends the scion
If I want to not be aggressive
All right. We're gonna send an envoy. They all still have their instruments. So let's go
All right. We all still have our instruments. We're gonna take the band over to cyan
You understand who doesn't have an instrument?
Okay, who doesn't have one?
A lot of you don't did you put them away?
All right, we're going half
horns
half maracas
And i'm gonna bring a present too chief get some food that's spears
No, those horns and maracas
Do all three
They're discussing science
Okay, get a gift. How do I get a gift? Your tribe is doomed. They are not
Let's go here. We have a gift. This is for the chief
I know we've had our problems. We've had our differences
We've killed way more people than you
You've lost way more people than we have we've had our differences
In fact, i'm not sure one person has died on our tribe, but I know a lot from yours have
Take the deal
Take the deal. I can't tell if he's trying to sneak or if he's about to wipe out this whole village
What is that?
All right. Let's try it. We have
maracas and wooden horns only
And if they like didgeridoos, then i'm sorry. We don't have those good maraca good
again, yes
Yes, haha
We did it
We've done it. Does that bring us up?
It does not it does not
It will maybe eventually though. Hold on this guy's freaking me out
Don't have that
That was just bad rng. We'll get it bad rng. I'll get it end their lives
No, i'm trying to be in the middle there. I don't want to be aggressive into the next stage
Come on one more. I'll do it. Give me one more that we have
Shitty rng. Come on
Just get the other instrument. It's just too long
He's getting closer
Should we just go kill that thing? Maybe together we should just go wipe that thing out
All right, so far so good. Just give me one more
I just need one of the two one of the two and it's done
What the fuck dude?
All right. Well, one of you just don't get it. Just
Go get a didgeridoo. Whatever what's going on?
But that's one of ours though
He's just been sitting here eating
Look
Hey
Hey, don't be afraid
Don't be afraid. I we were you before we we know what it's like to be you
To be not because that's like an animal right that you are you are us. Okay, whatever me didgeridoo. Okay, bring him back
These guys they keep just bringing food
We're not so different you and I
Hold on the band's coming back up. Everyone relax
Okay
Let's go
Mm-hmm. Mm-hmm
If it's all maracas and wrong i'll be so mad
It's gonna be all maracas. Okay, this is stupid
This guy's freaking me out though
I think that that's the tribal stage, right?
Does that bring us up into the middle and we should definitely go get the big guy
You made the cyan village your allies your totem is complete
You can advance to the civilization stage now
Your tribe reigns supreme when you're ready to get civilized click the advance button
Click here to found your first city. You'll be sent to the creators to design your city hall and vehicles
Kill the pickle. I'm just curious about him. Hold on
Hello, we can't dance for him
Oh time to go time to go get away time to go time to go let them deal with it let them deal with it
Run I just like inadvertently ruined everything. He's gonna come attack this city
Lavender village is offering you a gift. I think i'm ready. Yeah, but there's nothing I can really do here
Did I get into the middle?
I did
industrious
Industrious tribe sees the moment attacking or forming alliances when necessary. They make great allies, but watch out
Uh, let's go
Your tribal tactics have established you earliest cultural trait. This trait sets the course for your nation's specialty and the technological research
As your nation grows your citizens will develop unique tools that will assist your civilization on the path the global domination use them wisely
Very cool. I spent a lot of time down here. I'm not friendly at all, though. Let's go
I'm for civilization
The tribe now dominates this continent ready to advance from simple village life to civilized city living ahead of the rest
I guess so. So what am I making here? Name your city hall?
I mean we're civilized doesn't mean we know very much like we're still kind of like dumb, right?
No, i've never gone this far. I don't think
Have I?
I don't think i've gone this far
No one has
Okay, this is the city hall
New gronk
new grank
gronk grank city
City
new gronk city new gronk
New wasn't it grank new grank?
new grank
like
Like the gronks like the bronks the gronks new gronk perfect. All right, we're in the gronks
You're not naming the city. This is the building name. How about now gronk city hall
All right, that looks good. So this is city hall
How much do I have 50 000?
Wait, what what the hell?
I don't even know what to do. This is so
Should I make a toaster? Wow. Okay. Wait a minute. Whoa
What? Whoa, this is crazy. Hold on. How about this one?
It's got to be a little the bottom part's gonna be like thick like that and then we'll do
Hmm, it's gonna be a cake. I'm gonna make a big wedding cake
Uh, and then there's usually like a little thing on top
Whoa. Whoa, that was cool. I'm not done. These roofs. Whoa. It's a big berry
Yeah, it's like oozing over the top. This is a bird bath. It's not a bird bath
It's I'm not good at this. I can't do like infrastructure and like architecture
Cool windows. I don't do infrastructure. I don't this is not the job for me off center. I got it. Hold on
I should do some okay. There we go. Check this out. This works. That looks nice
We'll do a couple of those around each side a little higher right there flying. That looks okay. I don't hate this city hall
Oh, I have to have this get like get direct tv for everybody
Oh, I don't like that aerosol. I kind of feel like i'm playing one of those games
Where stuff just falls from the top of the screen and you have to go left and right to try to
Stack it so it doesn't fall. I mean, I don't hate that though. I do but I don't at the same time
Maybe a little bit. No, it's got to be bigger. Yeah, it's got to be like that
Ruben's sandwich stacker. Is that what it is bird bath? I can't even man. All right. Hold on. I want something details on it
Um about some of these some prongs. No, no prongs. How about uh, some boxes?
Oh, this is like marshmallows. Perfect a couple more of these I can I can call this right?
This is gonna be like yeah, i'm gonna drizzle some strawberry sauce on here. What do you mean ruined?
What are you talking about ruined awful awful? This is I have to do the coloring stop
What only the second floor has windows good. You don't want marshmallows on it. I think that makes me look cool
That's not funny. I'm not trying i'm not trying to be funny. I want I want I wanted those
There's nothing I know i'm not trying to make you laugh. I'm trying to make myself think it's cool looking
Okay, fine. Well, whatever. I like that. I like that a lot actually is it tilted. Ooh
The marshmallow is back. Yeah, what the heck? Fuck. Yeah. Yeah, you know what? Yeah, fuck. Yeah, I don't care
I'm put i'm doing it. Yeah, fuck the haters, right? Fuck the haters. I'm putting marshmallows on my building
Fuck the haters. Fuck the haters and they have to be different sizes, too
Oh my god, this is so omega oowee gooey
Dripping dozen cheesy different sizes different shape marshmallows. Holy shit. Shut up. Oh, we got somebody new
They did not like that at all and I don't blame you
I know I don't either just trust me when I say that i'm not doing i'm not saying that
For fun i'm saying that because I have to if I if I went to a stream and I heard somebody go
Oh my god, ooey gooey. Gee, I'd be like fuck stop talking. I know I get it. Trust me
We're on the we're on the same team we're in the same boat you and I we're on the same team
Okay, I gotta relax. It needs a little more substance over here. Look at that. It's perfect
It's perfect. It is if this could be like red and this could be white and this could be like vanilla
It's got a strawberry shortcake. I win just to color it. Hold on an acorn. Nope. Can't put anything on top of that
It's not a butt plug
Stop i'm keep seeing that and it's making me very upset. I need a whip. It's like a dollop of whipped cream
Not that make it thinner a little dollop of whipped cream and then I need a cherry on top of that
Like let me do the stupid thing I want to do or i'm gonna be very mad. Oh fine. This can be that
No, I want this to be
Cherry, is it too high? It's too high
Wrong category. Oh
Oh, hold on too high too high too high too high. Is it heart limit? I don't think so
Not too high. Okay
Gonna have to go to details. Yeah, it's I can't put any more on you can't put a detail on top of a detail
Um, well
Um, no, no, wait, can't make it smaller. I can't make it smaller as small as it can go. Oh, whatever
I'll just put it on there and it could be uh
Like it could be a cherry. That's a good cherry this I think that look that could be a cherry first in the fifth row
One two, three, four five donut. Dude. Wait a minute. Wait a minute. You sit down for just a second. Everybody relax
You sit down for one minute
Whip cream done people really asking me how this is whipped cream. Give me a minute. Give me one second
Like I have you're gonna watch the artist paint and when he does a stroke you say it looks horrible
You have to let him wait. Let him paint the painting. Let him paint the painting first. Make sure they're overlapping enough
It's pretty good. It looks better over here though. Hold on. Hell. Yeah, look at that
There's your whipped cream and there's a cherry and these are gonna be
Like yellow like a cake. It's gonna be a strawberry shortcake
I don't even care what building this is anymore bottom left stem very needs a stem cherry needs a stem
Does it know does it know? No, let the artist work you skinnier. Oh, yeah. Oh, yeah a bit longer
You think how long cherry stems not that cherry stems not that long bottom bottom bottom bottom bottom left bottom left
Oh, that's what you mean. Wait, does this one bend does this one bend? Okay, that's better. Yeah, it is better
Oh, that's so much better. Hell. Yeah, I love it. I spin it and go I want everyone that
Um was angry that I was making like a dessert building where you know, they left it. All right. Here we go paintbrush mode
Oh my god. Yes. Oh my god. I'm gonna be here for an hour. Oh my god. Oh my god
All right. We need a whipped cream. We need red for the cherry. We need cherry red, which is like the most
Um, like the best keyboard you can get for a mechanical keyboard, right? Oh dear
Um, wait, hold on. I paint it. Yeah paint it. I can't click. Um, I can't paint this
Oh, it has to be I have to have a texture. Okay, the stem is like a uh, like what was the stem make it glossy
I hold on. This is very important. You're right. Is it like brown black? Is it purple or is the stem on a cherry?
That's not purple. Yeah, it's like a dark. Um, like down here right a little bit darker. It's green
What color is it cherry stem? Is it green? It is green shit. It's yeah, it's like an olive. It's green
You're thinking of an apple probably. All right. Now we this is the whipped cream whipped cream's gonna
We're gonna make whipped cream nice and glossy though. I'm gonna make it white glossy white
Big problem, it's not glossy
Does it have to be blue frothy is not well, I don't think I can make it glossy anyways in this one
I think that's good, right?
All right. Now strawberries strawberries are a little darker, aren't they? I need this kind of like there they're kind of like that
Even darker than that
Why is that glossy?
Oh shit, I could do it. Wait, what's the any of these more strawberry like this one?
Excuse me need like metal. There's so many it probably is like a strawberry texture
I mean, that's I kind of like that one, but that's more like strawberry drizzle. That's not hmm
Hmm needs to be a brighter red. Hold on. We got it
Shit
You're big. Hmm. I like that though
Can't wait to do the marshmallows and some of them by the way gonna be toasted
Some of them are gonna be toasted and then I can't wait to hear the screams in chat about how wrong you were
How sad you were that you doubted me that you doubted me for even a second. That's that's pretty good
That's pretty good guys. Just needs to be the right color
Strawberries are a little darker
Mmm, not like that though. No and these seeds are gonna be uh, they're black, right strawberry
What color is the strawberry? I know, you know, it's the strawberries red
But it's like what some of them can be like kind of green can't they but does that mean that they've rotten?
I've eaten tons of them
Strawberry. Hmm. It's like a deep deep red
Here really what that really the same color going on? Um, did I break it? I think I broke it
You're choosing two colors
Oh
fuck
Oh shit. Okay
Hold on. It's even more red. That's less orange more red
Getting there. Maybe one more
Into here there it is and then this is gonna be black right or white white or black because then these are these are black
Well, wait, these could be individual sprinkles. It could be individual sprinkles. Oh shit wrong color. That looks all right
I think a little bit darker. That's too much
moldy
Mold that's strawberries have burning all of them greening black white spots
Yeah, they're like a green and black. They're little divots, but then these kind of have to be oh whoops
I mean those could be like little chocolate chips or something
He's right you psychos. I'm yeah look at get a strawberry
Get really close to it and look at the divots. They're usually like a dark green
Dark green into like really kind of like a black. I don't like the way that looks though
Hmm
I don't hate that
This could be a little like chocolate chips or something seeds are yellow
Well, you think about this while I go pee I'll be right back. I gotta play that game by the way
No brush an absolutely delicious turkey turkey snack
All right, give me a sec somebody's chat said germa I seriously worry about your diet
Let me be very clear with you. I don't just eat turkey jerky sticks for every meal
That's a streamer snack. You guys wanted these tips
I can give them to you little turkey jerky sticks chicken jerky sticks
Three and a half inches long four inches long that you can eat them in less than 30 seconds
They're just like boom chew delicious salty a little bit of protein calories. It's great apple juice
Well, no, those go-go squeezers are not a bad idea either. Look at that dude, mr blue
You did it, right? But soon comes mr knight
You go over his hand is on his shoulder. Never mind. I'll remember you this
I'll remember you this way in a lot of negative weirdos lately a germa fan you so I drew a positive thing
a lot of negative weirdos
You're eating dog treats those turkey. What did you say? Let's see
But let me see what the negative person said just those turkey sticks are treats for auto
Listen, yeah, I will tell you
Turkey
Any beef jerky stick i'm not talking about slim jim's slim jim's are disgusting. I've eaten plenty of them over my lifetime
Okay, they're gross and they stink all
Jerky sticks smell like the inside of a dog treat bag. They do they smell like dog food
I don't know if they taste like dog food because they've never eaten dog food
But i'll tell you if they did taste like dog food then dog food tastes pretty good
They stink like a dog treat if you take a piece of beef jerky
That's um in the stick form and you hold it up to your nose and you just sniff it for a sec
It's it's bad. It smells like
baloney and
And weird sausage meat and just fake kind of flavoring
It just smells like a dog treat just gave 70 so 69 community subs. Holy shit
Zap x coming in with another 69 subs. Oh my god, that's so much money
My brother hold on wait, my brother opened a bag of beef jerky on a plane and the dude in front of us was visibly mad
Oh, I I mean it has a heavy smell. That was quake germa. That was pretty crazy, but thank you zap
That's so much money. That's too much money. We can get back to uh, get back to the snow sticky note drawing of germ
Well, that's not a sticky note. That's pretty crazy. Are you coming to my wedding circle? Yes or no?
Yes, awesome stuff as always guys, let's go back to what we were doing very cool strawberry seeds are not yellow
Strawberry seeds are black. What are you talking about? Okay
Anyways, I want to go do the the marshmallow ones is gonna be the most fun
Is there you know, you get the white in here. Hold on
Let me just do a few marshmallows just so I know what i'm getting into and then like the toasted hold on
Oh, this is gonna be so cool
Oh my god
Look at that. Look at it. Just look at it for a second. Let me see more toasted ones
No, it's too toasted way too toasted. That's way too toasted too much. Some of them just be made out of wood
That looks that looks good
Oh
No, it's close, but it's not close enough. All right orange
Some of them get like that though
No, not mine
What are you talking about? There's many tiers of how to enjoy a roasted marshmallow
There's stick it on the stick and just warm it up a little so it's just the heat is inside of the the
Middle and it's a little gooey. It's not toasted at all. It's just warmed
That's tier one tier two is you put it on the stick and you rotisserie it
Perfectly until the outside edge is like I would say
Slightly brown and then it's crunches in your mouth. It pulls back
It's super gooey super warm in the middle and it's viscous in the middle. That's tier two tier three
Is the full on nuclear mode. That's when you let it catch fire
You just let the thing burn the whole thing
Until it's black blow it out and then you get the you take that skin off. It's like crispy fucking chicken skin
But marshmallow and you eat that first and then there's this little center of just
Liquid but it's still kind of a solid that's tier three tier four
Is you let it light on fire you sit there and you let it burn
It falls off it falls off into the fire and you're like, oh shit
And then three or four hours later after the fire goes out you go in there and you find it and it's this little
Black speck in there you take your finger you lick your finger you touch this little black speck and then you go
It's tier four don't do that though. That's actually horrible. That's really bad for you. Don't do that. Nobody does that
I don't do that. It was made it was that was set for comedic purposes only. There you go. Ooh
I like that. This looks good. I think this is the one at least some of some of them can be that holy shit
I love it. Mmm, gotta get a little bit of variety. There we go
Oh, and I I will actually scream in your face
If you tell me that the toasted marshmallow the toasted marshmallow jelly belly is not the best one
If you say buttered popcorn is leave
Now and don't come back. I was just kidding. You can stay okay
Getting i'm kidding. You can stay don't worry. It was a joke. Look at that. It's so toasted and roasted
All right, I gotta settle down relax, dude
This is making me want dessert perma band links, please perma band links. We will probably eventually links are gonna turn into something else
Probably these roasted marshmallows with the texture on them, too
Oh, please god not my links
Don't worry the cherry. I don't the cherry is okay. Maybe hmm you guys blew it
Well, the links are not gonna go away
But I want to find solutions to make them not very spammable and look
I've been looking for solutions in quotes for tons of things over the years
So I don't know that looks just like the jelly belly jelly bean
Oh, I wish I had a huge plate of those right now. Next is the cake which this has to be
Uh, like a yellow damn it. This is making me so hungry. Yeah, it's got to be like a spongy material
And this kind of looks like dinosaur skin spongy
No, this is like wood
Maybe
This could be ice cream. Wait, this could be ice cream. Couldn't it? It's dipping dots. Hold on
I need to get the right color. Reverse that shit ice cream with fudge sauce
Mmm, that's not a bad idea. Why is it doing that? That could be but that needs to be like a brown
This is making me so hungry
Look at how delicious this looks. This is actually making me really hungry. It's like chocolate and sponge cake marshmallow
Oh, jesus. I need ice cream on this though. Oh
my
Fucking god i'm gonna copy this. Oh my god a little bit more one more
Don't forget don't forget about the color right now. They're not eggs. Forget about the color. Holy shit
Okay, i'm almost done one more in the back a bit higher. There's like a two scoop right here
No, no, no, no, no, no, not good enough. There it is. Holy shit. Okay. Wait a little bit lower a little less
Okay, wait a little more a little less less. It was like the those you scoop up and just drop it on the sponge cake
Forget about the colors. We're not um, what color what uh ice cream should be, you know?
What color what what kind of ice cream's on it strawberry ice cream? Wait, it should be you're right
It should be strawberry ice cream. Holy shit. This is gonna be awesome
Strawberry ice cream, dude, are you serious? Oh my god. What are you thinking? You're a goddamn genius
No, that's not right. Should there be a pattern mint mint mint? Well, let me get this done. Hmm
Yeah, they need any texture in there smooth strawberry ice cream. That's that light pink color without anything in it
Is my favorite thing on earth. I just want to make sure everyone knows this
smooth
Strawberry ice cream barely pink color is the best thing
You that's my favorite thing in the world eating it just straight up is awesome putting it between like having it as like an ice cream sandwich
also
As a milkshake smooth strawberry ice cream makes the best milkshake. I will take that over any chocolate milkshake any vanilla shake
Man, it's so good. It's the best it really is paint the sphere. Oh shit this thing in the middle
What would that be? That's technically part of the strawberry should be green. This is technically the bottom half of the strawberry
Upside down, right? This would be like cut in half like a pink. We'll get to that in a minute. Oh, it's perfect
Shit okay the wasp nest
I'm not sure anything's gonna come closer though because that looks like you've scraped
I'm not sure I should go to anything else. I feel like this is the best we're gonna get
This looks like it's been scraped and like it's been dropped and
Make the antennas cones. Yeah. Wait, is this something that's better for a cone?
Mmm
Maybe this let's just test it and then we flip this fucking thing upside down and I flip it around
I can't wait. Wait, come on, but it could be upside down. It could be upside down
It could be upside down on top of one of these it could be upside down on top of one of these
All right, keep that out here. No, these are details. I can't do that put pistachio on it. Hold on
Don't tell me I can't do this. I got it. I got this and I tilt it. Let me tilt this shit
I can't tilt it. Why?
No
Use tab tab tab
Oh, yes
I almost burped. Oh
Come on
No, come on. I'm so close. I'm so close. I wish I could just put it here. Wait, hold on. I can't
Oh kind of hold on kind of kind of it's kind of doing it. Stop it control
Oh, you fucked it up. That was it. Oh my goodness. I love it. That's good. That's good there. That's good
All right, that's gonna make the cone. Yeah, that's good. Should I put hey check this shit out?
You know what I mean? Like it fell down here and went
One more maybe like right there remember you still have four more things to build you need to hurry up if you want to actually play
What are we talking about? Um, is this too much? I think this might be I don't know
What do you think? It's like it's spilling over the side too much. It might be it's getting a little busy
Hmm. Hold on and then hmm. I need to make the cone different color. This took an hour
Yeah, sure may have to make a spoon over there. Yeah, definitely good idea. That's a really good idea
What a perfect idea. It's gonna be waffle like shaped. Oh my god. Look at this shit
Wait, reverse those colors. I need to reverse that it needs to be darker up here
Wait, should I reverse it? Yeah, I need to flip these colors. All right, how did I get to that one?
Okay, that one's like a light
No, where did I get that from?
This one, right? Okay. No, how did I get that color? How did I get this? How did I get that color?
Go close close one more up. It's close enough. Okay, and then I need this one to be this a little lighter
Okay, let's try it. Shit. Why people people bored me bored. Oh, well, I'm whatever
Look over look at this. I'm making a masterpiece. It was better the other way
Yeah, it was I want this to be darker though by a little bit not that dark
No, no, what are you doing? This top one needs to be darker. Give me like a chocolate cone
Mmm, I like that. I kind of like the chocolate cone stop building. What what's wrong? What's going on here people are bored
Well get up and do some jumping jacks. What do I want to tell you? I'm having fun making my ice cream house
I maybe I shouldn't mess with it. Maybe it is good that way
Hmm, and that needs to be so much a little bit darker, but I can't get it
I don't know where the color is to do that. Maybe no, not that yellow
This brown i'm just gonna leave it. I don't want to mess with it. It's it's it's it's good the way it is
All right. I need a spoon now. This is late saturday vibe. Yeah, we're just hanging out man
Well, I you know when this is done, you're gonna love it
Change the door color. I will that's gonna be fucking pistachio. They're gonna be like mint or something. I don't know
I just got here. I'm just joining chats rage. Oh, well do the x-ray. All right
I need it. I want a spoon over here if I can do it
I have to okay
Here's the you want to know the best part about what you're watching right now
Like an hour is going into this one two hours is going into this one
The next three buildings I have to make are going to be cubes all that matters is the ice cream house
We've got some good spoon
Potential here this right here is that's a spoon to me. I just got to spin it around and put it in the ice cream
Oh, hell. Yeah, look at this. Are you kidding me?
Are you are you kidding me? Are you kidding tab? Are you kidding only real germa fans watching play with ice cream for an hour?
Hey, thanks
Hey, what's going on here? Did you sell that? What how do okay? How do I move it? How do I free move it?
Don't sell why does it want me to sell this because control can only move it up and down
How do I move it left and right because I can only move it up and down with control
It's shift the other way shift is left and right. It's not what's left and right hold
Hold shift hold shift. I can't go left and right. I can only go up and down with both shift and control
Hold alt no up and down tab holding tab makes me just go up and down
Wait, hold on shift
Oh, no. No, they were right. They were right. We're good. We're good. We're good. Everything's fine
Everyone can relax get that shit out of here. It wants me to sell it
No, i'm not. I don't want to sell this. I'm not gonna sell it. Why are you making me try to sell it?
Fuck off. Okay. Now let's bring it back up
Hold this way
I'm not gonna sell it. Stop doing this. I don't know why it's doing that. What the fuck
What the fuck dude? Why is it doing that?
Hey
German never sell
Is it out of bounds out of bounds? What that's annoying. Well, I guess i'm gonna do it this way and then this is it
Why did you have to do that? Oh, I game you're really pissing me off. No now you're making me angry
Now you're just upsetting me. It's so close. All right, I got it. I have it in position. It's in position in position
Almost hilt it right there. Oh, it's close. Come on. Come on. Got it done
It can be better. Oh, it's so you don't look at it. It's like kind of it's slowly almost falling off the spoon
Whoa, cool. All right
We can be better than that though. Mmm
I get a golden spoon. I'm just seeing what's available blue plastic spoon. That looks pretty good, too. I think that's it
That's the one door right? Yeah. Okay the doors. What are the doors gonna be strawberry marshmallows?
What goes with strawberry marshmallows chocolate syrup graham crackers?
Yep graham cracker doors graham cracker doors and graham cracker windows. That's perfect
We need a good texture for graham cracker though. I mean that's not bad. That's pretty good. Oh, hell yeah
And the middle here though the middle here needs to be
Um something what what is this this middle part graham crackers sitting on? Oh my god chocolate
Would be dark brown like it gets dipped in chocolate. Give it a look
Uh, so this is the chocolate base bar even bitten the cherry needs to be glossy glossy cherry glossy cherry, right?
Right, right. Hold on. I'll get you. Um glossy cherry yellow seeds yellow seeds yellow seeds yellow seeds
Oh shit, these gotta go back is kind of empty. I need something right here at the very back
How about a um one of the cherry put a banana here put banana?
Put a chocolate banana here banana, please a banana a chocolate banana
But I mean, I I guess this could be a banana. No, it's gonna curve. Oh my god
Oh my god
Oh
My god, which way should be facing like that. Definitely a little bit higher. I tilt it
I think i'm gonna tilt it a little just a little bit just to go up a little so it's resting kind of right
On it and tilt it this way. All right. Looks good. Perfect. Perfect. All right. I gotta gotta get the banana colors
They're almost they're not bad. It's close bananas are kind of like just barely off kind of white, right?
They're like a yellow off-white bananas are not yellow. They're like an off-white
Yeah, yellow and like a brown deep yellow with brown spots. No, no, no, this is not guys. This isn't
Um, hold on a minute. I think we're confused
This is a dessert
This is part of the dessert. The banana is peeled the banana's not sitting there in the banana shell
It's peeled it's part of the dessert. I just want to make sure i'm very clear about that
I mean that's already perfect. But does it need anything else? I feel like it's a little bear over there
If it's like chocolate speckles on it like it's been
Splashed in the chocolate. I think so a little darker. There it is
Um been done for five minutes one. Perfect. It's perfect. It gets been rolling around in the chocolate a little
It's so don't you want to just take a fork or a spoon and just smush it down on that banana
Take the piece down here scrape it so the little tip is on the spoon
Come over here drag it across here on the strawberry and then pick one of these off with your hands
The other hand take the spoon you had slip right into the cream
Into your mouth bite the banana bite the marshmallow at the same time chocolate on the tip. Oh, I see like it's been dipped in chocolate
It's been dipped in the chocolate I see somebody did a little we're done here it is what a mint chocolate chip roof a cigarette
I used a done cigarette. No, that's a banana. That's a banana relax
It does kind of look
Cigarette save and exit stop. Did you will you go do some push-ups or something burn some energy?
Yellow seeds yellow seeds yellow seeds for real. I but I don't even know. I don't think I could even fix that
I don't even know what the pattern was
Can't get over that. This was a banana until five seconds ago
Now you're making me want to remove it because it's a cigarette
I that's been a banana for the last 10 minutes of my brain until right now
No, all right, i'm not i'm not messing with it anymore i'm not messing with it anymore it's over
I did it. There it is the gronk's ice cream city hall
Maybe I should like
Put the banana. No, i'm not no more i'm stepping away yellow seeds where I won't eat it
I don't know where that is. Is it this one here? I gotta match the colors again. I don't think I can it's no it's green
Plus that's like mint chocolate chip sprinkles. I think they've been in a little larger. Leave it. It looks good. Yeah
I'm stepping away
Wow, it's not even textured
We're gonna make so much money and plus they're ice cream themed themselves. This is like the sherbert crows
We're gonna make cars or we're gonna make trucks or we're gonna make spaceships
See are they all questioning the guy that said he wanted to make pies and ice cream and stuff
Look at the building cars and cash no ice cream
You're about to enter civilization. Oh boy. What is this?
Name your land vehicle. It has got to be it's got to be like a graham cracker car
It's got to be like a banana chocolate car or something. Oh, no
Oh, no
Ice cream sandwich car. I mean I can do that pretty quickly. I think
I can do that one quickly
All right in the wrapper or out of the wrapper. That's important
Should have like half a turn around half wrapper maybe okay
Just so that's for me to remember ice cream sandwich
That looks pretty good. That's a good start. That's the middle
Hmm
Nope, this is the middle. It needs wheels. Yeah, that's true. That's a that's a good start. I like it
Okay
Uh, I can do this very quickly the body we need
Mmm cockpit. I think that's perfect. I can do this one pretty they all have this one
I think it's gonna be this one. They just stretch it a little bit. Not bad drink it a little bit. Mmm
Remember, this is the chocolate. Yeah, hold on just to make sure that I got I got question marks and I got like
What is he doing?
When I made the first marshmallow so I would like everyone to hope just relax
Just wait for the pog moment in like 45 minutes. Okay. All right. Okay. All right. All right. All right
Easy easy easy just slow down easy. Oh, fuck. Yeah. Oh, yeah
All right, and we're gonna have oreo cookie wheels is perfect cockpit body
Land. All right. I need oreo cookie wheels
Or like whipped cream gun. No oreo cookie wheels is perfect. This is gonna be so cool
Or should it be underneath the car?
Now where's gonna okay i'm just gonna make the car i'm just making me so hungry for dessert
The wheels are gonna be big big oreos because they're like tiny don't they like an inch or two tall
Okay, oreo cookie. We'll dress this up in a minute. Hold on
Um, this is like floating. Hey, don't do that. Why is this floating? It's fine shift to move the whole vehicle
Oh, there we go. Okay
There and then this guy that gotta have a little bit of detail work. Don't you think let's get the paint job going here?
All right, so it's
Let's get the let's get the look here. So it's actually the look is
It's just like this but just we need that exact texture this exact texture
Because I just want to regular just cream it just cream. Okay. Oh my god
It's kind of perfect but not quite I like that middle but I need it to be a little smoother
close
Very close
Let me just get the look first
I'm gonna go back and do this later. Just give me give me a sec
Okay
Ice cream sandwich
I need the money black up top just a straight straight up just black
What should I do? Let's just I want to see what it looks like. Let's just you know, you idiot
Idiot, go
Okay, nice and smooth
Nice. All right
Get that black too. Good. Okay
It needs texture though. It needs texture
um
Reverse it that's the way
I call that perfect if you ask me
You want to go look at what an ice cream sandwich looks like right now go look at the top
You tell me if that's not exactly what it looks like looking good. Very good. Oh, that's incredible. Okay
All right. I need something else to add to this to make it
Really? You gotta do cookies and cream wheels
That's gotta be
Let me just get a base here
Oreos are a lot darker
Add stats. What are you talking about? You need to add capitalist parts to make it actually functional. What?
a couple of gumdrops
Do you put gumdrops on a ice cream sandwich?
But I understand why you would want them on this
It needs parts
Um, I have a hold on
Okay, I got the baseline here. Hold on
So how we have wheels we have a cockpit see there. It's fine
All right. Oh, this needs health and shit
oh
that's
economic
coins
effect detail. Oh
I thought I actually have to do stuff
cockpit, but no whatever
These could be little gumdrops
Do chocolate coins?
Oh, I kind of like the chocolate coin idea
And they're big too
Chocolate coins. I want the big one to be visible. There we go. Okay, we got our chocolate coins
These need to be different. These have to change. This has to be like bright yellow, right? Bright gold. Oh, you can't
Oh, that's all right
Because we just we can pretend
Charmed quark
Eye roller economic power
This could be one big chocolate coin
You need to look at the stats
economic land wheel and deal your way to the top by land
health
economic power or speed
Economic power increases trade route profitability survive longer in combat and speed
This thing's fast
All right. This is economic. Um
sandwich car
All right. I need to the wheels need detail
the capitalist oreo
Other way the wheels need a little bit more detail in the middle just like the cookies and cream pattern
um
too much
Other way. Yeah other way
Um, not dark enough. Oh me actually
Make a ring pop
No, no, it's wrong. It's gotta be
Okay, hold on. Everyone. Just hold on a second
I think i've got a little bit of an idea here. I don't hate this or it's oreo cereal
It is good job
Good don't work. You've got it. It's oreo. Oh, that's right. It needs to be a little darker though
No lighter. Yeah, that's true oreo is right there
Need to meet a gear on the bottom ring pop. I'll make a ring pop like airplanes. Hold on
Add m&m's on it. Hmm
That looks so cool. I love it
Holy shit, it's it's it is a ring pop, but this doesn't work on the chocolate though
It doesn't work on the chocolate weapons dumbass. This is that's not this is a this is not a weapon car
This is an economic land vehicle
hmm
Needs headlights
Does it you have to have weapons or you'll not win about where the weapons I don't see any weapons effect
Where do you see weapons? This is it's an economic nation
I don't have any weapons. All right. I like this the way it is
I like the oreo owes wheels ice cream sandwich and then the chocolate coins for the economics car make gumdrop headlights
Oh, but that's a great idea. I think I have to do that x yeah, there's nothing here night light
Gumdrop. Hmm. What should they be right here gumdrops or no
Milk duds. I gotta stick with the theme gotta stay with the theme guys. Can't just
Hmm, but they're lights. It's gonna be hard to do chocolate lights
Brown light you're gonna want more economic put the economic stuff underneath. Um, am I really though?
There we go rock candy lights just clip it into the car
Hmm. Those are what just like stuff this in here somewhere just clip this into the car. Um
Is there a reason why I can't I can't mess with this. It doesn't want me to I can't clip it in
What it has rims now, but that messes with what the oreo owes underneath now
That's kind of hidden between the headlights. No, I don't I want to be hidden. I don't even like the headlights
I don't like them. I don't want them. I wanted to be simple hide the coins. I like the chocolate coins
Physical ring pop brake light, please
Hold on
But it doesn't go with the chocolate theme. There's a theme. There's a theme
What about the theme? Why can I not pick these up? It's annoying. I can't clip it into there
The theme we want brake lights there ring pop brake lights sing the raid song
What fuck the lights keep the theme? I think it matches a little it does match
We don't know who raided what you talking about put the headlights back now. All right fine
I'll get the headlights back because we're going away from the theme which one it was it was these ones, right?
Yeah, there you go. There we are. It's done raid song now. There's no I don't this stuff, but he raided
What are you talking about? Okay. I think this is good. This is an economic land oreo owes vehicle
I test it. Can I drive it ice cream sandwich oreo owes vehicle its health is bad. Oh gosh
60 economic power it does that 230. How do I get more health?
swamp heater
Holy shit
No, it messes with the theme
But the theme I don't want it. This thing's just gonna get the shit kicked out of it. Um, it's because your cockpit sucks
What if I just put another no hide stuff under it? It's all percentages. Oh, okay
So it's a 60 economic powerhouse. All right, i'm that's good. That's good. I'm done there economic oreo
Do a rocket popsicle. Uh, that is exactly what I wanted to do
the red white and blue
Um, we did it the age of technology and transportation has arrived your city is the first to appear on the planet
But your species no longer speaks with a single voice soon. Other cities will arise built by factions of your own species
You must unify to advance welcome to civilization. You now control the vehicles and the city planning for your nation
Starting with its first city
You must interact with other nations when they appear to begin your quest for global domination. Let's take a look at the bar
Each city you conquer convert or purchase will help you progress towards the goal to control the entire planet
Okay
Your nation begins with a single specialty, but you can add more by conquering other cities
My specialty is I don't know move the camera freely around the world
This helps you to check in on cities or vehicles to whom you have given orders
All right, let's pause for a moment and learn the basic camera controls and how to select a vehicle
Hold left and right mouse buttons at the same time to pinch and rotate the camera
kill
of the left
Use the arrow keys to pan the camera
Well, that's fucking mario galaxy's gonna make me puke
Yeah, i'm gonna throw up if I get okay click on your vehicle with the left mouse button to drag a box. Okay
What am I gonna do?
Look for a nearby spice geyser like this one then click on it to send your vehicle to claim it
Spices become a valued commodity mining. It will help you fill the coffers of your nations. Okay, so you have to go to spice geysers
Okay, your nation's goals will appear here your first goal is to claim a spice geyser and begin mining operations
Controlling spice geysers will increase your nation's production
All right. Well, let's save it
Okay
Get a spice geyser
Okay, claim the geyser
I see a sims character
claiming the spice geyser
King king notice the spice geyser you claimed has converted to your nation's identity color red
Click on your city hall on the mini map move your camera to it so you can begin building up your capital
Okay, design a profitable city buy a land vehicle
Should I get two? All right city planner
These tabs will help you navigate the city planner buy vehicles buildings or civic objects create an anthem or outfit your citizens
okay
anthem composer
Uh-oh. Hold on. First of all, I turned like the music way down because it was so loud
Okay, let's try that again like an instrument. Okay. Hold on the beat. I want is
Move and wait what now different instrument turn up the volume. I just did so much. All right, here we go
I want to start at zero. I gotta find the right ambience. Not too scary squeaky. I like this pretty good
All right. Number four is pretty good. Oh, no, no, it's too industrial. It's too like
Cyberpunk. I like it
Uh, it's okay. It's toss up between four
seven
Eight, I mean
Oh, it's a toss up
No, okay. This one
this one
Oh this one
Yeah, definitely this one
instrument
Okay, let's see doing
Auto play on and off generating new anthem
of
I go faster
Oh one i'm just playing around to see how it sounds like all right, let's see not that one
Nope
I like that one number five
That one too. That's a good that's that's guan
That's close to guan
We got five or
See it
No, no, no, no back up here
Again again
Again I want do do do do do do do
There almost told when I got a master with this one
Right. No, why did you do that?
I'm doing that. What the fuck I have to do this one like a tiny little map
Right. Go ahead
Got it and all right, that's it. It's not resolving on the one
I don't know. I have no idea what you just said. You just spoke a language. I don't understand
Is this toxic?
No, it's not
Don't you know that you're toxic oh fuck off no
It is
Do
This toxic is my anthem
All right, here it is
There's the anthem
City outfitter. Ooh, hold on
This is wait, this is wait. I gotta turn this shit down. Hold on a second
Oh my god, he's playing at 1680 by 1050 with a 2000 megabyte graphic cache
What a dog shit computer he must be on
Okay, oh I can make them into city clothes
Which I do
Okay, this is playing my song
Okay a hat
Hmm. Hey, that's better. Does this mean anything? No, it's just cosmetic. Okay mask. Um
What was this before?
Senator looks stupid his arms aren't even through the armholes. Oh, it's a bow tie. Okay, I get it. Uh
Scrub brushers. How about these? Yeah, that's that's pretty diplomatic. Just this is a cardboard. Okay, give him frankenstein bolts
No, I hate that
hair
They're all gonna have george washington hair and
All right, looks fine. It's a pringles guy. I don't I still don't understand this
This is just like a big where is it supposed to be? Where is this supposed to be on their body?
I don't get it. He's gonna hold it get us back. It'll be on the chest. How is this supposed to sit on there?
Let's fold the other way one. Please tilt it. There we go. Okay, now pull it forward
This is the best I can do like this. I can't make it very much better than that
I'm desperately trying to put this here. It just doesn't want to go back
Okay, and then hold shift see like what the hell just put it on his arms. That's better. I don't care
Okay. Now we need oh, no, no, no, you're gonna stay that you can say that color
I mean cock boy this I need to change this his mustache has got like flaming hot cheeto dust all over
Does that happen?
Okay, if you have a huge mustache and you eat a ton of flaming hot cheetos
Will it do that? Do you have to go wash your face your beard hair afterwards all the time all the time?
I feel like if you ate flaming hot cheetos a lot with a big beard and especially big mustache
And you didn't clean it out completely and you sneezed later. Could you sneeze flaming hot cheeto powder into your eyes?
Yes, you could the actual hazard that never happens to me. You could accidentally inhale it too. Oh, oh, oh
Yeah
Yeah, you could we go right in your nose. You would just smell it forever. Oh
Okay, this is part two to this conversation. How many of you guys like pizza?
Yeah, see I know yeah, settle down
I just asked you to raise your hand those of you that eat pizza all the time
You ever have a greasy pizza and after you have like pepperoni and there's like it's greasy slice and like an hour later
You just smell oil you smell pizza grease
It's all must be somewhere like on your lip or on your chin somewhere
Even if you've wiped it off, even if you've cleaned it that smell of pizza grease stays with you
so follow up to that last thing those of you beard guys
And mustache guys that eat greasy pizza is that times a thousand?
Yes, it's horrible because I wash my face. No, even if you wash your face it stays there. Yes. It's awful. It's awful
It's awful. That's pretty divided on this. Hmm. Just wash your hands and wash your beard. Something's wrong with you
No, it's not a kind of radioactive pizza. No, you just you don't get it. Those either get it get it
This really does kind of look like an old like ice cream man. All right, i'm keeping it. We're children
Oh, you're not I gotta pee again. Can I go pee again and get a water?
Yeah, it's a good time. Let's go pee beer back. Let's say purple alien enjoying his new year purple alien. Wow
Look at that sheriff. Cool. I love it
Okay
Uh, let's play the game now one more. Uh-oh
So what do you guys think is gonna happen when I inevitably do the cat boy streams?
Are we gonna get times two as many cat boy artwork or will we hit the apex of the meme and will we go down?
What do you think i'm not sure it's gonna increase
You'll get cursed and you'll never be able to take it off
What a dumb curse
Like honestly, if that's the worst curse you could you could give me what oh, okay
Think of the curses you've ever heard of
Your skin will start to melt off over the course of five years until you're nothing but bones
Everything you eat will taste like dirty shit for the rest of your life
You'll have cat ears and
A tube top on forever
Okay, what I don't care, but you don't understand it'll be you have ears
I don't care. Like what is it? Does this hurt me?
No, in fact way more people are gonna be interested in your stream
I'm gonna give more attention and and more money way more money and I mean like a hundred times more
I just have to wear cat ears. Yes
It's horrible
uh
Fuck fuck don't do that. Don't do that to me. Yeah, I knew I would get you eventually
Let's go. He wants to do it. I don't actually
And you'll have ears. You don't have ears already. Oh, yeah, I know but they're extra
No, fuck you chat. I won't become a cat boy. I'll become surreal
All right, let's go remember the dev is in the chat the dev of spore that's cool
All right, let's go. So what do we do? I get to design a profitable city
So let's go to let's should I get another vehicle? What do we got for resources?
I claimed this this is a thousand dollars a minute
What else we got?
There's one over here. Can I go in there? I cannot I need a c vehicle. There's one over here though. That's a thousand a minute
Claim this one. What else we got city planner buildings vehicles decorations
City hall a house design a new house increase city population and vehicle cap entertainment
Design a new entertainment building increase happiness which protects against religious attacks
Um, okay, I guess we can we'll put that somewhere
What I just do
Oh, fuck. Okay, we're gonna have to start making cubes
Is the entertainment house?
Okay, they're all gonna be minecraft houses
Yeah from here. So this just like I play minecraft
You have this elaborate project that you're gonna make
And you do it takes you six hours to do and then you have a few additions to put on and you're like
You know what? No, it's okay. It can be cobblestone and birch tree. I don't care anymore make it a gingerbread house. Perfect
It's done. It's a gingerbread house. Let's go. Perfect. That's perfect. Let's go gingerbread house easy
Making a nickelodeon house making a nickelodeon house make it a cheese house. Okay. Yeah, it's food. Yep. This is cheese
This is a macaroni and cheese house done. Can this be a restaurant? That's entertaining. Whatever sub only quick one
All right. Here's my entertainment macaroni and cheese craft macaroni and cheese somebody link me the um, the lyrics I can do it
That's so ugly. I'm gonna have to edit that and make it different. That's horrible looking looks like dog shit
Looks just like a wooden house. It looks like a bird house. It's stale pasta
What's the lyrics to the crab macaroni and cheese?
I want to do it right now. Come on. Let's see. It better mods. Holy shit
What are you talking about guys? There's 12 000 people here
You know how hard do you know how hard it is to moderate 12 000 of you
This ain't just a room of like like five of us. I think sometimes you guys forget that
It's not just you and me doing like once twice three shooting a room. This is this is a baseball stadium here riot riot riot
All right. Come on. Bring it on then bring it on. Let's see. I must like punch you
I just like punched one of you
German German
Calm down. It's just a chat room. What dude now you're going to jail. What do you mean? Why? No, i'm not
Come here
He's not getting up germa
Just one of you just one of you I I went too far and one of you just this eleven thousand
1224 of us just looking down at this person dude. What are you doing?
What you just knocked this fucking dude out. You don't understand. They were screaming at me. I I I you don't understand
They were yelling in there, but I just made them a scrumptious cake and it was delicious and they weren't mad at me
He's bleeding. No, he's not. He's fine. All right. I've got I'm all right. I'm playing the game
Are they booing me? Oh an ambulance design a new factory turret. Yep. Why is it playing that song?
That's the song that plays every time I do something
Every time I do an action it goes doom doom doom. What are they doing? They gambling over here. What are they doing?
Oh, whoa, whoa easy easy doom doom doom doom doom doom. Uh, what's wrong with my city? Why is it like that? Okay
um, I have entertainment now and
I've got
$2,000 a minute or whatever it is. It's my car. What's going on over here. There's a village over here. Oh fuck
What happened the tribe of your species has built a city on your continent
You may want to conquer them while they are still weak or attempt to make them an ally
These are your nation's unique super abilities. Your citizens will develop these technologies as your nation grows
I don't have any I have a macaroni and cheese house and ice cream propose a trade route. Oh shit a trade route. Ooh
Um, I proposed a trade route you and us we can do this together i'm hearing a lot of um
Can I read a trade route? How are we doing?
At geysers dear god, hold on. I'm wait a minute
Such a partnership can only help spread our faith. We accept excellent. I got a we got an ally
All right, i'm gonna send more uh people over there. You can also click on vehicles here in your fleet list
To select them or see their current activity
Double click them on a vehicle icon select all vehicles that type. Okay
Trade route no geysers trade route get more spices
What I already have one
Okay, this is not mine
bribe the workers
Spice must I need to go across the continent over here. Okay, I need
I need uh boats
Boats boats boats. Let's go
Take that not yet. Hold on. I need a boat. I need a boat city
vehicles
Use your sea vehicles to attack other continents. I don't toy boat toy boat toy boat toy boat toy boat toy boat toy boat toy boat toy boat
I'll do it every time and i'll win every time thanks for the money. Nobody gave me any money. Okay, I need to build a
Uh factory versus income but lowers happiness. It's okay. We have an entertainment center. Can I get a pre-built?
Just give me a pre-built. Just a big pool. Just a big jacuzzi. What is this a factory?
Okay, it's just the house the wizard's house in stardew valley. Okay, they don't like that
So should I put this over here? I hate that. What is the what are the lines mean name the city puke?
What was your question? Okay. Now I need i've got a factory
We're gonna make some money. I got a trade route buy an opposing city for how much how much is green worth?
Buy city requires trade route. Wait and buy this city. Where are you going? Okay. Hold on buy city requires more trade
Who owns the geyser over here? Who owns that me me need more residential. Oh shit. Okay, I need houses
Little gumdrop houses make family guy houses. No gumdrops. Uh, what is it? What's a gumdrop red orange?
What color is a gumdrop? It's a baby bottle. I actually kind of like this. I like that
I told you we weren't going to spend we I blew all my creative energy
I blew every ounce of the creative energy on the ice cream house. No, I don't like that
Okay, so they're happy about that. It was more residential another residential right over here. David
Mammite city is celebrating giving increased income
Haven is now available for purchase haven what oh I can buy it. How much does it cost buy city?
I understand why you would want fair haven for your own name your price
Not never mind. Not yet. I need more money
Yeah
Haven what's going on up here? Where you going? Where are they going? I want to trade route with them. Where are my vehicles?
Another vehicle. I want to trade with you. Where are you? Where are you you pieces of shit contact?
We are pleased with our relations. How can we assist you our people admire your wide tracts of land
Your people are descended from limbless space slugs
We come offering gifts. Do you accept?
We admire you
Yeah, we aren't we the same species. We admire your tracks
Your words show great wisdom
They do don't they we have a trade route with you. I want more trade. Give me another. I want another economic car
How will that trade up more trade? What's this? And then i'm buying out these guys over here. How much?
10 10 000 simoleons, are they fighting?
Whose tank is this?
Where you can only grow our might we accept
Hey, um, wait now. Well now it's gonna be way cheaper
Okay
um
It should be a lot cheaper now
How do I need to make military vehicle?
How do I make military vehicles?
I
Create your own where's a military vehicle help them with what I don't have anything. I have ice cream and macaroni and cheese
Factory you have no military need a military city. They're gonna be all right
Oh fuck
I don't want this one anymore
We have mediated it on all hours, but cannot decide whether you're a friend or foe. What do you need?
Your hunger doomed your allies. What?
Um, I don't know what to do about this. I don't have any military buy the city now right before it's destroyed
I understand why you wouldn't want fair haven for your own name your price
How about for 4 000 buy it now?
You are very generous. We accept
That's the cheapest I could have bought it for
Isn't it still under attack?
There's still there's a missile about to hit the capital
You bought out this religious city
If you keep the specialty you should target cities with low happiness in order to convert their citizens
You've bought out this
If you keep this specialty you should target cities with a low happiness. No, we're staying in economic
Buy an economic vehicle
And I want a trade route. I want by the way, give me that spice shit. It's mine
We're going over here with trade. I need uh
Over here. Hey contact
Please without relations. How can we assist you?
Uh
We admire you
Very much. So let's get a trade vote with you, please
I got 5800 bucks
I need more population over here. Oh economic c
But okay, I want to take a little bit of time make the boat. Let me give me a minute to make the boat
This is going to be what's it going to be make it a banana
Hmm
No, what what dessert goes good in the wind liquid? It's like a watery dessert
A milkshake or something. I can make a milkshake make a sundae. Yeah, that's not a bad one
That's what that's what's gonna be holding it in
It has to be a cockpit. So let's just get that in there
Doesn't matter. Okay. Now we need ice cream
Definitely. No
What's a fast one?
This is gonna be so cute
I want headlights break lights boat plug quiet. All right, let's get some gobs of ice cream. What was the banana? Oh
I don't think I can do the bananas. I don't have the detail anymore. Hmm. We make gobs of ice cream though big ice cream gobs
Gobs of I love that word by the way gobs of ice cream usually a couple there's usually a mound
That's bigger than all the other mounds right just blocking it out. I'll get it. Don't worry. Remember economic power. Oh, yeah
I don't even need a military. I'm just gonna buy everybody out
Look at those gobs of ice cream and then this typically
Typically, there's like a drizzle of chocolate sauce. This is a sushi boat. That's way better. I do. Okay
Yeah, this is like salmon sushi like spicy tuna a lot darker like that
It's not that red. I mean usually it can be that's better. It's like a good spicy
This is a good tuna not spicy tuna. This is just tuna. Let me get this right
Let me be pretend like I know what i'm talking about. What's it called? This is a specific name
Oh, what's it called? Oh, i'm gonna I
No, not ahi. It's a very it's a very high quality cut of sushi. What's it called?
No, no, not sashimi. It's actually like the tuna
No, not ahi toro. There it is. Thank you. God. I knew that how come I didn't say that toro
Four-year-old talking about all right. We need rice close
Not quite. Hold on. It's close
Mmm, it's as wide as I can get it make this make this uh, seaweed sail call. I need a better seaweed though
Here it is. There it is. Just darker darker than that. Come on darker than that. What the fuck come on
That's as dark as I can get that green. I guess that's as dark as I can get it
Yeah, see what he's really dark, but I wish I could go I can't go any darker than this
That still looks cute. Where's the banana?
I gave up after somebody said sushi boat and it was way more realistic looking darker colors are to the left you moron
What are you talking about? All right. I want that person to see what i'm gonna do and then I want them to
Be upset that look what happened and I want they right I want you to shift around in your seat
Understand that look what look what happened. Look what you did
Look what you did look at what you did different texture. Yeah, let's try that
Hmm
Ooh
Wait, actually don't know
No, not quite
texture is a little better, but
No
How did how did people even do donald duck? That's crazy
I think that the best I can get is the one I had before
Yeah, I think that's the best i'm gonna get it. That looks the most like seaweed do a donald duck compression right now
Just I can't wait. Why is it combining colors?
Yeah, that looks fine. Okay, it's ready. Okay, let's get one make a sushi boat. Oh look at it. It's so cool
Okay. Now we need to go
We're here. I steal that no I set up which oh, hold on trade route like your powers
Static bomb bribe bomb this ability caused enemy vehicles within bombs radius to attack each other
Really your trade is accepted. Thank you. Let's get a couple more of those
Two more two more sushi boats. It's more factories
That's a good call
Uh factory and let's get some more entertainment over here and then some more houses
All right, build it. Is it even possible to lose this game?
um
I don't know
Probably not trade with this guy over here. How you doing great? You have military. I got a friend this guy
This guy's got military
Can I buy you can I buy it's yellow again? Wait, I can buy him for a very cheap price
Just wait till he's almost dead. I'm afraid you can only grow our might. Yep. You're a true negotiator. Thank you
Every day every time I said he's about to be destroyed. I just come in and do the lowest
Bid possible than I win
And then the yellow backs away because he's not attacking me
I gotta find yellow. Where's yellow? You bought out this military city
Military your city's under attack defend. You said we're placing turrets. Hey
Stop stop stop stop stop stop stop stop stop
Stop stop stop stop stop stop. Stop it. Leave me alone
Oh, this is why I shouldn't have bought it
No, you have why are you still attacking me?
I need turrets
I need vehicles
I got scammed pause time. How do you pause time?
I don't have a pause time static bomb
but now what I
Now what? Oh military vehicle
Okay time to make a tank. I'm gonna make a tank with like a thousand guns on it
Make it a ketchup bottle
I like the way you think
I need a ketchup bottle. What's more ketchup bottle. This is pretty ketchup bottle if I squish it
No, this is more. This is deodorant
Hot sauce, that's kind of a hot sauce bottle. What is a vacuum? Um
I think that's the best we're gonna get
There we go. Yep. That's better
This is a little like at the top
Okay, this is gonna be a ketchup bottle cockpit's gonna go health. I didn't want more health
Double health
I I don't know. It's just just a fucking among us character. I don't even know. I don't i'm gonna make sure I hide it though
Okay, here we go. We need I want health
and speed
Is there anything that's double health?
I'm just gonna make a shitload of these and just absolutely wipe them off
Health speed health speed. There we go
Okay military time. All right out of the ketchup bottle
I'm gonna have a fucking monster monster missile. This is a computer mouse
Okay, and then that this thing's called war crime
Jesus
This thing's insane rocket pop rocket pop rocket pop. What a good call. That was what a good call
Excellent fucking call excellent work
Wonderful job
It's kind of going into the ground. Hold on
Okay, here we go
Need red white and blue
Do you have any big solid lines red white and blue ketchup? Well, no, it's a rocket pop now
I don't think I can do it. You need more health. I mean this could just be just like a yummy popsicle
It doesn't have to be exactly that that looks like a pretty yummy popsicle. You need more health. All right, i'll put it on
It's like a blue raspberry popsicle. It needs a popsicle stick. I got you. Oh, I got you. Don't worry cotton candy. Perfect
Okay, should I make it pink then actually kind of I don't know. I like that need way more health. All right. Yeah
Yes
Oh, it's wonderful, but not pink pink pink and then like light pink
Pepto rat here we go. That's easier. That's better cotton candy on a stick naked mole rat tank
Whatever, whatever i'm done
Any more health I think that's double health because right now there's a shitload of military power on here. What a health
26 health more get rid of the guns should I
Less speed more health and guns doesn't even move
Okay, so I got 60 percent 25 percent. I need a little bit more health. Okay, that's 32 percent health
It's 340 health and then 31 military power. What's that get better wheels? What do these have?
These ones are these ones are health and speed that these are the best ones. Yeah, these are the best ones guys
Legs, no, no legs. It's not supposed to be a rat. It's supposed to be cotton candy
No rat legs. He's cotton candy
It's cotton candy cotton candy rat. There you go
35 health 52 military power. It's a tail. No too much speed. No, no tail doesn't need a tail. All right, let's go
Okay, I need a military. Let's go build it save military vehicle. Where's the military vehicle? How do I play with it?
How do I get it out? I need more attack. Oh, I need more rats. They're okay. They're okay. I need another one
I need a thousand more. Hold on. I won
Kill kill kill kill kill kill kill kill kill kill kill kill kill kill
Kill kill why not? You only have three
We're fine autumn left pause button, oh
All right, thanks kill it
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah
What's the video the guy like on yeah, wow, wow, wow, wow, wow, wow like a reality show
I did it you think he's getting away. I'll stay here stay here defend. It's from survivor. Okay, everybody heal
Relax. I got 6900 bucks. I
This is not looking good yellow needs to I gotta take out some of these things yellow is military and they're
Fuck is that?
Something that I made
The first time we see it is this far in oh my god shit
I'm contacting them our military gathers at your borders. We agree you only to mock you
Mmm, we admire your wide tracks of land. Let's trade
We've had our differences. Look, I've just bought this place. I don't know what your conflict was between I
Don't even know what color he was
Was he was blue? I don't know what your conflict was with green, but there's no reason I don't know who that was
Do not attack me. I'm trying to start it. I'm trying to set up a trade route
Trade route we do not need to trade with well, then you're dead
Okay. Well, fuck you then fine. Okay, that's fine. Good. Cool. You I'm gonna kill everybody in the entire city
That's fine. Any nation that gains more than a single city will appear in your communications panel
hover over any nation's icon to see your relationship status check the reasons for their current attitude or conflict them directly the nation's too big
That's why they're upset about it. Our influence continues to expand
Our crusade has added the city of de jay Varan to our nation. Who is this? Who is this?
Red nation and that us
Aren't we red? We have need of your forces. Will you fight on our behalf? You are crimson not red. Oh
We need of we have need of your forces. Will you fight for us which city will you fight for the city of?
Deaxius I would like for you to fight and attack the city of how mutual lied how mutely
We could help you out of for a price. How about forty four hundred bucks? You got a deal
You got a deal one of your cities is under attack
We could use your help. Would you declare war on the orange nation?
Well, you know, maybe if you give back two thousand of the dollars I gave you maybe
Will you declare war?
Sweeten that deal a little bit and you got a deal sounds good. Glad you had. Thank you. Thanks for the thanks
We're you I paid you twenty two hundred dollars now to do that to the four thousand. Thank you. Let's go
War has been declared. I need to turn over here start firing. Where is it? Where is it? Great, please?
The hell's this I've declared war on orange. Are you going in wait for me? Wait for me. I have I have tanks here
Wait for me before you go in that's a partnership can only help spread our faith. We accept good you going in
I think they're going in
It's time to show us progress of respect we demand 3100 spore bucks
You didn't even do anything fine take it the epic creepalope the melon is attacking this city
What the hell is that? All right, we're going in
Caps in the city. Holy shit. This is perfect cap to the city
This thing has instant killing laser fire bombs
Caps to the city. Holy shit. He's killing things instantly. Oh
Go this way go this way go this way get away from him after the city. Why is this thing even here?
Why is this here? What's under attack? What the who's attacking me? Why what about my spice thing?
Yeah, I mean can I convert this to a military city this thing is just an economic city
I don't know what to do. What's happening over here. It's not the breaking bad theme
Um, I want to talk to let's talk to orange this planet trembles before our mighty Armada
You will not survive prefer for war is they're about to they're about to get wiped off the face of the earth
What's happening? I kind of did I kind of no idea what's going on. One of your cities is under attack. Um
Okay, you're spice geyser, I think I'm figuring out why I stopped playing at this part coming over here
This is a confusing mess. You said you stopped at the tribes. You lost a city. It's like going too fast
It's like just it's yeah, I don't even know it's how I there's two different reds
That already fucked me up. There's two reds. They're your crimson. What I cannot see the difference in these colors. There's no difference
That's the same image is literally that's literally the exact same color on the map. There's no difference at all
I don't own that even has been captured
Where's Haven is this Haven?
This is just like we all just took out the game of risk and like snorted lines of coke and start screaming at each other
I've no idea what the hell's happening. Okay, this is there's an orange and a yellow yellow is down here in Australia
This is Bloomin that's all they have yellow has Bloomin orange has
Haven and
Humilitarily and then this blue over here and then this crimson up here and then this red I have one military city
So I fucked up. I should have had all military cities. Okay, um
Four hours customizing only to lose in 20 minutes. It's it went very it went very quickly
It went very quickly
Maybe I should contact blue. I'm gonna contact blue. See what they're up to. Wait, what? I can't contact blue anymore
Let me contact yellow
This is blue. What's the where am I? What that was a yellow indicate? What happened? What's going on? What?
Yeah, I and tell me I'm confused. Tell me I'm the one that's confused your civilization perplexes. What are your intentions?
We need your forces. Will you fight for us?
What city?
We would like for you to go after I thought was literally yellow when I clicked on it
Frizdov, no, I don't want you to take Frizdov. What do I want Haven? No, cuz Haven's mine. It was I
Only have one thing now. All right, send it to Haven. I don't have 56. I'm gonna lose
Fuck it's blue again. I wear my land vehicles, please
Can I take this shit back and the fact that the whole thing's a fucking sphere does not help
It's like this. I like I'm going down with my cat my mouth. Look what I'm going on the mini map. What the fuck? Oh
Hey, no, don't put whatever we demand money. I don't have any money. I don't have anything left
What are the cheat codes? Just give me a ten million dollars. I don't get this this part like him sucks
I can't build anything. Most people love this part. No, they do not
Kill it kill this thing
Destroy it, please
Come on epic cantaloupe. Please destroy the city
Whose is this? You know what? I think the problem is here
This is from too many friends over your house. That's what the problem is with this
And this is the problem I had since the very beginning
They were one two three four five that what six seven people on the map on a map this small
Too many fucking people over your house to play risk
You can't play risk with six or seven people like that's too many people you play it with like three or four people four people
Not six. That's too many friends over your house. It's too spread out to be fair
The game is very hard while playing when you go in blind. I mean I I don't care
Do something I'm so overwhelmed. I don't even know where to start. It's like too many things have happened
I try to make like okay
I tried to make a trade route with two different cities and then like the world collapsed. What the fuck?
It was like I'd like to have a trade route
Yeah, everyone's dead your world is exploding make more factories. I don't even know what the factories do. Oh
Remember you made that monster. Well, why is it here?
Why is it just sitting outside their gates?
Is it asleep?
At war
My god, holy shit, can I take this?
This is ready to take this is what you fucking deserve you deserve you deserve this shit
Oh my goodness. What is happening now? I have do I have is this mine? This is mine. Okay, I need a
Military I don't I don't know. I have no idea what's going on. I think I lose I'm pretty sure I just lost
Yellow nation is captured. The red nation is gone. Oh
How do I skip to the other stage take Haven back? I can't I feel like restart
Look at how much shit I'm surrounded by you don't have to restart. I don't
Control shift see more money bribe orange. Oh sift see bribe orange
more money
We come offering gifts. Do you accept? Here's four thousand bucks
We come offering gifts of house four thousand more dollars
What the fuck will you like me yet? You are no longer at war with the orange nation. Nice
All right. Now I'm gonna buy all the cities with all the fake money that I have
I don't care. I don't care. I don't care. I don't care. I don't care. I don't care. I don't care
I don't even care. I don't care. Ask me. Ask me if I care. Do I care? I don't care
Good, ask me. This thing is still attacking their city and then I'm gonna buy these motherfuckers
Worst gamer moment. I don't know that's day. I don't care. I know I don't care at all
I don't like this part this part stinks to me. I'm gonna buy orange and then
explain in detail of why I
Willing to bet that if there's 12,000 people here right now, it's just under 12,000
Those who that played this game before you probably don't remember
You getting to this part in the game and going I don't I'm just want to skip this
And then just giving yourself $50,000 is going to the space stage
Yeah, I think a lot of you just don't remember. They don't want to trade with me
We admire you and we want to give you free money. You like me yet your people our people admire you
We have more gifts for you. Would you like to be our friend and trade with us? Don't please don't oh my fucking god
Damn it, dude
This thing's got to go. How do I declare you're a threat to us your nation's too big?
Well, can I buy you we set up a trade route with the other guy?
Blue listen to me trade route. Hope you lose cheating
What is going on over here?
Middle is hard. This middle road is the hardest for this stage. Wait, did I get bad RNG and got in the worst spot?
That's an excuse
Here's me. Would you like to trade?
great
Trade with the city and by the way, I will handsomely pay for your city and your capital
Is it gone?
Economic is the easiest. Yeah, but you guys I think you guys are misunderstanding that like I've never played this before
Yeah, when you were like 15, you probably came home from school every day. You probably played this a thousand times
This is the first time I've ever seen this. I went to the creature stage
I've made the guys like elongated his tail and made a big head and then I never played the game ever again
Cheat more. Oh god. Damn it. The orange took this but what is this? What's this?
You're at war with orange. How do I declare I get stop declaring war?
What's the cheat to like drop a bomb?
Give me the bomb cheat. I want it
Unlock super weapons. Thank you. Oh, this is
I don't get off the steam overlay
Nine hours, holy shit nine full hours. Has it been that long?
global merger
happened whoa, I
Guarantee you half of you guys got to the stage and knew that existed and just pressed it and by the way
What yeah what kind of that's just for people to skip like here to launch your space
Exploration program if we sent it to the creator to create a ship for your maiden voyage modification can be made later. Nice
Mental gymnastics Andy the choices are your evolutionary history of go. It's just a straight line. I didn't do anything
That's an endgame thing your traits affect not only your inherent abilities
Okay, I beat this in multiple times as a baby without you weren't a baby. You were like at least 12
Creators are in it for the profit. Their only allegiance is to the almighty spore buck
Instantly makes trading systems available for pretty cool. All right, I legit beat this when I was 14
Yeah, you know how developed your brain is when you're 14. That's fine
You probably played this you probably played this every day
look if me and a 14 year old were in a knitting contest and
That 14 year old knitted every day and it was super into knitting and they did it every day after school
They could get any they were really really into it. They're gonna beat me in a knitting contest
You could take a 10 year old that can juggle right the juggle every day and you put me in
Okay, you're in a juggling contest with that 11 year old. That's an 11 year old. You'll be I don't I don't know anything about juggling
You're gonna beat me 11 year old. You're good at juggling
I have not learned any juggling video video games are your career
Not this one. I
What do you what does that even mean?
That doesn't matter all games are different
Every game is different from another what that are you really?
This game is wildly different than the last game that we played on this channel
Wait, I'm supposed to know how to play every single video game that's ever ever released
Europe I'm a professional
Bore-streamer, this is the exact same game resume. You should be banned from every game. This is a kid's game
It doesn't matter out of a kid's game or not. It's the this isn't even a kid's game
Will Wheaton when he made this when he like got on stage
He was like this is gonna be the fucking most revolutionary game for everybody to play and everyone was like, holy shit
This is awesome. Whatever his name is not what's his name?
Not
Will Wright, yes, there it is. Thank you. Will Wright didn't get on stage into the going to the microphone
I'm gonna introduce my latest kids game
This one is for children. It's called sport. It's for kids
It's like gonzo didn't get on stage after that by the gonzo is not for kids either gonzo sick
I love that if that makes me a little kid. I don't care. I fucking love gonzo
Anyways to complete that statement
McDonald's is better than Wendy's more than half the time. I like eating there more than I like eating at Wendy's. I
Can't believe you cheated
You guys have fun I like having fun with you guys whoo, I like that bully button
Videogames are your career
Unprofessional gamer. Hey, you know somebody could tell you I
Streaming it's my career not video games
The video game really matter a lot of the time think about that. Hold on a second. Think about that. It's a good question
I'm an e-clown. I'm not a video game. I'm not a professional video game streamer. I'm a goddamn e-clown
Get it, right. You cheated not only game, but yourself. Yeah, I did and I would do it again, too
I would do it again. I would do it again right now. I would press ctrl shift Z
ctrl sip shift C and type in
Dominate galaxy and win. I want to make this a rock-a-pop. I don't think I can though. I kind of like this little guy
Okay, but the spaceship looks sick Jeremy
It's worth hacking in space because it's really really hard to get money
Well, I mean, I'm probably only gonna just drive around and just look at stuff
The space days sucks to be honest. This part sucks. This part is bad. I'm gonna be really mad at this
I'm a duster. Ooh
Ooh, I like that. It's cool. If you play with the tools, okay goes to 11. Hmm sausage phone. I
Want some no, it's very bright. Should I be that bright? I feel like that's not a good idea
Well people just be able to see me. Okay, and wait, there's oars. Why would I need this on a spaceship? Sonic reducer? Oh
Oh cool. All right. That's so cool. Oh cool. There you go
Well, I like it finding earth is the end game. Did you spoil spore for me?
Wait till fucking will
Wait, not will we why did I say will Wheaton? Okay. Now I need
Frusters. Ooh, it's good last wings. Ooh, these are cool, too. No, I like the simplicity of this
Well dog shit. Oh, he said dog coin. Oh, whatever. Oh, I like I like the McDonald's one, too
Mmm, which maybe I'll just do a pre-made keep it white. Ooh, that's cool. This is Rockwell's modern life
I want this I think I'm ready. I might want to add a little bit one or more detail here a
Ventilation to add gills, but I like it. It's a turtle ship. It's pretty cool. I like it. All right, you ready Rick and Morty
It's so easy to visit make so many people that
You know
I was actually thinking I was gonna buy a Rick and Morty t-shirt
And I was gonna just turn on the cam and not say anything about it and just it was a shirt
I had on just watch you guys freak the fuck out
Lift off you've successfully developed a ship capable of spaceflight
The heavens beckon in the cosmos awaits the universe is at your fingertips if you can learn to fly this thing me
Captain German at 8 5
Welcome to the pinnacle of existence the final frontier the wildest wildest West space
You control the ship and from this vintage lead your race from planet beyond civilization to a vast galactic Empire
Let's look at how you progress
This bar tracks your progress towards badges you earn as well as your proximity to the center of the galaxy
Mish and God nobody heard that mission control on the planet surface is anxious to speak to you
Let's learn how to communicate this short-range video communicator is your contact to those in the world below
You must be in the planet's orbit to open the line. Okay, the flashing signal means you haven't I didn't fart
I just burped really loud under my breath and leaned back
So the limiter didn't pick it up is an incoming transmission if it's blinking. Okay, so it's blinking
Congratulations cadet. You've got a fine ride there
We're still adding new equipment to your ship, but we should have it ready for space travel in no time
Have you flown a spaceship before no, well, nothing like a test flight while the entire population of the germa might of planet
Zircon looks on what do you say ready to earn your captain's badge?
Yeah, each city on planet Zircon
Has launched a giant orb in celebration of our first spaceship really you can't miss them
Take your ship on a spin around the planet to seven of our cities fly through the orbs to break them
Okay, your immediate mission goals are tracked here in the mini mission log
You can track up to three missions in mini form from the full mission log by hitting the L key
Okay, I through the orbs the right mouse button use the arrow keys to fly
See if you can crash fly through the orbs or more
64 it kind of is fresh joke
Come on
Job cadet worth flying like that. You'll make captain in no time now that you're an ace at flying
We're ready for you to use some of the sophisticated tools. Just whatever it will happen. It won't happen
We've been working on the ability to scan the planets and animals you discover on your travels
Looks like this tool comes just in the nick of time
The sporepedia record of one of our own animals recently became corrupted at the same time the animals started exhibiting some odd symptoms
We need you to scan the animal so we can collect more information about the species
The creature in question is exhibiting a glowing tail an odd glowing trail
Just wipe that part out and rewrite over it
Your ship has been equipped with a radar tool that can be turned off and on in the main tools panel
It will point to emission targets and items of interest when on a planet surface
The radar beeps faster when you're closer to your target. I'm laughing
I keep glancing at what you guys are writing. It's like the scan tool. Oh my god
There's a lot of tools your tools panel is sorted by type
Your scan tools found in the main tools panel look up your scan tool by clicking on it or just press 2
Okay, scan to enter the information targeted so we have to find somebody remember when I was down there and I was one of these
Get them pick them up
Let's get doing
Execute him. What am I supposed to do?
Scan him. I'm
Trying to left click on him. Oh, well, it's always right click. What do you want to do next? Okay, quite valuable
It is now third or so. We need to examine the species more closely ship is equipped with an abduction beam
abduct a species
Use the abduction beam found in the cargo panel to collect this creature for further research
Make sure you deploy the tool long enough until the creature is fully secured in the ship's cargo bay
Stopping too soon before your cargo is secured may result in less than desirable circumstances for the victim. Oh, I mean the specimen
Okay, we're getting drunk. Let's go get him. Okay this one here. All right, let's get him
Your active tool is shown in your spaceport your ship portrait
deactivated tool press escape I kill him what I clicked on him I
abducted a diseased animal
abduct a ball-luing animal
Drop off the ball-luing within the city walls
Measurably fine work cadet. You've provided us with excellent specimen to research probe twice abduct once
I always say now what it appears the specimen you collected was sick and is infested with a virus that is capable of spreading at
An alarming rate it could endanger our entire ecosystem. Okay, take out the infected creatures while while avoiding the healthy ones
Look at how many tabs there are down there
Be careful you point that laser. It's capable of destroying buildings vehicles and other spaceships. Oh dear
Okay, I have the laser equipped and be careful only kill the ones that are here
Damn, okay
More over here
Don't fire at me. What are you doing? I'm in the air over here
Well
You
You want to kill this guy? I mean that wanted me to kill him remove one more diseased animal
Why is it making me go this way?
Where they're diseased? Yeah, I know but where's this last one over here kill everyone from the city?
Psycho, that's kind of weird. It was pointing at that other guy
Okay, that's that I need to go BRB one more time because Otto wants to go outside. He just went hey
He doesn't yell to me. I'll be right back final BRB of the night. I would assume you're back. I have returned
I got some chocolate while Otto took a poop. I'm just sitting there watching him
Out there just eating chocolate while he's shitting and I don't know it was I didn't mean for that to happen, but it did
Somebody just writes thanks for sharing
Yeah, that story did not need to be told like I didn't need to tell you that
No, none of you needed to know that happened. I don't know why I decided to tell you there was no relevance to do to explain that
Anyways, let's continue. What we're doing. We were examining creatures
Laudable job. You're on the right stuff
You've earned your homeworld's respect and confidence
We want you to pile this spaceship and lead our race forward into galactic explanation and glory. It's getting stuck
You've earned the badge and title of captain. It's coconut. That's why I thought it was weird
I always feel like I'm eating fucking like shaved wood
Chips our scientists have developed an interplanetary drive for your ship, but you'll need to install it first
Use the trade panel to buy and sell tools
spice and rares
Items from your cargo that can be sold will appear at the bottom of the trade panel. Okay
I can't it's still there click on the items in the trade panel. You wish to buy and sell I'll take this
Alright, let's do it
Let's go see space
Stop bragging about eating a coconut eating chocolate coconut. What's that?
Okay, get your spandex suit we suspect you're not alone in the galaxy. We picked up strange radio signals. Let's do it
It's time for interplanetary space travel. You've earned the badge and title of captain
Okay, your collection your Michael gives you access to your mission log badge clicking tools and rears. Hmm. Oh my god
This is like a the world of Warcraft achievement book. He's this loser unlocked by earning badges
This is cool. Some tools are consumable and require restocking others who's a permanent. Okay, cool
We're not gonna see any of this by the way. All right, cool. Let's go use the mouse wheel to exit the solar system. Whoa
Whoa, why do planet Dorges? I read I've
Dorges, okay, let me go in and it Dorges cool. Something is showing up on the ship's radar alien
It's a crash spacecraft that is emitting a strange radio signal. Why don't you use the scan tool to investigate the crash site? Okay
Okay, this is a cool planet. I wish I played here. All right scan it. What happened?
You wish you could retroactively go back and make a game score higher
You know how much I've fought with the fact that Outer Wilds was an 89 aliens
But no signs of life looks like they drew some type of cryptic map before they died
Wait, the wreck has triggered a transfer beam. Some items are coming aboard played out of wilds for like two hours
What I beat the whole game missiles and interstellar drive
Which seems to have an unknown stars coordinates programmed into it the wrecks damage looks like it came from a fight
The ship must have been sent from some of the planet to get help. No game is perfect outer wilds close
Well, I said 89 but I think that's cuz I was just very mad at flying into the Sun like the thousand times
It's probably 91. Okay, leave the solar system in a galactic view
What the hell it's responding to a beacon from a nearby star that matches the coordinates in his memory
This must be for the home planet. Why do planet Voral a hell avilus planet Voral we go in here
What the fuck? This is what this end game is like. It's a world to keep going into in here
Oh my god on top of it. The end game is running errands between space colonies
Nothing's glowing on the radar. It's a lot of fun, but it's really long
Well, at least I got to see it scanning the ruins may help reveal what happened get it
End of the spore voice. It's coming. It's coming pretty soon
Not immediately, but it's gonna happen soon
Activities on the radar. Oh shit other spacecraft the scam was to trigger the colony's defenses
These drones don't look friendly wait an incoming transmission
warning grok's intruders to
gronk's intruders all grok's intruders will be terminated initializing self-defense called gronk's
999 all grok's intruders will be terminated. We're not grok's all grok's will be intruders. Let's get out of here
Okay returned to your home world back to home world
Execute grok's number six sixty six or wild is like a seven. No, I disagree with that
Radio signals emanating from the star fly in and explore it. Isn't this where I live?
Oh, I got red spices
It's going bink bink. I was doing that mission accomplished
We knew we weren't alone in the galaxy trace of an extinct civilization hostile security drones in the grok's
It's obvious that we must continue our exploration of the galaxy and potentially prepare for hostilities
In order to do so we'll need to set up colonies as basis of operation
Scientists are already reverse engineering the interstellar drive to replicate its technology
We've also developed a city device for your ship
We'll pick up signals of other sentient life in the galaxy indicated by radio signals over stars that you target
We need you at the helm of our space program. Mm-hmm expand the empire and get more wealth
There's some volunteers to be part of the crew. Okay. Well, I'm
Leave me alone calling me. Okay. How do I establish a colony? Excellent placing a colony is easy
After flying to planet Neem on
Select the colony tool that has been added to your colonization tool bin and place the colony on land near a spice geyser
It'll instantly unpack creating a colony. No assembly required
I want to make contact with a colony to make sure the citizens packed in there
unpacked safely, okay
Bye, we're good to go to planet Neem on he hook you who control the spice controls the universe. All right, where's
Thuja to system star map filters my empire. Oh, okay. Okay missions, right?
Thuja to zoom out all the way baby. All right, holy shit. Well, I'm not seeing any of that
I gotta go to Neem on
Planets in green orbit paths are easier to terraform and colonize than planets on red or blue orbit paths
I have question question for you. So spore the game
They made a space simulation game and then added like a funny character creator onto the bottom of it
That what I did how this worked this feels like way more detailed than the rest of the entire game
Okay, there's Neem on base mode is a slog
This is 90% of the rest of the game 90% of the game from here on is the game
Does that mean that we did 10% of the game? Wow
Colonies can be established on any planet from barren moons to lush terrors go or three oasis
Fruitful colonies mine spice that can be traded. I said we plant a colony near the spice geysers
Let's get shot. There we go. I
Used to want place for so badly, but I only had the weird DS game. That's right. They did make a weird DS game
Didn't they I forgot about that completely what hold on?
I want to look this up. You just brought back a memory that I've buried for so long
Spore creatures. Yeah, I do remember this it was weird too. You have your own Empire cool. Oh, this is cool
We're in the endgame now Peter. So I mean, this is like cool
Report back to the home world report back to your home world for glory. All right, I love doing running around doing spice trades
Yeah, this is cool. What if I go get some I'm gonna go here. Why not? Let's go to Tantarok
Spore hero arena, this is cool. Cool. All right dark spore. Yeah, that was a
Arpg right that one was cool. This was no man's sky a decade before no man's sky. That's true
There's a no man's sky fun. You collected spice. It's a valued commodity. It cool depends. It's better now
Yeah, it's supposed to be fun now
Be counting on you to visit this colony frequently to collect spice from it. Oh shit. You have to actually physically go there
Catherine we've intercepted transmissions that we believe are coming from other advanced beings in the galaxy
We need to investigate attempt to establish first contact use the Shetty tool equipped on your ship to help find them
Okay, let's go. We've been able to pinpoint the exact location of these transmissions
You need to explore a bit. All right, let's go get the hell out of here
Find an alien Empire find another spacefaring Empire and communicate with them
You will know they are spacefaring once you get close enough to their harm star system
Establish contact with them using the short-range video communicator. All right. All right, let's go. Let's find them
Where are they they on future too? Oh shit. That's your colony, right? Right? Oh, hold on over here
Look, I'm trying to hear the radio. No radio radio means nothing. It's a visual. Okay
Nobody over here over to I hear something somebody over there. I'm right here somebody's here
Big's equation was right a living alien race
We're not alone looks like they have sent an envoy to greet you talk to them. Welcome. Welcome
Always a pleasure pleasure to meet another friend provided. You are a friend, of course
Give us your name. I am from the gerbomite. I come in peace
Behold I am from the great and mighty planet Zircan call off your fighter before I blasted into pieces behold
I am from the great and mighty planet of Zircan
We agree that you are absolutely tremendous. Will you spend money now?
I'm not as small as you think but let's continue
Yes. Yes, happy to help happy to help. What can we do for you? I get my ship repaired, please and my ship recharged
Please and let's trade. Oh
Okay, I've got some red spices. What do you think about that?
You have way too happy with that. That's like you have four aces in your hand at the poker table
Um, is it my getting I can scammed
Diplomacy I'd like to know about your race. Please accept a gift so we can be friends
I like to establish a trade route. Tell me more about your race
Thanks to the philosophy of prosperity. We the Kurgle Empire love everything. We love our empire. We love other empires
We love happy people. We love unhappy people
Most of all, we love our profit margins and we love all the other things because they contribute to our margins
Okay, you want to work with us?
We offer rewards equivalent to many important professions such as dock worker in dishwasher
I need a quest so good of you in your stature to visit one as insignificant as us
If it wouldn't be too much trouble, we have a favor would you travel to planet?
Teebo nor rawr and see what opportunities might await only if it would not be too much trouble
Okay, commanding a spacecraft is only half the responsibilities of a space captain
The other half requires planetside tactical skills where you and your crew will need to leave your spaceship and beam down to planets
Okay, you have to beam down like Star Trek. Let's go once you get to
Teebo nor rawr. You will need to beam down to the planet. Oh, that sounds like fun
Is it that Teebo on Teebo Ronar?
Turn to the homeworld. Okay
The allies and enemies filter will show you the regions of space controlled by friend or foe the Empire filter will show all stars
They're occupied by alien races. I do have the space DLC. I got it for the parts mainly
All right return to the homeworld and I'll go there it's too far
How do you compare pointer addresses and see plus plus using the modules operator turbo?
You could put a briefcase on the table right now with a million dollars in cash in it
I would not tell you how I would not have any idea the download from your data recorder is quite amazing captain
We had no idea other spacefaring civilizations were so close by
We are gonna establish our place in the galactic community. Oh, I'm in we produce spice and record amounts resulting in surplus
We need to look for potential buyers. All right, I get it. That sounds pretty lucrative trade partners
Let's go make a deal. All right, visit vat tego on planet tip on our RR
Okay, I'm planet bo runar. We're going where am I this is bulbar to visit vat tego and tip over an R
Where is it? It's the flag. There it is at tego and adventurers
my god, um
Okay, cool. Uh
Energy meter tracks how much energy some of the abilities using how much is stored and recharge my batteries cool
All right. Oh, you're good. Sounds like you're having a panic attack. What hey somehow these look worse box cock
I'm like that. This looks horrible. But whatever cock streamer talk. Oh, sorry. Yeah. Yeah his end of the stream voice, by the way
Yeah, we're at the end of the stream voice. I'm losing me you add weapons. Yep, a hundred percent end of the stream voice
Shit I don't have any weapons though. He's losing it. No, I'm good. I'm good. I'm good. I don't have any do I need weapons?
I thought this is a diplomatic mission
Imagine there's a conflict going on in this beams down and dabs your path will gain experience once you complete this adventure
Okay, let's take a look you get batteries and generators. There's the map. It's a progress bar. I
Talk just GTA music it is
But you still sing I mean the quartermaster. That's our 2d2. Come here. Come here. Come here. Come here. Come here
Come here guy
Robot shall rule the earth already drop kick this thing. I feel like I'm playing an
MMO right now. I feel like I'm playing the city of heroes
Big low just arrived. And why can I save it after the head bought? All right
Spaceport Authority and it's your servant
Welcomes you captain if you look to become a great space captain
You've got it right you come to the right place to be afraid to have a look around and introduce yourself to the local life forms
If you're left the merchant will notify you of his latest merchandise and how to take possession of them
Behind me the space traveler will inform you of the interstellar customs for obtaining new assignments
This is way more detailed than all the other ones combined
Crew members on the right. Okay. All right. Why can I save it? I
Dance still this is all DLC. Oh, I love this music
Okay, being allies with the empires will add them to your fleet you can beam down
Cool, all right dance. Let's dance. You got moves like that
Often truly awful still can't pose. No, I can't
Hello, I'm the guy that sells stuff
Need crew members. They're over here
You want batteries I can sell you batteries this is you just completed a mission in GTA 3 plus respect
Wow, you do look cool. You look really cool
And take on adventuring missions and shit. Oh
It's gonna save the game. Okay. Goodbye. There's another one. There's a look at this screen. Um, oh geez
Energy slash I want to go back down there. I want to be meet back down here. Holy shit up to five hours
I thought he didn't like this game. Wait, what? Oh
You must have came in here when I was defending myself as an e-clown
Imagine like imagine listening to that conversation. Oh, I'm not a video game streamer. I'm an e-clown
Okay, I don't stream video games. I mean I played them, but I'm a claw. I'm an e-clown
I don't care. I would have to be in full makeup on the phone
I think full clown makeup with a controller in my hand like a GameCube controller and a cigarette in my mouth
Trying to keep up with this with all the shitty that all these kids like these days
I'm just smushing my face in his ass
Goodbye, you know what? I'm done. I'll see you later. Let's see
Music they I say it's right before that Sunday stream, please Sunday stream, please. Sorry. You're gonna be very disappointed
there's no Sunday stream and
It's not even a Monday stream. There is a Tuesday stream
There is a Tuesday Wednesday Thursday stream Oh
Yeah, I'll be back on Tuesday, right? But today's Saturday, right Sunday, but yeah, I'll be back on Tuesday
I'm gonna try to get Pikmin 2 ready
That's the plan. I can't take this anymore. I gotta get out of this wrong thing
I'm gonna try to play Pikmin 2 on. Oh, that's really good. It's from that painting game such art
I'm gonna just retire if you hate us so much
What the hell oh look at that it's the bear back-to-back cool
We've seen a couple of those if for some if for some reason I do not play Pikmin on Tuesday
I'll play it on Wednesday or Thursday, but the plan is to try to get Pikmin ready
Try to have everything set up and play Pikmin 2
If it's not Pikmin 2 on Tuesday, then it'll be a mystery game and then we'll play and hopefully beat Pikmin 2
Next week play Nintendo land by yourself. Will you beat spore?
No, this is probably the last time you're gonna see spore. It was very fun
I heavily enjoyed my time except for about
except for the for the part of
It was like a 10-minute portion of the civilization phase
Had to skip it because I didn't like it and I wanted to get out of there
What would you give spore for a rating 89 now 87?
Too much of water. It's not an 87. It's on it realistically
The crew okay the creature part the creature creator is like a 95
the video game of spore is like a 4 if I have to be totally honest, but like the creature stuff is
No, I would say even like 98 when that first came out. That was such a big deal
but like the video game portion of it is
Mmm, like a 4.8 for like the video game portion. So you average those two together. No, no, no, that's not for it
Let's say 6 a 9.8 and a 6 together is an 8.7. It's important bits about thousand-year door. There is I mean
Let me look at let me okay. Here's some bits. Jerma film yourself eating an entire jar of olives now. That's not thousand-year door
Uh chat don't tell them just take your time and have fun Jerma. You don't need to rush
Where did your brain is bad Jerma? I think you want the game's journalist difficulty
I don't see anything about thousand-year door. That was like my favorite part of the whole night
If you want to play a thousand-year door, please play the way you want not the way others people say to do it
I've been told that I'm gonna get heavily backseated in thousand-year door. I'm ready for it whenever we play it
It's a bug for the original thousand-year door game
It's very important that before you start playing you take a stinky whatever there was the spore city level also filled with concrete
I don't know. I thought that was a photo of me for a second
Alright, I'll see you guys on on Tuesday. If it's not Pikmin 2 then it'll be something else
Expect Pikmin 2 within the next two or three streams. That was spore. It was a lot of fun
Thanks for watching as always everybody. Thanks for hanging out for as long as you have
Yeah, it is getting late Eastern time. So I know a lot of people are you know getting tired
So let me get to the the credits a little bit more art. Here's all the subs from today
Resubs gifted subs everything. Thanks a lot as always everybody. Let them roll
You inspired me to reinstall spore and play it again
It's I mean if I joke about a lot of the shit in there you guys know, it's just jokes, right?
It doesn't deserve a four about it. I mean it does but it doesn't right. It's a fucked up
I know I know how long I'm gonna try it. Can I grab it?
Hey, I fixed it. We said they would literally give me a copy of thousand-year door if you need it
I will not take it. I appreciate it though. I
Do not I will not I do not accept anything from anyone. Don't just let you know for the future about two copies
Except for money. I mean you got you you got me you got my what am I gonna?
I don't have I have nothing to say you got me there
Well, but money also doesn't I mean look the the systems in place for twitch for you to send bits or subscribe
Is not I have to we have to correspond you have to send me mail take the money. He just wants money
See you guys on Tuesday
We should raid. Well, yeah, we're right again. Where we gonna go. Where should we go? He's streaming right now. I'm trying to
Remember who who have we not rated in a while or maybe somebody knew we knew
No, I mean, don't I feel like I feel like we just good
We cut I feel like we just run around in a circle on this channel. We knew
hmm
Gus Gus Gus Gus Johnson Gus wait Gus Johnson is streaming. Hold on. Oh shit. Oh, he's fucking hilarious
Yeah, let's go to Gus Johnson. I've seen a bunch of his videos
Yeah, let's go make sure I spell the name correctly
Gus Johnson. That's Johnson. Yeah, go say hello
Go raid
I'll see you guys on Tuesday. Have fun
Yeah, I didn't even know you knew who he was
He's got some very popular videos that have made the rounds a few times
But I don't know personally but seen a couple of the videos
Yeah, go say hello
Good night. Goodbye
Take care