I hear it's a good game. I hear it's an incredible franchise. I haven't played
Metal Gear Solid since I was probably 16. I played the first one and I played the
second one. I don't know the story and it's become so complicated and so
intertwined at this point. I seriously don't even know where I would even start.
Dozens of hours of cutscenes, tons of reading. I don't got time to read. You
always got time to read nowadays, you know? So what I did is I picked up this.
This is, got this online, a comprehensive Metal Gear NeuroStory
Electrodump. They have them for all kinds of things. This is for Metal Gear
because obviously the story is so complicated like we've talked about. So
that goes into the CD tray. I think it's just a standard disc at the sole. Now we put
on the electrodes. That goes there. Okay. Standard USB. It goes right in the back
of your computer. Just like that. That should be it. Ow, my teeth. Ow. Okay. Let's all
get hype for Metal Gear Solid 5. Get hype. Play button.
Big Boss was the boss. No, the boss was the boss and then Big Boss, Big Boss Man
took over because he had to kill her because the third game into the fifth
game, the fourth game in the worse than second. God damn it. I gotta watch it
again. I gotta start over. I gotta start over. I'll get it this time because I just,
it was getting confusing when they were all clones and shit. One more time. Get
hype. Get hype for Metal Gear Solid 5. Get hype.
What's happening? Where am I? Oh, no, no, no, no, no. Metal Gear Solid story. I must
not have hit play. I must have fallen asleep. I got time. It's for the launch of
Metal Gear. Metal Gear Solid 5, the launch party.