Hey what's going on everybody? Germa and MLC Stealth here. We're going to be playing some CSGO Live and I'm not sure how well he's going to do but I know I'm not going to do that well. But that's okay.
Oh I'm already dead. Oh that's one. So I'm not going to do very well. You better spectate me. I'm going to go in a tirade. This guy right here. Oh get locked down.
Oh that's his name. I just like said the guy's name while I shot him. Anybody? What do we got? Did you not mean to? I said his name and I was subconsciously saying it and I said it by looking at it. That was weird.
Oh. There's nobody back there. What are you doing? I'm checking to see if there's any spawn brats. I don't know. This isn't Call of Duty. There might be somebody that's like AFK.
I got to be careful here. There's only me and someone. You don't even have Dead Silence on you. You're just running rampart. Rampant. Our teammate's dead. Oh so it's a 1v1 huh? Where'd he die? Oh okay. This is where it gets interesting.
Pick up that sniper. Hey just hit E. Control me. I'm a bot. I'm trying. Oh get out of town. Oh yeah nice crouching. Nice 60% of the team killing.
I didn't really introduce me but you introduced me for me so it's alright. Well introduce yourself for your help. Hey everybody.
Alright that's. Hey everybody. Wait I already have everything? Oh yeah so we tried doing this live commentary once but about 14 seconds into it my computer said no and it just like cancelled out of Counter Strike.
So as I was saying before we're both like awful at live commentaries because we can't multitask. Yeah I will agree with that. Please don't hit me. I have the AWP now. Why did I just click? I'm an idiot. I need to buy some grenades. Oh my god.
Lockdown got his revenge. That means I can follow you. Well there you are. Oh you dead? Yeah I'm spectating you now. Where am I getting shot from? Top and bottom looks like. Oh really?
Come on Slayda. Did he shoot through surface? Is that what that. I got killed by Dwayne the Rock Johnson. Well there goes my AWP. Dwayne. Oh yeah I got killed by Dwayne the Rock Johnson. Yeah I think that means they shot through a surface. I'm pretty sure that's what that means.
I'm two and three. Dang I'm just. See I'm used to bots not knowing how to like move and standing still and spawn and running the same way every single time. Why are these guys doing that? I don't know I mean these are. There's only one bot in this whole game and he's on our team. Anyone see him? Oh my god. I got killed by Dwayne again. Where is this guy that you just got killed by? Oh people are really going to love the live commentary on my part. Spectating the whole time.
It's just me I'm the only person alive. Oh great. This is fantastic. Get out of here. Oh where was that guy? He's killing a lot of us. He must have seen me kill his brethren. He must have seen you kill gangster bobber. Only explanation. I didn't even use my grenades. I was so taken back by my team getting destroyed.
Alright this is going to be the one. Me and you are both going to kill the whole team. You ready? Were you sure? I'm going to get that MVP again like I did that one time. You weren't recording? I actually was recording. But you said you weren't. Yeah I just wanted to make sure that I didn't have any pressure on you. Alright I'm right behind you. I'm throwing this in there. Eat fire. Oh I'm dead. Do I have a bot? Oh eat fire. Where's the guy? He's right down there. I'm sure if you keep shooting he'll eventually run into your bullets.
I don't want to get lucky headshotted though. I always just turn the corner and go and just get nailed. Oh that's what I've done for five rounds in a row. I'm not even guarding the bomb. I'm trying to get that last kill. There he is. Come on.
That sucks. Is he just going to sit back there the whole time? I don't know probably. Look at our guy with the AK just trying to like strafe shoot. Hopefully this pirate will get him though. There you go.
I don't have money because I keep sucking. I'm going to go deagle. I think I'm going to go deagle this round. Hey give me money. I don't even have enough for like things. Open a trade and I'll give you like a thousand dollars. Is that even possible in this game? I don't think so. Because I'm not sure if you're joking or... Open up a trade. Let me give you like a couple of guns. Hey let's go right again because I have a sniper now. I'm way behind.
I'm behind you. Oh looks like you went right. Yeah. Oh my god. This game scares the hell out of me man. It really does. Can you crouch jump on this? Oh don't worry I took control of a bot. I'm good. I have a sniper rifle. Why does this bot have the default pistol? Oh I'm going to shot you in the head Jerma. I got shot in the head regardless from gangster boobies. Whatever that guy's name is.
I'm pretty sure I shot him in the head. Nothing happened. There you are. Oh no I shot his up. Gangster bobby. Hey look I killed him. You did? No not even. Oh I'm on ego. Ego reptile. Let's go M4. Time to buy the aug and no body armor.
Run with the pistol man. Try and get one kill with the pistol so you don't have to waste money. I've tried that several times. I'm just awful at this game. Right now. Right now anyways. Don't be so down on yourself. You know what you're right. I'm going to throw this bomb over here. Now they can't come over here. That pretty much did absolutely nothing. I don't know why it did that. I'll shoot you through the barrels you bastard. Oh what? What happened?
Who killed that guy? I didn't kill him. You're the only one alive. There's two others alive. I'm the only one alive. Damn. This guy's trying to get like a wall bang. He's not even shooting at me. Alright let's go EG reptile. I'm pressing E. If we both press E at the same time we might be able to override his plan. Let's see if he can do it. Yeah throw that grenade. He's all smoked out right now. He's in trouble. Oh. Oh.
Oh my god. Oh my god. This guy's going to do it. He like had that. He really did. I have to say something. I have to say. Damn. Alright give me that Kevlar and helmet and no money for anything else. You just rolling around with Kevlar and helmet in the default? Mm hmm. Well at least you'll live. I'm starting out with zero dollars each round. You might live longer. This guy said I don't miss. Okay bullseye.
I missed. Okay call us feral from phone booth. No I just got flashed. Geez I'm like pan. I'm like afraid. This game scares me. Like playing against bots I'm all calm but I can't even aim when I see like a person. Grenade out. It's just me again versus five people. Do I have a grenade? I do. Eat it. That rolled like a foot in front of me. It didn't really. I pretty much grenade like blew myself up. Damn these
other team is whooping our ass.