Hey, what's going on guys? Jerma here with a market garden rocket jumper gameplay. Now this is going to have some fantastic jumps and fantastic kills.
No, no guys, no.
Ooh, you ready to see me do some sick market garden skills?
Dude, I'm ready to see you go across the map in the sky and duck down with a shovel.
This is it. That didn't work.
I landed on his head. What? You get penned.
How the fuck do you do this?
Some timing. Are you kidding me?
Oh my God. I would have had that guy. That guy in the sky. You nearly met him.
Oh, are you going?
Nobody can hit me. Oh shit.
I actually did get someone.
All right. So one time I saw Star jump from the very beginning of this point all the way to like the other end of spawn.
So I'm going to try to do it right now. You guys ready? Here we go.
You ready, boo? First attempt. Yeah, I'm ready.
I'm waiting at the other end for you. I got it.
I'm going. I got this. I'm doing all right. I'm doing good. I've got it. I'm almost there.
Let's aim for 13. Oh, does that count? Does that count as a market garden kill?
Does it count if I didn't jump in the air? Check this out motherfucker.
Here we go, baby. Star underscore niche.
It's me. You're sick, dude. Boo, help. I'm stuck.
Well, you can get up there. That's not a spy. I just didn't bump into him.
We're going to go all the way around. We're going to try to get shot in the back.
There's a scout with a pen. No, I'm scared.
No, Jimmy. I'm all by myself.
What am I doing? I was trying to like rocket jump across the ledge and I like missed the lip.
If there's one thing that does be an uber, it's definitely enhanced gravity at a bottomless pit.
They can definitely kill an uber. Come on, push it down that little cliff.
Push it down. Come on, use all your strength and get it down.
Here we go. Here we go. Spy.
It's not working in here.
I can't. Joan, stay right there. Don't move.
Dude, this guy has no idea and I can't even like...
Here we go.
What? Would you? Would you? Huh?
What? What happened to me?
Oh, fall damage. Oh.
Oh, oh, oh.
I didn't even... I forgot to shoot the rocket.
I'll distract him.
What the hell is this guy doing?
Don't kill him. Don't kill him. No.
I wanted to crit him for a tickle.
I wanted to crit him and he would be like a still target.
Like standing still for me.
I just did like a full moonsault.
Have you ever seen... you know like WWF, the moonsault?
Oh, you mean like a full on like Jeff Hardy.
Yeah, I just Jeff Hardy moonsaulted off the top turnbuckle onto somebody.
I want to get this guy to peek his head over and me to get him.
I keep forgetting to shoot the rocket.
This guy doesn't know. This guy doesn't know. Let's see if I can do it.
What the fuck, man?
If I landed, if I registered a hit, I would have killed that engineer.
But I'm just awful.
Oh, I think I got him.
Yeah, you did. There's still a teleporter though.
Okay. No, I died.
There we go. It's done.
I got it.
I thought it was like a lot of action in there.
You're just like in there with like a shovel.
Come on, get back over here.
Oh, Gemma, you're in a tight spot.
I know, I'm out.
Jump away.
It could happen here though.
I'm going to try to go back to the spawn area.
Oh, yes.
Yeah, attaboy.
Oh, let's do it again.
I did it. Three.
Three rocket jumping, rocket garden kills.
Thank you. Thank you so much.
It only took me like an hour and 15 minutes.
It's the magic of editing.
It's only been like five minutes, whatever it's been, you know?
Sup, Spy?
You're not going to get away with this one.
And it didn't register.
I'm being such a piece of dog crap right now.
Like I cannot kill this Spy.
And he's like killing people on our team too.
Heavy?
Dude, I'm bumping into Spies everywhere.
These guys are snipers all over the map.
How am I nervous?
That guy was so confused.